Forever.
Dog.
Warning, this is General Thunderbolt Ross, the Hulk's potential future father-in-law.
Thank you for volunteering for our Talked Secret government project.
This podcast episode will shoot your body full of gamma radiation.
Be prepared to have supercharged opinions on launch coasters, complicated locker systems,
and the music of Fallout Boy.
Chase Mitchell joins us to discuss the incredible Hulk coaster on Podcast the Ride.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, the show where before we hit record, we say every time, I
think this time it's going to work.
I'm Jason Sheridan here with Mike Carlson.
Yes, I'm here and I do think it's going to work this time.
Yeah, yeah.
Now it's become a good luck charm, we have to say.
Scott Gertner also here.
Yeah, and I'm glad you explained what that is because this is a, I say it, we all say
I've never known what it meant because I've gotten braver but I have not been brave enough
to go on today's topic.
One of what I will say is the most intense roller coasters in the country.
Oh, hey, well you're cutting me slack, I appreciate that.
Yeah, it seems like it's probably, well that's a thing to ask about.
How much of a level up is it?
Do you think I can handle it next time around?
Hey, but let's bring our guest in who picked this topic with us, writer for The Tonight
Show with Jimmy Fallon and the upcoming inside job on Netflix, Chase Mitchell is here.
Hey guys, thank you for having me.
Thanks for being here.
Yeah, yeah.
Thanks for joining us.
Yeah, yeah, and for throwing this ride out among a bunch of other rides.
I guess, so you seem like a parks person to some extent.
Well, yeah, big time.
I mean, like, so I grew up in Atlanta, Georgia and so we were a big like drive to Orlando
family.
Oh, sure.
A lot of summer trips.
Oh, gotcha.
Okay, very nice.
How long is that drive?
Gosh, I want to say like at least like six or seven hours.
Okay, so you can do it in a day but it's not the most like risky.
Yeah, yeah, it's not, yeah.
Yeah, it was not fun.
There's a lot of like my dad making the same bad jokes every year because there was some
kind of like when you're driving through like South Georgia, you know, like I love Atlanta
and I feel, you know, I always kind of like vouch for it and and but like it's a very
blue city and a very red state.
And so when you leave, as soon as you like leave the perimeter of the city, it's literally
surrounded by a highway.
And then when you get outside of that, everything is bad.
And so we would we would there was like all kinds of like weird like nut farms and stuff
like that and like weird like side of the road kind of stuff.
And my dad would always make the same shitty jokes about the about the billboards that we
would see.
I see.
Yeah.
Would you stop ever?
Sorry, I was like, is it like world's largest ball of yarn, like stuff like that?
It wasn't even stuff that was that interesting.
Ball of yarn would have actually been great.
Yeah, no, it was it was just a lot of like a gas station.
It's bigger than a normal gas station.
Yeah.
And really proud of that thing.
This is kind of a great part of the the theme park experience that I think we've never brought
up because I definitely had this growing up, too, especially when it's like a regular place
that you go a little more frequently.
I only went to Disneyland like once a year as a kid, but we'd always always pass by camping
world on the way down.
And my dad would always say like, guess what?
We're good.
We're doing change of plans.
We're doing camping world instead.
And why can I just laugh at that?
I had to go, no, I don't want to go to camping.
Like, why did I have to take that?
Well, what age are we talking?
I probably still eight or nine.
I'm worried he's going to do it.
I guess I could say eight or nine.
If you said 11 or 12, I was going to be a little more worried about it.
I think I kept whining to that degree.
I was whining about plenty at 11.
I was also the sort of child who, if my parents said something like as a joke, but said it
a little seriously, you know, like, hey, we're going to this instead, I would lose it.
I would get very upset.
It is not surprising to me that we share that characteristic.
Yeah.
Weird anxiousness.
I guess you got to remember a child doesn't understand irony.
Yeah.
No, this was a statement made in jest.
So if I had said before we started, by the way, we're not doing Hulk, we're doing the
storm spinner ride.
You both may have flipped out on.
I have a lot to say about storm force acceleration.
OK.
So yeah, you might you might be OK with that.
All right.
No, all I would have done that for is if you'd said we're repeating anything from the downtown
Disney or deal.
OK.
We have to do level three stage two again.
No.
A new store opened.
We're back to Wetzel's.
Is there six flags in the six flags out like right outside of the city, six flags over
Georgia.
They were probably the last one to still have a Confederate flag as one of the flags.
Yeah, one of the six.
There is like a very like kind of uncomfortable, like plantation section of the of the park
that hasn't aged well.
I think they may have updated it.
I haven't been back to six.
I believe they have.
But yeah, they didn't do it soon enough.
Yeah, I can tell.
There was it.
There was an entire ride like a dark ride called Monster Plantation.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
So racist monsters.
That was fun.
Yeah, it was basically.
Yeah, it was it was sort of like the haunted mansion.
With uncomfortable history.
And they were it's not just the if because if they were racist against each other, the
types of monster is considered a race and they're racist against each other.
That's not really hurting anybody.
I still know one should be racist, not even against other monsters.
But I just I just wouldn't even understand the affiliations and where the problems were.
I just wouldn't like the message.
Yeah, either way.
It's still you could overlay the hate into your own world.
If Frankenstein's didn't go along with Dracula's.
I guess they probably.
That's what you're saying.
Yeah.
But if not, because they're monsters who are mad at each other in like a fighting way,
if it's just more of a hypothetical, more Dracula's moving into town.
I see.
Yeah.
Well, the ride is different now, right?
I believe they've changed the ride.
I think it may be called like Monster Mansion or something.
They just like lost the word plantation.
Right.
And they like changed maybe hopefully the architecture outside a bit.
Yeah.
They finally admitted who really won the war.
The monster war.
I like a lot of these.
They stopped calling it the war of northern aggression.
Yes.
Yeah.
Monster.
The monster war of northern aggression.
Yeah.
I have it.
OK.
I also do.
I don't want to put I don't want to put you on the spot here.
But when we were talking about potential rides that we could talk about, you did you did work
at you did work at Jimmy Fallon.
You've not been on Race Through New York.
I haven't.
I actually left.
This is I don't I don't think I'll get in trouble for saying anything.
I'm going to be dreaded careful.
Wait.
Before you do, because I thought about this and I wanted to give you an option because
not too long ago, Griffin Newman volunteered to do Race Through New York with us at some
point behind the paywall.
We feel a little bit a little bit safer.
But yeah, so if there's anything you feel is dicey, maybe leave a voicemail.
Or you can be like or you can just you can say like you can say a safe word or something
and then we can just like snip this out and move it over.
Well, I mean, I'm totally fine talking about they actually were working on that ride sort
of right up until the time when I left.
And during during my time at Fallon, we did I believe two years prior to that, we did
a week of shows in Orlando.
So we were there for one of the.
We would do a week of show.
We did a week of shows in Orlando and then we did a couple of weeks of shows
here in L.A. where we would stay at the Hilden that's right there on the in Universal.
And we would basically we'd be working in the studio there and then we would have access
to the park. Basically, we just like basically just like walk out and like people would do
that. I got to go to the bathroom and then we go ride the Jurassic Park ride and come
back. It was pretty sweet.
The in Orlando, it was it was more fun because frankly, it's it's obviously it's a much
bigger, better park because they're not dealing with they're not having to plan a park around
a working studio.
They're like, quote unquote studio in Orlando is like I think the biggest thing they ever
made there was like a Jimmy Buffett music video.
Like they have plaques on the wall of like the stuff that they made there.
Yes, we know.
I'm talking to the press.
But it was pretty cool because like we'd be working in the studio and like you just hear
of the roller coaster whoosh by like every 35 seconds because we were literally right
under the that rock and roll pride.
Rip right in rock. Yeah.
Oh, that's right. Because that just like took over where all the sound stages.
Yeah. Odd like kind of unthemed ride.
The theme is interrupting work on.
Yeah. Like as they stopped doing like Nickelodeon shows there and stuff like that, they just
gradually it's just become like less and less of a studio and like more and more of a theme
park, which is great.
But yes, we did a week of shows there and then I don't know when they made the decision,
but somewhere along the way they were like, we're going to we're going to do a Jimmy Fallon
ride, which is so I remember when they told us at work and like it was so strange because
it's like it just doesn't seem like something that's the basis for right.
Like there wasn't like a Johnny Carson roller coaster.
No wish.
No, if only or and it's a small world.
Yeah. Dancing Edo's.
Carnac's Haunted Mansion.
Oh, his head.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
She is well in retrospect.
Now there should be this.
Yeah. Jokes the whole time.
We've been missing opportunities.
So then were you part of any conversations about what?
No, it was pretty it was pretty high level stuff.
We had our our supervising supervising writers kind of handled.
They basically wrote the ride.
OK, OK.
And they worked on it kind of as a side project for, you know, I believe like a year or so.
And there was all kinds of like there were days where they were shooting.
They were shooting in the studio and stuff like that.
So, yeah, I still haven't seen it.
But I along the way, I did see a lot of the like kind of test art and stuff like that.
And there were there were totally weird things like I think I was telling you about this
in the DM, but like there's a character on our show.
We had a recurring character called Hashtag the Panda.
It was like if you could imagine like the masturbating bear from Conan, but like without a joke to it.
It's basically that.
But he exists.
It was it was kind of started as I mean, it was still funny for us.
I don't know why it was funny for audiences, but like
Hashtag the Panda is one of the writers, John Haskell.
And the bit kind of started because Jimmy thought it would be funny to basically torture him.
Like he puts him in this insanely hot, heavy bear costume and has him dance while the roots play.
And Jimmy can kind of cue up the music over and over again.
And basically what he would do is just keep going until he would wear John out.
Oh, OK. Oh, the point of it for us watching.
It was very funny because we would see our friend basically being tortured on national TV.
But yeah, then he kind of became like he became like a very often recurring character.
And he became he's kind of the big bad.
Did you say you guys wrote it? Yeah. Yeah.
OK, so, yeah, he's kind of the as I understand it, he's kind of the big bad on the ride.
Like he's there's kind of like a King Kong moment at the end or something.
Yeah, it's sort of it kind of replaces or it's the same beat a little bit as Maggie on the Simpsons ride.
Yeah, it's up giant. Yeah. Yeah.
So which like and then is that is that your phrase that that writer?
He's that he that's him. Yeah.
He's been immortalized in giant mode.
It's like are you he is he Andy circusing?
Yeah, I think he got paid like 200 bucks or something.
That's all the park rides pay. Yeah.
That's day right.
Now they have some poor guy in Florida who now has to wear that same suit
and dance around and pretend to be the same character.
Wow. It's like he planted this little torture game.
Yeah, like said, like the in the ultimate move, it's now like a virus that is spread to underpaid Orlando.
I I do think someday I'll make it back down to Orlando and check out the ride.
But it is kind of surreal because it's so they did another week of shows there when they were opening the ride
to kind of like go promote it and celebrate and stuff.
It was a big cross promotional thing.
It's like the same thing as like Universal putting Jimmy in Jurassic World is like the guy who's,
you know, which did feel very Jurassic World for all of its like faults,
like does feel very accurately theme parky and very universal.
That video is very and like the hijinks that happen while he's like spilling liquids in a science boat.
That feels like, well, that is what it's so true to like what that park would really.
Yeah, and extremely similar to like the videos he made for the.
Yeah, because he's the tram guy, which I will having.
When I worked there, it was the Whoopi Goldberg clips.
And I will certainly say the Fallon clips were like, yeah, I know who did the talk to the current guides
who have to watch these videos many, many times every day.
I don't know that you're slanted, but I like a better written than Whoopi.
But what we got eaten by scarabs. That was cool.
Well, I like that. And I like that they still use it because they didn't do a new one with Jimmy.
And they just couldn't.
Well, what are we going to replace the video? That's too much work.
So and I swear I did one tour where I like they didn't replace it.
And you have to say, Whoopi Goldberg, what are you doing here?
And she has not appeared in the tour.
So it's just her looking horrified.
I forgot that they left her in.
I even made that comment just now. Yeah.
So they did leave in the best Whoopi thing where she just gets eaten by bugs
and a horrifying thing like a horrifying scene.
Yeah, yeah. The entire screen is eaten.
And it's just this.
I mean, I like it maybe a little bit as a non sequitur that Whoopi Goldberg,
who you have not seen up until that point,
it's kind of like a good just like out of nowhere cameo.
Yeah, that's true.
I wonder, though, was it like Jimmy didn't want to get eaten by bugs?
I think they just forgot. That's his contract.
Maybe they. Yeah, he just is like, I don't want bugs.
No bugs. It's a very odd grouping of.
So it's Whoopi Goldberg, Jimmy and Chucky, I guess.
The only characters who appear.
Well, you have the as a guide, you have a lot of options of videos
that you can play or not play.
Oh, right. The writer, director of The Mummy, Stephen Summers.
He'll talk to you if you want.
I think they left one Ron Howard, who was the host before.
But just a weird stray.
You can make it a really confusing mess.
Oh, I think still current guides can correct me if I'm wrong,
but I still have the option to have like I'm Frankie Muniz in our new movie.
Big Fat Larn. Yeah.
Like still just promotional.
He says he has changed his name.
He's going by Cosmo now. Just a heads up. Is that real? Yes.
Whoa. That was a tweet he said out the other day.
I want something more mature sounding.
I'm going by Cosmo.
Is it Cosmo Muniz or is it just like a single word?
Single. That's a great question.
I don't know. You will figure we'll check back in on that.
I'll check on that. Yeah.
I that's really OK.
So guides don't use the big failure scene because he's Cosmo.
It's disrespectful to still use Frankie.
Yeah. Chase, can I ask a question?
Was the when you were in Orlando, was it the year that Jimmy went on
the roller coaster with Kevin Hart?
Kevin Hart. Yeah. Yes. OK.
Because I remember that, which is funny because I found a video
of what we're talking about today with two other celebrities going on.
I saw the same thing. OK.
We'll just tease that delicious.
Yeah, this is a real like torture celebrities ride.
Like it's a go to. I'm sorry to correct myself.
It's not Cosmo. Oh, it's Cisco.
Like Cisco systems like not like song song.
Cisco, see, uh, SEO.
I turn 34 next week and I think I finally outgrown the name Frankie.
It's very childish.
So from now on, I hereby declare I want to be called dot dot dot Cisco.
Cisco just screams professional adult who's got a shit together.
Yours truly Cisco Muniz.
S Y. Is that what you said?
Cisco or is SI?
No, see, I like communications.
Oh, right. Yeah.
So it's not like Benjamin Cisco from Star Trek, Deep Space Nine.
And it's not Cisco thong song Cisco. No, it's a different Cisco.
It's a different Cisco. Formal Cisco.
How seriously is he taking this? Do we think? I don't know.
I don't know. We're going to have to.
And when was this announcement made?
How long have we how long has it been a post Cisco world?
Eleven twenty eight November twenty eight.
Huh? Oh, wow.
Gee, we're going to do a whole deep thanksgiving.
I guess something's burned him on Thanksgiving Day.
Start practicing in case we have him on Cisco.
What about you changing your name, Jason?
Oh, I'm Cosmo now.
Now that you know Cosmo's free.
No mistakes, only gifts.
But as far as we know, Cisco hasn't been on this ride.
As far as celebrities have.
And the three of you have been on this ride.
And I was just in Orlando and I did not take the opportunity.
I'm curious what I might have thought.
Did you even for a second think about it after all the progress you've made
in your life? I.
And and what you're referring to is that I went to Orlando
and I was doing a lot more launching because I was dubbed a no launch queen.
And I've tried to overcome that.
And I did a lot of launches specifically in Orlando.
I did not do this.
Now that we're talking about it, I kind of wish I did it.
I feel like it was just a jam packed day a little bit.
That's that's a bad excuse.
But like not only that, but you guys did it.
But you also were like you kind of complained about a little.
You were a little as rough.
Well, yeah, we had to complain about it.
Sorry. Oh, no.
Has it like is it rocky?
Well, it's it's it's interesting because they've they redid the whole track
a couple of years ago. Yes.
And I have written it free and post that.
Yeah. OK, so yeah. OK.
Because I wrote it.
I've written it three times in my life.
You've written it like I've written it.
It does. I think I love this ride.
I love the first version of this ride.
I'm going to come out right away with a hot take.
The new version is worse.
Oh, yeah. It's bad.
It's not as good.
I miss the the the the I miss Bruce Banner.
It's the silliness.
I miss Bruce Banner saying, oh, I think it's going to work this time.
Like I miss him being locked in that cycle of failure.
Like you just fucking up every time.
Yeah. And you know, on the fourth, no.
Yeah. That's when you launch,
when you go from nine miles an hour to 40 miles an hour in two seconds.
And now it's just like a very sedate kind of it's it's a female voice
who just sounds kind of like a, you know, a launch code
person or something like that.
Just like just saying, like everybody stay calm.
And they kind of they change the story.
I have like I have complicated feelings about
roller coasters that are trying to also be a themed ride,
because I feel like it complicates things like and I think it's really hard to do.
Like I rode the Incredicoaster at Disneyland earlier this year.
And I think that's maybe a more successful version of it.
But I also think like it's very hard to like cram a story into a roller coaster.
Yeah. And I think that this one, they made the story like more complicated.
Like, yeah, it's the only re theming I can really think of
that gave it less of a story. Yeah.
Like they took out a lot of the Bruce Banner, the whole.
Yeah. The titular guy. Yeah.
And they added a lot more Thaddeus Ross, everyone's favorite general
Colonel Thunderbolt Ross is now of the Hulk.
Yeah. Not an enemy. Sometimes friends, sometimes enemies.
His girlfriend, wife's father, Betty Ross's father.
Yeah. So it's like he's just always he always is so mad at Bruce.
Yeah, it's like a real like 60s sitcom relationship.
Yeah, he's very mad.
Guys, my daughter and I hate him.
He said, bum is a little good bum.
Ten or 15 years.
He is also a hulk sometimes, but he's red.
He's the red hulk.
It's too much to get into right now.
I don't really know it either.
I feel like everyone in the orbit of Bruce Banner's life
just eventually becomes a hulk at some point.
Yes, it's true. There are a lot of hulks.
I read a bunch of hulk comics from the recent run, and it's kind of like a horror
thing where it's like in order for the Hulk come out,
Bruce has to die every time.
So he has to die.
And then the Hulk can only come out at night.
So he's just like stalking.
But then like they are touching on like everyone around the Hulk
gets infected by Gamma in some way.
And they're all in a hell of their own making.
How many people? That could be dozens of people.
Right. Yeah, it's a lot of hulks.
Well, Hulkling Hulkling is a hulk. That's his son.
That's his son.
Who's the newer hulk?
The main Amadeus chose on his way.
The show is a hulk.
Yeah. Bruce.
Jennifer Walters, she holds a horse.
Yeah, you see none of those characters you see, and you don't even see
Thunderbolt Ross. I don't know when he became Red Hulk,
but you don't even see Red Hulk in the ride.
Who is fun? He's Hulk, but he's red.
But it's in my.
Oh, sorry. I was just like that might be like a if you're going to put that character in
then, oh, is that a little tease of maybe they added they added stuff to they had Red Hulk?
No, did not do that.
He's hiding in a tunnel or something.
It's always like kind of historically you think of I mean, most people,
if they are aware of General Thunderbolt Ross,
I think he is an antagonist.
He hates the Hulk.
But the right now is that they want to they want to turn everyone on the ride into hulks.
Yes, they're going to do hulkification to you.
And they show you footage of past test subjects, but no Bruce Banner.
Yeah. So the Hulk, you know.
So this ride should now be called other hulks
because they have shown you other hulks and you are about to become a hulk.
Or like Hulk yourself, Hulk yourself.
Go Hulk yourself is the name of the ride.
The ride. Well, I did.
I did copy paste a quote, I think, from Terry Koo.
I could be saying both of those words wrong.
It was like a big universal major universal person at this point.
I think it's from him.
Is it theory? Coop?
Very well, I think.
Yeah. It's a mix of either one.
I don't know.
But this phrase was this press release.
He phrase was so odd.
I had to say it exactly.
We wanted to give our guests a first person experience
on what it's like actually hulking out.
So the whole that's the point of it is you're hulking out.
You kind of already did that.
Like you were helping Bruce because the original story was that Bruce
was going to try the Hulk experiment again, this time thinking it would unhulk himself.
That's what he thought.
Yes. Yes.
And he's 100 percent.
He thought he would synthesize the Hulk out of himself.
And what it really just did was wake up the Hulk and more.
Or just the same. Not even more.
He's not twice the Hulk.
Yeah, just the Hulk.
He's not the Hulk, but he's angry, which in.
But he's always rules.
But he's when the angrier he gets, the stronger he gets.
Yes. And that's why they can never kill him because it just makes him stronger.
How do you this is a little fun.
I get to ask all these questions having not been.
I haven't even watched the pre show, which I should have before doing this.
But I just get to now do Q&A.
The does he is that conveyed in videos
that he thinks that like and so the by the end of this, I will be unhulkified.
Do you watch him filling out paperwork like we check the unhulk box
in the older version?
Yeah, they pretty much tell you like you see clips of the Hulk destroying.
Steve said he's like, this is why I need to stop this and my experiment.
I'm going to try this to try and undo it.
But I'm going to try this big cannon.
This is going to get in a cannon cannon.
But and then something goes wrong.
So that's a classic theme park trope.
You're doing something with good intentions and it goes wrong,
especially in Universal.
I feel like all the ride love it.
The premise of all the rides is like it was supposed to be something else.
And then you get knocked off course or something like that.
That is a world fair.
It was an open house.
It was the set of the mummy.
And then real mummy things happen.
It's the set of Ghostbusters and real Ghostbusters things happen.
Feels like a needless layer to add on top of things a little bit.
I mean, for the Jurassic Park, right, it really works
because that's kind of that's fun.
That's like because that's the movie.
Yeah.
The now if you lay race through New York on top of this, it is not that
you are challenged to a race in the Tonight Rider and then you go on a race
in the tonight.
You're it's surprising what happens to you, but it's not the tonight
rider malfunctioned.
Yeah. And I think that the right.
So basically I left like before when they sent an email like
pick your seats on the plane because we're going back to Orlando.
I was like, I put in my two weeks that day.
To avoid it.
That's it. No, no, Orlando.
This is the last straw.
But so, yes, I didn't get to experience it.
But my understanding of it, it's really like surreal seeing it
because they created basically I know it's on like New York Street
and they basically created a small 30 rock sort of. Yes.
So everything's kind of styled like 30 rock inside it.
Is that right?
And yeah, which I imagine would be eerie for somebody who's.
Yeah. There.
Yeah, I think I just didn't want the PTSD.
Sure. Yes. But it's rare that anyone's
place of work is recreated in a theme park unless you've worked in architectural
architectural ruins or a crazy man's collection
in a giant tower.
If you alphabetized a crazy man's collection of physical beings and dogs,
yeah, very, very few depicted.
But I guess it's like,
I guess like it's sort of based on the idea of like they will race
around the studio a lot and like go karts.
And I guess that's kind of where they that was the jumping off point for this.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah. And things don't they they I'll give I'll give that credit
that it breaks from that. OK. Tradition.
It's not that a taping goes awry.
Although I kind of like this time now I'm spinning out like the Jimmy's kidnapped
or like just the, you know, Tariq is kidnapped.
The Symbionese Liberation Army is back.
It's them. They've got a real target. Yeah.
Oh, no. I mean, they can update.
This is a 3D movie ride. They can do a new movie.
I would kind of like to demand a different talent story.
Keep the Tonight Rider in it, like some of the elements. Yeah.
But yeah, well, if you have that at your disposal, you're going to.
Yeah, you're going to use it right to prevent future kidnappings.
It does feel like those rides would be easier to update than they.
I mean, maybe not like like Transformers has because it's like a hybrid
where you're also kind of on a track and stuff like that.
Yeah. Harry Potter one.
But the ones that are like Simpsons, like it feels like they could do
like a treehouse of horror Simpsons.
Oh, yeah. They just brought it out every year.
Yeah, absolutely.
Good. And they never do.
Yeah, very good idea.
Yeah. A scary Simpsons.
Yeah. Geez.
That's it. You know, they'll play the treehouse of horror music
and in Springfield and stuff like that.
And that's fun. But then you then you just ride the same ride.
I'm like a natural.
That's a really natural, not tortured holiday overlay. Right.
And the and a good excuse to like liven everything up and do a
you know, like brighten the ride.
Yeah, they tried. Right.
Didn't they try to brighten that screen?
I don't remember. They did.
That's OK. Never works.
Yeah. Yeah. It's a good idea.
They're going to do it.
Um, anyways. So.
So the current storyline of the Hulk.
Yes. Is that you are volunteering for a military experiment
where you will become a Hulk.
They're trying. Now they're trying to replicate the Hulk.
So that makes sense.
They know how to make one Hulk.
So in theory, they can make more Hulk.
But why do they want to?
Seems like it's scary to do. Yeah.
He hates those hulks.
Why? Yeah. He's a body horror story, honestly.
The other thing is like the the so the first one.
Yeah. Science experiment gone wrong.
Thing goes wrong as a theme park go to.
This is an experiment that goes exactly how it's supposed to go.
They start like as you are the launch, it starts saying initiating gamma exposure,
Hulk transformation, accelerating.
And then they say, do not be afraid.
Then they launch you like that.
Pre line. That is the pre line before the launch. Yeah.
And there's a totally different vibe than.
No, no, no.
It's kind of like you accept your fate.
Well, it's like I think that's also like the thinking now.
And you can see it with whatever they're going to do with Avengers
like campus and Disneyland, where it's like you become the Avengers,
suit up, sign forms and become a member of Blank.
And it's like it's all about your experience now.
And it's like, I don't know that people care about that.
Like, I don't think people just want to see the Hulk
or they want to see Iron Man. Yeah.
It's not like I need to like go train.
Walt Disney ran into this like with the first batch of Fantasyland rides
because you were supposed to see it from like Snow White perspective.
You know why he wasn't on the ride and everyone.
It's like, where are the characters we like? Yes. Yeah.
And I I cannot to just beat a dead horse, but I kind of like
I kind of like the ride where C3PO is in charge.
And that's why the flight goes awry in all these memorable ways
as opposed to where I'm in charge and I'm just stressed out.
Sure. I think that will drop it there.
But yeah, I think what you're saying,
not the requisite 20 minutes of it.
There's nothing I have to say about it.
Yeah, no, I mean, I think that, yeah, I think that it's like fun
being around characters you like.
And it's like, I don't know who's more fun, Iron Man or me,
Mike Carlson in an iron suit.
I wonder if they're kind of taking a page from Universal on that,
because I feel like Universal is very big on when the ride is over.
They're like, congratulations, you saved the world.
Like the Transformers ride, they say that like, hey, great job.
You saved. I like that, obviously.
But that's one of my favorite things.
That might also because they clap a lot, like at the end of the ride
that I think is a tie in to like when you wrap a day on set.
And it's like, all right, the wraps and everyone claps sort of thing.
Yeah, maybe I like that.
You're making me realize I kind of like when there's applause for me.
Like Harry Potter, like Harry Potter.
Yes. And I think kind of today to the Guardians clap.
Yeah. Well, they don't clap, but they wave.
It's kind of a name came out.
Yeah, that that works.
They're like end of SNL
moments where they wave and thank the host and Harry Potter.
Video of all of the characters for the movie clapping for you, right?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Wow.
Is just something else have clapping or am I just thinking about a question?
Because I do like it.
I mean, they always on the mummy when you get off the mummy, they always clap.
Well, the cast members clap.
But the key other characters, universal.
Spider-Man takes your picture at the end.
Mm hmm.
No, clack like Stanley doesn't clap when he's driving a truck.
Somebody help us out here.
Please respond on Twitter.
Another ride that ends with applause.
I feel it doesn't do any of the Star Tours endings in with applause.
I don't if you land on Batu, dude, I don't think there's no one.
No, I just I just landed on Batu and Star Tours like a week ago.
And there were no claps.
No, no, no. They're going about their business.
I think, yeah.
When you're on the gun, when you're in Gungan City,
you end up just up on the ramp on the marina.
It's very interesting as I go through the scenarios.
There's the Namu one where you always get beheaded.
That's the same.
Well, should all be clapping.
I think maybe that's my very you like being thanked.
I think I like being clapped at.
Yes, because it makes me feel like I finished a show.
Yeah, that's true.
A round of applause makes everybody happy.
Yeah, tonight's show, I wonder, does that?
I don't remember what I'm now calling tonight's show, the ride.
It feels like that one probably ends with you back in the studio, right?
I assume it does.
Spoiler alert, but you're the audience.
Right. So why would they clap?
We're clapping.
Just help us out on Twitter.
Tell us if it tells another ride that ends with clapping.
I know there's an obvious one and I'm not coming up with it.
OK, so the reason I think because I was thinking about this,
like I do like aesthetically, the ride looks like a little more modern now.
It doesn't look like the gaudy great.
Don't get me wrong. I'm not saying gaudy in a bad way.
Marvel Superhero Island.
They stripped all your purple.
Yeah, I know. That's a bummer.
Marvel Superhero Island itself looks like it's stuck in the 90s,
but Hulk looks a little bit more modern.
And it's like, as you're saying, like there's not like characters on the ride.
So it feels like any kernel of character
like that has been stripped away.
So we're just like begging to just please give us a little of the Hulk.
And that's gone.
Yeah, it's just like that.
We were like, we're still we're starving.
We're thirsty for Hulk.
And now he's missing from the ride that barely he's not in it at all.
Well, even just character in the other sense of like
it used to there used to be a lot of purple and green everywhere,
like the color of Hulk and his cartoonish purple pants.
Yes. That's fun. That's kind of fun.
Now it's all like drab.
It's all like dark blues and silver and stuff.
It is sort of a color scheme.
I think you would you're going to get if there another Hulk ride gets built.
Like that's probably the mode.
We're not in a cartoon mode.
We're in a like making superheroes grounded and real.
Yeah. And that's why they took out the flat with the big Adam
Qbert drawing of Banner becoming the Hulk and put in the big Hulk statue
where he's ripping the track apart, which is cool.
Like that looks cool.
That's your old track that they replaced.
They used it for like the Hulk ripping it apart.
It's like, yeah, yeah.
If you went to Peter Pan, though, and it was just a Peter Pan statue outside.
And that was it. Yeah.
Like you didn't get to see him.
I do kind of like the I missed it.
I missed the purple.
That is like just such a fun, like comic booky color combo.
Yeah. You just don't see any.
That's so him.
I do kind of like they added a lot of like
LED kind of like sizzling, like effects and stuff like that.
When you're in the tunnel.
Yeah. You used to just be lights, right?
Yeah. You just be blinking colored lights and now it's kind of.
Yeah, it is more LED.
That looks nice. That stuff is clearly unimproved.
But at what cost?
Yeah. What cause?
I will say this, I think.
I read a site that didn't seem to have like the total,
the most confident info in this, but I think that could be the longest
array of LED screens anywhere.
Interesting. Doesn't mean it's the biggest LED, but the law.
It means it's longer than whatever's in like the Space Mountain lift.
Oh, so if length does anything for you, then that's good.
Can we talk about, though, the
maybe the most prominent plus up, which is the score?
Oh, well, of course, yes, I was waiting for us to get to this.
Of course, there used to not be any score.
You that Riley just kind of roars like the Hulk screaming.
But there is a new score.
Would you fill us in?
Why the score added in 2016 is by Patrick Stump of Fall Out Boy.
Deep singer, Fall Out Boy.
We are now rocking with Fall Out Boy.
And what I put together is that, OK, so this is summer 2016.
This overlay happens.
And this is the exact same summer that Fall Out Boy is rocking the planet
with the new way, a thousand times better
theme from Ghostbusters. Answer the call, Ghostbusters.
I'm not afraid.
Uh, to use the example of the to use the
ride that we're talking about.
Ray Parker Jr.'s Ghostbusters is a real like wimpy Bruce Banner of the song.
And they turned it into the Hulk that it was always meant to be.
So this is an all star summer for Fall Out Boy.
The 2016 the year the year of the boy.
Is that when the Uva Thurman song came out?
The monsters. Is that them?
The Fall Out Boy? Is that around that too?
Uh huh. Can I just I else?
I have to admit, I had it queued up on on on Spotify.
Oh, sure. There's just a little taste.
Yeah, baby.
Wait, let me see.
What is this? Oh, yeah.
What? Oh, um.
I think I that style of singing.
And when he gets around,
I'm invisible man.
What an insane phrase to scream in that way.
And then Missy comes in.
Mm hmm. Who is afraid of ghosts?
I'm not afraid of ghosts.
What would you do for the new one?
Who would you have redo it in a new the right man?
The new right man, Jason Reitman.
Oh, geez. Stumps back, baby.
Yeah. Yeah.
Boys back.
Follow up, follow boy again.
And we're just increasing the time, the time by 10.
It's like 10 times faster and louder.
Way, way, way, way.
No, no, no. Because Ghostbusters, it's a it's a team.
It's got to be a team up like fall out boy and Missy.
And I think, you know what?
Yes, yes. Well, I'll include what you said, but also add.
Yeah, no, this is it.
All star lineup.
A fallout boy meets chicken foot meets Jared Leto.
Oh, you're a little boring.
Or 30 seconds to Mars.
Let's get them all in there.
Yeah, let's let's get all my other favorite.
It's Mike.
Oh, yeah. Chris has got to come.
Yeah. Yeah.
And you know what? Bring some of your weird cult friends to bring the.
Yes. The backup backup chorus.
Vocals from the entire Jared Leto cult.
OK. And then for the.
There's 5000 singers on the new version.
For the listeners who might not know chicken foot is Sammy Hagar's band
that he has with Anthony from Van Halen,
the drummer from the Red Hot Chili Peppers and.
Hey, when who's that? I know I.
You never heard of that outrageous.
Who's the other? Is it Steve Vai?
Is he in the group? Oh, really?
And he might be in the group as well.
All of it. And they all get a guitar solo.
Yeah. Yeah. Like a minute and a half.
That new Ghostbusters.
I'm still not afraid.
I want to be 35 minutes long.
I mean, I welcome that.
That is right up my alley.
I'll say this for the whole school. I don't mind it.
I don't know. It's a pretty standard roller coaster score.
And the queue theme is is fine, too.
Yeah, I don't I don't hate that part of it, but I'll say this.
I just it just I just forgot about Ghostbusters.
I'm not afraid.
I just needed to I needed to express it.
They they made a big thing of like we replaced the whole track
and brand new cars, and it is I find it no smoother.
If I kind of want to rougher.
Yeah, I think it got harder.
Yeah, that's what I was going to say is like the first time I rode it was before.
And it was like a couple of years, a year or two before they took it down.
And it was it's it's very intense.
But I wasn't like my neck or head didn't hurt that.
I thought one of the at the time, I thought one of the smoother
like metal coasters. Yeah.
And then you had you hold up on this, right?
It's it's very weird for a track post renovation to get
to get rougher because I there was a there was a roller coaster
at Six Flags called the Ninja.
It was I remember it was a big deal when it first opened.
It was back in the 90s.
And it was the first
might have been one of the first metal coasters at Six Flags over Georgia.
And it was it had six loops and that was like a huge deal.
It was the most the most loops that they had in the south, I think.
And it was like a super smooth coaster when it first opened.
And then like it's almost unrideable now.
Like when you ride it, it just ping pong is your head back and forth
on the headrest.
And yeah, I mean, I think I I agree.
I think I think it's it is a little you don't
want to have to like force your head to the back of the headrest
to keep it from banging around.
Yeah, yeah.
Be doing any work with your own body.
Well, on a red when I wrote it two years ago,
I don't remember what I was doing with my head, but I remember getting off
and be like and Lindsay and I both were like, oh, why does our head hurt?
So this time we went on it and I was trying to like, OK,
I'm going to like kind of relax.
Yeah. So I relaxed.
And as yours is, just as you described, my head ping ponged.
Oh, no, once or twice.
And I went, oh, shit, I can't do that.
Which I can't relax on the ride.
The original version of this was actually pretty good.
I didn't find that happening a lot.
Yeah, like the redo.
And I admit, I'm sure part of it is also my brain is slowly decaying
as I get older and my body.
I can't do this three times in a row anymore.
But when you and I wrote it, I thought it was it was all right.
But I went back later that day and I felt like I had been in a fight.
You did it again. I did it again that day.
We did it.
We did it. And even though even though I had ping ponged
and there was a spot where I almost grayed out a little bit,
where I was like, oh, like, yeah, I was not in like
I did not have a headache after it.
It was better than the time before.
We wrote in the front.
We wrote front row. Yeah.
Are you guys are you guys typically front guys or back guys?
I am scared of I'm trying.
The past few years, I'm trying to get better at roller coasters.
So I generally don't want the front.
This just sort of happenstance. We ended up in the front. OK.
Yeah. For this one, it's kind of fun to be typically like
I don't even know. I don't even know if this is fucking true.
But the idea that like when you're in the back,
you're going faster because you're being pulled.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
So that's like the back is faster.
The front is scary because you get to.
But the front is you kind of sacrifice that thing of like, oh, well,
you'll also be like further down the hill
down the first hill before you pick up speed, which doesn't really apply
on this one because it launches you.
And I still remember very vividly, I think maybe my best experience
on this roller coaster was maybe the first time that ever did it,
because I did not know that it was a launch coaster.
I didn't know that was going to happen.
And the first time that happens, it's so like unexpected.
Yes. I guess it's you're in the the time in the cannon.
Yeah. So it's possible to be looking at it, not know
that it's not just a slow climb through.
Yeah. And it was the first launch coaster that I ever been on.
So I I just didn't know that they could do that.
Like, yeah, yeah.
I'm used to the click clack all the way to the top.
Like, that's kind of the that was the traditional experience.
And that was what I'd always sure was what I was accustomed to.
And it launches you up at an angle into a zero G roll.
And then you drop one hundred and fifty feet down.
Yeah. Like it's great.
Like down heading like you're going to hit the water. Yeah.
There's a lot.
There's a lot of a fat cobra rolls and and
I think it's called bunny hops.
It's so like so many.
It's such a crazy thing.
But I still I prefer this launch
because the thing that gets me is the anticipation.
Yeah. Usually it was as being a scared kid.
And like I never went on most of the six flags, the Great America Coasters,
even though like when Batman came out, it was the same thing
where I was like, oh, cool, a Batman ride.
And my mom was like, I don't think Batman's actually like on the
just a roller coaster.
I was like, oh, like it was frustrating as a kid
as I heard Batman ride.
Yeah. Your mind runs wild with what that should be.
Yeah. Six Flags over Georgia.
Oh, all the six flags, actually.
I went to the one in Massachusetts earlier this year, and it's a lot.
There's so many rides that are like it's the Riddler ride or the Joker ride.
And yes. Oh, I mean, not really.
Yeah, it's green or it's black or.
Yeah, six flags, coasters to age, like a fine wine
that you have just opened and the clock is ticking.
Yeah, you have to drink it.
If you drink it a few days later, it will be cooking wine.
Three days, three days. Yeah, I'm getting I was just excited.
We didn't really talk about it, but Jason and I just did the most
anxiety inducing law.
There's a thing called hang time at Knott's Berry Farm
that takes you up like that rip ride rocket 90 degrees.
And then it just dangles you off the top for like
what feels like five minutes, probably 25 seconds.
Yeah. But you're just hanging there on the top.
And I've never if I was a kid, maybe I would have like started crying.
But I've never been that anxious in my adult years going on a ride as I was
like clinging to the front as we're ascending 90 degrees.
And I'm just laughing like I'm just laughing because Mike's
just sitting there going, oh, my goodness. Oh, my goodness.
Well, then we got we get that.
You said goodness.
He was saying good. No memory of it.
No memory.
Yeah. You're the sweet.
You're the most good boy in your profanity.
If my mom is listening to this right now, she went, that's nice.
She's very happy about it.
You yell, I think when we got stopped, we did the stall at the top.
You just yelled, oh, my God, it's taking so long.
You just started yelling.
I didn't know. I didn't realize like it just yeah, it does feel like an eternity
up there anyway. So like the it's a dream at the launch.
I'm sorry. They get it over with.
Well, we later that night, right before we walked to our cars, we rode
I think it's called Ghost Rider. Yeah, yeah.
And it's not it just looks like a smaller wooden roller coaster.
It's practically in the parking lot.
And I never gave it much mind.
And we got on it.
And it is one of the most intense things I've ever ride.
It is I would put it up.
I wouldn't do it again. I did it one time.
I'll do it again.
But like it does like scare the shit out of me.
I had to just hold on to my glasses at a certain point because I was worried
there was just a wooden roller coaster, but they redid it.
And it's just so intense.
It doesn't appear with a hole.
It's like a logical story.
But it's so loud.
Wooden coasters are scary in two ways because like
the ride is scary.
And then you're also just never sure if it's going to be the last one
that they ever do. Like, yeah.
The whole piece just snaps off.
Do you have an ideal type of coaster or coaster?
Or is it a coaster guide?
Yes, I am a big coaster fan.
Although this is like an unexpected thing, I am finding that
my past two theme park experiences were usually, you know, I go to Universal a lot,
went to Disneyland for the first time this year.
I grew up going to Disney World,
but, you know, went to Six Flags a lot, liked coasters,
loved them as a kid and would just do them over and over again all day.
But like this last experience going to Six Flags in Massachusetts,
I we did this get the line pass and I bit off
like more than I could chew.
It was like my like 35 year old stomach, like couldn't handle it
because it was fun in the moment.
And then like I had I had horrible anxiety for like the rest of the night.
We were back home and like we went to dinner and stuff like that.
And like I just like my heart rate was jacked.
And like, it's like I can't do that many roller coasters in a day anymore.
It was also like I think it was because it was skipped the line.
So we did everything and then did a couple of things twice and stuff like that.
Yeah. But yeah, it was it was intense.
Six Flags kind of fucked me up.
I believe it was it more your stomach now more than your head?
Because I just find like a little my head is a little bit my head too.
Yeah, yeah. It was like it's just kind of a dizziness that like didn't go away.
Yeah. When we weren't riding the rides anymore.
Yeah, it was.
I think I think I'm going to be more of like
I'll go stick with like a more of theme rides and dark rides and stuff like that.
Yeah. Nothing wrong with that.
Nothing to be ashamed of.
Is it sort of like were you ever was there a peak age really for any of you?
Was there like, well, and that was a time where nothing bad ever happened to me.
And I think bad.
Or you mean just like the physical toll where you it's like I could do
I could ride roller coasters the entire day, do everything five times.
The problem with that, I think, is that I'm at my bravest
when it comes to rides right now. Yeah, yeah, me too.
Yeah. So I didn't.
It's a look as a journey, you know, with podcasts.
We all on a journey, really.
That's where we started it.
So, yeah, I don't physically I'm trying to remember like
because like I've last or I guess this year I went on the Guardian six times in a row.
And by the sixth time, I was a little bit woozy, but I still held up OK.
Do you got do you prefer Guardians to a Tower of Terror?
Did you guys go to Tower of Terror?
We've taught we talked a little bit about it's tough because the theming of
long story short, the the Florida one is better.
Than all of them in a lot of ways, because it is a really cool
fourth dimension room, which moves forward.
And that's like very unexpected for that elevator to go that way.
Yeah, I remember that because I was part of Tower of Terror as well.
Yeah. Yeah. And that's not in the California one.
Not in California or I never had that.
I always get I get annoyed when a ride is not the same in two places.
Like one of the other
areas that I pitched to Scott was talking about the mummy ride,
because the one here sucks my balls and the one in Florida.
Sure. Great. There's there's a whole leg of the ride.
There's a false ending of the mummy returns ride in Florida
that this one does not have. Yes. Yeah. Ceiling catches on fire.
You see like what looks like a ride operator.
It's a fake ride operator and they shrivel up and die and stuff.
And it's like it's so cool.
And that's just not.
And also Brendan Fraser thinks you at the end of the ride.
And that's not part of this one as well.
And he gets does he get eaten by scarabs?
It's implied he gets like a ghost creature.
I don't think it's OK. It's right.
Isn't it like a ghostly spirit?
I was excited. Finally got his coffee.
I like rides where people get eaten by scarabs with.
Yeah, it's pretty limited. Yeah.
That's what I like. I know what I like.
That's another with that applause thing I'm saying that that's another
like here's there's this little like, you know, talk amongst yourselves
or write in our comments or anything.
But like worst ride
ratio or what it like biggest difference,
worst difference between rides in different places.
And it could be mummy.
I might have. Yeah, that's still.
And I've like and I've gone to the park with people who haven't been on the Orlando
and we'll ride that ride.
That was really fun.
I'm like, you have no idea what you're missing.
Phil, her magic has it like really has its fan.
The Florida one really has its fans.
And found after we we talked.
Yeah. And the theater is obviously built for in Florida.
The Tower of Terror, though, real quick to answer the question.
The Tokyo one is the best themed one, I think,
even though it's missing a fourth dimension.
But Tokyo one is a completely original story.
And I think I like that aesthetically the best.
The one in Florida.
I like the Tower of Terror aesthetic better than Guardians.
But I will say this, though, I'm used to having fun on the actual drop,
which is what happens on Guardians.
So you get a little fun. You get the music.
And anytime I've been on the older, the older ones,
I find the drops lacking. Yeah.
So it's hard.
The more active
and the launch, the initial launch of Guardians.
Yes, you like I like that.
I did too. I like to do anything.
You think the Guardians drop is longer?
It is. I think it's the longest one of all of them.
I could be wrong.
I when I wrote it, I was like,
didn't feel like it's as long as when it was Tower of Terror.
But I could be totally wrong.
It's been years since I think it's long.
I think it's the longest one.
Somebody probably correct me.
Florida, Tara is partially the view is partially obscured by the letters.
Right. Yeah.
I'm imagining that.
Hmm. Yeah.
How would I think we actually let the letters of the hotel?
Maybe. Yeah.
I think they made that longer after a while.
Maybe those are similar.
The one in Tokyo is short.
It's like closer to the original.
But they then do a thing for a couple of months where they make it longer.
And then the one in Paris I saw,
I don't I don't know when it starts or if it has started already.
Oh, that was crazy.
They're doing three different ride profiles for the Tower of Terror.
And I wonder if they're doing it seems like they might be.
I wonder if they're sort of doing a type of Guardians show
only like Twilight Zone related.
So maybe you do go on down and you see stuff open up
while you're going up and down, which is cool.
And like would plus that right up everywhere.
And then you get to keep the cool aesthetic of the towers.
I wonder.
Did you feel it with your first Disneyland visit?
Did you feel a lot of like better in Florida, better in Florida,
like like growing up there?
I I really enjoyed Disneyland.
I don't know how the sizes of the parks compare,
but there was a lot of stuff in like California Adventure that I really liked.
And there was stuff that, you know, wouldn't have been there
when I was a kid that was here at this.
Like I liked the Radiator Springs, which was interesting
because I don't care for the Cars movies, but I think that's a really fun land.
Yeah. That ride is really well executed, I think.
Yeah. And that might be the create.
That might be the biggest sort of gap between people, adults,
maybe liking a movie. Yeah.
And everyone loving the ride is the best cars thing that Pixar has ever made.
It's better. It's better than the films.
It is a rare.
That's an interesting category, too, like where the ride is better than
all of the in the multiple films.
I guess I kind of feel that way about and I'm jumping around so much.
But I do. I kind of feel that way about Transformers as well.
I enjoy that ride more than the movies.
That maybe should have just been a ride.
Like it probably didn't need to be a five movie franchise.
As Marty Scorsese says, Theme Park, he's talking about these movies
that have a lot of effects.
And Transformers is honestly even a better example than the Marvel movies.
Because Transformers is literally just metal smashing against each other.
Like every movie is mostly that maybe not Bumblebee.
I haven't seen it.
But it is like such an aggressive thing.
You may as well just be along for the ride like you are on the ride.
Yeah. Can I bring up a Hulk related thing?
Because we're recording this a little bit early.
We're doing this in December, we can say.
And this is going to be out, I think.
I could be wrong, but I think we're putting this out beyond the time,
which by this point, the Oscar nominations will be out.
And Mark Ruffalo certainly definitely will be nominated
for best supporting actor for for the whole.
Yeah, as we know, because they are Marvel or Disney is nominating
13 Avengers for Academy Awards. Is that true?
They are. Yes.
There's four year consideration campaigns for 13 of the Avengers.
Which one?
There's the whole list is somewhere.
I mean, for sure.
I mean, I got the screener and it's Robert Downey Jr. on the cover.
The cover of the screener looks like a like an indie drama that costs like.
Yeah. You think it's a movie about slavery or something.
Yeah, it's real. They change the font.
Yeah, it is definitely not like Avengers.
It's Avengers. I'm really surprised that this is the one.
I mean, like, you know,
I think all these movies do pretty well with critics and stuff like that.
But like, I'm surprised that Infinity War wasn't the one they push more
because that was more that was more the Empire Strikes Back
and kind of like ends on a real downer.
The boldest story decision made maybe.
And then this is just wrapping it all up.
But it's a way to honor all of their careers for.
So go ahead and read who are now there's at some point a cap.
There's only 10 slots, but certainly 10 of the slots are filled by some of these.
Well, there's a is 1313.
13. Yeah. Robert Downey Jr., Chris Evans, Mark Ruffalo, Chris Hemsworth,
Jeremy Renner, Josh Brolin.
We know Renner is one of them.
All right. And they're
congratulations by now we can say congratulations, Jeremy.
What will you be wearing if he doesn't win?
He's going to kill himself and his wife.
That was something that I didn't.
He didn't just invent it.
Google it.
So please, Academy and don't really doesn't have a name.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, boy.
Did they go straight that haven't don't have a song renters in on New Ghostbusters
song and oh my God, why didn't I include him before?
Uh, did I say I said Cheetal course?
Scarlett Johansson, Gwyneth Paltrow, Paltrow, Pepperpots will be nominated.
You remember that she was in a movie.
I think that's cute.
Honestly, I like her not knowing she was in the movie, but she's barely in the movie.
Yeah.
Um, I and I think there's no question that Karen Gillen will be nominated as Nebula.
Nebula is not. She's in the list.
I forgot that movie was this year.
I forgot I saw that in Larson who disappears from the movie.
She starts in the movie and then they go, oh, she's got to go somewhere else.
And then she's really whole movie pieces out for the entire second act.
And she shows.
Yeah, she shows up at the end.
Everything's OK.
Everything's good now.
She doesn't flinch when Thor's hammer goes by.
Sure. Behind closed doors, Hollywood still incredibly sexist and racist.
But she didn't flinch when Thor's hammer went by.
Problem solved.
We fixed her. Yes. Sexism is gone now.
If they do the hammer there.
I think maybe Mr. Rogers sneaks in there.
Maybe Tom Inks, but the rest, I think we're talking.
I think it's Renner V Downey V.
Can you write in votes when you're like, I think you can write for Oscars nomination?
I think so. Who?
Because I honestly I'm not satisfied with this list.
I think we should give a different Avenger an Academy Award.
Well, they kind of did Tom Holland dirty, right?
He was on that list. Yeah, you're right.
Oh, he just shows up at the end, I guess.
Yeah, but he's still nominated.
So if you should be all Cumberbatch on there.
No, Cumberbatchy again.
We don't spoil his friend game.
He shows up at the end because he was snapped out of there.
Let's see, though, who could rock could should rock it?
When our favorite theme park character rocket, Bradley Cooper,
should he be her favorite James Cagney impersonator? Yeah.
Rocket shows up at the end.
You know, he's going to you might have trouble getting into the event.
Yeah, I wonder why.
I wonder why he wouldn't be able to get in Oscars famously.
Yeah, he's a hand scanning system.
And he's got to go up in the gantry lift at the Kodak Theater.
Busted into the Zebra Academy Awards.
How now if that there's all these articles about who should host
Rock. Oh, my goodness.
He brought it and Deadpool together.
Oh, yeah.
Let's just do it. Let's nominate Deadpool.
And for the first year, and see 17 rating on the Oscars.
Yeah. Oh, man, they would be Razzan Nicholson.
Maybe if he's there, I guess he hasn't been there in like a decade.
If he was there front row, Jack, your hand scan, Jack.
And then like, he just puts him up my hand scan like they're doing a bit.
That's great, honestly.
And then like, but seriously, folks, there's a lot of epidemic problems
in Hollywood and the way women have been treated.
It's not good. And when we're going to turn to Groot for more.
Well, there is a nice detail, but I'm going to let Groot take this one.
Great. Unfortunately, back down because of old tweets.
Excited to announce this year's host, Groot.
All the tweets say I am Groot, but they mean really racist.
They mean, my God, look at this.
I am Groot from 2012.
You son of a bitch.
Wow. So this is going to be an all Avengers Oscar year.
Interesting. So much fun.
I mean, it would be fun.
Yeah, I don't even like I don't even know.
I've never heard the name Nebula.
I don't know these movies at all.
Nebula is Thanos' daughter. Oh, well, that's OK.
Well, no wonder they nominated her. Yeah. Yeah.
That's a tough role to play.
Anyway, let's get back to the ride.
Yeah, you get nominated.
You yeah, you're asking about favorite coasters.
I think the Hulk is up there for me.
I think the original iteration of it
was like really maybe like my top five or top three or something like that.
I really love that.
Do you guys think it was a teen?
Yeah, yeah, we
there were like several years in a row where my family just
we would go to to Universal Studios and I think we tended
to be more of a Universal family than a Disney one.
I think maybe like the rides better.
We went a lot in high school because it was just nice to stay at a hotel,
stay at the Hard Rock and walk over to the parks.
Yeah, we just got into that.
That I have a very specific memory of like going a month
before I started college and like there was like had the express pass.
So walked right on the Hulk a bunch of times.
And I'm like, yeah, this year is going to be awesome.
Don't be afraid. Yeah.
Well, I mean, that's it.
That's my best.
Hopefully it'll work this time.
I wonder if you guys felt this way.
I'd like I bet you guys go in there a little more often
in closer to when ends of adventure open.
I think like this this structure, though I didn't go on this ride.
It rising up on the skyline, I think was very exciting.
It like I think it really announced a new universal and edgier universal
that we're going to do scary or riskier stuff.
And islands of adventure, it says it's going to maybe better rides
and scarier rides than what than what Disney's doing.
And like to have a big super like inversion kind of coaster.
Not not inverted. It's not inverted coaster.
But like there's a ton of loops and everything right at the entrance
of this park. It's just like really bold.
Yeah, I remember when I was adventure was opening.
It was it was really exciting because, yeah, the up until that point,
Universal was mostly like, oh, the Jaws ride and so it was it was rides
that I also really like, but rides that are more about recreating
the experience of being in these movies and stuff like that.
It was earthquake ride and stuff like that.
Twister, which we all love, man.
RIP love that. Yeah, love that twister experience.
Stage five. But yeah.
But when I was a venture was it was it was much more of a push for like,
especially I think superhero island in particular is like
it really has like, you know, a lot of good like thrill rides right there.
The Doctor Doom drop and stuff like that.
And I kind of I also like I, you know, I grew up reading comics and stuff.
So it was really exciting for me to like see all that stuff
and see that it kind of style.
It's very much like styled like the comic books.
It's not like, you know, obviously it predates the MCU and all that stuff.
But like it's very comic booky, like even the the the kind of parts
of the city itself and stuff that you see, everything is.
Yeah. And and the Spider-Man ride being like one of the first rides.
I like that. That kind of ride is copied so much now.
And that I remember that being like the first one. Yeah.
And that was they spent I mean, this island was the immediate hit
because of Hulk and Spider-Man. Yeah.
And they spent so much money developing the technology for Spider-Man.
They spent a lot of money developing like they universal creative.
And I think it's MTS systems.
They developed the launch for this like other rides had been launched before.
But this was like the first time using this kind of launch system,
like literally rigging up a dune buggy on a track
at a bunch of boxcars connected together.
And like there's footage, there's behind the scenes footage of them
like testing out like, does this work?
Like and then on top of that, again, they spent something like
30 million to 50 million on this ride alone
because then they had to build a power generator.
They had to build a specific power drawing device
because if it draw it on the local power supply,
it could brown out the surrounding area every time it launched.
It uses that much.
It's got its own like energy center, its own energy source,
which is so marveling. Yeah.
Big reactors. It looks like create a whole.
It doesn't look as fun as the stuff inside that's fake,
but it's because I saw a picture of it.
Yeah, but it does look pretty neat.
Oh, it's cool. It's cool.
You're saying it's not like cool, like lights and atoms flying around
because unfortunately nothing actually looks like that.
But like a plot could be a supervillain
stealing the Hulk generator and using it to power a nuclear weapon or something.
Yes. Yeah.
From the roller coaster, you're saying? Yes. Yeah. Yes.
So you think Dr. Doom or the Abomination is going to steal
the universal Orlando Hulk power source.
It's some world where the real Dr.
Doom is in the same world as the park,
the fake rides of based on him and his friends.
Right. And they revamp it again in a couple of years and redo the story again.
Yes. Yeah, that's it.
Yeah. Yeah.
It's about saving the power grid of the ride that you're on.
Yeah. And there should be like a like they have to throw up
like a dummy on each ride with Dr.
Doom holding the power grid and you hit him and you like take him out.
Oh, so you just shoot it.
A dummy gets shot into the water every two minutes.
It's just loading.
I would like more.
That would be fun.
Coasters do and more blood and murdering people.
It was just like the prestige ending in the bottom of the lake.
It's just so many Dr.
Doom dummies.
An open grave of Dr.
somebody's job at the end of each day is to just like
dredge out the dummy, dredge all the Dr.
Doom dummies and dry them out.
Let's be in one of the tunnels.
They like put like then now it's oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hmm. We're plusing it up already.
Yeah, yeah.
They spend so much money.
I mean, mother is the necessity of invention.
Dr. Doom's fearful is like an off the rack, like launch tower drop thing.
So, I mean, it's it's dressed up a little and then there's tons.
It's got a very cool like line and and videos and stuff inside,
but pretty much an off the rack kind of ride.
Yeah, because they spent all of their budget on these two massive rides.
Yeah. And they're still they're cloning this.
We're they're cloning this for Universal Studios.
Hey, right. And it's going to be transformers, though.
I was reading about that.
I saw that they were cloning it and I was like, oh, interesting.
I wonder if they're going to hold on to the the Marvel license or whatever.
Because the Marvel license is for America east of the Mississippi River.
Oh, specific.
Maybe Japan and Japan because they have Spider-Man there. Right.
Oh, yeah.
Do you guys know what the future holds for Super Island?
Are they going to be able to keep interesting?
Well, every few years, there's rumors.
Honestly, I think it's one of the most interesting sources of conflict
in the park, where it keeps it a little weird and a little interesting.
This piece of 1990s Marvel and Marvel 1999 is bankrupt,
is going through bankruptcy proceedings and
so that it's stuck in that period.
But Universal is obligated to keep it up and running and looking nice
where the contract is invalid.
Like it's such an odd.
Certainly. Yeah.
The characters have to be represented in that to not to be off limits
for Disney in Florida.
So like there's a whole thing with like they could.
There's maybe like Black Panther is barely represented in the Islands of Adventure.
So maybe they can use them, but legally they have to like still
like go through contracts because they had to list out all the characters
in the original contracts, supposedly.
Even though there's like a Murdoch Murdoch and Nelson law offices.
So Daredevils off the table.
Right. Just for one side.
But since Guardians weren't that popular and it was a different version of the team,
that's why they can use them in Florida.
Yeah. But there's every every year or two there's like, oh, Disney.
Their lawyers are talking to talk about like a trade, like an Al Michaels style
trade where they Disney traded Al Michaels or did they trade for Al?
You know what I'm talking about?
With Oswald? Yeah, for Oswald. Right.
There was a big trade between Warner Brothers and Universal might have owned
Oswald the Lucky Rabbit, and they made some weird trade for
sports broadcaster Al Michaels.
I've never heard of.
So like somehow, somehow.
Yeah, a deal was made where they want they always wanted the rights back to Oswald
the Lucky Rabbit, the other early Walt of Iwerks character
that had been tied up for decades and decades, which they still haven't
done anything with a little bit, but not a ton.
He's in that he's in a video game, but like not a little bit.
That was all how could that all have been important enough?
Right. And then but they yeah.
They traded Al Michaels for some like he had traded like he's on a sports team.
I mean, if he makes money, I have to remember exactly the details.
But I but there's been talk of like, oh, well, you know, there's things now
that Universal wants at Disney because now Simpsons is Disney, too.
And they're in Universal.
And there's got to be some quid pro quo that they could do.
So and then there's also we hear rumors every time we've brought this up
a couple of times.
There's a rumor that Jim Hill's talked about multiple times.
Jim Hill theme park podcasts are about the whole and getting a wicked overlay
and this ride specifically getting a wicked witch overlay.
Wicked the musical.
Broadway musical.
The Broadway musical.
Because you're like a wicked island.
A wicked, wicked, wicked island.
They just put a wicked coat of paint.
Which is like some culture war shit like that is like a Fox News guy was like,
well, Captain America's out of here.
And here come the Broadway New York actor.
Here comes the Broadway performers.
He said it a couple of times.
It seems insane.
I mean, it seems like I'm not accusing him of making it up or anything.
It just sounds so absurd.
I mean, Universal does own that.
And I do expect they're going to try to make a big movie.
The rings, too.
That was a big rumor.
Yeah, but it was something like that.
I mean, I would it would suck to lose Super Island
just because I have like so many fond memories of it.
But if you had to really the only ride that would be super affected is Spider-Man,
because you just can't do that.
And I think that's the thing.
Spider-Man is still such a well reviewed by guests attraction.
And also the thing is, Universal probably wants to keep Disney,
Florida from having a big shiny land devoted to the most popular movies
right now on the planet.
Like there's probably a there's an incentive for them to keep it away.
It makes more sense for them not to have Disney open this crazy thing
that everybody wants to go to in Florida.
He said it's east of the Mississippi, right?
So is that why they can do Guardians here?
Yeah, and they're doing a whole land next summer.
So they can do they can do everything here.
Yeah, but they can't.
They don't really use Marvel.
But they were right.
But they can't use Marvel, the word Marvel for some weird reason.
So that's why, like when they did a summer of superheroes last year,
it was called the summer of heroes and not like Marvel summer.
That's that's especially crazy because Marvel,
the official title for every one of those, the MCU movies is Marvel's blank.
And all their TV shows is Marvel's blank.
They love. Yes, the branding at all. Yeah. Yes.
But it's so especially with all these companies merging and things absorbing,
I think there's this is probably still one of the most tangled legal things
that they have a stake in Hulk.
That's one of the reasons why they have trouble getting.
Yes. Solo movies off the ground.
So for some reason, there's a weird legal wrangling that you can't.
Marvel can't make a solo, a solo Hulk movie.
They would have to do the deal like what they did with Sony for Spider-Man. Right.
But they can put Hulk in whatever they want.
If he's in something else, he's in something else. Yeah.
But you can even make like Wolverine versus Hulk,
which is a rumor I've seen thrown around like that's fine.
You can't just make like the incredible Hulk unless they make a deal with Universal.
I don't understand anything about that or why that is.
But it's very confusing.
Thank God we got that one movie to introduce
General Thaddeus Thunderbolt Ross into the MCU beloved character.
Still love to see him pop up. He's going to be in Black Widow.
He was in Black Widow, D-Aged.
The trailer came out last night.
Yeah. Sorry.
Which which of the live action films is General Thaddeus in?
He's the Ed Norton Hulk. Yeah.
And he's William Hurt.
He's really the only he's really the only
connection that that movie kind of has to the current movies.
And I mean, like, I think vaguely, I think Mark Ruffalo says
in the first Avengers movie says like, oh, I broke Harlem,
which is a reference to like the ending fight at the end of The Incredible Hulk.
Oh, yeah. But it's really kind of like the bastard stepchild of the MCU
is the lowest grossing one.
Yeah. Yeah.
Norton not Edward Norton not brought back apparently.
There's a Sam Jackson cameo in it.
Is there a Downey Jr.
There's a down at the end of the post credits is like, is it?
I know it's General Thaddeus Ross and Robert Downey Jr.
Yeah, that's so confusing.
Yeah. And it's the second one.
It's right after Iron Man.
So it's like they put those two first into the proper MCU.
You know how much this old Disney thing is fucking and they've taken over my brain.
I don't remember who put out the first Marvel movies.
Well, you talk about the ones we're talking about.
Put out Iron Man.
Paramount Paramount.
But Marvel was no memory of it.
Yeah. Marvel formed its own studio at that point with whatever characters they had left,
which they didn't have Spider-Man or the X-Men.
It would be a hit. It was a gamble.
It was a real gamble.
In the 90s.
Because in the 90s, those were the characters that a lot of places were like,
well, no one gives a shit about Captain America or Iron Man or Thor.
Like, those are the boring ones.
And I won't say as a kid, I was like, those are the more boring ones.
Yeah, I was never.
It took it took the movies for me to give a shit about Thor.
I was Thor was like, wow, he talks like a fucking Shakespeare character.
Like, I don't know.
Because all of the big artists were on like X-Men or for a while Spider-Man.
Yeah.
Which kind of is interesting how little X-Men presence there is at Marvel Superhero Island.
But the more I thought about it, I think Hulk and Spider-Man are so internationally identifiable.
Yeah.
As part of it.
Yeah, I wonder.
I mean, the X-Men thing is odd that there wouldn't have been a big X-Men ride.
I'm sure that was in the thought like planning because it just makes total sense.
They were the biggest thing.
But Spider-Man probably more internationally recognized.
Yeah.
And anyone can be under the mask.
That's a big thing.
Always talk about that.
Who doesn't Disney have now?
I get so confused.
OK, so they can't make the Hulk movie because universal, but they can put Hulk in anything they want.
Yeah.
They don't own.
He can be in Lady and the Tramp.
He could be in Lady and the Tramp.
Lady and the Tramp.
Lady and Hulk and the Tramp.
This is the night.
They don't have Spider-Man.
Sony owns the rights to make TV shows and movies about Spider-Man.
They're just licensing or not licensing.
They're just borrowing the character.
And they almost read, read divorced.
They almost read divorce.
They went through a little thing.
Yeah, that was all just posturing.
It feels like that.
Well, yeah, that's I I will say I called that immediately.
You did call that.
And I was like, they were going to solve this in under two months.
And they did.
I do think that's an interesting thing, too, because they're they're headed for a couple different ways.
I don't know if that will relationship will last forever.
Yeah, but it's really tenuous.
And it's also strange because Sony is really still trying to like lean into like, oh, we're going to every Spider-Man
villain is going to have a movie.
And a lot of those look like they're going to be like really bad.
Well, yes.
So Swiss Miss might have been cross.
So Sony's making long fingers grow.
Scott, have you been taking Swiss Miss meetings and all the gala?
So I respect NDAs.
We should all go in the room for that.
So, yes, Sony's doing its own Marvel universe, but just the Spider-Man
characters, Jared Leto's Michael Morbius, the vampire movie coming next year or this year,
depending on when this comes out.
Oh, fucking yeah.
But there's also now that we're on the topic of contracts that apparently I like,
there's something in the contract of if if because there's rumors that Apple wants to buy Sony.
So Apple buys Sony, Spider-Man reverts back to Marvel.
So if there's any big sale of Sony as a whole studio, Marvel will get Spider-Man back.
I'm like having trouble even wrapping my mind around that sentence.
Right. It's like, yeah, I know.
There's like too many companies in the sentence.
Well, because Sony is also weak enough that it's like Disney could just buy them.
Yes, I yes.
So Apple, who if they decide that the morning show is not
setting their entertainment world on fire, maybe they decide we're watching us see
all the big all the big Apple.
We love to see it.
We love to see the Apple TV Plus.
So if they decide that maybe, you know, let's just buy Ghostbusters or whatever.
Like that might happen.
Sure. And then at that point, those
they won't they will lose Spider-Man.
There's also reports that Marvel was just thinking about like giving Sony
five billion dollars to buy it back.
Which like they valued Spider-Man it like something.
It might be more than that, honestly.
I am with I'm with you, Chase.
I'm like I need like this needs to be a PowerPoint.
I need logos in front of me and I need the logos to move.
There's so many characters.
I'm so I don't even as I said, I don't really watch these movies.
I don't know who Nebula is, but like it is like such a dense web from the Sopranos
with like little like pieces of red string connecting.
And if anyone dies, cross them off just like because take them off my blade.
I can't deal with those reading comics in the 90s, though, actually got me trained
for this type of consolidation because so many companies would spring up
with like VC money and go under within a year or two.
And then sometimes they get bought by Marvel or DC or sometimes they just fold.
Or like Jim Lee's Wildstorm imprint, which was an image originally.
Yes, it's just Jim's Lee Studio image was like all these guys,
the guys, six studios, one company seizure.
He sold his studio to DC.
Right. He sold all those characters to DC.
So now Warner Brothers owns all of these characters he independently created.
And by the way, did you know that Cindy Krover's husband, Randy Gerber,
has a tequila company?
I don't want to go to camping world.
So it's just, you know, there's a lot going on.
Who owns the Casamiga's IPs?
What do I want to know?
Well, someone bought it.
I'll get interested in Casamiga's.
Constellation Brahms.
Constellation Brahms becomes the.
Oh, yeah.
Very smooth.
Doesn't cut up my throat like Swiss Mizz.
A big change in this ride occurred before the re-theming
that we hadn't touched on in 2011.
Or no, sorry, I forget.
In 2011, there were a bunch of incidents of stuff flying out of people's pockets
on specifically the Dueling Dragons coaster, which is the other
BNM coaster that opened Islands of Adventure.
And stuff flew out of people's pockets.
In one case, a man lost an eye from this, like got hit by something.
Oh, a real eye.
Oh, no, a real eye, like a phone or a wallet hit him in the eye.
Oh, yeah.
His origin story.
So Universal made the rule for at the time
Dragon Challenge, Hulk and the Rip Ride
Rocket Coasters, like nothing in your pockets.
And you have to go through a metal detector, specifically Hulk
and Rip Ride and Rocket.
You have to go through a metal detector.
So there's lockers.
That you can put your stuff in.
This was not the case for the first, like
12 years of operation for this ride.
Well, what year does it start?
This started.
I guess it's longer.
This started around like 20 or I think with the redo, I think with like 2015,
when they were redoing it, they put in all the security stuff.
Right. I would ride with shit in my pockets all the time.
The whole coaster,
especially in the height of the popularity of cargo pockets.
It was very easy to just Velcro your stuff in an exterior pocket
because I wanted to see the Q videos with my glasses.
I'm blind as a bat without glasses.
So you were what?
Sorry. I was going to say, I feel like in a lot of cases, like the lap bar
or whatever, I can't remember if this if it comes down over you
or if there's a lap bar.
But a lot of times the lap bar can do a good job of holding stuff in,
especially if it's like a big like, you know, rubber or plastic one or whatever.
That kind of covers everything.
Sure. Yeah.
This is shoulder restraints that are then buckled in.
So the restraints fail.
The buckles catch it.
And like the sitting down aspect with that restraint does seem like
that shouldn't be much of a problem.
But obviously it happened a few times.
So they don't want to chance it.
I get it with like the standing coasters and the day your legs dangling.
And then like with the one I went to at Six Flags.
What's that one called?
I always forget the one I went out with Anthony Geo.
Oh, X2.
Crotch crusher.
Crotch crusher, which happened again, by the way, on the hang time.
Like his penis got crushed.
Yes. I said, I think I turned.
What did I say?
I think the employee came by, pushed the thing on my crotch
and just shoved my penis into my body.
And I go, oh, my God, it happened again.
And I was trying to.
I think it happened at Ghost Rider, too.
And you're like, it's not as bad, but it happened again.
So I get it.
I get it why on the other ones you don't want that to happen
or something that's extra crazy.
But this one does seem like it's not that big of a deal.
But obviously, what do I know?
I mean, it sucks the guy lost his eye.
Yeah.
And now his story is someone asked him like, what happened?
He's like, fucking Hulk, man.
Yeah.
The machine.
It didn't.
Wait, what's the line?
It didn't work out.
Oh, I think it's this time it's going to work.
The glasses thing, I didn't.
Yeah.
Now I remember you had to put your glasses away.
I put my glasses away.
We had to walk a lot.
And we were like, you have to guide me because I.
Magoota, because it's so dark.
The queue got darker, too.
And they're not great at chaining off or directing.
They're not as good at directing you where to go.
So everyone in this line is vision impaired, like forcibly.
Well, that's what I was realizing, because like.
I don't know if as many people as me are as.
Or as. Yeah.
So do you keep them on during like, like Harry Potter and stuff like that?
Yeah. OK. More for that. Yeah.
Even some I've gone on like even some.
I think I've kept them on for like California Scream.
And I usually take them off.
But my dad used to keep his on all the time.
And we I don't know.
I wear plastic frames now, so they're a little looser
than like tighter metal ones.
But yeah, I mean, so for so for the Hulk, when the first version of it,
I used to like to walk through the queue and watch the videos and stuff.
And then I put the glasses in a case, put it in my pocket.
And yeah, it's a big they have to have like a glasses case on the right.
And they have to put like a little there has to be some like that.
That is a kind of an oversight, honestly.
Not building people should be like maybe like a pouch in front of every seat
or something like that, like, yeah, that you can that seals, you know.
So it's not going to like nothing's going to happen to it.
Yeah. Yeah.
There's a lot of a lack of that on all like at a certain point,
Universal was like, nope, lockers everywhere.
I think the lawsuits probably cost them a fortune.
Yeah, maybe getting hit by stuff because then they also had to change
like Dueling Dragons whole thing was the coasters launched at the same time
and they go in and out.
And that's why people got hit by stuff.
But like there's no lockers on rock and roller coaster.
There's no there are or not.
Sorry, not you're right. No, not right.
Yeah. And there's no California Screamin lockers. Right.
And there's not as many coasters, obviously, in Disney World or land.
But if you put if you have glasses on the ride,
then aren't the glasses going to halt out?
Mm hmm. You're going to break.
Yeah. Well, they'll just burst.
All right. You're not going to I just pictured like, you know, oh, giant.
Yeah. Yeah. Big mostly.
That is a great point is glasses are often illustrated as breaking,
whereas his pants stay mostly together.
Yeah. Well, they're made selectively.
They're made using unstable molecule.
Reed Richards is invention unstable molecules, which we all know about.
There is a mention meaning that they can stretch.
Oh, oh, that's why he can wear pants.
They just yeah, they explain it away because the fantastic four like Reed
Richards, he stretches.
So his costume has to be able to stretch.
So we made something called unstable molecules for him and the family.
And then Hulk's purple ripped pants.
So frayed at the bottom.
They still rest of those. They just cover your penis.
Yeah. He made it so like the there was like a cool like
and there was a ripped pattern in the below it.
It was all stable molecules.
So those would rip out because it looked yeah, because it looked cool.
Yeah. Then you look like a pirate in a play or something. Yeah.
Yeah. Reed was interested in that.
But he didn't want to do like one giant Hulk ball hanging out.
No, no massive.
Just what?
Yeah, that's what I like.
Well, not the full penis, but just one ball.
To where you'd be looking up at it like, what's that?
Oh, oh, oh, no.
You distract his enemies.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah. You'd look down, huh?
Oh, he punches you in the face. Yeah.
I think I may have a possible answer for why on like those two Disney coasters.
I think they go slower because Hulk,
well, it launches you up to 40 miles per hour at top speeds.
You reach 67 miles an hour.
And I think the Disney ones might scream.
Those are 40 scream and launch 60 or no, is it 40?
I thought Rock and Rollercoaster is like 50 something.
Am I wrong? That one might launch quick.
But maybe it's just the way that the cars are.
What are somebody will answer this is Rock and Rollercoaster
and rip ride rocket.
Two different. Yes.
Yes. They sure are.
I always get them mixed up.
One is one Aerosmith. Yeah.
How are you roller coaster is Aerosmith.
Yes. So one gives you a choice between like six different songs.
The other one's like, no, it's Aerosmith.
One gives you six different Aerosmith songs.
Yeah. Yeah.
Theme park specific Aerosmith songs.
Yeah. Just singing about haunted mansion.
Oh, Aerosmith covers of all of the.
Yeah. Oh, man, that would be great.
Mm hmm. Yeah.
So I don't know. Well, somebody will answer that question.
You know what's I think an interesting little effect about the Hulk?
I think also correct me if I'm wrong in this, but I think first universal launch.
It would have to be. Yes.
And I think the first launch in Orlando.
Oh, because because Rock and Roller not quite open.
A little bit later. A little bit later.
Yep. Yeah. I don't know.
I'd have to see, but you might be right.
Really? I that that tracks, I think, because I definitely remember writing that one before.
I don't think I wrote.
It's the same year, though.
Right. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. We did their first launch for this man for BNM, the manufacturer of this coaster.
Then they didn't build another launching coaster until what is it?
It's called Thunderbird.
It's that holiday world.
That is the holiday themed park in the Midwest where soda is free.
That's you guys know, the most Midwestern thing I've ever heard.
Holy shit. It. Wait.
So is it different holidays or is it all?
It's like Christmas land, Halloween land.
So it's all these different lands and one of their big selling.
They have a few great marketing techniques.
One, it's in Santa Claus, Indiana.
Two, parking is free.
Three, soft drinks are free.
Well, found drinks are free.
It is Pepsi and just plant its dancing fountains.
You can just walk up to any just just like walk up to a fan, just fill your cup up.
I will say the the time when I went to Six Flags in Massachusetts earlier,
this year, and I think honestly, like when I'm at Universal,
I see more people drinking huge sodas than anywhere else in my entire life.
Yeah, sure. Yeah.
Because because yeah, in the hey, in the in the showbiz city,
some people aren't like doing gallons.
But yeah, particularly at Six Flags, there was some kind of like
it was free refills or something like that.
So people were just walking.
People were lugging these from ride to ride.
That's what they you know, instead of their like valuables or whatever,
they were putting like a huge Dr.
Pepper in the thing and like getting him and they get off the ride.
To wash out the taste of Panda Express Express
limited menu.
Panda Express down made with less care.
Well, now imagine the kind like the rollercoaster days that are challenging for you,
but add like more soda than you'd know in a year.
It would have been bad.
Geez. Yeah, you do it.
That's probably why I would like hit my limit as a child for going on coasters.
It wasn't wear and tear.
I was just terribly dehydrated from only drinking soda. Yeah. Yeah.
There was also some that were just like deceptively nauseating.
Like there was one that looked like it looked like almost like a kiddie coaster
or something. But I don't know if you guys have talked about this type of coaster
before. I feel like I've only seen them a few times, but the ones that are like
instead of having like, you know, being inverted or doing a lot of loops
or something like that, like it's kind of like a cart on a track sort of.
And a lot of it is like taking hard turns.
That's like wild mouse.
Wow. Just came up. Yeah.
We're talking about this with Danny and like how the how goofy
Sky School we avoid and yeah. Yeah.
It's a surprisingly tough little.
And there was another one.
I don't think this was the same one, but there was another one that
you spun as you were on the track.
So it was like doing a rollercoaster, doing a teacups and the rollercoaster
at the same time. Wow.
Which you're looking at and going, well, this is for kids.
Right. And you're on it.
And I really I had to we were on it.
It was me and someone else.
And then we were there with like a little girl and she kept wanting to like
spend the thing. I had to be like, I can't do this anymore.
Stop this.
My insides are 35.
Please just go on it again with someone else who can handle this.
Yeah, I know we maybe need to like
we got to examine the wild mouse
for law and figure out maybe like scientifically, why is it so deceptively freaky?
The I think the feeling of like I am going to go over the edge.
That's not how it's very like psychological.
It's very like Temple of Doom, mine, Carti, like it.
Yeah. Even though you know that you're attached, like it really feels like the
inertia is going to like drop you off the side.
Yeah. Yeah.
And any any time heights are involved, speed
just makes my brain forget about the height.
Like that's what I like with the launch or anything.
It's like speed is what's tricking me into
not caring as much that I'm very high up.
Right.
So it's like the wild mouse coaster that's not nearly as high up as a giant
roller coaster, much scarier than the other one.
And often you can see everything.
Yes. In the dark.
Yeah, I mean, that's part of Hulk is so imposing.
I mean, it's it's tallest point is 150 feet above the ground.
And also a lot of it goes over water.
So like there's an unnerving feel,
but there is a lot of psychological stuff with when they did the revamp.
Did they did they add any track?
Did they make it longer at all?
Because I was just seeing on on YouTube, there was there's a
ride through that was pre the revamp.
And it's like a minute and a half long.
And then there's and I don't I didn't watch the whole thing.
So I don't know if they skip some in the middle or something like that.
But then the all the more recent ones are like like three and a half minutes
or four minutes long, which is weird.
That is weird. Yeah, I don't think no, they it's not longer.
I wonder if it's just they're more in show or inappropriate show.
I don't know. Yeah, maybe.
Maybe there was more of like the build up to, you know. Yeah.
It's strange that they they replaced the track, but didn't do anything different.
I think people were people just so like addicted to that design.
Yeah, yeah, maybe.
I mean, it's very well reviewed, like it won a lot of awards,
very well reviewed by audiences.
It's I but from what I understand, it's very hard to add track to coasters
that exist because it's like it's a it's a math equation of how much
like energy you build up and how much you can sustain. Oh, sure.
So it's like Tony Baxter was talking about Big Thunder Mountain.
He's always been disappointed by the last in Disneyland,
specifically the last like the third like exciting part,
because it's not as fast as the rest of it.
And he was like, well, there wasn't enough like track.
There wasn't enough room to do it. Yeah.
So it's all like a weird math thing that you never really think about.
So I think it would be like hard, very hard to extend it.
I would think if you were going to like change something on it,
you would want like a like a Hulk style yeti like on Everest,
like pounding at you somewhere. Yeah.
There's a tunnel.
You go through a tunnel. Yeah, right. Yes.
You get a hole in there, but you go so fast.
It does seem. Yeah, it does.
Because like like I was saying earlier with the credit coaster, they've they
have like every member of the Incredibles family, like somewhere along the things.
And there like kind of is a story to that one where you're like looking,
you're helping them look for Jack Jack or something like that. Yeah.
And it would be kind of cool if they added like a couple of hulks along the way
or something. Sure. Hulkling, a little Hulk, babies, babies, baby.
Like like little Shrek, like little baby Shrek's. Yeah, I
it's like I was trying to think of like what the most successful
coaster that has like characters are theming on.
And I guess is it Everest?
Is that like because Everest is a giant.
It doesn't work. The animatronic doesn't work.
But when it did, it was incredible. Hagrid's now.
Yeah, I guess Hagrid's is probably a new standard for it.
So, yeah, it's like you'd probably it'd probably be too hard to do it
as elaborately as Hagrid's.
This is the new this is the motorbike one. Yeah. Yeah.
Which is really good.
Oh, really? OK, cool. It's something. Yeah. Yeah.
It was a sneaker.
Flight of the hippogriff sucks out.
Yeah, certainly. Yes.
That's another quickie fix of like that's a standard like. Yeah.
Yeah. No, it's right.
They go. Oh, right. Yeah.
It's no it's yeah, it's it's no that.
That's yeah.
So it's like and you can't put it under like a building
because I will say skyline wise, it's fantastic.
Like when you're when you're sitting on that porch of Margaritaville
at City Walk and you see it, it's really nice.
It's a real nice picture right there.
And like it would ruin the skyline to put a building over it.
Yeah, because that's the front of the park.
Well, let's you know, here, while we're plusing it up and Hulk plus ups
certainly are a lot.
But here's I to go back to the Marvel superhero island thing.
I was thinking legitimately, OK, the deal the deal got made.
We got to pull out of the Marvel is out of Universal.
Have to fix it.
They're not going to take this coaster out like that because you can re theme it.
What do you do?
Well, are we do it's probably you have to decide what the whole land is,
I would assume, because it's got to be a whole land.
I think so. I think the others could follow.
Certainly you could you could amend what is like the mean the drop tower.
But we've talked about it, I think, before.
But it's like, is it is it just Shrek land?
Oh, that would be you barely got that out.
You know, the answer is not.
I'm saying it's like you hit the brake platform.
What universal character is riding?
I'm trying to think practically here.
Oh, Grinch paint the Grinch coaster.
OK, well, I mean, there's rumors of a Grinch coaster for years.
But there's a loose land over the land.
But you don't want that much.
So yeah, yeah.
To soothe the rides are kind of intense for for it.
Yeah, yeah, to be Grinch.
Yes. Yes, potentially. Yes.
The ride is how you're it's how you feel inside when he insults you,
like on his famous snarky billboards. Oh.
Aliens like a Nostromo evacuation.
Oh, shit.
Disney has. Oh, man.
I guess I could see it, even though the rides in that section of the park
are pretty intense, if it was like illumination land or something like that.
So you got minions and you got then you have the Grinch.
Yeah. Whatever else they've made.
Well, we got to see your life of pets coming bizarrely post the
movie kind of bombing.
Oh, what about Valley?
It's a back to the future.
It's a big delorium. OK. Yeah.
What about that?
That's good. But what about mad about you?
What about about you, Coaster?
Original. You have to be a spectrum customer to enter that.
Yes. Enter your enter your parents.
Log in. Well, and grace your parents back to you are at a Comcast Park,
but enter your parents back to Jimmy.
I mean, Jimmy Fallon is a ride.
What are their famous and the Today Show Cafe now?
Oh, my God. This is us.
Crockpot explosion.
Oh, so it's like an accident in the kitchen accident.
Yes. Yes, that's good.
And then somebody dies because that happens on every episode.
I've been under Crockpot.
I don't watch the shows. Crockpot explosion.
Apparently, one season, a character died because a Crockpot exploded.
And then Crockpot had to come out and go, our products do not explode.
You're thinking of pressure cookers.
Good for them. But yeah, OK.
You're like now the tube is like it's a cylindrical kitchen.
Yes. And Crockpot explodes and launches you on the on on a journey to death.
Yes. That's good.
Always heard rumors about like, I mean, this is the thing.
Why what you were saying, like, yeah, it was strange they made a TV show a ride.
Like movies kind of hang around the popular consciousness much longer,
even though they're so much shorter than TV shows.
And I feel like I remember in the early 2000s, like theme park rumors like,
well, heroes, everyone was curious.
They got to get heroes in the park.
Imagine if they were stuck with that.
They were stuck with Siler.
You have to save the cheerleader and save the world.
Save the cheerleader from Siler.
You did it. You saved the cheerleader and saved the world.
We proud of you.
Wow. That Horn Room classics animatronic.
I still often describe saying every so often.
You do know me.
I know you don't know any other heroes characters, but
yeah, well, you know what shows never go away or soap operas.
So, you know, you can do these are the days of our lives.
You're in the hourglass.
OK, I thought our marriage was going to work.
No, no.
Abominable. Oh, the snow.
The snowman. Yeah, it can be all be abominable.
It's now it's a like really intense bobsled ride.
Superstore.
Yeah. What about like your yeah, like what could you
is there like a pneumatic tube or anything in Superstore
that they send messages back and forth between anyone watch Superstore?
Is there any NBC property with a pneumatic tube like a bank?
Isn't a character in a wheelchair perpetually cold and done?
Is in a wheelchair. All right.
So like where this is going.
Yeah. You're on a you're mad.
You know. Oh, yeah. OK. Yeah.
Handicap chair ride.
It works out for you.
You survive. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Should be fine. He built he built a invented a 16 person wheelchair.
I'm not sure why.
For like, you know,
I always love that part of the ride in the in the pre show
when they're telling you why they've invented this completely impractical,
like bigger version of whatever is like part of that world.
Yeah. Yeah. Because I'm sure it would only help the let's make the DeLorean.
That'll help us get to 88 for carrying more luggage.
Is there a tie in between the video we saw of the two famous people riding the ride?
Oh, yeah. There's so many famous people.
You know, written by this.
Well, the video ice, of course, the best.
Are you talking about the best friends?
Ellen and Usher. Yeah.
Yes. Ellen and Usher wrote it together, seemingly for usher's social media,
because that's where this video lives. Yeah.
Is that it wasn't she was it wasn't part of the tape down there sometimes.
I don't know about that.
I honestly all I saw she was like, I don't know if it was a contrived thing
where she's like, you're going to tape this.
She kept like yelling at him, like, you're going to lose the camera
because he's just holding it unless he had it strapped to his wrist.
Supposed to do that.
And unless you have a GoPro harness or something, he was like, no, I'll be fine.
And then it's just a nothing really happens.
Like that was really I stopped watching it is boring.
Boring. Like the Jimmy Fallon hanging out.
Yeah, they just go on.
And Usher isn't even talking to you.
Right. Not like, yeah, I'm here with Ellen and we're going to go on the ride.
Nothing happened.
Nothing happens. They both enjoy it.
Like the Kevin Hart, Jimmy Fallon video, if you haven't seen it,
Kevin Hart is melting down. Yeah.
He's losing his mind. Mm hmm.
So at least I know I'm right.
Right. Rocket.
But like I watch the in sync and Rosie O'Donnell ride the Hulk.
No, I have not seen that. That's that's wonderful.
And the right is older than I thought.
Yeah, I know. Sorry.
Oh, 2012.
What? What?
Wait, what is this from 2012?
Well, do we have another unit?
They did ride it in 99.
This was OK. Oh, well, it was kind of hard to see.
Yeah. So 99, they wrote it for her show.
Her show was still going in 99. Wow. Yeah.
Geeze. Interesting. Isn't that Fallon taped?
I think it where Rosie used to tape.
Mm hmm. I think I could be wrong.
I mean, they probably just it's a nice video of them enjoying it, I assume.
Oh, yes. Here's them walking up to it.
And I'm going to I'm going to go through all the loop.
They've got some big shirts.
Was Lou Pearlman our big shirt was Lou Pearlman there?
Lou Pearlman and Sink and Rosie all riding together.
We got a vest.
We got a vest over short sleeve button up in shorts.
Pearlman, he's in dreads.
Real life doctor doom.
Real Lou Pearlman.
He he's not allowed in any theme parks anymore.
He's doing too much recruiting there.
They're doing a lot of bits and stuff.
Well, we'll watch it to see if there's anything good in there.
Great. So maybe maybe it's just a celebrity coaster.
You know, your celebrities and you're that cannon.
The pressure cook you're in is is to simulate what it's like to work at the Ellen show.
Oh, yeah.
They replaced the soundtrack, which is her screaming at you.
Is there like, boy, this is a lot scarier than the whole was.
All right. So it's not like that teasing from Dakota Johnson.
Everyone bat.
I saw that.
All right. So it's either Ellen or Shrek.
Got it.
It's oh, by the way, it's a classic.
Fart cannon. Fart cannon.
Oh, very good.
Oh, yes.
We're trying to build the
thought attempting the world's biggest fart.
The fart, the the hugest fart ever attempted.
As I say that, that makes so much sense.
That universal would do it, especially when it's reboot.
Shrek has been in a few years because the universe is more adult.
And they'll go there.
That's the humor. Yeah.
Well, I think I dig it.
Chase, any last minute thoughts?
Plus up Hulk memories.
Any the hulking out you wanted to?
Would you like to Hulk out?
Uh, no, I mean, that's yeah, it it it is a very fondly remembered
bride for me and and yeah, it's a regret that it's not what it once was.
But it's still I think it's still fun.
Yeah, it's just whatever reason like it's maybe just our ages, honestly.
Should be.
But yes, it's the the the.
They're blaming it on like LEDs and it's all like headache.
As far as related.
Yeah, as far as the headaches is our ages in the pre show, obviously, is their fault.
The pre show pre show you feel a little more fun.
Now it looks like this CG you see when like they licensed the Avengers
to like a park in the Middle East that doesn't have the rights to the actors.
License. Yeah, they just do it real quick in the CG.
And yeah, the way that it was before the the pre show video was it was kind of
it was kind of
cheap looking and like in like an endearing way, like it was.
The animation was like kind of bad looking. Yeah.
Marvel had a string of cartoons in the 90s and X-Men and Spider-Man were the big ones.
And then there was like, all right, turn out some more.
So then there was Iron Man and Fantastic Four and Hulk.
And those were all just syndicated all over the place.
A little cheaper, a little cheaper.
So maybe a lot. I don't know.
All right. So well, we plus it up perfectly.
Yeah. Yeah.
I don't know what else there is to do.
Oh, can I say this is just this is really juvenile and I shouldn't read this.
Let's do it. But the company that's responsible for putting it up.
Did you see that on the Wikipedia, what it was called?
Superior rigging and erection, which makes a lot of sense.
But I don't know. I've never seen a company with just erection.
They use the direction.
Superior rigging and erection.
Of course, that's what it is.
The construction company who literally lifted the beams and stuff.
Yes, right. But hey, they deserve credit, too.
I think I might. Well, here's an idea.
Here's how Universal can really spice it up.
It's the for that.
That island becomes the first like adults.
It's the first pornographic.
Oh, OK. And the and the Hulk is that is then the canon.
That is you are a you're a sperm getting shot out of an erection.
Well, this sounds like actually a learn.
It's like actually a learning tool, maybe two for kids.
Yes. OK, it's not.
Yeah, it's not. It's about.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You go to in the way people, you know, sometimes schools go to Six Flags
to learn about physics.
Yeah. On the roller coasters, you start going to islands of adventure
to learn about the reproductive.
You enter in the cowper's gland and you shoot to the vas deferens
to the urethra.
Yeah, somebody. Yeah.
That's exactly what I assume.
Yeah, there's like kind of like a glass slide that people will bring around.
And you see you can.
It's an overlay.
You can point at the labels of all the parts.
And so that means you have to at the station land back
through a vagina, I guess, or just or land in it.
That's the well, if you're shooting an egg, that's the yeah.
No, I think that you yeah, you have to fertilize to.
Yeah, that's the that's a triumph.
It's a tantric thing. It's internal. It's all internal.
Yeah, because you can't see it.
You're already in the vagina in the universe of the roller coaster.
Oh, I suppose you have to be inside already.
Half of the yeah.
The implications of that not being the case, I don't even want to talk about
what, frankly, it's too far for me already.
Yeah, let's bail before it gets too uncomfortable.
Awesome chase, vigil, you survive, but guess the ride.
Thanks for being here.
Thanks for having me, dudes. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, thanks for hanging out.
It's extra to the gift shop.
Anything you'd like to plug?
I mean, yeah, I that so yeah, I'm working for a Netflix show.
It's not it's not going to be out until 2021.
So, oh, man, I don't know if that beats the infinity train
in terms of advanced.
Yeah, really?
But it'll be called Inside Job and just check it out whenever it lands.
And yeah, I don't know if you want to follow me on Twitter.
It's at Chase Mitt, C.H.A.S.C. MIT.
Yeah, great tweets, great tweets all the time.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Thanks for being here.
And for more podcast, the ride, follow us on Twitter, Instagram and Facebook
and this three bonus episodes every month.
If you subscribe to podcast, the ride, the second gate
at Patreon dot com slash podcast, the ride.
Yeah. All right.
That'll do it.
Let's end the episode. I'm not afraid.
Not afraid, not afraid.
Forever.
Oh, this has been a forever dog production
executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner,
Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts dot com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify
or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter
and Instagram at Forever Dog Team and liking our page on Facebook.