Forever.
Dog.
Warning, today's episode gets political,
but we at Podcast The Ride feel this is a good thing
because a healthy debate strengthens
our core amusement park beliefs.
So prepare for a heated yet robust discussion
about grain and people possibly doing lab work.
Carly Weisel returns to graze the third rail
of theme park politics, Epcot's Living with the Land,
today on Podcast The Ride.
["The Ride Theme Park Theme Song"]
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the theme park podcast
that's not afraid to touch the hottest topics around,
namely slow, plant-based, learning-based boat rides.
My name is Mike Carlson, joining me as always,
some fire throwers like Jason Sheridan.
I'm just here to talk about a great ride
everyone knows and loves that we all enjoy.
And Scott Garen, I think I meant to say flamethrowers,
not fire throwers.
Flamethrowers?
Hi, I'm here to, I feel somewhat counter to Jason's POV,
but you know what, I would like to,
I'd like this to be, I'd like it to be a learning experience
for me as well.
I'd like to be taught why this isn't the boringest ride
I've ever been on.
Sorry, everybody.
Okay, all right.
But this is good.
I like that we're, yeah.
Scott, let me reassure you that in order to do that,
I'll just go ahead and tell you the technology exists
and the technology is not.
I'll just go ahead and tell you the technology exists.
Really all we need is the courage and the innovation
and the ability and the will to do it,
the will to educate you.
Oh my God.
As Dr. Carl Hodges of Arizona.
Oh, why are we?
Arizona State University, who helps create this attraction.
Why are we recording, how did we end up recording this
on a Tuesday night instead of first thing in the morning?
I should have just drained coffee.
I should have doused myself in coffee to make this possible.
I will be asleep by the end of this.
I don't know, we'll see.
This might get ugly.
Coffee, the bean, of course,
which grows in tropical climes.
No.
That's the first biome.
Let's bring in our guest because I like our guest.
I think there's something I enjoy,
a fan favorite, an us favorite,
a theme park journalist for so many great publications.
Carly Weisel is here.
Hello, good boys.
Hello.
It's good to see you, although I was,
when this came up, it was undeniable that
when you suggested it, like, well, of course,
that has to happen.
I was like, well, this is how it becomes
instead of two against one, three against one.
Because this is becoming an inevitable topic for us.
Yes.
So now I'm severely outnumbered.
And like, you add the Facebook group to it and a lot more.
It's funny, because this has a real
city hall meeting feel to it.
It doesn't feel like a bunch of people who love theme parks
coming around to just gab about rides they like.
It feels like we're each gonna spend four minutes
at a podium driving each other crazy.
I think it might.
We're also recording this in the exact sliver of time
that the Iowa caucus is being, like, what, stolen?
What's going on?
I don't, we're not sure.
We'll see.
We'll see in maybe a couple weeks.
In a couple weeks, maybe we'll know.
Maybe a couple weeks or months.
We're recording this in the fog.
This episode might come out in April.
I have no idea.
So I don't know, but if that might add to the procedural,
there's a very governmental order in the room, I suppose.
I mean, I'm not gonna be harsh with you,
but I do feel that you will emerge out of the other side,
both staring at random strangers on a screen
and in love with this attraction.
This is why I am glad that it's you here to talk about this.
I think you will make this a positive experience,
an experience of growth, I hope.
Or I'm just a raving madman by the end of the day.
We should explain why, for anyone who doesn't know,
what the tension is here.
We are talking about a boat ride at Epcot Center.
This is called Living with the Lambs.
I would say it's not just any boat ride.
We're already.
I would say it's number one boat ride at Epcot Center.
I'd probably agree.
I would agree, yeah.
Guys, madness.
This stat has already been said.
I don't know if I can agree with that.
Thank you, Michael.
Mike is a moderate.
I appreciate that.
No, don't say that.
All right.
What could possibly.
Mike, a general in the clobacarmy.
No, I'm not a moderate.
Look, look, Scott.
I'm Bloomberg, of course.
No, you know what, fine.
I am a theme park moderate.
That's who I am.
I want reasonable.
Before we started recording,
you're like old Epcot must die.
I cannot wait to meet the spirit of storytelling.
I am so excited to meet my new favorite character.
I hope Dame Judi Dench,
I hope Moana uses her water abilities
to send Dame Judi Dench to the watery depths.
Let the old ways die.
No, I don't know.
Okay, look.
You're Kylo Ren in this situation.
Before we get into opinions,
we have to explain what this is
because there are listeners who don't know
why this episode is like this already.
Now let's please make sure to give its current name
and its former name.
Yeah, yeah.
Go ahead.
The current name is Living With The Land.
The previous name is Listen To The Land.
Listen To The Land from 1982 to the early 90s
when the craft sponsorship ended.
Or no, I'm sorry.
Yeah, is that correct?
Should we just play some of the original
Listen To The Land song real quick for everybody?
Let's start it off hot.
Just with the...
I've never heard this.
You've never heard this?
This is how the ride started.
This is how it originally...
You can't be mad at this.
Well, I'm not, I'll explain.
Oh my God.
I mean, that's the gist.
It's a very John Denver-y type song, children's choir.
In the family with the energy song,
less universe of energy and more that other one.
Energy.
Making my day.
Yes, because they were written by the same man.
Yeah, hell yeah.
What you don't realize is of course I can't be mad at that.
And you just played into my argument about this thing.
Oh, interesting.
I'm amazed you haven't heard this.
So that's from the original 82 up hot.
I never heard that.
And I didn't think it was possible to like this ride more.
But now knowing that it truly has a banger attached to it
from years ago.
It does, but you'll see.
I'm gonna flip this.
You'll understand in a minute.
Let's just explain what it is.
Yeah, so okay.
What's this ride?
And you know what?
I think this is good for...
As somebody who is on the counter on this ride,
I would like somebody to go ahead and try to
just explain it with no frills
and don't add any editorial anything to it.
Somebody points to the ride and said,
what is this ride?
What do you say?
I would say it is a slow moving boat ride
through some different show scenes, animatronic animals,
different terrain that is supposed to educate you
about the land and what the land gives us,
what you can grow in the land.
And then the second half,
you take a slow boat ride through some plants growing
in a greenhouse.
You go through four greenhouses,
four different biomes.
And see a lab.
You can't say the word biomes to a stranger
if they're asking what it is.
Yeah, I was trying to...
They have to be agriculturally versed.
Everyone was talking about by 70s and 80s,
the biosphere, people love talking about biomes.
Habitats, artificial habitats.
This is 2020.
How many people are we talking about biomes all the time?
I would go ahead and say that this ride
only gets more important as the earth starts to dissolve.
Well, then we have another argument to get into.
Global warming is a hoax.
We're changing the topic of the episode.
No, no, okay.
So yes, now that's a pretty good,
just fair description of the ride.
Now let's add to this that somehow I've made a lot
of people angry by saying,
I don't like what you just described.
Right.
What happened was when we went to Disney World
a couple of months ago, I did not go on this ride.
I elected not to, my wife Erin elected not to,
and your girlfriend Lindsay elected not to.
And we decided it would be more fun
to watch Lindsay eat cereal
than to go on this slow moving boat ride.
And I said this on the show and the Facebook group,
among other social media and a lot of people on Twitter
lately have been very upset that I said this.
Living with the Land Bros came out in full force.
He's toxic.
They're in my mentions.
I think some of them are unbuilt Russia pavilion bots.
I agree with that, yeah.
Not cute bots like Smart One.
No, not Smart One.
What cereal was it?
In my head it was Cheerios.
I should have paid more attention.
Lindsay will be home maybe in a little bit
so maybe we can yell at her.
If you went on the boat ride,
you would have remembered that.
Maybe.
You would have learned maybe where grains come from.
Honestly, you would have actually appreciated
her eating cereal more if you had been on the ride
and then seen the cereal.
The cereal possible.
So that's what brings us to this, Jon.
Yeah, there was no question.
I led us to the land pavilion and I was like,
well, let's, okay, two things.
This is where the chocolate, there's a chocolate thing.
And what that was was just a pop-up rack
of Giordelli chocolates,
but they were giving out free squares
so everyone got free squares.
So point in my favor.
Now, wait, you can't count that on the boat ride.
I'd go into the land.
It's all land?
Sure, maybe.
No, no, no, no, no.
That is a separate from the ride.
That's a little bonus.
Oh, okay, now we're going to have to split up a pavilion.
A clean bathroom into this argument?
A clean bathroom on the third floor
is part of the boat ride?
I didn't use the bathroom in the land.
Okay, so we get our free chocolates.
Regardless, I was like, well, I'm going to boat ride.
Is anyone coming with me?
And then no one volunteered.
So I stuck my bottom lip out and looked sad.
And Mike went, all right.
Wait, was I that resistant?
You were like, I think jokingly,
you were like, I guess I'll go with the boy.
There we go.
Yeah, that sounds exactly like him.
I don't remember.
Maybe it's three against one.
Maybe it's three against one and a half.
I don't remember being that against it.
But maybe that is what happened.
I don't remember exactly.
I don't remember being like,
oh, while we were on the ride or anything.
No, you weren't, no.
Because we also, the ride was very bustling.
There was people working at the lab.
There were people in plants.
The lab.
We will talk about that later.
We need to bring you in on this.
Agitating things and signs showing
what parts of the plants growing
were used in the food and wine festival.
Amazing.
Pretty cool.
Signs, wait, what?
So yeah, they'll have signs that say like,
oh, you see these berries growing?
Well, they're in the cobbler outside at the food and wine.
I've always interpreted that as being like,
you know, berries, heard of them.
We also sell them here.
I don't know if they're the same.
I swear some of them were the same.
Some of them were food and wine.
I have pictures of Jason looking longingly
at a couple of the signs where it says like,
this is for the pie outside.
And that has always been, that has never changed in the ride.
Them pitching, now, how true it is, I don't know.
Them pitching that the stuff we create here in the land
goes to restaurants.
Namely, they say, the fish go to the coral reef restaurant
for you to eat.
Weird.
Which my family always went to that restaurant
and I haven't been back in years.
It's the only place I refuse to go.
Really?
Yeah.
Is it just too morbid?
I think it's rude.
Yeah.
I think it's real rude to eat a fish in front of fish.
Yeah, well, this is where,
you're in front of a big tank,
so you're watching fish go by.
It's just, like, you don't have to eat your fish
in front of the fish tank.
You can eat your fish anywhere, so eat it elsewhere.
That's really weird.
Yeah, it would, I think, make me just like astral project
outside of myself and like, wait, what are you doing?
It's too much.
Yeah, it'd feel shame, I think.
Yeah.
There's a big turtle in there, though,
because we ate there like six years ago
and the big turtle was awesome.
I'm not gonna eat the turtle.
So if you're not eating a turtle.
Well, at some point they had snapper soup.
That sticks out if I've ever eaten one.
You have had it?
As a child, I've eaten snapper soup.
We have established that Jason has had,
like the shredder, wants to drink turtle soup.
Have you not had turtle soup?
I've never had it.
Scott?
I have not, no.
Okay.
It's not, I wanna say it's a New Orleans thing,
but I think it's more so dopes from New York City
coming on family vacation to New Orleans
and going to like one fancy restaurant
where they're like, what do you sell turtle soup?
And then you all have to order it.
And then you're like, ooh.
It's like a fish house, like yeah,
a lot of big fish houses still have it.
So you, Jason, and Shred are all of a taste for turtle.
What?
Listen, not a bad crew.
I'm into it.
Sure.
He's cool.
He is cool.
Carly, let's bring you officially into this argument.
Because you.
I feel like I'm at a Thanksgiving dinner
that's going sour very quickly.
I didn't realize what I'd stepped in
when I recommended this as the episode we're doing.
Now I'm very nervous.
Maybe Aunt Carly will calm things down.
Oh my God.
Okay, you, so what, I mean,
you recently have been tweeting about the attraction.
You're.
Yes.
I mean, well, here, let's step outside of the argument.
Okay.
Like someone exiting Coral Reef restaurant.
Because you propose this not even realizing
the depths of it maybe.
Just talk about the attraction.
Why are you fond of this attraction?
So I, the reason I thought this would be a good one
is because I, like you, once did not like this ride.
There we go.
And I have grown to become someone
who is wised up and appreciates what it is.
This is wonderful.
And maybe there's a way that this can happen
while we're recording.
Now, let me tell you the first thing I like about that statement
or besides the hope and the possibility for me,
I like that you validate that it is not insane
to think this is an extremely boring attraction.
You thought this at one point in time.
Oh, big time.
Okay, so listen to that everybody, first of all.
In a way, it is like truly being on a trash barge,
but then it's also, I'm sorry.
No one has ever made me spit water in an episode.
Thank you for that.
I'm so sorry.
That really made me laugh.
But also, like I really sat down and thought about it today
and realized that it has every element of a Disney ride.
If you consider yourself a fan of anything Disney,
you're gonna get a dose of it here.
Granted, it may be like a sleepy time tea dose,
but it's still there.
But you know what words I kept coming across
on like comments on blogs and videos and stuff,
people saying the words peaceful, relaxing, educational.
How many of the Epcot pavilions still stay true
to that original idea of entertainment
that is educational?
The land, for the most part, living with the land
has not changed much.
There's been some changes, for the worse, for the most part.
That's what I'm saying.
I think this was a better ride once.
But that applies to all of Epcot Center.
Yeah, you gotta really hold your loved ones close.
Like the fact that there's really no characters in this
means like we gotta just keep shoving our bodies through
so that it's like people love it, see, see, it's great.
And like keep it pure.
I got a lot of thoughts all at once here, sorry.
I know, we got a lot to get to.
I don't wanna yell over, I wanna be civil.
I'm a moderate, I believe in civility.
We need to get back to when we get along.
When we get lucky, yeah, 50 years ago.
Tip O'Neill.
Your friend Corn Poke always told you about civility.
That's right.
Tip O'Neill.
Me and Tip O'Neill and Corn Poke
were all so civil to each other 50 years ago.
So you talk again, I'll collect my thoughts
and then I'll raise my hand when I wanna speak.
Something's brewing on that side of the room.
I'm worried about that.
This is kind of like.
I'm just a moderate over here.
I'm just a moderate friendly.
I think you can flip.
So I think there's a lot of possibility
on the mic side of the room.
You say there's no characters in this ride.
There are robots in this ride.
Oh, I'm sorry, I mean like this isn't Moana's journey
through nature.
Which I am actually, I am a fan of IP in the rides,
which is like a whole other seven hour segment.
But this.
See, I wasn't sure where you stood.
Oh, a big fan because I love synergy.
It makes sense if you're a child and you go see a movie
and you're like, I love these characters
and you would go to the theme park and see them.
Boom, makes sense.
Yeah, well and sometimes the argument against IP
involves people saying things like,
who likes this character?
No one.
And that person is not a child,
does not have children, does not know children.
And when we're like, all right,
now pull this group of children.
Oh, all 100 of them love insert IP here.
It feels to me just so authentic.
It's just really, it doesn't make sense that it's there.
It seems like the first thing they would have cut
to be like, we're slowly growing tomatoes,
get this out of here.
We could be putting anything else here.
And the fact that it's still there is a small miracle.
I just like that.
I like weird little rides surviving and thriving.
And you know, when I, oh, sorry, no, no, no.
No, I was just gonna say,
I maybe you're gonna save this for later.
I think there's another boat ride
you would call the best boat ride in Epcot
that is also I think a quaint little ride
that you could maybe make an argument like,
oh, this could go away.
Yes, well, I don't know, we can talk about that now.
About frozen ever after?
No, no, no.
Too much.
I, no, you're probably talking about
what I call Mexico boat ride, the Mexico boat ride.
The three caballeros.
You esteem it so much you don't even use
El Rio de Tiempo starring the three caballeros.
Because that's not what it is in my heart.
In my heart, it's Mexico boat ride.
That's whatever, I don't even know what the first name was.
Was it Real Rio del Tiempo, always?
We have a before three caballeros was it?
That is why I don't, it doesn't matter.
It's the Mexico boat ride.
That's just the way.
That's all, that's the umbrella for all of them.
Yes, that is a dopey little ride that certainly could go.
You just put up one construction wall
and nobody ever knew it was there.
But this ride has atmosphere.
This ride has characters.
It has animatronics.
It has fireworks up on the ceiling.
It has projection.
It has TVs and screens and little like physical comedy.
There's things happening in this ride.
It's now called the Grand Fiesta Tour
starring the three caballeros.
A much less evocative name than El Rio de Tiempo.
You also didn't have the esteem to say the right name.
Oh yeah, everyone's missing their esteem today.
Where's everyone's esteem?
I'm growing more and more sad for you
that you didn't even go on this.
Well, I have.
I have gone on it.
How many years ago though?
2009 probably is less than.
You went on Living with the Land.
Yes.
What was the scenario?
Who were you with?
Was it hot out?
Did you enjoy sitting in that time
or did your joints still work?
Oh, this is crucial.
So maybe you have to be like in worse shape
to have for this ride to count.
Yeah, you gotta be a little tired.
Here's the scenario.
And I'm gonna create another villain here apparently
but I think she'll own it.
I went with my wife, Erin, who went on this ride
and said, that was the boringest thing I've ever done.
Don't make me go on that ever again.
I would argue not untrue.
Okay.
But.
Yes.
Well, see it's interesting.
I don't think Lindsay had the hate that Erin had
but I also think Lindsay was like.
I think her blood sugar was dropping
and we had done it last time.
We had been there a year, well no, two years prior.
Yeah.
I mean, she also I think would acknowledge it's boring.
It's interesting when we say boring
because I think this time when we went on Spaceship Earth
and this might just, I might just get all the hate now.
I think after we did Spaceship Earth,
I think I said that's the best boring ride
at Disney World or Upcut Center.
I think so.
I love it so much.
Gosh, is it a sleepy little ride?
Oh, a lot of effects are dated.
Animatronic scenes are great but also they're sleepy.
Very, everything's very sleepy.
Loud clunking.
Oh my God, you hear the gears.
You end up in that second half where nothing's going on.
Yes.
Very out of date interactive videos are going on.
Oh my God, the worst.
The ride just glug, glug, glug, glug.
And that's like half of it.
It's literally like Casey Jr.
You may as well hear Casey Jr. going like,
as your car wheezes backwards down.
But it's such a great.
Maybe I can't, maybe I can't.
Fuck, oh shit, oh no.
I could once.
But no longer.
But what a great boring ride and still one of my favorites.
And it do, it is not as, this living with the land
is not as good of a boring ride.
But it does fall into the genre of boring rides.
It just doesn't have quite as many things going on.
But I have to appreciate it still in the same genre of,
God, I do like how boring this is.
I really can appreciate how aggressively boring
living with the land is.
Which busser ride teaches you about the difference
between aquaponics and hydroponics?
Oh, wait, wait.
Can you explain to me the difference?
Yes, I can.
Hydroponics is where you grow plants
in like a water solvent, so without soil.
Aquaponics is like fish farming
that oftentimes you can incorporate hydroponics into
and create a symbiotic relationship
where the waste from the fish will feed the plants
and the plants will help feed the fish.
See, Scott, that just screams vacation.
Look at that, he learned.
He learned.
This is all good stuff and the people involved
in both kind of ponics, thank you very much.
You're making the world a better place.
This is probably a good point to bring up, Carly,
that you have a history with agriculture.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, I do.
Please.
I went to University of Illinois,
which is literally in a cornfield,
which is not a complete joke
because they had a cornfield on the quad.
It was experimental, very cool.
And because I was not smart,
I had to get in through the back door,
which is what we called it,
and it was through the agriculture school.
So for one semester, I was an agriculture student in college.
And what were, do you remember like course names?
Do you remember like any specific?
Yeah, ACES 101.
I think it was agriculture, consumer, and economics.
A was in aquaponics.
Yeah, aquaponics, all the ponics.
But it was a very, like there was a lot of people
at the school who did corn for their major.
And I proudly am one of them.
What does it mean to do?
What does that mean to you then in your life?
I was only in it for a semester
because the long story short,
I'm not a total hack, I promise,
the journalism school didn't really take freshmen.
It started junior year,
so I couldn't really apply to journalism
unless I was a newspaper editor at the time
and I wasn't, et cetera.
Oh, gotcha.
I transferred halfway in, but we took a class
and we learned rotational crops.
And you learned the basics of farming,
not out in the field,
but in a classroom with a PowerPoint.
Wow.
Hypothetically, if the world goes real shitty
and you had to just take a little patch of land,
you think you could apply what you learned?
Was it enough information for you
to actually be able to grow a couple different things
and have an advanced skill versus me
who would just take seeds and put it in the ground?
I drank a lot in college.
Yeah.
So maybe.
Okay.
But there was a girl who did agriculture journalism
in my journalism lab.
Oh.
So it was like, they were everywhere, all these farm folk.
If you found your old notes, you might be okay.
You couldn't go off a memory.
I didn't do any work till sophomore year.
But anyway, I had a real good time.
You were ignoring your agricultural duties
to drink alcohol?
I think I could, but I would need a few years.
Sure, yeah.
Sure.
I think I could do it.
Do you think that this backstory for you
enhances your appreciation of living with the land?
It definitely does, but it's not the reason I like it.
Okay, sure.
Which we can keep going into,
but I feel like I just threw Erin, my wife, under the bus.
Oh, no, no.
But I also have to bring up,
so then I have to bring up the other thing you told me
via DM about your husband.
I don't wanna put him on the spot, but-
Oh no, what did I say?
You said that he hates this ride.
Oh yeah, he won't go on it.
There we go.
I am not, Erin and I are not these devils on an island
plotting against these wonderful little rides.
Other people have these opinions.
Yeah, but-
People we love.
But he's not a Disney fan.
He's not someone who gathers weekly
to discuss all the happenings.
Sure.
Well, yeah, this is another one of those-
I am, look, as far as living with the land,
I have a big tent and we're all welcome under here
as far as opinions in living with the land,
so yeah, I don't wanna make you feel bad.
You just gotta sit down and have a beer
and look him in the eye.
Yeah. Listen, listen, Jack.
We have more in common than we do.
We have more in common.
Than we don't, I mean.
Well, are you a Pirates of the Caribbean fan?
Of course.
What do you like about that ride?
Robots, lots of them.
What if I were to tell you about a few robots
that were made out of molds originally allocated
for the Western River Expedition?
Sure, I like that.
Yeah.
That was a ride for listeners who don't know,
there was maybe gonna not be a Pirates in Disney World
and there was a thing that was gonna be like Pirates
but in the old West,
and they started building robots for this ride, apparently,
but they did not do the ride
and they instead did Pirates and then Big Thunder Mountain.
So there are, just tell me about these robots.
Are they as fun as the auctioneer
and the dirty foot guy and the prisoners and the dog?
You got a buffalo, you got a prairie dog.
I believe it's a prairie dog.
And you got a dog sitting on farmhouse steps
who looks like the dog.
Yes, he does.
In Pirates of the Caribbean because the rumor,
people say that that dog is modeled after one of Walt's dogs.
Yes, also no women are being oppressed in this attraction.
Yes.
And if you look up to the corner,
you can sometimes see Mickey Mouse
making his rounds at a restaurant.
Yes.
What?
At a restaurant, the restaurant originally called My Turn,
a rotating restaurant that overlooks the first half
of living with land.
Now it's called Garden.
I'm a big revolving restaurant.
What is it?
Garden Grill.
Wait, I have the name, and who sponsors it?
Because the full name made me want to die.
Oh, I don't know who sponsors Garden Grill.
I'd say like...
Garden Grill Restaurant presented by Smuckers.
Smuckers.
And they un-rotated it?
This was a revolving restaurant and now it is not?
Madness.
Is it still revolving?
It did it for a little while.
I asked you guys and you said no.
Did I went to that moment?
I don't know the current status of it.
I guess I was sleepy that day.
I don't remember that either.
My brain no longer works because there's too much Disney news
all the time, but it should be rotating.
If it's not, get it rotating.
And then it's a whole other story.
Hey, don't leave the chicken hanging.
They got a chicken in there too.
They got a chicken.
And the mailbox for the farmhouse says 82.
A little nod to Epcot's opening year.
Ooh, I love that.
Yeah.
And what you're gonna love even more
is that the second story of the farmhouse,
which is not very easy to see from the boat ride itself,
only from the restaurant, is fully themed.
It's fully filled with a globe and a tennis racket.
It's a full bedroom.
This is the standard.
This is the base standard of what I think.
It's a full bedroom.
I am not gonna get too credit.
That attention to detail.
They dressed the room.
The thing that any ride.
It's like Steve Jobs said,
you gotta paint the back of the drawer.
You gotta make the back of the drawers
look as good as the front of the drawer.
I agree.
That's what all rides do.
Well, I think that that's nice
because there's obviously, there's another tool.
I don't know if you get to walk through the robots.
You don't, but there's that extra tour you could take.
Behind the Seeds.
It's called Behind the Seeds.
Which we didn't have enough time.
That was on my.
I will be on Scott's team
because there is not a chance.
I love this ride.
I will never take that tour.
You would not take the Behind the Seeds tour.
Absolutely not.
Everyone tweeted at me because there was a whole debacle
that we'll get into shortly about living with the land
on Twitter that happened this past week.
But everyone's like,
you should definitely take the Behind the Seeds tour.
And I'm like, fuck no.
Don't you say.
That was my big regret of the Florida trip
that I ran out of the sign.
That was on my extended like get to list.
Have you ever seen people on the tour
while you're on the attraction?
Have I seen, I haven't.
Have you ever seen it once or twice?
They are miserable.
Don't you think maybe you're projecting though?
Not at all.
It's all like parents who were like,
oh, this tour is affordable.
We should take it.
And they're teenage kids being like,
all I wanna do is be on Snapchat.
Why am I here?
It is bad.
It is a bad vibe.
Also, you're standing for an hour.
No, thank you.
I'd rather be sitting taking in
the cool greenhouse breeze.
The boat aspect is the only points I will give this.
It is a boat and I like a boat.
Do you get to wear a lab coat while you do the tour?
I believe not, no.
You have to wear your regular clothes.
Jason, do we know?
It seemed like a lot of people in regular clothes.
Do you get to do anything
or do you just get to walk around?
Well, you get to taste some of the things grown
in the greenhouses.
That's what Jason's after.
The berries for the cobbler.
Probably some leafy vegetables.
You get to pick a tilapia out of a tank
and just take a bite.
That and Jason.
Oh, gosh.
Heathcliff.
Jason Heathcliff.
I'll Heathcliff that bad boy.
Ding ding ding ding ding ding.
They rise up and pitch the bones of the fish.
Someone told me they got to feed a fish,
which was cool.
Oh, wow.
And they got to taste a plant.
But that's not what I'm in it for.
I'm in it for being on the boat,
taking in the sights, taking a break.
Because you can't go hard all day.
You need to break it up somehow.
Sure.
But this is where I go back to Mike's point.
Because I think Spaceship Earth is a great example
of the glory of the boring ride.
I'm just going to sit for a while.
If I doze a little bit in this, it's not a problem.
But I think that's as boring as I'll go.
I think my boring threshold.
That ride is going away.
It is changing.
It will no longer be boring.
This is the new boring ride.
I give them crap.
I think they can manage to still make it boring.
That ride's not going to be boring.
They're keeping a lot of the first scene robots.
They're recontextualizing.
Am I wrong?
Yeah, but if they're going in and redoing it.
Yeah.
I've been looking at the water.
It's going to be screaming at me.
They're going to be blasting those fucking songs.
What was that song?
In Spaceship Earth?
Yeah, people have been speculating.
Characters are going in.
So what I understand, they've only
released one piece of artwork for the new Spaceship Earth.
And it is what looks like a huge Moana projection.
And everyone was like, what is this?
Because it looks like it's just going to be like, hi, I'm
Moana.
Join me on a trip across the planet.
And it's going to be all characters.
From what I heard, that artwork is not indicative
of what the full ride will be.
That was just one thing that they showed us.
But it's going to be a brand new redone ride when it's done.
My understanding was that it was mostly the same boring scenes
first.
And then it would be like IP, because it's
the power of storytelling now.
So Michelangelo's Sistine Chapel,
he's storytelling when he's painting.
Yeah, there's like twinkling.
And that ties.
There's a little Tinkerbell sort of almost thing.
Yeah, and that ties into like whatever,
Disney's new live action Rescuers Down Under that'll
come out in 2023.
And they'll be able to project that on the dome.
So that's my understanding of how it's tied together.
But who knows?
I had my one day funeral for it.
And I expect it to barely be enough Spaceship Earth,
but still be.
It's because it would be for someone who shows up to Epcot
and goes, oh, there's a thing in the bowl,
and goes in and gets the Disney ride they would expect.
I see.
Sure.
Yeah.
Is it going to be like it's always a good time playing
the whole ride, like where the Yeti is roaming?
Not Yeti, the you know what I'm talking about.
My husband Aonard that song.
So I don't think we get residuals.
But if we didn't, no, no.
Wow.
Can we do a whole episode?
That city, Carly Rae Jepsen, the good time?
Yeah.
He went to the, I don't think he's
going to want me to talk about this,
but he's never going to listen, so it's fine.
Now I'll know if he listened or not.
He won't.
He went to the video shoot, and I
was mad because he didn't let me go.
And Carly Rae Jepsen was there.
Oh my gosh.
Huge Carly Rae Jepsen fan.
Same.
Did you talk to, did you meet her?
No, because I wasn't allowed to go.
Imagine if Erin.
Oh, you weren't allowed to go.
Imagine if Erin spent her work day
going to hang out with CRJ, and you were stuck at home.
Oh my god.
Yes, the jealousy that would be.
Then we would not be on the same page.
But I mean, for my sake, I would love
that to be like, you know this song every time
I go on Spaceship Earth.
Yeah, well, I mean, it sounds like maybe it'll happen.
But that's not a Disney song.
I mean, once that's.
It's in the parade, though.
Yeah, it's.
Oh, do they use it in the parade?
No, they use.
Or it's in Wreck-It Ralph.
That one's in Wreck-It Ralph.
And then this one.
It's remixed for the parade.
Can we do this again?
Oh, that.
Uh-oh.
Oh, that's the other All City song that's in the parade.
OK, OK, I gotcha.
I'm mixing up my All City.
I had a question in here somewhere.
Oh, I know.
OK, so you're pro-IP, but it sounds
like maybe you aren't into what they're
doing in Spaceship Earth.
So I've been doing this for half a decade now,
which is terrifying, because it feels like it's been five
minutes, and I still know nothing.
But I generally, I don't allow myself
to feel nostalgia, because my job is writing
about things that are new.
So it's backwards if I am sad.
It's going to be better if you're excited about what
you're going to see.
Or, but I can't be against new things,
because then I'd have no job.
Right, sure.
Well, if she doesn't want to see the new things,
we want to find her to see the new things.
So I have to approach it all with an open mind.
But I had a few things, and I was like,
these are my untouchables.
And one of them was Spaceship Earth.
OK.
So I've said my piece, and now I've
transferred my love of that attraction
over to living with the land.
So that now is the bastion of original Epcot.
To me, that it has it all.
It has flowing water through rocks.
It has an animatronic dog.
It has a little part of the beginning
that feels like an old school Navi River journey.
Yes.
Yeah.
It has fruits and vegetables.
It has herbs hanging from a thing that
looks like a dry cleaning rack.
It has everything.
No, I will say, OK.
I will admit, I think the hydroponics are fascinating.
What about intercropping?
It was starting to be nice about something,
and then you swatted me down with a duller word.
No.
Very interesting.
They demonstrate by growing coconut and cocoa together,
around each other, so you can minimize water and soil usage.
Go ahead.
Jason, while you were maybe correct,
I did not appreciate the tone and the way
in which you cut Scott off there.
I just want to say that.
There we go.
Civilty.
If you're correct, that doesn't matter to me.
I just think you should be a little more kind and a little
more polite.
I think you just said intercropping
to me on National Podcast.
You just said intercropping.
Why don't you go run for something?
All right, Scott, as you were saying.
OK.
What was I saying?
I like that there's animatronics.
I'm really happy there's animatronics.
I think we're overrating these animatronics a little bit.
I think these are the supporting cast
animatronics on a pirate's type experience.
The buffalo's nodding his head.
The chicken blinks.
Why am I excited about these animatronics?
I was just going to say, in defense of these animatronics,
I do think a showy groundhog or a showy buffalo or something
might take it away.
You're right that these are not as distinct when
it comes to animatronics.
You're not getting a very specific weird faced
pirate or a country bear.
But I think if you're trying to really nail
what they're trying to nail in this ride, they have to be subtle.
Which is what are they trying to nail?
They're trying to ultimate realism.
An animatronic as boring as a real animal.
Yes.
So I think that they weren't going to make this like,
it's not going to be like the end of Splash Mountain with an animal review.
No.
And you know what?
Again, let me go back to the Mexico boat ride.
This is kind of boring.
I find delightful.
And I'm not even just talking.
I like the three Caballeros version.
I really liked before the they had and all that.
I like them both.
I think I liked the 10% more.
And I liked that, what is this?
Why is there nothing for a while and then just
a screen with cliff divers?
I think that now that one I do see, I just I don't know.
Maybe that one just spoke to me more.
I think there's more, you know, I think there's more mood.
I don't get any mood from living.
Well, now this might be the spot to talk about some of the changes that were made
because and I'm going to shout out Martin's vids
who does very in intense recreations of old.
Sometimes the only I watched a full ride through of listen to the land.
I was shocked at how thorough it was.
And the first few scenes were a little more ethereal and dreamlike.
Yes, yes.
I'm thinking, yes.
Plants light, light pulsing through plants while that kind of
singer, songwriter, country song.
You're not going to get a disagreement from me.
I think all the way down to the lobby itself of the land pavilion,
which if you saw any of these videos, there were like cool,
like light up kind of umbrella things in the land.
These were to name to name check a nepcot restaurant.
These were electric umbrellas.
The land looked cool as shit in 1980s.
I cannot disagree that this adds so much to this.
I will say also, I believe that the state of the land in the area
inside when you walk into the pavilion hurts everything inside
by the weird shopping like shitty shopping mall feeling of it now.
I completely agree with you.
And I think that hurts my it's it's like the pre it's like taking out a cool
pre show and even if the ride doesn't change without the cool pre show,
I'm not as on board.
I think the land was cool as hell.
And now it is like it's like a supermarket.
Yes, it is so boring.
It does. I do believe that hurts.
Soren and Epcot. Yeah.
Soren is back there.
It does not nearly have the cool facade we have out here.
Yes. And I like for whatever reason, psychologically, I don't really
feel it is as good as the one here, even though the exact same right.
Well, because it doesn't make it's it's called the land pavilion.
And that rides about sky.
So that's true.
But you're flying over the land.
You're seeing the land, I suppose, except when you're over the water.
I think the bigger hindrance to living with the land of all the changes
is removing the cast member narrators.
Yes. There used to be guides until 2006.
Disagree. Narrating.
You think the recording is fun.
The last time I went out living with the land, I went on with
I think it was two or three of my friends.
And because there's no one ever on the ride, you can talk the whole time.
So it's like going to a meal or going to a bar,
except you're just watching something and you're on a boat and it's chill
and you can gab. And it was amazing.
I'd like to respond. I'd like a 45 to respond.
Yes, Jason. Jason, 45 seconds on the clock.
I will cut you off when it's done.
Please don't go over. I will take that out of your time later.
OK. A few years ago, I went on when it was narration
and there was a lot of people on and
the lack of a cast member in the boat made people think they could
talk the whole time at full volume in many different languages.
It was impressive.
Well, not but demonstration, not necessarily about the
not the same person speaking many languages, not the same person.
Not necessarily at that same volume.
If you are trying to listen to the narration and maybe they were translating
it in real time, which would be very impressive.
Jason's like, I'm trying to listen to the land here.
I can't hear the land. Yeah.
What is it saying?
I think the presence of a guide kind of people.
Well, it focuses your attention, certainly a little.
I so here's what I'm discovering is that some of the arguments here
acknowledge the boringness and that is an asset.
I agree. Not a bug.
Is that the phrase? Yes.
It's a feature, not a feature.
Not OK. OK.
This is helping me get around this whole thing.
Like that that kind of argument, I understand the charm of the doll.
Because if you're trying to tell me this is actually an extremely exciting ride
and I'm missing that somehow, then I don't know how to be in your brain.
This doll is being part of the argument.
It's a bit dull until you get to the greenhouse portion.
That's where the magic happens.
OK. OK. Because you're seeing things at various stages of growth.
And sometimes you are seeing some gourds that are bigger than you ever seen.
Gourds.
Gourds. Have you, Scott Head, have you considered gourd size?
Have you considered the type of gourds?
Well, when you say gourd size, I think of state and county fairs.
Where you can see gourds that are way bigger than these gourds.
Can you see them shaped like Mickey Mouse?
I do like that.
I will I will I will give you a point.
That's not how debates work, but I will donate a point to you.
I'd like to ask a question to each member of the party in the room here.
What is the largest gourd you've ever seen?
Like, just has it been something truly insane?
I'm trying to I went to a pumpkin patch once and I feel like I saw one that was like
I'm trying to think maybe as big as the like the outline, the fireplace right here,
which is probably like 200 pound, 250 like a pumpkin that size.
Yeah. Yeah. I think I've seen about that.
OK. OK. 250, we think.
Maybe any bigger gourds.
No, no big memories tied to gourds or pumpkin.
Oh, I saw I where was I?
I was at I think I went went to the Disneyland and there was a big, big gourd.
That was he was also shaped like Mickey.
He was right in the front of the park.
I have seen the huge and all it was his face and the ears and his face was carved out.
It out of it. Yeah.
So I think it'd be that they have to grow that every year.
Why they do it every year and they grow a new one.
Yeah, that's right.
So they have to probably like have the next one ready to go November 1st.
The same turkey leg steroids they use for the emus for the emus.
They inject emu DNA.
They work an emu out really hard.
They give it steroids and HGH
and then they cut the legs off and they serve it to you and call it a turkey.
And Walt's frozen head is in the haunted mansion.
That's right. And they've also one of the bus.
If you cracked open one of the bus, that would be you'd see Walt.
And it's preserved.
They've shot it with steroids.
They shot it with HGH and he's ready to go.
And they solve his cancer, I guess.
Tell me more about the screen now.
So what else am I looking for in the next?
Next time I go, what am I?
Because I'll go.
Well, I can't tell you what's in season right now because I haven't been in a few weeks.
What do we think is the best season in living in the land?
Well, because it's a greenhouse year round, things are popping.
Yeah, they can just stick in the cycle things in and out.
Does anyone have a seasonal plant in their head?
I mean the pumpkin.
How about a Guinness World Record plant?
OK.
The tomato tree that produced 32,000 tomatoes in a 16 month period.
Yeah, but bulk amount, that's a size I think.
What, do you hate tomatoes?
Come on.
I certainly don't, but I read that stat.
I want to, it's like the snake on the Indiana Jones ride.
I want to see a big snake.
I don't understand a bunch of little snakes.
You want that the tomato that Bart grew or who grew it?
T'Lisa grew it?
No, no, no, no.
When they threw it, it's Skinner's butt.
T'Lisa grew it is like a world hunger solving tactic.
And then Bart threw it at Skinner's butt.
That's right.
I do love seeing the eggplants.
What's that?
I like the eggplants.
That sounds pretty nice.
That's a highlight.
You see a big row of eggplants?
That's kind of cool.
All right.
Vertical plants, the plants that are growing with the exposed roots
in the air.
Oh, yeah.
That's very impressive.
See, there's a lot of, it's like what you want from a museum,
except you don't have to stand.
And there's the added novelty of a boat ride.
Let me propose this.
I think that if this were in a museum, I would be obsessed with it.
I would probably be telling you guys, we have to do an episode about this
boat ride in a museum.
So if I'm judging it by museum standards, it's amazing.
If I'm judging it by theme park standards, it's very boring to me.
Is there a part of it that you can say-
I just made you very sad with this.
I'm trying to find the pictures of Jason and I on the ride.
After this episode, there will be a petition to get me removed from the podcast.
We will see this.
Did you go on Carousel of Progress when you were there?
Yes.
Did you enjoy that?
There is no reason why you shouldn't love this ride if you liked that.
Disagree.
Robots.
So many robots, a depiction of a bizarre 1994 future that we're already past.
But this whole ride is showing you truly what we're going to do about food
when there's too many people running amok around the earth.
Yes.
Er.
This is the actual version of the final scene of Carousel of Progress.
How many rides?
It's not going to be some psycho oven.
No, the final scene of Carousel of Progress.
Yeah, it's ovens going amok and it's grandma playing video games.
Yeah, but we're going to be eating pills for meals unless the stuff they're working out in that lab happens.
Well, I'm not against what they're doing in the lab.
I'm very happy with what they're doing in the lab.
I just don't know if I need to be going into the lab.
I mean, how many-
I don't want to bother them.
They're going to get more work done if I don't go in there.
How many rides started with such a noble purpose?
With a major educational institute consulting, with the US Department of Agriculture working hand in hand
to grow fruits and vegetables used around the corner at Garden Grill and Sunshine Seasons.
People complain about theme parks being a simulation or fake or phony.
This is reality. This is real.
This is the earth.
I have the photos here in front of me of Jason and I on the boat ride.
Here's just a few of the things.
Yes, please.
Here's one that says pineapple.
And Jason's looking at it.
Oh, wow.
Yeah, pineapple.
And it's used on the Kluah Kluah Kluah pork and slider.
But I don't know if that means that pineapple or pineapple.
It's a good question.
Because I know that I once ordered a salad the same day that I dragged my husband on this ride at dinner at Flying Fish.
And it was before they redid Flying Fish.
So I don't know if they have the same produce from there anymore.
But he's like, you're going to buy this twenty dollar salad.
Like he was so pissed that I got this like dumb leafy green salad just because it was those special greens.
It's featured on the ride.
But it was like they were shouting it from the rooftops that it was a greenhouse salad.
Interesting. You're probably right that since they're bulk ordering all that food,
it just like it's coming from somewhere else and it's cheaper and not as good quality as what they grow in there.
But they put like, for instance, this photo, it says banana and it says, oh, you know what?
I think I cracked it. It's sponsored by Chiquita.
I bet they have a banana and pineapple monopoly throughout the resort.
And so they're highlighting their goods.
Oh, interesting, because this one is used on the banana almond sundae at the it's the shimmering sips Epcot International Food and Wine Festival.
And you zoom into that sign, you zoom past Jason, who is looking observantly.
As if to take mental notes.
I was in deep consideration and thought because I went through my photos just now.
It's like, oh, I have no photos of this.
I just have photos of the just a reminder for us to talk about at some point, the insane signs that ring pop century.
We forgot to do something.
Oh, sure. Yes.
And a lot of Skyliner footage.
Are you guys going to put these online somewhere?
Is this just people listening to us?
No, no, no.
We'll post those.
Listen to the pics.
Here's one. I think this is coffee.
They're growing coffee.
And then it's they write the doughnut box under it.
Fresh yeast doughnut with coffee, sugar and chocolate espresso beans served with coffee.
Sounds great.
I want to I want to hear more about your husband.
Does he does he actually dislike all of that?
Where do you actually calibrate his theme park?
He wants to go and do only the things that he wants to do, which is basically what he would call the good rides, which are thrill rides.
And then he wants to leave, which I respect.
What's just in it for like the hits?
Sure. And then it's like, it's too hot and then leaves.
Sure. What's the most boring ride he likes?
Oh.
Like pirates, for instance.
He won't go on pirates.
Really? Oh, interesting.
OK. And why is that?
Because it's too long, too slow.
He's in for the hits.
And he doesn't consider pirates a hit?
No, because he just wants to go on a roller coaster.
Loves a space mountain.
OK. We'll do a big thunder.
We'll usually do Haunted Mansion because I ask him to.
If he's annoying me, I will take him on.
It's a small world.
But like I made it.
We were in Shanghai a few weeks ago and I made him go on Peter Pan there because their Peter Pan is exceptional.
Oh, because they made it like after 2010.
Like, I don't know when they designed it, but it came out in 2015, 2017.
What year is it now?
2020. 2016.
2016. That park opened in 2016.
Yeah, 2016.
And so it's Peter Pan, but with new technology and it's beautiful.
And I kept being like, isn't this amazing?
And he was like, it's Peter Pan.
So. Interesting.
OK. OK.
But just because he won't go on this doesn't mean he's right.
Sure.
I think it really comes down to, you know, you want to see something special.
Shibuya Crossing is special.
A sunset is special.
Yes.
Neither one is better or worse than the other.
Just different.
Sure.
So, yes, it's slow.
Yes, my dad falls asleep on it every time, but still, it's a nice break.
It's a nice time to catch up and talk at a moderate tone or people don't fully hear what you're saying.
So you don't disrupt their journey.
It's just nice.
It's cold, but you're still kind of outdoors.
It's very moody at night.
No, here we go.
Oh, interesting.
I've never done it at night.
Moody.
I think I upset you the most by saying that I don't think there's any vibe to this ride.
I think there's no.
Yes.
So you're very.
OK.
That adds to it, you think?
Because that pavilion, like you said, it feels like a mall that hasn't announced its closing yet.
You know, where like some of the main stores aren't there, but like people are still getting paid.
They work there.
How are they going to fill the Mervins?
Now, that's interesting to me because that's one of Scott's favorite places to be.
Yes.
But I don't like really beige, styleless malls, which is what I think the current colors and architecture of the land.
I, as I said, loved the land for the first 10 years or so.
And I think it's like I think it's deeply bland these days.
Living with the bland.
I can't be living with the bland.
Let's touch on something we haven't talked about yet.
The original ideas for the land, which was going to be these giant biomes, these giant greenhouse crystal things.
This is good.
And that quickly got scaled back from the blue sky.
But the ride was originally pitched as a suspended dark ride called Blueprints of Nature.
Okay.
That was.
I've never heard any of this.
This is news to me.
Okay.
Traveling underground to a carousel theater pre-show, guests would be introduced to the attractions host, the Land Keeper.
The land.
We've heard of the Land Keeper.
We haven't discussed him in a while, I feel like.
Oh, boy.
I don't know if I believed in fate until this moment.
From there, the Land Keeper would take guests on a hot air balloon trip through the four seasons and a series of simulated biomes located in greenhouses at the front of the pavilion.
This was scaled back, the craft came aboard as a sponsor and it became a boat ride.
A lot of these ideas were rolled over into Journey, into Imagination.
Wow.
He became the.
We looked at some pictures.
I think when we talked about Land Keeper, which feels like it might have been two years ago already.
I forgot.
Yeah, I forgot and relearned Land Keeper.
He looked like this.
Whoa, like a Colonel Sanders.
Like a rainbow.
I can't see that far, but it just looks like a Flamin' Hot Cheeto in a rainbow sash.
Like a ripped orange.
He's quite far from me.
Yeah.
Or no, Rip Taylor.
He looks a little bit like Rip Taylor.
Oh, I was looking at the thing next to him.
There was a red blob.
Well, that was him.
That was a closer shot of him.
So he is almost he has a very Captain EO like shirt.
Yeah.
Yes.
He has like a rainbow stripe across a white.
A little pocket.
He looks.
He's very much you could see like they were going for Dreamfinder relation.
He's like some weird link between EO and Dreamfinder.
Yes.
Wow.
Can.
OK.
Does any.
Can.
Will anyone say that living with the land is better than that would have been?
Of course.
Yeah.
I couldn't possibly.
I'm very happy.
Jason.
I'm very happy with it.
Well, I mean, this is a problem we run into on the show a lot is does the blue sky version
a place you could never been?
Is that realistic to hold that standard?
Hold hold actual things that do exist to that standard?
Well, I will never ride the Knights and White Satin ride.
There's no she's a little mermaid ride.
We've seen the better version of the DVD of Little Mermaid, what the cooler version
would be than the one we have.
But is it fair of us to judge the new one based on the seemingly ride that would be better?
Yeah, it's got the land keeper.
It's better.
I unfortunately have to agree with Scott.
It's got this guy with a rainbow that's coming out of his top hat.
And how is that going to not be better?
We're an accountant for the rainbow.
Yeah.
I mean, the land keeper, unfortunately, yes, puts it over the top.
Honestly, like the ride itself sounds more exciting, more cool or whatever.
But as long as there's just a white haired old man.
Why can't they just remove this guy to the boat ride?
Because that seems like a crappy Charlie and the Chocolate Factory where instead of candy
you get grass, like it's just pointless.
And also that's you say crappy.
I am a little I do have a few questions about the land because one, if you're it's the land
is dirt and greenery and that's an all white suit.
You've got to be a little crazy.
And also, like, you know, it looked like he's in perfect health.
And you if you want to push what you give with the land, the bounty the land gives you
to sustain you, I don't know if this guy is bulbous.
Skyseeds, you know, certainly true.
I mean, maybe though he you know, maybe, yes, he is.
He's got like a sip and savor pass to one of these festivals.
He seems like he's mostly interested in what they're doing with the land and like Islay
or Dublin. But yes, I look, I hear what you're saying.
But also we like, you know, I I'll just speak for myself.
I really like see I like the rides being connected with characters.
If we have we open up the the Finder world, you know, we opened up the keeper world.
On our our downtown Disney ordeal.
This is the Finder world.
Multiple finders everywhere.
And though he's a keeper, you classify him as a finder.
Yes, clearly a cousin of the dream finder.
Yes. That's what I'm basically. Yes, I'm saying so keepers can be finders.
Keepers can be finders.
I want everyone to repeat that with us who are listening in your car.
If you're alone right now, keepers can be finders.
Yes. Like you guys said it.
Now, the the thing, though, if they had built the ride like this,
they may have pegged it for demolition quicker.
But you would have gotten more out of date.
It's more it's more out of date quicker, more complicated to run.
You're saying they would have bulldozed the landkeeper by now.
The landkeeper by now by making it a more practical functioning.
He would have been replaced.
He would have been replaced by a toilet.
Like a dream finder was on Journey.
Well, it's the little toaster, the brave little toaster and his new friend, the toilet.
The brave little toilet.
They would have added to add IP to the right.
They would have added the brave little toaster.
Hey, it's me.
What if instead of toast, I put a stink bug in me?
Yeah, I mean, toilet on the ceiling.
They got the toilet.
We're talking about the redo of Figment's ride, which is just a travesty.
Yeah, which I assume you agree with us on that.
Yeah. Yeah. OK.
That final room scares me every time.
It is scary. Yeah.
I'm a grown woman. I know it's coming every time.
The big buzz thing that what is it?
It's like a big horn.
Like walls drop. Yeah.
Yeah. Loud.
It scares the shit out of me.
It's really unpleasant.
It's like horror nights when you can see.
Yeah. Horror nights specifically, when you see something coming and you go,
oh, there's a person right there.
They're going to scare me.
And then they have the sound and light cue, which you cannot help but be scared by that.
So it's an extra thing that even if you know it's coming,
it's not it's still your body's going to have a visceral reaction to it.
Yeah. Scariest ride in Disney World.
I have a thought while we're talking about this ride.
OK, we have just said a ride that you would almost certainly list as lesser than living with the land.
What other rides at Epcot Center would you put or attractions?
Well, I'll open it up.
Would you say are lesser?
The what? What does living with the land outrank all of them?
Come on.
I think at this point in my life, I think you agree.
Mission space, mission space, mission space for it all.
It goes on. I would rather know.
No, no, no. We're saying mission spaces.
We're listing what's worse.
Wait, I'm saying what is worse than living with the land.
Mission space. Yes.
Yeah. 100 percent. Mission space.
Test track at this point. Not kept up, not maintained.
Feels awful.
Like my car will break for me at this point if I don't do it.
I don't need to be driving a fake car to see if it can resist wind.
We all slammed into our seatbelts while we were still next to the ride operator.
Something went wrong. Like that was the start of I haven't.
I haven't done it lately and I haven't gotten to do it with the Tron.
Eskvibe. That is not what it was.
Mike, you've done your as the moderate.
I'm thinking here. I don't want to declare both of them equal.
I am not denying that Test Track has its issues and maybe maybe belongs
in the scrap heap at this point.
Maybe that's controversial. Like, it sounds like it's not.
I mean, we didn't get Jason went on on the trip, but we didn't go on it.
I had gone on. I've been on it a couple of times.
I will say these are my personal opinions and not those of my employer,
which is myself, but enjoy whatever they would.
Yes, this is not between podcast guest Carly Wiesel and writer journalist.
I'm like, oh, that story I just wrote of all the rides ranked
that does not line up with this.
That is like those aren't your opinions as much.
I understand for many reasons, certain rides are considered
and will be deemed better than others.
But according to me for my own life and how I spend my time. Sure.
I'm going on the boat ride through the greenhouse.
Do you remember from your list in like this public facing recommend
recommendations list that is less your personal opinions?
Do you remember what you ranked lower than living with land?
I actually I redid it like a month ago.
I'll look it up to the glutton for punishment.
Because I think it's post this woman's address.
Oh, it's not your phone number.
It was I got some real interesting screenshots from friends
who saw it being shared on the Internet.
Nice. That's probably all.
But if I'm going to Epcot these days, which is usually alone
or with my family or with some friends, it's not like my once
in a lifetime trip, like I'm spending my time there.
I'm hanging out.
I'm I mean, before I would really only go on Spaceship Earth.
That was the one I had to go on.
And now that I've kind of said goodbye to that.
Living with the land is my jam.
Do we have an official like goes down for refurbishment?
I don't believe so.
I don't think they've announced it.
In my brain, it's in hospice.
And it's kind of like if I get to see him again, great.
It feels like a masculine.
Is that going to be they're going to have it down for the 50th?
I believe so. Right.
Well, I would say yes, but that's only things I've heard from the rumor mill.
So I can't really trust it.
TBD. OK.
Now, do you is there any truth to that?
And I know there is.
But when will Galaxy's Edge get converted to be based on the live action?
Latin. Oh, didn't that happen last week?
I think. Oh, did I miss it? Oh, yeah.
It's already. Wow.
Yeah, we went on Rise of Jafar's Gang.
That was the ride.
I was about to make a joke.
It really get me in trouble.
Oh, oh, man. It's a Latin.
OK, I'm looking for the ranking.
Oh, interesting.
Forty nine grand fiesta tour.
Haven't seen living with the land yet.
Wonder what I ranked it.
Oh, sad. Oh, no.
A real solid 44. OK.
Is the only up got ride grand fiesta tour?
43 just above it.
A little bit better.
I said Primeval World because it is a coaster.
OK. So it has to be tomato ride.
Are you not then a fan of grand fiesta tour?
I think it's fine.
I really wish that you could drink a margarita on it.
I think that would be a game changer.
I think if it was like the history of tequila or something,
it would be a hit.
And I would like to see plants and manufacturing.
Yeah. Now or now or in my.
OK, let's replace the entrances.
You put living with the land in the Mexico Pavilion.
You get that great the Mexico Pavilion.
Amazing. Oh, my God.
One of the greatest things you get, as you're saying, some margaritas.
You can look at cool little trinkets and stuff.
I love it. We all love it.
If living with the land was put in there,
I think the thing goes up a letter grade.
Does that imply that the beginning of the ride goes through past the restaurant?
Yes.
Then yes, because that I think is a big reason to like grand fiesta tour more
because it's atmosphere.
That room is cool.
That's like Blue Bayou.
That's like beginning of pirates.
Blue Bayou?
Living with the land literally goes under a restaurant.
Under though.
It isn't quite as foreign to see.
It doesn't quite have the the ambiance.
That's what it is.
Not you're not in a swamp.
You're not in a cinematic.
See, grand fiesta tour is literally downstreaming the ambiance of the rest of the pavilion
and just riding it through.
And then you're like, wait, why am I on this?
This ride stinks.
Living with the land, you like start, you know, you start with a bunch of what's happening here.
Why is there flowing water across rocks?
Like it's beautiful.
And then all of a sudden you're like, whoa, I'm outside.
Am I know it's a greenhouse.
What's a greenhouse?
Let me learn.
I think maybe this is where just the personal.
I think I just don't feel those feelings.
I don't think I like I'm not swept up in the mood.
University of Arizona horticultural expert Dr. Carl Hodges talk about his his work.
How is their program?
I didn't apply there.
Dr. Hodges.
Dr. Augustine.
He seemed very intelligent.
I believe who who is the singer in in the same Epcot special, which I only saw the clip of.
I didn't see his introduction, but someone he sits on on riding the boat ride,
strumming a guitar, singing this land is your land.
Yikes.
Going through the ride.
Here we go.
Here's let me let me direct it a little more
because I sense that this is a room that is not 100% on frozen ever after.
Not me.
I truly love frozen ever after.
Carla.
I really do.
I'm weary to say this publicly.
You don't have to.
But I hate it.
Hate it.
Jason.
That's fine.
I'm with Mike.
I love it.
And I love Maelstrom.
Now I Maelstrom way better to me.
I wish there was still Maelstrom, but.
Sure.
I do.
I I do think they did.
They did a good job.
It's good robots.
It's that that good robots.
Every scene is good.
Every scene has a little something that I like.
Rock monster thing.
I don't want to get you in trouble.
Say what you're willing to say.
I mean, I don't want to turn this into a frozen ever after.
Sure.
We can do that at a different episode.
But it won one of the most painful rides at Walt Disney World.
That shift when you get to Elsa where you go, it's so painful.
Really?
Extremely painful.
On like knees or back?
Back.
It just jolts you to the side.
Then when you're going backwards as she's singing, you're going through
a tunnel that is completely unthemed.
There is no excuse for a Walt Disney World attraction having a stretch of a ride that
is just black nothing.
It is a long black tunnel.
Like put up.
We're seeing magic.
And then it stops and it goes shh and they put some smoke in and then it's just black.
It doesn't make any sense.
I've never even noticed that.
You won't not notice it now.
Okay.
It infuriates me.
Also, the contouring of the projection, their face is projected on, but just you guys don't
know contouring.
It's weird.
I know what you're talking about.
I get what you're saying.
Like barely their neck and then you're like, that's not them.
And they're like, it's the most advanced animatronic ever.
And you're like, she can move a finger.
Like what?
I don't care.
I'm not impressed.
They've already the footage they have shown of like the bell animatronic or the bell in
the beat like that are coming.
It's like, well, this already looks rough.
Like this already looks rough compared to this great.
I went on it like two days after it opened.
It looked bad.
The solution of the shiny monitor faces that Ann and Elsa have is a little strange.
I feel like I forget which scene is bad.
I mean, I have to rewatch it.
There is one scene that looks extra weird.
The very last one to me.
Maybe it's the last one that looks really like in Haunted Mansion, but except there's
two of them and it's creepier.
It's bad.
That's why I'm like living with the land really might be my favorite attraction.
Also, and I know Maelstrom is insane.
Like, yeah, I get it.
Kids nowadays don't like mouse because it was insane.
But you know what I think is more interesting that frozen is the culture and people of Norway.
And call me a square.
But I guess I'm just old fashioned.
I guess I'm just old fashioned.
Mm hmm.
I think we would call you old fashioned.
That podcast that you were on, Tomorrow Society.
Yeah.
I think it was on that.
I listened to a guy who worked on the Maelstrom and we'll do a Maelstrom episode.
I'm dying to do that.
Yeah.
Like he had a guy on who worked on that ride who explained that it is exactly what you
think.
It was fun and validating to hear this.
That there was a version that they did that was like all trolls and scary stuff.
And then so he said, no, no, no, they're not going to like that.
Do all Vikings.
And then they presented it to the Norway people and they were like, no, no, no, we are about
oil barracks.
And then Marty Sklar says, okay, you have to figure out how to make something out of all this
that makes everybody happy.
And that's why that ride is this bizarre mix of all of that.
Which I love.
I think that it's insane.
It's kind of insane.
I love.
I think that's a great necessity as a mother of invention.
And frozen ever after is a little more like Apollo 13.
Like, all right, they got this.
We need to make this fit into this.
And we got these two that we got.
This is what they have in their ship.
Do you think frozen ever after is worse than the Little Mermaid ride?
Oh, God.
I think expectations.
Oh, man.
I have the same issue with both.
Okay.
All right.
A wonderfully done sidekick, but terribly replicated lead character.
Yeah.
But I think they got Ariel better than Enel.
I'm going to have to say Ariel wins because you're in a little shell.
Even if her face scares the shit out of me.
Plus, Buddy Hackett, at least to sound alike.
Points for Buddy Hackett in a ride.
Buddy Hackett sound alike.
I call me old fashioned.
You enjoy the humor of a Buddy Hackett type.
I love a Buddy Hackett.
Shubuppy.
Hackett in.
His performance of Shubuppy terrific.
If Hackett was doing all of Gadd's roles.
Oh, my God.
If Hackett was LaFou.
Oh.
If we could get a Hackett.
If we could get, you know how they bring celebrities back for commercials.
Jimmy Stewart learned a great voice actor in his last role, Five Oaks Goes West.
Oh, yeah.
He's a sheriff dog.
There was actually a couple of minutes ago when you were delivering a line and I said,
he sounds like Jimmy Stewart.
Your voice is slowly turning into Jimmy Stewart.
I do want to say for the record before everyone yells at me on the internet
that I don't really go on the aerial ride, but I do go on Frozen Ever After
because every time my friend Todd Martens, who is a wonderful Disney reporter,
he loves Frozen and he loves that ride.
And we have gotten into very public fights about this at like one in the morning.
And everyone's like, you guys got to calm down because I hate it and he loves it.
And so I keep going on it to try to learn.
I want to know why he loves it so much and I can't get there.
So if you see me on Frozen Ever After, I'm not a hypocrite.
I promise I'm truly just trying to do right by Todd and learn.
You swear you're not having fun.
Well, I try.
I try.
It's still Living with the Land.
This is what I need to do clearly with Living with the Land, although I won't
because it's far away.
I will try.
I should try.
I'm going to say this, guys.
I didn't like it when I was a kid either.
My mom didn't like this ride.
I think I might just be like this is a Gardner family genetics.
I don't have a memory of being a kid.
I don't actually have any.
I don't have a memory of being a kid in general.
No, no, please.
It's my whole life.
I don't really have strong memories of it as a child.
I just remember going on it when I went back at 18 or something or not 18.
I don't think it's intended for you to remember it.
I guess that is probably right.
It's just the thing you do.
Kind of like how you have to drink water to survive.
You don't really like doing it, but it breaks up the day and you do it to make
the things that taste good taste better and compare.
Yeah, you were supposed to remember to respect the land.
That's what you remember.
That argument says that things are better than this.
But you got to keep in mind of like 2020 framing.
You're at Disney World.
You've made it.
You either showed up and ruined your trip by not planning anything or you are an adult
who very likely woke up at four in the morning to try to get a fast pass and didn't get the
one you wanted.
You are entering this trip with a lot of baggage and a lot of stress and you're like,
oh, soren, oh, I didn't get the fast pass, but it's an 85 minute wait.
I guess we'll do it.
There's some dumb game in the queue that we can like point out city capitals.
Sure.
So then you go through this and you walk way too far to get to the entrance of soren.
Just like an unbelievable length of space where there's a one direction escalator and
a staircase and you're like, which one do I go on?
You finally get to soren.
You wait in line and then you're like, that was cool.
And then you got out of there and then you go to the very busy but very large bathroom.
And then you're like, well, what do we do now?
It's not time for lunch yet.
And next to you is magically a ride that has almost no weight where you can sit and it's
indoors and you can avoid the rain or avoid the heat, which one of the other is always happening.
And you can just sit after waiting and toughing things out.
You can just board it and enjoy.
And I think that's the magic.
I'm sorry.
What you're describing is exactly how I feel about Mexico boat ride.
It was a horrible, horrible storm and we needed somewhere to sit and every single bench was taken.
And then I thought there's one place with a bench.
It is this ride.
I will get on the bench on the ride and the sitting was complete and the resting was
completely the appeal.
So I get it.
I get that makes total sense to me.
And that is a facet.
So I can admit that.
I think the greenhouse and the show, uh, show scenes should be swapped.
I don't, I think the greenhouse should start the ride.
I think the animatronics should be second.
It's an interesting idea.
I also think, I think this would change the perception of the ride because it's such a dry
learning thing of all of a sudden in the middle of a real life.
Oh, we're in the real life.
But wait a minute.
Now we're not.
Here come the animatronics.
Here comes the mood.
Here comes the great sandstorms showing us.
I think that gives the also gives the ride a different vibe.
I would advocate now that they don't have it a very impressive entrance way.
They just advocating.
They flip it somehow.
You don't think all those quotes from children about the land, they solicited 800 quotes
about, uh, they pick 10, a less exciting way to finish the ride.
Oh, I met in the queue.
I met.
Oh, I see.
I see.
Yeah.
Yeah, that could certainly be plus.
They're not going to do that.
That would be impossible.
You may as well just trash it, but that's my feeling.
I'm saying like, this is all I have left.
They can't.
What could they like?
Here's what could they do?
Well, they did.
They've plused up August of 2019.
Here we go.
They redid the footage and I think they may have replaced the screen.
I do not remember inside the ride.
And I know because I went on with a friend who was writing for a website at the time.
That's like a, uh, a Disney world news website.
I won't mention the name.
And we were on the boat and we were like, new scene, new scene.
And we were so excited and we saw this crisp new footage and it was very exciting.
What is the footage?
It was just new footage of some corn and a tractor.
I believe there's a lady bug.
It was just nice and new.
And it's the type of thing where like, you know, now we have like phones and electronics,
keep us busy, but once upon a time, like tops were entertaining.
And I think it really, you know, channels that less is more aesthetic.
That's what I love.
I mean, that's for the, you know, kids love that bugs, farm equipment, trucks.
I love that stuff as a kid.
We've been saying, we've been saying that the Anna and Elsa ride is shit.
And you were saying kids love bugs and tractors and stuff.
Well, the tractor footage, which I believe may not actually be footage.
It looks digitized and fake.
It still looks more real than Elsa's face at the end of that ride.
Sure.
Take a deep fake tractor editing.
Okay.
Let me say this.
And, you know, we do our plus it up stuff and that can be like bits sometimes,
but let's try to actually do this a little because I, all right.
The idea of, we're just going to like ham fistedly insert some character,
some IP into this ride.
I don't think that's the solution.
Is there a way to just like, there's more going on in those scenes.
There's more going on with those animatronics.
We actually go out with a little more of a bang.
You talk about tractors.
Can we have like farm equipment, like moving around or do it?
Can we have like big show pieces and they like, it seems like one's going to like,
you know, crash into you, but then it backs up in time.
You're saying not have like Mater on the ride or something.
You're saying like a real life.
If people, if anyone is thinking, well, Scott probably just wants IP on the,
that's not what I want.
I think there's something in the character of the ride.
I can, we have, let's bring the, well, first of all, the song, bring the song back.
Why did we take the song out?
I think some of my issues are all we've done is remove.
We removed the tour guide.
We removed the song.
Yes.
And so, and it's, it's just literally lesser than it was when it opened.
Except for this new footage of a tractor and a ladybug.
This deep fake tractor.
Okay.
Two things come to mind for how they could improve this ride.
Yes.
One, live actors.
Put an actor on like that fake ass porch in front of that house.
Have it kind of be like the thing in the tram tour, universal studios, Hollywood,
where you like comes out with a knife and you're like, oh no.
You want Norman Bates on the porch?
It should be like American Gothic come to life.
Yeah.
Farmer Brown with the big bushel.
And being like, remember when we, it's just like an,
like a boomer yelling at millennials.
Like that's what I want from that farmhouse.
The other thing.
I like this.
Yes.
Corn used to taste better.
A man with a musky yell and stay away from my daughter.
All of this would be brilliant.
The other thing, give me a free banana at the end.
Think about it.
Sponsored by Chiquita.
Yes.
Drives the point home.
I would do anything for 20 minutes to not pay for a resort banana, which is usually like $3.
That was my, like my main expense on the trip.
Bananas are.
Pop century bananas.
So there must be a 700% markup.
Yeah.
It's really.
If you go on the ride and you get a free banana and what if the Chiquita sticker has a Mickey
mouse on it.
So then like your kid puts it on something.
Come on.
This is really good.
Easy to do.
This is great.
Really good.
Can we have like a bunch of bananas on a conveyor belt, like whirring around,
like a simulation of like, what if you were in a packing plant?
And what if they talk about that thing where apparently bananas will go extinct?
Oh yeah.
Really drive the point home.
That's educational.
That's interesting.
Should I be in marketing?
I was going to say though, you know, like, cause then when a reporter goes and covers,
you know, a political event or something, they are worried like, I don't want to become
the story, but right now you're verging on giving such great ideas.
Do you think?
Yeah.
Maybe.
I might have to go internal.
This might be, this might be the shift.
That's kind of what I'm saying.
Is this, is it, are you in danger in a good way of that happening?
Maybe.
If I can work for Big Banana, I'd be thrilled.
Sure.
Um, I, okay.
I've got a couple things.
First, here's my plus up.
You know, there's been a lot in the last few years of like, you know, imagineers and
universal creative, like, you know, experimenting with like directing people's attention to
places that Harry Potter rides swings you at what they want you to look at.
You know, the, uh, uh, pirates ride in Shanghai, the boat rotate, like it's like a director
telling where to put the camera here and the viewer will look at this.
In this boat ride, like they're not, they have RFIDs to cue the narration,
but they're not going to be able to move that boat ride very much.
But if all, if so much of this, uh, grow house stuff is modular as you narrate, like,
look at this thing, swing that planner towards the boat.
Oh boy.
Swing it.
Like, look at this.
This is what we're, this is where we're directing your attention.
So you go in and you take in a wide shot of it.
And then when it's telling you about the, uh, intercropping, like, yeah,
push a little of that towards the boat.
I like, uh, land is reaching out to you.
Lighting cues.
Perfect.
Very, very, uh, uh, simple to do a simple theatrical trick that I think people would like.
Would the lights though interfere with the greenhouse?
Well, now that is, they do have like sounds and light, like they, they do have to manipulate
that a little, like they said, there, there are certain sounds and winds and stuff to, uh,
simulate the environment.
If there was a strobe light constantly going in a greenhouse, would it fuck up all the plants?
That probably depends on the plant.
Cause like in the, the fish farms and the aquaponics, they eat, there's red lights,
which are there to stop algae from growing.
And that's where my point of clarification.
Uh, so I've watched old ride throughs of this and one of those tanks is baby alligators.
Did they yank them or am I miss they're gone, right?
There's just a, there's like a something in there shaped like a Mickey.
I think it's like a hose or something, but it's like fish tank, fish tank, fish tank empty.
Yeah.
Like I, okay.
So the memory is a tricky thing, but I was like, I know there were, they're going right.
Like, I know they don't want them loose ones on top of a cage.
Yeah.
But I think they've removed a lot of gator stuff from Disney world on purpose.
Do you have a pitch on what to put in the tank?
Cause I do full size Navi.
Yeah.
They're growing it.
They're farming a Navi.
Or what about like a bunch of baby ones?
Sure.
Yeah.
Oh, no, no, no.
They're all you like that.
And I don't know, no, no, no.
Baby.
I love baby Shreks.
I like baby.
Oh, baby banshees.
Oh, but did they, are they in water?
I think the avatar have to be in water.
I think there's water stuff coming in this next one.
Oh, they're for sure.
There's a big whale in the ride.
Yeah.
Whale kind of thing, baby versions of that.
Can we talk about, is there a finale that we can do here that would be more satisfying?
And I said that, I'm saying that, we were going back and forth on Twitter about this.
Yeah, we got something to talk about.
I, okay.
I'm not even going to say my own thoughts on it.
I'm going to say, I haven't brought this up yet.
There is an article that was in Gawker a couple of years ago that talked about living with the land.
I didn't see this.
And there-
I'm a Theoman, I don't recognize the website.
There's, it is, it is several people who like some of the assets that you like about it,
namely sitting, but they don't necessarily have great things to say about the ride in general.
I felt seen when I read this.
One thing they said that I liked was,
the name of this ride doesn't even attempt to make it sound interesting.
It might as well be called The Land is a Place.
Okay, but the thing that they brought up was the finale of the ride.
And they quote this article,
the strangest part of the ride to me was the very end when our boat sailed by a screen
flashing pictures of people wearing the same colors as food.
It is like, you know, 12 trapezoids and there's photos of like very Kodak stock models.
And I was trying to look at specific ones.
There's a boy in a blue shirt and he's in front of a bunch of blueberries.
And there's a girl in a red beret and she's in front of tomatoes.
And that is the grand finale of living with the land.
The problem is there's not a ton of room.
No.
To expand.
Well, I would actually say the problem is not the ride, but it's your perspective.
Because I recently went on this ride with my friend Christine.
Yes.
And at the end, she lives in Orlando.
I don't know if this is a local thing, but at the end she goes, I'm so and so, who are you?
And I go, what?
And she goes, oh yeah, you choose, we choose who we are.
So you like choose, choose a totem.
So you let one of the people there represent you.
She brought an interactive element to the ride that was not there before.
I'm blueberry boy.
Yeah, you decide who represents your feeling that day.
Who are you?
There was some woman in a strange hat and I selected her.
I was like, I am woman in hat.
Like a meme when there's some like crazy picture, crazy tweak,
everyone around the internet and they say tag yourself.
I'm like tag yourself.
I'm young boy with blueberries.
Yes.
Yeah.
Well, okay.
That's a lot of fun.
Doesn't that make it better?
Your friend brought to it.
I don't know to do that.
Also argue that that's like the underground tiki bar of the ride.
What?
Then it's like, oh, it's like a speakeasy experience of living with the land.
Like you got to be in the know.
To know the thing that your friend did?
Yeah, to like know like the fun game.
It is now, but it wasn't until your friend did it.
Yeah, but it, you know.
It's really cool.
I like it now.
It's going out.
Yeah.
See, you make your own fun.
That's what this ride is telling you.
Yeah.
You're the creator.
You're the land creator.
Can I propose that, okay, maybe there's a solution
that isn't removing the wall of 12 trapezoid people.
Is there some way to, if say there were an insane mentally ill person
who thought this was not the most exciting ending to a ride.
Are you willing to budge on anything or does it have to be the still?
Can it tell me, like choose your avatar?
Like can we play that game officially?
Can they be videos?
Can these, can Blueberry Boy talk to me?
What if it's like the technology at the end of the Haunted Mansion in Florida
and it like removes your head and puts it on one, like Blueberry Boy.
Oh, yes.
Yes, you got it.
Now we're talking.
I'm Blueberry Boy.
You are actually Blueberry Boy.
Just a new theme for character.
The kid from Dragnet who does drugs and then he started Blue Paint.
I do know that reference.
Scared me as a kid.
I was just complimenting the Dragon movie, but I don't remember.
No, no, no, no, no.
The very first episode of the 70 year old show, the pilot of Dragnet from 1960.
Is about a kid who does Jack Webb, Harry Morgan.
What happens?
He's just covered in paint for some reason.
Like a drug addict or like a drug head.
Honestly, the kid could have done drugs once and he's painted blue
and they're like acting like he's going to kill a city.
Nick and I used to use that in their commercials a lot.
Now I was like, what is this blue boy?
I think Nick and I, they're like, you're transitioning from like,
sniff from all that and then you're being told and then watch Harry Morgan nail blue.
Yes.
That's how I got very into the Mary Tyler Moore show.
That was a good transition actually.
That and I love Lucy.
Yeah.
When they started introducing the 70 shows, that was like, oh, we're like,
a nostalgia is evolving.
I get to experience the 70s now.
Those are good times.
Well, look, Nick at Night was there first.
Like some of that Nickelodeon program, it took a few years to like ripen.
It's a few years before all that came along.
Make no mistake, Nick at Night came first.
Nick at Night was going for a few years before you got into all that and a snick
and that sort of thing.
Oh, yeah, certainly.
Yeah.
Start a campaign to reboot Dragnet and have you be blue boy.
The answer is of course, yes.
Is he a recurring character?
Why would I even ask it as a question?
Prestige TV Dragnet is a funny idea.
Prestige TV Dragnet with you as blue boy.
It just becomes the wire, a more wire kind of take on Dragnet.
I have a pitch going off something currently new in the land,
The Awesome Planet is the new film that's in the theater upstairs.
I think it's similar to the BBC Planet Earth and Netflix thing that
is just Planet Earth that the BBC should probably sue them for.
They should just take those super high def cameras and film a bunch of plants
and project in that area.
Yes, that's fun.
I don't think it would take much and I don't think it would change the character of this
ride.
I think there's a way to make me like this thing more.
I mean.
It isn't like.
You wishing death upon blueberry boy?
He can stay.
He's grandfathered in, but can we add something else to the hallway?
American farm?
I mean, high def of real small American farm.
I mean, they're suffering with this trade war stuff.
It's insane subsidies for American farms right now.
What if it shows how hard it is to be a farmer these days?
Yeah.
Or how we transition to corn fed animals and how that was a poor choice.
All of our cereals replaced rice with corn and.
A bunch of Monsanto heavy corn syrup.
Slashing tires.
This would be good.
This would be legitimately educational.
What if you put headphones on and listen to it's always a good time by all city during
the ride and that's another little hack.
You have to bring your own music.
My family would love that.
Since they don't play any anymore.
Yes.
There is a major part of this that we have not discussed yet.
The lab.
Okay.
Yes.
Uh-huh.
So I knew that we were going to do this and this was not intentional at all and I was just
like I work out of a co-working space and it's like a long walk to the bathroom, whatever.
And I was walking to the bathroom and I was like, I wonder if anyone has ever seen anyone
in the lab.
Truly just was curious.
Has anyone ever seen someone working in the lab that you see in the end of the attraction?
Now, if there were people in there, what hypothetically would they be doing?
What kind of lab is it?
Um, like a science tubes?
Microscopes.
Tubs?
Honestly, my only reference is the Theranos documentary.
Oh, yeah.
It's like high school science.
Then the next thing I saw was Theranos.
Like they'd be like jiggling tubes or be like checking levels, pipettes perhaps.
And so I tweeted it hoping that I'd maybe find two people who'd seen someone in the lab
or been like, oh, I once saw someone holding a Petri dish.
It's like just hoping, just a pipe dream.
And what I got was an onslaught of people who see someone in the lab every time.
I did not know that I was the one who had the rare experience.
I thought it was just normal to never see anyone in the lab.
And apparently a lot of loud people on Twitter seem to think the opposite.
The land bros.
That it was like it's busy.
Everyone's like, yeah, I always see people there.
We saw someone.
I've never seen.
We saw someone and they were doing something.
Stuff was being agitated.
Yes.
I've seen stuff being agitated.
Maybe saw some agar.
I truly like the reason.
Agar is the gelatin-like substance that you grow stuff in.
Oh, interesting.
That must have been the second semester of my program.
Yeah.
But I truly like I tweeted that to just kind of fact check for like,
oh, I'm going to go on this.
I should make sure so that I don't say the lab's closed.
It's non-functional.
And apparently the lab is fully functional to the point where one person,
I wrote her name down so I wouldn't forget it.
Where's she at?
Her name is at Radscorpion69.
She said that she used to work somewhere where they processed the purchase orders for the lab
and they spent almost $13,000 on mixers.
So some serious science is happening in there.
Whoa.
Yeah.
It is interesting.
Epcot in general, like, because they have these massive fish tanks and stuff,
there's still so many people that are maintaining these facilities there.
It's pretty crazy.
Yeah.
There's people doing tests.
Wow.
Ghosts that I've never had the privilege of seeing.
They need to do a better job of showcasing those people because as I was being
flippant by saying they were doing something, I don't know what they're doing.
We can't see.
I know that's maybe for the upcharge.
Behind the Seeds.
Behind the Seeds tour.
I get that.
$25 per adult, $20 per child.
Right.
See, and that's, people like it because that is probably the most affordable tour on property.
Yeah.
But like, if the scientist could like hang out the window and yell at each boat what
they're doing, that's something.
Yeah.
That's good.
Can we get just a kind of a display that says like today's?
Yeah.
That would be good.
Terry.
The tram tour.
Like the tram tour, Universal Studios Hollywood.
Here's what's filming today.
Yes.
That would be nice.
When I watch their Ghost Whisperer, always and only Ghost Whisperer.
Great.
I remember hearing somebody who was a guest star on that show that Jennifer Love Hewitt said that
a ghost was actually haunting her at the time and was moving furniture around in her house.
What are they doing in the lab?
Are they learning to whisper at ghosts?
We'll never know.
What are they doing in that lab?
It could be really interesting stuff.
This is another, this is a very good plus up.
Let's make sure there's people in that lab.
Yeah.
Let's finance.
Let's make sure it's teaming with people.
Is there a way to make the, can we get anything into the greenhouse area?
You were talking about swinging plants.
Would a robot in there bother anybody?
It depends what kind of robot.
It can't be something with too much personality though.
I'll tell you that.
These are the rules of living with the land.
Yeah.
If it can be a very, like a barely moving ape of some kind, barely moving though.
And in the distance, far away.
I mean, they went for like, they've gone back into Epcot's past for designed elements for like
next generation Epcot.
Yeah.
So I think you could design a pleasant, interesting looking smart one robot.
Butler.
I thought you were going to say like kitchen cabaret, have all of the real food gone and
replace it with singing.
Oh, that's good too.
Make real food sing.
I would love to see them like in line and the guardians coaster and rocket, like look at these
idiots.
Songs are terrible.
I like the idea.
They're talking.
I don't want to give too many spoilers on the new Star Trek Picard, but they're talking about
androids that are like created basically with like real bone and skin at this point.
Could you make an animatronic vegetable, but really like from a real cucumber?
So a cucumber is going to like talk on this thing.
Yeah, but it's built out of a real cucumber.
It's not like, you know.
And can it like kind of follow the boat like Olaf does?
Yes.
Bouncing along.
You know what?
I'm going to declare yes.
This is what I believe it could be possible.
Yeah, absolutely.
Okay.
I will say pretty exciting.
Actually, is it only a cucumber or does he have?
Do we get an eggplant in there?
Oh, I do love those.
What about talk?
If his little like stem part is like a hat.
I need to.
What if they had something like growing but sped up?
It's like you go past, you know, very slowly in that boat and they have an example of like
how quickly things grow.
It's like those videos are like a baby goes from like nothing to this.
Like time lapse.
Yes, that's the word that I thought would arrive in my brain.
Oh, so something like instantaneously goes from a little seed link to like to a, you know,
a massive gourd.
Okay, that's good.
Yeah, I like all this stuff.
I also think genuinely you have a smart.
Maybe it just is.
All right, if we're getting nostalgic for all Epcot stuff, where's smart one at?
The little robot when Epcot opened and he doesn't even have to be doing anything.
I actually think you could take, you know, with awesome.
In his still appearances on the do that with smart one.
He's like checking on the hydroponics.
He's in the lab looking at a microscope.
He's, I don't know, delivering mail to the farmer.
The beginning for unmoving smart ones throughout this ride.
And I'm 20% more in.
I can't disagree with that.
You paint one green, you put a straw hat on another.
You put a lab coat on a third.
And the fourth one's holding a musket.
Oh, like get off my.
Yeah.
Get away from my daughter.
It's smart ones country home.
Yeah.
It's where he went to retire, get some peace and quiet.
And then the damn boats are rolling through.
I would perhaps enjoy at the end, not to say blueberry boy should go,
but I think that, you know, the core of living with the land,
which they don't maybe play up enough is that things die and decompose.
And from that comes a new, which is kind of happening in Epcot right now.
So I wouldn't hate the end using that as an analogy for everything we love
from the past having to change to make new Epcot be born.
Yeah.
And there's still the old spirit.
You needed the old one for the new one to grow.
Because very soon this area will be called world nature.
Yeah.
And that is still strange.
It's getting gerrymandered.
All the Epcot pavilions.
Everything.
World nature.
After the census.
World nature is pretty weird.
I am interested in that.
I do like Moana, the movie.
And I think the way of water, the journey of water,
I do think that's an interesting idea for a pavilion.
And I'm like, oh, okay.
I'm fine with Moana teaching me this.
But part of me is like, well, it could also be some dry water scientists.
It'd be some very dry, you know, I'm hoping there's some education.
Wow.
You love to learn.
I love to learn.
Yeah.
I'm the target audience for like, you know, 1982 Epcot.
Wow.
Yeah.
What are we thinking?
Are we thinking we've...
Well, I guess I would make a statement here.
I wanted to say, you know, America, listen up.
If the four of us can come together in this room and all arrive in a very similar place,
I believe so too can our nation.
So listen to this episode and share it with your friends, Republican, Democrat.
It doesn't matter.
If the four of us can reach a majority consensus on the issues with the
Epcot Center ride, living with the land, don't you think that you can too?
I believe our nation will heal with this podcast.
A full standing ovation.
You can't see it, but we're all standing.
Thank you.
That is a good...
The rarely maybe never achieved full standing ovation.
All hosts and guests.
Thank you.
Mike, you've healed the nation with your moderacy.
Okay. Yeah. Good.
I mean, you can't, there's no way to...
That says it all.
And I believe Carly, was it you survived podcast the ride?
I don't think I survived yet because I don't know if your opinion has changed.
Well, you know, well...
Consider this the boats hitting each other at the end of Pirates.
Oh, I thought we were done.
And then, you know what?
Well, I was thinking in terms of these mission statements as well.
And I think what I'm seeing is that the boring is part of it.
I think we all, everybody...
I was saying boring in an accusatory way.
Everybody else is saying boring like it's a nice thing.
And I am not proposing...
I believe there is a better future for living with the land.
I think there are changes that can happen to it.
And I believe that Mike is playing music.
I believe there is a better brighter future for living with the land.
One that unites the people who have loved it from the very beginning
and the people who called it boring as hell on this very podcast.
And I think the common thread is boring.
It's what we can all agree on about this ride.
But I've come to realize that boring can be good.
And I do not wish to insert IP.
I wish to do what you wish.
Keep the land weird.
No, not weird.
Fuck.
I was saying that phrase in my head.
Keep the land weird.
No, wait, we're pulling the music in.
Okay, forget that ever happened.
I want to do what you want.
Keep living with the land boring.
Does that sound insulting?
I don't know.
That is what I think.
I think there's a version of this that makes everybody happy.
I agree.
I just want you when your next trip to actually physically go on it
and see it through the lens of this episode and hopefully you will enjoy it.
Well, I like the sound of that because I really enjoyed this episode.
I'm going to guess that Erin is not going to do any of this, but I will promise.
She could eat cereal.
I think she'll love it.
You know what?
This was nice.
I think it was a fun mix of there was some argue.
There was some fussing and a feud.
But there was a lot of agreeing.
That's right.
And a lot of I can't think of another word for agreeing.
So let's just all officially wrap it up.
Thank you for proposing this for walking into the hornet's nest.
Woo.
Did not know what I was getting myself into.
Thought it'd be a fun time talking about pumpkins and oh, boy.
I had a great time.
Well, I did too.
You know, I feel great.
I feel hopeful.
And it was wonderful.
Now, we need to have you back for something where it's not like this.
This was the one.
No, no, no.
I keep coming for the random ones and it was like, this is it.
We're going to do a ride.
We're going to finally make something real out of it.
And then I show up to a high school debate class accidentally.
But I will come back and talk about anything.
Well, you made excellent points.
And you're a great guest as always.
So yeah, thanks for being here.
And let's exit to the gift shop.
Past blueberry boy.
Is there anything you'd like to plug?
To the kiosk outside the store and bathroom?
Do you want the Star Spangled Banner playing in the background?
Or do you want Listen to the Land?
Oh, Listen to the Land.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
All right, that'll play us both.
OK, so plug away.
Oh, you can find me on the internet.
It's real weird, real weird with the backing track to do self-promotion.
I wish there was an instrumental.
I write a lot of stories about Disney, but I spend more time on Instagram.
So I would highly recommend finding me there instead.
It's where the most Carly can be found.
Yeah.
All right.
And let's listen to podcast the ride, the second gate at Patreon.com
podcast the ride where we'll someday cover behind.
Keep going.
No, keep playing.
Keep playing.
No, this is division.
Oh, man.
We're not agreeing anymore.
Girl talk just walked in and he saw two songs and he's like, this is going to be one song.
Living in the land.
The land of America, the beautiful mashup and three bonus episodes every month.
No, that's why I said that part already.
I'm so confused.
Keep Portland weird.
Fuck.
What am I saying for more podcast the ride?
Follow us on Twitter, Instagram and Facebook.
Oh, it's good time.
Do we have to hold for you to?
Yeah, maybe I need to find what else?
What do I play?
I'll play.
Let it go.
If you play more than 15 seconds of this, UMG's lawyer will be on.
Yeah, bring it on.
I say, okay, here we go.
And wait, let me get let it go in there.
Thanks for listening.
Wait, I need the chorus.
I'm gonna close my eyes.
Forever.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson,
Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.