Five, four, three, two, one.
Timber, welcome to podcast the Ride the Second Gate.
My name is Mike Carlson joining me as always,
Lumberjack, Jason Sheridan.
You were so excited when we said, who wants to start it?
And you're like, yeah, I can see why.
I didn't have this.
This came to me in the moment.
This was not a planned thing.
Also joining us Lumberjack, Scott Gardner.
Yeah, hey, am I the singer of Fallout Boy?
Because today's topic has got me feeling like Mr. Stump.
Wow.
We're having a lot of fun already.
We're having a lot of fun.
Yeah, well of course, because we're talking about a tree stump.
Today's episode's about a stump.
It's about a stump.
Yeah, can't stop the stump.
Stump.
There was a character in the Ninja Turtles Archie comics
named Stump and he was a wrestling promoter,
but he was a tree man.
And he's one of my favorite characters
and they've never used him.
In fiction.
In fiction, yeah.
He's a tree man who was a tree man
who was a sneaky Don King style promoter on a planet,
on a wrestling loving planet.
So anyway.
Some of my least favorite characters in fiction are trees.
Yeah, we'll talk about it.
Most alive trees are horrible.
I hate it in the Snow White Ride.
I hate it in Wizard of Oz.
I'm creeped out by talking trees in FAO shorts.
Grandma Willow from Pocahontas.
Don't much care for Grandma Willow.
Lord of the Rings trees.
What's, Lindsay, what's the-
I don't know though.
Lindsay, what's the tree from, is it the last,
what's the tree that is a bustier woman?
What's the busty tree from?
It's last unicorn.
It's, what's the character's name?
Who gets tied to the tree?
Yeah.
Shmendrick.
Shmendrick gets tied to this busty woman tree.
And it's like very disturbing, right?
He gets tied to a tree,
and then Shmendrick, to try to get away from it,
turns the tree into a living tree.
Oh.
She becomes a busty woman.
Does anyone have time code for this horrifying sequence?
I think you could probably just Google
last unicorn busty tree.
Got it.
Yeah, so that is a scary sequence.
Well, then it's good that we're talking about a tree
that died a long time ago, because good riddance.
So many scary trees.
I want them gone.
Cut every tree down.
Is there a good, is there a good talking tree?
Anyway, I guess stump is my, I like him.
But other than that, it is tough to find a good talk.
Groot.
Groot?
Yeah.
Groot is good.
Yeah, Groot is a good talking tree, yeah.
Does the giving tree talk?
Does the, oh shoot.
I don't think so.
Yeah.
I think it just gets used for parts.
Right.
The first thing I ever worked on for Funny or Die
was I edited a video starring Tim Allen,
where he was a, he was in a liar, liar type scenario.
He like, his son made a wish and then he becomes a tree
and it was called Arbor Days, like D-A-Z-E.
And that was the first I ever did anything for them.
And I got to go through Tim Allen Daly's,
while he was painted to look,
his face was superimposed onto a tree.
So they painted his face,
basically he was like in blackface in the raw footage.
Because they painted a brown oval around his face
to be comped, but I'm looking at all the raw footage
and just like, this is weird.
He just has like a raisin print on his face.
It was very disturbing.
Yeah.
I'm glad the audience didn't have to see what I had to see.
That does sound disturbing.
The video was disturbing, I think too.
Already, yes.
Yeah, so you would.
Hey, I'm a tree.
He mainly, and in the raw, they're saying like,
improvise and just have fun with it.
And he's like, okay, yeah.
Hey, I'm a tree.
Look at me, I'm a tree.
I was like about what he could think of to do.
He was doing his best.
Maybe he hasn't been through all the levels of UCB.
No, he also in the raw footage complained
about the sound quality because he,
there were planes going by, so they had to hold.
And he's like, I thought that's why we live
in this damn city.
So we could work in sound stages where it's soundproofed.
But the one in the damn world.
So he did easily improvise about being mad
about that they weren't filming in a soundproof environment.
Yeah.
Was that in character as a tree though?
That was just as Tim.
Well, it was in that like, when he's a tree,
he's like, hey, I'm a tree.
And when he's Tim, he's like, hey, I'm Tim.
He's got a lot of, he's got some range.
Yes.
There was a range in what I just did.
Yeah, you'd have to rewind it
and to really analyze it to tell.
Well, back to this tree.
It's not a tree anymore.
It's a petrified tree.
We should, this is early enough that we should say
what the hell this is in case you don't know.
And you might be looking at a photo of it
that we tweeted out.
But, and you might really not be familiar
if you haven't been to Disneyland
or spent a lot of time at Disneyland.
Because this has not been reproduced in the other parks.
No.
This is only at Disneyland.
And this is some real old Walt Disney stuff.
In Frontierland, you get to the river
and you get to, you know, like,
just past the Golden Horseshoe.
You start approaching, you know, where Fantasmic happens.
And there's this tree that's been up since 1956.
And it is framed as a gift from Walt Disney
to his wife, Lillian.
And there is a plaque that explains what this is.
Now we're talking about it.
Yes.
It is believed to have been part of a forest
55 to 70 million years ago.
Yes.
But due to mineralization, it has become rock.
So I feel safe in including that, yes,
the petrified spires of Batuu are fake rocks.
Cause I read up a little more on petrified wood.
And I'm like-
Oh, this judgment of do those count as rocks?
I see.
Petrified wood is kind of like fossils.
The fossils we think of are like imprints,
but this is actual wood that is like transformed into
minerals.
But you wouldn't call this petrified tree a rock.
It is rock.
It is now rock.
But the plaque doesn't say here's a rock.
No, but for all intents and purposes,
it is mineral now as opposed to vegetation.
That's true.
But I think there's even this question.
I just wanted it out of the fake rock.
There was so much to get through.
That seemed like an easy technicality.
Yeah.
That was as close as we could come to saying
one of the competitors took performance enhancing drugs.
Yeah.
So they're out of the competition.
Well, this tree gambled.
This tree gambled on itself.
So it's got a knock.
It is fake rock, but it took a circuitous route to get there.
Sure.
Yes.
Yeah.
This is real rock.
This is actual rock.
Yes.
This is, yeah.
Do you guys remember noticing this for the first time?
This feels like the kind of thing that maybe
does it maybe take a lot of Disneyland visits
to notice this detail?
I mentioned it to Erin, my wife, who
had no idea what I was talking about.
She's never noticed this thing.
I've never noticed it either.
Really?
Didn't know.
Whoa.
You suggested it.
I looked it up and went.
I suggested it and you looked it up and went, oh.
OK.
So you've never looked at that plaque before.
I guess not.
Whoa.
Yeah, I guess not.
Well, it's good.
This is really why we might be explaining this
to a lot of audience members for the first time.
And it's really important that you know,
because when you hear all of the exciting stories that
are to come.
I read up.
It's, boy.
Yeah, hey, we're going to go to Colorado.
We're going to talk to a boy who gives an old man a tour.
Butterflies are involved.
A bug man, not a bug man.
Not a bug man.
Ha ha ha.
Unfortunately, we could call him.
We could get him here.
We wanted to spice this episode up.
Now that you know about it, what do you think?
How do you feel?
Well, I feel deceived by the plaque
because I don't believe I would have, from what I understand,
is not completely accurate.
Well, it's a little family joke.
The facts are yes, but the story of it is a bit embellished.
Little Jebediah Springfield-y.
Yeah.
OK, so this is framed on the plaque.
This is something that Walt gave to Lily and his wife.
And the story that they played up for people
is that this was an anniversary present.
And that she looked at it in sort of a Simpsons big old head,
a gift from Mr. Burns way, and was like,
this is not going in my home.
We've got to put this somewhere.
This is going to Disneyland.
And which would make this really like the ultimate regift.
Disneyland has a permanent regift.
It's had it since 56.
But it is disputed whether or not that is accurate.
Because it seems that via the Disney daughters,
this was never in their house.
Right.
There was not a stretch of time where they tried to have the tree around.
And there's a letter that you can find where Walt said,
deliver this to Disneyland.
Yes.
There is literally a purchase order for like,
I have paid you just over $1,600.
Please deliver it to Disneyland.
The letter E is available online.
Also, it says, please deliver during business hours.
Please deliver this five tons.
Please don't deliver before or after business hours.
Please deliver during business hours.
I'm sure they had a lot less staff back then.
But also, please drop off this massive thing,
this massive five ton thing, while this amusement park is running.
So did they?
Did like a truck drive in and like,
and, you know, like knock over kids on the way into the park?
Just right down Main Street.
Yeah, with a petrified tree on the back of it.
These brazen tree deliverers.
Be more careful.
Yeah.
The happiest place on earth.
Well, at least he has to use the warehouse entrance on West Street,
which I don't believe is that a street anymore in Anaheim?
West Street?
It's changed so much.
I think it is, maybe.
Is it?
I'm not sure.
Does it have a series of restaurants and hotels we could review?
Oh.
Let's hope to God not.
No, this is a service road.
We don't have to review the service roads.
Not yet.
Maybe in year eight.
We're edging ever closer with this topic, with this like, you know,
very functional topic.
West Street, Anaheim.
I'm looking at it.
Hey, we're talking trees.
We're doing tree episodes.
I want to take the lead on a Halloween tree episode.
What's up with the Halloween tree?
Well, we'll have to get into it.
The Halloween tree is in Frontierland as well.
Every Halloween, a tree is turned into Ray Bradbury's Halloween tree.
The spirit of Halloween.
Really?
I don't know.
I don't know that either.
It's very simple in execution, but it's got a fun.
It's a fun little thing they do to nod a guy who was very influential
throughout the Disney parks history.
Where's the Halloween tree?
It's right by the shops in
Frontierland.
Yeah, it's covered in lights and lanterns.
Yeah. So you got a couple of famous trees right across from each other.
Huh? Oh, well, I guess I want to do a tree now, too.
But I don't know which.
I learned about some other Disney trees.
I don't want to get off topic, but I in Googling this petrified tree,
I found a listicle of like other important Disneyland trees.
Do you know about the Dominguez family palm tree?
Mm hmm.
There is a palm tree that was part of the farm, the original farm
that is that was the farmland that was purchased for Disneyland.
And part of the deal was there was this one tree that was very important to them.
And they said, don't demolish this tree.
And they did not.
And it's still up in the Jungle Cruise.
You're looking at the Jungle Cruise marquee.
It's probably like 20 feet to the right.
Interesting. A palm tree that is that predates Disneyland.
Wow. They never move. Sure.
There is another one that I'd never, ever heard of before.
Do you know about the little man of Disneyland? Yes.
Yes. I've never heard of this.
Really? No, never got this.
Well, let's make that one, too.
Let's put that aside.
That has to be a separate episode.
The little man. Well, you can read the storybook live on air.
I think the little man is at least a patron.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Because there's a whole story about him.
OK, so there's some off the little man here.
There's some Lasseter little man stuff, too.
When they reintroduced the little man a couple of years ago, D23,
it's a video to steal your impression.
There's a little man of Disneyland.
This was the thing that made a park special in me.
Yes. So much less arm flailing with him out.
You don't have any more presentations.
We have Eiger who doesn't do anything with his body.
No, no, he's too scared to.
He can't move at any.
He doesn't want to offend anyone with any sort of gesture.
So he just is perfectly still.
Any little motion I could make could be some gesture that would offend the Chinese.
Yes. I don't want to risk that.
Yeah. Yeah.
Let me purchase another company, please.
But I cannot.
All right. So these but these are other trees.
This is this is counter to you know, it's also
it this is probably the oldest plant life in the park,
not bested by the Sequoia slice in the Redwood Trail.
Oh, right. Yes. Yes. That I was like, when is that from?
That's called the Millennium Tree, apparently.
And that is that's maybe from eight one eight A.D.
It's a distracting year.
That's a lot of our area codes of our phone numbers. Yes.
This tree is from the eight one eight.
So this is much older, as you said, 55 to 70 million years old. Yeah.
Isn't there a tree Tony Baxter took from Disneyland, put in his backyard?
I believe so.
When it fell over or struck by lightning or something like that.
Oh, he also took something and had it transported to his backyard.
And you pointed out to us the the Matterhorn tree,
I believe, when we were there.
That's shaped like the Matterhorn. Yeah.
I think somebody else actually does someone else from Dennis McNicholas.
Yeah. Yeah.
I'd never noticed that before, that there's this tree.
If you're in Frontierland, there's a tree that is cut in the shape
of the Matterhorn to block the Matterhorn so you can't see it from Frontierland
because it would be it would take you out of it.
Why would there be this Swiss mountain in the frontier town?
It is eerie when you look at it now, like you can't unsee it.
You look at it from the other way and it's clear even without the Matterhorn
there, it's clearly the shape of the Matterhorn. Sure.
That is very strange.
Listeners, what's your favorite Disneyland tree?
Yeah. Let us know.
Shout it out now, or if you want to write it down and send it to us
and we will peruse it and go, hmm.
And that'll be the end of that exchange. Yeah.
I was going to say I like all these trees, but I you know, they're not fake.
I think we would like them a little more if they were fake. Sure. Sure.
We have a favorite fake tree.
Well, I mean, is the tree of life count?
I guess I guess that's probably it.
So probably too obvious.
It is too obvious.
Well, look, it is also if it is the best fake tree than it is.
Yeah. And or the treehouse.
Do we think the tree of life is better than the than Swiss family or
Terzins treehouse?
Are there actual real trees involved in that?
Or is it all fake trees?
I think it's mostly fiberglass, isn't it?
I would assume that.
But could there be one that it's in question shows you how it is all fake?
It's very well done. Yeah.
OK, I like that, too. Yeah.
What else has fake trees?
There's a lot of fake trees in the trouble is it's a lot of forests.
Yeah, it's a lot of like, you know,
it's hard to point out an individual one in the adventure in Hagrid's. Right.
It's it's the bulk of the trees.
Although, wait, no, those are real trees, fake trees in ET.
And they're all very good.
Yes. And real trees on Hagrid's. Yes.
There's a lot of disguised like electrical poles or boxes
throughout, if you like, wooded areas of parks.
Well, and with the in outside of the parks,
there's a lot of like antennas and things disguised as trees,
like along the freeway and what have you.
Let's give some respect to those.
Yes. That really is themed entertainment outside of theme parks.
Yeah. Yeah. Good job with those fake trees.
I'll see people when it comes to trees and decorative elements for trees as well.
They were doing we miss this with downtown Disney ordeal right around the holidays.
They put these like neon circle things.
Remember this around the trees and which I believe they're gone.
Last time I was there, they're gone, which is a bummer.
But maybe they'll be back for the holiday.
So I like that. That's half that's that's fake and a fake element on a real tree,
which very much makes it seem like they're like future trees. Yeah.
That was like the the like good guy component to like the weird
like Melania Trump, like White House trees, like the last few years,
the like, let's take a tour of my White House trees.
And they're just like so sinister looking.
You're gothic and terrifying and like York video elements.
Simplistic like like modernist and simplistic, but like horrifying.
Like, I don't know, the neon trees of downtown Disney were like.
Mm hmm. Good.
But when you just create, you said the phrase fake elements on real trees.
I mean, that's like so that you're describing Christmas trees.
I was also. Yes. As I said, almost everything.
Yes. A lot of any light on a tree counts as that.
Yes, that's true.
Well, I guess the Christmas tree that they put up in
around Christmas time in Disneyland.
Mm hmm. That's real. Real tree. Yeah.
OK. Yep. Yes.
No, they don't just like pack that away
and in a Disneyland closet and put it back together.
And it's a new tree every year, right?
I don't put it back in the ground.
I don't believe so.
I don't think they go in and out of the ground plant and replant.
All right. I think that's not how it works.
But if you can move a tree, how often can you move a tree and it still survives?
Hmm. It depends on if you're moving, if you're just soil to soil, I think,
or like soil to like could you tree planter?
Could you move a tree every month and still have it survive?
I don't know that. I don't know.
It's like a question for a way on.
Well, that's like then you're like the military brat of trees.
Yes. It's maybe technically you survive, but it was.
Yes. Yes. Who knows the psychological effects?
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
I mean, you would just be the tree
is to make new friends at a new school.
That's so hard. It is very hard.
Might not integrate.
And especially, you know, if you are a palm and then you're planted amongst pines.
Yeah. You might not fit in.
So you should be accepting stupid snooty pines.
You're talking to try getting along with a tree that's not your kind.
Hmm. Hmm. That's a whole different show.
I still it bums me out to think that they just throw that tree away after Christmas.
But lots of places do that.
Many, many of places we did it.
Yes. Yeah. Well, all of us individually, but like massive places
throw that, yeah, get massive trees.
And then that's the end of that.
Yeah. They hopefully use it for something good and important.
I don't know. It becomes part of the land.
It's the circle of life.
Mm hmm. That's it.
When we die, what does Mufasa say?
We die, our bodies become the grass and the antelope eat the grass.
That's the circle of life.
I think that is what Mufasa says.
It is exactly what he says, right?
Like hauntingly what he said.
You just said it with no inflection.
All right. Here's the deal.
When we die, we become the grass and then the antelope eat the grass.
All right. That's the circle of life. Got it?
All right. Let's eat dinner.
I don't know why they got James Earl Jones again
when you offer a much different, perhaps more modern take.
Well, I need an agent so I can get these hot voiceover auditions
so I can redo classic Disney lines in the most dry, monotone way possible.
Hey, it's no, I'm not going to say that one.
Oh, I'm not sure what you were going to say.
Hey, it's Mike. I'm Siamese.
You can still reference the Siamese cats.
Yeah, they thought of it.
You're making fun of how inappropriate it is.
Whatever.
They're making fun of the inappropriateness, not the actual.
That's probably the better way to do it also than some voice
that's going to bother people. It's Mike.
We are Siamese, if you please.
We're Siamese.
I got to tell you, we're Siamese if you don't please.
Yeah. Yeah.
What are you going to do? Mm hmm.
I like this take. Yeah.
All right. Move along.
All right. Let's go dinner.
Get this spaghetti.
You just want to see the spaghetti.
You want to see the CGI spaghetti?
I did not. We did. We watched.
We scrolled through it and.
When Walliners here right after the we watched
because we were watching Boogity during the episode.
Yeah, it seemed we were surprised that F.
Murray Abraham sings the Bella note. Right. Yeah.
I don't think I don't think I have any observations about it.
No, that's these movies are designed to be observation free.
They like like Bob Iger's body language are designed to be
as inoffensive as possible, is not distracting as possible.
Give anyone any handle.
Don't like create an opening to have an opinion, good or bad.
Right. Disney is aiming for perfect seas.
Yes. Like like a perfect circle, like a scientifically perfect sea
is what all these movies are trying to be.
There is an assembly line designed to make the movie too good.
Can make it too interesting.
Can make it much different.
We just want people to go, huh, OK.
And then we'll forget about it.
So then in two months when this similar thing happens, they go,
you want to go see that other movie, the movie that we it's a remake
of the other movie we like.
And they go, yeah, OK. And then they go, huh, OK.
That was fine. Then they forget about it and happens two months later.
Yeah, it's insidious.
It's a brilliant insidious plan.
I don't think Disney has the monopoly on that, though,
of like churning out movies.
No, not at all.
But they are like so the fact that Disney does it in this
like shot for shot way. Yeah.
I think they they're there.
They're more than other franchises reinvent in a in a boring or eye rolling way.
They truly just can we just kind of like use the old one as a demo
and not really change anything. Yeah, for sure.
Is it possible?
Do you guys think at this juncture that Mulan is better than the other ones
have been or the or that like in maybe interesting in a way?
Because like, I don't think anyone needs
Mulan animated Mulan to be remade shot for shot.
So maybe they're going to be a little it just might be like a cooler looking movie.
I think they're a little cooler. Yeah.
I think they're they're they chose a different direction.
Like I did. There's no songs.
Mm hmm. That's fine. Who cares about this Mooshu in the movie?
But I think they cut Mooshu really.
I think it's more of like the second or more like Teddy Murphy. Right.
Oh, yeah. The animated.
Yeah, they're more the PJs.
Who's rank those?
I think I think in terms of public love, it would be Donkey Mooshu.
PJs or PJ. Mm hmm.
I think I think.
Well, it's a lightning strike.
And the listener hear that? I don't know.
I don't know. The creator of the PJs is angry.
I would put PJs at number two.
I'm not just saying that it's a threat of some sort of weather phenomenon.
Fine, fine. You're moving up, Mr. PJ.
I like the PJs.
Uh, I don't remember.
I don't think maybe I just don't care for Mooshu, though, too much.
Like Mooshu fine. I just haven't seen the movie in a long time. Yeah.
Mm hmm. But I think it is more of a straightforward martial arts period movie.
Maybe that's a good self is better than what it was before.
Would you know with Harvey Fierstein and
I don't remember a lot of it.
I don't know. I'm like that one's like 70 minutes, I feel like.
Is it that short? Yeah.
Huh. Yeah, it is an interesting story.
It's got like you could do.
So, yeah, potentially they've they've made something interesting.
We'll see. Mm hmm.
This is a shot.
It's the first one where I haven't rolled my eyes at every
snippet of it I've seen. Yeah.
So we shall see. We will.
But they impress me in my ability to be very dull at every turn.
Very interested that through some like cross
studio cooperation, Harley Quinn is in it.
That kind of breaks the seriousness.
Harley Quinn is now in Mulan.
I didn't know that. I guess they've been hiding on the trailer.
Huh?
Come on, M.
We got a bunch of conquering armies.
We got to take.
What's this episode about the tree?
The tree. Let's let's should we should we.
Explain war.
The actual truth.
Is it possible listeners also let us know if you can hear those lightnings
because they seem very loud to us, but I don't know the power of microphones.
Thunder. Yeah, it's too big.
Thunder strike thunder.
I mean, I assume there's lightning somewhere.
Usually that's what happens.
But if you live in a city so it could be soundproof,
goddamn lightning strikes, I'm a tree. Wow.
How fitting.
So so the real story, the real story of the petrified tree,
as we said, always intended for Disneyland, became a family joke that like,
yeah, Walt Baldi has an anniversary gift because he did buy it two days before
him, his and Lillian's 31st wedding anniversary.
They were vacationing in Colorado Springs. Yes.
At the time, they were working on a project
to add a mineral museum to Frontierland called Mineral Hall.
Yeah. Where you could go and buy, look at mineral samples
and buy souvenir minerals.
And this was there. This this did happen.
It did happen. Yes.
It didn't stick around. Sure.
But yeah, it was there for a little while.
It was sponsored by the the Blacklight Corporation of America.
And they sold black lights so that you could, you know, view your minerals
where under cool looking black light.
So, yeah, while it was in bed with the blacklight people
and needed something to put in these stores.
Still very novel at the time.
Blacklight. Yeah.
And not in the parks like crazy. Yes. Yes. Right.
So so they did build it.
Yeah, there was a mineral hall.
And that's why.
Well, I'll save that part maybe just if we're going through this story in order.
But yeah, there was a store called the Mineral Hall.
And if you go and it is where now the restaurant Rancho del Zocalo is.
And there is if you look on a building there,
it says Mineral Hall on the second floor
as a nod to what used to be there at one point in time.
That's cool. Something over.
I was so excited, flailing my arms around.
This is why Iger avoids doing this kind of thing. Yeah. Yeah.
You should be more like Bob.
You were saying that to Jason.
Oh, yeah. So so they were vacationing in Colorado.
What did not end up in Disneyland
was a collection of rare butterflies and insects from a man named John May.
Walt wanted to buy this collection
and John May wanted to rent it to him
with a promotion for his main museum audits in Colorado.
Colorado be an ad for a Colorado museum.
Yes. You have to look at in Disneyland.
Yes. Hmm.
But Walt wanted his name on it.
Well, one in his name, I like everything for the most part.
Well, just wanted to buy a bunch of dead books.
Yes. But he let me just take these to Disneyland.
But he wanted to call like Walt Disney's Dead Bugs.
Probably. Yeah. That's what I read that he didn't have any.
He didn't want the connection to Colorado.
He wanted to act like he found these dead butterflies.
Yeah. He picked them all.
Yeah. Personally, unless he was getting a ton of money from a company like Monsanto,
he didn't want to have another name above another person's name.
Yeah, that was his thing.
OK, unless it was a ton of money involved, which the butterfly man
did not have a lot of money. No.
Like Monsanto did.
He let though Aunt Jemima into the parks.
Yes. That's not really a person unless was there a real Aunt Jemima?
Well, there was an actor would play.
Well, there was as far as the history of the syrup company.
I don't know.
But there was a there was a woman who played Aunt Jemima at the pancake
house in Disneyland for many years.
You go meet Aunt Jemima. Yes.
Yeah. I guess that's more of a hype.
I don't. Hmm. Was there a real Aunt Jemima? Not sure.
I don't know. We have to look that up.
But that's but that's still more of a spokesperson, I guess.
Yeah. And they were getting probably money from the syrup company.
For that, I assume.
Oh, yeah. John May.
Yes. Why am I going to put an ad for John May in my park?
Right. There's not a John May walk around character, the butterfly man.
I don't think unless he was proposing that, but I didn't come upon
come upon that in the research.
I don't think so.
So he yeah.
So he said no.
He said no to that.
But while they were in Colorado Springs, Walt said, let's stop by
this place called Pike's Petrified Forest.
According to an article at the Disney Family Museum website,
this was one of only two petrified forests in the country
that had been taken over by the park service.
This was a private establishment.
Again, petrified rocks and fossil, all of that.
Now, mostly you can still see plenty of it in the country.
I've been to the petrified
Forest National Park, I think, in Arizona. Very beautiful.
So but Walt stopped by this private one end of the day,
pretty late in the day.
They were about to close.
My favorite detail of this story is Walt said he would be real quick.
And Lillian said, I'll wait in the car.
Didn't even get out.
She didn't get out. Wow.
So the day of butterfly, dead butterfly and rock viewings
didn't wasn't thrilling. Lillian.
Well, I don't know if it was the exact same day, but definitely same trip.
Mm hmm.
This is honestly like
Lillian is like some of the podcasts that write significant others
in the sense of like, what are we doing? OK, do I have to?
What are you? You're making me listen to what Jim Hill and Lentesta podcast.
OK, I'm all right. I'm good.
That was kind of how mine felt when I said we were doing an episode about this.
OK, sure. What is it about that tree?
You know, the tree ever seen the tree in front of your land?
No. Why were you talking about the tree? OK.
All right, have fun.
I'll be in the car.
She's in the car.
She's in the car outside.
This is a quick. It's raining.
It's it's healing.
It's hailing. It was hailing.
And now what are those rocks?
Do we consider Hales rocks? Oh, no.
Hale is ice. It's ice.
But ice is rock.
I disagree. It's rocks from the sky.
OK, OK.
I'll allow it.
I'm just going to be contrarian about every item.
Hale does rock.
But that's a whole nother conversation.
But well, there's no disagreement about that.
Yeah. Hale rocks.
So I also I think we can all agree Spider-Man rocks.
Spider-Man does rock for sure.
So Walt took the tour.
Thirty five cents.
He was apparently gone a while.
This article says his brother Roy later recalled
he was gone quite a long time.
And when he came back, he knew she would be provoked with him.
It was near their anniversary.
So he said, honey, I bought you an anniversary present.
This in reference to the giant petrified tree.
Apparently, other accounts said that, like, you know,
Walt took this tour for thirty five cents.
They gave him like a real quick tour and Walt's like, I'd like to buy something.
And he said, well, the gift shop's over there.
It's like, no, I want something bigger.
I want that. Point it to this giant tree.
This is like a real living with Michael Jackson scenario.
I'm sure we've referenced it before on the show where Michael was walking
through that store and just buying expensive things.
And Walt had a similar.
I have that. I have that.
Yeah, I want that. I have those.
I have that tree. I have that one.
I have one. Give me one of these.
And he bought this boy who gave him the tour.
I'd like to buy this boy. He owned that boy. Yeah.
So is his own.
I assume. Yeah, it's a similar thing of like a rich guy
getting off on buying something that's insane.
So he was just pointing to. Yeah. Yeah.
The boy who sold him the tree he bought.
And then when he passed, he was petrified and is used as Pinocchio in the ride.
I was going to say little man of Disneyland.
The small boy of Disneyland.
My boy can't just be a plastic little man.
Yeah, it's got to be real.
He he paid sixteen hundred and fifty dollars for this.
I just ran the inflation calculator in twenty nineteen dollars.
That's fifteen thousand seven hundred and forty dollars and eight cents.
Still kind of a bargain for a million year old five ton rock.
Multi-million year old.
Well, and so I guess you said earlier, this is a private
park, not a national, but you probably couldn't buy a big tree from the national parks.
That's what enabled us to be here.
Trump is trying very hard, I think, to get legislation passed.
So you can just buy trees from national parks as pointed trees.
And they're your tree.
Is any of the am I wrong?
Is he not the click to declassifying national parks for you?
Because then if it's not to drill, you can drill.
And that sort of thing.
I read an article that they're like there's like a beautification for buildings
project now to which federal contract buildings
that are government buildings that are new and being built.
They're trying to push it more towards, you know, beautiful stuff.
Columns, big Roman columns, which is real, which is very flashy.
They're Trump.
Yeah, they're trying to beautify in that sense and get away from modernism, which is like
the first step in once you start controlling how buildings look like.
That's so all the national parks are going to look like the outside of the King Kong ride.
Yeah. Like Penn Station.
Yeah, it'll be more marble columns with that, like knock over very easily.
Yeah. If one tips, they all domino.
Yeah. Yeah. Just like the wall, that part of the wall.
Oh, that fell over on this cave.
Yeah, it was just plywood.
But soon we'll be all be able to like bid on petrified trees
that are millions of years old.
Me. Yeah.
I mean, so we'll just all be able to get it for sixteen hundred dollars in 2019 money.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
And then that obviously like that'll appreciate in value.
So maybe it's a good investment for all of us to go out to that when the national parks
are privatized to go out and purchase them before they become oil refineries.
Somebody will show Kevin Garnett a big petrified tree and he'll become
convinced that it has luck and he needs it to win the championship.
Judd Hirsch when he comes out of retirement, the auction.
Yeah. Part of this tree apparently did mineralize into opal.
Oh, wow.
The black opal, the black opal, black opal wall.
That's real black.
Hey, man, I'm building the Avengers E ticket.
I need this.
You got to let me take this.
Let me take the part of this tree.
Just let me take part of it over to the other gate.
Like just for a few years, man.
Is that Joe Rody? Yeah.
Joe Rody to JPEG.
Yeah. Yeah. Come on.
And then he has to go to he has to take the little man tree over to like a tree
bank to like to get the I forget how that system worked.
Yeah. Or he took the ring.
Never mind. I don't remember.
He took it to like a.
That's what I'm doing. Yeah.
I don't know how I just hold it.
You can the way pawn shots work.
You can pawn something and they won't sell it for like
10 to 12 days or so.
And so you can come back and rebuy it back.
So it's essentially a loan.
The collateral being that object.
Well, yeah. And does he get you get the same amount of money?
What's that?
Like if you were to put it, give them the item, do they give you
the exact same amount of money back?
You probably have to pay some interest.
Right. That's like that's what I'm for them to do.
Yeah. So what can we could I pawn?
Like Oswald, Oswald statue.
An Oswald statue in this room.
Yeah. Adam West, Batman hot toy.
I'm assuming most valuable thing that's worth a couple hundred.
You know. Yeah.
So I could take that to a pawn shop and get 200 bucks right now.
And then I could come back and get it in a week if I needed it.
You could try putting it for like a hundred and come back.
Oh, I see. And fifty.
Right. It was new when I bought it.
So do we need to change the episode title from Walt's Petrified Trees
slash how pawn shops work? Yeah.
Slash an informational.
It's a very helpful.
By some cursed guitars.
So I don't know.
He bought this. Yeah, he bought this thing and he bought a bunch of he bought
one ton of little petrified stones.
And that's what he sold in the mineral hall until the mineral hall was no more.
So Walt really cashed in.
This is a real there will be blood.
I want that.
Why don't I own that?
And then he just and then he sold all these rocks that he got just in
like kind of a bulk deal from I.
According to some stories, it's like a 12 year old kid named Toby,
who he pointed to. I want to buy that.
OK, gave him the tour.
OK, maybe he didn't do the arrangement ultimately.
But Frederick of or Pike,
Pike's Petrified Forest, Mr.
Pike, I believe, made the final decision to sell.
OK, the rock.
And this has been I believe this property has been folded into the park service.
And I believe Walt then ultimately found
brought Pike out to his house with the private bowling alley
and threw bowling balls at him until he bled out.
Well, he threw petrified wood at him.
I'll kill you with your own wood.
He had a bowling alley with pins made of petrified wood.
Yeah. And that's how you really got to get that ball.
Oh, and you really got to get some spin on that thing. Right.
I eat your gemstone.
I eat them up.
So, yeah, so Walt murdered this guy.
Walt murdered Pike is what you should take out of this episode.
And now it's in the it's in the park.
It's in the park.
I believe, you know, there's a website called Disney History Institute.
And they were really like, you know, in the early days and to some extent now,
Walt really did see the park as part museum because you think about
Main Street has all the old Penny arcade games and the replicas of the old
vehicles and the train and stuff.
And yeah, there was a lot of minerals and recreations of stuff in Frontierland.
This feels very it feels very Knott's Berry Farm.
The way Knott's Berry Farm has like here's a real old locomotive or,
you know, this schoolhouse, this cabin we just we bought from somewhere.
And it's a real historic thing that's in the park.
I like it in that regard that it's like a tie to the early days,
you know, when it when it was there was this Americana feel to Disneyland.
Yes. And the person the Disney family touch and her being referenced on the plaque.
It reminds you of this era where this this was theirs.
You're like visiting this family's weird.
Yeah. They did.
With a lot of family inside.
What was the other inside joke?
Like, oh, it was too big for the mantle.
Oh, very wholesome humor.
Very wholesome humor.
Yeah, it was because it wasn't the original Penny arcade had some
like museum type elements to like there.
There was an element of the idea, as you're saying Disneyland, where it was like,
we want to preserve things and like people can learn.
And it's obviously not the case anymore.
They're not going to build anything that you'll learn anything from anymore.
But we're going to learn about the journey of water.
So that's true. You're right. You're right.
We'll learn about water.
We'll learn about rocket in a new adventure on a roller coaster.
We'll learn about classic rock.
Learned about rocks in the parks.
And the guardians will teach us about classic rock.
It's a good point.
The parks will be keeping rock and roll alive.
The only place potentially.
Uh huh. Pat Benatar.
Who was this?
So wait, I take that back.
It's we're still doing museum and learning.
Yeah, it's all educational.
Yeah, absolutely.
Uh, here's a little educational fact.
Also, I was thinking about we haven't talked much about Lily and Disney.
That's really in Disney was I didn't realize that she was a Waltz employee
when they met. She was an anchor at the studio.
I learned that from that to Funkland video.
Oh, the one that we're in, the one that we're in.
Yeah.
I gotcha.
Yeah, she made fifteen dollars a week and then met him and married him.
I don't know. But she like she worked on playing crazy.
The first Mickey.
Yeah, she like had her hands literally on that very historic piece of animation.
And then the big fact about her, this always says that Walt came to her
with a cartoon mouse and said, this is this is Mortimer Mouse.
Right.
And he said and she said, I don't know, that's not so friendly sounding.
Maybe that should be Mickey.
So she she named Mickey is the big. Right. Yeah.
People don't lie. Shut up.
You're wrong. You're wrong.
Just sobbing, just sobbing because he knows she's right.
And he took her idea and never thanked her for it.
He ever mentioned it.
He begged some of his male friends to like, you just like come up with a name.
And one of them happened to throw out Mickey to and then, OK, there.
All right. Now that he really nudged him toward Mickey.
Yeah. Yeah.
Maybe like we kind of end with a Y because it's like what about Nick?
And he's like, no, no, no. What about if it was an M?
And what do you mean? Like Mick? No. But with a Y on it, Mickey.
Yeah. Thank you. Thank you, Bob, for coming up with the name.
Monkey Mouse. No, no, no, no.
By the way, monkey mouse is funny.
You should make a character called Monkey Mouse.
I like that a lot. That would be the worst.
There'd be a real fail of a wheel of fortune.
Oh, you have the M and the Y
and the K, you have the M, the K and the Y and all of mouse.
Moxie Mouse.
Monkey Mouse.
Monkey Mouse. It's Monkey Mouse.
I honestly I think you should you should start developing your
cartoon monkey mouse right now.
Is he more monkey or more mouse?
Very equal parts. I think he's half and half.
Yeah. Half and half.
Horrifying.
I think he was just in my mind, he was just a mouse with a funny name.
Oh, that's one approach.
Or he could be a gorilla,
a gorilla sized being who is mouse like features
or a mouse sized creature is gorilla like features.
Either a gorilla raised by a by a mouse or a mouse raised by a gorilla.
That's cleaner and less irreverent.
It's kind of like a jungle book, really. Yeah. Right.
So like you think that it's a little mouse that thinks he's big and strine
can like, you know, scream.
That's good. We've talked a lot about trying to, you know, buy IP
like Marvel McFay to start our own theme park.
But maybe it's time we just keep we start coming up with characters.
Maybe Monkey Mouse is the anchor for the new park.
Yeah. Monkey Mouse seems like a winner.
The new PTR park.
It sounds instantly familiar.
It's partially because it has a lot of the same letters as Mickey Mouse. Right.
It's very similar.
And there are two words we know.
It sounds like something where like a child mispronounces Mickey Mouse
and says monkey mouse and then the family that that's the family joke for forever.
They never stop. They never stop talking.
Yes. I know if I had said monkey mouse, yeah.
My mom would never never hit the end of it. Yeah.
The parents end up getting like four stories in 18 years of child rearing.
And then you just cycle around over and over.
They have a set list like a rock band.
You got to play the hits.
And especially if they're around like your wife or girlfriend,
you know, they do the same stories over and over again.
Family Christmas is the same story.
I understand. But telling other people the same story,
do you not get embarrassed by that?
No, when you meet new people, they then get to hear the hits.
Yeah. Well, that's yeah.
You need to have like a set that because for a lot of people, it is the first time.
Yeah. Even though if you're like the tour manager, you're always with them
as we are as our parents, children.
Can we each go around and do one of the greatest hits that our moms tell?
I'll do I would do mine first.
Yeah. When my mother was pregnant with my sister,
she said that, you know, you're going to have like a little baby sister or brother.
And I said, I don't want that.
I want an older brother who paints.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
Yeah, I wanted a painter.
You have features.
You had you had a design and you had features.
You wanted like you were buying a car. Yeah, that's true.
Older brother who paints.
That is what she tells.
All right. This kid idea. Sure. Got it.
But I have some requests.
I think I said like, no, no.
Like I refuse the idea of a younger sibling.
Do you still want an older brother who paints?
It'd be awesome.
He was like a cool painter.
Like I think I was also imagining like a traditional like a beret wearing
Renaissance painter.
This guy might be dead, though.
He might be like, what is the guy gets?
They who do that?
What kills the characters in Moulin Rouge?
It may be dead of some mostly defunct disease.
Consumption. Yeah. Yeah.
Michael, I am dying of consumption.
I want you to have my son accused CDs and my box of condoms
because I'm a cool older brother.
My little brother, the only joy in my life.
I like the idea that he's also like 40 years older than me.
He's not even like 10.
He's like 10 years older.
He looks like Picasso. Yes.
Yeah. The year is gone.
The year is gone. Yeah.
He's a heroin addict.
I like this brother.
Yeah, I want an older brother with a drug addiction who can paint.
It's got you need to.
Mike, Mike, you need to.
You're confused.
Older brother.
You need to get me the absence.
You need to get me the sugar cube and the little spoon.
Six. I don't get my bottle.
I'm very young.
Light the flame, please.
My hands, they don't work from all the painting to see the green fairy.
One last time.
Scott, I don't think I can top that.
The one that I jumped to was when I was really I was a real pain about doing chores.
And there was just one.
I was always mad because my dad always wanted to do yard work when the Nicktoons were on
the like holy block of Rugrats, Doug and Ren and Stimpy.
Right. And there was a lot of leaves that need to be cleaned.
And I think I snapped one day and said, I'm not your slave.
Oh, my God. Classic.
That's a classic.
I hear that, like, you know, once every couple of months, then when that one comes back,
a lot. Right.
But maybe rightfully so.
That's pretty that's pretty good.
Jason. Well, they're really short one.
My I was short when I have a more complicated one.
But the short one is that my bro when they brought my baby brother home
after a little bit of time, like family was visiting or something.
They're like, how do you like having a baby brother?
And I responded, he's such a fussy baby.
Clearly just repeating something I had heard in the house.
Like one of my parents said that and I was just echoing.
Now, the real story that gets told a lot
is my mom and dad went out of town for like a weekend trip.
And my grandmother was watching us and she was making breakfast for us
one Sunday morning and she was frying eggs.
And she leaned over the burner
and lit her bathrobe on fire.
Just like a small patch, like right,
you know, on her like stomach chest kind of area
about the size of like an apple, I would say.
Like and she turns around and she's screaming,
I mean, my brother is screaming and she gets a towel and gets it out real quick.
And we're just like, whoa, whoa.
Like we're all just so freaked out.
And her immediate response is to come over to us and go like,
don't ever tell your mother about us.
Don't ever tell your mother about this.
She'll never let me see you again if that happens.
To two horrifying things a week or two later,
where my whole my mom and dad and my brother and me are sitting around
watching TV and somehow it comes up, you know, that my you know,
you know, no, no, no, no, no.
Here's how it came out.
One of my parents said, like, oh, yeah, that was nice of your mom
to watch the kids last weekend.
Like, yeah, we were worried she was going to burn the house down.
And my brother and I just look at each other and just start wailing,
just start sobbing and just go like,
my mom lit a robe on fire.
And she said not to tell you because then you would let us see her again.
And my parents were just like, God, damn it.
What the hell?
What? Oh, it's fine.
It's OK.
Like they were just like so annoyed.
It's like, why would she tell you the like?
They were like, OK, thank you for telling us.
Yeah, please tell us.
Tell your parents these things. Whoa.
Wow. Long story short, you never saw it.
Thanks for telling us.
Now we know to excise grandma from your life.
Wow.
Wow. Wow.
And she made it so much worse with that.
She made it so much worse.
But also, like, I do have to admire her self-preservation
because like the the robe was still warm and like it left a hole.
Like it left a hole.
It's probably just polyester.
It's probably like went right up.
What happened to Mrs. Doubtfire?
Yeah, basically very similar doubt fire and put out as quickly.
But like we were real young, like I might have been first grade
at my brother's a couple.
He might have been in preschool or something.
So like you don't you don't try to make an arrangement with kids that young.
And I don't think you should ever say like to children,
like, don't ever tell anyone about like that's how many horrific books
and movies start with.
And then an adult told the child, don't tell anyone about this.
Well, this is I sincerely hope your grandma was sent to jail.
Well, she used to be when we were very young, she was kind of like
I we always thought of our grandfather's happy go lucky.
And like she was kind of the strict one.
But then she really mellowed out with with age and she was a lot more
like goofy grandma.
But that was still during like her strict period.
But I don't know why we were pretty easygoing children.
She transformed.
She sort of changed her essence much like a tree petrifying.
It's like a tree petrifying,
petrifying, calming, sturdy rock.
That was a good.
Yeah, that was seamless.
Say all that.
Yes, I think it was a seamless process, much like a tree being petrified,
being mineralized, mineralized, mineralized, becoming the minerals,
not just imprinting on minerals.
Yeah. Well, do we do it?
Is that the answer by walls petrified trees?
I think that's how we all thought it would go.
So, yeah, yeah.
So go next time you're at Disneyland, go check it out.
And I have to check it out.
Yeah, you might do it for the first time.
I sincerely think you will do you will do a very hearty
and listeners go check it out and think about Jason's grandma
lighting herself on fire and it's got you.
Don't tell anyone.
But don't you don't tell those people about never
be allowed to listen to the podcast again.
If you tell the main feed people, don't don't tell.
This is for only the lucky few who are paying for this content.
Pay to keep Jason's family secrets.
We promised to reveal one shared and family secret each.
Don't promise that.
As we do one of them, that's part of the part of the gifts you get with this.
Don't tweet about it.
Don't leave the secret in an iTunes review from OK.
Here's what you're going to do. Tweet it, Jason.
Your secret is safe with me.
Oh, good. Oh, good.
Everyone, please.
That's good. Intriguing advertisement for the second gate.
Yes, you're right.
There's secrets being told.
Now I can get. There we go.
I never missed a chance to.
What's the best way to make it intriguing?
Is it like see like per the Patreon?
Your secret is safe with me.
That's good. That's nice and clear.
Or your secret is safe with me behind the second gate.
Patreon.com slash.
And then put the right link.
You are advertising for us.
Be do you want to be a podcast, the right influencer?
We don't have the money of the Michael Bloomberg campaign.
Well, by the time this comes out, he may have won this.
He may be the nominee.
Rightfully so.
I mean, that's the way it should go.
That's what America chose.
And you can't argue with that.
Well, I guess you survived the podcast, the ride to the second gate stump edition.
Yeah. Remind Jason, your secret is safe with you.
And yes, more secrets to come behind the second gate.
That'll be a permanent fixture from now on.
Yep. Yeah.
Well, we'll do another one soon because we have to.
Yep. Bye bye.