Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, The Second Gate.
I'm Jason Sheridan here with Mike Carlson.
Yep, I'm here.
And Scott Gardner.
Correct.
It's part two of our look at the Imagineering Story, the Disney Plus limited series, I guess you'd call it, six-part documentary.
I think they saw a little discussion of that maybe there's more due to the success of this, seemingly.
I don't know how to measure Disney Plus success because they don't release numbers because streamers all decided they don't release numbers.
Yeah.
It seems like it went over well and there might be an appetite for more of this.
I think so.
I mean, I think they could do deep dives on stuff.
For whatever reason, when Disney Plus was launching, I thought this was 10 episodes and a few episodes in, I was like, wow, they're really going fast.
What are the last few episodes going to be?
I mean, I think if they could piecemeal ride specifically, they could do longer profiles of certain Imagineers.
I mean, I think if they were willing to give us behind the scenes looks at every new thing that comes out, or if they put a new one out in a couple of years,
and then they've documented the making of Runaway Railway or a longer Rise of the Resistance or whatever.
It does feel like they should just use the team to do the lead up, like what they would have done on ABC to promote Runaway Railway 20 years ago.
They might as well just use this team.
Do it this way, because then you get deep dives, you get better footage, it's not just these promotional pieces.
And the newer stuff, obviously, in these documentaries, there's a lot less drama that they reveal.
Yes. Well, that's what I was going to say.
The last three episodes shift from, slowly shift from history, like a look back, and people are a lot more frank and stuff has come out,
and much more to recent history of more like making of.
It shifts a lot more to cruise ads.
Well, yes.
I'm going to go ahead as a complaint I have about the back half.
I don't know. Why don't we, we don't, I feel like the three of us don't care about these cruises at all.
Oh, I have, let me see. Did I write it specifically down in here? Hold on. I think I wrote more cruise stuff.
I have a similar now.
Yeah, I just wrote in all caps, cruise stuff.
I had a friend who was really digging the first few, and then I said, oh, you got to make it to four.
Four is where it gets crazy with all these failures and this in Superstar limo.
And then he wrote me and said, hey, four is pretty good. I could do with less cruise ads though.
Yeah, the cruise thing is very interesting. So yeah, if you don't know what we're talking about, there's part in four, part in five and six.
Maybe.
I think it was just four and five are the ones I remember because the Disney dream is in four.
And then magic is in five. The Disney magic.
You know more than I do, my man. I don't know the names of these ships.
They like cram the, and I guess here's the thing. The cruise is a popular business for them. People go on them. I've never been on them.
I'm not like against going on them, but I think I might be against going on them.
That's any cruise.
That's fair. I mean, I've never been on a cruise.
Yeah, me neither.
So I've been on one. Right. When I was pretty young. Yeah.
But they put so much cruise, like it's so much less interesting. Who gives it like, you know what?
I could have done for one cruise segment. I thought this is the right. Yes. The smokestacks.
Yeah. Okay. You know what? I'll say a nice thing about the cruise too. The segment is I was interested that they build the two halves of the boat.
Yeah. And then they like put them together and like weld them together. And that's how they put the whole boat together. I go, oh, interesting.
And I like that Eisner yelled at them about how it needs to look like a ship.
Yeah. And then you saw the mockups and there was a big duck one. I mean, that's called the mighty duck.
I, the problem, I like that. I go on that boat. I think we might like the mighty. Yeah. I know at that age I would have liked the mighty duck a lot.
Yeah. There's like a giant yellow rubber ducky. There's a giant like Donald Duck in Shanghai Disney. That's like floats in the water. Nice.
That's like really cool. Like it doesn't look quite like that drawing, but it's giant. And I feel like if I could travel on a big duck, I would like to.
I would are like penguins duck vehicle in Batman Returns. Oh, yes. That's very good. Yeah. That's very good. So if it was like that.
Mm hmm. I feel like it would have been that's the kind of thing you would have liked for the first year.
And now they're in year 23 of the giant rubber duck and it might. Yeah. Oh, it would look like shit by now. Yeah, it would look really bad.
It would not have held up well. Whatever. Like the aesthetic that they used to like to design it at the time would have be, it would be wildly out of date.
That's a great segue into episode four, into the projects covered in chapter four hit or miss.
Now, when we were talking about how to discuss the Imagineering series, I do think a way to view this is like in pair.
Like I think one and two, three and four, five and six go well nicely together. They kind of make sense together.
That said, if we had done an episode that ended with episode chapter four hit or miss, boy, it's grim.
Like rewatching it, I was like, oh, this is much grimmer than the first time I watched it.
I'm sure everyone though, because hearing about all that and that they are like open about all of the nonsense and all the failures, it's they could have like just brushed past all this.
And I love that we got like polished documentary with the nicest footage of Superstar Limo. I think that exists. Right.
I mean, as soon as you open, they talk about like anything you do is the potential that you've miscalculated the audience misfires and that they immediately show shots of Disney Quest to the ESPN.
Yeah, thrown under the bus right away. Right away. Yeah. Well, and then those kind of viewed as like, you know, like we used like not that long ago, we were building these like massive sprawling adventure play in Indiana Jones.
And now we built like a building. Here's like a place where there's like a pinball machine with John Madden's head in it or something.
Like if it got so just got dull more than anything, I don't know.
Just like less adventurous and and so like corporate branded time that like ABC.
So now they have to plaster ABC and ESPN on stuff. They redesigned the ABC studios in Times Square, which I know I didn't know.
And Angel Stadium. Yeah.
Has that big rock work feature. Fake Rocks. Angel Stadium.
If you haven't seen an Angels game or been to that stadium, it is fake rocks.
So if you're not a fan of baseball, but you do like fake rocks, you know, you won't hate all of the baseball game you go to.
They did not mention the Encounter, the restaurant in the center of LAX, that weird spidery looking building.
I would have liked to not Encounter.
Because that they imagine years worked on that, too, when they redid it and it was reopened for a little while.
But it's never open anymore. Like it's open for shooting film and television.
But it seems like any any attempt to get it back off the ground as a restaurant.
I've never been there, which is amazing because I like airport hotels and bars and stuff.
And but it's so it's yeah, it's barely open and it's really inconvenient to get to might be the most inconvenient thing in the city.
Yeah, why would you want to go?
I had a reservation one night and then it turned out to be that night that they were trying to stop the ice blockade.
Yeah, shit. Well, my Encounter reservation is ruined.
I guess I'm not having firecracker shrimp tonight or whatever.
Damn you protesters. Think about who you're hurting.
The big thing they kind of point at in this chapter is they filled, you know, Frank Wells is dead.
Eisner had a heart attack and needed to go a little easy for a while.
Geez, that too. And they said they promoted businessmen.
Eisner promoted businessmen. Eisner promoted businessmen to fill voids.
Pressler thrown under the bus. Yeah.
The biggest villain of the series.
I think he kind of is. Yeah.
Now, yeah. So Paul Pressler was promoted out of he ran Disney stores and was a rare case of that kind of person,
a retail merchandise person, then running the creative side of the Disney parks.
And as a California resident and a nerd with no friends who was looking at Disney message boards through the late 90s,
there was no bigger enemy than Paul Pressler. Right.
He was like, truly. I mean, like we'll see some scuttlebutt about JPEG this or people don't like that.
But sure, sure. But I don't think he has nearly the level of fan hate.
Oh, yeah. No, no, no, no. People were so and people used to call Paradise Pier Pressler Pier
because it was like indicative of how lazy the whole area was.
Like this was his dream. This is what he wanted was like off the shelf rides.
They are. This technically rides here. OK, now now by like.
And then he also helped lead seemingly to the merchandise being really boring that for being a merchandise guy,
you would think that he'd want like a crazy variety.
But I remember around that time you'd go into Frontierland, Tomorrowland, Fantasyland, wherever.
And it's just the same shirts that just say Disneyland. Yeah.
The merchandise also got extremely boring and generic. So even his area wasn't fun anymore. Right.
This is a thing I think Universal still needs some help with.
Like you get the same stuff is everywhere. Yeah.
Convenient if you forget something and you want to go back for it.
Scott invented the best like just all this like this is not this is not a merchandise.
It's a food thing. But you invented the drink at Jurassic World with the Mr. DNA sugar.
Oh, yes. Something like that.
Like they don't have like with merchandise and food and beverage, they don't have the vision.
They don't have their Mickey ears. They don't have like right.
Here's this like goofy thing you can put on only when you're here.
I mean, they have the potential because the Harry Potter stuff is so specific and detailed and a lot of it nicely made.
Yeah. That merch is all yeah. The merch. That merch is all.
The Potter stuff is great. I mean, I would argue for I think everyone,
I think America needs to wake up to the Homer slippers where you put your foot inside his mouth.
I think that stands a chance to be as iconic as Mickey.
Here's everyone to walk around the park, dirtying up their yellow slippers.
That's the trouble. I think maybe OK, maybe.
Yeah, you don't want to wear slippers around a theme park. There's so much walking.
So I think they need to develop like a nicer version of the Homer foot.
They need to partner with Converse or Nike or something nice.
And so everyone slips on their shoes.
There should just be like a shoe cubby like when you would go into like a ball pit where you put your shoes.
Man, the shoe cubbies in a long time.
Yeah. You put your shoes in there when you come in and then you put your feet into Homer's mouth and then you go.
That's the only way. Yeah. They got a lot of work to do.
They have to build infrastructure to make. I'm just saying don't sleep on.
I don't own them myself, but they delight me when I see them.
I don't even know exactly what you're talking. I can I can imagine it.
I don't think I've seen the ones where you put your feet in the home.
There's two Homer heads. His mouth is open and you put your feet into his mouth.
That aspect of it, you have two Homer heads. Yeah, that's weird.
Funny in and of itself. It's not like minions or there's multiple of.
There's only one Homer. So you have to buy two Homer faces and stick your feet in two of his mouths.
One of them should be Yankee Herb. That would be better.
Oh, yeah. I mean, the fact that they don't like merch out the Simpsons into oblivion with like weird niche.
I know that's shocking to me that they don't like exploit the first eight or nine years of the Simpsons with merchandise.
Yeah. I mean, they have like I have some of the toys which they have all those characters and I have, you know, yeah.
Hank Scorpio and Gil and everybody.
You like want to wear that big cowboy hat and have the like air blower that Homer has.
And that was that during Wacking Day. I forget why he has those things that they should sell the Wacking Day, Matt, like the club.
They should sell a lightsaber experience for Wacking Day. Yes. A fan man backpack.
That's good. That's good. Yeah. They should sell toy Homer's car.
I don't think they had the Homer, the green car that I loved as a child.
I didn't understand why everyone hated it. It was bad. They played the cucaracha on every horn.
And a horn here, here and here. You never find a horn when you need one. This is awesome.
Lisa Pearls and Marge Pearls. Yes, that seems like a no brainer.
Everyone wants to wear who wouldn't love wearing just big round pearls everywhere.
The closest they've come is the Bort license plate. OK. They do sell a Bort license plate.
That took a little while. It did take a little while. They did not launch with the Bort license plate.
But a Mr. Plow jacket. Yeah. They're making like Chalkaline as a company that makes all these crazy jackets now with properties.
Homer mouths. There should be a big brown bulbous beard line. Terrifying.
Everyone should wear Homer masks everywhere. Yeah.
Remember those realistic when people render a realistic human to look like Homer?
Just have it be like that. Nightmare. That character should be a walk around.
Realistic Homer. Yeah, realistic Homer. They got to up their game. Disney's done it.
Disney's gotten better with the Mer... It was just a supremely boring time.
Very, yeah. I feel. And then Pressler is really shanked at the end when they really like...
Without any commentary, they just say, Paul Pressler left to become CEO of the Gap.
And that tells you everything. There's technically no commentary in there.
Right. But it certainly does tell you the, wow, the man in charge of Disneyland, who in charge of starting the second land of Disneyland, became the CEO of the Gap.
And then I got curious about his time at the Gap and what he did there.
He, of course, started kind of a second gate of the Gap.
As you guys know, everyone say with me, fourth and town. We all remember the Gap's second store, fourth and town.
Wait, was it a store? Yeah. The phrase sounds familiar-ish.
Just because those are words in English language.
It sounds correct in the Banana Republic family of brands. It sounds...
It sounds like Crabtree in Evelyn. It's like something ampersand something. Seems like a store in a mall.
Well, we just haven't thought about fourth and town in so long because it was only open from 2004 to 2007.
And then he was out. He thought of this new Gap brand, immediately failed and then out by no more of that.
And now he's like on the board of directors of some nightmare family of brands venture capital.
Just a legacy of shit. He's never made less than like five million dollars in the last 25 years.
Yes. Yeah. Yeah. The destruction and like a portrayal of destruction in his wake.
It is a shame Robert Forrester is no longer with us because, man, he could have played Paul Prezler.
It's not like as soon as Paul Prezler showed up on screen, I'm like, that's what he looks like?
That's I was just so caught off guard. And also, too, you know, I don't I don't want to speak for Irvine and Baxter.
They're very professional, but you can just tell they're furious that they're not happy.
Yeah. Paul Prezler still. Imagine having to start a theme park under those circumstances where the like we, you know,
we covered the monotony of downtown Disney for so long and that downtown Disney cost like as much as they were allotted for the theme park.
Yeah. So stupid. And they built a very nice hotel. But even though it's hell feels like kind of like fakey, it's like nice to me.
But it's not like it doesn't feel like this. Like it's not the level of Grand Floridian. Nice.
And it's like detail and molding. There's pieces of it that I like a lot. But then there are some. I like it.
I like it. Yeah. I think the outside still looks sort of like it looks like California Adventure Cheapo, which we get into here in a very interesting run.
You get to hear, I believe the imagineers, Kevin Rafferty, who's later responsible for Cars Land, and you get to hear him just music to my ears,
just breaking down what sucks about early California. Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Is that what's just all stucco and cheat that Golden Gate Bridge was bad. The idea of the Golden Gate Bridge being your entry point and where the monorail goes through.
Great. That was not a good Golden Gate Bridge. It looked like Legos.
And in my favorite snippet of maybe the whole series, when he says then the icon of the park is a big gold sun, like a metallic sun that could be at a mall in Newport Beach.
Why is it in our theme park? I don't like a sailing malls in Newport Beach. Fashion Island is a wonderful place.
But but yeah, truly that completely and to hear that from the guy who built what is now the icon of California Adventure and why you love California Adventure in this wonderful, detailed, incredible land to be in.
What's so interesting there? I think there's a couple reasons. Obviously, it's a it's it's fact that this was a failure because they fixed California Adventure for the most part.
And you really want to build up how dire it was before the hero shows up, the hero CEO shows up.
Yes. So I think because of that, yeah, because of that, this section of all, like almost not of all, but like this section, I feel like there could be six episodes on California Adventure.
Yes, please. Justin, like if they're willing to trash it and throw like press under the bus and whatever, let's get it.
Because all the Imagineers you could tell are just dying to complain about what the situation is.
Any SNL book, any SNL oral history, clearly the most interesting part are those bad, say the Rod Denny Jr. year, the first Eddie Murphy year that didn't work, the Gene Dominion year, the fall apart years are always.
And that like Disney has that Disney has like a maze. This is definitely the Anthony Michael Hall era of Disney parks.
Just years, years of everyone being frustrated and just put the camera in front of all the people that still work there, whoever they can get. And man, would that be a good series?
Yeah, that would be the best.
This is I feel like this is the last bit in the documentary because you're at a 20 year distance, but it starts to slide into recent history.
And I feel like people are less critical of recent history. One, there's less perspective to a lot of people still alive. But this is far enough. It's far enough away. It was a big enough kerfuffle.
Everyone agrees. Everyone agrees.
There's no like other viewpoint on this.
The combination of the smaller part of DCA, Disney Studios Paris and Hong Kong, where they're like, we build smaller parks now and everyone's like, this is not as good. What did you do?
It's so dreadful when Angela Bassett says that this strategy had failed for a third time. Man, and that's like darker than you'd think they would frame it.
Yeah.
Yeah, I swear though, it's only the reason is because they need to get it in the narrative to be at the lowest possible point for the hero to swoop in.
And then he comes in.
Yeah, they're the villains, but they're also the heroes, which is what they, I don't know, is interesting about this whole series. It's like one hand of Disney is the hero and one hand is the villain.
We said in the last episode that we were comparing the imaginary story to Boogie Nights.
Yeah.
And I, the way it's slotted kind of like before the dawn, when it's dark as before the dawn, I think especially the footage of Superstar Limo is like when Dirk Diggler is like jerking off in the car and somebody's watching him and then he gets beaten up.
And then like, well, Don Shields got blood on his face from the robbery. And do I take the money? And like, this is, this is the grid. This is everyone's meltdown happening at the same time.
Mm hmm.
It's a Superstar Limo is a sad car jerk off.
Paul Prezler throwing fireworks in meetings, like setting up little fireworks.
Who's that weird little guy? He's from the Gap. Don't worry about him.
Don't worry about him.
Yeah. Ah, I fucking love this song.
I wonder if they even, they, I, you know, they probably don't. I should, I answering my own question is I think it, there were like safety problems. That's a minor way of putting it during the Pressler era.
Yeah.
And I was like, I wonder if they're going to even go here. They obviously did not.
No.
Why would they? But like still like, that's how bad it got is like maintenance issues killed people.
Yeah.
In the grimace ways. I don't think we revel in like, let's talk about the deaths.
No, no.
This was bad. This was very like other Disney deaths had felt more accidental and that guy just didn't listen to the instructions and he flew out of the thing. This was like, this was bad.
And for sure due to budget cuts.
Yeah. And like what I understand is like, like a budget cuts of like, well, we're going to let it go completely broken.
Something has to like break before we fully fix it as opposed to like, that's a little wear on that. We may want to replace this.
I don't think any of us are desiring to talk about it.
No, I don't.
It's the Columbia thing and there was a big thunder thing.
Yeah.
That was later I guess. But Columbia was truly like, everyone look it up on your own. Don't make us be sad.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We don't want to do that.
It's really bad.
A lot of Disney getting dragged, I think in this one publicly. I mean, historian David McCullough dragging Disney when they, because they briefly touch on Disney's America.
Yeah.
Well, just again, they just didn't have the guy who handled that. They didn't have Wells, who probably could have navigated that.
That's so interesting that Eisner says if Wells was alive and I was healthy, we would have just done it.
We would have plowed through.
Plowed through. Yeah.
Yeah.
That's interesting.
Wow. If people don't have this thing memorized or haven't watched it twice. Yeah. He had a, Eisner had a quadruple bypass. It's a crazy.
I forgot about that.
No, not really. No. And that's, wow. Without that, a death and a, this is kind of a grim, crazy story. Without a death and a quadruple bypass, they could have taken over a bunch of Civil War battlefields.
Yeah.
Built a park that probably would be like weird and unpopular now.
With a roller coaster that made you feel like you were in like World War II planes. Was that the idea? Or like.
Something like that.
That's what they say in it. I think it was World War II. There's like, there's a dueling coaster with World War II planes.
We really got to do, we're way over doing it in America.
I, yeah.
I, my parents, I think dad remembers, he's like, yeah, I remember it was in the newspaper. We're like, oh great. Disney, Disney Park two hours away, a drive as opposed to a two hour flight. How convenient.
That would have shaped your middle school and you might be working there now. You'd be like a blacksmith.
I could be a congressperson. I was so inspired.
Right. Yeah. You were, you were in the Trump administration now because you love America so purely.
I'm the head of HUD.
I did, now one things I know it had, where it was going to have, that are kind of shown in this, there's a Lewis and Clark raft ride.
Yes. Yes.
And an industrial revolution mine car. Like you're going through a factory or something.
I mean, I do want this. Obviously we want this to be built still.
Yeah. Maybe there's a chance. Well, there was, and then there was the weird that they were going to buy a Knott's Berry farm and reuse some of these ideas.
Right.
And make that the overarching theme.
We don't want that to happen.
It would have also, it's not really talked about in this, but I think it's very possible that Soarin could have ended up in that park originally.
For sure.
Which they frame in the California adventure stuff. Like that's the one thing. It's a, we can all admit they got Soarin right.
So it really could have elevated Disney's America too.
Yeah.
Made it completely work.
So nice that, yes. So that's one of the nice things in this chapter. Soarin, they really give, do a thorough talk about Soarin and Animal Kingdom.
Yeah.
This is the first Joe wrote. Joe wrote. He gets a lot of time in this and later on.
I was just going to real quickly. I love it that they were just getting like political cartoons.
Like in every newspaper.
And they're like, he was like, we, I was like, we were getting hammered every day.
And then like fat mouse.
Like a big loaded mouse with a cigar.
Isner seeing these on his desk every day.
Oh god.
It's the one Mickey Mouse.
The one I remember was Mickey Mouse meeting Lincoln and Lincoln going, where's Grant when you need him.
And it's like, do you mean that Grant would do an assault on the Disney core six?
Is that what you were implying?
Whoa.
Where's Sherman to burn down his company?
Isner in these interviews, correct me if I, he seems like he could play kind of a mob boss in a movie in his older age.
He's got the voice and the gravitas.
And then when he says like, we would have just pushed through it.
Like I was like, Ooh, this guy's this guy, he's got a whole new demeanor now in his older age.
Yeah.
So you're saying he, we know he has acting ability.
When does he start showing up in Irishman type?
That is what I'm, yeah.
Is a heavy.
We're a softy brothers, you know, one of their unconventional castings.
Yes.
We know they're good at like bringing unexpected people.
Yeah.
Who do we know that's making things?
Put Michael Isner in a Michael Isner in it.
Um, I mean we want to be making things.
We had Charles.
Oh yeah.
Let's get him in search party.
Yeah.
Put it in a serious part.
Isner in a serious role.
Like a chilling.
Yeah.
All right.
Well you all have your own.
We named us the one person we can name.
Charles.
Who's making anything?
Charles, help us.
Charles, please.
Please.
It's not even for us.
It's for this old man who doesn't know we're getting him.
It's going to be so good.
Get him an Emmy.
Get him best actor.
Well, let him beat Alec Baldwin and best guest actor at the Emmys next year.
He has like $10,000 hours behind the camera.
Lauren too.
Hey, why not?
We know people at SNL.
He should.
Oh yeah.
I mean like we need like another guy to like a Bob Barr.
The next sort of like new figure who rises in impeachment world should be played by Michael
Isner.
Yeah.
I think that's good.
That's the next cameo.
Audience freaks out.
Yeah.
He'll kill it.
Wow.
That's a great idea.
Yeah.
Muller comes back if De Niro's tired.
Put the wig in the eyebrows of Isner.
It's time.
Wow.
But yeah, Rhodey shows up in this in his kind of first appearance, like sort of like walking
through Animal Kingdom in a bright yellow hat and shirt.
And this also feels very cinematic, like the appearance of some, some new character oddity
and like, what do you mean?
Like that weirdo in the back is going to be part of like getting the ship back on track.
Yeah.
Wait, wait, wait.
No, no, no, no.
Let's listen to him.
The weird, he's a freak.
No, no, no.
But he might have some good ideas.
He's got a funny mustache.
No one with a funny mustache is a good idea.
It shows he's willing to think outside of the box.
Yeah, you're right.
And he didn't think outside of the box.
It's funny how Animal Kingdom is framed as this like scrappy.
Yeah.
Like it's against, against, I mean, there was obviously like problems when they were
opening it and the animals and stuff, but also like just in conception.
It's like, oh, we don't, who knows if this will work.
He almost describes it as like a toss of like Michael Eisner saying, what's the quote?
We have the magic kingdom.
We should have the animal kingdom.
And it's like, well, yeah, that's turned out right.
That turned out good.
Yeah, that was a good idea.
And then he was, it's up to him to figure out what does that mean?
What is, what is the Animal Kingdom park?
And now you've got the narrative of we recruited the experts onto our side.
This time the experts are ours.
We bought Jane Goodall.
Jane Goodall vouching for them.
They touch on, I think they show a clip of some otters and one of the protesters explaining
that animals had died.
I believe if memory serves what happened was they put different types of plants in the
otter habitat, one of which was they should not have put there because it was poisonous
to them.
But it was such chaos.
I mean, they describe that area as part, what was it?
Part swamp, part sinkhole, part cow pasture that they had to turn into animal kingdom
that they had to turn into lush savannas and different habitats.
And yeah.
And then they, yeah.
So Jane Goodall was always like, I'm so curious with the Goodall Disney relationship because
like it seems like she was involved early.
Yeah.
But like, but as, yeah, what, what, I guess you just pay her enough money and she comes
in and is like, they're trying their best.
Well then that's like sort of her vibe where she's like, they were trying.
They weren't trying to harm animals.
Right.
Yeah.
They didn't have, she's like, some zoos shouldn't exist and some zoos they're trying.
They, they credit her with saying like that.
She said that the animals should have a nice place to live.
Disney's like, I hadn't thought about that.
Huh.
All right, fine.
Okay.
A place to live, eh?
We were just going to have them in a cage, a tiny cage.
Food, eh?
Huh.
Okay.
So she helped.
So she helped and then she helped here with the spin, the PR spin.
She's still helping.
Yeah.
And check out Disney nature and Nat Geo, one of the pluses on Disney Plus.
I have not, I always read like, not that she's like Mother Teresa, but you always read like,
oh, you know, Mother Teresa wasn't, she had bad stuff.
And like, I wonder if there's a whole like ex-Bezan Jane Goodall.
There might be.
Maybe.
No one's perfect.
Everyone's human.
Well, that's true.
I mean, I didn't, like personal issues were, you know.
Oh, okay.
I'm just, I don't know.
She yelled at people.
She threw stuff at them.
She was mean.
She was mean to a monkey.
Shut up, Coco.
Stop talking.
Did she know Coco?
Probably just in passing.
Okay.
Sign language gorilla.
They acknowledge each other at a party, but they weren't like best buds or anything.
Yeah.
They would see each other backstage at stuff.
Did we talk about, did we talk about on the show where like people are saying like the
Coco thing was fake?
Coco didn't really know sign language.
I think that's Eva's a big proponent of like that is a fraud.
Coco is fake.
Is that a conspiracy theory?
Is that like the Stevie wonder isn't blind conspiracy theory?
I don't know.
I'm just asking.
I'm just asking questions here.
We're just asking questions, folks.
I don't have answers for you.
You can't put limits on that.
This is America.
Okay.
You can ask whatever question you want.
Was Coco a fraud?
Why didn't they build a berm at DC?
Why did they leave it so you could see active city streets?
We'll never know.
If you have the answer to these questions, let us know.
Hey, sorry we messed up about Y2K.
Remember that?
Oh my God.
People are mad at us.
We don't know what we're we don't know about anything that isn't berms and stuff.
I what do you want from us?
I qualified if I say I don't know what I'm talking about.
So I think we were not trying to be a historical.
I think we were just talking about our personal experiences as adolescents and, you know,
people's memory in the popular conscious.
Yeah, I said like people like parents I knew who were working on in the computer field
like had to do a lot of work for it.
Sure.
Yes.
Well, you know what?
Actually, I still think it's a hoax.
Yeah.
No.
And a good evidence, you know, and if that was a hoax, then is it possible global warming
could be too.
I'm just asking questions.
Yeah, we're asking questions.
You can't limit our ability to do that.
I can't put handcuffs on our amounts.
No, no, we could say whatever we want, especially behind this.
Delicious paywall.
Sure can.
Yes.
We can live it up back here.
We can live it up back here with our bad opinions.
Jane Goodall killed Coco.
She orchestrated the whole conspiracy that Coco could talk with sign language.
She planned it out.
Bring down a pig.
When Coco when it was revealed, then she took Coco out.
She took Coco out for good.
And she's been on the Disney payroll.
Take the shot.
But everything Mike just said, including that quote, had a question mark on the end
because we're just asking questions, just asking questions.
Is the earth flat?
Take the shot.
She was just asking questions to just asking questions.
So anyway, I don't you get to watch Jorodi looking at a roof like a tin roof.
He's pointing at it and saying, like, when you look at this roof, there's a message about
ingenuity, there's a message about economics.
And you're looking at like some tin and then more tin.
And of course, it's well-themed and it's wonderful.
But as he's saying all the things that there's a message about in the roof, I was like,
what does this remind me of?
And it took me a minute. And then I was like, oh, Jordan Schlansky, Conan's producer,
who they go wine tasting.
Yes. And he has so many thoughts about what's in every sip.
And Conan is like, eat your mush.
There's definitely some crossover there.
When Conan's taking them house shopping or when they're looking for houses, when he
moves to Los Angeles for the Tonight Show, that's one of my favorites, because he's
talking about what he's looking for in a home and he's talking about like a certain
energy that he's looking for and like certain like vibrance, I don't know, specific
vibrancy or whatever.
And Conan goes, oh, you mean windows?
You're looking for windows.
OK, why didn't you just say windows?
Yes. Very good.
There's a Jordan Sienzki bit with our friend Nick Mundy if the audience hasn't seen
it. And Mundy bled for the pee.
If you look closely, he smashed a beer can against his forehead.
Yeah, I would have said he bit.
He bit the can with his teeth.
Yes, and he bled.
There's two. There's a male and female stripper in the sketch.
Mundy bites a beer can.
It's all in and it's all in Schlansky's office.
It all takes place in Jordan's office.
Oh, no. If you ever if you were so mad at Mundy, you wanted to watch him bleed.
He did. Does he bleed from him?
It hits his head. Is it from the forehead?
I don't know. I actually didn't know that he was bleeding.
I've seen it, but I didn't notice the blood.
I think they mostly cut out the blood.
They did not want him from the audience.
Mundy bites into the can and Conan, I think, is just legitimately shocked.
Like, oh, God, I think he does like a thing where he goes, oh, like he there's this
noise that comes out of him because he's like scared because that's like a dangerous thing to do.
Yeah. And like, I assume Mundy hadn't been doing that maybe since college.
So maybe he's not even in the best.
Like, I'm just saying he probably didn't want him like 20 a night
when he was in real good bite and.
Yeah. But but yeah, maybe.
I don't know. Back in the saddle.
But, you know, back in the bicycle.
Turn the TV, turn the TV cameras on.
You got to do it.
Old habits die hard.
Where he buttons this episode to with
imaginary as a place is very frustrating for business minded people.
Oh, I love all that. Yeah.
Yeah. And that's a good.
That's a good explanation of just creativity and business
working against each other.
And they I thought this was a nice visual of like the big painting
that had angry Mickey pointing at like happy go lucky Mickey.
Like as he's saying that, like.
Yeah, yeah.
Of course, then this rolls over into
the next one with the business minded person.
Who's a hero?
Who's the superhero?
Are we dead? Wait, before we move on.
I got a couple of things from four.
So the well, because I'm just my list is just like you get to see
when you get to see Tokyo, Disney, see shit in progress, like half mug.
Like human like people pushing around
mock up 20,000 leagues vehicles.
And like now that they're all my friends, now that I'm seeing
like a not built aquatopia, like a not finished aquatopia car
spinning around and the lava monster lava, my good friend.
I oh, God, you got to get to Disney.
You got to do it. I mean, yeah.
Get there. Everyone listening, go that you go there.
You got to go there, Jason. You got to go to Japan.
Yeah, but I'm going to take a bath on like Olympics year pricing.
If I go in 2020, maybe, yeah, I guess you could.
Yeah, but I want to go in 2020.
Yeah, maybe after I think you can get a deal.
There's a clip. Somebody this is not my own thought.
Somebody pointed this out
online that they think there's some generic roadie footage
at the end of him just like looking through.
There's a roller coaster.
I was thinking the same thing.
And people people are speculating like this is roadies tomorrow.
Yes, because he he physically picks up
the Carousel of Progress building.
Yes. And moves it away.
It looks at the land like, hmm. Yes.
Yeah, I didn't catch that second watch.
I'm so glad you brought this up.
This is a like this is a.
I couldn't figure out that because there was a big black roller
coaster track that looked like an internal like an inside roller.
It looks like rock and roller. It does.
And I was comparing it to Tron. Is it Tron?
I don't think it's Tron. It's not Tron.
For sure. Something else.
Well, this is there's been working on Marvel a little.
He's not. But that Marvel.
There's some I don't think that's could be because if he's doing
a little bit of Marvel, that's not the rock and roller is becoming.
He's not the head of Marvel anymore.
He was the head of the Marvel project.
But then that's somebody else now. OK.
I know that. But do we think he's doing tomorrow?
That's a rumor. I have heard.
Oh, I've heard that for a few.
Rumor around D23 was that he had been spotted for like two hours
walking along the people mover track in Anaheim.
That was how because he doesn't have the panel was going to end.
The panel just ended on right.
Was the cruise ship while there was? Yes, there were.
Yeah, there were Brian Cornell.
We know tomorrow and redo tomorrow and redo has been coming in some form.
It needs to be coming for a few years.
But the rumor is roadie.
He doesn't have a major project that we know because I throw bridges
the head of all the Star Wars stuff.
Well, he has an island.
Oh, yeah, that's true.
He announced that at the 23.
Yes, he has a roadies island.
But yeah, I there's been so many rumors.
I can't even keep them all straight.
But I've heard a rumor that they they just demolish all of Tomorrowland
in the end, including redo redo Space Mountain.
Sure. I'll take anything.
Anything you got. Great.
Which I would say I would sacrifice Star Tours for.
I don't want Star Tours to go away for nothing.
Yeah. But for some like toss together, you know, it's the I don't know
what they're they're promoting.
It's a lady in the tramp simulator now.
But like as long as it's not some shit like I would let all of tomorrow
all of Tomorrowland.
I'll say this, and I've gone back and forth on this a lot over the years,
but I think my current thinking is that Autopia and the subs got to go.
Yeah, of course. The future.
I mean, we we face an existential threat with climate change.
And if you're doing a land about tomorrow, about the future,
you cannot have gas guzzlers and a giant water sink.
Well, that's really is cars that exist in the world.
Millions of gallons of water just stagnant and used.
Like you can't have those.
Well, sure.
I mean, I know it's always like Tony Baxter talks about, you know,
it's your first time in driving a car and there's moments people have memories.
There's a better way.
There's got to be a better way.
You can replace them with like equally interesting,
the transformative children ride thing.
There's no reason that that has to be completely.
This whole documentary is about Walt was was bold and did big, bold things,
took big, bold swings.
I think what will be the first to blow up the Autopia?
I think that's right.
Kill it. Blow it up.
Is it possible?
Ash, is it possible that track is a new track for Tomorrowland?
Is that for Space Mountain?
Maybe. Is that possible?
Boy, I because I think what I think what's happened,
what I've read is at least like the people mover track and everything
is so intertwined with the land that there'd be so much construct.
Like you would have to at the very least,
Space Mountain would have to go down for a long time while they cleared track out
and like change the infrastructure around.
Wow. So is there just a chance of what we may as well just like redo it
completely, make a cool space?
Is it possible? Yes.
Make it more like Paris.
Is it possible that's a new space mountain?
It is. Please, please.
But I think the Anaheim Space Mountain, I don't know that it needs it.
It's the Florida Space Mountain needs some fixing.
And I could see after Tron opens them like fixing that track because that's
rough. I don't think I don't think though that the tomorrow
they don't feel like Florida's Tomorrowland is as big of a priority.
I don't think it's not because I think it's got stuff people like.
Yeah. And I think it eats people.
And I think, yeah, I think you'll probably you'll probably have to get
to the other side of the 50th anniversary of Disney World
for them to even consider putting their space mountain down.
Like, yeah, like I think that that has to run the whole year.
OK, sure. Not longer. Yeah.
But they can now that they have Galaxy's Edge open, like so capacity isn't the same.
People have plenty of places to go. Yes.
They could just say Tomorrowland is closed for three years.
I mean, that's what we all kind of were hoping.
Yeah. What's going to happen?
Yeah, I don't know. Jim Hill on the newest podcast.
You listen to the new ones. There's pretty behind.
Yeah. But I swear, Jim Jim claims Marvel's the e-tickets opening
in like twenty one twenty one, which I'm skeptical of.
That seems too fast.
Because I think in the last episode, I said there's no way that's coming soon.
And then he said, I swear, twenty twenty one.
Have they broken ground?
I don't think so. Yeah.
But I don't know.
So, yeah, but with Marvel and open with Galaxy's Edge open.
Yes. Tomorrow shut all of Tomorrowland down.
But they just put up a new sign or they put up a new sign.
They're going to redo the like landscaping there.
And they just put up a reflective wall.
I haven't seen this.
We did the wall by shiny.
Yeah. OK.
Which has always looked like kind of like that.
Yeah, I didn't understand.
That was a big deal. Yeah.
Somebody yell is now mad at us for saying.
Instagrammable now.
Is it more Instagrammable now?
No, maybe. Maybe.
But it's always they're doing those little things.
They're getting rid of those rocks.
I feel the seeds of it.
And I think it's coming.
Yeah. So I think Jim, the carousel progress thing.
Yes. Yeah.
Nothing I would rather say than watching that building just get removed.
Literally, Joe Rody himself picks it up and throws it in the trash.
Do something. Anything.
It's time. Let's do it. I've read.
So, yeah, real quick, I've just I've read versions where it's like Tron.
Tron is sort of the thing that gets you into Tomorrowland.
It's a different version of the Tron track.
OK, they keep Space Mountain as kind of as is, I think.
Maybe they have to shut it down for infrastructure.
People have speculated of putting you could like put a flight of passage
style thing over where the. Sure.
Where a thousand trees and just have every just make it the green future
and just the glowing, the colored lights of the Tron built perfect.
Yeah, it's great.
And there's no reason you don't have to do it as Avatar.
You can do it as a new thing.
Like a new thing. If it's a tech now, if you just want to clone it,
at least make it like a different ride thing.
Yeah. Timekeeper bring timekeeper back.
Bring the timekeeper or the eagle, the same eagle from America Sings.
You fly behind, fly behind him while he sings Polly Wally Doodle.
Jason's favorite song.
I need a minute.
CGI Polly Wally Doodle.
Just bliss out. We'll cut out the bliss.
Polly Wally Doodle 2.0.
Camp town races.
Remix my Diplo.
And then, yeah, so Star Tours goes away.
Buzz Lightyear goes away. Sure.
It's just it's just you can't even get into it for two years.
You can't just I think is the plan. Let's do it.
I sign off. We sign off.
Yeah. Future Eisner helpers as we establish.
Go even further with like Mike.
Mike, the Star Wars food of like plant based stuff and Boba bubble thing.
Like make it like and what they're doing.
What seems like they're doing in Epcot, which I like a lot.
And they need to do in parks and general more multi level
like spaces to hang out.
Yeah. Yeah.
Like like like the castle in Shanghai, which comes up.
Yes. I didn't actually realize that until watching this.
I don't think I did either. There's like four stories.
Yeah. Yeah. But like a couple different like literal like Tomorrowland Terrace.
Make it a terrace that's above.
And you can sit there and have a meal and watch lights and fireworks.
Go up there because there used to be a ride on level three.
Another ride on level two. Right.
Now is now you can't go anywhere. Yes.
So I am assuming, you know, they know that that's cool.
So they'll do that. But I feel I love hearing this roadie stuff.
This is great, too. Yeah.
I wish there was a little more than in Galaxy's Edge.
I wish there was a second level somewhere you could sit and just kind of enjoy
look out over the atmosphere.
Yeah. You get kind of elevated above the Falcon like that outside of docking bay.
Yeah, that's true. There's some like tears, but a little more.
A little more.
I mean, speaking of like finding out little Easter egg things.
OK, so Tony pitches Westcott, but it's going to cost three billion dollars.
And it's this it's this sad thing for his career that doesn't happen.
But then there's a meeting and then what are we going to do?
Let's figure out some new concepts and California adventure comes out of that.
I did a little freeze frame in that section and you can see cards indicating.
Yes, I did this to do the same thing.
It seems to be like cities of America.
There's like a Nashville.
It says Nashville, San Francisco, San Francisco.
We all notice this Yosemite, New Orleans.
There's going to be like all the big pieces of culture.
That's an interesting park idea.
That's not a bad park.
Not a bad park.
I mean, they have a see of like New Orleans Square and Disneyland.
They've done a little of like that.
Did you see what one of those index cards on the other side of the board said?
I think I know what you're going for, but play.
Oh, no, I didn't notice.
Oh, did it just say play?
It just said play.
And I was like, you got to be shit.
You got to be.
That's been I think the idea of play has been to me.
It went by so quickly.
And I was like, oh, that yes, stuff never goes away, huh?
What I saw was Chicago gangster shootout.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
And we get our crime stoppers finally.
Yeah. Yeah.
And we're going to go to sing sing.
We have a guy who could work on it.
Reddit, Ted, Ted.
We know a perfectly castable person.
They ever bring this around.
And there's and there's another I feel like there's another one of these later,
like a little freeze frame there.
Or maybe maybe I was thinking of the ready thing.
But what else and for I mean, I we slowed you down, Jason.
Oh, no, I was just coming.
Oh, you know what? They didn't mention all of this.
They talked about the cruise line so much.
They did not mention the phrase that sticks in my head.
The big red boat.
Oh, yeah. It's free.
I mean, that was wrapped up by like the early 90s.
But Disney had the licensing deal.
I think they had two ships in a fleet operated by a now defunct cruise line.
And in the early, early Disney parades, I remember watching as a kid,
they would always be like, come to Disney World, then take the big red boat.
Yeah. And yeah, I think the guys there was the one who's just like,
let's just make our own cruise line.
But they just keep expanding.
Yeah. Yeah. Which has been nothing but a money printer for them.
Pretty much.
Do we tell is this in my my notes are too far away to read.
Was this where Eisner defends himself?
I think it's in four could be always where financial limitations.
Well, he says he says, you know, he acknowledges that people don't like
they can complain about the parks, but he says like Disney was never he's like,
you never want to put in jeopardy the institution.
And he says at the very least he never put the company at risk.
After 1983, very dramatic.
Yes. He's never going to not be a Disney company.
That's I think where I really felt like he was at his most mobbiest, his mob
bossiest. Yeah. Where he's like, but you listen to me.
I never put the company in danger.
I protected the family.
Let me tell you something.
Orlando, the greatest city in the world, the greatest city in the fucking world
is my city. I'm Michael fucking Eisner.
He's the god of you.
You got your no show jobs.
OK, you got your no show jobs.
What do you want?
You got 20 no show jobs for you wanted to ride with a little more fucking character.
Is that what you wanted?
You don't think Cindy Crawford is a good character?
Well, fuck you. Fuck you.
Should have bought more coffee mugs.
Asshole. We could have built more.
Drew Carey is funny.
Go fuck yourself. Watch the show.
Then you'll like to ride more.
Melanie Good, young Dakota.
You should have seen Dakota's face looking at her mom, Melanie's role bit.
I thought that was the that was the prettiest damn sight she ever saw.
Made her want to be an actress, too.
And she's a big star, make a big bucks.
I did that. Me.
I protected a family.
Something I was thinking about watching this again, thinking about the competition.
I was wondering this isn't a perfect one to one comparison.
But the Disney this era of Disney were like,
was this the episode?
Maybe it was the previous one where Marley Marty's Claris got like people would go
to lunch together and the Disney sea people would have unlimited money.
And the California adventure people would have a very tight budget.
And I wonder if the mid 2000s at Universal will be looked back in a similar fashion
because you had a run of those screen based Simpsons, Kong, Fast and Furious.
And that's all happening.
And then the Harry Potter division just gets unlimited money to do the most detail
rich like like work.
And I know some of that universal was like, well, let's put in the studio tour
and then we'll expand it to a bigger ride in Florida.
But it did feel very similar of like, well, there's the expensive version of this.
And then there's the kind of like quickie cheaper version of that.
Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, I've said it many times how insane
it is that California adventure is happening at the same time as Disney.
And seeing that illustrated, just like like what an unbelievable just like a
world beautifying project they're doing in Tokyo and then cutting and then intercutting
with like there's a really sad shot of like they're finishing the Hollywood area
of California Adventure and there's tarps over everything just kind of like flapping.
And then there's that milkshake with star sunglasses.
That's often like after you've just learned about like, yeah.
So we had seven cannons propelling smoke and fire into the air out of the volcano
and LED lights lighting up the lava and then a fucking milkshake with sunglasses.
And the other
that shit.
Oh, yeah.
It's really depressing.
It'd be like in the 90s, if like a writer from one of the Seinfeld rooms went to
lunch with someone on the single guy, like right.
How's things at the single house?
Things at Boston Commons.
I can't.
It's sort of like like if I like that, there's these like
lights in dark times.
It's like, you know,
Disney is like John Lovitz being on the worst season of SNL.
There's one good thing.
You see equals John Lovitz and the cruise lines equal Dennis Miller weekend update.
There were two things that worked in an otherwise dreadful time.
Right.
It's a good way to think of it.
Hong Kong Disneyland equals Randy Quaid.
That's like a neutral.
I don't know.
It's all good.
Disneyland.
It's kind of that didn't work initially.
Just people were just for a long time.
I think it took some saving.
That kind of works on paper like Randy.
Right. Like Randy Quaid on SNL works on paper.
You would think it would be a slam dunk, but it's not.
There was some thought.
There was some thought there because they got the Feng Shui
Feng Shui consultant.
And they changed the entry.
Like, I thought that was very interesting.
I like that it was like, you're about all the water.
No water. We can't have water.
One Feng Shui guy says, how about some water?
OK, let's go to water.
You're going to have problems.
Of course, the bench is sinking into the cement.
Very similar.
Again, history repeating itself.
Boy, they really drive home.
I mean, we know this, but like the drive home,
like these people that, you know, go and work in this country, like a country for years.
I mean, Tony did it.
So many of these people go over to this country and like just devote their life
to opening this park. Yeah.
And like, especially with something when it's like ends up being overwhelming
and underwhelming, it's got to be just so bitter.
It's so like draining.
I love when Tom Morris, the Imagineer, says that they were considering a done in flats,
small world style castle, that the castle wasn't going to be three dimensional.
That is wild.
Such a that really illustrates that I'd never heard that fact.
And the mock up they show is pretty chilling.
They really I get this is another thing where like there's so much stuff here
for the Imagineers to pitch about.
Yeah. Yeah.
I just want more of it.
Yeah, truly.
I also how Shakespearean is it that Roy Disney brings Eisner in?
Yes. And then shanks him 20 years later.
He's the very person he has to do it against him.
Well, it's like I don't want to spoil too much about Irishmen.
But, you know, Frank has to do the job to his best friend.
You know, this is sort of who else do you want to do?
You know, that's actually the perfect.
Get so close. Right.
I hear you paint flat castles.
Do you want to be a part of this history?
Yeah. I mean, that's a I'm trying to think.
Of course, he has that a lot in his movies
where like the guy's best friend has got to kill him and not their best friends.
But obviously thought highly of him to make him the CEO.
And then the opening of Hong Kong with Eisner on stage next to Iger,
sharpening his knife, sharpening.
So, well, yeah, now the hero, a hero rises.
Yes.
Yeah. Let's start.
Chapter five is called a carousel of progress.
And the description I saw in the app under Bob Iger's leadership,
the Imagineers begin a creative renaissance, plussing parks worldwide.
You're giving away the game too much.
You're giving away.
Well, I mean, they want it.
Look, they wanted this all to get approved.
That's true.
And in and in like, you know,
I think like sad victims of this zone, especially when they're going through.
OK, so Pixar is killing it, but the Disney movies flop after flop.
And then Emperor's New Groove is in there.
And you're like, hey, what?
Yeah, like that.
Why is that? What a diss of Emperor's New Groove,
which you can watch elsewhere on this streaming service.
They again, they just need to.
You just want it to be like the companies at its lowest.
They just have to present it that there's nothing cool going on.
Yeah. Yeah.
And then which was true.
I don't dispute that. No, no, it's all exaggerated.
Certainly. That's what I'm saying.
Perfect hero, Eiger, who himself has the physique of like of a superhero.
He looks like he could play like an older Superman.
I have somebody who's like, oh, he looks like James Bond.
He we let's revive our discussion of can CEOs get it?
Well, I mean, the thing I figured out watching Eisner and Eiger this back to back,
I was like, I think one of the I think Eisner just has a warmer voice,
like a friendlier way of speak and more endearing way of speaking and more casual
and is better style.
Yeah. Here's a robot.
Yeah. And I think Eiger just a little more
stiff, a little more polished.
And I think Eisner just seemed a little more human.
I think you have to let's be on a technical basis here, just like standards of beauty.
We were praising the looks of Card Walker and Ron Miller.
Right. I think Eiger is a more attractive man.
He is.
Well, you don't get that magnetism.
He doesn't have the he doesn't have the style yet.
He figured the style out, I think, a little later, too.
When you see him like coming on stage here, it's like you can see he's handsome.
But I don't think he's got his dress down.
I don't think he's got the suit.
The suit doesn't look I know it's also the style of suit at the time.
And I think Eiger, his hair got a lot better.
That's what I'm saying.
I mean, it is queer, I ask, like bringing out the best of inner version of himself,
because now he always looks like immaculately dressed.
It's like the perfect fitting clothes.
He's a he and the Honda Anacca are one in the same.
He goes very realistic.
He goes into imagineering and a team dresses him like they dress Honda Anacca.
There's just roadies feverishly pointing out all the actuators like so he can do
anything that a human face would be able to do.
He can buy any company you want.
He can he has the ability to point over and say yes, buy and he can do anything.
Anything you want.
This is one of the most realistic robots we have.
He can merge companies.
He's the first time a robot's been able to.
In Lincoln era, you never could have dreamed of a robot that could
know kickstart mergers.
No, he can fight.
He can fire 20000 people from the company he's bought.
That was a little that was another bit of narration.
It was a little too cutesy for my
Bob Iger went on a franchise spending spree.
And it's like that's one way to put it.
I don't know that like a kid's are a
toy run.
How many can we throw in?
It's a supermarket sweep of.
I think we usually just call that media consolidation.
Yeah.
Yes.
Yeah, it's getting more Marvel getting Marvel is like getting the giant ham
and supermarket sweep.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
You got to go for that twenty dollar that big plump.
That's Marvel. They're all hams, though.
You know, if you because you that would there's it's a shopping cart with nothing
but hams. Yes.
And there are the fun little items, the fun little snacks that delight us
through our week after we've shopped.
Yeah. You're right.
The Star Wars ham is turned the Star Wars ham.
No, that was recalled. That was recalled.
We forgot to take that one.
They
I hope in this Leslie Jones supermarket sweep that they don't.
I understand maybe it's a more sensitive like people are eating less meat,
hopefully these days, but they need to retain the hams.
Impossible hams.
Impossible and possible ham because it's so much.
You know, we were talking about.
Yeah, because it was so much fun to see people load a ham into their cart,
like multiple hams. Yeah.
One request on this show.
My name is fine.
It's that the Star Wars ham wasn't prepared the way that the the
way that the the the the pig farmer requested.
Like now make sure.
Yeah. That when you serve the ham that it's done like this.
I just put it in the microwave. Yeah, sounds good.
That's easier. Yeah, that's a better.
I think that's a better way.
Better way of putting it of like, you know, like mom makes requests.
But yeah,
mommy said just don't don't get crazy just to the pineapple and the cherry.
Just do the traditions like what about Chipotle this year?
Chex mix on it.
Put Chex mix and Chipotle seasoning.
No, it's it's too much.
One of the hams is like Maker Studio, too, right?
Like a really expensive ham that fell on the floor.
Who cares?
That was the Listeria lettuce.
God, I forgot about Maker Studio.
Like a billion dollars.
Yeah, the dog.
Yeah, the dog got sick after.
Oh, well, that happens in a franchise spending spree.
What do you mean dogs can't eat grapes and chicken bones?
I thought they loved that.
They choked. What do you mean?
There should be more like they should have like done an animation of him
buying two. There should be like a cartoon.
Iger like putting a big bag of money on desks like they should have done something
like that, say grabbing big hams.
That's that's one of them says Muppets.
No, that was Eisner.
He bought the Muppets.
Oh, he did.
Like, why did you do this?
We did not want this.
Tired to make it right.
Yeah. To seal this deal.
Always better.
Never closed it.
Yeah.
So back to this home, the home run after home run.
Yeah, the rest of this special knocking hams out of the park.
This is sort of where the series starts to I get a little tired of watching
the series because the drama is lower as we said, we can't really talk about
anything and it is just like success, success, success.
I don't impression in my head of how the narration starts to become
the imagineers were in grave trouble.
They had to figure out how to do a thing.
Fortunately, they figured out how to do the thing.
The imagineers had done the thing.
And that's sort of what it becomes from here on out.
Yes. The ear.
I guess that's drama.
Yeah. Which is what were they going to do?
Right. If he had misfired the ear and chopped off somebody's neck with it.
Fortunately, they banded together and figured it out.
Yeah, it's not there.
There is just the most superficial of problems.
Yeah, that's all they're allowed to bring up.
Usually solved by extra few months of building and
like two million dollars extra than they thought.
Like, I don't know what to tell you.
It was freed up.
It took longer and it was more expensive.
Why there's not so much you can feel the
scrappiness in some of these earlier eras.
And that's why a soren in a cheap era feels like such a triumph.
But now it's just like there was plenty of money and the money was spent and the
money was spent on a pretty good thing. Wow.
They did it.
I mean, it's fun that there's footage like I like them.
They're pitching Midway Mania.
There's a little video of that.
And I would love to have seen like the pitches for all the rides that made.
They probably won't show us stuff that didn't make it.
Obviously, that sounds great to see pitches that didn't make it because they
might use them again. But still, that is interesting.
Like, is if like, you know, you watch old reels of people auditioning for Star Wars
or famous movies and it's like Kurt Russell auditioning for Star Wars.
It does seem like that's that's you could open that up.
That would be fun to look and see if they're willing to.
Yeah, they should be more so.
And why not?
So there's like little pieces of stuff I
find interesting, but they only show a little of it.
And I sort of I don't know.
Maybe I miss this entirely when it happened.
I recently discovered this lore and it's really spelled out in this.
And I'm sure it was a surprise to a lot of people in the imaginary story that they
were separately preparing Car Land, right?
I'm aware of cars, the movie.
And then they merged it into Cars Land.
I see our land and fake.
Yeah, I know.
I think there was talk of Route 66 in original DCA and it was cut.
OK, I don't know as detailed as it became.
Yeah, I don't know.
I mean, I thought it was interesting when they were like they made this big
commitment of the redo of DCA during the 08 09 like recession.
That was an interesting bold move.
I've already said this other places, but
could it could have done without all those Lasseter sound bites in this one?
I don't know.
Well, it's tricky.
It's tricky.
There were cuts of this that were there was a cut of this, I'm sure, where Episode
Five was all was all Lasseter.
It's the story of Lasseter saved it.
But like, yeah, not at all.
But like Lasseter, who they kind of have erased, although they were still trying
to get rid of his wine a year ago with DCA, still trying to get through a few
palettes, I can help him with that.
It's tricky because like you build a land like his his like the cars is like his
thing, yeah, so it does feel like you have to acknowledge him.
But yeah, I don't know what the disc.
This is disgraced filmmaker John Lasseter.
Like, what is the they don't really.
Yeah, they don't.
It doesn't say anything particularly revolutionary that they had to.
I was a kid.
I loved the cars.
And our app, which is they go vroom, vroom.
And I
they could go fast, but they could also stop.
And that's why I love the car.
Lightning McQueen is red.
And as a kid, I loved red.
I ate apples.
I
is like stop signs.
I like all the red thing.
That's fun. You've done your your Lasseter before.
And now I just did a little to do it audio, but it's all just it's yeah, it's
Robert Earl very similarly to say little arms flapping.
Every word gets the flap.
It's fun. I was just that's my first time doing it just now.
And it is a fun, fun impression to do.
Well, that could be we could both age.
That's maybe that's what we're like in our 60s and 70s.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Wearing a Hawaiian shirt.
Big, big flapping arms.
Hopefully not women running away from us.
I would certainly hope not because we're
like ice, like being a menace in the workplace.
Yeah, I don't need hugs that badly.
I can go.
I assume people don't want to hug me.
Yes.
I usually initiate the and then some people will.
And I'm actually I'm happy to hug.
I'm just saying this in general.
But like, I don't I don't assume not
hungry.
And then I feel like I maybe I'm rude if somebody's trying to hug.
And I don't seem like I went in for it immediately in the perfect way.
You know, you turn around one eighty as if to avoid the hug and they have to hug
you from behind. Yeah.
When I see somebody, I go, hello.
And then I turn my back to them.
Then they like sometimes hug my back.
You wait. You count to 10.
Make sure that they are not desiring a hug.
And then you turn and begin the conversation.
Who's among us does not love being approached from behind
being a big surprising hug from behind.
That's a Monday move.
That is a money.
There's I forget somebody did that to me like a couple of years ago.
It is just the worst.
So scary.
Monday hugs are wonderful, though.
He's good. Yeah, yeah.
I'm not saying like I would see like but this person,
the one I'm thinking of is somebody I didn't know even was there,
like ran up and did it to me.
And I was like, what the hell?
This is I'm an adult man and like a horse.
You kick if you get surprised.
I saw out of your field of vision.
You kick.
Well, someone once said I walk like a fancy horse.
Oh, so that's not a joke.
Why was that said?
Well, because I have sometimes when I'm like being slow, like when I'm walking
and it kind of the lazier way, I have this weird like cloppy walk.
You're a tall man.
You have a graceful, you have a tall gate.
I think sometimes if I'm kind of like
lingering a little bit or if it's not, I'm not headed in somewhere specifically.
I kind of like shuffle a little bit.
Sometimes my friend Luke has a he's been doing an impression of it since I was 15.
So, yeah, so there's a little weird.
I don't know. Check out my walk next time.
I'm going to ask him to do it.
I want to see it from him.
His impression, too, I think at the time I was like a lot of allergies as a teenager.
So his impression is also coupled with me,
like like touching my face and like blowing my nose.
So his impression of me is just this like
massive a human who is like shuffling, walking while he's trying to deal with like
excess mucus. I'm sure your confidence was very high.
Very, very high.
You I grew up.
You're so much more together now.
Yeah.
Yeah, I was up for that clop.
But you people describe it as graceful, I guess.
Yeah, the clop is better.
My clop has been fixed.
Your clop. You had an eye glow up.
The Eiger glow up in this episode and in Cars Land, you get to meet Zolt, the fake
rocksmith, Zolt.
Zolt's very much seems like a protege of
Brody, because Zolt has some very fascinating style, stylistic choices.
Yeah, I never knew that the fake rocks were made by like a guy who's like
Martin Short in Father of the Bride.
He's like a
kooky. Yeah, yeah, exactly.
Zolt, the fake rock man.
Namesake of the Disney wedding pavilion.
What's that?
Martin Short's character in Father of the Bride, the Disney wedding pavilion at the
Grand Floridian is named after that character.
That's funny.
That is such a great Easter egg.
Yeah, I kind of like that.
Franck has got to come back and Disney Plus, right?
Full Franck series.
70 year old Franck.
Yeah.
Fresh off the morning show.
Can they? Yeah.
What? Is Martin Short in the morning show?
Yeah. Oh, no.
Playing a character named Dick Lundry, which rhymes with Nick.
It almost rhymes with Nick Mundy.
Oh, yeah. Very close to his Twitter handle.
Dick Fundy.
That's a good point.
Dick Lundry.
Disgraced director Dick Lundry, who was a whole song and dance in the morning show.
You get to see.
Yeah, because you're like, well, so is this guy like a stand in for Woody Allen?
I guess. Yeah, that must be it.
And then you watch him perform a song and dance.
Like, well, now I don't know what he is.
That's unbelievable.
Sure. We're going to sing and dance, right?
He's playing like a Woody Allen type.
Would he really? Yeah, sure.
Yeah, I know.
It's very like you haven't seen it, Jason.
You got to see it.
And I do like Citizen Kess.
A certain man.
It's like a big song celebrating Steve Carell.
The man. It's such a sorkin.
It's not a sorkin show, but it's such a sorkiny like sounds like the worst part.
Yeah.
It's in the past.
So it's very newsroom.
Yes, yes, yes.
And but it's also a studio 60 ish.
Yes.
Well, Gilbert and Sullivan love Gilbert and Sullivan type.
Oh, no.
You know what I'm saying?
If people have not done, let's say I know we're talking about another streaming
service here, the morning show starts real strong, then it gets kind of boringly OK.
And then it finishes wonderfully schlocky bad.
Oh, boy.
Like, just stick it out or just skip ahead.
Just don't jump to the last three.
You can just. Oh, yeah.
Go to Vegas, get to Vegas, get to Vegas.
And now morning shows rolling.
I haven't done all of it, but I've seen a couple episodes and then the clip of.
Have you been to Vegas?
No. Go to Vegas.
It's all about Vegas.
I won't even tell you what's up in Vegas.
We get so sorkiny.
Oh, my God.
We're visiting past events.
Just get to it.
Get your ass to Vegas.
All right. All right.
What else?
Oh, my God.
The
camera, everyone's mean to Kim Irvine because we're putting changing attractions.
Yeah. Running thing.
I know I feel so bad for her that I said, I think I said in the other.
There's an article about her when she was
what she was redoing the colors on the castle.
She's just so concerned with like making people happy.
Yeah. And people are so who's making her afraid to go out at night?
She says she was afraid to go outside.
Yeah. Cool it on Kim.
What are you doing? She sees she's very nice.
She tries hard.
Yeah.
Delivers like, I don't know.
I think the characters in Small World are cute.
Yeah, I know.
Imagine her wants to put Cinderella into a ride about dolls.
How dare you?
You go live in a hole.
I don't understand this one.
Why was anyone ever mad about this?
Everybody cool it.
Haunted Mansion Holiday, a huge hit.
Runs a little long for our taste, but huge.
You can't deny those lines.
You know, you can't deny this.
I'm still not against it.
I'm taking I'm sticking with I'm fine with it and I'm fine with the timeline.
Oh, you you're fine with it.
September to December.
Yeah. OK.
People really need I need my Haunted Mansion on Halloween Day.
I need this so much that I'm going to be mad about it.
Well, it was fun to go on the
mansions. I realize that's so fired up about it really.
I go to the parks if you haven't heard fairly often.
So it's not like I don't get to go on it.
But I get the argument that it's a little too it would be interesting.
Like it would be fun to go on Halloween.
I just don't.
I'm like I enjoy the change up and I enjoy the change of two.
So I this is not like I don't really
it could be a couple of I feel like the tide turned where people now hate the thing.
Well, I still think that that's a minority.
I still don't think because the lines are still crazy for it.
It's always like double the amount of the regular Haunted Mansion.
It's these vocal minorities that that's that sounded horrible.
And I just said, oh, God, oh, my God.
That's OK. Let me finish this.
You're a cancer theme park, a small group of detractors.
There. Thank you.
Thanks for saving my.
Oh, God, please.
No one use that clip.
We're going to go through your Lasseter impression.
No, that's not going to help.
Oh, sorry. I mean, we're going to need what I can only assume is the fixer
character from the morning show.
There's got I'm assuming there's a fixer or a crisis matter.
We need Ray Donovan.
Not really. That's the problem there.
If they be on they'd be on Cloud 9 if there was a if they had a solid fixer,
they spent all season trying to fix it.
It doesn't get fixed.
It's tough game.
Morning show game.
Well, I think I wrote Bob Iger is the fixer of the Disney company on my note.
Oh, he's the Michael.
He's Michael Clayton.
Yeah, Disney.
He comes in and cleans up the mess.
Sure. Yeah, yeah.
He does it.
We put sparkles on Peter Pan and Peter Pan makes it all in a small world.
It's all better now.
This one's the but I'm if I will say five is my least favorite episode
because six you get like the new cutting edge.
Yeah, dogs, avatars, the Star Wars.
I think that's fair.
And this one's just kind of like, OK, world of color.
Fine. There is the ducks.
There's a cute moment where some ducks take up
habit, like start living in the Peter Pan construction site.
That was cute. Yeah.
The they talk about
designing lands with no or more minimal queue lines.
Very interested in that design area, the virtual queues or the play.
I feel like the play area, like the the Dumbo.
You don't really wait in the line for Dumbo in Florida.
You go in like a play area and then they call your number, whatever.
I'm interested in how that goes on, how it develops.
Uh huh.
Yeah, it's not working for everywhere.
Yeah. Tease Jimmy Fallon episode.
Yeah, they show too much.
I watched the Mystic Manor.
I have never watched a Mystic Manor ride through.
Oh, really?
So this I was like, all right, fine.
I'll watch.
Because like, am I going to go to Hong Kong soon?
Probably not.
But I watched that stuff.
I have broken and watched that right through.
It's so good.
I know. Good.
And it really reads as a ride through to.
So I can only imagine being there using music to tell the story.
I thought was interesting.
Getting Danny Elfman to make original music for it.
Again, very interesting.
Yeah, I got that.
The earthquake, the Japanese earthquake segment is very moving.
Oh, my God. Yeah, it is.
It's a devastating.
So, you know, I got to maybe I'm underrating episode five because it is this.
Which is that is probably the major heart emotional highlight of it.
I always wonder.
I'm always like everyone who's involved is like getting very emotional about it, too.
So I shouldn't like doubt its claim,
but I'm always like a little suspicious of corporate propaganda.
But I still was like very.
Asking questions.
And I mean, I remember just like in general,
like when something people love reopens after a horrible tragedy, it's such a
cathartic. Yeah.
Like SNL.
Much like. Can we be funny?
Can we be funny? Can we ride rides again?
And so just so OK, so when this overlay,
and you guys will be fine with this, right?
Duffy is Giuliani.
The signal that we're ready to reopen.
Uh huh. Yeah.
Great. Moving on.
Everyone approves. That's yeah.
That's one to one. Yeah.
It is very know that there's Duffy's being handed out posts.
Oh, I know.
That's how do you not well up?
I know. It's really.
Yeah, it's really people.
I remember people posting on Twitter as that was happening and people.
Yeah. Being given blankets, everyone being fed and taken care of.
Yeah. Yeah.
So I guess, yeah, I guess the end, it ends strong.
It ends with it does well.
But this one has because we've said there's some very good cliffhangers.
This one, you know, indicating the rise of Eisner.
There's just cool ones in general that the company might stop making parks.
This one, I think, is the worst cliffhanger
because it implies that the company's future depends on Robert Eiger
making a business deal with China.
Yes. Well, how will this play out?
The the phrase
for the 60th Disneyland Park looked immaculate.
That is not how I remember it.
I remember it looking a little chintzy.
It had some blue some ribbons, some ribbons that were up for a while.
It did look better than it had.
It looked better than it had, but there wasn't really.
I mean, the 50th seemed grim, but like the 60th didn't seem.
After all that 2012 plus up, the 60th felt very quiet to me.
I just remember it like it looking better.
That's all this around.
It's around the time, though, and it ties into this,
like the Shanghai is sucking up the budget.
That is true.
I don't know how it actually ends up lining up.
Now, it's I know very little about Shanghai
because we don't do a lot of watch and ride through the things.
You know, so things that come up like that.
There is a whole big area in front of the
castle called the Gardens of Imagination and his rides in that.
It's not just like a little hub, things like that.
I did not know.
So I'm so this thing was educational Shanghai wise and Shanghai seems incredible.
Oh, yeah. I mean, I watched the Pirates ride in the.
Yeah.
And Tron.
Obviously, those are great.
Those seem like two of the greatest rides on Earth, probably for sure.
And I there's been rumors of them building a version of the Pirates, right?
Because like Tron is coming, obviously, so we'll get to do that.
But you would think they have this crazy
ride system for pirates that they have not used anywhere else yet.
Yeah.
So there was rumors of like a Jungle Book
version of like the Pirates ride coming.
The boat guided by magnets, right?
Yeah.
So it can spin and move you.
I heard the rumor was Epcot in like a new pavilion, maybe.
But a giant ticket.
I don't know if that's just the thing I read.
So but yeah, it's such a like one of the best.
So many different like ride, like like
technologies and newer versions of it, there's like that big screen area that you
can do like project, I don't know if it's 360 completely, but it's like,
you know, I'm talking about when you go
like under the water and the Pirates Shanghai ride, like crazy stuff.
There's this discuss, I saw people were a little mad about this.
But imagine your Bob Weiss says that for when he takes
Chinese guests around pirates who have no nostalgia for pirates, that they say
that the ride is slow and boring.
Right.
And I saw people upset about that or how dare you had to.
But like, it's also a you can't argue their perspective.
Sure.
And B, don't we want to even think that the stuff that we think of as the Bible
could be improved a bunch?
Sure.
I think that's like, I think he has the forward thinking.
I don't agree with it.
I love pirates, but like you don't get this incredible new ride without.
But if you don't have the reference point for it and the historical perspective,
I mean, I'm sure there is plenty of Chinese culture I would not understand or
stuff I would say was slow and boring.
But it's like, no, no, this is like the keystone to something.
Sure, sure.
There's probably teens, though, that would go on pirates right now.
And they've been to six flags and they've been to other places and going on rides
and go, this one's boring.
Yeah.
Slow.
This is where the Breck Eisner story comes from.
Which is fine.
I think what you need is a mix of I think if that this is slow and boring and then
you rip out something that's sweet and charming, I think that's a bummer.
But if you're just building new, I think the optimal Disney park has
like little sweet, charming things and crazy high tech and thrilling stuff, too.
That's the optimal balance.
In 2020, there's no reason to recreate the ride that opened 50 years ago.
Yeah, there's no reason to do that.
Yeah. Yes.
Why would you just go and stamp just because, yeah, people expect it to be
the exact same, I don't think.
And if tastes differ, I mean, they make a point of like, yeah, Main Street is
different. There is no railroad.
There is no steam, but they don't.
These things did not come in the same way in this country, and they don't really
have the affection for it or the knowledge base for it that it would be
enticing to them.
Sure, sure.
No small world, no Haunted Mansion, no Jungle Cruise.
Yeah, that's a crazy Disneyland.
No small world feels a little I don't
that one feels weird.
Some of this feels weird.
Some of the.
What do you mean?
The Chinese governmental system of like
the Communist Party, but it's also the most capitalist place on Earth.
They have a space program that launches over villages and parts of rockets fall
off on the like, you're saying there's some weird shit in China.
The weird parts of the government.
It's sort of like it wouldn't have been appropriate to put that into China.
Is there one in Hong Kong?
I don't know the answer to that.
I'm not sure.
But I mean, I think that they can't have Winnie the Pooh because people make fun
of President Xi Jinping because he looks like Winnie the Pooh.
And you can't insult the president.
It's like, OK, well, that's a little.
Well, that's I mean, the politics of putting these parks in different countries.
Yes.
Any other returned bears?
Could you have the guy like Robin Hood's friend, Little John, Little John?
Like that would be OK just because nobody's made that comparison.
Right. But then if you built a whole
ride about Little John, we're going to visit Little John Little John's forest.
But then like that day, somebody said, oh, it's like Xi Jinping.
Then, yeah, it's got to go coming out.
Yeah. They had a country bear Jamboree and somebody called him Big Al.
That's rough coming out.
I think you can't even play with fire with country.
Oh, yeah. No, no, no.
Yeah. Does he is it about the appearance or does he is he like a bear?
In any way, Cuddly is the is he?
I don't know. I don't have the idea.
I don't quite know.
I think people picked up on it on the Internet that like Disney is coming to China.
It's like, oh, you know, the president's kind of a little round, like low.
And those people were all shy.
And yeah, she's check them out at the bodies exhibit.
The bodies exhibit.
So that's behind the second gate.
I mean, look, I know here is here, right?
No, no, no, no.
Owners, they got to subscribe.
You know, five thousand years of culture.
I you know, it's a really lame thing in this that you
hearing this, you know, in the imaginary story documentary, you get to hear where
the Haunted Mansion came from, you know, the story about Pirates of the Caribbean.
And then you get to hear how Robert Ager thought of the phrase authentically
Disney, but distinctly Chinese, and then you hear about it again.
It's like your dad repeating a not that good story to you several times.
That's so that's how I thought of this.
That's so yeah, that is.
I just remember it occurred to me just so like I didn't even
know effort just like a flash.
So poetry, I don't know.
Is it possible that's like his biggest
contribution to the whole project other than giving like funding it?
Is it like, you know, like he thinks I think.
Right. Like that's like this was the best
thing I did were pretty we're being like we have soft hands about this one emperor
in this episode and then about another one where you have to pretend that
authentically Disney, but distinctly Chinese is an important cultural
contribution. Yes.
Make sure you show it again.
You know, I think is I'm disappointed is
that I did not try to speak Chinese at the opening of Shanghai like Eisner,
what if, yeah, and butchered the language.
Look, I for one welcome our Chinese over at Lourdes.
But I will be the first to say I do not understand this country that is everything
all at once like Blade Runner, billions of people
in a Blade Runner esque like the most futuristic buildings and then also ghost
towns because they built towns for the Olympics and no one lives in them.
And we'll learn.
Wow. You'll get out works when that's how America is.
Well, yeah, sure.
Yeah, we'll be there in a few years.
We'll be there in a few years.
They don't get into this is that this is
the Shanghai thing at the time when they were building Shanghai Disney.
It was way behind schedule.
They they allude to that in the special
that there were issues and like people were Iger was talking about how stressed
he was about it, but I remember this time because I'm selfish.
I remember this time being, well, we were going to build some cool stuff,
but the money's all going to Shanghai.
It's over. It's all going over budget.
And I do remember around this time,
like garbage cans filling up with garbage in Disneyland.
I remember like they've cut maintenance.
That's what message boards were saying.
And I do remember going like I can feel like they have cut staff here.
I remember almost getting crushed in a crowd on Main Street for like a parade
because there was no one directing like, all right, here, if you're going to stand
and watch from here, if you're just trying to walk and then people getting irate.
And I'm like, where are you?
Like I found the cast.
I was like, what is going on?
Like some fights about to break out if you don't get down there.
Like I remember this time in Disneyland.
Yeah, I remember.
Yes, it would always be like, oh, Shanghai.
They have the budget problems and every other park is feeling it.
Yeah. 2012 to like Guardians and Avatar opening.
There was like pretty minimal development, I feel like, in terms of new attraction.
Oh, yeah.
Guardians.
This is the episode where Guardians and Avatar open the same weekend.
Wow.
Rhodey just just
goes to go both his projects hitting at once like Phil Collins being both live aids.
It's
all.
Yeah. Wow.
It's crazy that I don't know why my brain, my brain thinks Avatar opened five
years earlier than Guardians or like a few years earlier.
It's not.
No, I guess it's just a different coast.
That description that it's like tossing a baby up and down and it makes you laugh.
Like, wow, that just explains what is the sink.
Yes, completely explains what that ride is and why it is worth doing and having a
different version than Tower Terror.
Yeah, he really lays it out, the whole thing in such a way that's very clear.
I mean, sometimes, yes, he's very like heady when he's describing things.
But that one's just succinct as can be.
Yeah.
And that's they ask him.
I don't forget which one it is.
They ask him, like, do you ever get it?
Do you ever get a sign stuff that you're not excited about?
And he says, yes.
Yeah.
But Avatar.
But like, I wonder if I don't know.
I wouldn't think he would be like super
excited to destroy a ride everybody likes and have this.
I don't know.
He just doesn't.
It doesn't seem like a fit for him.
He doesn't seem like an irreverent or whatever he says about the movie.
But like he figured he did figure all the angles out.
Hey, that's yeah, he might have that ability to like, I'll I'll find my in on this.
Right.
Make it work.
And it is like it's using that ride system in a different way.
It's not scary.
It's like there's thrills.
And the baby thing is I never even thought about that.
He got the music like, oh, people like the old music.
In these movies, like people like the sound.
Let's get some songs.
He just sold the seemingly the feel of Guardians of the Galaxy into like a like
more than the story.
Yeah.
Let's let's portray all the things that happen in the movie.
Just like got the vibe really.
Yes.
He like, yeah, he's he's he's a good I'm trying to think what you would an
interpreter or what like he's he's good at synthesizing.
I mean, there's no one I think I would want to redoing Tomorrowland more.
It's great news because it seems like
an optimist and very and then future forward thinking, future thinking of like,
I'm not going to design this for the future of twenty twenty one.
But like the future that will like stick around.
Everything he does is authentically Disney, distinctly roadie.
Very good.
That's a very true.
I like that.
I'll say it again later.
His sketches.
It's crazy.
Like his sketches are so deep, like it's like, oh, my God, like
the sketches are so wild.
Yeah.
You also with Avatar, you get to see what this great melding of worlds,
character people that we know meeting other people, roadie meets Cameron.
And they get along famously.
Buds and Cameron's producer, John Landau meets Zoltz, fake rock Zoltz,
and you meet another fake rock guy named
we what's a Fabrice Fabrice and Zoltz, the fake rock man.
It's so nice to know they did not.
These characters did not disappoint.
Can we get fake rock people for Breeson Zoltz on the show?
Are they Disney employees?
Are they I think current Disney employees are tough.
Right. But that's what I'm saying.
Are they Disney rock people?
Are they a different company?
Rock people. That's what we have to look into.
I think at least one of them was credited as an Imagineering executive.
OK, I thought it was interesting.
Some of these people they interviewed in this episode,
their jobs ended in 2018 when they clearly wrapped a lot of Shanghai.
Oh, interesting.
Yeah. Yeah, that happens when a big project ends.
Yeah. Tons of people get fired.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's so yeah, I like the Cameron and he's like a road,
Joe Rody got Avatar.
He understood it was really.
It's what a fun meld of people.
I wish there was footage of them in like a sub together.
Rody must have gone in the sub, right?
Maybe they traveled the world.
The whole section, I think this is I'm getting ahead of the whole section,
but Cameron talking about like how he fixed Flight of Passage essentially.
Oh, yeah. It was really funny to me.
What did he say? He said it was like very aggressive.
Oh, yeah. The ride.
But he said, no way back it off to like that's too aggressive, which I wonder.
I'm always interested.
They left that in.
So maybe that is just a fact.
But I think that's interesting.
Yeah.
They talk about the river journey, like an attraction to inspire serenity,
like not a feeling you associate with like parks necessarily.
Yeah, that's that's true.
I do find it very interesting and pleasant and soothing.
I think people
are a little critical of it because the wait time balloons so easily.
But I like I just thought it was nice.
I just thought it was very all of Avatar.
I found so moving and pleasant.
And you could do another.
I think if it's like a couple of it was a couple of minutes longer.
I feel like people are expecting a little like a little bit longer of a
transformative experience. I was getting ready to not be in the world of
I think that was my personal like, you know, some people cried because they had
to leave out there. I was like, hmm, bed hotel room.
I can't wait.
We were up early, though.
I was a rougher day.
Yeah.
They do a lot of talk about the Shaman of Song and I'm trying to just let me to
think and maybe I've asked this question on the show before and I forgot.
Is the Shaman of Song in any of the Avatar sequels?
That is my big question.
Was she in the first one?
No, that's an original character for that ride.
And if she walked on screen, would I have any idea that's what was happening?
Well, the answer is no.
Someone someone pitched us for a second
gate episode and it's an easy fix for you and me.
We watch Avatar for the first time and then talk about it.
I watched Avatar.
Oh, wait. Yeah, they're wrong about that.
Really?
I guess I'm just the only one.
Hmm. Then you.
There is a narrative starting and I like to think that I'm responsible for this,
but there's a narrative starting that Avatar is fantastic.
The new ones are going to make so much money and they're also going to be fantastic.
It's kind of like Star Wars reactionary.
It is seemingly we need a new IP that won't like the Marvel phase one is done.
Well, I'm seeing it from Skywalker stories done.
So we need a new.
I'm seeing it from, I guess, people we know mostly who are all prequel.
Also the same thing with the prequels.
Yes, prequels are amazing.
There's not a single problem with them
and you don't understand them.
Of course, the correct, the unassailably correct opinion.
Yeah. And I'm seeing that happening now with Avatar.
Yeah. And I think that'll continue to happen.
But I'd like to take some credit for it for years ago.
Talking about Avatar and the money.
I think here's what happened when we started talking about Avatar in the pockets.
We were all like smiling, a gleeful smile.
I think Jason and I, our smile was because Avatar is kind of lame, right?
And your smile was, no, I love it.
And it touched me and it moves me and its spirit is in me.
I think you're mostly right.
You're mostly correct.
But it's also like Buffett where you like,
I'm going to get into this to make fun of it.
Oh, wait. Well, yeah, yeah.
You end up coming out on the other side.
I mean, I am going into watching this movie fresh,
but with a ton of goodwill from these attractions and this land.
I think, though, Jason sees it and loves it actually more than me.
Jason loves movies.
I it's very rare that we don't see a movie and you don't go like, hey, it was good.
I just I mean, I do like the experience of going to movies a lot.
And I definitely can think of some clunkers.
Rolling up in your sweater as rolling up in my sweater and backwards.
It's the only movie you could possibly do.
There's the only movie I've sucked.
I mean, that's easy.
We got one on the horizon that we're not
optimistic about what we're going to see.
Oh, yeah, we should.
We'll see if it's interesting to talk about or not.
But the only time I've ever seen a come out of a movie with you and you were upset
was Infinity War. I just thought it was too sad for the kids.
You were just like, the children will see this and they'll be so sad.
And I was like, yeah, but it was like actually was good and dark and like it's
a cliffhanger. You're like, yeah, but they're all going to be so sad.
But yeah, but also like 25 years of Marvel comics just not letting up on the dark.
Unlike Grim and Gritty, I just think it's funny.
That's the only one. So like Avatar is not that sad.
There's some sad. It looks hopeful.
You're singing the song.
He's going to be the biggest fan.
I mean, we'll see. Yeah.
We've made it to Star Wars, but I'm I need to go soon.
What do we do?
We also we haven't watched the Rise of Resistance.
I haven't either.
I like scrubbed really fast.
And when I stopped seeing Star Wars stuff, I picked up.
And so the the end, the last six minutes of this episode,
they kind of like tie up like, well, we're still working on stuff.
And they show the flipping robot, the flipping robot man that clearly is
making Spider-Man poses as it comes back down in the art for the Marvel land.
I believe that I don't know if it's the same thing, but there's a there's a little
hook on the Spider-Man ride that's clearly for Spider-Man to swing,
like an actual Spider-Man to swing outside of.
And I don't know if it's that one or there'll be a performer.
I'm not sure, but hopefully it's that crazy robot that flips.
I liked, oh, the Shaman of Song, before I forget, when she says,
I look forward to seeing you on Pandora.
Was that OK? Like like it was a real actor doing it.
Yeah, that was. Yeah, I remember.
I just hadn't seen it in years and I was like, oh, that's fine.
Yeah, that is nice.
It's so unnerving.
They talk about Star Wars.
I mean,
look, again, the execution of Batuu is very good, but Pandora is so beautiful.
Pandora is, Batuu is meant to be weathered and beat up and lived in.
So it's it's two very different things.
Yeah, we talked about that.
We've talked a lot about that.
You know, I like running between the Turkish market that they visited.
So I like the Grand Bazaar.
I really like seeing the Millennium Falcon ride, like what it looks like.
Yes. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The turntables. Yeah, that's a really impressive mechanism.
So much of it that's, you know, for whatever problems we have with it,
so much of it's so impressive.
And Scott Trowbridge talking about like they knew they were going to do it,
but they didn't like they approved it.
But this technology is not there.
And they haven't figured it out until like a couple of months before.
It's pretty impressive.
It's crazy. Yeah, yeah, we have our little problems, but it's like, I don't know.
I think I think there's a couple of things that can get Falcon to be like crazy.
I think there's a few simple fixes.
Yeah, yes, for sure.
But then showing like sort of what the screen kind of looks like outside of the
cockpit is crazy, because like it's all designed to make you it's like almost.
Yeah. If you if you could see the full
picture of all of it, you'd probably be more impressed in a weird way.
They do it so see everything so seamless.
The cockpit changeover is so seamless.
Everything is so perfect.
It almost minimizes actually what's going on.
Yeah, it just feels like a tiny little screen and it's shaking.
But like the crazy this contraption with
turntables that have the cockpits on them and so many of them are going at once.
It's crazy.
The fact that it loads so quickly and so many people are up and in.
But yeah, look, resistance we haven't won.
Now, by the time you're hearing this, we we've probably hopefully been on the ride
and we can, you know, we'll say what we thought about the clips of it in this
documentary.
But for now, we can't do it.
We're not we were afraid of spoilies.
Show the clip of George Lucas.
Oh, they dedicate they show the clip of him going like, well,
this looks great.
It could have gone very bad.
It's so fun.
Like you can tell he doesn't have exactly when he starts talking, he doesn't know
exactly what he's going to say.
And then when he comes, when he finds it, it gets a big laugh because it is so like
what does he get? He doesn't have to worry about offending.
And it was George fucking Lucas.
He's deciding, do I call them white slavers again?
Do I use the word because this would be the time white slavers would really land
at this event. All right.
I'll be nice.
Yes. In case you know what Scott's talking about, he refers to Disney as white
slavers in a Charlie Rose interview after Force Awakens because he was upset that
they made so casually is what's funny.
That phrase is so, so shocking.
But then you watch it and just, you know,
because the white slavers and they didn't like he didn't say it like in a big bowl,
like Yelly way because he's so like so repressed or what he's so inside.
Like that's probably the most rage he can express at this point.
But obviously that's a mad and furious term.
You go to fucking hell.
Yeah, that's a term you don't throw
around lightly.
Yeah, no.
But that's like that that illustrates what he feels happened to his characters.
Like that's how upset he is.
Shock. No, he apologized for that.
Also that back the dump truck of money of like make a new movie, George.
We're talking about it.
Look, it could happen. Yeah.
I don't think that's out of the question that he comes.
He's been back also.
That's what's funny, too. And that's what's funny about that.
Red tails. No, no, no.
I'm saying he is like there's always like, oh,
he visits the set of The Mandalorian.
Like I think there's something in the contract that he has to sort of still
like kind of be the godfather of all this until they were great.
Animatronic that takes his place until they build an amateur with a lot of
actuators in the face that can take and he doesn't have to go do anything anymore.
Luckily realistic, George.
And then he'll be walking around
Galaxy's Edge so that everybody can go, oh, he looks he loves it.
Luckily, they don't hear all the time.
They don't they don't have to use the new
robot technology because he doesn't emote very much.
So they can use just the Lincoln animatronic,
which is probably too much.
It emotes too much for his face.
They don't need the tiny motors the size of a pinky.
They can use the old hydraulic fluid ones.
Nobody hated white slavers more than Lincoln.
There you go. That's true.
Put a stop to them.
There you go.
There's some wrap up.
I was going to do another.
We were two running over.
Yeah, I do need to leave.
There's some thoughtful wrap up.
So I think it's actually in the previous episode where the maybe it's Bob Weiss.
Asked John Hench like, what does all this mean?
What do we do?
Yes, I like this.
This doesn't make me the parts.
Tell you that you are going to be OK.
It's all going to be OK no matter what happens in the world.
I think we're there all the time.
Yes, it's true.
I mean, yeah, he cracked it.
I wonder I wonder if that's his own thought or that was like Walt figured that out.
We're going to war.
We're going to be like hiding in the bathrooms overnight.
We never have to leave.
Yeah, it's going to be huddled.
We're like, OK, so crouch above the toilets so they don't kick us out at night.
Yeah.
Can we stay at Disneyland for four and a half weeks straight?
A good question.
I think we could I think we can crack that.
Yeah, I think for sure.
That's what we'll work on in 2020 is how to actually live there.
The very least we could like figure out which lots are open, sleep in the car
for a couple hours and then go back into the park.
Yeah. With a mobile in our car.
That's like our favorite characters.
It's Mickey and Hondo and Eisner and Eiger and a little Chime.
So we never have to leave our favorite little universe.
Yeah. Yeah.
That's the rest of our year.
I have to leave.
So I'm going to say you survived podcast the right.
The Imaginary Story.
You have more, though, clearly.
You have an anxious low.
It'd be funny if you just left.
If you guys want to keep going, I just have to go.
Yeah, you should just leave. All right.
Well, say whatever. All right.
Well, then you said Scott's part.
But all right. Well, I don't know.
I don't have anything left.
But you need to say that much.
I don't know.
There was a roadie wrap up quote at the very end.
I mean, they show a lot of like Tony Baxter looking at Big Thunder, Bobger
greeting people.
There's a Marty Sklar dedication at the very end.
He says you have to let yourself feel emotion to do this work.
And I think that's the big thing.
That's the whole big thing.
People get very emotional doing this work, coming to this place.
We get very emotional.
Anything to tell me about Randy Gerber, too?
I have a few thoughts about Randy Gerber now that you mentioned it.
And you survived here.
You guys wrap up if you want.
I got to go. All right, Scott.
Bye. See this.
I'm just documenting this to show that this is real.
This is not a bit for Scott.
Has to leave here. He's going.
He's leaving. He's leaving.
Here's Edwin. Edwin is going to follow him.
Luckily, he didn't knock over the recorder.
Scott is gone.
All right. There's Jason.
Now we are continuing the podcast.
Yeah. The roadie thing about feeling emotion and the hinge thing that you're
going to be OK. I mean, those those felt like the most concise, like sum up.
I'm like the closest I've ever gotten to a feeling of like, oh, well,
what's the start of the answer to the question?
Why do you like this so much?
And yeah, yeah, I think that's yeah, I think we've talked about that before
of what it is that that makes you feel.
I mean, the others all you can get into, like what it is that makes you feel
comfortable, a lot of it's nostalgia, a lot of it's being a child.
Yeah, a lot of it's living with characters and it just, you know,
it pushes bad stuff out of your brain.
But of course, it's the Disney bubble that people talk about, too.
Yeah. Which is nice as well.
So, you know, a nice doc, a nice series overall.
A nice series. I thought pretty good.
Would love to dig in, as we said, this is just to sum up, but like love to dig in
more with this team and let them like, yeah, really shit talk.
I think like there's a very interesting either it's the first 10 years
of Disneyland or first 10 years of Disney world of like almost like an oral history.
And that maybe that's more of a book sort of approach.
Yeah. But like, like really down to the nitty gritty operational.
Like, well, here's actually what went wrong.
And here's like the crazy stuff we haven't.
It's been a century or it's been half a century.
We can talk about this now. Right.
But I mean, yeah, like like how big it was going to be.
Mark Davis is Western River.
What is it? Adventure?
What is it? Expansion.
Sorry. Or Big Thunder.
Like there's a there's two hours of that and talking and showing sketches from the
what could have been with the River Ride versus Tony with all of that.
I mean, there's so much you hear Tony talk
on season pass or any of these other interviews.
And there's just so much material and stuff that obviously happened.
So anyway, we've talked a lot.
Is this two hours? Are we going like over two hours?
Maybe unbuilt, unbuilt, imaginary.
Oh, that would be a sequel.
I don't know how much they want to.
Well, that's a lot of stuff out there like with Westcott and stuff.
It's like there's a lot of art out there.
And Tony's talked about it again on season pass podcast a lot.
He's talked about all the 45 minute boat ride that had like so many robots and you
could get on it at four different points.
So like he's he's talked about a ton of stuff.
He's talked about, you know, Geyser Mountain that was going to go back.
Yeah. Over where Star Wars is.
And that was going to be like their tower of terror, essentially.
So like so much stuff is out there.
This doesn't even know about all the season pass podcasts.
I don't know. I don't know exactly what the deal is.
Tony was talking about that Ozland they were going to build for the Franco.
The Franco Wizard of Oz.
And he like explained like he didn't explain, you know, he he was a little bit
self-censoring because he said like he explained how you were going to go into
the tent and see the Wizard of Oz.
And like he was going to like do some magic and the tent would flip around and
then you'd open up and you'd be in Oz.
So like a very cool entrance to the land.
I'm assuming some sort of hot air balloon.
Some sort of I think it was going to be like a medicine showy tent.
Yeah. Wagon cart or something.
But then he said there was some sort of e-ticket with technology that he didn't
want to talk about because it would be maybe used later.
Right. But still, like that's you could you could talk about it up until that point.
Sure. You could show some art from some old timey Huckster.
Yeah. Trying to sell people something.
I'm always more more Huckster characters in the park.
I'm always down for that. Yeah.
And then that maybe could be a job for you.
I would love that.
All right. Well, yeah, that's good.
Yeah.
You've survived podcast right again.
Yeah. And Scott is in his car.
Yeah, we wish him well. All right.
Bye. We'll see you later.