Five, four, three, two, one.
In tonight's Plus Us Up second game movie,
a young boy named Mikey meets a possum or something,
and their bond causes Mikey to become very distant
from his family.
Hello, I'm Scott Gardner,
co-head of the podcast The Ride Company,
joined by Michael Carlson.
Hello.
And Jason Sheridan.
Ah, that felt good to do.
Yeah.
So driving a car, you're very comfortable,
or a car you've always dreamed of driving.
Yeah.
Did you know we would do hello?
I think I was hoping.
I would have been, that was a good yes ending.
Yeah, here we are.
This is the thing that you, the audience, sentenced us to do.
Although we chose within this.
If you didn't hear a previous episode,
we talked about the Imagineering story a couple of times,
and that's on Disney Plus.
And we said, send us to watch something on Disney Plus,
and you know, what's kind of the strangest thing,
and the thing you'd most like to hear our thoughts on.
And we got a lot of fantastic entries,
and maybe it's a thing we could revisit at some point in time.
A ton of great, was there anything else that you guys were tempted by?
Well, I forget the name of it,
but I remember specifically,
I think it was Bethany Squires tweeted at us,
like, you should check out this Apartheid comedy.
And I'm like, excuse me?
What? Wait, I missed this.
And I think it's about the power of friendship with a Caucasian girl,
and a person, a girl who's a person of color.
And I was like, is this from the 80s?
And it's from 2000.
And I don't quite know what this mystery is.
Was this a thing that, I believe when this aired,
I could have the wrong movie,
but I think this may have aired on the Wonderful World of Disney,
or whatever they were calling it at the time,
with a Bill Clinton appearance.
Okay.
Potentially a Bill Clinton appearance with Eisner,
because I was trying to find,
I was movie by movie trying to find every Eisner hello for the montage.
So I'm aware of what a lot of the individual ones were,
and I don't remember the name of it,
but I think as aired on TV,
it may have been a Clinton meets Eisner scenario.
Oh my God.
That's insane.
Is Eisner on the flight logs?
I don't think so.
No, I've looked.
I think I've looked for Disney employees and I didn't really find any.
Only someone whose TV series was bought by Disney.
Yeah.
And is now available.
That narrows it down.
The one with 700 episodes.
Oh, right. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It was just a foot massage from a 13 year old.
Yeah, yeah.
That's all it was.
Bethy Squire.
Sorry. Excuse me.
The color of friendship.
Yeah, I think it's a friendship.
I think it's it, but it's like from 2000.
So it would have been in that later.
Yeah.
This was the thing we're talking about today was on the magical world of Disney.
I think that's right.
It's going to keep them straight.
And a lot of things were the Disney Sunday night movie.
If you look it up on Wikipedia,
it's a very dense Wikipedia that goes way back to a wonderful world of color.
Disney land.
This used to be called.
They just considered Disney anthology to be one giant thing that was once
hosted by Walt Disney and years later hosted by Michael Eisner and has also
aired with no host.
It's a big confusing mess.
Right.
Did anything strike your fancy, Mike?
Did you want to feel like campaigning for anything else over Fuzz Bucket?
Well, I mean, the stuff we've talked about already, you know,
the Mighty Ducks series, the animated series.
Yeah.
We did talk.
We were just talking about Meet the Deedles, which I do feel like.
It's got a lot of votes and I ended up watching Meet the Deedles and we made
Meet the Deedles maybe worth looking at down the line.
And when we were casting our final votes, making this decision,
one of you guys, I forget which said when I brought up Meet the Deedles,
oh, is that the movie about the guys with the blue hair?
And I said, no, no, no, that has nothing to do with anything.
The blue hair are big surf waves and all that that's supposed to communicate
is that it's about two surfers.
But it's clearly a poster that failed you.
Yeah.
Thirty years ago, not 30, when was that 98?
Like that's they gave you the wrong impression forever ago that was never
corrected.
We thought I think Jason and I both thought they had blue hair.
I thought it was a family that had blue hair.
I never thought about it.
Maybe you saw a poster in passing.
They were like Marges.
Yeah, they were Marges family and the Simpsons in human form.
The live action Marge movie.
Something that will eventually come to say like there's no reason why each
Simpson shouldn't have their own show and then go for 30 more years.
Oh, finally, it'll live actioning.
It is maybe that maybe that is what Disney does.
The three PCG of each individual Moe.
I got.
Yeah, he's Moe.
Josh Gadd is Moe.
For Christmas, I got the DVD set that has Haunted Mansion, Tower of Terror,
Crunchy Bears and the live act, the mysterious live action, Mr.
Toad, Tower of Terror and Mr.
Toad are not on Disney Plus yet.
No, I'm glad we weren't doing Mr.
Toad because so sad this week, Terry Jones, Terry Jones, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It might be a while ago when we put this out.
Yeah, but poor.
Yeah, that's the record.
Yeah.
So I mean, those are all probably worth watching, though.
I would do all of those.
Yeah, because we got votes for Country Bears, too, which I think I think we'll
hit that at some point, maybe in the vicinity of talking about the the
attraction, maybe made a little progress in figuring out how to do it.
Yeah.
But oh, also, Old Dogs got a lot of votes, but it's not technically as of
this recording, it is not technically on Disney Plus yet.
It's one of those like coming up soon.
But that is Disney.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Because Wild Hogs was Disney.
Yeah.
Is that on Disney Plus?
It wasn't Wild Hogs a big hit.
And then it seemed like they tried to churn out like, oh, let's turn out.
But those aren't the same.
Those aren't the same universe.
Wild Hogs.
Same director.
Right.
And Travolta's in the bus.
Similar.
It feels like reaching for the same audience.
And there's an OGS in the title.
Yes.
Is also what they have in common.
But it isn't.
Is Wild Hogs.
Wild Hogs.
Travolta is not the same character, though.
No, no, no.
OK.
I think it just killed.
As I recall, the failure of Old Dogs killed Wild Hogs, too.
Really?
Yeah, I think there was going to be a sequel that was canceled.
That feels unfair.
Yeah.
It's a different movie.
Mm hmm.
Well, it's like if you make one of the worst films ever put on movie screens, then you
don't get to do a Star Wars anymore.
Right.
You don't get to make episode nine.
I guess.
I guess that's the same thing.
Even though people are now saying maybe should have kept him.
I don't know.
Well, we've seen the leaks.
We don't know.
I haven't seen an iconic line in these leaks like The Dead Speak, though.
So.
Yeah.
They did one thing.
It's one of the best lines.
The way the human brain works, it always feels like the grass is always greener.
Like, oh, what could have been like that possibility allows us to reach for the stars, but it also
shackles us to the ground if we spend too much time thinking about.
This is very unfair.
I like this light.
And what an episode to have it on.
The subject is so very.
About a creature from who lives under the ground and should probably have stayed there.
Place.
Home going.
Going.
God.
Brutal listeners.
I like to think I've given you some joy or respite from this cruel world.
And I only ask now why?
Why did you do this to us?
Why do we do this to ourselves?
And there was a we should now blame this person, though I will say I appreciate his passion.
Nick Hoffman is the Twitter user who said there were discussions on a discord about
that.
Like, well, we should maybe present a solid case for Fuzzbucket.
And that was impossible to deny.
And it got a lot of votes, too.
So that's great.
Passion.
Great.
Why for this?
I mean, I guess now you're getting it now.
You're getting us.
You do get to hear us complain in a hopefully funny way for a little bit.
I hope it's funny.
I feel like you can draw a straight line from Mr. Boogity to that.
Like, this is like.
Clearly cousins.
Yes.
The oddity.
It's in our wheelhouse.
And I also like I mean, I should we give a little background about what this is first?
Because I have a little more about the.
I do as well.
Yes.
Up the name.
It's called the.
The Disney DVD on demand Disney Generations collection.
Oh, I have no information about the Generations.
Okay.
I've got a little.
But if you want to if you want to go ahead and say what exactly is Fuzzbucket?
Fuzzbucket of the week.
Fuzzbucket aired on either magical world of Disney or Disney Sunday movie on May 18th,
1986 and bizarrely surprising surprisingly to a lot of people when Disney plus did the
dump that one day of here's every title that's going to be available.
There were the big there were the heavy hitters like, oh, finally, this will be somewhere
and current big movie Star Wars Marvel and then mixed into it.
Mr. Boogity, I think, got all the love.
But Fuzzbucket as well to present Fuzzbucket.
I think most people were like, what is Fuzzbucket?
I had the vaguest recollection because of the Eisner intro, right, which we'll get to.
But so this yeah, this aired one night and the whole.
It's it's very short, as we discovered.
Yes.
Forty five minutes.
And I think the story with that is that this is, I think, technically a failed pilot.
Yeah.
Five minutes in.
I'm like, this has got to be a failed pilot, right?
Yeah.
And and it's in a listed in a book about failed pilots.
And even there's a fun little montage which will tweet.
I recently watched a special that is a cutdowns of a bunch of failed pilots.
That's pretty fun that aired on ABC in the early 2000s.
That kind of makes fun of it like actually kind of shits on all these shows or in some cases goes like, how do you not pick up this one?
Or it was actually a cool little thing.
So Fuzzbucket, there's a little two minute cut down and this show was seemingly similarly horrified as we were the night that it aired May 18th because it's only 45 minutes and that block is two hours.
They had to pad it out with something else.
And I think it bears mentioning that that night it was a double feature between Fuzzbucket and a another failed pilot I believe called the Deacon Street Deer.
The Deacon Street Deer is about a group of streetwise kids who have to rescue a deer that's lost in a big city.
I think this wasn't it because how does that become a show?
Do they have to rescue a different deer each week?
Maybe it's different deers.
22.
Bastards.
22 deers a season.
They then couldn't call it the Deacon Street Deer unless just every there's new Deacon Street Deers over and over.
What if it's like boxcar children where once they get the deer in the first episode then they and the deer just solve mysteries.
I think the deer lives with them now.
I think the deer lives on Deacon Street now.
So the deer lives in their bedroom and then they ride it to a mystery.
Yeah.
Away from mysteries.
All the three kids climb on Deer's back and who probably talks like Deacon Deacon Doo.
Yeah.
In this film one of the streetwise kids a young Mario Lopez notable thing and probably the craziest thing about it Deacon Street Deer written by the very first writing credit of James Mangold.
Really?
Eventually Logan of Walk the Line of most recently Ford versus Ferrari.
Wow.
This is his very first writing credit system.
Heavy hitters in Fuzzbucket as well.
Yeah.
I came across that too.
The thing I real quick came across the Generations collection.
Yes.
OK.
So this was I believe like I said it seems like this was a thing that was popular for a little while DVD on demand.
The thing that comes to mind most is the Warner Brothers archives.
Are you guys familiar with this?
They put out kind of more like deep cut movies and like you have to order it right from them because they make they don't make them until someone orders them.
And it seems like Disney tried this in 2011 and 2012.
I found an old WordPress blog called Open Vault Disney that seems like it's cataloged most of them and most of these are still available on Amazon.
There's 12.
It looks like there was 12.
So just shout out anything that piques your interest.
Amy Student Exchange Gold Rush colon a real life Alaskan adventure.
I'm all blanks on this.
Fuzzbucket.
Yeah.
Child of Glass.
What?
The Waltz King.
Back to Hannibal colon the return of Tom Sawyer and Huckleberry Finn 1990.
What?
Beyond Witch Mountain.
OK.
I've heard of that.
Endurance.
What?
Justin Morgan had a horse.
That I've heard.
I have heard of that one.
All those titles.
All of them.
The Leftovers and the Richest Cat in the World.
That's a Disney Plus.
That came back.
Yeah.
I think one or two of these are on Disney Plus.
Unless I'm confusing it with the cat from outer space.
And not that darn cat.
Not that darn cat.
Either 70s one or Christina Ricci one.
Right.
There's something I've been trying to work on this theory of like there is something
about the Disney film division of like when you commit to not making R rated movies.
Something happens to people's brain.
Like you try to be too family friendly.
You end up with like.
Fuzz bucket?
Fuzz bucket.
Yeah.
It's.
Like it's so they soften anything that could be sharp until it is nothing.
Yeah.
Until nothing is left.
Although I would not maybe apply that to fuzz bucket because there are things in fuzz bucket
that are like R rated I feel.
Yeah.
We actually found fuzz bucket kind of bleak.
And all of the characters seem to hate each other.
Like despise each other.
And whatever.
No they don't feel like a family at all.
They don't feel like a family.
And also whatever film green they used made it feel like harsh.
Yes.
Like unintentionally French new wave kind of harsh.
There's shots in the kitchen where we're up front at the sink.
Mom's doing dishes or whatever.
And Mikey the boy walks up from the bed and he is the most out of focus I've seen in a
like a non-student film.
Like John Casametti is about to walk in and start screaming.
I mean though it is to be fair to them I have a feeling they haven't remastered this footage
for a new generation.
I mean that's true.
Maybe not.
We need to go in they need to go in and clean it up frame by frame.
Yeah.
It's not a true restoration.
No.
Probably not.
Nor did anyone go in and add the word McClunky after the fact.
Though maybe.
It feels like something fuzz bucket might say.
It does.
It's a little grito-esque I suppose.
He's got a snout.
He has a lot.
I mean I think he's very inspired by Yoda as well I would say.
Yes.
Rearranged language equals.
But he doesn't really he knows most words he just kind of like flops them weird.
Yeah there's not really a consistency to the way he speaks.
No.
Sometimes he just shouts a word over and over again.
The point I wanted to quickly make is that about the sit the idea that it was going to
be a show is that the cover of it is the whole family like.
Yeah.
It's like closing around fuzz bucket as if it's like Harry and the Hendersons.
But this doesn't happen in the movie.
No.
Most of these characters do not meet fuzz bucket and are furious at the idea that he
might exist.
Yeah.
So like the idea that they're all friends and the cover is wrong.
So this feels like a promo shot.
Yeah.
For a potential series.
If you were looking for the moment where they all gather together.
Keep looking.
Look for another.
Go to Alf because there's never a part where they all hug.
Also you don't want these monsters to gather together.
No.
They need to stay in the hole.
They need if they're gathering together they need a family therapist or some sort of counselor
or something.
Oh you meant the monster.
I meant the family.
I meant the fuzz bucket.
Yeah he meant the.
I meant the family and the school administration.
They're all no they're all monsters as well.
They're all monsters.
Everyone in this is a monster.
Maybe not Mikey.
But he's also a little unpleasant.
He's a very unpleasant 80s kid.
Yeah but he I feel like he is very much an 80s kid.
For context this movie came out in 1986 and the big thing that I looked up is OK.
Yes.
He came out right after ET.
They're clearly swinging for ET and Alf came along not too long after.
Alf is in the same year.
Same year.
Right.
Like someone was speculating they were trying to beat Alf to markets.
But I don't I can't confirm that.
There's something coming.
There's something on the horizon.
It's going to kill us.
A writer just stressed out.
We got to beat Alf.
I got to get this draft.
I don't know what this Alf thing is but people are talking about.
It's like Gabbo on The Simpsons.
You just heard the word Alf.
Alf is coming.
Oh shit.
We need our own Alf.
God damn it.
Every network is like we got to beat Alf.
I've heard he's some sort of alien puppet.
Like a Muppet?
Yeah.
Well kind of.
Kind of.
All right fine.
Well let's figure out our own character that's going to be just as enjoyable.
I don't know.
Fuzzbucket?
There's a cleanliness to Alf.
I mean three letters.
It's just so pared down.
It's perfect.
He talks.
He speaks in perfect English too.
Should Fuzzbucket?
No.
Should he like make funny quips?
He should just sort of be stressed and you know lick people.
Yeah and then like demand a kiss.
I don't want to get ahead of ourselves here but when Fuzzbucket demands a kiss from Mikey.
I'm glad we were all scarred by the same.
The rough shit.
The fancy kiss.
Some rough shit.
The writer director is a guy named Mick Garris and I have to say very interesting career.
Yeah I wasn't really familiar with this guy.
Directed the later TV adaptation of The Shining.
Directed a lot of TV Stephen King stuff.
The Stand.
That star studded version of The Stand.
Did an Amazing Stories.
He wrote an Amazing Stories that got an Edgar Award which is a mystery writers award.
The Fly 2.
The Fly 2 wrote Hocus Pocus.
Wrote Hocus Pocus.
The iconic stuff there.
Yeah created some of those horror, later horror anthology shows.
What was the Showtime one?
Was it Masters of Horror?
Masters of Horror and then NBC tried one called Fear Itself.
There's a lot of guys like that like Joe Dante I think he seems similar to career to Joe Dante.
He had some big stuff and then has done a lot of horror kind of anthology stuff.
Probably big in that world.
Yes very big in that.
Pulpy.
Really stuck to his guns in the genre.
He also he was seemingly part of something called Coming Soon.
That was I've never heard of it was a compilation of old horror trailers strung together with connective tissue.
It was segments with Jamie Lee Curtis.
Filmed on the Universal lot.
And that seemed to be the way that he came up with the producer of this film John Landis.
Maybe you're getting here but did you see he's an uncredited zombie in Thriller?
Oh yeah I do.
That's crazy.
Wow.
He's a Thriller zombie.
He worked on something too called is it Michael Jackson's Ghosts?
He was always part of Ghosts?
Oh I love Ghosts.
That was a later promotional.
He also made a lot of making of stuff.
I know way too much about ghosts and I won't get into it here.
But that's the bizarre Stan Winston thing that was paired the only way you could see it was paired with Stephen King's Thinner.
He had to wait around after Thinner to watch a very long much worse Thriller that also stars Mos Def.
Wow.
It's a very bizarre thing.
I have a lot of respect for the horror world.
I was never a horror kid and I don't understand it but I respect it as like seeing it as adjacent to like the comic book world or like the theme park kind of world.
I understand it.
I get it.
I get it folks.
And there's those people there's the Tony Baxter's of that world.
These like cult heroes to people who if either you maybe you don't know who they are if you don't know that world but if you do this person's like a hero to you.
Yeah.
And and I also I respect Fangoria for coming back and like not really putting much online like you have to track it down because like it came back in print.
That very first issue had like a long conversation between Jordan Peele and Paul Thomas Anderson.
Wow.
And I'm like I gotta find that somewhere like I guess I gotta find that issue of Fangoria.
This was this kicked off a pretty exciting summer for John Landis.
This aired in May 1986.
So all right.
Summer of fun and the summer ended around the beginning of September was the beginning of his manslaughter trial.
He was producing Fuzzbucket.
Wow.
This was one of the one of the projects three amigos as well.
I mean you probably spend more time on things he was directing but this was one of the things that happened between the Twilight Zone movie accident which killed actor Vic Morrow and two underage actors in which he was considered responsible for in some regard but then acquitted later.
But this is one of the things he did like between accident and trial.
Right.
I had no idea.
I thought what happened was he like went quiet or went underground after the accident.
No.
He made some of his biggest stuff at like the most things you know the most.
Training places was pretty soon after the accident.
Yeah.
Three amigos.
Into the night.
Coming to America is 88.
Right after.
It's so crazy.
Yeah.
I was trying to figure out what event in the the Twilight Zone accident happened closest to the release of Fuzzbucket and it is this and it's pretty good because I have a book about the whole thing.
I never remember the name like unjust conduct.
It's like it's like a really judgmental name.
But I got this book out.
And OK so May 86 Fuzzbucketers June 86.
They're trying to gather up people to testify in the trial.
One of the people is producer and Jimmy Buffett friend Frank Marshall.
Of course.
Who people have always thought knows more than he's ever said about.
He was on Island Time.
He doesn't know.
He was at a cocktail.
What happened?
Oh too bad.
Oh well another pink.
Whoopsie.
Apparently apparently the fire chief inspector was on fire time too.
Or I think I have fuck.
But like fire time.
This is the sort of Fuzzbucket you distracted me.
You're rearranging words.
You stupid son of a bitch.
That kind of happens at some point.
Why did I ever take care of you?
You never did nothing for me.
He gets really he really yells at Fuzzbucket.
The kid is right.
Yes he is.
He is right.
Yeah well I'll move into.
I'm sorry.
I'll move into.
But the.
So really quick.
So this is June.
They want to see if Frank Marshall will testify in the trial at the end of the summer.
But he is in London prepping who framed Roger Rabbit which he's producing.
So they send somebody from the American Embassy in England to go serve him.
And they go to his where he's staying and they buzz.
And he says oh sure.
You know what.
Look I'm busy right now.
But if you come back later in the afternoon I'd be happy to talk to you.
OK.
Sounds good.
Person leaves within a half an hour.
He is on a private Amblin plane to Paris.
I was well you added the you added the Amblin there.
I was assuming it would be like Buffett picks him up in his sea plane.
Were they buds yet though?
I don't know.
This might have pre dated.
They were.
Yeah they were for sure in the 90s mid to early 90s.
I'm not sure if they were yet but I like the idea that like Jimmy I need a I need a way out.
Jimmy flies the seaplane over with like a rope.
Climb aboard.
Or there's like a monkey holding like hanging on the rope and he like grabs Frank and they just sail away.
Fins up.
I would have thought he would have gone somewhere without extradition.
Right.
Paris isn't that far.
He's still going to get his work done.
I guess so.
Rebecca says a lot of demands.
Yeah no computer.
Finalizing the Hoskins contract.
Paris is like a Jimmy Buffett safe hold like a stronghold like he has control over Paris.
He lives in the Arc de Triomphe famously.
Don't go you're not allowed up there.
It's all island shit.
It's all deck chairs.
I think actually if you bring that up though Jimmy Buffett didn't get crazy crazy popular till the 90s till like the early 90s.
Sure yeah.
He wasn't like having the same success.
In the way that the Grateful Dead kind of like super came back as this tour and never went away but really exploded as a touring entity.
It seems like it was a similar like that's what really got him there.
Yes I think that's right.
So yeah maybe I'm not accusing Frank of not being a real fan or anything here.
I'm just saying maybe you may be right.
He might have been maybe he didn't know Buffy yet but he did he got in the private plane and like okay get me out of here.
Hey and could you put on something relaxing like volcano or something fun.
I'm stressed out.
Yeah.
I didn't look I'm not for violence on film sets but after learning that some of these timelines and recalling that Landis showed up at Vic Morrill's funeral.
I have to say Eddie Murphy might have been right to choke him on the set.
I'm coming to you to kick his ass.
I also just found the Arsenio Hall clip where Eddie Murphy says I'd more likely or Vic Morrill is more likely to work with John Landis than me.
Yeah.
But then he did on Beverly Hills Cup 3 the New Park one.
Was like 94.
Really soon he did it again.
Really soon like he just kept working.
How how did you how.
And then after that I feel like he kind of went quiet and he also I feel like John Landis I associate with like a few documentaries and those horror again those horror anthology.
He took safe haven yes in this.
Yeah yeah yeah.
Well he cooled the career down because you know he had to focus on his family.
Yeah.
That raising a great family.
Well as well.
Yeah sure.
That's all I have to say about that.
So fuzz bucket huh.
Fuzz bucket.
Well you know if you want to see a picture perfect American family.
I'm trying to I'm trying to find when Frank and Jimmy were friends.
Jimmy Buffett is in hook in 1991.
He's a shoe.
He's a pirate right.
He's a shoe stealing pirate in hook.
Uncredited.
Colin Collins and Buffett both pirates in hook.
Whoa.
Wow.
Do you think they taught they didn't they didn't cross over.
They've no no no.
That's too much to worry about.
You got like you know flying scenes.
Angela Roberts and Buffett and Collins on the same day.
I OK I just got very distracted.
I apologize because I looked at composer on Jimmy's IMDB and there's something called Mara Lagoville from 2019.
That's probably just him they used a song and some shit thing.
Because people attach like musicians to shitty IMD like to their crappy thing that they got on IMDB.
Well we have to find that.
I mean check it though.
I'll check it.
We'll do it later.
Sorry I got distracted.
Yeah.
So I bet that's just like somebody probably on IMDB.
That'll make Mara Lagoville really take off.
Right.
Guys we're going viral.
OK.
So fuzz bucket.
How do we briefly synopsize this film.
I tried to at the top a little bit but it's it's clearly very posty T.
It's a sort of troubled youth who's clearly like you know artistic and has a lot of imagination.
He starts talking to an imaginary friend and his family is skeptical.
And people at school are skeptical but it turns out that it was never imaginary.
It was this odd creature named fuzz bucket and now Mikey has to help him get back home.
Yes.
That's good.
That's that is what it is.
That's what the movie is.
Yes.
That's what it is.
That's not how it feels.
No no it feels like this is like going you're going through molasses or like a sludge through the dirt.
Unpleasant.
And there and there's no you would think maybe the movie is going to be like unpleasant until something happens magically.
And then it's just like it's just as bad.
Yeah.
Now there's a care like now there's a little character.
The things to elevate it the things that are visual just make it worse.
My favorite part of this.
Does anyone want to guess.
I don't know if I can.
Is it the dinner order.
No.
OK.
The principal.
No.
I mean that stuff is all fine.
My favorite is my favorite thing in the movie is the little child's name.
His name is Mikey Gerber.
Last name of my favorite people.
Cindy Crawford's husband Randy Gerber.
Got me.
So I like to think this is like maybe me if I was raised by Randy Gerber.
I like that is the one in I had for this movie.
They sort of whenever they would say Mikey and then they were talking about Mikey Gerber it would be like oh wouldn't it be cool to be Randy Gerber's.
But does that imply that Randy Gerber is like an overworked like unpleasant man whose job appears to be going to business where he just works a lot doing his work.
Like this was what he was doing maybe before like you know he had to build an empire or hit the tequila before the came when he and George magical suitcase was.
Yeah.
And the greatest story of all time.
Greatest story ever told.
Yeah this is I like to yeah this is him and George work.
This is him and George trying to figure out the tequila going to the places and learning about making alcohol.
And well that's what would have happened in the series is he would have made a tequila with fuzz bucket.
That green goo.
Yeah that's why the like oh putting the stuff in the blender.
This looks so weird.
And Worcester sauce and chocolate.
Let me.
Not bad.
I need to find the brilliant mixologist responsible.
Essentially created like a weird backwards mole sauce.
So I like to just the Casamigos connection is a my favorite part of fuzz bucket.
I this is a real little thing but when the mom like is in the car the key.
Mike he's up in his room and the mom yells out we'll be back.
We're going to get a pizza and some spaghetti.
So unpleasant to me and I have a table set set the table before we're home that combination like I pulled up some articles.
I should I meant to do this last night because I had them I didn't really get a chance to read them because I was like wait when did Buffalo wings become nationally popular like they were popular in Buffalo before they kind of went world like country wide 70s and 80s they took off more as a bar food and then I think like pizza restaurants started to add them once like Domino's and Pizza Hut started to add like once it reaches popular consensus.
So we know where fuzz bucket lands in the timeline of those helicopter deaths but not in the timeline of the rise of Buffalo wings.
I think I think throughout the country there's a common pizza and blank pizza and sandwich pizza even if they like maybe baked seedy but the only time I remember eating pizza and spaghetti is like all right.
All right. We're having left overnight like what's in the fridge like I was a couple of there's some spaghetti or some leftover pizza.
There's some like pork chop.
You'd be bad. Would you still be bothered by pizza and spaghetti.
I can scarcely imagine this would be a problem for you.
I would. It just felt like such an odd thing for a character to go say like I'm going to go pick up and order like not like that and that she clar clarified that it was pizza and spaghetti as opposed to like pizza and something else.
It's just odd. It's just if it just hit my ears in a weird way to carbs a lot of carbs.
It's a lot of carbs. Yeah. I hear what you're saying. Yeah.
We all gladly went to Bucatabepo and where you were what we had order pizza and spaghetti for every meal.
Yeah that's true. I feel like that's part of the experience the abundance right.
But they weren't going to get a better. No they weren't.
That's another we don't know when Bucatabepo I don't know where this falls in the Robert Earl timeline.
Right. Do we know if the rise of Buffalo wings coincides with the rise of Jimmy Buffett in the 90s.
Did he have an opportunity to brand them for himself. Right.
Buffett low wings. Buffett low wings.
I've had them at Margaritaville. I have had them. I think coincidentally it starts to like I do and maybe it's just as a kid you start to become cognizant of more things but it did feel like the 90s was like the like we got wings now.
Like you feel like that was a marketing ploy. But you feel if this had been filmed at a later time it would have been pizza and Buffalo wings.
Yeah. I just she had just said we're going to pick up some pizzas. That would have been fine.
But pizza and spaghetti just like felt so weird to me. I don't it just runs me such a wrong way.
And I was already like the movie had me in such a weird mood.
There's a point where they sit down to eat dinner and it's an unpleasant dinner and then it fades to the child sitting alone at the kitchen table in the near darkness.
Are you most of your complaints about the movie. The dinner and what type of dinner and the mood at dinner.
Because it's so unpleasant. Yeah. Little.
Do we ever see. Oh, I was gonna say. Oh, well, yeah, I was gonna ask. Do we see what fuzz bucket eats? Obviously we see the bizarre.
The goo that makes him seeable. Yeah.
Which I have some questions about. So yeah, he all right. Fuzz bucket is invisible for the first half of the movie and even we're questioning what's happening. Yeah.
Is he there? Right. And then at some point, somehow Mikey gets the mission to give him a bizarre drink that consists of every type of sauce that's in their house. Right.
And the drink pretty quickly makes him like you see liquid falling onto. It's like they took some shape and put it on green screen and poured liquid on it. So something starts forming.
And then people were saying how this is like the director, the horror guy couldn't resist getting all horary because it could just be a cute thing where now the creatures here, Bing.
But they have to step it out where first it's a skeleton. This is so crazy.
This was cool, but very upsetting. Yes. With a better context, maybe skeleton organs skin like blood and guts.
It doesn't. Yes. Mid part is so crazy. Just to underline what you're saying. When he transforms from invisible to visible, we first he's standing perfectly still and you see his skeleton and then you see his organs and it's like circulatory system fill in.
And it's slow. This takes a minute and a half. Yeah, it feels like.
And there's no reason.
Why would he be not be moving? Yeah, it feels like he's taxidermied until he actually moves once. It feels like he's being created. Now, like this feels like his creation.
Like why start of him? I forgot. I like kind of looked away for a second and didn't make the connection that like all the blended sauces was the green goo in the next scene.
And I was like, is fuzz bucket just drinking paint like they should not be making a kids movie where they're like, drink paint. So your friend appears like get a bunch of drink paint and you'll start seeing new friends.
But then the other big thing is like child acting against invisible friend is it's cheap. Like it's a cheap thing. Like you only have to have the costumed actor less.
It's so cheap and it's also so hard to go like, that's crazy. That's even crazier to like nothing.
Yeah, and he's fine. He's doing as good a job as he can, but he's pretty young. Yeah. Yeah, it's a lot of. Yeah, just watching this boy.
This boy dressed as bizarrely as I dressed as a child. It's like ill chosen three sizes, two big sweaters. It's it's all it's an unpleasant scene.
Yeah. Well, could we go back a little bit? Like if you were analyzing the movie, like what is this movie saying? What is it about?
I think it's about the failure of the mental health system in America for families and children. Yeah, that's that is kind of what I'm getting at because the idea is like the kid is acting out.
I guess even though you don't really see much evidence, he seems like a nice kid. But like everyone is so sure he's crazy. Yeah.
And problem like, can we stop with the fuzz bucket already? Thank you. I had an imaginary friend. Yeah. You would imagine a friend. Of course. Scott.
I remember if I did, you're not so committedly. Do you remember the name of yours? Because I remember mine. I have a bunch and I like talk to myself all day. I had a couple from things and just.
I had a couple too. Now that I'm thinking about it, I do. I will remember my mother loves telling the story. My imaginary friend's name was Doinkle Viner and he lived by the library.
Oh, wow. This is a revelation. Yeah. And you're sure this isn't the creep who you've muddied over time.
You mean this wasn't like a rat faced creature that lived underground that was actually real. It's not. It wasn't just like a street person who bought. Oh, I see what you're saying. And no, your mom didn't believe you. He had a house by the library.
I should have clarified that. Oh, good for doing great. He was doing great. My mom said I used to point out the house as we drove by and she I would be like, that's where Doinkle lives.
And she'd be like, oh, OK. Doinkle. And I think, yeah, Doinkle, which is good. It's a pretty good name if I think about it. Doinkle's good. And I think there was another I had another one that lived a guy who lived inside the shower massage or the shower.
Excuse me. There was a imaginary friend I had that lived inside of that. OK. Yeah. I don't know what that's about. That's some psychological. He's my friend I get to see when I'm naked. Yeah, there's something weird going on there, isn't it? Yeah.
Yeah, I think about now that I say that out loud. He looks down on me. Yeah, I think I said he like fixed it.
What? Fixed what? What? The shower. Just fixed it. This is all stuff I'm just coming up. I remembered I was coming in with Doinkle today, but I didn't remember. I think the guy's name was Howie who lived in the shower head.
And again, you're sure there wasn't just like a little haunted household and a man lived in the walls and watched you. There was a repairman.
There was a man who lived in our walls who watched me shower as a little boy. And now I'm just blocking it out. Is it possible? I guess anything is possible. My memory of it is lather up on the back.
Harrison Ford. My memory of it is that I think I remember thinking it was like almost like a David the Gnome style character inside the shower.
Well, he's benign. I mean, he's a good guy. Yeah, that's my memory of the character that I created. He's not watching kids to get his jollies. No, he's waiting to die. He's jolly already.
He's saddest thing of anything. We really should do some David the Gnome stuff. But yeah, David, if you haven't seen it, the finale, he was a little gnome person that lived in a village of other gnomes.
And he had a fox called Swift and they had like adventures. And then the final episode, he and his wife go out into the pasture and die.
And it is one of the saddest, shocking. And then the worst part about it is the fox watches. The fox sits and watches as he and his wife become trees and turn into like part of the part of the earth.
And yeah, anyway, so yeah, he was a nice guy. And that's my memory of that character who watched me shower.
So yeah, he was a nice guy. Yeah. So David the Gnome is what I've done. Turned into trees.
Hey, the fox had a second act in their career. They booked the part of the Chaos Reigns fox and Antichrist all those years later. You've seen that meme.
You probably haven't seen that movie. You probably haven't seen the movie.
No, I haven't. I should also add David the Gnome voice by Tom Bosley, the dad from Happy Days.
Oh gosh, yeah, that's nice. So dude, what do you think the shower guy sounded like? What was his name?
I think Howie? Howie? I think that's right. Howie?
Shower Howie. When are you going to have the money, Howie? When?
I think I'm trying to think of what it was like. I can't imagine. I don't think I ever talked to him. That's the thing.
I mean, but I mean, if I'm thinking now it's he sounds like Tom Bosley is the gentle voice of Tom Bosley.
So an old man is your shower. Yeah. Yeah. An old man lived in my shower. That's what I thought.
You didn't speak. You didn't have to. The connection was stronger.
My mom's going to be mad. My mom hears this. She'll oftentimes be mad.
Like she'll there'll be one detail like I'll get Howie wrong and she'll be like, you know, that's not the name of the character of your imaginary friend who lived in the shower.
And then I'll have to be like, I'll issue a correction, I guess. He lived in your toilet paper. Right. He said thanks every time you wiped.
The creepiest shit I've ever. Yeah, maybe that's the worst thing you've ever said. That's the weirdest thing.
You got to throw a fuzz bucket on mute on the TV. Oh, sure. I guess. Do we need to?
No, I thought we talked about that before. I thought you were joking.
Okay, never mind. No, I mean, my back is turned. Okay. Jason wants it and I'm happy to oblige.
I think it might actually even be loaded as long as as long as mute is the key word.
I don't want to hear that. The principal. Should we talk about the principal?
Well, yes, the principal. The kids, the parents are shit talking.
Mikey Garber and there may be the walls are paper thin. Yeah.
Yeah, poor kid is listening to like Mikey is a problem. He's making things up.
And like it says the full volume. Yeah, this kid is feeling like shit. It's like, don't you know your house?
Like, don't you know your house at this point? You know, you can go to talk about your kid without him hearing.
They need whisper something counseling or a vacation or something like it just feels like so much animosity right under the surface.
Yes. For all these characters know what caused it.
There's also a really like full volume. I'm working long hours for those kids. Feels like a ghost. Yes.
The dad is Joe Regal Budo, who, of course, we know from Murphy Brown.
And he's one of our all of our favorites who we were so delighted to see return when Murphy Brown made her triumphant return to the small screen with our favorite most likeable politician, Hillary Clinton.
So we were so like just obviously are excited to see Murphy again, but to see Joe Regal Budo, we've never stopped thinking of when will he come back?
Just as an all an event only to be topped by the Spectrum original man about you.
Well, I did think nothing would top the Spectrum original man about you.
And then I heard that there's a Turner and Hooch series coming to Disney Plus.
That's the only thing that I think could have topped those two things that you were talking about, how we all were so desirous to see.
We yes. OK, here's a question for everyone.
Does the mom pass the Helen test? Oh, I don't know.
Anyone catch her name? No.
No. I'm sorry. This is a trick question. She is credited solely as mom.
What? And that is credited though as dad.
All right. But the sister Stevie, she gets a name.
The mom and the sister are the biggest example of like underdeveloped women in maybe anything I've ever seen.
Like they give them nothing to do. The mom is concerned.
At some point, she says like she I think she punishes Mikey of like you're not leaving this table till you finish your dinner.
So then he just waits it out until darkness and then she comes downstairs and it's like, OK, I'll make you a sandwich.
And it's like, is that what he's going to actually eat now?
Wait, again, more food is nearly clean.
Like there's like a little pile of it.
I was like, this wasn't evenly spread on those pieces of bread.
I don't understand the power dynamic for this punishment.
The food is unpleasant, like puppet.
You're just like this food doesn't make sense.
Unpleasant. Everything is unpleasant.
The sister just despises the brother.
Yeah. And like Robin Lively, teen witch fame.
Yes. Like Lively's mom.
The mom was on Falcon Crest. Oh, I love the last season of Falcon Crest.
But yeah, she had nothing but everyone's a jerk to Mikey.
Even when she starts defending him, it's still unpleasant.
Like, he's not weird. OK, just everything's done like.
Yeah. And then and that's just all of that.
Forgetting the most unpleasant voice in the film, which is Fuzzbucket.
But I guess before that, what else is in the prelude?
Now are we at principle? Yeah, I guess so.
So Mikey starts he's starting junior high and the principal is a very recognizable figure.
He played Dean Wormer in Animal House, which I forgot.
I was like watching it and I was like, why is this so familiar to me?
And it's he's essentially playing the same character directed by John Landis.
Mm hmm. And what he says to Mikey, can I if I can do a line reading?
Because I am assuming you have the same line that I have written down.
I think so. Do you want to take some of it?
I have a video, but I'll let you do it. Yeah, you can do it.
You nervous about P.E.? A lot of the young fellows are at first not used to taking showers with the other guys.
Get real bad stomach aches, but they get over it soon enough.
I mean, Jesus, that is a sinister, sinister, like, threat, seemingly a threat.
Not used to taking showers with the other guy.
Like this is the airplane you ever seen a grown man naked line, but delivered straight.
That's what it reminded me. It didn't occur to me until then. Yeah. Yeah.
The real life version. Yeah. Similar vibe of a guy. Very straight and young.
Stomach aches. The way he says it, too, is just so evil.
It's so scary. Then he turns the blinds right after.
Yeah. It's a great performance for a different movie. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. One day performance. He didn't get a vibe on what is the tone of his bucket.
He got some scripts mixed up. He thought he was making an adaptation of The Chocolate War
about the very strict boarding school and then someone dies.
It's just so intense. It's just like this guy is great, but he is again in the wrong picture.
You know, if you need someone to help usher you into the shower, kind of to be your guide.
I'm more than happy to lead you by the hand. Introduce you to the other boys.
They've seen me in there a number of times. Nothing to worry about.
You are saying that the implication is from this conversation.
Got a big bottle of Tums if that stomach aches back. You know, lot of young fellas.
You want to talk about being scared of seeing your friends dicks?
Is that what we need to talk about here? Not a big deal.
You get over it soon enough. You'll get over it. Soon enough.
Describe some of what scared you. Could you describe the details of some of the things you might be imagining?
Did anyone watch this back when they shot it? Because you know, making movies and TVs is hard.
It's hard.
You know, and sometimes maybe you shoot a scene and you don't know what it feels like until maybe you're watching the playback.
Did anyone go, this is fucking weird?
Yeah.
Did anyone think that?
Because also is the same scene maybe done like a, are you nervous about PE?
Are you nervous about probably seeing some of the other boys? What am I saying?
I'm verbal diarrhea-ing. Like if you play like he doesn't know how to help and he doesn't realize he walked himself into it, that he's digging himself a hole.
But instead he seems committedly, I am going to talk out the shower issue very slowly.
Did you guys have to shower in PE? We didn't do that. We changed for gym.
I think we avoided it somehow.
In high school?
Or middle school.
Not in middle school. Well, yeah, no, not in middle school, but in high school when we swam.
Oh, even in swimming, we would just like rinse off in our bathing suits and then just change.
Well, yeah, I guess you're right. I guess we would rinse off in the bathing suits and then, but we would still like change in front.
You try to like hide it with your towel.
Yeah, hide it with a towel. I think I have to remind myself like TV and film usually written by like dorks.
Some of who like had traumatic high school experiences and that's why there's always like plots about like showering or climbing the rope.
Like I've never climbed a rope. Like that was such a trope.
Yeah, a lot of those things that I've spent, I spent my whole childhood afraid of things that were going to happen in high school that did not happen.
Yeah, I didn't like it. Also, by the way, I didn't like it.
Like I was a little bit traumatized by the idea of like, and then you got to like take your clothes off in front of everyone.
You?
Yeah, believe that or not.
But once you had to do it, and there's nothing wrong with a shower because you got a little buddy up there.
I'm still with you.
I followed you to high school.
Now I'm watching all of the boys.
Hey, what?
I've got eyes on every boy now.
Howie, what are you doing here?
I don't know how to do Tom Bosley.
Yeah, I have the gnomes.
I was just watching an interview with a, what's her name? Mariam, who played the mother on Happy Days.
And she used to say she used to tell stories and Tom Bosley would be like, no one gives a shit, Mariam.
Like just ruining his reputation as like a kindly old man.
It's always the way.
I don't know, I think his stock just went up for me.
I don't like that he's doing it to his nice seeming.
Yeah, very like sweet.
Actress partner, but oh boy.
Now I'm going to be in the rest of this podcast as we, you know, any episode as we go on and on, I'm going to imagine him.
Nobody gives a shit.
David the gnome, like not like in the middle of a lesson.
Who the fuck cares about this shit?
Tom Bosley.
It's a ride. You go on it, you move on.
Fuck you.
Father Dowling with a foul mouth.
Father Dowling.
He was Father Dowling.
Yeah, he was Father Dowling.
Scott, if you turn around, you can see the body horror.
Oh, here it is.
Oh yeah, this is kind of where we are narratively.
Oh.
Here's Fuzz.
This is Fuzzbucket.
We're watching him appear again.
Again, a skeleton face.
A little animal, a human that's short of the tail.
A dinosaur with a human skull.
Yeah.
I would say like a little dinosaur with a human skull.
I guess in a human rib cage.
Why the guts step?
Yeah, this is like, yeah, this is he's getting a little bit of like his horror voice out.
So slow.
The slowest is all you've ever seen.
It's also exactly like the last scene of the movie Zardoz, where Sean Connery and wife
experience all of life through a series of fade shots that don't move.
Right.
They have a baby, the baby gets old, the baby leaves, they get old.
They have the worst press day experience you've ever seen.
They turn into skeletons still holding hands.
Which is not.
And then they're piles of dust.
That's not dissimilar to what happened to David the Gnome and his wife.
Wow.
That sort of fuzz bucket is just making us stare at this picture of death.
Doesn't say it's not so bad.
Just a couple of fades and it's all over.
It's just near a nice tree.
This another big 80s go to for kids entertainment.
This kid has like the most elaborate tree house.
At some point they liked him enough to either get a house with a tree house or build the
tree house for him.
It's a very book of Henry.
I was desperate for a tree house like this.
And this is just like impossible to build this.
Yeah.
Also incredibly dangerous to just climb a rope up to like two stories to a house.
You'd have a ladder.
You'd have to have some sort of a ladder.
Well, speaking of building the tree house, if we want to jump around a little bit, this
might be a good point to talk about the Michael Eisner intro, which frustratingly is not
included on Disney Plus, but you can look it up on YouTube.
I'd seen it before and it's wonderful to see Michael Eisner and Mickey and Fuzzbucket
all interacting and in a rare peek behind the curtain, he actually says what sound stage
the set of the tree house is built in.
It's on stage four of the Disney lot, which is the was eventually the home improvement
stage.
And it's today where Black-ish is filmed.
So if you act or work on Black-ish, remember this was once Fuzzbucket's home.
It was also it was originally it was they actually split stage four eventually into
two different sound stages, four and five.
It was originally the hugest sound stage they had and they built it to do force perspective
for Darby O'Gill and the little people.
They had a light people, they had people really far away to make them look extremely small.
And that took so much light buried deep.
They had needed so much light to pull off this effect that one time while they're filming
that movie, they blew out the power grid for all of Burbank.
The entire city got fucked by Darby O'Gill.
Wow.
Also on Disney Plus.
Worth it.
Yes.
One of the finest.
We'll watch that soon.
The kid has a for the time normal sized TV in the tree house.
Oh, yes.
And now.
OK.
So this is where this is one of the first creepy things is the first time we actually
see Fuzzbucket and they're hanging out and we see what their dynamic is like.
And very quickly he Fuzzbucket requests tunes, tunes, tunes, just very upsetting.
And they watch a cartoon together and the cartoon is seat central.
It is nothing but chickens turning around and showing their rears and then they're
watching this and they fall asleep arm in arm.
Yeah.
So now this has become a movie where a boy and a possum cuddle while watching chicken
skirt shots.
I think he likes Fuzzbucket because Fuzzbucket is not openly cruel or dismissive to him,
unlike most of the other characters in this movie.
But Fuzzbucket still treats him like shit, I would argue.
You have to look at it.
This is some fun.
I was just going to Fuzzbucket to describe if you don't know what he looks like at this
point, he looks like a facially balding Ewok.
Like if he if an Ewok has started going bald on its face, like that's how Ewoks go bald.
Yes, skin.
Yeah.
Wow, you know if you shaved your cat or dog, how awful their skin would look.
Fuzzbucket, that jump.
That jump is the funniest shit.
That's like Mack and Me style.
It's very Mack and Me.
And that's something I thought while watching this that we all owe Mack and Me a big apology.
Yeah, yeah.
Because Mack and Me, obviously, if you don't know what this extremely unpleasant E.T. ripoff,
but I found I've I've sat through all Mack and Me several times and there's parts like
obviously the Paul Rudd used a clip on Conan, the wheelchair falling.
There's parts of it that are so much fun or the Mack dancing in a teddy bear suit and McDonald's.
Did you see the clip that was edited out?
I said I showed it to Jason.
There's a clip from Mack and Me where he gets shot with like an automatic weapon wheelchair.
Yeah, there's a standoff.
The kid.
What?
Yeah, I should check.
He gets shot.
Wait a minute.
Because I know the movie because there's a huge explosion and then he dies essentially and the alien family
all has to bring him back to life.
But you don't you don't understand why the fire killed him.
He gets shot in the gut.
So in the cut in the full scene, he's just shot with the assault rifles.
Let me see if I can throw this up on. Let's see how easy this will be.
From one unpleasant post E.T. film to another.
Mack just ran into like Stevie, his sister and her friends.
They're very E.T.s.
I pulled up. Here is the scene from.
Oh, and now the Mack's parents have guns too.
Oh, it's the police.
The police have opened fire with handguns and shotguns.
Now the explosion I know, but I always wondered why he dies.
Yeah, so there it is again.
Mack.
He gets shot.
And the alien points at the police, but it looks like he's pointing as if he has a weapon.
He does not.
It's only on the Japanese media release.
Yeah, so that's the funniest thing I've seen in a long time.
Wow. Thank you for that.
You're welcome.
Geez. Yeah, I do love Mac and Mac and me is in the bizarre.
Have you seen the bizarre trailer with the Ronald McDonald intro?
I believe so. Yeah, because they helped produce.
Ronald, you're needed in makeup.
Makeup me.
It's the creepy laughter of not unlike your pet.
Oh, right.
That laughter.
Fuzzbucket hides in the mailbox, which is unpleasant.
Although shout out to the good people of the United States Postal Service.
They do great work.
How did you get into the mailbox?
Well, apparently he gets in the like latch on the bottom of it.
Like he just got out of it.
And then, of course, the Mikey gets yelled at by like a homeless man who was there to be just another character to yell at Mikey.
This around this point in time, Aaron, my wife pointed out who liked one thing about the movie, which is that it was 45 minutes.
She really lit up when she saw that runtime.
But mainly around here, she asked, well, why, as we've said, why does Mikey like Fuzzbucket?
Because it seems like as soon as Fuzzbucket comes into his life, nothing but bad things happen.
His parents get more unpleasant.
He's yelled at by a homeless person.
He's brought into the principal's office.
His sister's friends start talking shit about him.
He sees a rat and has to throw a can at it.
It's on our screen right now.
He has to spend the night homeless, essentially like Fuzzbucket causes nothing but shit.
It's implied by the mom at one point that Mikey does have friends like he's like, I called all his friends houses, but they do not appear to be present.
I guess if this was a pilot for a series, we'd meet more characters.
Presumably would introduce his friends to Fuzzbucket.
Who is he dressed like?
I'm trying to think there's somebody he's really dressed like right now.
Fuzzbucket is wearing Elaine Stritch.
It's kind of like the glasses.
I think the glasses are using the glasses and the floppy hat.
The only other Elaine Stritch look is with the long dress shirt with the no pants on or the spanks kind of a look on.
We're in the heart of the worst part of the movie.
The most terrifying part.
Mikey had to throw a rat clamped onto Fuzzbucket's tail while he was in a dumpster.
Mikey threw a can at the rat.
And then Fuzzbucket ran off and for some reason on the way out licks Mikey's hand.
He licks a young boy's hand.
And I have some of the dialogue written down because I don't.
There's a lot of resistance to like, can I come see where you live?
And he's always, no, no house, no, not good for you.
Home going, home going, can't go poof no more.
We're going to talk about, I guess we could talk about his voice real quick.
Yeah.
My first thought about his voice was, is this Sterling Holloway?
Yes, me too.
This sounds like Winnie the Pooh.
And it is not, but it is of course, and let me look up his name unless you have the name right there.
Hal Smith.
Hal Smith, who is owl on Winnie the Pooh.
Strangely.
Strangely and has done Winnie the Pooh at least once.
Took over as Pooh before Jim Cummings.
He was briefly an 80s Pooh.
And I'm assuming you saw the specific TV movie I'm about to mention, Too Smart for Strangers.
I did not.
Pooh and it is.
Oh, is it the one, the live action one?
The terror, can you see?
Oh God, it's, of course, that's where I know the voice.
Another one of the creepiest things I've ever seen.
Yeah, so like live action Pooh before the Disney Channel live action Pooh?
Maybe.
Do you know, did you watch Welcome to Pooh Corner?
Was that the puppet Pooh?
Yeah.
They were in suits.
It's a lot of like green screen backgrounds.
Kind of, and that was 90s, 80s.
What is this Too Smart for Strangers though?
Is it like a PSA kind of movie?
It's a PSA type movie that also should be on Disney Plus.
Yeah.
Wait, really quick.
Does it, I don't remember the parts offhand, but it's like he has to go into like if someone
touches you in a way you don't want to be.
Yeah, it's like they do real stuff about like getting to, it's, this is a boy.
Pooh Corner is before, is 83.
So when we were watching Pooh Corner, it was obvious, it was old.
When I was watching it on Disney Channel as a kid, it was already old.
It felt that way to me.
Most of going to elementary school in the 90s was being taught to reduce, reuse, and
recycle and tell a trusted authority figure if a less trusted authority figure touches
you in a weird way.
That was most of public education during the Clinton Bush administration.
Hellsmith was for sure Pooh on that as Pooh Corner as well.
God, he's like haunted my brain.
I knew it was, so he's, it is this weird alternative Pooh who only acts in things that involve
like molestation and boy touching.
Hellsmith has cornered the market on.
I mean, that is one way to put his career into perspective.
I mean, not all of it.
That's unfair.
Just fuzz bucket has a lot of creepy shit and then, and a lot of like meetings of the principal
and then this creepy Pooh special.
He also is, which I'm very excited about, Otis the town drunk on Andy Griffith.
Oh, yes, of course.
He did.
He also apparently was Santa Claus consistently anytime Santa Claus was on the Flintstones,
which I guess was a lot.
Yeah, I guess.
I don't have any memory of that.
According to credits, like he did it in the 60s and 80s.
Really?
He needed Santa a lot.
When we was, since we mentioned the voice, I just looked, I forgot I wrote down at the top of my second page of notes.
His voice is just awful.
Fuck.
Once he appeared, I had a visceral reaction.
Once he started talking.
Go poof.
He was Santa Claus on bonkers as well.
What?
Okay.
And in the town Santa on Cartoon Network in 1993.
He was also in Camp Candy, which I believe is a John Candy cartoon.
The whole very unpleasant theme song.
Yeah.
And then he was in Beauty and the Beast.
He played Jafar's horse in Aladdin.
What?
Jafar had a horse?
I guess.
I don't remember this.
And he did owl for a long time.
But then they kicked him out and had Jim Cummings do it.
Well, it's while you're here.
It's cheaper.
I guess.
But he's the original owl?
I believe so.
From the look of it, 19.
Well, when was the first poo?
To the 60s, I think.
Also to go back to the Eisner intro.
That's the first I ever heard the voice.
And he magically appears.
And then there's this little scene that requires a lot out of Eisner.
Eisner has to do a cross.
He has to get out of the way.
And you can tell physical action is tough for him.
And a little acting scene.
But then just forever and ever and not in his usual backwards language,
you just get to hear Fuzzbook kiss Mickey Mouse's ass.
Just a total sick of fan.
I've seen all of your movies more times than I could count.
The great Mickey Mouse.
I watched your show.
And Mickey buys it hook line and sinker.
See through this guy.
He just wants something out of you.
He's new at the company.
And he knows you're at the top of the food chain.
But instead Mickey's just like, sure.
That's a lunch.
We're going to cheese omelet.
And it's clearly the in the bin.
It's the same Mickey for sure.
Off Mickey.
This is not standard issue Mickey.
So these two voices combined.
Oh, it's mixed with all.
It's clear that Fuzzbucket is a user.
Straight up.
And they are writing him in that.
I actually didn't not see the intro, but it's clear.
They're writing the character consistently.
He is a user.
Fake friend.
He's a fake ass friend.
And at least they were consistent, I'll say.
But Mickey shouldn't.
So you're finding a good valuable lesson for kids.
Legitimately on Fuzzbucket.
But they don't really spell that out.
No.
You have to read into the subtext of Fuzzbucket to know this is about like a leech in your life who just wants your connections.
Towards the end of the movie, they have assembled a posse.
Like an actual search party.
Police Rangers.
The fugitive.
They're hunting for like a missing child.
Outhouse, backhouse.
Like this is serious.
Like our child is missing.
We don't know what happened.
We might be mentally unwell.
Tommy Lee Jones with a gun at Fuzzbucket.
No, no, make me go poof.
I don't care.
Bang, bang.
No, no.
Don't point metal.
Bang, bang.
It's Fuzzbucket.
There's also now in that search party part.
Sorry to jump around.
But Mikey is found and his ordeal in the cave is over.
And there's a great part where his parents and then some officer you don't know, they're just kind of walking up towards the set of trees.
And then the officer is like, look, there's something.
Wait, wait, pan over.
The something is Mikey just lying on the ground.
What's that pile of rocks?
No, that's the boy.
The boy.
Then Fuzzbucket goes for the cops.
I want freedom for fellow Fuzzbucket.
Yeah.
Grant us amnesty.
Mikey right now, what we're watching is he's underground now.
He finds the Fuzzbucket like family.
They just live in like tunnels.
They live in dead man's marsh.
Dead man's marsh.
No humans go there.
A murder of Fuzzbucket.
A group is called a murder of Fuzzbucket.
And then Fuzzbucket is about when Fuzzbucket, so Mikey sees a bunch of the Fuzzbuckets and they all get scared and they run away from each other.
And then he's about to meet Fuzzbucket because he's like very dejected that he hasn't found Fuzzbucket.
And here comes Fuzzbucket with the best line in the movie.
Oh, what's this?
Do you know what I'm talking about?
No, you get this one.
You know what I'm talking about though, right?
I can't remember.
How are we doing, party boy?
Now that's a real cousin of that thing that was that Mickey in drag says, fresh boy.
Oh, oh, fresh.
Oh, yeah.
Soak your head, fresh boy.
Yeah, yeah.
Definitely.
Soak your head, fresh boy.
Oh my God.
How are you doing, party boy?
How are we doing, party boy?
Fuck.
In this, if you were-
The rock and roll clown does cocaine.
And we're, he also, or also around this time, he says, use the noodle, fellow.
Yeah.
Awful.
And if we, this is truly the creepiest zone you've ever seen because it really set the tenor to hear how we doing, party boy.
And then, Mikey, the boy who doesn't want to go back to his home, he wants to stay in the cave with Fuzzbucket and he conveys this by saying, I want to be with you.
Oh God.
Yes, he says that.
It's a say anything feel.
I want to be with you.
And then, and the response to that is, aw, funny boy.
Horrible.
Yeah, horrible.
This is, this film is pornography for the worst person who's ever lived.
Like the most disturbed person.
Yes, I don't even know.
I don't even have a full picture of that person's brain who would be really, really into this.
This is, okay, so then Fuzzbucket, he's telling him, you can't, look kid, you can't stay here.
You can't, what we had was nice, but you can't stay here.
Like that's essentially what he was saying.
And then Mikey is starting to be the saddest kid and he's like, but we were friends, right?
You weren't using me.
Yeah, of course.
No, we were friends.
We're friends.
No, you can, all right, five years from now you get tonight's your fair and square.
Yeah.
Mikey, tonight's yours, but enjoy it, buddy.
Five years away.
Nothing's wrong.
Nothing's going to go wrong.
You're a good guy.
You're a family guy.
You're a family man.
Jay Leno is now Fuzzbucket.
Also around this.
You can have the cave after me.
She's all you want.
And then, well, and also, maybe we haven't given enough time to the family.
We haven't.
I found an article that noted.
We've also got 90 minutes.
I knew we.
Well, no, an hour and 15.
Okay, okay.
So longer than the film.
Much longer.
But no, don't, whatever you want to say about the family, I don't have a heart out.
They're called just he calls them Fuzzbuckets, even though his name is Fuzzbucket.
Right.
So a group of them is is are just they are a Fuzzbucket, I guess.
And then when Mikey sees them for the first time, they're all just marching in place in this bizarre cramped court, which is a whatever they whatever ritual they are doing.
Aaron dubbed this buzzfucking.
Whatever it is that they're up to.
Yeah.
You caught the boy caught us buzzfucking.
They're horrible.
And then they're like giving him only one of them is named Stinky.
Thank you.
Which is cute.
I mean, that could be a term.
Endurance.
Jason loves Stinker.
Jason loves Stinky.
New fuck has nicknamed Stinky Stinky Sheridan.
And he but Stinky.
All he does is go like he just like glares at Mikey.
Right.
He wants to eat him and Fuzzbucket says others crabby, but OK.
And then how does the kiss come about?
You mean Scott this kiss?
What's the actual line?
Can you maybe put on the audio for me?
I'll turn the audio off.
Hold on.
So if you weren't creeped out enough already.
Yes, the little boy and the possum monster kiss.
Sorry.
We're just listening to this.
Oh, I see.
Stinky sucks.
Stinky bad apple.
Oh, no, I didn't know he was a bad apple.
OK.
You love Fuzzbucket?
Give smooch.
You love Fuzzbucket.
Here's what I thought just now.
I have the words you give Fuzzbucket, give smooch written down in my notes.
And I was like, is that an idea for a bit or something I wanted to do?
No, those are the lines in the film.
You love me?
How much do you love me?
Show me you love me.
Prove, show me your love.
Oh, God.
Put some love on me.
Horrible.
What does he say about his eyes, too?
Baby blues, right?
Didn't he say baby blues?
Yeah, he did.
I know.
He's getting over the context.
Oh, my God.
Again, that you are a parent and your child is an actor and you let him near a John Landis
movie.
I mean, come on now.
Come on now.
Yeah, I.
Yeah.
All right.
He got off on that.
He wasn't.
He was acquitted of manslaughter, but he should have been banned from having any children
on his set.
Yes.
And he said every and probably should have been banned from having children.
That's another matter.
Horrible.
I.
He's the journey of this boy in 45 minutes from a principal talking to him about showering
to he's trapped in a cave where a creature is making him kiss him where a possum creature
blows him off.
You know, but first makes him kiss.
Gotta go.
No, we can't hang out, but kiss me, though.
They get over it.
He's trying enough.
He tries to fuzz bucket, tries to ghost him, first of all.
And then when he finally tracks him down, he's like, yeah, yeah, we're friends.
Hey, kiss me and then leave.
Fuzz bucket's a fuck boy.
Yes.
Damn fuck boy.
He's a friend.
Fuck boy.
Yeah.
That's true.
Fuzz Buck's a fuck boy.
Oh, I was going to say fuck bucket.
I don't like it.
You know what they should call me.
Is this the most unpleasant thing we've talked about on the Patreon?
Maybe.
What's worse than this?
Well, the paddling, the paddle coming for your ass.
Yeah, but that's not unpleasant.
I guess.
I don't, I didn't care for it.
Well, of course, in the Las Vegas story where you were worried there was a paddle coming
for your ass.
I mean, maybe that.
From the stern female owner of the German.
The Ubermensch.
There has been.
Oh, sorry.
What is the same when Jason threw $20 on the table and said, I got to get out of here
because he was too high and he was worried about a woman paddling.
A sausage sandwich.
That's why I got to get out of here.
Like, this is too much.
It was too big.
You had to pay for the paddling.
She wasn't going to paddle you without like a monetary exchange.
A lot to figure out if you're high.
Yeah.
I mean, I think watching Fuzzbook, it probably made you feel as stressed out and paranoid
as being trapped in a beer hall where a woman was going to paddle you.
It's a, it's a trap.
This movie is a trap.
Man, this.
It really makes Mr. Boogity look good.
It makes the Apple dumpling gang look like Citizen Kane.
Like I was at the record show.
Like Apple, people have positive memories of Apple dumpling gang.
Don Knotts, Tim Conway, esteemed careers.
Like I think that's a different ballpark.
That's a different genre.
I would agree with you.
Disney plus first came out.
I was like, Oh guys, remember Apple dumpling gang?
And yes, we respect the Apple dumpling gang.
We respect the Apple dumpling gang.
I respect Boogity.
Yeah, Boogity I thought was pretty fun.
And I ended up liking the performance and the guy and even the stuff that happens in the interim.
This is just 45 minutes of horror.
There is more 45 minutes ones on Disney plus.
Are there?
I think there's other ones.
Well, if you want us to watch anything else, 45 minutes helps.
Oh, it really does.
Yeah.
45 minutes to an hour.
Oh, and you know what got the most likes I should say is the, the Mickey Mouse short potato land, which, you know, which thanks for the suggestion.
I watched it.
It's wonderful.
I remember Lindsay telling me about it a while back.
It's really great.
It's a lot of fun.
You know, there's not 90 minutes worth of nightmares to describe with the very good theme park referencing potato land.
Yeah, I do recommend potato land.
Sure.
Maybe we should have though.
Maybe there's still time.
I'm trying to think if anything else in that tweet, because we got a list.
Nick, who suggested this, gave us a list, like a big list of reasons why we should consider this one.
I do want to make sure I hit the list.
We hit a lot of them.
I mean, we did.
This is a yeah, this is just a legitimate search party.
They do find the kid.
They find Mikey.
Again, I cannot.
Yeah, the mom, the mom in this is like nothing to do.
And the last bit is that.
Oh, the parents, right?
Well, they get gifts.
Oh, yes. Yeah.
Yeah.
So fuzz bucket.
So yeah, basically they all go home.
When the parents find gifts in the house for them and it's what the gifts are, what again, nicely do they open them?
It's a like a music box and a novelty sized Hershey kiss.
But nicely wrapped, right?
It's just a foil of a kiss.
OK, I see.
I don't know how the music box was wrapped, if it was.
But yeah, he buys Phantom presents for this fighting couple and they neither of them question where did this come from?
They just look at each other and gaze at each other and kiss.
And then there's eerie green footprints on the carpet and he's running out the window.
I like it from behind.
They don't believe fuzz bucket exists.
So the idea that some stranger came into our bedroom and gave us gifts and they're just like, haha.
But I think they did it for each other.
Now, I miss that.
I see.
I think it's happening.
You do love me.
You know, I like big chocolate.
Wow.
And that's music.
So chocolate isn't a good way.
Jason, Jason, you'd rather have a bunch of small kisses instead of having a gnawed giant.
Well, you know, that's one of the issues with the chocolate frogs at Harry Potter is it's just a giant chunk of solid milk chocolate.
It's a novelty and a novelty isn't going to put a marriage back together.
Yeah, they're going to have to scrub the toxic goo waste out of the carpet.
They're all going to get like the fights are going to begin instantly from fuzz.
Is he bleeding?
The way he walks.
He's got himself.
Is he bleeding?
Fuzz bucket's green blood is bleeding out the bottom of his feet as he goes on the carpet.
Bleed from foot.
Bleed.
Blood's bleeding.
Bleed for you.
Bleed cut me.
And coming up next, Mr. Boogity.
All right.
Well, and you know, notably it is the I can't believe I recognize the Landis font.
All of his things are the same font.
Interesting.
So that's mainly because I don't really sense his stamp on it in any other way.
But I but good job standardizing the font.
Mike, scroll down to suggest it.
What's that second one in?
I read about this one.
It's the ghost of Buckley Hall.
It's about.
OK, so this is from 1980, even though it looks like it's from 1960.
Ghost inhabiting a cast strapped Academy enlists the help of a shy cadet.
Now, this is an hour and 32 minutes.
This is a full feature.
And 1980, if you think about the world in 1980, this this looks like a ancient,
ancient movie.
20s.
So who wants ghosts of Buckley Hall?
Let us know.
Hashtag bucks us up.
I got a little for case busters.
Also, I've watched Sultan in the Rockstar yet.
Oh, gentle tiger being hunted for sport.
See details for advisory.
What in the heck?
47 minutes. Let me add this.
Another 47 minutes.
Go to details.
What is the advisory?
Oh, oh, yeah.
That's spot on Disney Plus where it's like outdated cultural depictions.
Uh huh.
What are they warning us about?
From his fans and obligations to hide out on what appears to be an island
paradise.
When he arrives, he discovers a tame tiger living in the jungle and befriends it,
but then learns that the island's cruel owner is hunting it for sport.
Will you risk it all to save this gentle beast?
Contains tobacco depictions.
That's it.
That's all.
Yep.
Unbelievable.
Timothy Hutton.
Wow.
They should have had the cigarettes out of the tiger's mouth.
Oh my God.
What is can of worms?
I don't know.
I think maybe a Disney 99.
This is a scary ass fucking worm.
He's cool.
He is cool, but he's also scary.
Um, yeah.
So there's a lot of like Pillsbury.
I would do.
I would do a plus this up again, as unpleasant as this was.
Yeah.
I think this is an interesting little experiment.
There's maybe something that I don't want to tilt the scales is maybe something to meet
the details.
People were making a good case about case busters, ironically.
Uh, so I don't know.
Maybe let's maybe we'll do it again.
Just look out on Twitter if we do it again.
Um, but for now, uh, as fuzz bucket would say, how many clocks, how many clocks, which
means, uh, times, times out.
I'm declaring it is no, I'm not talking about this anymore.
Yikes.
I can't believe we did.
We had that much to say, but I think we needed the therapy.
Yeah.
Just like the parents.
As long as fuzz bucket more pleasant.
We'll bring back.
Uh, we will again, we are always saying how available we are, but we are available to
bring fuzz bucket back to Disney plus still.
Yes.
You still want to do this IP, uh, for this bit that I've started here.
I'll do for the bit, but I will say this.
Uh, I have a big threshold for characters and finding them pleasant that other people
might find unpleasant.
Uh, I do hate fuzz bucket.
He does suck.
He fuzz bucket sucks.
Well, we'll keep talking about this.
We all hit the showers.
I know you two are nervous, but you'll get over it soon enough.
Yeah.
You nervous about what the other podcast hosts might say and what they might look like down
there.
Calm down.
You'll get over it.
They all do.
All right.
If somehow you desire to stay subscribed to podcast, you paid for this.
And when you just heard, you paid for it.
You made us do this.
This is entire you.
This is what us rot.
Enjoy it.
They're not all the gruff hours for you kids.
So enjoy it, but enjoy the next stretch of unpleasantness.
Tell your friends to sign up for this.
Make them suffer too.
It's these guys.
They talk about awful shit.
All right.
Bye bye.
You survived by the second gate.