Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast may contain a 456 foot high view of a parking lot.
It may also include an erstwhile margarine spokesman and a high degree of branding for
got to be glued hair spiking glue.
We journey to a jungle called New Jersey with Dan Klein to talk about Kingda Ka at Six Flags
Great Adventure on podcast The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, a podcast about theme parks where today at least one host will
speak with authority about a ride he would never ever go on.
I'm that guy, Scott Gardner.
I don't know about my co-hosts, Mike Carlson.
Before this podcast, I think I wouldn't have gone on it, but now I do feel I have like
going on when I went on hang time with Jason Sheridan, the other co-hosts.
He's here as well.
I don't know that I would have done that, Coaster of Knots, if not for the podcast.
You know what I mean?
Right.
I got you into shape, which I feel to some extent, but this is far beyond what I would.
Right, but I'm saying there's scales like you were not doing drop rides, you were not
doing launch.
So now you're doing that.
I was doing that before.
So now I have to take it up a notch.
From where you were at, but I'm still handicapped.
I still have my handicap.
Right. So maybe two years you'll be doing Kingda Ka.
Maybe so. And in two years, I'll be like hanging out of like a plane or something.
I am disappointed myself.
I haven't been on this.
Yeah. It's a little after my time of going to Great Adventure.
That was my childhood Six Flags.
Well, Jason, you started like you since you started the podcast with a higher threshold
than all of us for you to take it up higher.
Do you have to like try auto erotic asphyxiation or like what you ever do?
You should do a you should do auto erotic asphyxiation, but then do a halo jump
like Tom Cruise did in Mission Impossible Six.
Oh, yeah. So you get like a huge boner and then jump out of a very high plane.
My thing that I usually don't do with parks is anything where it's like an additional add on.
I mean, partly I'm cheap.
Second, like it's always like a slingshot that a teenager like.
It's always like a scrap metal capsule.
Oh, yeah. On bungee.
And it's like for an extra twenty dollars, you can be launched into the sky.
Which they have at Six Flags, Magic Mountain.
Yes, which they do have there.
Which you just are like Superman.
Did you see this? Did I send you a video that there's just a thing where you you
and like three people, they get stacked together like Superman,
and then they just let you go off of a bungee and you go back and forth
on a bungee like Superman.
And it looks just it looks very cheap.
It looks very scary.
Yeah. And kind of the bigger the town in the Jersey shore,
the more likely you are to have launches or bungee jumps or something like that.
And when we when we run out of rides from Disneyland Universal,
the three of us will have to just go do random teenager run slingshot.
We will. Well, sure.
A month of slingshot experiences together.
Three Superman. All right.
We'll talk about that. We got years to go for now.
OK, we should say that today today's topic is the world's tallest roller coaster.
And we're talking about it with one of the world's tallest comedians
in terms of talent.
He's a writer for AP Bio and great news and much other great stuff.
The very funny Dan Klein.
Yes, I think I'm five foot eight.
So regular size man, but the talent, but talent.
Why? 400 something feet tall is that?
Kingda Ka is four hundred fifty six feet.
So I've been on it multiple times.
OK, so in terms of bravery, yes.
Maybe one of the most brave guests.
You can rank in terms of actual height at where you feel you fall on the scale.
It's yes. Yeah.
And certainly the brave.
I'm the only one that's been on it here.
So, you know, yeah, I'm the bravest person here. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Quite. Yeah. Quite easily.
And how many times like a couple of times to several times?
I like so
basically I would go to Six Flags Great Adventure
as an adult later, probably past my like, well,
Coastal Riding Prime.
Yes. Yeah. Coastal Riding Prime is what?
Like 13 to 18 something like that.
But while your brain is still growing and you take the abuse.
Yes. Yeah. That it's like, oh, this seems fine.
Even though you should probably should not be doing it at that point in your life.
Yeah. I doing it's like an old person.
That's those are the people that should go on rollercoaster.
Yeah, because they're already losing it.
Yeah. What's the point? What's the point?
Like, this is my time to enjoy myself.
Or if it kills you, then it kills you.
Seems like a fine way to go.
Or your brain cells, whatever.
Yeah. Yeah.
So you just want to have some fun at that point. Yeah.
But I was doing it in my 20s that I would go with a couple of other friends.
We did it, I think, three years in a row, and we would stay in my house in New Jersey.
Well, that's more my parents house in New Jersey.
And we would go to Halloween Horror Nights, which.
Oh, wait, no, wait. Fright.
Fright. So sorry. So sorry. Oh, my God.
That's fine. All the New Jersey fans are going to kill me.
Fright Fest. Learn your brand.
Yes. Your park scare brand.
So, yes. Yeah. Yeah. Where you get scared.
I've been scared on the East Coast. I've been scared on the West Coast.
She's scaring across and getting scared across America.
Actually, that is another thing that I could talk about is that I was always too
scared of that stuff.
Yeah. I would really avoid it at all costs.
But we would just go because the lines were shorter at that time of the year.
And if you went on a Friday night, especially all the children were gone.
Right. So the lines were really short.
And we would just like run through the park and get on as many rides as we could.
And we would usually start with Kingda Ka.
Oh, sure. Just get there before any line starts.
OK, OK. But that's also terrifying because it's very strange to be the first person
on a roller coaster, like the first person of that day.
Oh, yeah. If it hasn't been like vetted and like it, like there hasn't been a few
like any pig. Yes, they've done like you've seen it like go up and down like empty.
Yeah. But still, to be the first person on a roller coaster that day feels strange.
It seems like this will be the time that there would be some issue.
Yeah, especially which seems like there there are errors.
I feel this thing's they did like they know there's going to be problems sometimes.
We'll get into that. But sorry, what are you saying?
Oh, I just sometimes the vibe at Six Flags feel like great adventure.
You usually have their act together, but sometimes the vibe is like,
oh, yeah, this ride is opening late because like Kenny was 20 minutes late.
Yeah, because he blah blah took too long.
But yes, yeah.
So it's just like, oh, hey, man.
Sorry. Sorry about that. Come on on.
Come on. The teenager that we hired to like, yeah, run this thing that is
run this up front to God, to God's kingdom.
Who was trained like for a day by a video and presses a button now is like running late.
So but yeah, there were a few times where they would be like talking,
you know, this the 10 year old Six Flags employees that were running this thing.
And you're waiting in line and wondering what's happening, what's going on.
Is everything OK? And then they're like, oh, I think it's fine.
Like, come on in. Yeah.
There's such like astrophysics involved in this attraction,
especially all roller coasters.
But this seems like you need degrees to operate.
There should be more scientists.
I feel like a scientist on call at all times.
Six Flags scientists to just be like, everything's OK.
I've done the calculations again, just sitting next to like an old computer,
you know, to make it seem like, yeah, everything's a go.
Let me see a list of like five articles you've written.
And then, yes, yeah, trust you.
It feels like we were we were just we did this crazy new Disneyland ride,
the Star Wars ride, and we were told there were 30 Imagineers in the basement
making sure that everything was OK and monitoring it.
And I feel like Six Flags just has like one handyman
that's in the middle of the park somewhere.
And then they go, hey, something's wrong.
And he goes, OK.
And that's or they don't even have him.
He's like at home and they have to call him.
Yeah. And if our if a sink is broken in a place we live,
yeah, we're going to call the handy. Yeah.
Yeah. There's no real like sink guy.
It's like I know how to like use a wrench better than you do.
So I'll tighten something. Right.
There's not many like guys that are specific to this one thing.
Yeah. Yeah.
We also do. We did this episode behind the paywall,
which allowed us to be more honest about the Six Flags experience.
But there's a fright fest here in L.A. at Magic Mountain that I mean,
go listen to it on the second gate or patron thing.
But the like the most scarring image for me was the
discussion of teenagers sucking fog.
Yeah. Like getting what you were there, you could say.
Yeah. So so in fright fest, of course, they have a lot of fog machines.
And there's a lot of teens.
Of course, they're very, very tired.
They're trying to impress each other.
Yeah. So there was a teen that was specifically very impressive.
He impressed you.
He impressed me and my friend Anthony because he went up to the fog machine
and just sucked the fog right straight from the machine.
Is that some kind of drug?
Or is it just like it was impressive because it's like he was experimenting.
Like, yeah, if synthesized correctly, he could have pioneered.
So maybe he already now in the month since this October,
like figured out how to synthesize it or make it solid or something. Right.
Isn't it a vape track? Like he was like, oh, well, like, oh, it's like a big vape.
You know, it was. Yeah.
Fog machine, if you think about it, it's just a big vape.
Yeah. So I think that is what he was like doing, like blowing it out for his friends.
I mean, the teens were everywhere.
They were.
That was the craziest thing I think we saw from teens that night.
Fog sucking, fog sucking teens don't care about Legionnaires disease,
lingering, no, there is disease.
I'm not a big topic in team talk.
No, you didn't see any fog butt chugging, though.
Oh, my God.
Nobody bent over a fog machine
or squatted over a fog machine, because it would go up.
Fog goes up.
Fog can go up.
So you could just squat over it
and then try to like spit it out of your mouth.
Let's see if it makes it all the way through your intestines.
Oh, and burp it out or something or blow it out.
I guess that's a long distance for fog to not dissipate all the way from anus to mouth.
Yeah, that's like it would be like a David Blaine style trick.
A true sorcerer. We need to do that.
Which takes time. It takes a one hour special.
Yes. Yeah.
On Sunday night, this week on ABC.
David Blaine butt chug some fog for Harrison Ford in his house.
Yeah, that's unbelievable.
For very high Harrison Ford.
Callista, get in here.
You got to see this.
You got to see this fog in his asshole.
Do it again.
Don't leave. Keep doing it.
Holy shit.
Ever since it was I was a boy, it was my dream to butt chug fog
tonight with you watching.
I was thinking about being a teenager recently,
and the things that I would do that I thought were just like,
oh, I'm just like a teen.
This is but looking back, it was to try and be impressive.
And one of the things was just like cursing loudly, more in conversation.
Did you guys ever do this?
Showing you a new curse word?
Yeah, like you could curse like and it doesn't matter.
Like you're not affected by the cursing.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
You don't like look around before you say the curse word.
You just barrel it.
Yeah, you're just like you're performatively loud.
Yeah. Yeah. Loud.
And as if someone would then hear those curses and be like, that was.
Yes, that was very impressive to me.
And I have to say sexy.
You were let's say inside the Actors Studio.
What's your favorite curse word?
Or what was it when you were?
I think it was probably just fuck, right?
It's just you just want to say that as much as possible.
Find a spot for it and hope that a beautiful woman hears it
and has never heard a little boy say it.
So what was that word?
I mean, you could just say this. Yeah.
You have the confidence, the gusto.
The teacher is yelling at you, but she's like, but hold on.
It's the after class. Yeah.
Class never seen a little boy swear before.
I know. That was very cool.
What age? Like doing this? Yeah.
I mean, I don't know.
It probably ranged anywhere from like 10 to like 21 or something.
I think I was eighth grade when I started.
Oh, your first like swear.
Curse word. Yeah, I think that's awesome.
I feel like it's a late public curse word.
I have a lot of things in my life.
Yes, I feel like my friends are probably starting to do it.
Like, I mean, I remember a kid saying in third grade saying, oh, yeah,
on the playground at school, but he was in a dire situation.
Yeah. So he what he had where he had, he was getting sat on by a bigger kid.
Oh, and he said he yelled to get this big bitch off of me.
And we're all like, whoa, whoa.
I really. Oh, my God.
I spilled water. Water's been spilled.
But you didn't swear. I didn't.
No, not anymore.
This with this wet bed or spilled all over those little bit.
Because we can pause a second. Yeah, maybe let's pause.
OK, we're back.
I'll say in case we leave the spill in
and we're talking about teens and cursing.
Oh, and we're talking about big bitches.
Yes. Yeah. Yeah. Get this big bitch off me.
Famous moment from my elementary school.
So I think it was around then that people, you know, probably curse
at the bus stop. Sure. Mm hmm.
And in a great, great.
That's your cursing journey. Yes.
It which dovetails nicely, I guess, into into roller coaster.
Oh, wait. Well, we have to talk about the thing you mentioned.
Your in your life's roller coaster journey.
When I was talking to you about topics, you I was delighted when you brought up
this tape that you had when you were growing up, you had a roller coaster tape,
a tape that I watched frequently.
Yeah, it's I couldn't even get there like 10 minutes of it.
As I recently watching the YouTube.
Someone kindly put it on YouTube.
Not just it, but it's two sequels.
Oh, I will say I did not watch the sequels, but I did make it through the first one.
People might. Boy, people might cheer if this was also a childhood favorite.
I didn't know it before, but it is called America's Greatest
Roller Coaster Thrills in 3D. Yes, it is in 3D.
And what does that mean?
Nothing. Nothing. It comes with glasses.
They mount the camera in the front car of the coaster.
Yeah, it feels like you're on it.
And I have to say, I watched it.
I watched the full hour.
And then I put the sequels on to like peacefully go to sleep.
Oh, that's nice.
It activated something in my brain where I was like, yes, this is this feels good.
I there's something nice. This is good.
It's a very easy way to experience a roller coaster.
You don't have to leave your house and you get to see the thrills.
See the thrills.
Some of these are gone to Drakken Fire and Big Bad Wolf are both gone.
Oh, man.
Big Bad Wolf, I thought was so cool.
They're like hanging. Yes.
And seated because there was the Batman hanging where your legs are kicking.
But Big Bad Wolf had like little boats that were like hanging.
Oh, I think when I was watching it, there was some familiarity
to me about the little boats because I think that the proper term they got.
I will say it is now.
It's little boats.
I went on something oddly in the same video.
There's a roller coaster called Top Gun, but I went on a different top gun
at King's Island that was a little boat coaster, not a flying coaster.
And so I think I like the boat.
As I recall, I was especially a coaster wimp,
you know, in 2005 when I did this, the boats I could handle.
I think I'm a fan of little boats.
OK, nice.
Please direct me to more little.
It also just looked cool going around the turns and stuff
because it like kind of swings up in the air a little bit.
It's very satisfying.
That was probably my favorite coaster to watch on that video.
Huh? Yeah.
Now, I'm watching the video.
First of all, the beginning, there's banter between it's a man and a woman host.
Yes. And professional host.
Yes. Yes.
Host people who I can peg listeners, if you don't have a chance
to look it up right now or don't care about it.
Imagine they imagine someone says, OK, we need a Harry Anderson type.
And we need a Suzanne Summer type. Yeah.
Can we get them? And they're like, absolutely not.
We have no money. No, they will not do this.
But we have a guy who is credited on one episode of the Tim Conway show.
Oh, nice.
What was also the what was the Tim Conway show?
I'm sure there were multiple Tim Conway shows.
It was the one that was just called the Tim Conway show.
But that was like a long time ago, not like a podcast he did.
Oh, no, no, no.
Long time ago, 70s, 80s variety show kind of thing, I think.
Yeah. Anyway, but there yet it's a guy and a girl.
And the dynamic is, guys, a real coaster hound and girl like,
oh, you would know.
She says you would take an act of Congress to get me on one of these things.
Great writing. Big bitch.
Yeah, it's like I'm a big bitch. I can't get on this.
But then she doesn't get on the coasters.
No, eventually she does.
Oh, she's done. OK.
And then it's really confusing.
They get they clearly the hosts only went to Magic Mountain
and they didn't travel the country for this thing.
So they go like no money.
Yeah, not at all.
So they go on whatever it is at Magic Mountain.
Could be Batman the ride even.
And she goes on it.
And then you leave the go the host for a long time.
You go on five more coasters, which is it's all long and tedious.
And then we come back to the skit that's like he now he's now
she's making him go on.
So it's like an art. He's got the taste. Yeah.
There's a little story, a little three extra to this story.
You meet all sorts of characters.
You get meet one guy from Arrow, the the manufacturing company Arrow,
which I did look up and it is now defunct.
This arrow is gone. Yeah.
Arrow dynamics. Yes. Yes.
Yeah. Ron Toomer is his name. Yeah. Ron Toomer.
His name is Ron Toomer.
I was like, this is such like this all feels so fake.
It feels like a Tim and Eric sketch or something. Yeah.
Yeah. Watching a 90s VHS of roller coasters.
Well, especially because now we talk to the coaster expert
and his expert analysis is kind of like, yeah, you know,
he's got to figure out a good way for him to bend.
And that's how to make it move. And that's important.
I don't go on. I just bend him.
And here's how you do it.
And then he takes a wire and just bends it around.
And that's how a coaster that made me so nervous.
I was like, he's going to get smacked in the face with that.
Because you seem like he was having trouble bending it. Yes.
And then his eye goes straight on the socket.
They would have left it in if it happened. Yeah.
They wouldn't have cut it out. They just had one time to do it.
So, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, we got if he got hit in the eye, it's like,
don't go on roller coasters.
Look what they could do to you. My warning.
If just the small one did it, imagine what a big one you could die.
You'll be like me, Ron Toomer.
You were saying VHS, but I found it on laser disk on eBay.
Whoa.
Fifty dollars for this laser disk.
Five dollars shipping like new condition.
Oh, it's like new. Yeah.
Mine was not like new. It was played many times.
Well, mine really were this.
So did you like because to explain what they mean by 3D
is that they just play you the POV like now on YouTube.
You can watch a ton of POV shot on people's phones, roller coasters.
But at the time, they had to set up big broadcast cameras
and like and mount them and it was like in a complicated manner.
So you just get to watch 10 roller coasters all the way through
as if you were going on.
I think it was probably like as a child, my version of reality TV of like,
yeah, you just kind of leave it on.
You don't have to watch every scene.
It kind of blends into the next thing.
You know, like I didn't want to watch a narrative.
And someone gave it to me as like a birthday gift, I think. OK.
And so I I don't know.
I mean, also looking back as a kid, I'm like,
I don't know why I was watching what I was watching
other than my love for just a television being on for me.
Yeah, you like it was around. It was around.
There was people on it.
Like I just watched every sitcom imaginable.
I don't think I liked any of them.
Yeah, but I watched all of them.
Whereas now in this era where you can choose, choose if it's bad,
you just don't want although people are still watching crap. Yeah.
Yeah. Crap rises to the top.
It's all about the people love crap.
Crap. It'll never stop.
It'll never stop.
They will crap food. They love crap TV. It's true.
I remember another podcast, a radio lab from like years.
I mean, they still make it.
But years ago, there was an episode where I think they found like an old trash
heap from like ancient Egypt.
And there was they kept finding this book.
And it was like erotica, like crap of the time.
And like that's what people were reading was just crap.
I have a crap like an old Egyptian book.
Yeah. I mean, like a romance novel for Egyptians, essentially.
Like ancient Egyptians.
Yeah. It's just like porno bad porno.
Yeah. It's just like you're like run of the mill, like pulp.
Yeah. V.C. Andrews. It's the V.C. Andrews.
So it's yeah. And they're like, that's what everybody wanted to read.
Yeah. That's just what's going on now.
Geez. I like that being able to judge that, like finding something ancient
and old that should feel important and being able to say it sucks.
It's crap. Yeah. Like the writing is horrible here.
This is just about sex and nothing else.
Funny that it's like maybe back then it was considered good.
I'm not sure. Yeah. You know, maybe they were being harsh on it.
Right. But like it could have been like a 50 Shades of Grey.
Yeah, that's kind of what I think they were trying to say.
Like this is like people read that now.
People read it then.
Sure. We're all the same. We haven't changed.
The aliens combing through, you know, the remains of humanity
and just going like, what is a million little pieces?
This must have been an important book for them.
This is it. This was their god.
Yeah, this was their god. Written by a non-liar.
Yeah, that's the one.
Oh, that's the one by the liar.
I haven't watched that one.
But isn't that that's the This Is Us?
Right. Wait. No. Oh, no.
I mean, that's a million little things.
Guy who went to rehab, but made it up.
And then he was on Oprah and there was a book club
and then it like sold a ton and then it was like, oh, I lied.
I made this. He made all of it up. Right.
Yeah. That was the idea. OK.
Sorry. I was thinking of a million little things that short lived drama.
I think maybe I thought those things were related to it.
Just people like that idea of like a bunch of something.
You know, something I guess.
So that's never changed either.
Yes. People like crap and they want a million of something.
One time when I was hosting the tram tour, as I as I did long ago,
I had an especially non responsive audience in the front row.
And if people don't pay attention on the fourth car of the tram, whatever,
I think I can't see. I don't care.
But the first row of the first car, you really notice.
And there was somebody just like brazenly reading that book
on the ride at the theme park.
Why even go on the ride at that point? I don't know.
I guess there was some it was pleasant background noise.
Yeah, I guess like the roller coaster tape.
But they decided to go do it in person.
Yes. Yeah. I like being around it.
Yeah. I just you know, I get wind in my face.
It's nice. I can't drive my own car and read at the same time.
So I'm going to pay this place to drive me around.
Maybe I'll turn and look when the shark jumps up.
But otherwise. But I was like really I was man.
I like tried to roast him.
And I was going to say, are you allowed to like Rickle style roast
the people in the front row on the tram tour?
Probably not. Not Rickles.
I guess you can't say Rickle style.
No, really. Because that's not a big bitch.
Look at this. What are you a Nazi?
Because Nazi.
I guess you probably can't do that.
I tried to make fun of that.
I think I'm sure it was much more sputtery at the time.
But I tried to say, hey, if you're going to read a book in front of me,
can it be a book by a non liar?
That didn't do it.
Yeah. That is that clear, clean thing I just did.
Is the book still good even if you know it's a lie?
I mean, most books are lies. Yeah, right.
It's true. I mean, all of entertainment are just lies.
Lies upon lies.
Yeah. So is it did it did its effect, this positivity in the world
actually make up for the lie? Yeah.
It's like that Simpson episode with Joe Bidaya Springfield.
Is the legend better than the reality?
I don't know that it is.
You think? No. It's not what I see out on Rax.
Oh, you're saying the book. The book.
You're not talking about the idea I'm talking about.
Life of Pi tried to pull that too.
Do you guys see Life of Pi?
I haven't seen Life of Pi.
Can I ruin it? Yeah, sure. Go.
Life of Pi. Listen, jump ahead.
If you recall, it was that Ang Lee.
Yeah, yeah. It was like spectacular, like animal things going on.
But it turns out at the end, well, first it starts with like
by the end of this story, you're going to believe in God,
which I'm like, I'm already annoyed.
Like, yes, the character like is telling a story.
And then at the end, someone's like, OK, I think what actually happened
was that you were stuck on this boat with your family.
And this animal represents this person and this represents this person.
And what really happened was like this horrible thing.
And it's like, yes, but what version do you like better?
And I'm like, well, you didn't show us the other version.
So you're just dismissing it as if it's not interesting or worthwhile
for anyone to hear it.
You're saying like, no, no, no, you got to hear the monkey version.
And so I'm like, that really like bothered me.
Sometimes it was like literary bestsellers like do not make good
like The Goldfinch was this hugely successful book.
It's a giant brick of a thing.
And a movie came out and did any of you see it?
The Goldfinch? No, really?
Just like, yeah.
Well, but this one at least was an Oscar nominated.
I mean, that one's true.
But like even even those like there's something gets weird in translation.
Sure. Yeah.
That is very aggressive to start off with a very aggressive.
You're going to believe in God. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
Only the only books to do that are Life of Pi and the Bible.
The Bible. You're going to believe in God by the end of this book.
Not till the end.
But every page and then you'll get it.
I actually just started reading the Bible.
Really? Yeah.
Like genuinely, I want I was curious.
I was like, I've never read this thing.
Sure. But it probably doesn't occur to most people to like sit down and read the.
Yeah. And I don't know anything.
I don't I really don't know much about religion at all.
And I was sick of being like seeing things on TV or movies.
And people are like, oh, that's a biblical reference.
You know, and I'm like, I don't know what they're talking about.
I know like the basic ones.
Uh huh. Where are you adding it?
It's still pretty early on.
Like still I'm still in Genesis.
OK, you're doing all.
I'm just reading the Bible. Wow.
Yeah. It's just Genesis been a slogan.
It's usually it's very small type.
So it's taking. Yeah.
I'm actually reading it on an app.
The Bible Bible.
There are several Bible apps. Oh, yeah.
And I'm reading like it's called the New Learning one or something,
which is supposed to be the easiest just to understand what's happening.
I see. Yeah.
And I mean, I'm on like Genesis Chapter seven or something.
Oh, oh, yeah.
And I'm still a ton of chapters.
Yeah. And Adam and Eve are still there, but they're like super old.
But they just had another kid.
Wait, so they had another set.
They have like Cain and Abel.
And then they go through this whole line of people and all this stuff happens.
And then all of a sudden they're like, and then Adam and Eve had another child.
Wow. I know about the other kids in the Old Testament.
Yes. Yeah.
It's like this person had this person and this person had this person.
Yeah.
And you like skip the baguettes or did you try to read the baguettes?
I mean, in this version, it's not as horrible to get there because it's like,
oh, it's more like they've cut down.
Yeah, it's more plain English.
But they are saying like, then this person had this and then this guy had two wives.
That was kind of cool.
Lamac and they do a little.
I mean, I don't know how to say his name.
He has two wives. They don't care about it.
They're just like, he just does. Wow.
Do they put so weird?
Is there like modern slang in there to make you understand?
Like, yeah, side chick. Yeah.
Yeah. They're like that. That that song slaps. Yeah.
Stuff like that. There's a lot of tick tock.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah. That would help me if I would.
Yeah. I can't get into something unless it talks about tick tock.
Yeah. That is. Yeah.
I hit the dab on the Pharaoh.
Yeah. This guy huge on tick tock.
And there you go, because that's what they have to do now in movies.
Right. For a while.
Like, I think it was in Chef where, you know, he got he went viral.
Yeah. On YouTube.
Oh, there's still a lot of people going viral in movies.
Joker went viral.
Joker went viral in a very strange way.
Yeah. Right.
They said, like in the 70s, that has to be a cut scene.
Right. That there's no mention that they're filming.
Yes. And on on film.
Yes. When you see it, it is still it is shot really, really nice.
Yeah. Yes. That's true.
Why didn't they?
But I guess it's like this is too much.
No one's going to care. Right.
Yeah. Like these losers who aren't going to like it anyway.
Yes. Fuck it.
But yes. Why is there a viral?
And it does that 70s style talk show play clips often of local bombing.
Why didn't they just say like, you know, tonight we're shooting.
We're shooting a video for.
So you can be a star.
Yeah. Yeah.
Why not just have a line of saying yes.
And then they got it.
As opposed to someone was secretly
like the loudest loading magazines of film.
It's a light something with that for that kind of camera.
The last thing light in these people's faces.
They would have noticed.
Yes. Definitely.
Even somebody has messed up in the head as the Joker would have noticed.
Maybe the most messed up of all.
He's probably the most messed up of all time.
I have top five. Top five.
Yeah. Well, you guys read the Bible.
God is up there.
You're going to meet some real characters that might be shifting.
Yeah.
If you want to go on a ride that gets you close enough, maybe to touch God.
By that, I mean, it is very tall and it gets you close to heaven.
King Kaka.
Oh, yeah.
Maybe that ride.
I didn't know.
That could have done that segue on that tour.
You just don't talk to anyone else for the rest of the podcast.
You're so proud of it.
I did my work.
Go ahead.
Enjoy some little solo smoke time.
I didn't realize that it's still the tallest roller coaster.
Still the tallest.
Lost the title of fastest.
It was fastest.
They went and opened.
Tallest and fastest.
Fastest now.
You probably have it.
Yeah.
Formula Rosa at Ferrari World.
At Ferrari World.
In Dubai.
In, yes.
Oh, wow.
Abu Dhabi, I believe.
Oh, OK.
Abu Dhabi.
Yeah.
That whole place seems really bog.
We got to get there or something.
I don't know when we're.
How willing are you guys to go to UAE?
I'll go.
Scared.
That is where my fear sets in.
I'm scared to go anywhere, but I'll go.
We have to go.
Scared because if you slip up, you might get thrown in jail.
Yes.
Yeah.
Scared of anywhere where the buildings of the future are built by slaves who have their
passports taken away when they enter the country.
And I am on record saying things like that.
We're going to edit this out though before we go.
OK.
Yeah.
We're never going to get invited at this rate.
We're going to have to come through a lot of past episodes.
There's one episode where you say something about Abu Dhabi.
This government is run by insane people.
Do we have to cut out references to when I talk about Garfield mailing Nermal to Abu Dhabi?
They're still mad about that.
They still hate that.
They probably don't like that stereotype that it's a place where cats get mailed.
Or hated cats.
Although can you imagine if at one of these theme parks in Abu Dhabi,
they had a Garfield ride and it started with Nermal getting out of a box?
I would be cool.
That would be fantastic.
The ultimate Garfield reference.
Yes.
I think that they need to do this.
We've embraced this.
It's literally what most children think about.
When I say children, I mean men in their 30s.
So it's still.
It was.
All right.
It's now the fastest coaster in North America.
It is the longest drop in the world still, I believe.
Because of the structure of it, presumably we will have tweeted out the episode,
art and promo that shows you what the thing looks like.
But it really is just this straightaway and then a big upside down U,
which involves a corkscrew.
And then you're back down and the rest of it is just kind of like losing speed from how crazy it got.
Yes.
And it's a big launch at the beginning.
And you're up to the top of that thing within seconds.
Really fast.
0 to 128 miles per hour in 3.5 seconds.
So twice as fast as the Hulk.
That's zero to 60 in a few seconds.
It's crazy.
There's a whole thing on this.
There's been a runner on this show.
Guest Matt Rogers was here and he dubbed me a no launch queen for my inability,
me being scared of going on launch coaster.
Launches are the coasters of the future.
It feels like a lot of things have shifted to launching.
I guess it's probably easier and cheaper for them, right?
It's newer tech, I feel like.
Yeah.
So it's still cool.
It's still pretty cool.
Now they've figured out how to do multiple launches, but less intense.
So it's starting to get woven into family.
You can do coasters now.
There's this Harry Potter one in Florida where it slows down for a little bit so you can see
some scenes and then it goes really fast again.
Yeah, they can control the speed as opposed to just letting something drop from a tall height.
You'd have to build up the energy for the coaster up at the top of it.
And now they can do it a couple times.
Yeah.
I was saying with my history with it that I've gotten braver, have become more of a launch queen,
but the one that I've stated, and we've talked numbers before in the podcast, but I got freaked
out by going on the Rock and Roller coaster, which is this Aerosmith themed ride in Disney World.
Rock and Roller is really just dying this horrible death.
Everything rock themed and oriented in the last 20 years.
It just sucks so bad.
Yeah, you understand.
It's been a harsh exit interview and future generations could scarcely be
made guilty for not staying on board with rock music.
Yes, based on the last 40 years.
It's really heinous what they've done as old men.
This morning I watched Dan Rather interviewing the three members of Sticks who stuck around.
The hairstyles on these men, just age, just age guys.
I should not have blue hair when you're 70.
When I saw Blondie a couple months ago, some of the guys have the wig version of what the
hairstyle they had in the 60s was.
So it would be like that, you know, like what Keith Richards had, and he had this big poofy black
hair when he was a young man.
They just have a wig version of it.
And it's so funny because maybe far away if you kind of squint, you're like,
oh, yeah, that's a youngish.
And then you get close and you're like, ah, no.
It's the worst of both worlds.
Yeah.
It can't be shot on HD anymore.
Or what's his name?
The DJ, Rodney Bingenheimer, who has another wig version of his hair from 40 years ago.
Oh, right.
I don't actually know that these guys have wigs.
I should probably not be slandering them.
It still looks terrible.
Yeah.
Chances are they don't listen to podcast the ride.
Most likely.
Chances, but.
The guy from Blondie or Rodney Bingenheimer.
You know, but so I, all right.
So I went on this, I went on this Aerosmith ride, mainly admired the way they were dressed,
how many feathers and scarves they were wearing.
But then, okay, this one is zero to 57 in 2.8 seconds.
And that one was like a little out of my comfort zone going to 57.
This one goes to 128.
That is how much bit that's more than double.
Right?
I couldn't do this fucking thing.
I don't, I can, I maybe I was starting to feel like a launch queen.
I don't know if I can say.
Well, and the thing with Kingda Ka is everything around it is like
gravel and like metal and fencing.
Like I think the one thing watching that roller coaster video that stuck out
was like the pleasant footage to watch is like the big bad wolf, which goes through a forest
and goes through a little German town recreation or anything at Cedar Fair,
which is on a lake.
But it is crazy how many big roller coasters the like speed and number of loops and stuff
was the appeal.
But then it's just the most industrial looking gravel lots.
Yeah, you basically, when you get to that, the top of the drop in Kingda Ka,
you just see like the Six Flags Great Adventure parking lot.
Yeah.
But it's still pretty cool.
Sure.
Well, you supposedly from the top, you would have to like really get your bearings immediately.
But if you knew where to look, if you could like stand on top of that tower for a long time,
you could see Philly, I think, and maybe even New York.
Yeah.
And another city that's not occurring.
What else is crazy?
I think that's all it takes.
It doesn't seem like it's that tall, but I guess it is.
So for 56 feet.
How tall is like I'm thinking of the Freedom Tower in New York.
That's now that's a thousand feet or something.
Yeah.
What are the roller coasters are built?
I don't know.
I watched something that said that the Statue of Liberty could fit under Kingda Ka.
Oh, wow.
But that's not like a statue.
It's pretty small.
Yeah.
I mean, in the, you know, it's.
And I didn't answer your question.
It's tall.
Yeah.
But not for like a structure for a structure for an impressive structure.
I have no I don't want to just look up building heights, but I should have done
buildings versus roller coasters.
Yeah.
Well, you know, it's just somebody to ponder, I guess.
No one will ever know the truth.
Mm hmm.
I know the numbers are there.
It's probably probably a lot of the Seven Wonders of the World are much shorter than
this thing.
Let's kick them off.
Yeah.
Like old old.
Like how tall are the pyramids?
I don't know.
They're probably old and shitty like that book.
That dirty book.
Yeah.
The dirty book that's all stuffed in there compared to Kingda Ka.
All right.
What I want is for a new Kingda Ka style coaster to be built on top of the pyramids.
Yeah.
I'm actually surprised there isn't.
Pyramid.
The Great Pyramid for 481 feet.
Taller than Kingda Ka.
It's still taller than Kingda Ka.
That's a little taller.
That's a wonder.
Yeah.
All right.
Fine.
You get to say.
Deserves that.
But Kingda Ka right on the other side of that parking lot, there's wild tiger.
There's tigers.
Yes, it's true.
Drive through safari.
Do they still have the safari?
I want to say yes.
They haven't gotten it.
I want to say the drive through safari and we should say it gets cold in like
this is considered central Jersey, right?
This park only operates like half of the year and weekends some of the rest of the year.
Yes, they have fright fest.
Fright.
Yes.
Oh, sure.
Some Christmas stuff, minimal Christmas activities.
Freezing.
Stuff.
Yeah.
Oh, it's going to be cold.
Are they closing probably now?
We're recording this in like late January.
Yeah.
So right now you couldn't go.
Don't think so.
I have a little bit more about tigers because this was part of they made a whole area out
of Kingda Ka.
They made it called the Golden Kingdom, which I guess is the it's all kind of themed to
Asian jungles, I suppose.
And they all right.
So they did a tiger show, a Bengal tiger show for a little while in the near Kingda Ka.
They even named one of the tigers Kingda Ka.
Hunter like a snake.
I think I think well, yes, cause it sounds like the snake.
It's like King Cobra kind of thing.
Yeah.
And cops jungle book is the tiger.
But I saw news reports saying Kingda Ka or as it translates to King of Coasters.
So if that's true, the ancient word for Coasters, I don't I don't think that's right.
I think they made that up.
Also, another news report says it's it's it vaguely translates to lose your lunch.
But I think that might have just been a joke.
That's a joke.
I think so.
That one's a joke.
But several pieces of real literature said King of Coasters.
So why is a tiger named King of Coasters?
Yeah.
Not correct.
Shouldn't be.
Yeah.
Anyway, there was a show with a trainer where they did tricks and stuff and jumped through hoops
and that kind of thing.
And then they closed the show in 2010.
And they seemingly they just moved the tigers to the drive through Safari Park that you guys
referred to.
But there is one guy on a message board who was not satisfied with that answer and was
assuming the worst.
And let me just skim through this message.
All six of the tigers were banished to the Safari Park never to see their human companions again.
Well, interesting.
That's what he that's what he was worried about, not like the welfare of wild animals.
No, I guess just that they wouldn't get to interact with the trainer.
Yeah, they want to see their friends.
But he also he doesn't know that he could say at least that's what the park says.
No one has seen them in over a month.
This is clearly the trainer, right?
That's right.
Oh, yeah.
He's losing his game.
What are you reading this off of again?
Some theme park message board.
I'm not sure what it was.
You don't remember the name?
It might have been theme park insider.
Okay.
But so he keeps going and he's blaming the guy who was running this park at the time,
John Fitzgerald.
John Fitzgerald closed Temple of the Tiger and fired the trainers for wanting to mate the Tigers.
The biological clock is ticking.
It was a now or never situation.
She may be pregnant.
If so, will the park have the Cubs aborted?
Oh, my God.
Wow.
That's a leap.
Isn't it?
This man, Tom Fitz, John Fitzgerald, head of Six Flags is going to command.
Press a button.
Have the Cubs aborted.
I love the idea of someone giving a Tiger an abortion.
Bring me my Tweety Bird Sunday and have the Tigers killed.
This is worthwhile for us.
In a facility, yes, with Sylvester the Cat smiling down.
In New Jersey.
That is a sort of tri-state area passion.
Yes.
It's a good old fashioned New Jersey Tiger abortion.
But also, then there's videos recently of Tiger Cubs.
They still, there's Tiger Cubs running around this place all the time.
And that's now in 2020.
Why did this guy jump to?
I don't.
They're going to kill the Cubs.
I think that's theory that if the trainer, it might not be wrong.
Yeah.
He knows too.
He's going to know so much.
Someone's going to kill the Cubs.
This is a warning.
Someone with a high powered rifle.
Full metal jacket.
Did anyone respond to that post on the message board?
That I don't know.
It could be Googled if you want to do the further entomology.
I believe that Theme Park Insider.
Look for John Fitzgerald.
Just Google John Fitzgerald Temple of the Tiger Cubs Aborted.
So there's been some changes.
They still have a safari park.
You could see Kingda Ka in the distance.
Wow.
A real safari.
With llamas.
This is a massive off-road vehicle that you ride in to do it.
They also offer VIP options or school group options.
The VIP options is just like an SUV parked next to a giraffe.
This is a white G. That's a OJ's Bronco.
But in the 90s, you could get in your, in my family's case, your Plymouth minivan.
You would follow a road, a paved road through the safari park
and get pretty close to the animals to the point where,
please remove your antennas or take them down.
Or else the monkeys that crawl on your car will ruin your life.
First off, they sometimes go crazy and beat up the cars anyway.
But like the animals with like a rip off antennas.
And I believe people have been mauled there.
Yes, I think there are lions.
Tigers now.
Yeah, I think people have been mauled.
They should have killed them in 2010.
They're like, don't feed the animals.
And people's immediately like, what if we brought like food and tried to give it to them?
Please remain in your car, ladies and gentlemen.
Please remain in your car.
Oh, I'm getting out.
Yeah, I got to get out.
I got to get.
What if I get close?
Yeah.
Got to feed them some Jersey Mike's.
I got two exposures left on this disposable.
Get them, honey.
Oh no, he's whacking me with my own antenna.
The subs gave him strength.
Any, any clues?
I looked up the gentleman's username and it does say he's a season pass holder at Six Flags.
Could still be the trainer.
He's not.
They're not mutually exclusive.
I found there's a there's a post here from somebody who
said he was posted a video of what got the temple of the tiger closed.
That's right.
The tigers caught in the act looks real dangerous to me.
Not.
And then it has the link like spurned trainer.
So I will look up the YouTube link here.
125.
They gave me a time code.
The video is unavailable.
No, damn.
As a tiger trainer, if at a certain point they're like, hey, you can't we can't have this show anymore.
People don't like this stuff like, you know, treating animals this way anymore.
What do you do after that?
Like, what does he do for his next job?
Yes.
Maybe some shady circus could hire or he could just does it just like he becomes a
particularly cruel like child actor trainer.
Yeah.
Like, I'll make sure they hit their foreign country or something where they don't care as much.
Rules are more lax.
When is the Siegfried and Roy accident?
Is that the number one job if you're a tiger trainer in the mid 2000s?
Is being on team to be on the team.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Gotta be.
I mean, just the the glamour alone.
Yeah.
Do you? Yeah, you get issued like a big white fur when you get that's your uniform.
Rolling in with those guys to like a casino buffet.
Could there be anything better?
Yeah.
Can you imagine the two of them?
High to their power.
You're walking around in their entourage.
You're like Johnny drama in the Siegfried and Roy entourage.
And you get to scoop like eggs and bacon from the buffet with like a diamond encrusted ladle.
Oh, yeah.
You get your own.
Yeah.
And the MGM grand large cats were different than the Siegfried and Roy ones.
Is that correct?
A lot of cats in Vegas.
All of them now prowling the city for their next meal.
Out you go.
Good luck.
A lot of food for Tiger Whip.
Yeah.
Knows where to find it.
You know, we haven't talked about it's just like what's what did what this thing feel like?
How did you feel?
Do you feel like you did?
Yeah, it rocked.
It's a great ride.
It was very fun.
Yeah, it was.
I mean, it is very short.
Yeah, it seems like.
Yeah, it's it's it's up and down, but it's a crazy up and down.
It's just a crazy up and down.
And it I liked it because it was so fast and so smooth and that when you're done with it,
you don't feel sick or anything.
And I definitely wanted to go back like get in line again, but it always had the longest line.
Oh, sure.
Yeah.
So you hit up the other rides and then maybe come back later.
Oh, sure.
Makes sense.
Yeah.
But yeah, especially on like a chilly night for the Fright Fest in New Jersey,
shooting up there like with the cold wind in your face.
Wow.
Whoa.
Felt really good.
I've said this before.
I think the launch like this actually, as much as it looks scary, is a lot less scary
psychologically than like hang time, which is a Nats coaster that droops you over for like what
feels like a minute pauses.
It makes you pause.
It goes up 90 degrees slowly, which makes you feel like you're going to fall off that.
Then it hangs you.
And then it does a regular thing.
Like this seems like it's so fast.
It's in crazy intense, but it doesn't destroy your brain.
Well, that with the drop, there's this slight corkscrew.
And I think it was because like to slow it down or something or right.
And it makes like the drop more tolerable, but you do get a second of looking down at it.
But at that height, it's unfathomable.
Like what's going on.
So you're like, I don't know.
This seems fun.
Yes.
You wouldn't even know what you were experiencing.
Say you were to get launched off this thing or, you know, like sure if the straps didn't work.
Oh, yeah.
And you just like fell off.
I don't think you'd really be able to process it.
No, it would be fine.
Everything would be fine.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
You would land on your feet and walk away.
Just land on a tiger's back.
Yeah.
All right.
Tweety Bird Sundays for everyone.
Yes.
Yeah.
Do they have those?
I don't know.
Well, I'll tell you what they did in the mid 90s.
Six Flags did have like come back if the rain was really bad.
They would or like they would give you return tickets.
Sure.
That's cool.
And they were but they called them Twickets like Tweety Bird.
And I remember I had to write like how I spent my summer vacation.
And I wrote about Six Flags and wrote that detail in.
And the teacher like circled it as a spelling error.
And I had to go to them and go like that's actually what they call it.
It's not a spelling error.
I am correct.
You told the teacher this?
Yeah.
What did the teacher say?
She docked points because of Twickets.
Yeah.
Like no, I want.
It's a brand.
And so she was like, I apologize.
I had not heard of Twickets.
Yeah.
Wow.
Exactly.
Did you explain like you know how?
Okay.
You know Tweety Bird, right?
Tweety Bird talks a certain way.
Like it's like Tweety Bird.
Yeah.
Okay.
I would love a video of this.
Yeah.
A 10 year old man.
Man-splaining.
We got to settle this.
We got to settle up.
Okay.
I want a public apology in front of the entire class.
And an acknowledgement that I'm cool for going to places like Six Flags.
Yeah.
Wow.
Twickets.
I didn't know about Twickets.
Yeah, I do not know about Twickets.
That's amazing.
If you recall Twickets fondly.
I was not.
Will you Google Twickets really fast?
I know when to Google it.
Yeah.
Or don't you mean, did you mean tickets?
Oh, I'm praying it's wrong.
I'm praying it doesn't exist.
I'm praying I have lucidated.
The Wikipedia page is just like, these were a spelling error on a third grade.
On one batch of tickets one summer.
Why did they write a whole Wikipedia article about that?
There is a first, the first thing that comes up is there's a company in the United Kingdom
that I think is a resale.
Okay.
Called Twickets.
That's what I mean.
They call like candy bars Twickets over there or whatever.
They call everything like, you know, everything something stupid.
Everything something different.
I looked up.
It's a boot, not a trunk.
Twickets, Six Flags, and it goes to the.
Hold on.
Oh, whoa.
Oh, wait a minute.
I'm not doubting it.
I just want more.
Yeah, yeah.
Details.
I took it in.
Here's a message board.
This is from 2010.
My boyfriend and I were at Six Flags Great America a couple weeks ago,
and we knew we would be back in October.
His uncle happened to remember the Twicket promotion they used to offer.
Yeah.
Where you could upgrade your ticket for an extra $20 before you left to be good for another day of admission.
So that's a different Twicket.
No, that's what it was because we went back and then the day we went back, we got rained out.
And so with the rain out, so ended up going to Six Flags three times for like.
But the first thing you got, you had a Twicket, took the Twicket, but were rained out.
Yes.
Yeah.
So then you went back to reuse the Twicket again.
In the fall, like Fright Fest season, like, yeah, it would be cold or it would be rainy,
but the crowds were very low.
Yes.
Would it run like the Lethal Weapons Stunt Show or the Batman Forever Stunt Show?
Yeah.
And like compared to Universal Studios out here with the Horror Nights,
the Fright Fest was like really low rent.
Yeah, pretty small.
A few zombies here and there.
Yeah.
Amazes?
Were there full?
No, nothing like that.
Like no haunted houses.
It was just like, it's dark outside and we're going to have a few people scare you every
once in a while.
But overall, like you could avoid them easily.
Whereas at Horror Nights, like you're going to get spooked no matter what.
Those guys are, they're gunning for you.
Yeah.
They, there's like real full coverage of the property.
But just maybe like.
Hacked with zombies.
And you maybe see four zombies your whole night at Fright Fest.
It's like, yeah, if we just walk fast enough, they won't bother us.
They're not going to come after us.
Because they walk slow.
Yeah, they have to walk slow and they don't feel like doing it either.
To build it up.
Whereas here.
I think it's a little bigger now.
Out there?
Yeah, I had all of them.
All of them.
I think they duplicate Fright Fest stuff.
Yes.
Yeah.
And just, I feel like all of the actors and makeup artists in Los Angeles that have
probably the free time around Halloween to go all out.
They really do a great job.
Oh yeah.
Whereas Fright Fest is New Jersey people that are probably hired to like do another job there.
And they're like, you got to be a zombie tonight.
Yeah.
And they're like, all right.
I'm at Fright Fest here.
I'm at the haunted hayride here.
Yeah.
I'm at the other thing.
They did.
When we went to Fright Fest in October, there was a maze that if you recall,
had a massive pile of shit in it.
Human?
It was not real.
That's part of the narrative of the sewer maze.
Oh, okay.
Just shit.
They're like, guys, we have to be honest.
This is a sewer.
There needs to be a big pile of shit.
Yes.
They want it to be very accurate.
Can't people just imagine that?
Can't we just let them know, yes, they're in a sewer?
It's like, nope, nope, nope.
They're in a sewer.
We got to see shit.
They wanted to see you to experience the horror of the plumbing system.
They wanted you to know what it's like.
What a nightmare.
How underpaid, how underfinanced the sewer system can be.
Yeah.
That was a 3D one.
We had to wear 3D glasses.
Wow.
And it showed you all the numbers at the end of how much it costs to run the sewer system.
Uh-huh.
How much?
Underfunded.
Facts of hourly rates.
Which administration's gutted, the funding for it.
The year of the last pay raise.
They're like, oh, the horrors.
I'm terrified.
Yeah.
Clinton was president.
Poor infrastructure.
So there have been incidents on this attraction.
Mostly it's run pretty safe.
Actually, we should talk about this is not an incident, but it is an oddity about this ride.
And I was trying to remember if we talked about this aspect with your wife, Kelly,
a while back, that the strangest thing about this ride, that you can,
they tell you before you get on that there is a possibility of rollbacks.
You could make it all the way to the top and sit there for a minute and then not quite crest that
hill and then roll all the way backwards and have to do it again.
Never seen that before.
Really weird.
Never seen that side.
This has to be the only roller coaster where they tell you there's the possibility that
it might not do what it's supposed to do.
Make it up.
Yeah.
That little Casey Jr. might not think I can.
It's way up.
There's versions of it.
I think on Hagrid's, I think I could be totally wrong, but the new Harry Potter
coaster where it does sometimes like that'll roll you back and you do the launch again
in certain sections.
It could be totally wrong.
I'll cut this out to make myself not look stupid if I'm wrong.
So I like there is something like that, but this seems like such a crazy.
Yeah.
You might go like 430 feet.
Yeah, you might miss it by five feet.
Yeah.
Because that's what, yeah.
In the examples I saw, it seems like it does get up there and then just doesn't have the
forward momentum anymore.
Right.
You do the entire thing, which if I were like, if I were coerced into going on this thing
and I did it begrudgingly and then I made it up, oh, few, we made it up.
Wait a minute.
What the fuck?
We have to go down backwards and then do it one more time.
Yeah.
That's bad news for me.
I don't know if it's just because it's a basic, some sort of basic version of whatever
it launches where it's not a perfected system.
It's kind of just seems like it's just like some peg that grabs you.
Right.
That's what it is.
It just hooks it and it shoots you up and sometimes it misses by a couple.
It must be that they wanted to make it so tall to get the world record or something
that it's like, all right, we're pushing it here.
We probably could have lowered it by 10 feet and gotten it right every time.
Oh, yeah.
We need to say that it's the tallest.
They bump up and then they start running tests and like, well, it's mostly getting hurt.
Well, they haven't really replicated it anywhere and I'm wondering if it's just like,
yes, it's not worth the headache.
Definitely not.
This was in the news a lot, these incidents you have, Scott.
The local news every now and then would be like, well, Six Flags, trouble at Six Flags,
yet again with Kingda Ka, something would happen.
Yes, no one has died on this one.
There's a more infamous story of there was a fire and a haunted attraction in the 80s
that led to a massive court case and new laws about inspecting dark attractions or dark
businesses where your vision is obscured.
Oh.
But that did not happen with this.
The incidents are odd, but no one grievously injured.
Yeah.
Well, the oddest one probably is that one time a couple years ago, this coaster pulled a Fabio.
By that I mean somebody got hit in the face by a bird, like some kid, like a 12-year-old
or something.
I don't know at what point on the ride.
Pulling a Fabio.
Yeah.
The most famous bird hit incident, and this one wasn't as cool to look at.
The Fabio one was so crazy where there's this blood coming out of his nose.
Maybe the thing just wasn't photographed because it seems like it didn't...
The kid who got hit in the face wasn't that affected.
It just hurt a little bit, and I think he did have to get some money from Six Flags.
But he described it as the bird exploded and the people behind him just had feather
guts all over their faces.
This is like a cartoon.
The Fabio was like he got hit with a pointy beak and busted him open.
His I think was a bigger bird too, I believe.
This was a pigeon, and Fabio was like a goose.
It was something big and grand, I think.
Canadian goose.
Very rare, it was the last one.
I know the answer to this, but we should do a whole episode on just Fabio getting
hit in the head with a bird, right?
Oh yeah.
I always thought of that.
We got to see what the date...
Well, actually, I have the date.
We should do 90 minutes, like the Zabruder film of it.
Last year was the anniversary.
We should have done it for 20 minutes.
Oh, what's the date?
I don't have the date.
It just says 1999.
Oh, the solemn event.
We should take a minute of silence.
Yeah.
I pulled the Philadelphia Inquirer had a story about it.
I couldn't tell if it was from the Inquirer or the Daily News because I think they merged
at some point.
Detail in this, the boy's name was Shane.
Shane said that he was briefly distracted by the sound of an alarm and turned his head
to the right, which was when the bird collided with the side of his head.
Had he not, the bird could have hit him in the eyes.
Oh my God.
So he happened to look away and got hit in the side of the head.
Jeez, do we know what kind of...
We don't know what kind of bird.
Scott said it was a pigeon.
Oh, you said it was a pigeon.
Common pigeon.
Yeah.
I'd like to think that maybe at that speed, maybe this is too fantastical to happen in
the real world, but maybe it would have been a fly kind of scenario where he...
Became a pigeon?
Yeah.
Gets pigeon powers or something.
The DNA is just...
Yeah, you're saying it's so fast.
Like the Hulk.
Like the Hulk cannon.
The molecules get fused together.
I don't know.
It's like a good origin story to someone.
That's pretty good.
We should follow that one away.
A roller coaster.
I don't know what pigeon powers you would want, but maybe none.
Flying?
Flying.
Yeah.
Okay.
So you get to fly.
But maybe you would also somehow get roller coaster powers.
Because you're also the DNA of a...
So I am now a roller coaster pigeon creature.
So then he could launch him.
Oh, in a bound.
Yeah.
Yes.
He launches himself.
He has the power of magnets.
He can launch from 0 to 128 in 3.5 seconds.
Yes.
Yeah.
And then he could kind of fly a little bit.
A little bit.
Yeah.
That's pretty good.
Now keep in mind he stinks, but remember the launch part.
And also he doesn't always get all the way up.
Sometimes he comes and then he's good.
Sometimes he immediately falls back down backwards.
Shitting constantly.
Yes.
So decent powers.
Carries a lot of diseases.
Others are lesser.
It comes out in the wash.
Fabio was specifically a goose hit him.
Was a goose.
Wow, you got it right.
The end of the article about King Daka, the boy getting hit on King Daka,
does mention the Fabio story.
And I think it's worthwhile reading this summary.
Yes.
But a similar incident in 1999 bloodied the famous face of Italian model Fabio Lanzoni,
the erstwhile margarine pitch man.
He was riding Apollo's chariot at Busch Gardens in Williamsburg, Virginia when a goose crashed
into his face as a roller coaster sped into a 210 foot drop.
He couldn't believe it wasn't butter.
What?
That is the last line of the article.
Dude.
A major newspaper of the time.
How is a goose?
Exactly.
The goose was not.
He couldn't believe it was not butter.
The goose wasn't butter.
He loved doing those ads so much and was so locked into it that he questioned whether
everything in his life was butter.
The erstwhile margarine pitch man.
Puts it up with a past episode.
The head of a guy who owns a park in Asia was described as a mercurial casino magnate.
That's a good cousin.
Yeah, it's a good cousin.
Erstwhile margarine pitch man.
Oh man.
You were in a Dunkin' Donuts commercial.
We can describe you as an erstwhile donut pitch man.
Well, yeah.
Erstwhile enthusiastic.
Current donut enthusiast.
A pitch man makes it really seem like it's your product and you're trying to get it out into the world.
Billy May's style.
Yes.
I'm like.
Yeah, come on.
Get this hot sauce off the shelves.
Like, Fabio is really like margarine.
Like, it's the new thing.
He consulted with the food scientists to make the recipe to his liking.
It sounds like an elixir.
You know, it's like Fabio and sons selling an elixir of some kind.
That's a pitch man in my mind.
Yeah.
You want your hair to be luxurious like mine.
And then like it gives it to like, you know, weird little weird short guy and old lady and they all end up with Fabio.
Yes.
Yes, exactly.
Like, I gotta buy this now.
That's a pretty good ad campaign.
Did they have margarine commercials anymore?
I feel like I haven't seen a margarine commercial in a while.
I feel like Brummel and Brown was the one with yogurt.
Remember that one?
No.
Remember Brummel and Brown?
Jason, name your top five favorite margarines.
Easy Breezy, Brummel and Brown, Eat Scott Yogurt, Blend It Right In with Creepy Taste of Butter.
Wait, you're saying this is modern?
No, it's from his childhood in the 30s.
Like late 90s.
This feels made up though.
That song didn't rhyme.
Yeah, do the song again.
I mean, that was an excerpt.
I don't remember the full song.
Okay.
There was more to it.
Yeah, there's more.
Were you a margarine family growing up?
Every now and then we'd get Brummel and Brown, but I think mostly from the jingle.
Is that a local margarine?
I don't know.
I think those are dash commercials.
That's the song the man sang who delivered it to your door.
This is the second episode where I'm the margarine man.
The erstwhile margarine pitch man that would go to your home.
Your local erstwhile margarine pitch man.
BrummelandBrown.com creamy butter spreads.
Deliciously creamy.
Made with real yogurt.
That logo is real, Lawrence.
Let me see the logo.
No way.
That logo is like all in the packaging.
It's like how Land O' Lakes makes spreadable butter now.
Doesn't that feel like it's, I don't know.
I just don't like that graphic design.
The design looks like it was made on Microsoft Paint.
It hasn't changed since 1999, I'll tell you that.
That was the logo.
Well, that's probably what they made it in.
While we're talking about jingles, what I remember very clearly about Six Flags Great Adventure,
they got a lot of life at Batman on the Ride.
Gave them commercial footage for like a decade.
That loop where you go on the outside, your legs are dangling.
But the radio ad for a while would end with a jingle that just went,
Six Flags Great Adventure, we had fun.
Oh, yes.
Yeah, yeah.
That was it.
That was the, someone's like, I got it.
I figured it out, gang.
Yeah, I guess it's inoffensive.
It's inoffensive.
Yeah, you wanted people to have fun.
I think this is what we had fun.
In the past tense.
Like you went.
Those people already went.
Yes.
Even though you're watching an ad encouraging you to go,
we're hearing from people who went.
So I guess, yeah, the idea was like they're telling you,
we had fun, so you should go and do it as well.
But they don't mention that part.
But they don't say that.
But that should be left to assume.
They don't even mention they're going back,
or if they would go back.
It's like, yeah, we had fun.
It's just a commercial for advertising people that were happy,
satisfied with the experience.
Yeah, the experience overall was satisfactory.
That's nice.
Satisfactory.
15 seconds, new for 2005, Kingda Khan for 20 bucks.
You can add Wild Safari Park, Six Flags Great Adventure, we had fun.
Your little five second fill-in part.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
But why don't we have fun?
No, we had.
We went.
Those people went and had fun.
But why not we have fun?
I think we have fun is weird.
I don't know where that's coming from.
Is that the park or is it?
Yeah, because that almost seems like the people.
Yeah, it's like, we'll have fun anywhere.
Yeah, we have fun.
You'll have fun.
Swingers or something.
You'll have fun?
You'll have fun is good.
Oh, you'll have fun.
Might have been.
Maybe that seems like a mushy or something.
Don Draper all of a sudden in here trying to punch this up.
You'll have fun seems like it's like, come on, you'll have fun, go.
Come on.
Come on, where's the other one?
It's like, you take my word for it if you want.
I had a good time.
You don't have to go.
But then you're like, I want to go.
These guys had a good time.
And they're playing it so cool.
They're playing it very cool.
They won't describe what happened.
They're not even telling me to do it.
No, yeah.
So let's check it out.
Yeah.
Let's go to Jackson.
I think that's the town that was in.
I guess that's like playing it cool with somebody want to date or something.
Yeah.
It's like, don't be sweaty.
Don't be desperate.
Hey, we had fun.
It seems like you're avoiding something.
Let's just see where it goes.
It seems like something horrible happened.
It's like, we had fun.
We had fun.
Well, Shane had a thing at Kingda Ka, but he's OK.
He's OK.
Shaz is uncomfortable talking about Shane's act.
Shane had a thing, but we had fun.
Yeah.
It'd be so much different if it was Six Flags Great Adventure, but we had fun.
But we had fun.
Nevertheless, we had fun.
We had fun.
Don't ask Shane.
He's OK.
Most of the family had fun.
This ride is currently, there's an incident currently in progress,
like in the month that we were recording this.
Oh my god.
Somebody was horribly injured involving Kingda Ka, but not on the ride.
So Kingda Ka was like an accomplice?
Essentially, and more so the teenagers working Kingda Ka.
What happened was a guy was getting on the ride and he was didn't know what to do with
his cell phone.
Like, I got to put this somewhere.
Do they not have lockers?
This is OK.
So this happens in a lot of things where it's very confusing because they have cubby holes,
at least in Magic Mountain.
So you're supposed to like dump your phone just out in the open and a cubby hole and
anything else you have.
And there's a, at least on the hang time or not hang time.
What's the one?
I always forget Twisted Colossus.
There is a little like envelope to put something in front of you.
And usually at Disney, it's like you can put like a bag in.
The one here at Six Flags, you could put like a Manila folder in.
It was so tight.
Your documents.
You could put an important document.
Not more than five or six.
You could slide those in front.
But anything else you had on your person, you had to go just throw in like a cubby
hole as if you were taking your shoes off to get in a ball pit.
The cubby hole system implemented before people carried around thousand dollar phones with
them.
I guess that's a good point.
Yes.
But they don't have like, I think maybe one or two.
And Riddler's Revenge at Magic Mountain too.
It was just like go throw all your shit on a table and then go back onto the ride.
Not a bad system, but there's something worrisome.
Should I leave it there on the table?
Table works fine.
Knowing that many groups of people will pass by the open table while I'm in the sky.
Knotts had a thing for Pony Express.
They have the cubby as well, but they close the cubbies once you've all put them in and
then have the other cubbies load when you come back.
Some sense of privacy and security.
Yeah, a sense.
Ultimately, it's still a cubby.
Which is all honestly we have in this life.
That's all we need.
Yeah.
Uh oh, someone else could read that good book.
Yeah, it's all we have is a sense of his greatness.
Let's just follow it.
How are you going to know these quotes?
You got the quotes at your disposal there.
I think this ride figured out the worst possible system because a man asked,
what do I do with my phone?
And the guy said, I don't know, go put it in the bamboo over there.
He did?
Yes, as the official Six Flags employee responds.
And nearby there's a little patch of bamboo, perhaps because this is an Asian jungle themed
area.
So he went and hid it under some foliage.
And then he went on the ride and then he got off and like, okay, go retrieve my phone in
the bamboo.
And his full shoe stepped right through a sharp piece of bamboo that went through his foot.
Like through the shoe, through the foot, required stitches.
The article I was reading had the reminder that sharpened bamboo on the ground was used by
Vietnamese soldiers against American soldiers during the Vietnam War.
Yeah, they said that in the article?
Yeah, they reminded you just like-
To tell you how sharp it is.
Yes, yeah, just as an indicator.
Charlie.
This was meant to destroy the killing power of soldiers.
And in this case, just a man trying to go on a roller coaster.
And so he's suing the park as we speak and we'll see how it plays out.
But what in the fucking world?
Go hide your phone in the bamboo.
I could see every different employee having a different place for you to put your shit.
There's no unified-
Like, first of all, the kid, when we tried, when my friend and I, when Anthony Gio and
I were on Twisted Colossus, we had like collector's mugs from the press events, like skull-
Full Steins.
Investments.
Yeah, I have them in there. And they were the same ones as the one at Universal. So they all
had the same like clear light up skull mug vendor, essentially. So we were like-
Mike taking calipers to the skull mug to like measure, like, how to say-
Slightly different sizes, but the same skull design from both Universal and Six Flags.
So there's a man or a com- I hope it's just a man who makes all these. One person.
But yeah, we tried to get the employee to take them because we didn't, we assumed we'd just be
able to put them in the thing in front, but it was only for six pieces of paper. So we were like,
Oh, here, here.
Our title.
Could you take them?
Registration.
Because we were like, could you take these? And he's like, I'm not allowed to touch anything.
Anything.
So we're like, oh, okay.
Even the button to start the coaster.
Nope.
So I'm handing like Anthony, like all my stuff because he has to now get out and go over to the
area. So I could see every single part. Like also maybe the kid was just saying like,
I don't want to do this shit. You do it.
Yeah. It was probably partially a little bit of column A, a little bit of column B.
Yeah. Because like, is it really some legal thing where it's like,
can't touch it.
We can't sue Six Flags if we're the one who puts it down on the dirty table.
Right. Yeah.
But if this kid puts it down on the dirty table and it breaks or somebody steals it,
then we can sue.
I could see like an older employee telling me, he's like, just don't touch anything.
Okay. Cause like so and so got in trouble.
Just to someone to ask, just don't do it.
It's not company policy.
Yeah. It's like unspoken. Like just don't just say you can't.
You're in the clear if you don't touch it.
Yes. Yeah. Yeah. Trust me. Like you'll make it farther if you just don't touch stuff.
It's all in the throat and the bamboo.
So yeah. So like whatever like table they had set up here in that situation,
it was full maybe. And he's like, I don't know, just go throw in the bamboo over there.
And he's like, the bamboo.
Climb into the landscaping, the decorative landscaping.
Put it in the tiger nest.
Yeah. I like that.
If you put it in the tiger nest, the tigers will protect it while you're on the ride.
They'll think it's one of their eggs. They'll think it's a tiger egg.
They'll sit on it. They'll keep the phone warm.
Yeah. Yeah. And then they'll suit it.
No one's going to abort them. It's fine.
As soon as you come back.
Those babies.
We don't know that.
Yeah. Yeah.
We haven't gotten confirmation.
Wait a minute.
When I went to a Mets game once, I had a metal water bottle with me in my backpack
and they were like, you can't bring that in there.
And I was like, like, it's just a water bottle.
And he the guy was like, just go hide in the bushes,
like outside of like a major league baseball stadium.
And I did. And it worked out for me when I got back.
I mean, I guess it's not the same thing that someone.
Well, I guess this guy, his phone didn't get taken.
He just got his foot in his foot.
Yeah. Yeah.
But yeah.
Follow up. But that's what they're arguing in court.
But did you get your phone back?
Yeah. Case closed.
He's got your big Android, your big Android phone was there.
It is interesting.
He did get his phone back.
Yeah.
He just got his foot messed up.
We're supposed to pity this guy.
You got your phone.
What's your problem?
You got your phone back, buddy.
You'll walk someday.
I wonder if it was like, you could see a situation where he would be like,
I can't. It's my phone.
I don't want to just leave it on the table or in this cubby hole.
Like, what do we do?
Well, then hide it somewhere.
I don't know.
Hide it somewhere.
Right.
We're not going to fucking hide the phone right now.
Everybody else is doing it.
Look, buddy, I'm hitting the button on the coaster in 45 seconds.
You fucking go over and do something or you're just we're leaving without you.
Because that is how it feels.
I would imagine it probably sounded like that too.
Like, listen, pal.
Cobra leaves in 45 seconds.
Yeah.
You got 3.5 seconds to get up to speed if you miss it.
He's got his hand on the button.
Dude, watch me.
I'll put it.
I'll do it.
I'll fucking do it right now.
It's lowering.
Oh, fuck you.
I'll fucking go walk in the bamboo.
You really want to stand in that line again?
That's 20 minutes.
It's 20 minutes of your life.
You never get back.
It's how long it takes for my mom to make a pasta.
I could be eating right now.
I could have.
I'm standing in the line again.
My mom's gravy.
All the people on the roller coaster are like, just go to the fucking bamboo.
Just fucking walk in the bamboo and put your fucking thing down.
We're trying to ride here.
Got to get to Sunday dinner.
It's different.
We've got places to be.
Grandma's making a gravy.
Get on the king of the car.
I've got so much time.
We've got to get on king of the car.
Just get in the, just go in the boo so we can go to the sky already.
Guy leans over, tries to hit the go button himself.
I'm doing it.
I'm fucking doing it.
I love about great adventure in general is just imagining
everyone there having New Jersey accents, which is true.
Oh, yeah.
It's just like, it's so crazy to me that they're investing millions of dollars
into these roller coasters and stuff for just a bunch of New Jersey people.
As a New Jersey person, it was fascinating to me.
With that real New Jersey humidity too in the summers.
Yes, yeah.
It's brutal.
It is.
It's such an odd place for a theme park, but I guess there's really no great places for
to put a thing that doesn't belong.
Drive through safari in New Jersey.
That's the craziest to me.
It's like, really?
You guys are you guys checking to see if like, you know,
the temperatures and the climate are OK for that's fine.
He looks fine to me.
You're seeing a fucking gorilla.
Is your fucking draft?
If they get out of line, we'll shoot them.
It'll be all right.
All right.
On your way.
Did they say where they got the animals from even?
And don't worry about it.
My cousin, my cousin.
It fell off the truck.
I don't know.
I didn't open it.
It was there was stakes.
There was animals in there when I got.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I know.
But when I got there.
We got to put them in a field.
I'm not going to keep them in my apartment.
Yeah.
He's going to lower the value of my Jersey Shore house if I leave him in the yard there.
More he stomps around.
Giraffe tracks.
Yeah.
All over the lawn.
There's there's one more thing I have to say about this place that has
I didn't realize until now also kind of adds to the Jersey ishness of it,
which is that I was reading the article about the bamboo impaling the man's foot
and it had a picture of the car of the coaster car itself towards the end of the ride.
And, you know, as we know, Six Flags is not crazy deep, but detailed with the theming.
They are not going to like make this like, you know, all right, so you're in like a jungle
it's not a coaster car.
It's a safari vehicle and you're going to climb aboard.
It's just it is a coaster car.
It's slightly thing.
It's named something jungle ish.
But so the the coaster car I noticed on the side of it is just a decal for got to be glued hair spiking glue.
Excuse me.
Whoa, wait, so there's ads on the cars?
Apparently, yes.
That was happening when I was there.
Maybe this is a new thing.
This is this photo.
This article was from 2020.
So this could be brand new.
Wow.
Yes, it's a hair gel.
Yeah, got to be glued, which and it has photos of yeah, it's not just people with spiked.
It's not just people who like make their hair a little tall.
It's full on big old spikes.
And as I say it, I'm realizing super situationy.
Oh, yeah, right.
Yeah.
Okay.
I know this.
I've seen this brand.
I don't use got to be glued, but I have seen it in the store.
It's not a household name like a Brummel and Brown.
Brummel and Brown's yogurt spread.
Well, butter with yogurt mixed in.
Oh, got to be glued.
We got yogurt in there, too.
It's yogurt.
How's the stick?
Really weird.
Very strange.
Already a bright blue and orange and green car.
There's a guy on this bottle that looks like Mark McGrath.
Also, I guess you're going to see the car, the coaster car as you get on it.
But overall, people, it's going so fast.
It's not necessarily like a good advertising location.
Hmm.
Only track would maybe.
Maybe if a pigeon was keeping up with it and going at the same speed, they might be able to read the ad.
Yes.
What pigeon isn't going to buy a hair styling gel?
No, they got nowhere.
Pigeon got nowhere.
Maybe the you know, this guy that becomes part pigeon, part coaster.
Oh, yes, the man, the hero.
Maybe he like has to use the hair gel for something.
He's like, I got the DNA of that, too.
It's to make his hair into antennas to find out when people need help.
Great.
Done.
It's a very clean superhero.
Yeah.
Six Flags, honestly, they should just go all out and put ads on every ride vehicle.
It's pretty good.
Yeah, it is pretty good.
May as well just what kind of like integrity.
No, yeah.
Like they should have like Bugs Bunny in like a shirt for like a local salon or something.
Just like whatever you have.
Five hundred dollars to have Bugs Bunny wear a shirt for like a month of your business.
For a Chinese restaurant.
Like a tinted windows business.
Like when they tint windows and Bugs is wearing the shirt for like easy tint.
Do you think that because there'll be a new Space Jam movie coming out at some point in
the next couple of years, will more people go to will that bump up some Six Flags sales?
Oh, I wonder.
They'll probably have some space.
It is kind of the only place where you can potentially go meet Bugs.
Bugs.
Yeah, you don't see him otherwise.
Yeah, I don't know if they have a costume of Babs.
No, not Babs.
What's the Babs is Lola.
Lola.
Lola Bunny.
She'll probably show up, though.
Yeah, if she's back.
Yeah, Lola.
For the new Space Jam.
She's got to be back.
I did actually read that she's back.
I did recently get curious what is up with Space Jam 2 and there's very little info except
that Bugs and Lola are back.
Yeah.
You read that on Deadline?
Lola Bunny.
Told you.
Told you Lola is back.
Repped by ICM.
Like Brad and Jen with their SAG Awards backstage laughing.
Bugs and Lola are back.
Oh, Bugs and Lola still get along after the divorce.
Still friends.
So nice.
Good.
Something we haven't mentioned, in May of 2009 Kingda Ka was struck by lightning.
And it closed until August 21, 2009.
So pretty much the summer season it was out of.
It reopened for like a Labor Day.
Wait, what did the lightning do?
Just the idea of being struck by lightning?
They were like, it's down.
It made it faster.
It caused enough damage.
It was damaged in Hurricane Irene too.
Jesus.
In 2011.
So they had to repair it.
It's only going to get worse with climate change.
It's got to happen.
Yeah, this one's probably not going to make it as long as other rides make it.
Yeah.
Poor Kingda Ka.
Well, but maybe it'll be when the sea levels rise,
it'll be sticking out much farther than most rides.
So as the world is ending, it's one of the few rides people will still be able to go on.
You have to board underwater.
Where do I put my phone?
Hey, in the starfish.
The rollback.
No, I don't want the rollback.
Yeah, the rollback would be very bad.
The rollback is essentially like a big water board.
Being water boarded on Kingda Ka.
Wow.
Kudos to you, Kingda Ka.
The one ride that will survive.
Did you guys realize or read that there's also then a drop ride attached to Kingda Ka?
There's also-
Oh, because it's so tall?
They had it built for a few years and then added another ride.
Like, look at all the space we're not using.
Yeah, that's pretty efficient.
They did this to Superman in Magic Mountain as well,
which Superman is a big crazy launch thing and then it goes back down.
It's not like Kingda Ka, but then they just added Lex Luthor's drop of doom to the side.
So they just plaster a different ride to the side of ride.
Oh, which, and Lex Luthor's ride was the biggest drop and now it's this thing,
which is called, oh, the name's good.
I want to get it.
Has it got to be like another jungle-y?
It sure is.
Yes. Zoomanjaro.
Does it say what that means?
No, but I saw a, this must have been the Wikipedia or something.
Somewhere I found the quote, the name Zoomanjaro has African influences.
But also just the word zoom in there, I guess.
Manjaro because that's Kilimanjaro, that's the African influence?
Yes. And the rest is referring to zooming.
So weird. So I guess also the only two rides that will make it.
It won't be as long of a drop.
10 feet.
You'll have to jump off or something.
You'll take a boat to the drop ride and then you'll get on and it's a terrifying plunge
into the ocean, the new ocean.
Yes.
The American ocean, I suppose we'll call it.
The ocean that is covering America.
Yeah, a beautiful future to look forward to.
Yeah, the bamboo already pillaged for weapons.
Yes. Yeah.
We know how sharp it is.
Oh yes. We should all go grab some now just in case.
Yeah.
If we need it in the future.
Start sharpening it up and start sharpening up our hair with got to be glued.
Everybody keep your hands on the coasters and don't forget, got to be glued.
Like got to be glued.
To make the announcements for the rides.
Then have to start advertising.
Hands and arms inside and remember for your styling needs.
Any closing thoughts about King Kong?
Any closing memories?
Do you think you'll get over there again?
I wonder.
I don't know if I'll, I mean, I guess I'll go to a theme park again when my child is
old enough and wants to go.
So I can't foresee myself going to any Six Flags before that.
You know, you have like a boys night out at a Six Flags.
Let's do it guys.
I mean, it does kind of sound fun.
Has anyone been on a big roller coaster recently?
Yeah.
I have.
Is it the same, I guess?
Like, I'm, I am a late bloomer.
So with these coasters.
You're really enjoying it for the first time.
But some of them, yeah, I went on like, I went on rock and roller coaster when I was
younger, but like out outdoor coasters, really just like your brain gets, it takes maybe
a couple of minutes longer to recover brain wise.
But mostly it's fine.
Okay.
Especially if you were doing it a lot as a kid.
Yeah.
You should probably be fine.
You could get, it's like a bike.
You built up pain in my head.
Yeah, you fucked up your brain enough.
It's like a concussion.
Your brain is used to swelling up.
Yeah.
So it'll re-swell when this happens.
Yeah, that's fine when that happens.
It'll be fine.
You'll build up your boy's tolerance and you'll like, and especially like get him sucking
some fog.
Yeah.
So yeah, well, I wanted to be an impressive teen for sure.
So.
He will.
He swears.
Yeah.
Butt chug some fog.
Oh yeah, yeah.
Loudly curse.
So you never forget that father son moment the first time you.
Curse and butt chug fog.
You teach your son to butt chug fog.
I mean, other than Kingda Ka, yeah, I don't know if I'll ever go back, but it was a really
cool ride when I did.
I did love riding it.
Sure.
So whoever, whatever aerodynamics like company, Ron Tumer, whoever made this thing.
Thank you.
The Ron Tumer.
He did a great ride.
It's good work.
And hopefully building the model didn't take your own eye out.
Yeah.
Impale you like some bamboo.
Sure.
Scott, I have a question though.
Is there something like, can we throw out real quick a couple of scenarios that would
get you on Kingda Ka?
Like say, for instance, just like if somebody goes, I'll give you a thousand dollars cash
and you don't have to travel.
Say you were there already.
Yeah.
For you.
Five thousand dollars for Kingda Ka.
No line.
A thousand bucks.
The nicest table for your device.
Clean table.
Not sharp, as smooth as can be.
So you'd have to think about that.
I'm looking for one that you go, yeah, I'd have to do it immediately.
Okay.
Here's my second scenario.
I don't mean to be a snob.
Yeah.
Maybe a thousand isn't enough.
Okay.
That's fair.
I'm just so okay.
Here's my second scenario and everyone feel free to pitch in on different ones.
Yeah.
You're with Mike Love and Mike Love wants to go on Kingda Ka with you in the front row.
It's just the two of you.
Oh man, my favorite beach boy.
You and your favorite beach boy.
That story you would tell forever.
Scott, come on.
The seat's open.
They're going to start the ride soon.
And he's, wait, does he have, no, do I still get a thousand dollars?
No, no thousand dollars.
Just it's.
But I do get.
Somebody's got a kind of a grainy phone video of it.
And it's you and Mike Love on Kingda Ka.
Yeah.
And if a pigeon were to strike him in the face.
I could say I was there for the moment.
Yeah.
Or a goose.
Oh boy.
Maybe just Christmas goose.
An 80 year old Mike Love gets hit in the face with a Christmas goose.
A goose three times as fast as the one that struck the erstwhile Marger and Spokesman.
Maybe Mike Love gets me on there.
Maybe still though.
And that I get to like, I'd get like, you know, I get 10 seconds to ask him questions.
Is it true that you were going to do a rap song with Bart Simpson?
I just love the idea of him being like, get on the ride and you think about it and say, no, thank you.
You are not enough for me.
You let me down.
You're not a true fan.
I'm sorry, Mike Love.
I'm just not interested in going on a Kingda Ka with you.
The Beach Boys.
I'll officially say the Beach Boys don't think you're cool, Scott.
Oh, oh my God.
Fired off.
And he makes it back safely and doesn't get hit by a goose.
If someone could in the audience paint, like I want a very good picture,
like drawn or no paint it.
I would like a painted photo of Scott and Mike Love on Kingda Ka.
That sounds beautiful.
There is the skill sets.
It's got to be a painter.
It should be a painter.
Do you have a medium?
Is it oil?
It's watercolor.
Okay.
I'm thinking watercolor.
Yeah, you wouldn't reject a like fancier kind of painting.
We'll see.
I'll see it entirely.
The only time I got to be gelled hair shell.
Yeah.
Different colors.
You're Kingda Ka is my skydiving is I'm too afraid to.
Oh, okay.
Sure.
Would you do it if Mike Love wanted you to do it?
As someone who's not really a Beach Boys fan, yes.
Yeah.
Easily.
They've played the Ocean City Boardwalk a couple times the last decade.
I think they've played great adventure.
Not too far.
Oh, is that right?
I think so.
Yeah.
Okay.
So really close.
So this could happen.
It could happen.
Wow.
Do they ride the rides after this?
This is why we do it, man.
They don't pay us at all.
We do it for the love and for the thrills.
I don't know.
Let me get the maybe out.
Mike Love.
Yeah.
Get me on that coaster with Mike Love and I'll do it.
All right.
That's priceless.
See that money.
That's going to be gone someday.
Yeah.
Love is forever.
But love is forever.
Mike Love is forever.
Well, fantastic.
Thanks so much for joining us.
Dan Klein, You Survive podcast, The Ride.
All right.
It's such a fun topic.
Thanks for bringing it to us and for introducing the glory of 3D
roller coasters.
Of course.
I'm happy to spread.
Our lives.
So peaceful.
Everyone at home, just sit in front of the TV.
Just watch.
Do a watch through all of those.
And really enjoy when the male host is on the ride and has to kind of still be hosting,
but screaming on the ride.
So he's like, oh, yeah.
Oh, oh, yeah.
That's a ride.
Like he's kind of still in host mode.
But he's like, oh, boy.
Yes.
Oh, boy.
He knows he's on camera.
Yeah.
Trying to keep it together.
It's wonderful.
Besides that VHS, let's exit through the gift shop.
Is there anything you would like to plug?
Well, actually, yes.
I worked on a show, Sunnyside, last season that was forgotten by time already,
even though it just came out to Hulu.
Peacock?
OK.
To Hulu.
But there was recently an article.
It's a show about a sitcom about immigrants.
And there was an article recently that I read about another show about immigrants
called Little America that mentions all the new shows about immigrants.
And Sunnyside is not mentioned because it was already just dismissed as like,
this was not a show.
But there's some really funny stuff.
And we learned a lot about immigrants.
And I really loved working on the show.
So check that out on Hulu.
Oz Rodriguez directed?
He did.
One of my favorite folks.
Great director.
Joel Kim Booster, Cal Penn.
But there's a lot of the supporting cast is very funny.
Wow.
So it is a wait.
So it is Hulu.
It's on Hulu now.
All right.
So don't forget, even though this article forgot.
And everyone wants you to forget about it so badly.
God.
Yeah.
Network shit.
Network and just TV in general.
You're like, oh, yeah.
If something's not like a smash hit, you're gone.
It is funny now to hear friends get jobs on new network stuff.
And you're not sure whether to go like, congratulations or, oh, I'm so sorry.
Yeah.
It's like, you just don't know.
Sorry in advance.
That can shift.
Yeah.
Godspeed.
Gone.
Yeah.
Well, from zero to canceled in 3.7 seconds.
Sunny side.
Although it's not even technically canceled yet.
But you can't tell if it's that because they forgot about it or they just don't want to
talk about it.
But yeah.
Very strange.
Hot topic too.
Gone.
No one cared.
Yeah.
That was a show?
That was a show.
We're not referring to the store here.
Because, no, that's live and well.
Yes.
Oh, I'm sorry.
What did I say?
Hot topic.
No, I meant that immigration discuss inside.
Oh, hot topic.
I'll never forget hot topic.
Come on.
I get shirts there every week.
Yeah.
I think we're bringing up a TV series called Hot Topic.
Why not?
About the store?
Yeah, sure.
Yeah.
That's good.
A show about working at a hot topic.
And somebody like having to, they're not like a goth already, but they need a job.
So they have to kind of goth themselves to get this gig.
I have a pilot already that has a guy working at a hot topic from like a decade ago.
Wow.
Fix it.
I forgot all about it, honestly.
The problem was it not being entirely hot topic centric.
Yeah.
No, it wasn't.
It was an analogous hot topic.
It should just be hot topic.
Hot topic.
As long as the lesson is that family is just the people you love the most.
Right?
Yeah.
Doesn't that sound good?
That sounds great.
Go for some text for hot topic?
Yeah.
And that's on one of the t-shirts that they sell at the store.
Something like that.
It's on a rancid t-shirt.
Yeah.
And a bunch of pop figures could come to life in it too.
Sure.
Yeah.
There's a lot of possibilities here.
Until that show is made, for more of us, follow us on Twitter, Instagram, and Facebook.
And for three bonus episodes every month, sign up for Podcast The Ride,
the second gate at patreon.com slash podcast the ride.
I'm going to do a little addendum here because I like when we do a little play us out kind of music.
And I want to acknowledge the music that was apparently played in the line.
I don't know if you can confirm or deny this, but I saw a Wikipedia or something that said
the line for Kingda Ka had very specific music.
It's kind of a jungle theme, as we said.
So what kind of music are we going to play?
Obviously, early 2000s trance music.
Hell yes.
Apparently, primarily the music of the Saffry duo, the most popular Danish act since Aqua.
Wow.
Since Aqua?
Barbie Girl?
That's pretty huge.
That was a mega song.
So that tells you the quality of this band.
The Saffry duo, not the Safdie brothers.
I saw it.
Yeah.
Saffry duo.
So here, just to play us out, here is the biggest hit by the Saffry duo, the Bongo song.
And just imagine being in line and this playing for a while.
All right.
So thanks for listening, everybody.
It does sound familiar.
Sounds like Six Flags, doesn't it?
I like this.
It's not dissimilar to Sandstorm by Daboud.
They apparently did a trance version of Sweet Freedom with Michael McDonald.
They got him in to do new vocals.
Really?
Yeah.
So thanks, Saffry duo.
Good work.
Bye.
Forever Dog.
This has been a Forever Dog production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Baum, Joe
Sileo, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com and subscribe to our
shows on Apple Podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at Forever Dog Team and liking our page on Facebook.