Forever!
Dog!
Warning! The following podcast will be light on funny warnings,
because we're all up to our necks in actual scary warnings.
We're gonna talk about this fucking virus and try to have some fun on Podcast The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, a podcast about places you can't go.
I'm Scott Gardner, and usually we say joining me as always,
but this certainly is not as it always happens.
Via social distance satellite is Mike Carlson.
Yes, I am here. I'm what, like what, 10 miles from?
Not 10 miles from, I'm 10 miles from you.
No one is that far away from each other.
That's what's funny.
I recently, the other day, I skyped into a meeting that was like up the block.
It was like within, it's like a 10 minute walk, and I was like, nope, not risking it.
Also not risking it Jason Sheridan.
Yes, I'm here. Scott is close enough that I almost texted him to like,
hey, could you drive by, and I'm like, no, I'm not gonna do that.
I'm close enough that I almost texted him to like, hey, could you drive by,
and just throw an SD card out the window or something?
Yeah, go ahead.
I was gonna say Jason drove by, because I had to give him a zoom to record,
and I just dropped it in his trunk.
We spoke through a little crack in his window, but we're not like,
Did you really?
It's crazy. It's crazy what's happening.
You're doing drops?
Yes.
Oh my God.
We did a bug out bag drop.
What is that?
A bug out bag, like a go bag.
Oh, okay. I know go bag. I didn't know bug out bag.
I think go bags are more for spies, and bug out bags are more for like survivalists.
We're really getting the last laugh right now.
Scott, have you ever heard of bug out bag?
I've not heard of bug out bag, but it seems like something crucial.
These are certainly bug out times, I'll say that.
You know, in case this is being listened to later, as in an archive sense.
We're recording this Tuesday, March 17th, around 4 15 p.m.
Just for historical sake, because like the situation is changing what's happening right now.
There's an outbreak of coronavirus, and who knows by the time this comes out what the situation is.
So I just want everyone to know it's Tuesday, March 17th when we're recording this.
So any relatives, any ancestors listening to this later,
just know that we tried our best. We fought.
We fought to survive, and we did the best damn theme park podcast we could.
Yes. And also just like, who knows? Yeah.
Who knows? Yeah, I don't. We could be.
I could be living. I can move back home in a couple of days.
Who knows? Who knows what happens? Is that on the table?
Are you driving? I would. I guess I would have to drive. Yeah.
Well, the flight. The deals on flights are great right now.
Yes. So there I have seen a lot of these.
So right now, obviously, everyone is being recommended in the world to stay in their homes,
not do much traveling, only by necessity, only for like groceries.
But the airlines are still at this moment operating.
So I have a Twitter alert that's set up when you get deals for different airlines
and they are going constantly. And it's like, go to Jamaica for fifty dollars.
So your dream, you're like you're checking and your points in a very grim way.
It is now come to pass. Like the best deals in since the beginning of flight are now possible.
Yes, basically right. But I cannot take them if I want to be like a conscious,
a conscious citizen of the world. If you want to be alive. Yeah, it's probably best.
Yeah, yeah. You know, it's strange how quickly this is all unfolded because we so we recorded an episode,
what, like a week ago, and we were saying like like in the episode, you'll hear it's like a Patreon episode.
And we should give the warning like we're not being flippant about it, but certainly was recorded in the before times,
that being several days ago. And while before we recorded, we were like,
is this going to turn into us like podcasting separately from each other's apartments to Quest?
And then how quickly that became? Yes, that's exactly it. That's what has to happen.
That's the only morally justifiable thing to happen. So after we finished recording,
I went to a Trader Joe's and was like, well, this is really crowded. People stocking up, huh?
Little to little did you know that very soon this would just be war zone.
Like it was seeing a product that a Trader Joe's would be an achievement.
Yeah, I was too I had Tuesday night. I had like that anxiety and I started like getting things.
But yeah, Wednesday is really when I think collectively everyone realized what was happening
because the NBA was canceled and Tom Hanks got it. Tom Hanks and Rita Wilson got the coronavirus.
And I think that was sort of cult like our moment when everyone went, oh, shit.
Yeah. Well, and in the midst of all it to bring it to our topics, theme parks,
none of which are available to go to everything. Everything we've ever talked about on the show is cannot be gone to.
Gone to. It's a staggering fact. You can still listen.
Hold on a second. Hold on a second.
Oh, wait, Jason. Yeah. Are some of the businesses at City Wall,
Hollywood still open, though? Jesus, I don't know.
I think that you are right. I think the downtown Disney and Disney Springs or maybe not Disney Springs,
but downtown Disney now is going to close.
Disney Springs and City Wall, Hollywood, I believe, closed all of the Disney and Universal run businesses
and left it up to the other tenants whether they wanted to stay open or not.
Right. So maybe the donut bath bomb place is still open.
I don't mean to discount that because soap and cleanliness are extremely important.
Yes. Yes. The movie theaters are closed.
Most movie theaters across the country are closed.
Yes. And I found out you can get a refund for your AMC Stubbs A list and pause the pause the accounts while the movie theaters are closed.
So don't let that billing go. If anyone has that program, don't let that billing go.
I mean, that the theme parks closing, yes, was like it was an intensely dramatic thing to while.
So for future posterity, yes. And this bizarre just watching them all go down, probably Disneyland, kind of the leader in it after sort of a false start where I guess.
All right. Well, there was an issue warning against mass gatherings, but Disneyland is going to stay open.
And then it was only a couple hours before. Right. Never mind.
And then I think one by one, everything else, all other parks in the country started going.
Yeah, it's that area.
Nicole mind. That was a canary in the coal mine for how insane companies would start to behave when Gavin Newsom said, well, I had a call with Bob Iger last night and we decided Disneyland could stay open.
Yeah, that's yeah, because look, I think we've all slowly sort of realized what was happening.
I mean, like I think in the history, at least as long as I've been alive, you'll hear about stuff and like swine flu and SARS and that that stuff's all deadly and bad.
But ultimately you would hear about in the news and then it wouldn't affect you for the most part.
Like we wouldn't have to change behavior.
So we heard about this and like I think it was last Saturday.
It was two Saturdays ago where I was talking to Lindsay and I'm like, does it feel like maybe they should shut everything down right now?
And we were like, yeah, I guess so.
All right, let's go to my birthday where there's going to be like 30 people talking to each other and touching each other.
That will that will be forever known as the last party.
It was the yes, it was the last party.
And I I chalk up some of this slow moving action to just our brains not being able to contemplate.
It's changing like our way of life, essentially.
So like our very American brains like other parts of the world do that like many times, either from disease or war, sectarian violence, that sort of thing.
But in America, our privilege, our privileged, selfish lives that we get to lead, it was like we're going to have to do what we can't do what.
So I chalk some of it up to that.
I, of course, chalk the rest up to like money and big business.
Sure. Yeah, I was I think wondering for a while, is is it hysteria?
Is it everybody overthinking everything?
And like, I think even a dumb part of my brain was like, we're shutting the parks.
That's going to make everybody freak out.
And I don't think I was syncing up with, oh, this needs to be done.
This absolutely is the only way we can move.
Yeah, I yes, I think that I mean, other people I've talked to, like who had gone out a couple of days after like Wednesday and I'd be like, what are you doing?
Because like I think, yes, once you realize like, OK, the reason we're inside is like to just not spread a disease because you could have you could have it and spread it, but not even know you have it.
And it's very dangerous for older folks for the in general.
That's a pretty fun thing about it.
You know, so how do you know if you have it?
Well, almost anything and no symptoms could be as that could be the ultimate symptom is no symptom.
Yes, that is very possible that you do.
You're asymptomatic.
So, yes, it has been a slow attorney, essentially turning off our economy and turning off of all of our just behavior that we take for granted and our ability to move has been obviously psychologically.
Tough for people.
And again, like we're not even roughing it that bad.
Well, Lindsay and I were in the apartment.
I'm drinking the same kombucha I drink.
I mean, I'm not really I'm not suffering right now.
You didn't fill a bedroom.
You filled a spare bedroom with that kombucha just so you would have it on hand.
Well, there was an Amazon Prime now deal, I think, for like two dollars a bottle.
So I do have a large stockpile of it.
So I am, you know, I'm fine.
And I'm like, people are being affected.
Like people listening to this might be affected and our hearts go out to you.
I mean, it's it's like real.
This is a real thing.
Yeah, that's what I think.
I think, yeah, there is no one listening to this who hasn't been affected adversely in some way.
And boy, I just hope it's not that bad or not recoupable in some regard.
And if it is, yeah, God, we feel terrible.
And all we can try to do is, you know, do our dumb usual thing and try to smile, which we will do.
We're just processing some of the some of the garbage.
We certainly are not just going to be be grim the entire time.
We're doing OK. I could say this is like a pretty positive conversation considering the mood of things.
I think so. Yeah.
And I think the episode we recorded a week ago, I am not concerned any more about the stuff being flippant.
I'm more concerned with it being Pat being like, oh, these jokes have already been made 20 times.
Oh, well, what are you going to do?
Yeah, no, it's it's fine. It's just it's so clearly we're saying, oh, we like like, yeah, well, things be radically different by the time this comes.
Yes, extremely, completely very different.
And to and to that end, that's part of needing to jump in and do an episode is partially to explain what they all we're doing,
because we've been banking episodes for a while.
We've we've been like we've almost never had such a strong reserve of episodes.
There's so many, including the one we just put out, the Kingda Ka episode with Dan Klein.
And I think it was just like, well, we should probably put something out soon where we explain that you may be hearing some episodes
where we are not in any way addressing the largest elephant that's ever been in any room.
So just know it's not because we're not thinking about it.
It's because the episodes are from the before times.
They're from, you know, early March when we could scarcely imagine what was going to happen.
Yeah. So if it's like we're like, oh, wow, I went to this restaurant yesterday and it was crowded and I, you know,
it was crazy. Someone dared me to lick the table and I did it like that's because it was maybe a month ago.
If we're describing our how our vigorous love of touching doorknobs and just really laying our hands on them for minutes at a time,
that's a very specific. I really enjoyed the doorknob run.
And I'm glad to know you all like doorknob touching as much as I do.
But it might be viewed as insensitive at this point.
Yes, that's a future that will be one of the future sort of inside jokes on podcast.
The right is our love of doorknob touching.
Yes. And there is an episode coming up where I say I'm just back from Las Vegas.
I was in Las Vegas again in the before time.
So I was not there doing doorknob touching.
Citizens of Nevada, calm your restless minds.
Yeah, right. So there's going to be so many of those things.
This is going to be like a standup sets where you say like, you know, I was at a restaurant earlier and that's not sure that happened three years ago.
We're going to be we're going to sound like liars for a lot of episodes in the future.
Yeah. What's crazy about this whole thing, too, is that we could have already had this thing.
This virus like who knows?
So like people had it in Vegas when you were there.
Who knows what happened?
What are we doing to Jay?
Let's not put that in Jason's head.
He knows he can handle it.
I do have to ask, how many times did you guys convince yourself this past weekend you had it?
Oh, because I I on and off had a tightness in my chest and I was like, well, here it is.
And slowly realized, oh, I've just been having a rolling panic attack.
I've calmed down now.
The other thing was, oh, well, having to go to the grocery stores to stock up the like don't go out a lot kind of defeated when one grocery store is out of something vital and you need to go to a second or third and then you finally find it.
But the second or third one has clearly been there for 50 years and has very, very narrow aisles.
And everyone put on cologne and perfume that day.
So I was like, oh, I'm not having Corvid 19.
I am having an allergy attack from the very potent sense in the very close quarters I have been in.
Maybe though it's good for people to mark themselves so that you know that you've breathed the air that they've been around and you know that if they have it, you now have it.
Everyone should just just mark themselves however they can just, you know, just to get out in front of it.
Yeah, I, I, I've left to do a couple of grocery runs and to mail something and then I quickly was like, I think we're going to need to do a lot of stuff remotely from now on.
So I bought what's called a capture card and the only they had one at Best Buy and I said, well, maybe I'll just pick it up at Best Buy.
But this is early too.
I'm still not quite sure because you see all these different articles about what's safe, what's not safe.
And I was like, OK, I'm going to run into Best Buy to get this.
I've pre-ordered it. They'll have it waiting for me.
I ran in there. They said, oh, here we go. Oh, wait a minute.
And then they took 15 minutes to find the item for me while I nervously stressed out, paste the refrigerator section at Best Buy away from any person.
I saw a guy cough into his arm like 30 feet away and I could feel like a chill run up my spine.
And just a few weeks ago, being in an electronics store with very few products is what we did for fun.
Yes, we happily we made a whole event of it at the now closed fries Anaheim, which, you know, I was really happy.
But I think it technically was it was under 50, I have to admit.
So that that event, while not advisable, is technically like allowed by the law today.
Yes, it depends, though. Yeah, it depends on the meat is palatial.
I think at this point, some places are saying 10 or less. Oh, my God.
So it would it would have been against that suggestion in some places.
Sure, sure. And I'm not saying I'm going to do it.
It's just, you know, what a what a different world.
What a contrast. And I'm just glad we got to see everybody.
I'm glad, you know, hey, we probably won't be seeing fans anytime soon.
Oh, yeah, not a live show for for a minute, unfortunately.
No, I yeah, it's going to be I don't know.
I don't know. You hear a lot of different numbers, but I would
I would not expect a lot of big things to reopen for a while.
That two weeks that Disney says it's going to be closed, I would bet a lot of money
that's going to be more than two weeks.
Yet even if it becomes like a loud like, OK, the parks are back over.
How willing is anybody to go?
Nice try. Nice try, suckers.
I mean, here's the thing, though.
We saw some clips of people like on a Sunday night still in the park.
I think people will be willing to go.
And yeah, you're thinking if you're thinking about it, I would suggest don't go.
I'd say probably don't go.
You know what? I think our audience inside of theme park fandom gets it
and understand from what I can tell, this is another side.
The sort of other end of like online theme park media.
I like because you guys have seen my favorite genre of what we've seen
in the last couple of days is the characters saying goodbye
because the parks are not going to be open for a little bit.
So all of your favorites are going to gather on top of the train station,
blocking the exits and making everyone gather in a one of the smaller hubs
available in a Magic Kingdom Park.
And they're all going to wave goodbye to you.
And there's one. Suck shit.
What were you thinking? Why would you do this?
I don't know. I don't know.
On any end, why are they doing it?
Why are there people filming it for me to see?
And my favorite one is one that I saw from Disney World where, you know,
it is I will say this, it's a fun gathering of characters that they assembled.
Why even some country bears are getting in the mix and we like them.
But the thing I don't like is a further outbreak of an infectious disease.
So the people gathered and who are where it really was me.
The video I was watching is that it's you know, you're seeing who's up there
and people are starting to yell the names of the characters.
Goofy, Goofy, Cinderella, Cinderella.
This is a type of fandom I don't understand.
There is like a virus in the air.
It's anyway. And you are so excited to see the obscure, never rarely seen characters.
Cinderella. You're going to shout her name.
I just don't I can't get in the head of.
Well, those people had the madness virus from 28 days later.
They had the. That's important context.
I will chalk up that to again what I'm saying, slow processing.
Those people were on vacation. Maybe they didn't get they haven't been looking at Twitter.
They haven't been looking at the news.
It's still strange to see it, of course, when we're quarantine.
But I blame the company a little bit more than I blame the folks.
Sure. I'll say this, though.
I don't know as much as we do this podcast and talk about theme parks all the time.
I guess still if I had to do the voice that I heard, it seemed to me like a, you know,
let's say north of 40 year old man.
And I think screaming Cinderella disease or no disease is a tad confusing to me.
But this is me who, when we talked about the Star Wars dance, a thought or whatever the fuck that was,
I didn't understand why everyone was so excited that Mickey came out.
It was so exciting, but it's not surprising.
It was a Star Wars show. You didn't know it was you didn't think of Disney character was going to come.
It was unexpected. Disney where it's in the in this Walt Disney World.
You're not going to win this argument.
It was shocking to me that Mickey came out at the end of the Star Wars.
Shocked, shocked, in a shocking development.
Fourteen in a row. And it's all Star Wars characters.
Scott, let me put it in terms you would imagine if those doors had opened and Peter Cotero walked out.
Peter Cotero! Cotero!
All right. Well, that was involuntary. It just came out.
But again, we're not in Cotera land.
So Peter Cotera is not seen anywhere else in Disney World.
He's not in like all the iconography.
It's not a big planter of Cotera yet that you walk in and see when you go into a Disney park.
Right. Yeah, I don't know. That's maybe not the best.
I'm trying to think of another comparison here.
Like if if we were watching the Aladdin, Disney's California Adventure Show,
which they used to be there, and then like, say, Spider-Man came on stage,
I think that would be exciting because you wouldn't expect it.
They're not in the same universe.
I suppose so. I don't think I would gasp as if it was the most shocking thing that had ever occurred.
But that's fair. I mean, I'm trying to think.
Look, we're not like so far away from being 40.
And I'm trying to think of the time, last few times I've yelled.
We went to see, we went to the 80s night at Disney a couple of months ago and we saw Totally Mini.
There's a little dance party that's based on the 80s mini.
I guess it was a was it a series or was it a special?
It was like a video. I think it was a prime time.
So this is the thing with Elton John. Yeah.
So when Mini came out, we lost our minds because she was dressed as 80s Totally Mini.
And we danced with her and we are old. We are old folks.
Well, you should have danced to it.
That is correct. And that's that's nothing that I object to.
If it was more of a specific Cinderella, like Cinderella from Cinderella 3, whatever that one was, would you currently gold?
Search for curly curly gold. Would that be acceptable?
I suppose so. Yes.
Some more alternate Cinderella or if Spinderella, Salt and Pepper's DJ had come out, that would have been more surprising to me.
That would be amazing. But still not excusable here in these in these quarantine times.
Sure. That's fair. I can get behind that.
I'm I'm trying to think of potential bright sides or anything fun that can happen in this way that we're recording.
Oh, no. Wait. Another thing we should say at the top also.
So you're in the episodes that come out week to week and you'll get it as soon as you hear certain ones.
So if you so if you don't hear us talking about of extremely frightening virus all the time, then that means that's one that we recorded a while ago.
If we say at the beginning that this is a sequester, so then you'll know that that's that's what's going on.
You might even hear a sequester. So the long time out from, you know, I want to say when we're not sequestered and you hopefully it's not that long.
But if it doesn't line up with current events, just know, hey, we're trying our best.
We're trying to try to plow ahead. It's going to be a confusing timeline.
Yeah, it's confusing as Cinderella, a twist in time.
Did you look that up or did you know?
What's that?
Did you just look that up? Did you know?
I'm not sure that that's Cinderella 3.
I know that there is a Cinderella called a twist in time where they go into the first movie a la Back to the Future 2.
Oh, wow. We got to watch that.
I mean, we will watch all things.
Things now we have time to we're going to we're going to burn through everything on that Disney plus us up idea that we're going to be out soon.
Yeah, we got to watch all that garbage now.
Yeah, I mean, things I am planning.
I'm planning to be in here for like two to three months minimum.
That's my psychologically what I'm thinking is going to happen.
It could be longer, but that's the minimum.
So we are going to miss out on things like Knott's Berry Farms, Boysenberry Festival, which I was very excited to go to this year.
We were going to cover all the different boysenberry treats and that's not going to happen.
We're going to miss. Yeah, we're going to miss out on some.
I assume Marvel will be delayed now because they have to stop construction.
Oh, yeah. Oh, that's another fun thing.
Yes. All the riots are going to happen for a while.
Those bastards, those those pets keep their secret, keep their secret lives secret for a little longer.
This is just what they want it.
I think they made it in a lab.
You might be on to something there, but that we had that right.
Universal was going to open in a couple of maybe a week or two and that will wait.
So, yes, Disney plus is where it's at.
I hear let me throw this out to you.
Maybe this will coincide.
I don't want to we don't want to say exactly what's going to happen because maybe we don't know.
But I mentioned buying a capture card.
Mm hmm. And I think maybe this is coming out on a Friday, maybe this Sunday.
There might be some podcast, the right activity on Twitch.
Yes. Yeah, I think maybe as well.
So stay tuned to our social media and because yeah, in the in the lack of being able to do live shows.
Yeah, let's let's have some fun.
Let's get into a new medium and try to the one that's like not the most embarrassing for nearly 40 year old people to be doing.
Yes, we should probably, you know, keep at least six feet away from.
But Twitch, I think we could have some fun on Twitch.
Yes, I have a pitch.
I'll give you guys a hint.
And let's see if you can.
You could don't have to say it out loud because I don't know if we're going to do this Sunday.
But eventually I have a DVD that's been sitting on my shelf for a while.
And all I'll give you is a hint is Christmas with the Cranks.
So maybe we watch that on Twitch with with the listeners.
Now is the time.
And as the time, it's not the movie Christmas with the Cranks, by the way.
That's not what I know.
I know you know what it is.
I know what it is.
I got it. I got it.
Yeah, yeah.
I think it is time.
I think I think this is probably time also to finally do the long, if not awaited, tolerated.
We've long tolerated the notion of doing an episode where we watch all of Father of the Pride.
Oh, yeah.
If there we finally found a scenario with this quarantine where that would be a less tedious thing to do than day to day life.
I have the DVD within arm's reach as we speak.
Boy. Well, then we're going to have to figure out there will have to be some drops in here.
But then beyond that, well, once we figure out some logistics.
Yeah, I think I think it's time.
This is going to be we're going to clear out the attic of all the ideas we've ever been talking about.
Mm hmm. Yeah.
And in fact, actually, we should throw it to the because this is we're going to get to some listener questions in a little bit here.
But that's probably a thing to ask.
What do you want to do with us on Twitch?
We're all hanging out.
We're all hanging out in disparate bedrooms and offices.
So, yeah, what do you want to see us do?
Let's have some fun. Yeah, I am also twitching a lot like on my prom.
I'm not private. I was going to say private account on my account.
Fat Carlson on Twitch and I've just been playing video games with Evan Susser.
So I'm I'm I'm entering this new streaming world.
And, you know, we're trying a lot of stuff out.
Maybe we could play a game as well.
Well, there are. Yeah, there certainly are video games to play.
There's that Magic Kingdom and yes, game.
There's again, once again, the the Universal Studios GameCube game, which finally again in sequester light feels like an actual.
Finally, OK way to pass the time.
My problem with that game, it involves running around a theme park and picking up garbage.
My my my GameCube is the only Nintendo system I have that is broken.
Oh, which I guess I can find a used one.
I'm sure it's not one hundred like thousand bucks or whatever.
Do we all want to get like start a roller coaster tycoon park again?
Well, I play that every now and then on my phone.
Yeah, I look there's no way to stream games off of your phone, unfortunately.
But I could see if I could download it.
You mean build a park together or build competing parks?
Oh, that's interesting. Maybe competing parks.
I don't we'll talk about it off air.
Yeah, yeah. Some of these logistics will we'll figure it out on our own.
But yeah, hey, tell us what you want.
Give us ideas. Do our work for us and we'll we'll figure out some fun we can have.
We can we can make this just like a three month long or longer snow day.
Yes, that's yeah, we'll do.
We'll do our best watching the movie Snow Day.
It might be fun.
I don't know. It's not necessarily applicable.
But again, very few things are there.
We're going to have to loosen the definition of what it is we do.
I have been so bored.
I put on the movie Memoirs of an Invisible Man with Chevy Chase.
It was also in Snow Day.
This is finally my chance to make it through the full Chevy Chase filmography.
Yes, I think that's a very good idea.
I just you know, speaking of Chevy Chase, there's a new film coming out.
That's it's like a Curb Your Enthusiasm with Paul Hogan from Crocodile Dundee.
What the fuck?
Yeah, it's the premise is that Paul Hogan like comes back to Hollywood and Chevy Chase is in it.
And it's like it's like really just Curb Your Enthusiasm with Paul Hogan.
And we should watch that if it's video on demand as well.
Oh, man. I bet we're going to make it to that Lance Burton movie.
Oh, my God. Billy Toppett, the Lance Burton movie that was direct to DVD.
My brain will not retain the words Billy Toppett.
I think you've said them to me six or seven times and my brain just swats it away like a ping pong paddle.
Every bad idea I've ever said is like 50 percent better now because we're in the house or in the apartment.
Is this where are we going to get so bored that we just we just do the harbor hoedown?
I don't know what boredom you're talking about is.
I live for this shit. I hate leaving my house.
I was born for this.
So, yeah, Jason, let's let's catch up.
What is your routine like now for the last couple of days?
Food wise, what are you keeping in the apartment or house?
You know, I've been watching my girlfriend and I had been watching a lot of the lights like 90s romantic comedies.
Most of a ton of which I had not seen or had only ever seen like half of like 10 things I hate about you.
Very good. Yeah, I really like that.
Never been kissed.
Also pretty good. Pretty good.
Weird. I mean, obviously weird.
But like, oh, John C.
Riley's first film role.
Interesting.
There's like a base level of quality.
If it was something was in a movie theater in the 1990s, it wasn't just like like wretched.
Yeah, for sure.
Yeah, there's some there's a lot of movies around them that are like really good, like three star movies.
Went backwards, went in a little more in my wheelhouse, watched the 1944 version of Meet Me in St.
Louis with Judy Garland on a weird app in the Roku store that has all these classic movies, but just feeds you an unseemly number of ads.
Like every eight minutes.
So the movies are free and a pretty good quality.
But like then you will see the same ad for like online online schooling for children.
Like you'll see it five times in a row.
It's clearly some sort of Ponzi scheme algorithm nonsense.
But great songs and meet me in St. Louis.
Why don't you give us a taste?
Oh, yeah.
What should I?
I mean, the whole time because maybe in St. Louis, if you haven't seen it, it's about a family, a large family.
We're very excited for the World's Fair coming to St. Louis, the 1904 World's Fair, which celebrates the Louisiana Purchase.
And so the whole time everyone is singing meet me in St. Louis, Louis, meet me at the fair.
Don't tell me the lights are shiny anywhere but there.
And so like just constantly singing that, which is a song.
That was nice. Thank you.
Very nice. Thank you.
Yeah.
Yeah, the movies kind of split between songs from that were popular in the time period and songs written in the 40s for the movie.
And it's a big MGM.
Like it's a big it's like split up into chunks like big set pieces.
And it's a big MGM movie musical, which I think are like if people don't like musicals are the most like interesting or fun like kind because they're just like so everything had to be done with a million.
Background members and chorus members.
Lave.
Yeah, it's very lavish.
These are these are films that would be deeply illegal or troubling in the current climate.
Yeah, no.
Yeah, they would have to be CGI.
Someone would have to do something called crunch to get it done to like have one person tap dancing.
But then Bugsby Berkeley would just have like 50 women doing making a giant cake like they turned to the other left and suddenly they're no longer a line of women.
They are a giant multi-tiered cake.
They would just that's what movies were.
I think maybe like I think we'll also be stretching the confines such to it.
You know, and we do have like a final four thing coming up, but maybe there's like a can we do the brackets for the best Bugsby Berkeley musical number?
Oh, of course.
Oh, yeah.
I mean, that was a good most problematic one, too, because there's some really like again, like incredibly giant set pieces and like Footlight Parade, the one that was like mentioned a lot in the great movie ride.
Some very poor racial stereotypes that I don't think aged well back then, let alone now.
Well, I think that puts them at risk of not making it all the way through the final four.
Yeah, some points for racism.
They will lose in the first round if they're racist.
Let's make that.
We don't want to make it too predictable.
But yeah, we'll all be shocked if a racist one makes it for the past round one.
Sorry, Shanghai Lil.
It was very cordial of you to apologize.
Very.
And of course, the title character of that song played by Rosie.
Is it Rosie Keeler?
I think was the name or Ruby Keeler, the very, very pale woman who starred in all those movies.
Yeah.
Okay.
My.
But James Cagney tap dances out of nowhere in a sailor suit.
All right.
Okay.
Yes.
You know, you enhance Jason.
All right.
This is the important question.
Treats in the house.
What are you keeping?
Okay.
Are you hoarding?
Are you stockpiling?
How's it going?
You know, I always heard during times of stress or trouble or economic recession, people went
kind of like went immediately towards comfort like that.
But I didn't really find any shortage of treats.
What am I looking at right now?
I got a half full bag of goofy sour balls.
I've got a bowl of Cadbury Robbins eggs.
A bowl show.
Well, like I opened the bag and dumped them in a bowl.
Okay.
Let's see.
Robbins eggs.
Yeah, that's what I always heard them called.
They're like sort of big oblong Easter.
Easter candy is still in stock.
Yes, that is true.
I was just at CVS.
Yeah, tons of Easter.
This is not affected the Easter candy market.
Take comfort in Reese's eggs, which I think are the best shape of Reese's.
I've got some Kit Kat ice cream in the freezer that I have like miraculously not really cracked
into yet.
I've got a couple boxes of cookies.
This is a lot, by the way.
Yeah.
Yes, you're right.
But this isn't even due to Corona.
This is just kind of what you got.
Well, it ticks up around Easter season to begin with.
You don't have Christmas Robbins.
You don't have Halloween Robbins.
I don't have Christmas.
I might have like one or two wrapped like stocking stuff for candies somewhere still.
I try not to keep sweets in the apartment unless people are coming over or there's some sort of special occasion.
But I will say I have for the first time in a couple of years, a package of EL fudges.
Nice.
Oh, that's some comfort.
Oh, just see it for the physically visually seeing our old pal EL.
He's really comforting.
Yeah.
Well, wait, what is EL?
Ernie Keebler.
Is that I don't know this mythology very well.
I'm trying to remember.
What does the EL stand for?
Is it is it Ernie Luther Keebler?
Were they like very proud Protestants?
The Keebler elves were all Protestants.
I didn't really.
Yeah, that's right.
They did not.
They did not like the papists.
It seems like you could either think of it as the ELF, EL fudge, ELF just stands for elf.
Then that's what it is.
But also, I'm also seeing that EL stands for everybody loves everybody loves fudge.
How about electric light fudge?
Yeah, I would also accept that.
Yes.
What is that?
So these the character is that little elf guy?
He's not EL fudge.
Well, that's Ernie Keebler.
I know I would bet my life savings on his name being Ernie Keebler.
Yeah, that's that's correct.
Yeah.
And he's I guess it doesn't mean his name.
I guess what you're saying, it stands for Al for it stands for everybody loves love Ernie
love.
You better believe I'll know.
I'll find out who all of these characters are.
Fryer Tuck spelled like because he fries Ernie's nephews, of course, are Zoot and JJ.
Oh, my God.
I love Zoot and JJ.
Do you know we're going to do a whole oh, Patreon on the Keebler.
Keebler the Keebler family tree, the linear family tree.
Yeah.
I'm super down.
Elwood, Leonardo, Elwood, Fast Eddie.
Oh, I know.
I love a fast Eddie.
Let's abandon the rest of this episode and just do the Keebler elves.
This becomes it is crucial in a trying time that we learn the names of all the Keebler
elves.
Wow.
I never thought about the Keebler elves.
I would love to.
All right.
So I'm going to go ahead and do a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little
bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little
bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of aving.
I would love to.
All right.
So while this one will turn this one around fast.
Yeah, they've been around since the 60s.
There's a long there's plenty of meat on this bone.
All right.
Keebler elves coming.
I mean, we should probably switch over to audience questions because we asked for for
some of those.
But what have we really not hit here to be said at this momentous tedious occasion?
If you go to our Facebook page, our Facebook group, our new group of moderators has been
kind of putting all of the press releases or emails of the park closings and dates and
stuff in one like long thread.
And that was very helpful to look at in one spot.
So yeah, I mean, do you guys have anything on on the park closings?
No, just that I'm sort of like, you know, expecting it to be a while in case you haven't
heard our our annual passes.
Obviously, this is one of the less pressing matters going on in the world right now.
But our annual passes will be extended as long as the parks are closed.
Yeah, that is interesting.
I'm curious how long that's that's going to be.
And I like that they did get that announcement out fairly quickly.
Yeah, I agree.
Who who knows exactly, but it's not going to be I don't think any I don't think anything
goes back to 100 percent the way it was before and at least like 18 months.
Like there may be a world where six months from now you have to take your temperature
to get into Disney.
I know what you're saying.
Yeah, there's going to be something like that because I've seen this compared to the you
know, it's like shoes at the airport.
There will be some like it's going to be different.
People have said no, like don't expect a vaccine until the minimum 18 months.
Jesus. Yeah.
So anything can happen.
But I mean, I think stuff will change and open again.
But I think that's yeah.
Prepare for things to be different for a while.
That's what I'm reading.
I had a couple of little oddballs in the way.
I mean, after the first couple of days of every company you've ever had any interaction
with emailing you that with their coronavirus procedures, then stuff started to turn ugly.
I mean, a lot of places laying people off and there's arguments there of like, well,
they have to lay them off and then rehire them to get unemployment.
That's a big leap to trust some of these flat out vultures that they are going to rehire
everyone.
Some very odd little moments.
I was saying Disney Springs and CityWalk Hollywood were first closing the Universal and Disney
owned businesses.
There was a news story at an NBC affiliate which just used the phrase about Disney Springs.
People will still be able to go and walk around.
And I'm like, oh, please don't do that.
Don't don't know.
And then the strangest thing, which someone I posted and then someone told me they have
kind of walked back.
But Universal Orlando seems like they did not quite get their shit together messaging
wise because they told everyone to go home and they'd be paid for two weeks.
And then Friday afternoon turned around and said, OK, everyone's coming in and you're
going to either sit in your break rooms or you're going to clean, which is insane.
And then it seems like they've scaled that back for the record.
Well, some of Universal staff can work from home.
Universal Orlando employs twenty seven thousand people.
So kind of a big group if you look at it in aggregate.
A bit of a mass gathering.
Yes, you might say a mass gathering.
I'm sure it's going to be weird from what I've heard.
Some of these parks like use like these people are employees and these people are contractors.
And that's going to be gnarly to see how that plays out.
Disney also like was ending the the rock band in the UK pavilion and the drummers in the
Japanese pavilion at Epcot.
I don't know if that was just when the contract was up, but that looked pretty shitty that
those poor guys were announcing it Sunday as everything is shutting down.
Announcing it with like and in the end, the love you take is equal to the love you made
for extremely dramatic moments, the end of the revolution or whatever.
Yeah, very pretty dignified exit, unlike the people showing them the exit.
So, yeah.
So, yeah, it's who I'm hoping by the time this comes out, there's some sort of like
national plan for people to get compensated.
That's what certain people are talking about in the government.
So, again, things are changing.
So I'm hopeful that people are going to get taken care of.
Who knows?
I mean, it was kind of before all this, but do you think is there any possibility of the
Sector Keeper being allowed back into cricket wireless?
That's a good question.
I think that maybe when they try to pass this, whatever this coronavirus stimulus for people
is in the Senate, that maybe somebody can sneak in the severance for the Sector Keeper
into the bill.
Oh, just put it in the fine print.
Absolutely.
Yes, yes, yes.
Do we think we have a member of Congress that listens to podcasts to write?
Do we think there's one in the House or the Senate?
I mean, we can burrow down.
We can look at the analytics and see what the numbers in like D.C. and Virginia are like.
At least some aides, maybe.
So, yeah, maybe yes.
If you're at least an aide of a senator or a congressman, please let us know so we can
get the Sector Keepers severance from cricket wireless put into a bill at the 11th hour.
And they're doing great.
The Congress is doing great on those bills right now.
You know, they're undercutting each other and that's all going very well.
Primaries in multiple states in the country right now.
Yeah, that's nothing I couldn't yell about for another hour, but we should answer listeners' questions.
That seems like a more fun thing to do.
We're going to take a quick break and we'll be right back and we'll answer some of your questions because we listen to our constituents, not like Congress.
Nice. Yeah.
Hey, and we're back to take some some of your questions.
Thank you for filling up this episode and giving us some things to talk about.
Before we get to listener questions, I have sort of a topically relevant question for you guys, which is this.
What who is your favorite sequestered or socially distanced Disney character?
As I was thinking about this, and there's certainly more than more than one, I think Rapunzel, you would have to say, entangled.
I wait, I'm forgetting a big one.
If you count them as Disney, the Han Solo in the carbonite is technically so he couldn't get anybody sick down there.
True. Didn't really choose it, but kind of forcibly so.
I I'm forgetting a very Gepetto.
I think Gepetto in the in the belly of the whale is right.
It is is is contributing to diminishing the curb.
The curb. Genie Genie in the lamp.
That's what I yes. Yes.
The genie. That's a very long.
Hopefully ours is not as long as the jeans.
Did you say beast in the castle?
Oh, absolutely.
Yes. Yeah, true.
Really all of the enchanted objects in their own way.
They don't quite keep distance from each other.
But, you know, we're still talking to significant others and such.
So we should pick a favorite of these or.
Oh, yeah, or just, you know, I'm just trying to make a list.
I think I feel if you have a favorite, certainly go for it.
But, you know, I think I feel less alone knowing that some of my many of my favorite characters have been sequestered at various times.
Yeah, I get that.
Are there any park specific characters that are more like sequestered?
Oh, that's a good point.
Yeah, do you mean the Yeti in Everest?
I might say yes.
And that's a pretty that's his choice.
He doesn't want you bothering him.
Right.
That's good.
Yeah, that's good.
Because I'm trying to obviously all robots are stuck there.
But we're saying in the universe of these rides and the story.
Yes.
Who like doesn't want to be bothered.
OK, on the people mover in Florida, the woman getting her hair done by the way.
She's not getting her hair done by a robot.
True.
That's yes, that's safe.
She's not harming the well-being of a human barber.
OK, I'll allow that one.
Yeah, I think that counts.
Yeah, I'm flashing down.
I'm picking universal.
I mean, any character you're disturbing like like the abominable snowman.
I think the the inciting incident of Guardians Mission Breakout is is is that Tyvon
allowing you to come see his opening his collection of the public.
He I think was sequestered until now.
Well, he's forcing all those monsters and aliens and the Guardians of the Galaxy
to be sequestered as well.
Yes, that's the entire thing is rocket breaking them out of being right.
So we're actually hurting the public good by going and rescuing them.
Yes, exactly.
Yeah, Tyvon seems more like he has like Howard Hughes kind of top floor office.
So he's self sequestered and everyone else is quarantined in a group.
Yeah. Would you rather be sequestered in your apartment or in the Tyvon collection?
Well, there's I don't know.
I think there's living things in there.
You know, figment.
And I like that's where I'd be worried about any germs that any of them have the figment or Groot as.
Yeah, God knows where Howard the Duck has been.
Not good. He's very sexually active.
So, yeah, yeah.
It was the 70s when he was created.
So he's very horny.
Mm hmm.
That is a film I will not be revisiting during my sequester.
I mean, I say that now, but it's like in a month.
The drugs sounded pretty good right about now.
Yeah. So, yeah, that's a lot of that's a good lineup.
And I guess I'd I'd pose that back to the listener, your your favorite sequestered or quarantined.
And they are different things.
Thanks for bringing that that color on the spectrum to that, Jason.
Yeah.
Mm hmm. Well, your questions, though, that's that's what we're here for.
Does anybody have one have one ready to go?
I have the one I saw first really wasn't a good theme park question, but I did want to answer it.
Mm hmm.
It says during this time.
Sorry, sorry. That's not it.
They basically they're just asking if Jason and I had our dream X-Men lineups,
which I think we talked about doing and we never did.
Matthew Hurdle asked that question.
And I have my answer real quick for everybody.
It's Beast Gambit, Nightcrawler, Shadowcat, Storm, Maggot and Dazzler.
So there you go.
Pretty good.
That's pretty good.
Yeah.
You want to come you want to come back to it?
Write it down while we're doing this and then you'll say at the end.
I already have so many things Jerry rigged.
I'm not going to be able to focus.
I'll give I'll give like a chaos one off the dome.
So Jean Grey Cyclops Wolverine, Cable Gambit, Shadowcat, Dr.
Celia Rise.
Oh, pretty good.
Pretty good.
Longshot.
Oh, long shot's pretty good.
He just says good luck.
Scott, do you have an answer for this?
If you just like of the X-Men, you know.
Yeah, mine would be Ernie Fryertuck, Zoot, not JJ.
Sorry.
Fast Eddie, Edison and Art.
Hey, it's all good.
Very good.
A lot of the non mutant ones.
But, you know, long shot with not technically a mutant came from another dimension.
Arcade world or whatever.
Mojo world.
I really I know I know I'm throwing a lot of shade by leaving them off at buckets.
Who?
You know, now that I think, you know, buckets being the one who throws the fudge onto the cookies, I probably should have included him.
But, you know, we're coming up with these just off the top of the dome.
That's Jason's favorite character in fiction.
Yeah.
I mean, I think you need I think your story possibilities really open up if you have Fast Eddie end buckets because, you know, the kind of antagonistic relationship they have is really something.
Well, a Fast Eddie wraps the products.
So an overage of fudge on the cookies makes Fast Eddie's job harder.
So it's tough for them to find a work balance.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Mm hmm.
Anybody do you have one?
I've got one about my bullshit.
Yeah, go ahead.
So sure.
From the Facebook page, Emily sure is asking vertical or horizontally sliced hot dog buns.
And I believe what that means is are you like if you were holding the bun in your hand, would you slice the side or would you slice the top?
And I have to say I mostly associate top sliced hot dog buns with like the northeast with New England kind of especially like lobster rolls kind of if you can picture one of those.
So I'd have to go horizontal because that's my I respect the top slice.
But horizontal is probably my go to choice.
Interesting.
Interesting. I think I'm a top slice guy.
I know I wasn't asked asked, but I think it's I think it's very novel and I am enchanted by it when I see it.
I think because it's so rare to be you're enchanted by it.
Enchanted.
Enchanted. Sure.
Enchanted is such a good word, such a flowery word when you spy a hot dog bun.
Well, you know what I also you know, a lot of those top slice, you know, get a little toasted or a little buttered, you know, so there might be a little extra surprise in there.
You never know.
I'm going to I'm going to direct one to my wife feel bad saying Mike's bullshit.
This is not it is a Mike directed.
It's insulting to a certain someone to say bullshit.
This is from Tyler FG.
If he could go to a theme park, what do you think Edwin, your dog's favorite attraction would be?
That's a good question.
I guess the bread tour at California Adventure because he would like the smells.
Although I guess, you know, any ride that Edwin could do a little smelling, he would be happy with.
I don't think he doesn't like a car ride.
He gets very upset.
He whimpers when he drives like anywhere.
He doesn't drive.
He doesn't drive. We drive him.
So I think anything with anything that doesn't move and has a smell.
So I mean, that's why I'm going to say bread tour at California Adventure.
Speaking of Edwin, someone is asking for the picture of Edwin in a sandal.
Oh, yeah, we post that.
I think it's got it.
I might have that. That's a good. Yeah, that's that's an important pick me up.
I'd also like to say maybe one of the only positive things about us recording in different places is that finally there are more pets in the show.
Pet lineup.
There is a possibility any time that we're recording one of these sequestrosodes that will get an appearance from my cats who I haven't talked about that much.
Certainly said that I have them, but it's probably time they aren't in here right now, but they could come in at any time.
And they really hate when the door is closed slightly.
I'm amazed they haven't come in yet, but it's probably we're all bored and it's probably time for you to meet my my cats.
There's Brenda who has jet black hair.
She's named after Brenda from 90210 and she's kind of, you know, you know, like skinny and feisty.
So what I would say scratches me a lot.
And and then there is Bunny, who is the one with the seat.
I've definitely referred to one of my cats having a thick seat.
And that would be that would be bunny.
So if you get an appearance or just get a picture and she's more like bunny colored, like gray and white.
So if you if you hear me referring to him, now, you know, the new show that's Bunny and Brenda.
That's great. I got confused. I thought Brenda had the seat, but it's bunny.
Got it. It is. It is bunny. Yes, because she bunny is more rabbit esque in general.
I think the seat is part of that. That's it.
She feels more anatomically like a bunny and Brenda, you know, because she loves to climb.
She's kind of like a little mini King Kong.
When I see the city walk, King Kong kind of reminds me of Brenda.
That's nice. So now, you know, the expanded lineup of the of the show pets, I'll tell you if they come in.
Let's go. You know what? Let's do an order. I'll go next.
I'll go next. Then Jason and so because usually when we do this, we can point at each other.
Now we don't have that ability. So we'll just go around Robin. How about we do that?
That's a good call. That brings it to you. Yeah, it brings it to me.
What are each of this is from Kevin Tully on Facebook.
What are each of your favorite theme park rumors that didn't and probably will never come true?
You can also include things that were announced and never built.
I'm going to stick to the first part. I'm going to say rumors.
I'm going to go with Wicked taking over Marvel Island, California, as they had Islands of Adventure.
That's my favorite, weirdest rumor. We've talked about it a lot.
I do want it to happen because it means then that Disney can use Marvel in Florida.
We have a we now have a drop that would require a drop ride, a high speed roller coaster
and an immersive, extremely expensive screen ride to all be different shades of the mythology of wicked.
Yes, this is if in case you're just joining us for the first time,
theme park podcaster Jim Hill has been talking about this for a few years that this has been a possibility.
It has not come to fruition yet.
But yes, that would mean that all of that stuff would have to be themed to specifically wicked.
So that that is the one I want to have.
He says this because Universal owns wicked.
There's been like a talk of a wicked movie that has not happened.
Right. I know I'm so confused about what's there's not been such a film.
Much much like Cats, the wicked movie, which is supposedly moving through the pipeline,
will happen much later after the wicked zeitgeist has died down.
Let's make sure to get people really make sure everybody really forgets what the thing was.
I mean, it's still running. It's still very successful on on Broadway and the books that it's based on, I believe, successful.
But yeah, I don't. I don't know.
I mean, it's clearly Jim Hill's life work is trying to get this wicked thing.
He's pushing it because it's what he wants. Well, mine is also a Jim Hill.
I've never stopped thinking about the idea that the Jimmy Fallon ride was going to be him interrupting twister.
Oh, yeah. Going live every single day from the Tonight Show studio, which would be a challenge right now as it is,
he's production and him in Jim's words, threatening to throw a cow at people.
That's what the Jimmy Fallon ride was going to be was him.
And he like crudely taped a sign over the wall that says Jimmy Fallon's ride,
but that it's otherwise still the iconic twister, write it out.
I think that's a new visitor to Universal Studios from China, I think, would completely understand.
Oh, yes. The attraction based on the 1996 movie has been taken over by the talk show host.
Yeah, that's good. I think mine.
Well, Mike and I always talk about there are those plans for a giant like massive Marvel rise in the Middle East.
But that I mean, that was a little far along, so not really a rumor.
But I think the original Star Wars land plans at Disneyland were very interesting of like the Millennium Falcon
sitting above you right in the center where that sort of metal sculpture is.
And then the Endor speeder bike run kind of taking over the land occupied by Autopia and the subs.
Mike, there was more. Right. Am I what am I forgetting?
Those are the two big ones. The idea, I think, like kind of where the is it where the people mover used to load?
Is that the thing that's been sitting up there like unused? Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Like that would have been the Millennium Falcon and it would have just been a walkthrough where you would have met Chewbacca.
And then they would have demolished America Sings building interventions building.
And yeah, it would have been a speeder bike ride. I think they were going to take out Autopia and the subs maybe.
So you would have like started inside. I believe that's right. Yeah.
And then you would have gone through like the forests of Endor.
And I guess, yeah, I guess Star Tours would have stayed the same.
Maybe Space Mountain would have stayed. So right in the in the middle of this would have just been Space Mountain.
But maybe I think people were thinking that space forever.
Like, I think people were thinking that the hyperspace was sort of a holdover from that idea.
Oh, maybe. So it was like a cheaper version of what they were thinking they would change if they had had Star Wars take over Tomorrowland.
I'm glad that didn't happen, though, but it still might be now, especially years away from Tomorrowland being different.
Hey, forgive me for being quiet during all that. But speak of the devil. Bunny came in.
I had some good pics of Bunny right at the microphone. She didn't she didn't talk or anything, but she's wandering around my the big contemporary hotel model that is on my desk.
So, hey, check out check out our Twitter for some of that sweet cat content.
Yeah. Who's next? Scott, is that Jason next? Jason, I think.
I got a very good one from Liz Blackerby.
Which of the Duffy gang would you most want to be stuck in quarantine with?
Hmm. That's a good question. I think I'm going to answer first.
I think it's and I'm going to say his old name, but I know he has a new name and we haven't talked about it yet.
Olu the turtle.
Have we all seen, though, that Olu's name is not Olu anymore?
What is it? Hold on. I'm trying to find out. It is Olu Mel.
Oh, so much like Cookie became Cookie Ann, Olu is becoming Olu Mel.
Yes, it's not just Olu anymore. And he's a turtle and he's chilled out because he's like he's from Milani.
So he's a very like probably a really good roommate.
Like Gella Tony is the of course, the Italian painter cat, and he would just be a lot like he'd always want to go party.
He would be like if you were stuck with him, I think you maybe would get on your nerves.
So that's why I pick Olu Mel.
Maybe I ought to go Cookie Ann because she's going to be making treats this whole time.
I'm stuck. That's a good pick. Yeah.
Just practical more than anything. Yeah.
Jason, what do you think?
I feel like has no one said Duffy yet.
I mean, I think it got I gave it up to the big guy.
I think he I just find him very rock solid.
I feel like he'd be a comforting presence.
I think the number of outfits that he has would probably be, you know, fun.
You do a little fashion shows, that sort of thing.
And so you yeah. So and he takes on all those skills, right?
Like when he wears the pit crew outfit, he is a handyman.
Right. I don't think that's I don't I think he's just playing dress up.
I don't think he actually like he's not someone who actually can like do everything.
I think he's just playing fun dress up.
You think he's doing stolen valor for any number of occupations?
OK, stolen pit crew valor. Sure.
I'm not saying that's not fun, because, yes, I guess I guess if you were in an apartment
having a big teddy bear go in and do like a pretty woman scenario, like where you were sitting,
watching him try on outfits would be entertaining.
Yeah, I think so. Yeah, he's he's like, is it different than we don't think it's like Barbie?
We're like Barbies in different outfits, but I think Barbie does the jobs.
We don't think she does. He's doing the jobs.
I don't think Duffy is doing the jobs.
I don't know if this is actually written down anywhere, but that's my reading of it.
That's the stressor.
Yeah, for the most part, it's just like he's wearing, you know, a polo shirt and khaki pants.
Yeah, I don't know if somebody has an objection to this, please let it be known.
But that's my take on Duffy.
Well, good picks. It would be nice to be.
I mean, I mean, like Mike, you are quarantined with some of the Duffy gang.
Oh, yeah, they're right here. I'm looking at them right now.
And I hopefully it doesn't come to this.
Hopefully you don't have to eat them.
I would start with Tippie Blue.
Good.
The bird mailman.
The least emotionally connected to Tippie Blue.
That's why I don't want to be so cruel.
But if that came to that.
It's good to have the order in your head, really any group of people you're in, even before all this, I think.
And after this, I think just whenever you get in an elevator, just kind of like do the math of what order you would you would eat people in.
Mm hmm.
It's just helpful. Practical.
Yeah. And listeners, please send us the order in which you would eat the three of us.
If you were in a situation where we were the only food, who would you eat first?
And somebody is like, all right, I've thought a lot about this.
So like this is drawn 25 page.
Yeah, no fan.
We don't want fan art of that.
That's one of the times I will say no fan art of listeners eating us for food and sustenance.
Yeah.
None of that, please.
I for.
Absolutely do a non-culture fan art.
Yeah, here's here's a fun one.
This is from Parker, a mama, mama.
What is blue 32 doing with all this time away from performing that he brings up a good point that there was a specific as we've had the moments of everything getting closed and sometimes in an email form via David Copperfield did make an official announcement of it.
This that he will not be doing the doing the production with his alien blue 32 for a little while.
I wonder if I I have that somewhere in a text.
Let me see if I can find it, especially in times like these.
Magic is important to me.
I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to find it.
It reminds me of a text.
Let me see if I can find it, especially in times like these magic is important.
It reminds us to dream and believe our own ability to achieve the impossible.
Nothing is more important than the health and safety of my audience, my team, and my family.
So we're pausing shows today to assess the situation.
Powerful stuff from from David and his love for us.
He's not he's not in the show.
I like to think that when David is performing, he takes blue with him.
Mm hmm. So they can be sequestered together.
That's that's not a that that's not a sure that they don't need social distance.
No, I mean, yeah.
Is it more likely that blue is just like stuck in a box in the back of the MGM Grand?
Yes. Oh, I like to think not in the world of the show.
Yeah, that is weird. The blue is just sitting somewhere.
Yeah, moving.
So it's possible that David takes blue with him.
Like, I assume David gets driven around because he's so famous.
But I'd like to imagine like David with a top down on a convertible has blue next to him in the car
and that they're just like letting the air flow, like flow through their hair and their antenna.
And they're just like two cool buds driving around Las Vegas together.
Like, Dan, Dan, Dan, Dan, Dan, Dan, Dan, Dan, Dan, Dan, Dan.
It's it's all their blast and rat pack there.
Yes, they're ignoring the quarantine because they have magic on their side.
So it doesn't it doesn't apply to them.
If they get infected, they just wish it away.
Yes, I think that there's no.
Yeah, I think that like David probably has sort of a sixth sense for everything.
Mm hmm. He has a spider sense.
So I think David, yeah, he knows when something's contaminated and he just says a couple magic words and it goes away.
And then, of course, blue is able to as if you've listened to our patron episode,
David's blue alien friend is able to pick out an audience member that's hot.
Right. So he is a power to.
So he so so maybe he's like,
if he's stuck in a room somewhere, he's probably like flipping through Tinder.
That's what he's doing.
He doesn't know when he's going to be out and on the prowl again, but he's like getting his cue ready to go.
She's hot. She's not left.
Right. Right. Right.
No, left. I don't remember which is.
I don't know which one's which I've never done it. Jason's the only one who's done it.
I don't quite. I mean, left to left is when you want.
No. Right is when you want. Yes.
OK. But I had to remember because you're you're.
Yeah, I guess you're making the same motion.
I it that would be a punch line for jokes, I feel like for a while.
Like and I would forget which was left and like I would forget like, wait, what is good and what is bad?
So just saying like, yeah, you're going to have to swipe left on that one.
You're like, does that mean cool, man?
Everyone else in audience laughing uproariously, you just like slow clapping to like, no, I get it.
I totally get it.
Let me go here.
This is from Doc Chapa at Twitter.
Who should the next R3X be?
An old retired character who should return to the park in a big way.
Oh, that's good. Very good question.
Thank you for that question.
Not that it has to be this way, but I'm certainly thinking in part of a big new development,
like the Marvel area of of California Adventure might be good.
Like it's like an old character that's a little anachronistic.
And how do we like fit it into a new?
I mean, that makes me think Marvel McFay in the Marvel line.
Oh, interesting.
Yeah. So it's you know, his name is Marvel.
So so he fits. He's allowed.
Yeah. What did he do?
I want to obviously see him come back.
What were you saying? Sorry.
What did he do? What was kind of his his function on this earth?
Spreading good sheer, I think. Great. Great.
It seemed like, yeah, he was just sort of like call for a good time.
Call Marvel McFay not in maybe a sexual way, but just, you know, to party to have fun.
For Lutz. Call him for Lutz. For Lutz, as you say. Yeah.
It was. Yeah, that was the old days.
All right. So he's dealing drugs to Iron Man. Great. OK.
Yeah, that's bad. Iron Man has a problem.
But I mean, look, that's opens up a lot of storyline possibilities, certainly.
Yeah. I also think people are going to be so like wiped out and emotional
after all this Corona stuff that I think Disney to brighten mood should just be selling drugs in the park.
Like, why not just give everybody everything they want?
Like, I think Marvel, Marvel McFay walking around with baggies of psychedelics.
Let's just make everyone real. We're all going to need it come October or whatever it is.
I think I'll say this. This. Yeah, go ahead.
The funny T-shirts like the funny Disney T-shirts with like Donald having Corona are just going to be awful.
Oh, my God. No, I don't want to see those.
I won't we won't make we made it.
We made a bunch of bad drinking Disney shirts, but we will not make those.
I can guarantee that. Old characters were we'd like to see back.
Yeah, I think Sam Eagle from America Sings. Yeah, we've talked about him before, but he's he's got to come back.
We got a context where where do we put him?
You know, people aren't happy.
Apparently, there's some people who are extremely unhappy about the eagle, the same eagle barbecue and Epcot.
So put him in there. He's a Disney character. He's Disney.
It's not an outside IP and he's, you know, he's he's cooking up ribs and tapping kegs.
Sure. Yeah. Walk around Sammy goal to tap the keg like literally.
Yeah, he has to actually run it.
It was the kind of thing they're going to have to do with budget cuts is make the suited characters also serve the food.
Yes. Yes. Which honestly was always my dream as a kid.
I thought, oh, they're working there. I thought that would be fun.
But of course, the reality is that would be very strange.
You want it to be that you wanted it to be the like goofy is bringing you food and it really is his job.
And if he doesn't do it, he doesn't get money.
Yeah. And he like he trips and like a bowl of pudding falls on my dad's head.
But what we don't see is like are the OSHA complaints after the fact.
Oh, my God. A lot of paperwork.
How unsafe would that kitchen be?
Just like that. Not like goofy would like he would be so he wouldn't knock, knock knives over and it would like barely not stab him to death.
Yeah, it would like knives and it would like perfectly form the shape of his body around him against the wall.
And that'd be funny for us to see.
But less funny for the other endangered chefs.
Oh, my gosh. I can't even imagine.
Yeah. Did keep goofy out of the kitchen for gosh sake, for gosh sake.
Goofy go home. Yeah.
You're only going to spread this virus further or with you do comical bumbling will hurt someone at some point.
Yes. Jason, what do you think?
Characters.
What? Sorry, I've gotten my birds confused.
Mike, what was yours again?
Sam Eagle from America Sings, the top hat.
Yeah, like a top hat.
Was that your choice?
Yeah, that that was who I was thinking of.
I just couldn't remember.
Like, no, I forgot that there are all Eagles are named Sam.
That's right.
Yes. Yeah, as we proved definitively.
I mean, Horizons, Robot Butler, Horizon.
I mean, if they're going to do Epcot, like vintage Epcot, Horizons, Robot Butler or Smart One from CommuniCorps, like, you know, they got to be somewhere.
I think I think there's no changes to Smart One.
He's just walking around. They don't update it. They don't do anything.
He's just rolling around the park again.
Everybody freaks out.
It's a huge Instagram thing.
Why are they just get them out there?
Yeah, that reminds me.
Scott, did you see the like there was an old, old Epcot show that like the video video of it just went up for the first time called like Mr.
Something's computer review that I think like would happen by Smart One.
Oh, interesting.
No, I haven't seen that.
I'll check that out.
I got to dig this up.
Yeah.
Great.
Wait, Mike, you had something.
I've honestly I forgot.
I forgot what I was about to say.
I'm trying to get my next question prep.
Oh, yeah.
Hey, you know, that's the dexterity of having to do these mailbag episodes.
Yes, I actually do remember I was going to say I was going to say my pitch is just for Smart One to move in with Jason.
Oh, that'd be great.
Just like two pills.
Would Smart One help me?
No.
Oh, it's more.
OK.
No.
He'd be more of a burden.
Well, oh, great.
So what is the worst remake quality Smart One would have leaking oil everywhere?
Motor oil.
Oh, yeah, that sucks.
I'm sorry, Jason.
All clean up after me.
My arms do not reach the rag and the floor.
I will spark.
I can have oil in me, but not outside me.
Light up my cigarette, too, please.
Wipe the oil before we light my cigarette.
Smart One, we're going to lose the security deposit if you keep smoking indoors.
Our landlord can get bent.
OK.
He sucks.
It's not very that's not very productive.
Smart One.
I'm smarter than him.
Tell him that instead of next rent check rate.
I'm smart.
Smart One is smarter than you.
Care of.
Fuck you.
I broke that.
I broke that toilet again.
I weigh 300 pounds.
With what?
On my body.
My butt.
Why were you anywhere near it?
I was trying to leak my oil in the toilet as you suggested.
That's not really flushable.
Oh, well, you should have said something to me about it before.
I said that.
I said it sarcastically.
Oh, by the way, did you know that my full name is Smart Ass One?
No, come on.
It's about my wicked attitude, my wicked toot.
Well, I don't care for it.
Sorry, you got to live with it, pal.
The S's in as are smelled with fives.
I like this.
New character.
This is great.
There's more questions, but that's hard.
That's hard to top.
That was a lot of fun.
Is there anything else we want to jam in?
I've got a good one, and I think this might be a good wrap up.
I mean, we're not going to get better than a piece of shit smart one.
Smart Ass One.
Yeah.
I think that's a good one.
Smart Ass One.
But this might be helpful if people are looking for entertainment during the quarantine.
David Agua Bubblegum on Twitter is asking, what are your guys' favorite podcast, The
Rides episode?
Interesting.
How can you pick?
They're like our children.
We did do the AV Club had us talk about some of our favorites.
Well, obviously it's this one in quarantine.
I mean, yeah, it doesn't get better than this.
They don't have to deal with any of those fucking guests.
I've hated every one of those guys.
There's an extra.
Scott's starting to crack.
When you say something funny, there's an extra half second to go like, oh, did what I say
was, was it not funny?
And then you might be hear a laugh on the other side of this.
Like that's, that's really good.
I really like that.
Yeah.
I think I just, I think some of my audio that I'm recording on my own just dropped out.
So yeah, yeah, stuff like that.
Jason leaving all the time.
I it's, you know, having problems to deal with tests, your rigors as a podcaster.
And that's why this current one is easily my favorite.
If I had the word hero is thrown around a lot.
If I had to pick a second favorite, it's probably McGruff.
The McGruff music episode.
Yeah.
And, and McGruff too.
I mean, now is the time to really like get down and digitize and do all the research
to, to figure out McGruff too.
I will tease this.
I can't, I have to keep it vague.
I hope I will finish it by, I will tease something extra that I've thought of for McGruff too.
Oh, that is going to, I think it'll, I think it'll turn out well.
That's all I'll say.
Neat, neat.
But there's, I mean, we promised a lot.
I'm still trying to hunt down the person who wrote the songs.
I'm still, we're in the process of digitizing the new McGruff or the old McGruff music that
we found.
We found an additional McGruff album we didn't know existed.
And there is something else I've got in the works.
My God, this might be McGruff two, three, four.
This might be a separate McGruff spinoff podcast.
It'll be like Avatar where we announced four different McGruffs with different subtitles.
It's an incredibly ambitious array of future McGruffs that will come out in 2032, when
we're allowed outside again.
I don't, I don't know if this is like the best episode to listen to.
And I don't, I can't speak to that because I don't listen to all of them back.
But I'm not a fan of the ones I do.
But I've never had more fun doing podcast the ride than the hundredth episode live show
with the Sector Keeper and Bugsy.
That's certainly the book.
When I think of like when I, when have I had just the most delirious fun doing anything
podcast the ride related, it is probably that one.
So if it's my favorite in that I'm the most fond of having done it.
But that's that that's me.
Sure.
The hardest I've laughed I think were the the two part failed parks with Jason Willner
on the Hard Rock Park.
And what are those?
Who are the what are those guys called?
The weirdos?
Sid and Marty Croft.
Marty Croft.
Yeah.
The two hippie weirdos.
So funny.
Where is the lie?
The lie.
But especially the the end of part one whenever whenever we ended up doing it I had to run
out.
So listening to the wrap up of the first part was I started laughing all over again because
I didn't know what it was.
And you two did a great job on that.
Thank you.
Hey.
Oh you mean the at the beginning of the episode or like this sudden like guess what?
We're rocking harder next week.
Yes.
Yeah.
Let's say that's that's I think that one was just this just hasn't been so much surprise
for us in recording one.
Hey.
So and then now we are a little we feel a little more loaded to bear like we think oh
now here's a good one and then we almost like put too much pressure.
That one was just snuck up on us so much.
How fun how funny all that got that we had no idea was going to be over three hours.
That was a ton of fun.
I felt similarly.
It was two episodes but we did them back to back.
The most recent run with Eva Anderson in the downtown Disney ordeal that like felt like
a mega episode because we did them back to back.
But the speed round of all the stores that's that's another one of the most fun I've had
recently.
Yeah.
So that lesson is the longer the longer we record if it's under three hours we're probably
it's the quality is going to be low.
Yeah.
So over three.
So yeah over three hours means good.
Yes.
Yeah.
We got to start doing these way longer.
So yeah I mean that's it for now.
I think so.
I think you survived podcast the ride.
Should we retire the term you survived in this scary.
That is actually really grim now that you say it.
Yeah let's put that away for maybe a little while.
We need a new catchphrase.
You you you listened to podcast.
That doesn't seem like it has as much fun in it but it is true.
No you you endured podcast.
I don't.
Yes.
Put up with podcast the ride.
You put up with a podcast.
You put up with podcasts the ride a sequester showed.
And thank you for for putting up with us.
You know it's going to be you know it's going to be different.
Mr.
Joe quote it's going to be different from now on.
But you know will the show be worse.
Yes.
Yes it'll be worse.
Sadly it will be worse.
Keep in mind all shows will be worse and in some cases not happening at all.
So so is it better than a show that isn't happening.
I think so.
I for one am looking forward to like the podcast final four final four when
everyone does a bracket of all of the different podcast final fours.
Oh yes.
Each other.
Yeah because there are yes because this this conceit that we do is also
something that all the other podcast and podcast were friends with like dough
boys and blank check.
Yeah I think it's time for all of the final four.
To compete.
And again then there is no you're going to listen to that episode.
Our final four in a world where there is no real final four.
So forgive us when we aren't mentioning constantly that this is a parody of
something that doesn't exist.
Yes.
Cut us some slack.
There will be again we said there'll be episodes where everything seems fine
and those are old but still fun.
We had no idea that they were time capsules.
It was just a slice of life of what it was like in you know circa February 12th.
Yeah.
So yeah there's going to be some whiplash but you know you're all used to it
from going on all these rides.
Yeah.
Whiplash.
You stick their necks hurt.
Yes.
That's my point.
So it's really we won't get for a little while.
So just listen instead listen to this podcast and shake your head around it's
fun.
Really Wayne's world it because that's how much this podcast rocks.
I had fun.
This is I'm going to say this is some of the most fun I've had during the
quarantine but the bar is extremely low.
I think it's like this and like making jokes on Twitch.
Oh yeah.
And remember Sunday to pay attention.
There's going to be some twitch activity.
So check on Twitter.
Probably in the evening in a type of evening that works for West Coast and East
Coast both of America that is.
Yeah.
We're going to have a little bit of a fun time.
Live something on Twitch and for other stuff.
Check us out on Facebook and Twitter and Instagram and you know with none of
these places are very fun right now.
We promise you there will be some nonsense.
There will be Edwin in a sandal.
We'll make sure that whoever of us has that and and Mike had at the at the
microphone.
What else.
Oh and hey and podcast the ride the second gate at Patreon dot com slash
podcast the ride.
I was going to do here.
Here I'm going to do a quick call back to end the show.
Jason I ate all your Robbins Cadbury eggs in the wall again.
Smart one.
I've had about a dozen technical difficulties to work with.
90 minutes and before this.
But your bad attitude is the worst technical difficulty of them all.
I ate the eggs just to annoy you.
I can't even taste them.
Well great.
It's working.
Now the chocolate has gummed up my mouth gears.
Oh smart one.
I brought you a chocolate.
I broke the toilet again.
Man come on.
All right.
That's the end of my.
Yeah.
Next week.
Maybe that maybe the light maybe the switch thing is that live.
Maybe we with a cardboard cutout of smart one we do this.
Play of that or at least a 21 minutes that comes out.
Yeah.
Great.
All right.
Jason get to work making that.
It's all good.
Right.
Oh man.
Yeah.
Me.
The crafty one.
The one who's good at drawing.
Oh boy.
Hey.
All right.
Stay safe everybody.
Yeah.
Take care.
That's it.
Yeah.
All right.
Bye.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been.
The end.
Bye.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson Jason Sheridan Scott
Gardner Brett Boehm Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey for more original podcasts please visit forever
dog podcasts.com and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts Spotify or wherever you
get your podcasts keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter
at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.