Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, The Second Gate.
I'm Jason Sheridan here today with Mike Carlson.
Yep, I'm here.
And Scott Gertner.
This is very sober.
Yeah, fresh from the oven.
You do actually say something fun like fresh from the oven.
I'm Jason Sheridan.
Well, I'm showing somber respect to a PTR legend today
because we're talking about the king.
I just mean, you didn't have to have any like prepared joke
where you could have said something dumb,
which is what we do oftentimes on The Second Gate.
That's all.
Well, I'm Jason Sheridan, the new king of sourdough.
And we're talking about the original king of sourdough today.
Papa Steve.
That seems disrespectful.
It is disrespectful.
Make that claim based on nothing.
Yeah, I don't like this intro either.
You wouldn't call the guy who took over
the king of sourdough?
Well, he has also passed on, unfortunately.
Oh, then the next guy in the succession?
Okay, so we're talking Papa Steve.
Okay, so yeah, Papa Steve.
Sorry, we're starting hot now.
We're starting hot, we're starting hot.
Like a fresh piece of bread from the oven.
Anytime I do the intro,
I am just looking for what direction the dragging is going.
You got lulled too,
because before we started, I go, that's good.
You don't have to have a joke or anything.
Yes, you did.
You did so well.
It was my bad, it's my bad.
Yeah, Scott's fault actually.
Papa Steve.
Let's explain Papa Steve.
I think our deeper fans probably know already,
and we have declared him a PTR legend.
But let's recap from scratch,
as a sourdough bread is fresh made.
Right. Okay.
So we basically, I'll speak personally about where we,
Papa Steve.
Where your Papa Steve journey began.
Yeah, so basically there's a bakery tour
in Disney's California Adventure here in California,
and you get a little piece of bread when you start.
You walk through, you learn about the mother dough,
you see the little process, what happens, blah, blah, blah.
Then there's a big picture of a man named Papa Steve.
He's a kindly old man.
He's holding some bread in the picture.
He's in front of a lot of bread.
Yeah.
Also like stacks and stacks of bread, holding bread.
A comical amount of bread.
And when we were going there a lot early on
in my time living in California, we'd always be like,
it's Papa Steve, look at it.
And then we'd point and then there's various pictures
of Jason I have with Papa Steve.
Do you have the, are you, have he?
I at least have one or two.
I think I have a bunch of pictures somewhere
on a hard drive somewhere, but I at least have one photo
of you and Papa Steve on my phone.
Yeah, cause we're going back to like 2012.
Yeah, a while ago, yeah.
And we know that he's Papa Steve because of the quote
at the bottom of the frame, which when his quote is,
motto is good bread, good food, good people.
And then there's no further explanation of who Papa Steve
is, which I think contributes to some of the oddity.
Yes.
Sort of like we're supposed to know already.
He's Dave Thomas or we're acquainted with him
due to commercials, but no, I don't know who Papa Steve is.
And in fact, the first he came up on the show,
I didn't know what you were talking about.
I had missed this.
Very fair.
I've certainly been in the bakery tour,
but I had never noticed Papa Steve before.
Yeah, and let's clarify.
This is not the bakery tour episode.
This is the Papa Steve episode.
I'm gonna ask about the rules here.
This is not the episode about the Boudin bakery tour.
No, well, I mean, if it comes up, it can come up.
It can come up casually, but yeah, it's just,
if I start talking about Rosie O'Donnell and Colin Mochrie,
I should probably wrap it up fairly quick.
That I think you should save.
Right, yeah, that's it for the official.
I'm not gonna like go do some material about it,
but if they were to even come up in passing,
are you guys gonna wince?
Well, they usually come up in passing every episode.
I'll allow a little, I'll allow a little.
Okay, but we just should not go overboard.
And then a further question beyond that.
Yeah, go ahead.
If this is not the Boudin bakery episode,
when that separately happens,
is that episode different than an episode
about the Pacific Wharf Cafe, which it services?
Different.
You're watching the bread be made for it.
I know the answer already before you even have to finish.
Obviously, those are all different episodes.
I assumed, I'm just getting the rules clear,
getting them on the page.
The Pacific Wharf.
Now they're certainly tied together
because you're watching bread be prepared
that is served in the Pacific Wharf Cafe.
Yes, this is more like though,
like the sunny eclipse episode of the Patreon,
where it's just, we wanna focus on-
Focus on a beloved character.
Yeah, beloved character.
Not a lot of topping bar acknowledge,
but not delved into.
Do we still then owe a separate cosmic rays,
starlight cafe episode that cannot be about sunny eclipse
for more than 5%?
Is, yeah, well, I would say more than 5%
can be a little sunny related,
but it's obviously gonna have to do a lot more
with those chicken sandwiches,
those delicious chicken sandwiches and the topping bars,
that dry iceberg lettuce,
that crisp dry iceberg lettuce you pull out
that has no nutritional value.
The wet caramelized onions.
Yeah.
We gotta talk about that.
Give me to that episode.
Yeah. Quick.
So.
The nothing tomatoes, the quality free tomatoes.
Yes, no nutritional value in anything on the topping bar.
It doesn't taste good at all.
So we, I submit to these rules,
I assume these were the rules, but I do,
I wonder if we can still do it and stay on track
without a sourdough keeper to keep us in line.
We'll try.
I feel like. If we need to summon somebody.
If we have to summon somebody, yeah, we'll find,
but I think if you have an idea,
if you have a thought about Pacific Wharf Cafe,
please say it now.
We'll just obviously have to get into it a lot more
on the other episode.
Is the thought allowed to be,
do we have to do an episode about it?
That is a thought.
Well, the thought is,
how long do we need to do this podcast in life?
So, I mean.
It's a marathon, not a sprint.
If we're talking a couple of decades of this podcast,
which I'm not trying to do a Doughboy's thing of like,
we need to end the podcast.
I don't think that at all.
I'm just saying.
I think opening day eatery with a secret menu item.
I mean.
I could see a scenario.
I could see a scenario where we do a mega episode
about like lucky fortune cookie, Pacific Wharf Cafe.
And then I forget the name.
Fortune cookery.
Cookery, sorry.
This is interesting.
I could see a mega episode of that.
Because I believe it's a Pacific,
I don't remember now that I think Pacific Wharf
is also the naming structure of the beer truck
where you get.
Like Carl Strauss.
Carl Strauss.
Yeah, exactly.
And then there's the margarita.
I could see a mega.
It's obviously.
A Pacific Wharf episode could be a catch all.
Yes, I could see, but again, a mega episode.
Yeah, that's.
Two and a half hours.
Okay, we're committing to who.
But it's so much real estate there.
Yeah.
That it's got a lot.
Yeah, Carl Strauss, the margaritas.
I can't think of the Mexican restaurant.
A jam packed episode.
You're right.
I was gonna say jam packed episode.
You're salivating thinking about it.
Jam packed episode like our jam packed tummies will be.
Jam packed tummies.
It's Kuchina, I believe Kuchina, Kuka Manga
or Kusina Kuka.
I fucked it up before.
I don't wanna get it wrong.
Is there a day in there?
Do we have a day?
Maybe I could be wrong.
Like a D.
Oh, the name of it.
Yeah, probably.
I mean, we should look it up.
Maybe not though.
Yeah.
Yes, possibly.
Frontierland one is Rancho Del Zocalo or something.
That, yes, that's a frontier one.
All I know is that when we did the early on,
we did the tortilla factory tour.
I was apparently saying a different language's
pronunciation of that word.
Oh.
One is Kusina and one is Kuchina.
Oh, I see.
And I kept saying the wrong.
Not as bad as.
I thought you meant tortilla.
Were you saying tortilla wrong the entire time?
Probably that too.
If we did an entire episode where all three of us
said tortilla.
Tortilla.
Like our grandparents.
And we just didn't know.
Like Napoleon Dynamite.
Sure.
Mm-hmm.
So anyway, yeah, I recommend the tortilla factory.
Cause remember you get a free tortilla.
Tortilla, yeah.
You do and then you gotta do the scale.
Tortillas are good and quesadillas.
Quesadillas.
Well, we'll hopefully not get it wrong
when we do that up at the episode about Pacific Wharf.
Pacific Wharf sounds nice.
Gotta devote some time to the photo opportunity
where it looks like you're in a book in a net of fish.
Oh, I love it.
I love that.
Yeah, so well, I guess that could be a main feed,
but that'll be a big Pacific Wharf episode.
But for now.
In 2031.
2031.
We have the podcast mapped out that far.
Yep.
So.
We're starting to bank, yeah.
We have it, it's pretty much,
what you're hearing was recorded several years ago
and we're, we've pretty much have it set through 2026.
That's right.
And just so we get a little topical,
we've done the Dana Carr VSNL sketch,
the Ted Koppel sketch where he's said different things
that could happen.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, exactly.
And we plug it in.
Yes, every possible way that Jimmy Carter,
I'm sorry, Gerald Ford could have died.
Yeah.
So if you hear us talking about the 2020 election,
that's us pre-guessing,
we've thrown out a lot of material about like Cuomo,
like people who didn't end up running.
Yeah.
We had to snip it, but we recorded it just in case.
Yes.
So yeah, we're covered all of our bases here.
So yeah.
So now when you hear us talking about
that it's down to just Bernie Biden, that's,
you just heard one of 30 options
that we recorded two years ago.
Yes, every possibility.
And one day maybe we'll release the alts where it was like,
we thought it came down to Bennett versus Biden
or Bennett versus Yang or.
Yeah, we had a lot of jokes about Bennett boys.
Bennett boys, yeah.
Or the outcome where it was clearly
Tulsi Gabbard unopposed.
Yes. That's true.
And then they also the option
where Jason entered the race somehow.
Sure, yeah.
Yeah.
And then we recorded all of, so without Jason,
because if he's the president, he wouldn't be there.
So.
The super delegates, all big fans of the podcast.
They love the podcast.
They love it.
They love minutia.
But anyway, let's get back to.
To the man.
February 2020 and.
Boy, the cat's movie was bad.
No, Papa Steve, there's so much.
The king of sourdough.
He sure is.
The man legend.
We're basically going off of a picture frame here.
And so it's up to us now to fill in the information
about Papa Steve.
Let's pay him the respect by saying his real name.
Stefano Gerardo.
Unless.
Gerardo?
Gerardo.
Gerardo, yeah.
Not Gerardo.
Somebody.
Yeah, not Gerardo.
There's no extra R.
Yeah.
So we learned about this man.
This is related to theme parks.
The thing that attracted me to Papa Steve,
because it is just like a largely contextless picture.
When you think about Disney parks, especially,
that is some of the most expensive real estate
in the country, if not the world.
So the fact that there is just a picture,
essentially an immemorial picture of him,
because he passed before this park opened.
Just here with no context and maybe a mention
in the earlier on tour is interesting.
And it also, I do want to clarify,
he is not the founder of the Boudin Bakery.
Right.
He bought it.
Yes, there was a Boudin family who you learn about
in the video with Rosie O'Donnell and Colin Mochrie.
Now this video is pretty entertaining.
Let me set the timer though.
Isidore Boudin, as I believe is the French pronunciation,
but the Americanized English version is,
they do call it Boudin, as I learned in an informational
little documentary on the Boudin Bakery YouTube.
Oh.
Which I'm going to put this out there now.
That video has a good number of views,
but they only have 64 subscribers.
Folks, give them a subscribe.
Give them a subscribe to the nice Boudin Bakery people.
Who's those numbers?
Yeah.
If you can get them some, some ad revenue.
Make them partners.
So yeah, so, so I've, I've been reading that it,
so do we want to talk about Isidore more?
Do we want to keep talking about Papa Steve?
Isidore is covered mainly in the, in the-
Yeah, you're right.
Isidore is covered, but his big innovation
was taking French bread baking techniques
from master French bakers of which he was one
and combining it with the sourdough bread
that the 49ers, the miners would have
because it keeps for a while.
I see.
Okay, okay.
And their business is up and running in San Francisco
for decades, bun decades, but is starting to struggle.
Enter Papa Steve.
Steve.
Papa Steve's story, very strange, born in San Francisco
but moved to Italy when he was seven.
Then-
Left Italy when he was 14.
Left Italy, all right, yeah.
We're all comparing our same notes
and moved to France to become a great baker.
That's right.
And at 21 moved back to San Francisco
and became a San Francisco institution.
But how strange that he was born there, moved away.
Was it that his parents left also for bakery reasons?
I don't remember about the parents.
There's not a ton of Papa Steve information.
Not really.
No, and I'll say this for a few minutes.
I was throwing for a loop
because Papa Steve's son was named Steven.
Oh.
And the San Francisco Bay Area newspapers
had obituaries covered both of the sales
and purchases of this company, their debts.
But this is the way he, Papa Steve died in 97.
Yes, 97.
Okay, so we have the right guy,
if that's who we're talking about.
So, he found stall, look, the guy found stall around Europe.
A kid with a dream, he was 14,
he wants to go be a great French baker of bread.
That's pretty early.
That's early to know what you wanna do in life.
I assume he would have grown up around it.
He would have some inspiration.
I'm only speculating here.
Might have been his first food.
Maybe his pacifier was carved out of sourdough bread.
Interesting.
So he had the taste, the first thing in his life.
Was there ever a time in your life
where you thought about not necessarily being a bread baker
but any sort of like, you know, cake maker,
any sort of working in a bakery like that?
Jason, I'm talking about.
You know.
Poor Scott, you can answer too.
I mean, no, no is the answer for me.
No is the answer for me too.
I never really considered it.
I think I'm an okay cook, an okay baker.
I never considered it, but I did think it was interesting
because in college, I knew people who's like work study,
they would work at the on-campus bakery
and their shifts were so early in the morning.
That was a big thing.
I am not an early riser and much respect to Papa Steve
because as we'll get to later.
Oh my God, Papa Steve was an early ass riser.
Early riser.
Wow, but it's completely that.
You didn't like to sleep in.
Well, I never really considered the culinary pathway.
I have a cousin who got a culinary degree
and considered taking a job at Walt Disney World
but I think went back for additional training.
I think she got a baking, you know, pastry degree
and then went back to get a full chef,
whatever training you get.
What if you, I mean, like things don't have to be baked
in the morning.
It's just generally how things will people,
commerce works and everything.
Would you be into the idea of like a bakery
that opened at 1 p.m.?
Oh yeah, absolutely.
Well, but again, you gotta have it all out by 1 p.m.
Why?
So, huh?
Why do you have to have it out by 1 p.m.?
Well, if it's opening.
You're setting your own hours.
Oh, I see.
What if?
Yeah, I think if you're suggesting idea of a night bakery.
Okay, so it has to be 6 p.m. is when it opens
because you roll into work at 1 p.m.
and then everything's ready by 6 p.m.
So it's a night bakery.
I'm kind of into that
because it is interesting like the LA donut shops.
Some are 24 hours and then some like close up.
At like 3 p.m.
At 3 or 4 p.m.
Right.
And then reopen at like 5, 6 in the morning.
So where's the one that opens at 3 p.m.?
Yes.
You swoop in when all the other,
when those quitters are closing at 3.
Right.
Yeah, I mean, look, this podcast was,
we saw the space for comedy focused theme park podcast.
It seems like there's space for a night based bakery.
So, entirely night.
Jason Sheridan's night bakery.
Third shift, I mean, swing shift, graveyard shift,
they deserve fresh treats too.
Yeah.
So yours can be good bread, good treats, good sleep.
Papa Jason.
Sleep.
Yeah.
Sleeping in.
I'm surprised to look at 16, 17 minutes
to get to Papa Jason already.
I mean, yeah.
I'm Papa Jason.
That could be another good way to open the show.
You said it's I'm Papa Jason.
Oh man.
Yeah.
Well, I did it in.
Okay.
I'm Papa Jason.
All right.
Papa's got a brand new bread.
I'm Papa Jason.
Papa Jason.
I feel like I do have a strong personal stances
on sourdough bread.
Sourdough bread, pretty high on my list of good bread.
Maybe number one.
Okay.
Of like the bread I like the most.
What did you consider everything in that though?
Do you consider like, as we've talked about
the pronunciation before, a croissant?
Do you, is that in the-
I'm not considering that.
Okay.
You're just saying it's standard bread.
I'm talking like brioche.
Brioche is probably up there.
Rye.
Potato bread.
I like potato bread.
Yeah.
Hmm.
But sourdough number one.
I think sourdough number one.
Sometimes it's too hard for me though.
Really?
I don't love a hard bread.
Unless it's like garlic bread,
like so hard that it like crumbles.
Yeah.
I'm into more of that.
I like a little resistance and the chewiness.
I think that's why I like it.
How much, let me ask listener,
how much resistance do you like when it comes to bread?
Let us know.
Biscuits, I mean biscuits are up here.
Well, biscuits are a whole different thing.
That's a whole nother world.
I also-
If you let us know with hashtag rise of the resistance.
That should make it pretty clear.
Very obvious what you're tweeting about.
I also have a distinct memory of being up in San Francisco
and visiting the Boudin Bakery.
Cause I was there for SketchFest
Doing your own artisan craft.
Doing my own artisan craft, that's right.
And then I did another artisan craft
of getting food poisoning.
And was very ill,
and miserable walking around San Francisco
and went to the Boudin Bakery
and got a small like thing of sourdough bread.
Cause they have it in every size under the sun.
That's pretty like tame.
It's very tame.
And just like walking around the wharf,
drinking ginger ale, gnawing on a small loaf
of sourdough bread to come back to life.
Like a rat.
Gnawing on it as the sea,
looking at the wonderful sea lions.
All those fun-
The sea.
There's a big, there's a wharf.
I know what you're talking about.
It's just the image of you like sick drinking ginger ale,
gnawing on a piece of bread while you're looking at sea lions.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
And you're like, uh, like you're on the throw off.
That would push the other off.
Nice.
Those fights are good.
Yeah.
You can stop and stare at fights for a while.
Sea lion fights.
This is beautiful.
This is Steinbeckian California imagery.
Yeah, this is the real deal.
I like this sentence.
I assume that we, there are three websites
that we all went to independently.
Stefano became known as Steve Two,
his friends and customers,
and Papa Steve Two, his employees,
in his 60 years as Master Baker of Boudin.
So he made his employees call him Papa Steve,
but not his friends and customers,
which honestly seems a little bit like a power play,
like a power move.
Did he make them or did they like?
Well, it's unclear.
We don't have, we hopefully will be reached out to
by some people that worked under him.
Did his children call him Papa Steve?
It seems, well, yeah, it doesn't say family,
but customer, it says customers and friends, Steve,
people that worked under him, employees, Papa Steve.
I think this, I think the Papa thing,
it seems to have some nice symmetry
to his strong belief in the power of the mother dough.
Yes.
Because he really, and you guys might have these quotes too,
but he speaks with a lot of passion about the mother dough.
Yes.
I'll just, I'll read one of them.
You might have the same one.
But always referred to as she, you know,
like a boat or a gun that you call she.
Like a mother.
Yeah.
A boat, a gun or a mother.
She loves to eat the sweetness of the flour.
She eats one type of sugar, which is maltose,
which is the only sugar the wild yeast can eat.
You need to keep the mother healthy
so she can keep having babies and babies and babies.
The mother, keep the mother.
The mother.
I know what the mother dough is,
but I don't feel comfortable explaining
the concept of the mother dough.
Well, it is,
No, go ahead.
I was just going to say, correct me,
cause I'll get it wrong.
It is like the original master mold, not mold,
but the original like master, what would you call it?
Like configuration of dough that by which all the,
like dough comes from, it continues,
like they grow it essentially.
So the idea is like, it's an unconnected,
it's like an infinite.
Like we all connect back to Adam and Eve.
Yes.
It's like Grant Morrison's hyper entity
where he talks about like,
if you could see time and space from afar,
you would see you walking through the door here
and you would see you go all the way back
and into your mother's womb.
And that's how you would,
if you could see all of time and space at once,
it was not linear.
So the mother dough, it's the same way.
You want to see that all the bread came from this one thing
they made, you know, whatever, 150 years ago.
Whoa, there's Michael Bennett being sworn in.
Yeah, you could see that if time and space were all,
were not linear and you could see it all at once.
It's a starter.
It's a starter, like that is used
and then you put a little aside to use the next time
and then you put a little aside.
Right, but it grows as well.
Yes, it's alive.
Right.
It's alive and fermented.
I see.
That's what's goes on.
And a little bit is saved with every batch
so that there's always a piece connecting it back
to.
Is that what it is or is there just a master thing
that they take a little piece off of
and put it in the new batch?
I believe it's that.
I believe they,
so you put a little in, you mix up the dough
and then you put a little of that dough aside
and you just keep doing that.
I see.
So there's not like a master dough that's still somewhere.
I don't, yeah, I think I used to be confused about this too.
I don't know that there is like the queen ants.
That is exactly what I'm saying.
This bizarre undulating creature.
The Metroid.
I'm imagining Metroid.
The game Metroid, that alien that's just float.
I assume anytime I've heard mother dough.
That's grown in power over the year
and lives in the San Francisco Bay.
Yeah.
Like a, what's the film, Tremors?
Tremors, yeah.
Is it a Tremors situation down below the,
I guess there's a lot of films where a character
is like hiding.
I feel like Godzilla starts that way sometimes.
Yes.
So that mother, yeah, that mother dough
is in the fisherman's wharf area.
And one day if displeased or if the mother dough hears
that a piece of her was not used in a batch of bread
to make a loaf, then she'll rise up
and like punch through the Golden Gate Bridge.
It looks like Clayface in my mind.
Batman animated series, specifically the Clayface
where it's like dripping.
Yeah.
Oh no, mother, mother rises.
Mother is angry.
And maybe somebody's happy, mother is like, finally.
Yes.
How else will they learn, mother?
Teach them.
Was Papa Steve married to the dough?
Papa Steve respected the dough on the official website.
The official, you can see there's like the lineage
on the Boudin website.
And it says about Papa Steve, he taught respect
for the mother dough and the Boudin family.
Here's another older picture of them.
I have that quote as well.
And then of course he is on every loaf.
There's an official seal with his picture.
Wow.
He's on every bag, every bag.
Right.
So we don't know his relationship with the dough.
You just know he respected it,
but we don't know behind closed doors.
We don't have a smoking gun document
showing the marriage attempt.
But I'd like to think that he made a little sourdough ring.
Yeah, oh my gosh.
For sure.
Yeah, yeah.
So I feel like sometimes with respect
comes a little bit of fear.
That's possible too.
He might've just reported back to,
he might've been just reporting back to the head honcho
like in private.
It was the emperor to Steve.
He was Vader.
Papa Steve was Vader and mother dough was the emperor.
I was saying.
It was really overseeing all of it.
So she was actually in control,
but she was more in the shadows.
Yes, yeah.
And then that newer mother dough that came,
that was just a clone.
That wasn't real.
That was a poor imitation.
That was a batch gone awry.
Yes, there were other attempts at it too
that were totally misshapen.
One of them was rye.
One of them, they got it wrong entirely.
They really messed up.
You gotta get seeds in there.
Yeah, there were no seeds.
Where did these seeds end up in here?
There were no seeds.
Sourdough?
So yeah, there was a clone of the mother dough,
but it was just, yeah, it was confusing,
but they figured it out.
There were books and.
I agree it's a confusing premise.
I actually did find it, again,
I'm sorry to talk about it,
but the Rosie O'Donnell tour,
I think is why I can visualize,
because they show here's a loaf
and a little plop comes out of it.
Right.
And that grows into the next one,
and then another plop,
and then just a little nickel-sized little piece
goes into the next batch.
It just seems weird,
because calling it the mother dough,
then it's like you don't know actually
that one of the pieces from the thing that came before
is actually going forward.
I know it grew out of it.
It's in there somewhere.
It's like putting blood in,
you know how you'd, I don't know,
you put blood in something too,
or like ashes in something to like.
Oh yeah.
The first.
It's like the multiple man.
It's like the X-Man.
It's like Jamie Madrox.
Madrox the multiple man, Jason?
Yeah, he can just keep making himself.
Like he just punches his hand,
and then there's another Jamie.
Yeah, but it comes from Jamie himself.
It doesn't come from one of his duplicates,
one of his multiple men.
Oh, that's true.
The duplicates can not make further duplicates.
That's right.
So if you imagine if he just keeps making duplicates,
he is the mother dough.
Mm-hmm.
Honestly, mother dough,
I really liked the idea of a mother dough
as like a character now.
So is this another episode now?
Separately the mother dough?
I think I may just go write a mother dough movie after this.
So maybe not even an episode.
Maybe this goes into my personal work.
Yeah.
Yeah, sure.
It's a good like, I mean, I don't know if it's horror
or action or sci-fi.
There's a lot of genres that it could take on.
Yeah.
Elements of all, I think.
Jason Sheridan stars.
Nice.
You want a CGI mother dough.
Am I, how do I feel about the mother dough?
I'm the baker.
Am I trying to stop it?
And I am, am I more like a reanimator type guy
who's really into it?
I think you're really into her, the mother dough.
I'm scared differential.
I think maybe you're carrying out murders
on behalf of the mother dough.
Oh, okay.
It's a turn.
Yeah.
It's like a horror movie.
It's a blown house.
Like blowing up restaurants of genres
that don't involve sourdough bread.
Just like, you know, like a Thai restaurant.
Look, you need a bread service, huh?
I'm giving you a good deal here.
What are you doing?
This bread lacks resistance.
Mother.
You're gonna rise us out of the simmer.
I've done your.
And then it's like, yeah, like a gnarly like 80s effect,
like a Clive Barker, like grotesque mother dough
that you report to.
So we sort of have this treatment
where it kind of rises up through sewers and pipes and.
Yes, that's good.
Like a blob sort of.
Yeah.
What part, one of the,
I think the first blob was filmed in Pennsylvania.
This will also be filmed in Pennsylvania.
Okay, great.
That theater is still there, the one with Marquis.
And we, the call time each day will be 1 p.m.
Yes.
So you will get to sleep in
because it's hard to get up early.
Can't go too late though.
I'll get too loopy.
1 p.m. to 5 p.m.
Oh, wonderful.
It'll take a year to make.
It's just in time for dinner.
Clint Eastwood directing?
Yeah.
These are Clint Eastwood hours.
One take.
Moving on.
Eastwood, Gervais, you know, the best.
Wait, does Gervais do limited takes?
They were kind of like,
let's get it done before footy matches, before soccer.
Is that in the afternoon?
I feel like it's more of a nine to five shoot.
It's also, this episode may come out
before a certain other episode,
but it's William Frawley.
Oh, right.
Hours too, where he's not working
if there's a Yankee game on.
No.
Gervais really the new Frawley.
Yeah, in a lot of ways.
Frawley really should have hosted some award shows
and roasted Hollywood.
You're all a bunch of bastards.
Everyone's quiet.
Go screw yourselves.
He's not even write jokes.
He's just cursing us out.
I'm going to take the piss out of you
and then I'm going to take a piss right here on stage.
Yeah, it falls over.
But first.
This concludes the Golden Globe Awards.
Curtin closes on his bald head.
Pretty baby.
By the light.
I'm so worried.
Please collect your awards at the side of the stage.
Shut up.
I got seven more songs.
So Papa Steve.
Papa Steve.
He loves the bread, you see.
Loves the bread.
He was called the sourdough king
by the late San Francisco Chronicle.
Yep, I have this.
Called his herb can.
Oh, of course.
Yeah.
It seems like maybe he was the first baker also
to have an open demonstration bakery.
Don't quote me on that,
but that seemed to maybe be the case.
Where, like in the Rosie O'Donnell, Colin Macri tour,
the windows are open so you can watch the process.
It's not behind closed doors.
That's part of it.
I love knowing how it gets made.
I get to watch those crazy shapes
and they cut the holes.
Seemingly, not so much the one here,
but in San Francisco or the bigger ones,
where they make like a crocodile.
They turn it into shapes.
They do like Mickey shapes, right?
Yeah, they do shapes here.
That's fun.
That's an underrated thing that more places should do.
Krispy Kreme over here in Burbank,
they have a, you can see into them making the donuts,
which is fun.
Excuse me, they have a conveyor belt.
That's all fun.
It's a glaze.
Yeah, you see the glaze, you see all of it.
And that's a whole, like while you're waiting in line,
you get to see a little demonstration.
And I feel like that's a real underrated.
You're smiling just thinking about it.
Is that right? I got a story about it.
Okay. Whoa.
So, and where I grew up, there was a Krispy Kreme
and me and my high school friends would go there sometime
because usually when you walked in,
if the conveyor belt was going, they'd hand you a donut.
You'd get a free donut if it was running.
And that happened to me here in Burbank once.
Yeah. That did happen.
And then I went back another time
the conveyor belt was going and I kind of stood there
and then I was standing there,
and the worker's like, can I help you?
I was like, oh, usually you get a free donut.
And they went, oh, that's for kids.
And I was like, wait, no, okay, maybe that changed.
But in the past, usually if the light is on,
if the odd light is on, which that's how you know
it's fresh, they're going through the glaze
and you walk in, they'll hand you one right after the glaze
and wax paper and everything.
But instead I walked in and was handed a brutal own.
The thing we do for children.
Yeah. But it was just kind of like, there's a nice,
I was like, oh, we just do that for kids.
Like there's a nice way to say that, but I was like, oh.
There was a deflating, that was more of a deflating way.
I don't want to deflate you further,
but is it possible that the first time
you were mistaken for a child?
I know, cause I would have been like 17 or 18.
Like by that point.
Were you wearing a propeller beanie
and holding a paddle ball or anything?
Well, the California sun, you gotta keep out
and the traffic is bad, but you can't be on your phone.
So you gotta abuse yourself.
Or a jug head crown.
No, that's an older person wears a jug head crown.
I've been begging you to wear a jug head crown for years.
I mean, it's like a beanie.
It's like a hood, a knit cap kind of thing.
Yeah.
I guess it's not practical to actually wear it
like jug head wears it, which is tiny.
Like how does it hang on his head?
How is it connected?
It's gotta be like bobby pins.
Yeah.
But yeah.
Comic book physics where it's just drawn.
Yeah.
It just drawn on there.
They will, I will say about Krispy Kreme over here.
I have been in there before where they have
freeze set out for everybody.
Yeah.
Less than a year ago when we were in line,
there was just a little section and it was free
and everyone was just taking one
as they went through the line.
Exactly.
Yeah.
So I got one curmudgeonly baker.
I think you should go to Hollywood.
Probably up too early.
You know, that's my problem.
I'm about real early.
I'm a little grumpy.
You're not gonna find this attitude
at the 3pm bakery.
Right.
No, not at all.
Papa Jason's night bakery.
Adults get free donuts at Papa Jason's night bakery.
Sure.
We cannot give you a free loaf of bread.
Right.
Free donut.
So, did you get more about the open thing or no?
No, it's that.
Okay.
So demonstration bakery, I think.
Yeah, I got a fact.
I found if you go to the Facebook page
or the Boudin Bakery, which I did,
they have some little tidbits and here's a tidbit.
Papa Steve was asked to make sourdough
for a dinner of Cardinals and Archbishops
during the Pope's visit.
Pope John Paul II, his visit to San Francisco in 1987.
So how about that?
Papa Steve making sourdough for the Pope.
Was that his same tour where he played
the Universal slash Gibson amphitheater?
Oh, that's a good question.
That's his visit to City Walk.
Yeah, I think it might've been.
Come to California, hit the big landmarks.
Yeah, maybe.
87.
Did Papa Steve meet the Pope?
The ultimate Papa?
Papa John.
Yeah, I stay corrected.
It doesn't say there wasn't much further information
on the trivia section of the Boudin Bakery Facebook page,
but I'd like to assume he did.
But at least he met a Cardinal or two.
Well, so go on the, add that Facebook page too.
Hit them up on YouTube and Facebook, get those numbers.
Then they can have a fully committed social media manager
so we can get more trivia all the time
and do Papa Steve too.
And if you're in San Francisco,
go see the like big facility at Fisherman's Worth
because it's a beautiful facility with lots of food stuffs
and a little bit of, there's tours and info stuff
on a bigger scale.
Sea lions.
I mean, the sea lions are, that's just a bonus.
Now, something I was trying to figure out is,
is there a framed photo of Papa Steve in other Boudin,
in that bakery or in other,
because there is a Boudin chain that's elsewhere.
I believe there's one in Huntington Beach here in California.
I think there's a lot of those.
And some of them seem to have a Papa Steve photo,
but it's not this Papa Steve photo.
In fact, he looks a little more cross
and kind of in work mode.
It's not as-
This black and white one?
That seems familiar.
Yes, the other ones I've seen are black and white.
All the photos of him in all the stuff I was looking at,
he does seem a little more stern.
He definitely, like, he seems so like jovial and kindly
in the picture at California Adventure.
He's the sweetest man you've ever seen.
Right, but maybe he was a tyrant.
Could have been.
A bread tyrant.
Why do you dispute that?
I think he was serious about his craft.
All right.
This might be a good time to say,
I did find video footage of Papa Steve.
Oh, great.
And I think it more supports him being a very kind man.
Great.
He seems very sweet.
The whole interview is very heartwarming.
It again, you watch him,
they think they say at the top of the news report,
this is a fisherman's wharf.
Not many people get to see,
but it's what Papa Steve sees every day
because he had to wake up so early.
And there's some fun stuff.
You watch him crack a loaf over his knee
to show the proper degree of hardness
it's supposed to have.
A lot of it, it's all very nice.
It's a good little profile
and I would have just played it all
except some of it's a little quiet,
but I wanted to put this one part
that'll give you his vibe,
but also show you,
it's a little piece of sourdough history.
I certainly didn't know.
So this is from like San Francisco news
in the 80s sometime.
And check it out.
Here Gerardo baked,
but also delivered the warm bread door to door
to people's homes.
You just pick up the loaf like this.
And they always had a nail sticking out from the wall.
You know?
And that's it.
So what we're saying here
is that he delivered sourdough bread
to San Francisco residents,
much like a milkman.
And the way that the deliveries happened
were that people put a nail on their front door
and you would just kind of like slam the bread
against the nail and it would stick.
So then you'd come home
or go outside for the morning
and on the wall
would as appropriately like a framed photo,
the main way that we know him now,
your bread is up on the wall.
Wow.
Waiting for you.
That's incredible.
So you would open your door in the morning,
you get the newspaper,
you get a fresh bottle of milk
and bread on your door.
I mean.
Lean out to that door frame.
And if, okay, San Francisco famously
prone to have earthquakes,
a lot of them up there
and I don't think this is still the case,
but the advice for a long time
has been wait under that door frame.
Like that'll protect you during the earthquake.
So if, you know, in 89,
there's a massive earthquake,
but like what are we gonna do?
We might be here for days without food.
Wait a minute.
Papa Steve has already been here
at four in the morning
and right here on the only thing intact,
the door frame is a piece of sourdough
and this will sustain us until the power.
Now, the structure of that sourdough
probably would, in addition to nourishing,
you would probably help reinforce the door frame
because I think the door frame
has been debunked as a system now.
Yeah, I think that's not correct.
Yeah. Right.
That is not correct.
But if you could cover the door frame
in a firm sourdough casing.
With the right resistance.
Right. Yes.
And you, because, oh wait, no,
I was gonna start to talk about that triangle.
That's debunked too.
I think the triangle's been debunked as well.
It's basically just go under a table.
Go under a table or if you're in bed,
just don't move, just stay in bed.
But if you have a big enough table-sized loaf,
that would be interesting.
You just hide under that.
So the safest place to be in an earthquake,
especially in San Francisco,
is at the Boudin Bakery.
As they start flying,
build a little fort for yourself
and hide under it.
And then, club sandwiches, chocolate croissants.
And then when it's all over, yeah,
then you've got a feast.
Yeah.
Just jamming that bread against the door.
I love that. So delightful.
And so what do you guys,
now you've seen him in motion,
you've heard him talk.
Yeah, he does seem very kindly.
That's great.
I'm glad he's like Santa Claus
because that's what he seems like.
Yeah. Absolutely.
But maybe he knew the camera's on.
Maybe he's really a tyrant.
We don't know.
He's like come close to like breaking doors down
by how hard he slammed those loafs.
Yeah.
We saw it hard too.
Do you think he ever knocked on a door with a force?
Maybe.
It's possible.
Yeah.
Is there, yeah, what?
Also, cleanliness.
Like we've come a long way on like
how we would treat food and stuff.
But like, I feel like most of us
wouldn't want to eat bread after,
well, not you, but if a bread touched a door,
I would go, I don't want to eat that.
But you're fine if the bread touched a door.
That's strange.
I would just try to keep my door clean.
So you've now got to extra scrub your door frame.
Yeah.
I, San Francisco is a little more hum,
I would be a little more,
in Los Angeles, it's so much dirt everywhere, you know.
Sometimes ash, if,
sometimes ash just falls from the sky here
if something's on fire.
True.
And in the Valley, it's just,
I feel like there's always just a fine layer of dirt
on your car unless you really get it washed a lot.
So how does this affect putting a loaf on your door?
I'm a little more hesitant of like current state doors
for this location.
But San Francisco, you feel better about it?
San Francisco, more of a humid climate I associated with.
So I feel like getting a little more of a washing
those doors.
Which they say is gonna be, wait a minute.
So you're, wait, you're okay with,
it's getting a washing.
And by that you mean the salt air in the sky
is keeping your door clean.
It's getting a constant washing.
It's windy.
Which is the drying process.
Yeah.
So you're fine with,
so I,
There's loaves on the door.
They're being cleaned 24 seven.
A season two.
Oh man.
I was gonna say, I was on my way to saying,
I think that is the idea with the mother dough
is that it does come from,
there's something in the air in San Francisco
is kind of the legend.
That's what they say.
It is that saltiness and that humidity that makes it,
it's why the only the,
if it can't be made in San Francisco,
it has to have a little of that mother dough
cause that's the little salty, humid spice.
Like on Jason's door.
Like on my delicious door.
Clean, clean door.
I don't wanna give out where you live.
Okay.
We really should so people can nail bread to the door.
Please don't do that.
Ha.
You get an extra long nail so that every day,
like 30 loaves.
Okay.
Remember dog studios.
Yeah.
A Patreon tier.
Where? Sunset Boulevard.
A Patreon tier where we give you Jason's address
and you're allowed to nail bread to his door
every morning if possible.
If you're in the area.
You get to.
Yeah.
You're paying us more for the privilege
of delivering Jason's bread every day.
Of doxing me with bread.
I don't know.
Doxing always is a bad connotation.
This is a good one.
Can you imagine?
Can you get something out of it?
All the different types of bread you'd have in the morning
nailed to the door.
Oh, but then you run into the tyranny of choice
and we all hate that, don't we folks?
You're eating 10 loaves of bread every morning.
So the company Back in Family Hands.
Yes.
Was not always, was sold in 19, in the mid 90s.
I believe 93.
Yeah.
They didn't sell to craft.
Right.
There was talk of it and they did not.
And in fact, a bunch of the local bread makers,
Boudin, Parisian, Colombo and Toscana
is all joined together to form
the San Francisco French Bread Company.
In a very, as I learned in a very mundane video I watched,
that was kind of like when the light bulb and the fish
merge into Mr. Sparkle.
Because this and this are now this.
Right.
Bum, bum.
But I love, oh 80s dull corporate videos I'll watch all day.
So it did teach me a little lesson.
The San Francisco French Bread Company was like,
you know, let's not go corporate, let's all band together.
We've all been competitors, but if we share resources
and there's strength in all of it.
But I think though at the end of the day,
Boudin won out and just is the winner.
Right.
So they were all the rest, we're all suckers.
I believe they were all Boudin breads,
the rebrand, eventually rebranded.
It just became the uniform.
Bun off briefly owned by the people who owned Hostess
and Wonder Bread who collapsed a few years ago.
And then the brands eventually bought by other companies
and brought back.
But then the company, the family rebought Boudin
in the early 2000s.
So it's back, so it is in Gerardo.
It is in Gerardo.
Steven, the son, I believe involved,
Louis, the grandson, still involved, still with us.
Well, somebody in this family is who posted
that video clip that I want.
They've posted videos about the family history
and the history of Sourdough.
So another YouTube channel you should follow.
Yeah. Like Gerardo, get those numbers up.
Get the numbers up. Yeah, please.
Did we find the imposter?
What?
Did we find the man who is calling himself Papa Steve?
Oh, and I think maybe, what are you talking about though?
There's a different, there's a company that makes a product
called Papa Steve's No Junk Raw Protein Bars.
I did find those, yeah.
Steve Dybold, some Stanford University grad.
That's too close.
That's too close to San Francisco.
And he is calling his product Papa Steve's.
Tsk, tsk, tsk, I say.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't care for this at all.
Bad blood, bad man.
Bad people.
If this were some sort of saga,
he would inhabit the sector keeper's body
and we'd fight him.
This would be a very good,
this is who would inhabit the sourdough keeper.
Yeah.
Unless the sourdough keeper
wanna appear to us now?
Silence, crickets, sourdough keeper?
All right, just checking.
Seems not to be here.
Seeing if the skies were open.
Yeah.
So I don't care, I don't care for it.
I think we should all boycott Papa Steve's
no junk raw protein bars.
You know, I will not specifically go to a website
to order these protein bars.
Yeah, do not do that.
I wasn't, I'll be honest,
I wasn't buying them before
and I will continue not to buy them.
This is like, you know, we have some sponsors
and we read some ads on the main feed,
but only on the Patreon do we have anti-sponsors.
That's right.
I've seen these in the world.
I have seen these.
I don't know about.
Well, next time spit on them.
One time purchase.
Okay.
Are you looking through the?
Well, I want to see how much, how many bars,
because it's saying a box is like 30 something bucks.
And I'm like, for 10 bars?
That's insane.
This is some ballast point bullshit.
This is worse than ballo.
I don't even want to denigrate ballast point.
They're on the up and they're coming around.
They're on the rebound.
They're on the, why are they on the rebound?
Well, they got sold to a different brewer
since we've done that episode.
They got sold.
They were?
From the, to a brewery in the Midwest,
a brewery company bought them.
Oh.
That giant beverage conglomerate spun it off.
Oh, okay.
So you're more okay with them.
I think they're kind of, you know,
getting their sea legs again, it seems like.
But price point is what you're watching.
Well, they might be watching it too, you know?
Sure.
After the, in the fallout of the episode.
After the fallout of, well, clearly they,
it seems like they were losing money
or like they tried to expand to,
I mean, all this stuff that happens with businesses.
Much like Boudin seemed like they expanded into Illinois
with their restaurants.
My hometown.
Which I think closed.
So, I mean, it's a real gamble.
Don't go to Illinois.
It's the fatal mistake any business can make.
Yeah, so, all right, back in the family.
As we said, he liked to,
he rose at 3.30 every morning.
Oh, can you imagine, Jason?
I mean, much respect.
Much respect to an early riser king, you know?
All right.
I mean, I find that when I hear about like,
executives or whatever,
Mark Wahlberg getting up at three in the morning every day,
I'm like, all right, I don't know, man.
But for Baker, that's kind of the life, you know?
It's the life you choose, yes.
He would like go inspect the operations
and talk to the staff,
and then we'd walk around Spreckel's Lake
in Golden Gate Park.
So one unfortunate day, that is where he collapsed
and subsequently passed away.
But he died doing what he loved,
being up early, saying hi to the family,
and taking a nice little stroll,
being part of the vibrant city of San Francisco.
It's at least nice that he passed away
in a place that was special to him.
Chairman Emeritus, even after the sale,
his title was Chairman Emeritus.
So he was still involved, and yeah, up to his death,
was checking out the Mother Doe.
Paying respects.
And if you wanna pay respects,
he's buried at Holy Cross Catholic Cemetery,
Colma, San Mateo County in California, USA.
This is public information,
I'm not digging this up somewhere.
It's on Findagrave.
Findagrave.com.
Which is, yeah, I forgot that exists,
and then, oh good, Findagrave.com.
And you can find a lot of, I mean,
of course, like Joey, is it Johnny Ramone?
Johnny Ramone is in Hollywood Forever Cemetery.
They're both dead.
Yeah, but one of them has like a statue kind of grave.
Well, find your favorite person's grave, I guess.
It's quite a bit in Hollywood.
This is what Jason is advocating.
I'm saying, like, there's quite a bit in Hollywood.
You can find a lot of graves.
Grave doxing.
Jim Morrison is in Paris.
Jason is grave doxing.
That's the one in Paris that has all this stuff.
Yeah, so I don't have anything else about publicity.
I do have a little bit of a side note.
I signed up for the Boudin Rewards Club as well.
Oh, smart, you're getting out of that.
Well, you get one free monthly bread reward.
Jason.
Do they send it to you, but you gotta be here.
You gotta go to the store.
There's one in Irvine, though.
Okay. That's not too far.
Not too bad.
Huntington, I think, I think is a closer one.
Oh, is there?
If that's close, I see now.
I'm not sure if that's a head or tails.
So yeah, I'm a Boudin loyalty member now.
And I think it's just, you have to make a purchase
and then you get like a free loaf of sourdough.
Oh, that's great.
So.
You're saving 89 cents.
Yeah.
Can you think about it?
You make sense to go up to Huntington.
Sure.
Or where is Huntington? Down?
Down.
To drive all the way, to burn the guest money,
to go to Huntington Beach.
Take a bus.
Buy something and then get free.
Bottle of water, maybe?
You're keeping it cheap.
Water and bread.
And you're purchase.
Great.
Water and bread.
Christ meal.
Once a month, Jason takes a bus down to Huntington
and he gets a bottle of water.
It's a three hour bus.
And a loaf of sourdough.
Cause that's how far it is from his house, which is at.
Okay.
All right.
Findahouse.com.
Again.
Looking for an address for Everdog Studios,
as I believe is on their website.
Don't nail bread to their door though.
Just leave bread in a wrapper that says to Jason.
Oh, and Sunset Boulevard.
But really, I mean, it's nice that we know
about his life story now,
but really how he'll live on forever
is in this part of the park.
And I think it, I'm just trying to analyze why we're so,
became so enamored with him.
And I think there is some, I mean, he's, he seems so sweet.
He just seems like pure love from that picture
that he's holding bread and he's in front
of a bunch of other bread.
And I was just imagining a greater scenario.
Like it made me picture that he lives in like a bread cottage.
Yeah.
And if you went to visit him, he'd offer you
cocoa boiled from bread served to you in a bread mug.
Yes. And he writes with a piece of bread.
He like dips the bread in some bread ink,
like liquid bread ink.
Like squeezed at liquid.
Yeah. Everything he does is bread
and he lives in a bread village.
And yeah, I think that's right.
He has a bread wife.
He has a wife.
I think Papa Steve on it makes him sound
like more of a character as well.
If it was like, just said Steven.
Yeah. Yeah.
It would be like, oh, okay.
Like we would take a picture with it,
but I don't think Papa Steven evokes something, you know.
Yeah. Well, it's like Papa Smurf.
Like Papa Smurf, yes.
And by that, if you're extending out from there,
if he ever wanted to swear,
he said the word Steve instead.
Steve.
That's Steven cat.
Steven, mother Steaver.
Stay out of my Steven store, you Steve head.
Yes. Yes.
He follows Papa Smurf.
He follows Papa Smurf logic.
So yeah, I think all of that combined is why.
It's Steve.
Even Papa Steven wouldn't be this Steve.
Papa Steven is such a name of a guy.
I'm Steve.
Papa Steven is like, I don't know.
It seems somewhat lascivious to me.
I immediately, I mean, I'm always thinking of Steven Tyler,
but it makes me think of Steven Tyler for some reason.
When I said Steven, I didn't think of Steven Tyler,
but when you said Papa Steven,
I thought of Steven Tyler.
I'm thinking Steven Van Zandt.
Little, well, he's a little Steven.
Oh yeah.
Little Steven also evokes something.
Papa, Papa Steven would have hierarchy on little Steven.
Certainly.
Yes. Yes.
Little Steven, yeah, he ranks lower because of the name.
Papa Steven lives in the house.
Little Steven, of course, in the underground garage.
Yes.
Papa Steve wakes up early.
Little Steven stays at, oh no.
Yeah.
No, I'm not going to bed till the sun's coming up.
He's like, hey, he was a gangster in Norway.
He's got a-
Well, sometimes it's always, the sun's always up there.
So yeah, I hope, look, I hope this doesn't go away.
I'm worried that like maybe Marvel will like start to
go over here in the park.
You would be mad if there was more Marvel and less and not-
Well, no, I'm a big Marvel fan.
I'm not going to be mad.
I'm just hoping that all of Hollywood land area
goes away before this area goes away.
I would rather than move that way.
I would rather, yeah.
Yeah, totally.
That's what I'm-
Because I think you lose a little bit of fun origin now,
like original California adventure with this part.
This part, I think like still works in California adventure.
There'd be no reason to do it.
I think you could, I think it can be one of the last to go,
but I think if we're getting rides instead of Wharf,
I think Wharf's got to go.
I think it's too profitable.
I think they make too much money.
I think people do-
It's ultimately kind of the big,
like it's sort of the food court essentially.
Yeah.
California adventure.
So obviously like they probably are going to keep it there
because it's people need to eat,
but it could be like,
it could be whatever a different Marvel food court,
which would seem like a bummer.
Any re-theming to IP food cart, who, what's the point?
Not for that.
If you want to put the X-Men's mansion here,
I'm not going to fight you.
Do I want a nod to Papa Steve in the X-Men's mansion?
Yes.
Yeah.
Just a little something.
Well, now what they have built in is that anything that goes
can just end up in the, the Tyvon collection.
That's true.
Oh wow.
Tyvon head.
The mother dough.
Honestly, I might like that more.
If the bakery had to go and Papa Steve was hanging up
in the line for Guardians.
Oh man, that would be great.
Or just like a little like kind of like kitty,
like in the corner, a little off center,
like, or in the basement,
like kind of stacked up on top of something.
Yeah.
Man, that I love that.
I think they should just, yeah,
take it off the wall in the bakery and put it in there now.
It'll get more people talking.
Yeah.
You'll notice it more.
Cause you could put, I mean,
you could put it in the line too,
where like the, the old Matterhorn Yeti is,
or snowman, whatever.
And then the 20,000 leagues octopus.
And then there's Papa Steve.
Yeah.
And then like, mom, who's that guy?
Why that, this is a nod in this ride
to a famous San Francisco Baker,
Steven Giroudo.
Yeah.
Oh wow.
Stefano Giroudo.
Sorry, sorry son.
You got it wrong.
Colloquially Steve, Papa Steve.
But as we know him, Papa Steve.
Wow.
Well, his legend will live on.
I'm, I'm, I'm sure of that.
They seriously, now I would,
if they ever did take down the bakery,
if they don't put them in the Guardians,
now I will be mad.
That is my.
Have they actually put anything new on Guardian?
I don't think they have.
They think they could be doing a lot more.
They could be doing a lot more.
Cause they were, yeah,
acting like they were going to cycle stuff in and out.
I always say that with everything.
There should really be a face of Khalifa,
the Whoopi Goldberg character.
Yes.
Golden dreams.
See, but I, yeah, I think it gets complicated
when it's a person, a public figure, a person.
Yeah.
The resemblance of a person.
Mike at Dicey.
Yeah.
In what regard?
That they have to ask Whoopi?
Yeah, probably.
She loves appearing in theme park attractions.
That's true.
So gladly they'll, they'll move her over.
No problem.
Yeah.
I agree with that.
They should put some Bugsland stuff in the queue too.
Sure.
Why not?
Yep.
Strawberry.
Big strawberry.
Yeah.
Strawberry for Guardians.
Great.
Well, until he ascends to his throne
in the Typhoon collection,
Papa Steve resides in the booting bacon.
And go, you know, go check him out.
Go take a picture with him.
Take a picture.
Send to us.
Yeah.
We want to see people enjoying the spirit of good food,
good bread, good people.
Yeah, please.
And then I will post the photo of Jason with Papa Steve
and see if I have any more.
You gotta try to find as many as you can.
Yeah.
I mean, I don't know if we did 10,
but I think we did at least five.
Yeah.
But I, on my phone, I only have one.
I must have.
I'll look too.
Yeah.
So yeah.
So for bonus content of Jason posing
with a framed photo of an old man,
follow us on Twitter, Instagram, and Facebook.
They know what they're getting into.
They know if they're here already.
Yeah.
Hey, and keep subscribing to the second gate
right here as you already are.
And I'll leave you with another nice quote
from old Papa Steve.
This is what he said to the guy who took the reins from him.
He said, don't worry about the ups and downs of the business,
but if you take care of the bread and the mother dough,
they will take care of you.
Nice.
Carry that with you.
Yeah.
The mother dough will take care of you.
Mother dough is, may the mother dough be your God.
All hail mother dough.
Kill for mother dough.