Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast may contain shadow play
and songs that have not aged well.
It may be low capacity, but it's high adventure.
From Wreck-It Ralph 2, Danny Fernandez helps the Good Boys become Lost Boys.
It's Peter Pan's flight on podcast.
The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the theme park podcast hosted by three boys who would not
make good members of Peter Pan's gang because they're deathly afraid of getting lost.
My name is Mike Carlson, joining me as always, Jason Sheridan.
Yeah, I like to usually know my whereabouts.
I told you once that I usually know where the ocean and the mountain is, wherever I am.
Is that really a thing?
Well, that's how I learned how to navigate LA, of like, the mountains are that way.
Okay, ocean is that way, downtown is that way.
Do you have a sense, like, if I placed you anywhere in Los Angeles, you just have a sense of where it is?
Or do you always just check your phone?
Yeah, I kind of have a sense.
Do you?
That's Scott Gertner.
Hi.
Do you like, there's places though where you can't see an ocean or a mountain, many places.
No, I can't, just more of a general set, not like, like special forces, I think you're supposed to like know when you're in a room, you're supposed to have an internal compass to know which way is stuff.
As do you if you're trying a new donut place and you're not sure where it is on a map.
It's helpful to get, yeah, be able to get back there by sense memory.
Well, let's bring our guest in to see if she knows where a nearby mountain or ocean is.
She's an actress, she's a writer, a podcaster, you know her from her podcast Nerdificent.
Ladies and gentlemen, it's Dani Fernandez.
Yay.
I actually don't have great sense, but I feel like I would know where I am in this town.
Yeah.
Like if you drop me off at like Sunset in Gower, I would be like, oh, this is Sunset in Gower.
You're in Gower Gulch, which amazingly has not come up on this show despite being a themed environment.
Yeah. So we talk a lot about like malls and themed stuff and that's like one of the prime themed malls.
Oh yeah, it's a little old west town is what it is.
Yeah, there's a Denny's in the parking lot.
Yes. Oh my gosh.
It's not the best Denny's I've ever been to.
No, not the best toros.
But always Hoppin.
Yes, Hoppin I will give it.
Yeah.
Do y'all talk about the Burbank Mall then?
The Burbank Town Center.
It's certainly come up.
It's come up.
Do you have particular thoughts and observations?
Well, I think that there's like a top floor that's nothing now.
I find that so fascinating.
Yeah.
I don't think anyone goes up there.
You mean the entire top floor?
Yeah.
Well, there's the movie theater.
That must be why.
The Burbank area has three AMCs and there's two of them are AMC 6 and AMC 8.
It is impossible to remember which one is where.
I think it's eight.
Oddly, the bigger one is in the mall.
Eight.
Well, there's eight, six.
Six and 16.
And I'm not kidding you, listener.
They're all within walking distance.
They are all within walking distance.
And the emptiness I think comes from the fact that the food court moved from the third floor to the first floor.
A phenomenon I've never seen at any other shopping mall.
We have not done a ton of deep dive Burbank mall yet.
We will get there.
OK.
But Burbank mall, it's going away a little bit, but Burbank mall has some of the best fake stores I've ever seen.
Like a store that just sells fake plants and like a big glass tiger.
And you're like, and there's a couple of those at a certain point, a couple of different stores that you could buy a fake plant and a big glass tiger.
I'll see some of those on Wilshire.
I'm like, how do you have this prime real estate and like you're closed most of the time?
Yes.
And like when you open, you're just selling like three chandeliers.
Like I don't want to understand.
Yeah, I that is one of the things if I was a ball, if I was like a Larry David type, I would wander in and go, how do you make money?
Explain it to me.
Can I see a business plan?
Can I see how much a day you make?
Like there's a video game store in the Burbank mall.
It's not GameStop.
It looks like a fake.
No, it's true.
It's a knockoff GameStop.
Yeah. And it looks all like the logo looks cheap inside.
They have very little stock of anything.
And it's kind of dark in there.
It's very dark in there.
It's a front.
That's what I'm getting at.
There's a lot.
There's it's a real mystery place because like there's a store that has like a lot of imported stuff, a lot of Pocky and stuff like Totoro's.
And then there is a second store that has Pocky and Totoro's.
It's like, well, now, wait a minute.
Hold on.
This mall isn't that big that there are two of these.
It's a fascinating mall.
It's one of the most interesting malls, this Burbank mall specifically.
I don't just.
Well, I think another reason why it's so ghostly and same with because I went to high school in Dallas and like some of our malls are shutting down there and like is because of Amazon.
I hope.
I think or Highland.
OK.
North Park's the super fancy one.
I spent a lot of time there on a Dallas trip.
I loved it.
I'm so sorry to alert you of this.
One of those is shutting down.
But I think it's because of Amazon.
Because everyone's like online shopping and stuff, which it's funny to me whenever something that started online actually becomes a store, though.
Like so in the Burbank mall, they have Fashion Nova and Fashion Nova was like huge because Cardi B's always wearing it and stuff.
And they actually got so big that they opened an actual store.
So it's one of the few like physical locations.
I have seen that.
What's a fashion?
What is a fashion?
It's like Forever 21, but like slightly sluttier and more just like you clearly want to look like you're in a music video.
I shop there a lot.
Sure.
Not kidding.
I haven't.
Do they have men's clothes at Fashion Nova?
No, they have a little bit.
OK, because I recently started shopping at Forever 21.
Yeah, really?
Because they have.
Yeah, they have a lot of it's not it's nothing crazy.
It's you know, I don't think I knew they had male clothing.
Yeah.
I mean, I have a sweatshirt with roses on it.
I got from there.
So I'm you know, I'm doing it now.
Believe me when I say I'm not trying to segue and get us back to the topic.
But Forever 21 is a perfect.
Yeah, it is.
Yeah.
For never growing up.
Yeah, you're right.
Forever 12.
That's where the Lost Boys would show.
That's where you buy like raccoon suits.
That has to be Peter Pan.
In my mind, he hasn't hit puberty yet.
Right?
Yeah, that's a good question.
I feel like he's starting it because maybe a little late comer.
I think he's like a he's tall.
He's at the growth spurt, but not the rest of the puberty.
Maybe he's at like Wendy because like Wendy's right on the line.
Uh huh.
They're both.
They both are.
Yeah.
So it's so changes are happening, but all of the changes aren't happening.
Maybe.
Well, they were happening and now I think they're frozen for him.
Yeah.
Can you believe that you're just in puberty forever?
Yeah, I really hadn't thought about the nightmare that that is for Peter, but he's like an eighth
grader with an army of fifth graders all in like, yeah, fast fashion animal skins where
it's like fashion Nova style.
Fashion Nova.
Yeah, it doesn't matter.
It didn't cost that many Neverland bucks.
If this gets messed up in one of the endless pirate fights you have to that is your life.
It's okay.
And we all know how when you graduate school, if you go to middle school and then go back
to your elementary school or your or your you get to college and go back to high school,
everyone worships you and follows you around.
It's not like people think that's weird and you should get out of the school as soon as
you've arrived.
For sure.
Peter would have an army of little ones at his disposal.
Yeah, it's a all of these things really take the fun out of Peter Pan.
This is really like thinking about it at all.
Yeah, analyzing it for a second.
Like that's a real bummer, isn't it?
Well, you know, I mean, what takes the fun out of Peter Pan is watching it.
Like, I think we all have to hold on to memories of what it is and not actually view the film
because I did.
I know Jason did and I did and prepare you inspire me to do it today as well.
And I think it is a film best unwatched.
It's problematic.
Yeah.
The ride is the perfect amount of Peter Pan.
Like there is a reason this ride is like incredibly popular, like shot lines like our pushing
our weight line sometimes.
It doesn't have a fast.
It's like the one of the ones that doesn't have a fast pass, right?
Right.
So it's like you have to if you love this ride, you have to stick it out.
And like it's wild because in fantasy land, which is largely for, you know, I think of like the kiddie ride,
the rides that kids can actually go on because like my niece and nephew can't go on Space Mountain yet.
It's insane that it's an hour wait always.
I haven't said this a lot on the show, but like if you're getting to one of the Magic Kingdom style parks
at opening or staying until closing, this is, I think, the ride more so than like a Space Mountain.
Oh, totally.
Like a Space Mountain, like you can give it a couple hours and it'll still kind of have a manageable wait.
But this the wait gets so quick, so fast.
And it's a line that gives you almost nothing.
You are just back and forth and back and forth.
That is very old school line.
I know in Florida, there's more.
There's a room that you go in and there's, you know, you do a little interactive displays with shadows.
Florida's queue watching the video of the current queue in Florida is shocking because it's like a full nursery with like shadows and pixie dust.
And like it seems fun.
Yeah. But this one, this is, you know, obviously this is an opening day of Traxxas in 1955 and it's a very 1955 style line.
It is they had not come up with any ideas of how to make a line.
It's the Matterhorn line.
They're the same.
Yeah, that is also very boring.
There is not much going on there.
It's just open.
There's nothing to do.
You go one way and you go the other way and you hear a type of music that isn't, it's not specifically annoying, but I would never choose to put on Swiss Alp music.
Which serious will I put on today?
Sounds of the Alps.
Is there any like updated Swiss Alps music like a Diplo produced Swiss Alps?
There's got to be.
Is there a Grammy category that I'm not aware of?
Right.
There's a thriving scene.
Because you look like real dumb if there is now.
Like I would never listen to Swiss Alps music, but then the kids will be like, you know, there's a, I was going to say dead mouse, which just made me look dumb.
Wow.
There's a newer, there's got to be a newer DJ.
If you're trying to stay forever 21, you got to update the references.
I blew this whole fell apart for me.
Have you guys heard that rave?
The Haunted Mansion one, but it's like rave style.
No.
Oh my gosh.
I have it.
I want to.
What is the artist of this?
I'll have to find it, but it would be great if they did all of the, all of the Disney rides as opposed to just.
We've talked about this album called Deconstructed.
Yes.
That is all kind of electro remixes of Disney songs.
What else is on there?
Winnie the Pooh.
Like Winnie the Pooh.
Oh, that sounds like fun.
Yeah.
There's a net Funicello song, Pineapple Princess.
It's an old Sherman Brothers song and they've like remixed the hell out of it.
And it's so unpleasant.
The original was like a fun, a fun ukulele song.
And now it's just this unlistening club club mix.
Strange.
And I don't think I'm being old man about it.
It really is unpleasant.
I'll just find it while we're talking.
I think they had to change the name.
It can't be like Haunted Mansion.
So I don't even know what it is in my Spotify.
It's probably like Spooky House.
Right.
We didn't get sued.
Cobweb place.
I mean, this, this movie has some recognizable song.
Oh yeah, for sure.
And then there is a song when I was watching it, I went like, you know, like the one I think you can least sketch.
Like this can't be what this is.
And then it was, it was a long song called What Does That Have To Do with I Think You Should Leave?
I was just watching like this song start and I went, this can't be what this is.
It's just a, it's a, I guess you probably shouldn't even say the name of the song at this point.
I wouldn't mind not saying.
Yeah, it's a, it's you forget all of the weird portrayals of Native Americans.
Essentially is what you're saying.
For Native Neverland.
Even though.
No, wait, is that the song that's in there?
That is not in the ride.
It's not in the ride.
Oh, you mean in the movie.
Rewatching the movie, going to Disney Plus and watching this.
And I don't know, maybe there was like one of those like a product of its time warnings.
And I was looking away, but I was shocked by this one.
There is a, there is a warning that comes up when you press play.
But the warning, they do not do the bizarre phrase they've done contains outdated cultural depictions,
which is on a lot of movies.
There is only contains tobacco depictions.
Oh, really?
Not the other?
And they don't, but these things are happening in the same scene.
So it's almost like they got distracted.
Like, okay, this is a tobacco scene.
And they just, and they forgot.
I was going to say, did somebody forget?
It's not like there's much of an effort to add a couple words.
Also, do they have that in The Great Mouse Detective?
Because like he's smoking a pipe and stuff, right?
Like, is there, you're not supposed to be smoking at all?
Yeah, probably.
That's interesting.
Yeah, I would assume that would be a warning.
You guys, I'm here for the deep dives.
Yeah, sure.
Bed knobs and broomsticks, actually.
They're smoking constantly in bed knobs and broomsticks.
Those knobs are bongs.
The children are ripping bong heads in bed knobs and broomsticks.
Are you a big Disney head in that case?
Yes, grew up just like obsessed with Disney.
In fact, my brothers actually hid the Lion King VHS from me because I played it too much.
They like hid it under the couch.
You were going to like destroy it?
Was that the fear?
Like you were going to, like it was going to turn to dust?
They were annoyed.
Oh, they didn't want to see it anymore.
Oh, okay.
I played it way too much.
We were one of those, I don't know if you all did this, but like with our VHSs, if we like something,
we just played it again and again and again.
That's how I know the mask, like word for word.
Jim Carrey's the mask.
You know, and it was like whatever my parents gave us.
So it's like, that's kind of what you latch onto.
It doesn't even matter if it's good, although I think that movie is.
Sure.
The repetition and that these kids, the kids now don't have to wait for the tape to be rewound.
Yeah.
They can just scroll immediately back.
The hassle that it was to rewatch a favorite scene.
You had to wait our entire, what, two and a half minutes.
Yeah.
Boy, our childhoods were rough.
Was Lion King your favorite of all of them?
Yeah, but then I don't know, it's kind of like changed.
So I really, really, well, I'm always a big fan of a goofy movie.
Like that was so, and now it's kind of had a resurgence, but for the longest time people would be like, what?
Is it like an extremely goofy movie?
I'm like, no, it's not the same.
Listen, there's like, you have to listen to the power line songs.
And I was just like such a big fan of a goofy movie.
And now like Target realized that and like capitalize on the nostalgia.
And now you can get like power line there, which is chill.
What happened there?
Why does, why was that like the cult Disney movie?
And then they figured it out.
Why was there this syndrome?
And how, like, because it very much felt like no one else was watching it.
But there was only one person in every school who was watching it.
And now everybody found each other in LA.
Well, they've all gone into the arts.
Every single one of them is.
Well, I think that's also because it's not like traditional Disney movies have like a princess or a, you know what I mean?
It's like some type of magical fantasy.
And this was like just a teen kid that hated his dad.
If you look back at it, when I watch it, you're like, oh my God, you're such an ass to your dad.
Like he just wants to spend time with you.
Yes, I still love Max.
But yeah, and I think Goofy is kind of like as much as he's iconic, he's kind of like one of the side people as opposed to like Mickey and Minnie and Duck.
Like, yeah, I think of Goofy as like no one's fave.
I don't know. I'm sorry.
It's definitely someone's fave.
It's a kid. He was my fave for sure.
But he's also like a sort of a side character in that movie.
Oh, totally.
I was just calling Goofy like literally, but he's just like a dopey like dad.
He's just trying. He's there to embarrass his son.
The movie is really I think it also hit for a lot of us at the same time when Max was we're talking about puberty.
It's like a puberty movie, too.
Yeah.
It's like that's also I think a lot of us saw it during that point and was like relatable.
And a reverse of that dynamic that starts off Peter Pan because Mr. Darling hates his fucking kids.
That was another thing watching this where I was like, wow, this guy really hates his kids.
Like between this and Mary Poppins, like British fiction, like British young people's fiction is just filled with like, you know, OK, so first off, your dad hates you, obviously.
Yeah, I think that was around.
But really normal to back then to kind of like just the dad is like allowed to be like that because he makes all the money and just like shoving the kids off.
Right. Yeah.
Yeah. Dads liking their children was new past the 30s and in America.
British dads, I think, didn't start liking their kids still maybe this century.
It was like 2003 or so.
There was an awakening.
Yeah. Yeah. Among all British.
I wanted to say I found the thing.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, that's it.
Isn't that dope?
That is good.
That's fun.
It like really breaks down though.
It gets. Oh yeah.
The bells come in.
Yeah, that's good.
Does it like have a dubstep middle maybe?
Oh yeah.
Just wait.
It's about to kick into stuff, man.
Oh man.
I'm ready to go.
I'm ready to party.
One, two, three, one.
It like gears up even more.
OK.
So anyways.
Who's the artist there?
OK, so it is Haunted Mansion.
I don't know why it didn't come up for me.
It's Spooky Scary Skeletons.
Spooky Scary Skeletons.
OK.
So artists to spooky scary skeletons?
Well, I'm sorry.
That's what comes up on Spotify.
No, I love it.
I want to know if they have more music.
It might be the album, but that's what's coming up on there.
Do spooky scary skeletons have just like regular love ballads and other types of music?
Like fun, bouncy, just songs about driving?
Yeah, like Beach Boy style songs.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, they do Beach and Cards songs.
But you could do the Peter Pan one.
Like think of a happy.
Yeah, I should look up to see if they have.
I don't think they have that on the deconstructed.
But yeah, it's music wise.
I don't I always forget other than that little first flourish when you're leaving the bedroom.
I don't I don't think of it as a songs movie in general.
But it is.
Follow the Leader was a lot of stuff.
That was a big like sing along songs.
Yeah, the croc.
But they're like the B side that they're clearly the second and third single.
You would know exactly what it was when you heard it, though.
Yes.
Yes. Yeah.
It is interesting.
Am I wrong in thinking those songs don't have the like, oh, like you don't think of them as much as in the Disney like the top.
Would you think of them in top 10 Disney songs?
No, no, no.
You can fly.
Maybe.
Maybe that one gets the closest.
But almost almost all of the movies really only have one big hit.
I accept Hercules.
I was going to say that was the other thing.
Hercules is so good.
I was big Hercules kit.
It's like go the distance.
Meg song.
What is her song?
Oh, yeah.
I hadn't thought about that one.
I want to know that she hates men, which I love.
Zero to hero.
A star is born.
Yeah, I mean, I could.
Oh, they're so good.
Yeah.
Yeah, actually.
Yeah, those are all pretty like tied.
Do we like.
I'm sorry.
Also, Mulan.
I actually all of them.
Mulan has make a man out of you and bring honor to us all reflections and shoot.
What's the one?
The other one.
I can't think.
A girl worth fighting for.
I just can't get like you list the other ones, but I'm just stuck in to defeat the Huns.
The most clear, like the whitest guy, obviously, Donny Osmond guy done survive.
Is that Donny Osmond?
Donny Osmond is the singing voice.
I don't think I ever knew that.
Yeah.
He could not be more pronounced.
I've ever met.
He really hits every consonant.
And he's doing it in the live action one, too.
He'll be back.
Yeah.
It cuts to a 65 year old Donny Osmond.
Like a Matt Damon sort of thing.
What I find so fascinating is that Danny Elfman did the singing voice of Jack for Nightmare
for Christmas.
Why didn't you just do the regular voice, too?
Who did the regular voice?
I don't have it at my disposal.
Yeah.
Who is that?
Why wouldn't he just also?
He sounds so much like the singing voice sounds just like him.
For sure.
Yeah.
And the songs are a little like talk singy a lot.
So, you know.
Jack!
You know, like that.
Like he's just so into it.
He's listed as the voice.
Oh, no, I thought he was just a singing voice.
Oh, wait.
No, I'm so sorry.
It's Chris Sarandon.
Chris Sarandon.
I read it wrong.
Related to Susan Sarandon?
I believe so.
Why don't Chris Sarandon is Chris.
He's bringing up Percules again.
He's in the Tate Donovan category.
So some of these people are like not that well known outside of these voice, unless I'm forgetting.
What is the big Chris Sarandon?
What's the top Chris Sarandon?
Oh, he was married to Susan Sarandon.
That's how she became a Sarandon.
That's why she's Sarandon.
However, she clearly took over that last name.
It is a lot more.
Yes.
She really commandeered it.
Good job, Susan.
Can you imagine giving your last name to someone and then they like take it over and I assume they're divorced, right?
Yeah, yeah.
So she like just took it and ran with it.
That is like kind of like a badass move, isn't it?
Yeah.
Who wins the divorce?
Susan wins by vastly overshadowing him career wise.
Now I don't know this, but were he a conservative man, he must be really furious.
Sarandon is associated with these left wing values.
And she went on to play Betty Davidson.
He's much more of a Joan Crawford fellow.
That's the ultimate insult.
He's known for Fright Night, Dog Day Afternoon, The Princess Bride.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
He's a prince and the princess bride.
Oh, well, there you go.
And Child's Play.
So sorry also to all of the Chris Sarandon heads who are screaming at us as they listen to this.
I don't want to insult anyone.
No, not controversial.
Tate Donovan to Goofy.
Yeah.
Sorry.
The great leading man out there.
My friend was Goofy in their college program that they have where you can like get college credit and go work at Disney World or whatever.
Yeah, taller.
Yeah, you had to be taller.
How'd that go for him?
Did he like that?
I think he did.
I think he liked being goofy.
I do find it fascinating that they can't really interact with like bad kids, you know, like they just have to put up with it.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I like their rules.
That's why some of them also don't talk like they have.
Isn't that like the Star Wars people don't actually talk, right?
They have the stormtroopers or do they?
Well, yeah, people there's a debate.
I feel like there's the same kind of lines they say.
So there's some mechanism by which they play a recorded.
That's what I figured.
That's what it seems like to me.
Some people have disputed that, but that's my reading of it.
If you're a cast member, DM us.
Yes.
I am curious.
Yeah, because they don't go like, hey, you in the blue shirt.
It's all it's pretty it's generic.
Yeah, like they have stuff for kids.
I think like you little Jedi, you won't defeat me.
Like, but it's never like blonde haired little girl.
It's never that specific.
Well, yeah, but the costume ones, they don't talk.
Yeah, goofy and Minnie and Mickey and those they don't they just like hand gestures and crap.
There's a talking Mickey head that they have retired.
There was one.
So for now, at least it was malfunctioning too much.
I don't know what it was doing, but we I saw it.
We it talked to us.
I was so excited when we went to Florida when Lindsay and I went to Florida because it was like you.
They were like, you meet Mickey in the magic.
He's like dressing room before his magic show, which is bizarre.
Now that I'm saying it out loud.
Mickey's about to do a magic show.
You know, he's a magician.
He's a man who does a mouse who does a lot of different things.
And then you meet him in the dressing room before his show.
It's before the show.
I think because you didn't see a show.
So why are you just going?
Are you just going backstage to see him?
I don't like to see anyone before a show.
It's bad.
I do not like the audience to see me.
Oh, yeah.
I don't want to stress Mickey out.
He's going to blow all the tricks.
But then there were multiple rooms because it was just a meet and greet.
And there would be only like one room with a working head.
So when Lindsay and I went to Florida, I was like, we got to go meet the Mickey with the talking head.
So we went in there and they bring us into the room, one of the rooms.
And you can see the other rooms.
They don't want you to know.
Of course, there's multiple Mickey.
So we went into one of the rooms and he didn't talk.
And I was deflated and confused.
And then we went to City Hall so I could complain.
And they were like, well, Mickey isn't always feeling so talkative.
He's not always like because they wouldn't say process.
I get it.
They wouldn't say it because they can't advertise that he talks.
But I knew it because I was looking at YouTube videos.
And then they're like, just go in and you can maybe ask if Mickey's feeling talkative today.
So I had to go and do like a weird secret secret like word like Mickey talking to them.
And they're like, maybe you're a grown ass man.
Like, it's so weird.
That's like something they would tell a child.
Like, why wouldn't they just say like, oh, no, I think it's out today.
Like, you know what I mean?
The jaw is not working.
Why wouldn't it just be adult to adult?
And so they gave you an answer that they would give a five year old.
Well, it is an adult who made a trip to City Hall to complain about this issue.
You just breeze past that.
Anyway, I'm sure this won't come back.
I'm going to finish the story.
No, but he's a grown ass man who's paid his hard earned dollar to see Mickey say like, thanks for coming to my magic show.
Speaking of rides and going to City Hall, my dad actually lost his keys on Indiana Jones.
Closing. Oh, no. Oh, my God. Yeah.
Yeah. And they found them.
I have no idea how I think like because they had to turn on all the lights.
They actually found it like pretty quickly, but it was and we didn't realize until it was a mass exodus.
Everybody was leaving and I was like 11 trying to find my dad and he was like, oh, crap.
And he like ran off towards Indiana Jones and had to run after him.
He's not the best dad.
Oh, no.
But they like turned on all the lights and found it, which if y'all listeners know, Indiana Jones is like the boss.
Indiana Jones is like the bumpiest ride, darkest.
Like it's insane to even imagine losing something in it.
Yeah, I would assume maybe, like, you know, if it was on the ride, the ride vehicle, obviously the easiest.
But if it like got lost in the snakes, that would be harder to find.
I don't. Yeah.
Especially if it was a snake patterned keychain.
Yeah. Yeah.
So, yeah, I left. I left the recorder.
Remember, I left an audio recorder the day the Star Wars opened.
I left it on the ride.
Which almost blew our big interview with Lentesta.
Yeah, we had a big interview set up with theme park podcast or Lentesta that day and it would have been ruined if I had left this.
But they found it quickly.
So there must be I'm assuming that these people just know very fast because they also other rides they shut down.
Other rides they shut down if stuff falls like immediately.
Did you put it in the pouch? Is that where it was?
I think it was in my pocket and I was worried because I had bought that Rex up there and I had it on the ride and I was too preoccupied with the Rex to make sure he didn't get hurt.
We both had giant Rex boxes on our laps on the bumpiest ride.
Surely we have to go on this ride.
Yeah.
There's no other way.
I was like, well, they'll let us just hold it with at the exit.
And they were like, no, put it on the ride with you.
It'll be fine.
And I was so nervous.
Do you have rides anyone that you were the most nervous about losing things on?
Because I'll put on Space Mountain and I put things in the pouch.
But then I'll leave like keys or wallet.
And then still I find myself the whole ride then like shoving hands in for extra.
It still just feels precarious to me.
Yeah, I that one I agree on.
I'm trying to think the worst.
I'm sure I said this already.
There's a ride at knots called Hang Time where you go up 90 degrees and you're supposed to take your stuff out of your pockets.
And I didn't like a fucking idiot.
And I had my phone in my back pocket.
Because I thought it would be better, which is also the dumbest thing you could possibly do.
It's much better for what's here.
And I could just put my hand in my pocket to hold it.
It's like so I'm like trying to like put my weight.
I'm distributing my weight as I'm 90 degrees.
And that's by far the most stressful.
Like I hope I don't lose something.
Well, we and you're talking about knots when we we did that wooden coaster ghost rider.
I thought my glasses were going to fly off my head, which usually on wooden roller coasters, I can leave them on and it's fine.
But like it was the most bumpy maybe ride I've ever been on.
And I am like holding this holding them onto the sides of my head because I like yeah, just didn't want to lose them.
Yeah, it's weird.
Drive back to L.A.
It's weird that doesn't happen more.
I guess it's just like like normal force.
Just everything stays put for the most part.
But it does feel like how would that not happen once a ride?
You hit in the face with someone's keys.
Yeah, I have been on Space Mountain a few times.
Where someone has held up their giant ass Android phone to videotape it.
And they at least once someone is going, oh, it's really dark in there.
And it's like, yeah, no shit.
I swear it got darker, though, because I think when I was younger, they had a little bit more.
Do you all remember that?
Wasn't there more lights or more stars or something?
I think the star lights are they just completely turned everything out.
Yeah, yeah, I think you might be right.
Yeah, it does feel like the whole thing about Space Mountain is when you get up there, you're supposed to be like, oh, my goodness, the majesty of space.
And then you're like, oh, all the stars look pretty dim.
Yeah, they are.
Yeah, they're all barely see them.
Yeah.
And then there's like a giant asteroid in there, but it's not lit up.
And if you look sort of your left when you're coming up, it's there, but it's not lit.
So I don't know if they were like they're like worried it's going to break the illusion that you're in space.
But they do that with the Star Wars overlay.
So I don't know.
Also, somebody tell us that we know a gentleman who works around Space Mountain.
That's all I'll say.
Yeah, he wants to tweet at us and let us know about the dimness, the dimness.
And if it's always been like that or that's just our memory, he knows who he is.
Well, I also wanted to say I watched on the Imagineering.
I don't know if you all watched any of that.
Yeah, Episode five is where they talk about Peter Pan.
And for anyone that wants to learn more about the ride as well.
And I guess that they so when they put the water in, like a duck family found their way into there.
And they said like a mom and her ducklings and they like pooped everywhere.
And then I started to think like, oh, my God, like, does that happen in pirates or like I'm just really concerned for the animals that like you're not like there's just not random ducks that find their way into the water.
Yeah. How do you how do you make sure that that doesn't happen?
Yeah, it seems like with pirates, it's a little more tucked away, I guess.
I guess it's not really I mean, I guess you could get a duck could easily fly into the Peter into pirates pretty much any ride.
Yeah, that's interesting.
I wonder I feel like I've never seen a real animal on pirates.
But I'm like deep.
Yeah, definitely.
All the way in like deep into the ride.
That would be really weird.
But yeah, you would think does Disney have a system for like keeping a bird from flying into Space Mountain and making a nest?
No.
Like Fabio in us in the dark.
Have you seen that new story?
Yes, where he killed a bird with his face.
Yeah, his face was so beautiful.
It killed the bird.
It died before it hit him.
The bird had a heart attack from the beauty.
The glow.
We've also promised we're going to do a full episode on that incident.
Oh, yeah, that's I was trying to remember what episode idea came out of the other roller coaster where a bird got demolished.
That's right.
Fabio coming soon.
Yeah.
Yes, please.
Let's do that.
So, yeah, that's a good question.
I'm sure they have all these different things.
There's like a secret like ways that snipers take the animal out.
Yeah, you're right.
That is that is a fun little snippet of the imaginary story.
And it shows you it kind of goes behind the scenes in the like the little redo's they've done the plus ups they've done into Peter Pan recently, which are very delightful.
I think we can all agree.
Yeah, so because they've done a couple different big updates of the ride since it's opened.
California.
I was going to say when it opened in 1955, they had it.
You were you were Peter Pan.
You were supposed to be Peter Pan.
And then they didn't.
So but when people came out, they didn't understand why Peter Pan wasn't in the ride.
Yes.
It was like, oh, because that's you.
OK, never mind.
We should just put him in the ride.
Which it's the end.
And the same problem with Snow White and the same problem with Mr. Toad.
And it's weird that they had to like overcome this big like storytelling.
This is how new what they were doing was.
They didn't realize like, boy, we are like not connecting with our audience on this major issue.
I get the idea in theory.
Like, wouldn't it be cool that you're the character?
But it's not like they were like that person was working on the ride wasn't like, all right, now imagine you're Peter Pan.
Go like you didn't get any sort of like hint that that was the case.
So you were seeing stuff from the movie and you were like, well, I'm in a pirate ship.
I'm not flying.
I don't have the hat on.
That's not what Peter did.
He didn't fly around a little pirate ship.
Right. Exactly.
If they strapped you in with a harness and then they put the hat on you, I think people would have figured it out.
Or even if these people looked at you and were like, Peter, help me.
You know, yes.
Yeah, that's good.
Yes. Peter.
Well, Peter's because there's multiple people on the ride and also Peter and Peter.
Peter.
Everything.
Just like Santa Claus.
You're Peter's helper.
Yes.
That would be good, too.
They also hadn't figured out how to give you missions back then, because nowadays it'd be like Peter.
Peter, Princess Tiger Lily has a mission for you.
I don't like those rides.
They get me too stressed out.
Like collaborative rides and things where you like people need you for things.
I'm like, no, I just want to sit here and enjoy.
Oh, too much.
What do you put in that category?
Like the Millennium Falcon, whatever.
Like any teamwork stuff?
No.
Yeah.
It's not what I signed up for.
You would just like to be having a nice time in the cockpit.
Yeah.
You don't want to have to push any buttons.
I mean, these don't assign me anything.
But even the idea of it like Optimus Prime needs you to do stuff, you don't really have anything to do.
Do you feel the stress even that he kind of...
I don't have to push anything.
It's just a give work.
The only thing I can barely handle is astro blasters.
But even then, my person next to me is always looking at mine to make sure that they're better than me and they are.
And so I'm just like, this is not why I came to Disneyland to be reminded that I'm inadequate.
It's so rude.
To give your hands a rest.
I think you just don't want to be a working machine.
I just get stressed out when numbers are involved and like...
Toy Story as well?
Yeah, that's what I mean. Astro blasters.
Well, there's the other Toy Story one too.
It's also, it's at California Adventure.
It's like you have to pull a pull string.
I don't know if I've heard of that one.
Well, then you would hate it.
It's like a 3D game.
You have to shoot rings at like a screen and your wrist just kills by the end of it.
You truly, it really hurts the hand.
So yeah, stay away.
There's no reason. You don't need that stress in your life.
We just came out hard against that right.
And you know what? And listeners, stay away.
And we're never going to do it on the show.
I don't think it's nice.
No, no, no. We're not.
We're signing now.
Toy Story made.
It's like an old fashioned carnival.
No, you're crazy.
Yeah, you can do that episode alone, Jason.
All right.
He just sits too straight out.
Carnivals are first.
The pull string as seen on many toys, including Woody himself.
Peter Pan.
We're jumping all around here.
Peter Pan, though, is the first Disney ride I go on as a little kid and like.
I try Mr. Toad.
I try Snow White.
They scare the shit out of me.
Both of them.
I'm probably like, I'm always forgetting when we went five.
I'm probably like five or six.
Won't open my eyes.
I go on Peter Pan.
It took forever because it always has and it always will.
And I loved it.
I thought it was the greatest thing and want to do it again.
And my mom was like, the line is too long.
It is.
Cannot do it again.
We have other things to go do.
It's rough.
My favorite is flying over London.
Like that to me is what makes the ride so special.
I think the other elements I can like give or take, like, you know, whatever.
But like that and having the clock tower, Big Ben and have like all the all the little things.
That they have there.
I thought was so cool.
I think it's a really wonderful scene and it's the scene that has changed the least since the ride opened.
And I think with good reason because like because you get it's a certainly at that time, like probably the biggest kind of set piece scene that any had been ever done in any ride.
I would think because you're in there for so long and you go in and then see it from a different way.
It's almost like a mini version of one of those like it's it's the precursor to the big Indiana Jones Mara room, the main temple or the at at room in Rise of the Resistance.
Like the big reveal.
Yeah.
You're going to be in here for a little while and you can look around and see things from different perspectives.
It's so great.
But done differently in all of the international version.
Like this this ride is duplicated in many parks.
All of them except Hong Kong.
Poor Hong Kong got shafted.
But all a little different.
Like the Florida London much longer but not necessarily more successful I think than Disneyland.
Has a little bit longer of a lead up.
You see Nana.
You see like the alleyway.
You see like.
Oh yeah.
It's just the scale is a lot bigger in Florida.
But I don't I wouldn't necessarily say it's a better ride.
It seems like Shanghai though which was built in 2016.
Like they went all out on the Shanghai one.
It was really good.
Yes.
I did a ride there and it's a little hard to tell from those but it is long.
Yeah.
Very long which they've lengthened the Disney one the Disneyland one over the years.
That's a pretty like sizable experience which one of these is the longest do we think.
That's a question.
Mr. Toad feels long.
Alice feels long.
Well Mr. Toad and well I guess they all kind of do.
They end so abruptly.
Yeah.
It's like you turn a corner and you're like back in the sunlight.
As a person like telling you to get off.
It's insane.
Yeah.
What's the one that is it's we did an episode about it and yet I don't remember offhand.
One of the Snow White iterations ends where the witch is struck by lightning and then you're just outside like happily ever after.
Like there's barely time for a.
There's one here and they're changing it now.
It's down for refurb and it's not going to be just the weird one where like the dwarves are on the mountain and she's about to boulder them to death and she gets struck and dies and then you're outside.
And that's the end of the ride.
So in the wind in the willows did he just die and go to hell and that was it because that's the ride.
I don't know.
He just goes to hell and then that's it and you come back out.
Okay.
In the movie.
It doesn't end with him in hell.
That's the end of a film.
That's pretty nuts.
Well I didn't even realize what happened until I was older and then I was like oh we were in hell and then you're just like back with the workers again like telling you to get off and I'm like what the heck.
There was no other scene after this.
Yeah that's the weird that is that for no other reason I guess I love toad but but the idea that you're putting kids thousands of kids every day you're sending them through hell not even giving them some sort of a resolution like it's going to be okay.
You're in hell but it's fine or like you will get out of hell and go to heaven.
You're sending them through that.
That is one of the weirdest most insane things that is still happening on a daily basis.
I think it's a PSA for drunk driving because that's what happens.
He goes and gets drunk at the bar and then he drives and he goes to court he like kills somebody or whatever he goes to court he gets sentenced he goes to hell and then you're back out and you you're getting off the ride.
Two of the dark rides are like morality tales.
Pinocchio is the same way.
Yeah.
Don't be an actor.
And also no drinking and no cigars.
Right.
Yeah.
You'll become a donkey.
I didn't put the drunk part together.
That is true.
You go into the saloon literally old timey man spinning beers.
Spinning.
Presumably you grab one narratively.
You like crash your car you're driving all crazy.
How many people die on that train that you hit?
If the train derails that's like hundreds of people and if it's not a freight train if that's a passenger train that Mr. Toad might be in for that might be he daily when on that ride kills hundreds of people.
It's him it's Hitler it's like who else is all in hell together.
Mr. Toad.
Mr. Toad and all of the.
Technically killed hundreds of thousands of people.
Mr. Toad is genocidal you could say in a lot yeah in a lot of ways because of just the infinite nature of the ride.
A rich man who thinks the law does not apply to him.
Oh this Toad hopefully they keep that forever.
Yeah that's the last if they'd had their way if there was a little more room they would have built a final room of hell where you see a bunch of celebrity.
Well.
Hitler at the time in the 50s who would have been the most on the wall would have probably put in a bunch you know any like commies who died recently Trumbo.
Trumbo.
And you'll go to a scene and see Trumbo in hell.
In his bathtub.
But it's filled with fire.
Trumbo and a bathtub full of fire.
Okay you love this ride very much because is the line a daunting.
Do you still make a point of getting through the line to get on it if you're going to the park or is the line too daunting to consider it.
Well so my it's one of my top favorite rides.
However like you were saying the ride that you would get to in the morning like first thing you go to for me even though it has a fast pass is actually Indiana Jones on just the sheer fact that it always breaks down.
So when I'm taking someone I'm always like you have to get on Indian Jones I swear by lunchtime it'll break down and then like by lunchtime it breaks down and then I'm like see aren't you glad we did it.
And I'm a pass holder so like I'm there you know so enough to know that that happens.
It's not just whenever I'm there.
But yeah the line can be super daunting that's why.
Okay so I went last year on Valentine's Day and it was like raining and that was great I love going when it rains because then you know that's the best time to get on all these rides.
But yeah I think it's really sweet it's crazy to me that everyone else still loves it so much too.
It's one of their most popular rides ever.
It's weird that it's never gone and it's not like they had to do those plus ups and digital effects to pump some life into the thing like it was a mega line always and still is after and yeah yeah it's just it's pretty eternal.
It is also low capacity when you talk about like riders like it gets through like very little it's hard to load and unload it's not as easy as some of the other rides.
Did anyone see the there's a yesterworld video.
I of course watched the yesterworld video explaining.
With a chart of what loads the does anyone want to guess if you didn't see it what is the low in Disneyland proper the worst the lowest capacity.
Right.
You have an offhand.
Is it.
Oh is it the Astro Orbiter.
No no amazingly.
Is it.
What is now guardians.
No I don't think so.
Those are pretty big rooms.
But those are only two elevator shafts right.
There's three elevators for guardians.
Okay.
I'm actually blanking now what it said I saw the list though.
It's not you wouldn't necessarily know offhand but apparently.
Oh no nevermind.
I'm just gonna keep guessing.
Is it storybook.
No.
Casey Jr.
Is number two because there's only the one train.
And you just got to wait for it.
That makes sense.
The arrows are pretty big.
Oh oh.
Chippendales rescue.
The gadgets go coaster.
No that actually that feels like it could be I think there's like such the lines aren't that big ever.
It only is one coaster though.
Yeah.
I guess anything where that's the case is kind of.
Well reveal it.
Roger Rabbit's cartoon spin.
Apparently.
Wow.
Yeah.
Really.
Part of it.
And I get that doesn't feel right.
No.
Send a lot of cars through.
But that line is always crazy.
I certainly complain about that line.
Very claustrophobic.
I don't get claustrophobic easily but I'd say the the queue for Peter Pan in the queue.
Oh yeah.
For Roger Rabbit.
Very claustrophobic and Roger Rabbit a lot more themed.
I will give it that.
Still a better line.
Is this the worst line.
I mean there's murals.
There's murals inside.
There are murals.
But it is open air.
But there's really nothing.
Yeah.
I will give the advantage to Matterhorn because of the beautiful wood carving.
OK.
That's good.
And then Snow White's queue has the like the like they were wishing well outside.
Or no they have the thing inside where people throw money which is weird.
But like there's a little bit of theming there.
I think anything with landmarks it's the same way that like a long drive where there's that funny billboard that you know weird thing to look at on the side of the road that abandoned water park or whatever it is.
But if it's a long drive that's just like flat land nothing for miles and miles.
And that's kind of what this line is.
So you're going to dock at points.
Maybe.
I think maybe just yeah because like even you're like mentally in Snow White like a guy passed the Wells and I'm at this point.
It is just Peter Pan is a grid.
That's all it is.
Here's the one thing I'll say about it and maybe you shouldn't count it in its favor because it's sort of inadvertent.
But it's one of the best places to see the evil Maleficent Queen.
That little secret.
When she kind of opens the curtains and looks.
When you're in the Peter Pan line that's when you see her the most and you go look at the Queen is going to be there.
I love the castle.
I love going up there and seeing Aurora.
That is very nice.
We've talked very little about the Sleeping Beauty diorama.
That is their diorama.
It's a walk through.
It's very nice.
Yeah I totally agree.
What else we like on the on the ride though.
So the opening rate or you go I was just going to say I probably we're going to say something similar.
The opening scene so you go in the you go in your little pirate ship and you go through and you start in the bedroom of the kids like in the movie.
Initially it was just like a very tiny little section with no characters and it had like I don't even think it had the shadow to start out with.
Well yeah I think that was a later.
It was a later edition and then they like slowly plus that up over the years like they added Nana and then they added a better Nana.
Well Nana was from the original.
I think they kept her is what they were saying.
I think maybe in the Imagineering it was like I don't know if they kept her from the original or the 83 re enhancement the 1983 because they re enhanced it then.
Yeah the yester world video was very confused about which when update was which as well.
So I'm not sure I know there was three got a lot more animatronics.
Yeah yes and then the so I think in 83 they had the darling kids in bed and then in this one they have them actually flying right on the wall.
Oh that was the change.
Okay that was the big change.
Yeah the last time they did something.
But this this it's so interesting with all this stuff because most people are not insane and don't go that often.
So anytime you go on this ride you go oh it must have always been like this.
Right.
I would imagine most people just go on and go yeah that's the great Peter Pan I remember but once you go through all this you're like all these little changes they've made to it over the years are great.
But like they never do something crazy where you go well that was not here before.
Well your memory like is deceptive to our memories are all bad.
We're human beings with bad memories.
There was something we went on in Florida I forget what it is and I was like well I remember this clearly and then I had remembered the mirror image of it in my mind like.
You leave the station and you go left and whatever this was you went right and I was like oh my god I I remembered the details of this ride but I flipped it in my own memory.
I mean that happens a lot.
I incepted myself.
I memory hold.
It's your Peter Pan set pieces.
It is tethered yeah you're tethered.
You're tethered went in and you never came out.
I thought this ride was right side up but it's upside down.
Nope.
Someone in planet this memory of Peter and the Native Americans doing a full musical sequence wearing questionable outfit changes.
This can't be real.
No.
Maybe it hasn't happened yet.
Oh no.
I don't know what Tenet is about.
Do we know?
Well what?
That's the new Christopher Nolan movie.
Oh yeah.
Oh I don't know.
No.
I don't know either.
But like stuff we might not know after we've watched it.
I was like I was thinking like oh Tenet is what they say in the movie.
They say no they say wait for the kick.
Tenet is the new movie you're saying.
Yeah Tenet is the new movie where they show like a 10 minute clip.
Didn't you see the 10 minute clip when we went to see a movie at IMAX.
Oh I did.
I just saw the trailer.
It's with David Washington.
Kenza Washington's son.
Oh is that right.
Yeah.
I didn't realize it was a son.
From Black Plainsman.
Oh yes yes yes yes.
And then Robert Pattinson picks him up in the car.
But yeah.
OK so that played before Birds of Prey.
Yes.
What I saw last night or the night before.
And I was literally looking I'm like where does Harley come in.
Like I had no idea because they just started it.
I really thought it was the movie.
And I'm like OK this is very guy heavy but that's chill.
Like it was all men all SWAT men all and I'm like OK so they're going to break it.
This is going to be a social commentary on something.
And they played like yeah the first 10 minutes so you really think that this is the movie.
And then it was and then it ended and it was like Tenet coming out blah blah blah.
And I was like what the heck.
Wow.
Like why are there like major movie stars in this who I didn't know were in Birds of Prey.
Yeah.
No true.
I was like they didn't say Robert Pattinson but I know he's the new Batman.
This is weird.
Anyways.
That must honestly happen a lot because again they don't they do it without warning.
They do not tell you.
Yeah.
So like you're hearing like you're like the movie looked like a little more like a fun
look like it maybe had like pop songs or something in it.
And I'm just hearing a droning Hans Zimmer score.
This is a weird droning Hans Zimmer Birds of Prey would I think make a very different
movie.
Christopher Nolan Christopher Nolan's Birds of Prey Hans Zimmer doing the score.
It's mostly dudes Harley Quinn's in it for like a couple scenes.
Yeah.
So that first scene when you're in the in the bedroom has been so updated over which is
just like thinking about it.
You're like wow it's so it is really good now.
But it used to just be like a little like three feet of room when people started out.
And I don't think you started from London rooftops in the like right after the mural
either.
Yeah.
I think it was just mural and then you're in a empty bedroom and then you're flying
and that's always been good.
But the first year the launch essentially not like launch coasters but the the before
the big scene.
Yeah it was kind of lame.
I think that.
Sorry.
I'm done.
Oh OK.
That was that ride mechanism.
The ride you know you being above everything you're going over everything and hanging
down.
I think that is a big part of the appeal.
I know my dad is one of his favorite rides and I'm sure like growing up with with Peter
Pan probably being re-released a million times because they always re-released their movies.
You mean it doesn't stay in the vault.
It doesn't stay in the.
Well it did and then they bring it down to the vault for a very short time and then they
aired some of them.
I want to say that I love Disney.
They've always been really great to me and so I just I'm a lot I love them and they know
that.
Oh yeah.
You're just teasing like a family.
We really should have brought up you're you have a you're in Wreck-It Ralph 2.
Is that correct.
Yes.
Yeah.
I'm in a Walt Disney Animation.
I got to go there to their Burbank Studios.
Yeah.
It's pretty crazy.
They animated me.
Wow.
And it's you.
I play myself.
I say like hey it's Danny Fernandez.
Right.
He's in the internet and I live in the internet clearly.
Why yourself?
Because I.
He is going viral.
They wanted someone.
Everyone's like how did you get that?
I'm like well they want it.
They have actually other people in it too.
Like they have big gamers like people that are big big in the online space and so all
those years paid off for me.
Yeah.
But yeah anyways they animated me.
They watched way too many of my videos because they like the way that I talk with my hands
and it's just too much.
Wait a minute.
They.
It's honestly aggressively like me.
Well yeah were you then because I'm like I'm like afraid of knowing what an impression
of me is like let alone this let alone people studying my body language.
Did it like freak you out a little bit.
Well okay so when they sent it to me she wasn't finished.
Okay.
So she just looked like a sim.
So I was like thanks.
You know I was just like she didn't even really look like me.
She just kind of looked like whatever game character you get in the beginning before it's
been like stylized.
The creative player default.
Yeah yeah and that's just like their placeholder and so they didn't actually show.
I was hosting the Ralph panel at New York Comic Con and that's when I saw her was with
everyone else in the room.
Wow.
Because they were showing like the some of the scenes.
So I was like oh my gosh she's so pretty.
They gave me what I call Moana hair which is like when you watch Moana it's like the
detail of her hair like each like strand moves.
Wow.
And so they had they had that yeah all the Disney princesses were in it and then I hosted
a panel with them also at New York Comic Con.
It was like the original Pedro Herra who's Belle and Jodie Benton who's Ariel and.
Oh I didn't know this.
Anika Nani Rose.
You had a panel with all of these people.
Yeah.
Wow.
And then I was like I'm not going to cry.
There was like a thousand people there.
I'm like I'm not going to cry I'm not going to cry.
But Anika cried because she was the first black Disney princess and then I started bawling
and then yeah I don't even remember.
How far back did this go who was like the oldest school.
Well okay so that would be Snow White right.
But.
It's not the original.
Yeah.
And so but we did have the woman who took over for Cinderella who's actually been voicing
her the last like 25 years.
Wow.
You know some of those original ones.
So I think the last person alive would be Jodie Benton who's Ariel.
Okay sure.
Yeah.
Most original.
Wow.
What a lineup.
That's crazy.
All of that is crazy and it's also in the movie because there's a scene in Reggae Ralph
too where they're all the princesses are hanging out.
You're like part of continuity though now with the princess you know what I mean.
Like if it was a different movie where maybe sort of oh this is in a different like little
pocket Disney universe but it feels like now you're you are canon.
Yeah you are.
Isn't that wild.
It's very wild.
Yeah.
But again it's you it's not a character.
No.
You are.
That's what's even crazier is like there are people in it and but they're playing other
people and I'm they literally I say like hey I'm Danny Fernandez.
Welcome to BuzzTube or whatever it is that they're making fun.
It was like BuzzFeed and YouTube.
Right.
But I went over to Hector Navarro.
I don't know if you know Hector Navarro.
I went over to his place and he when he was in Japan bought a Japanese version of Wreck-It Ralph.
And so he put it in for me and it's my character speaking Spanish but she said I mean Spanish.
There is that version my character speaking Japanese but she says Danny.
And so I was like oh my gosh like this woman also played me Danny.
So people play you yourself.
Yeah.
Localization.
It's not a language localization version.
It is crazy because like there's no like you know famous very famous actors have been characters but they haven't been themselves.
Yeah.
It's never been like I don't know why I first saw Mel Gibson but that was the first name that popped into my head.
But he was John Smith.
Uh huh.
He was not Mel Gibson in the Pocahontas.
I think he has.
Oh yeah.
You think Mel Gibson has been in a cartoon himself.
No hasn't he.
Was he on Family Guy.
People have.
The Simpsons.
Oh it is the Simpsons.
Oh yeah.
But I'm saying in Disney.
Nobody's been in a fit yeah.
There's be rare opportunity.
There's not a lot of modern films set in modern times.
Right.
Yeah.
It's almost one of the only movies you'd be able to do that.
So I'm really lucky that I got to do that because I don't know another movie you know that would take place in the internet that you would get to be yourself.
They also had you know like Grumpy Cat another.
Sure.
Grumpy Cat was also themselves.
They had the real Grumpy Cat.
Sure.
They had a real meow.
I don't know.
But like if there's a Disney Plus show about Powerline and they're having like somebody interview Powerline.
I'm just saying they could go back in the archives and be like well do we have a character in one of these movies that could interview or talk or it could be you.
Do we have any podcasters.
Yeah.
That could go and do it.
Yes.
Is there any podcasting in a Disney movie yet.
Oh.
I don't know.
That would have been it.
Maybe an Onward.
Maybe there's podcasting.
They have a long journey apparently.
It seems like an Onward.
It's like college guys right.
Yeah.
They're Marin fans.
Sure Rogan.
Someone grew up with like Lion King and watching all those VHS's as they were like sketching you.
Did you.
Because I feel like all I would think about is like those pre-rolls on the VHS's where they're like coming the summer of 1993.
Where they show the animals drawing a real lion but it's just they're doing it to you.
They're like sitting there.
I think the thing that weird and I ended up you know becoming friends with the directors and the animators and like I know all the storyboard artists.
Josie Trinidad who's actually now directing a Walt Disney Animation movie.
She was also lead storyboard artist on Zootopia.
But yeah I mean I got to know these people and also like hosting panels with them.
But the weird the thing that weirded me out was the idea that a group of animators were sitting there all together watching videos of me like that made me feel weird.
Yeah.
You know it's just super self conscious.
Like a lion as if you were.
Yeah.
Yes a subject.
And it's like the way that like my jaw moves and which is kind of like weird.
I mean the same thing for Sarah Silverman though.
She has like weird the way that she talks is very specific the way that she moves her mouth is really specific.
And so both both she looked like her character and John C. Reilly looks like his character you know.
So but it's still weird thinking that like someone sat and like which videos did they watch.
Yeah.
And if someone was like me a nerdist or like were they ones where I wasn't funny or like had a bad take on something or whatever.
You know what I mean.
Yeah.
Like if someone if two animators were arguing like someone's having a bad day that's going like she doesn't fucking do that.
Would you do like she doesn't do that.
Do your research.
Come on man.
I need some air.
Well I am calling on anyone who's working on anything with Disney Plus to put your character of yourself in another Disney Plus thing.
Yeah.
Because that would make it a runner.
I feel like well Alan Tudyk I forgot I think his first appearance was in the original.
He played King Candy in the original Ralph.
And then after that he's been in like every one.
He was like the chicken in Moana.
He was he was knows more in Wreck-It Ralph 2.
You know now he's in the Star Wars.
And so I'm like I want to be like him and just like get into one and then you get asked to be little side characters and all of them.
Now it's a run.
You're a rat's burger.
You're like perennially always in there.
Like haters kind of getting there.
Maybe he's in a lot of things.
He was in Ralph the second Ralph.
Yeah.
And he's in that's right.
Inside I was going to call it in and out which is the Kevin Kline movie.
Inside out.
He's one of the main characters and I feel like he's somewhere else.
But whatever.
Yeah.
That's great.
Power OK.
Power line show specifically.
You should be in that.
I would love it.
Yeah.
First the first pitch that there is a full power.
You and I just we said that that eye to eye is the best Disney song of all time.
We agreed on that.
I don't know if we've specifically said that.
I can't immediately think of anything to counter that.
It's like part of your world and eye to eye.
I feel like the two best.
Yeah.
One and two.
I don't know which order but yeah.
The two best I think.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I got nothing to lose.
I'll throw it in there.
All right.
Yep.
And then I said I and we will never cover Toy Story Mania.
That's right.
It's never Jason.
I'm working on my one man office.
You're taking your writing notes down already.
Yeah.
So you get back.
You get out of the bedroom.
You go over to London which they've only made like cooler and brighter.
I was watching a side by side.
There's not great archival video of the old.
No.
Peter Pan.
The pre 83.
Yeah.
Like for the first 20 plus years.
You do get those in Imagineering Story has this video of the tests of it.
This feels like one of the first things where you could see footage that they mocked this
up at the Disney studios and people are just like up on a wire in an unthemed room tutting
around and that this feels like one of the first like like imagineering feats where you
look at it and it looks bizarre.
People aren't supposed to be able to do that.
We had it happen.
They're conquering something.
They're like we figured some weird thing out that we haven't done before.
It's the technology is basically what I win that yester world video.
It says it's basically like factor like what factories would use to like make a
cart stuff around.
So like it almost feels like it's probably the same factory or same technology that like
you would hang a big slab of meat on and like roll it through the factory like it's like
some basic stuff that cleaners.
Yeah.
Kind of like that.
It's basically that.
Yeah.
Which is crazy.
So they just took another technology and used it for this.
I will say this is the only thing that's still kind of weird to me is that on this ride I'm
always a little worried that that thing is making too much noise that the mechanism is
making too much noise when I'm on it.
I'm like is that going to I know it's held for 60 years but I'm still a little scared.
Now this was a big thing thought that I had when reading about all this stuff as the
technology improves and this is a ride that we've said they've plus up a lot.
They've done a lot to the years.
Could they make it quieter because you hear that you hear that.
But then my other question so like could they make that the gears would like it quieter
but if they do that will people you know again memory sense memory would be if they did that
if they made it quieter would people be thrown because they are so used to you're saying
people complain that there's not a loud gear noise.
Well I got to complain about everything but I don't think they would complain about that.
As I was watching the footage I like five different versions of this ride I was like
oh yeah that sound is present in all of them but it's so charming the ride is so charming
you like I've never gone like oh that sound I've just always been like white noise until
now you did it now.
Well as I have a podcast to have these kinds of thoughts on the one in Tokyo is quieter.
I felt of course that's all you did it.
Tokyo is like they're all all the rides are better taken care of the Indiana Jones ride
is smooth as can be newer.
They are newer but also it feels like maybe they like fixes something is that little extra
really charming about Disneyland though and I try to explain it to my friends that you
know on the East Coast they only go to Disney World and I'm like but you just there's something
little bit magical like it was just made with more love more like literally made by
hand over at Disneyland and then when my friends would go there they're like you're right it's
just something a little different.
I friend of the show Zack Ryder was texting me after he had been to Disneyland and he
lives out in Orlando and he was saying he finally had to give it up he's like fuck Disneyland
is better like he seemed upset to have to concede that point.
I also think because that so last time I didn't even mention this I ran the Disneyland
marathon the Disney World marathon and the Disneyland Half marathon because I was crazy
in college and I just was like I can do this.
It was because I saw in a runners world magazine that you get this huge Walt Disney the Walt
Disney Mickey statue that's at the front the middle in front of the castle you get a medallion
of it when you do both.
And so I ran both but anyway so last time I was at Walt when I was at Disney World there's
so many buses you have to take to get everywhere like that I was so irritated by.
It drove me crazy when we just went yes I really liked the skyliner this gondola thing
that takes you around and I got that I liked a ton so then having to step down to the buses
so I had some buzz rides that were truly patience testing.
Yeah I mean whereas with ours it's like oh I just want to go over to I'll meet you at
Guardians and it takes like 10 minutes you know from get to one end of the park to the
end of another park or whatever.
The trick with the buses you just have to dedicate a number of hours to studying transportation
infrastructure and maps.
You love riding on a bus.
He made a point of I'm going to see how the internal like how the transportation works.
Jason said he was going to test the limits of the infrastructure.
I got it.
Cut out the last bus of the night out of Hollywood Studios which I took a boat to.
Wow.
You do like a bus though right.
I like a bus yeah I like a bus okay well especially in Florida because it's so hot and the buses
are so strongly air conditioned.
They are sometimes a relief.
So if you're a fan of transfers then you're not going to find that at Disneyland.
Do you recommend running those marathons?
Well if you're going to do any marathon I don't recommend running marathons but if you are
and you're like dead set on doing it it's the best one because there's a lot to see.
So you get to run you run through the park before it opens and there's all the characters
out there and people stop to take pictures but like there's a line I'm like I'm not messing
up my time.
But there's like a lot it's like really cool and especially if you're running at Disney
World then you do have a lot to run through you're running through all the kingdoms.
It still is 26.2 miles.
I think when people hear that I ran they're like oh you ran at Disney World that must
have been you know easy and I'm like no it's still your feet moving 26.2 miles.
Still regulation.
Yeah and also you can't go like if you are running you know too slow they'll come and
cart you because they have to eventually like open the thing up and it's like you know what
I mean like you can't it's not even that bad but like it will catch up to you if you haven't
trained at all.
I didn't train as much as I should have so I was in a lot of pain.
How do they cart like do they just are like golf cart.
Wow they're literally a cart.
Well yeah I mean like you can't you can't take all day to run it right.
They give you a time limit.
Right.
Wow Jason you should do that because then you'll get the experience of running and being
in a golf cart.
My thing with marathons or you're hearing the harsh I mean those you do have to like
train a bit.
You do have to train a bit yeah.
Or like your body start to shut down.
It will shut down.
If you try to jump into.
Right.
But I'm well I'm just saying that maybe even if you don't train they'll just golf cart you
pretty quick and you'll get to take a golf cart through everything.
They just give up right away.
Well they're so the Disneyland one I don't even know if they do it anymore they have
different themed ones like they used to have the Tower of Terror like 10k or something.
I did the half marathon at Disneyland.
You actually ran through Angel Stadium as well because like just Disneyland proper wasn't
enough.
Cool.
But that one was only 13 only 13 mile 13.2 miles or whatever 13.1.
And back when I was running in college I'm like anyone could get to about 10 miles without
training like if you had to if you like if you were running for your life.
But now that I'm a little bit older I'm like there's I can barely run a mile.
I don't know.
I like don't run anymore.
So but that was my like I didn't really train for the half one because I already done a
full and I was like I have enough and I still was in so much pain.
So anyways the medals though were pretty dope.
Well yeah.
What's the medallion.
Wait explain describe this medallion.
Yeah I'll show it to you.
So I got so you get one for each one for each.
So the marathon I got a Mickey medallion.
Some years they do a castle.
You get the castle which is really cool for the half marathon.
I got Mickey running.
It was a medallion.
And if you do them both in the same year it's called the coast to coast marathon.
You get the Walt and Mickey.
Wow.
Oh it's of that.
I wonder are these like valuable too because I feel very few people probably do both or
do you like.
That's really cool.
That's heavy duty.
Oh yeah.
Wow.
That's big.
It's them.
It's a good material.
So you technically get three right because you get the one from Disney World you get
the one from Disneyland and then you get the medallion.
Wow.
How do you get those displayed.
Well me right now just in like a jewelry box but other people you can look at you know
they have these huge ways.
The goofy one is if you do the if you do the half on Saturday and the full on Sunday.
I think there is and there are some weekends where you can do a 5k on Friday the half on
Saturday and the full on Sunday.
Yeah like an Iron Man.
It's like if you want to kill yourself there's different metal levels and stuff.
Yeah medically that is not recommended I believe unless you are like peak physical kid like
you know you have pledged your allegiance to eating a lot of.
Oh I do need to say I'll probably get kicked out but I don't care though.
So there's a run Disney Facebook group that has like thousands of people in it.
And it has the most drama all the time.
I'm like what in the world.
But then you think of like people that run marathons and they're probably obnoxious and
like suburban like parents that like well we so I'm a kinesiology major.
That's one of the reasons why I ran it is like I was just really athletic.
And so they had us one of the things it's exercise science one of the things one of the classes
you have to take a sports marketing.
And so we learned like with marketing what they market at marathons like who can afford
to run a marathon.
You actually have you know what I mean.
Like if you if you dissect like you're paying for airfares travel stay you're paying like
hundreds of dollars to run right.
It's not for free.
So it was just fascinating.
So then you see all of that coming together in this run Disney group of like slightly
entitled runners who were also Disney Disney people too.
And there's a lot of I said our Facebook group is really wonderful and and super powerful
and super positive.
And I sometimes you see them say which is this is nice that this group is great because
I've been in other Disney groups that are not great.
Yeah.
The baby Yoda groups I'm in turn to hell.
No I shared them on Twitter.
I'm surprised because I'm like I'm a weasel like I will share what people are posting
and I share it.
There's thousands of people in there.
You also forget like what other parts of America are like.
They're very like homophobic and racist.
And and so I think baby Yoda is probably gay.
I don't like that.
No but there was literally when they show there was a huge thing in the baby Yoda group
whenever they showed and I'll send you guys my thread because it's just insane.
I was like keeping track on Twitter of like all the awful things people were saying there.
But when they showed Pedro Pascal's face which like how did you not know it was Pedro Pascal
like we're all speaking of like when you call people real Star Wars fans how did you not
know that that was Mando.
And so when he took his helmet off we were like what.
And then somebody was like he's just a little gay looking for me.
I'm not into that.
But I mean if you are and we're like this is really home.
She was like I said if you are it's OK.
I'm like OK but it was wild.
The baby Yoda groups were like they went to hell.
And multiple there were multiple groups that all had discord.
Pro vaccination wanted an anti-vaxxer.
You laugh but I'm not.
Oh another fight that sorry I could talk about this.
No keep going.
I was going to say another fight that got started was when it was like I don't have kids.
I'd rather have baby Yoda than kids.
And like everyone started it's just a joke.
You know people started it.
But then people that have kids were like I love my child.
So it was like this huge fight.
So all I did was just screenshot it and share it.
I would black out names unless they were like super racist.
And then I was like you deserve it.
But in the run Disney group it's the same thing.
It's so petty.
So like somebody was like hey I don't really like the border for the Tower of Terror which isn't a thing anymore.
But like I don't really like the border.
Is there another border that we can get for when you're crossing the finish line.
And someone did the SpongeBob mean it was like is there another border that we can get with this.
And I'm like you guys are so awful.
Do you have nothing better to do with your lives than like attack each other on here.
That's the suburbs.
Oh wow.
Oh my God.
I also I'm in a lot of these Facebook groups and the more if it's a really big group generally you're going to see that type of thing.
I won't say what.
Well one of the nicer ones I'm in is the Chuck E. Cheese fan page.
Are they OK.
They're OK.
They're more.
It's a much more pure Chuck E. Love.
But the other ones I'm in are very can get very toxic very fast including my hometown's Facebook group.
And then the Facebook group.
And then the Facebook group that's called like Schomburg uncensored because they felt they were being censored in the main Facebook group.
Wow.
I have one like that too.
So I'll have to tell you from for my high school I went to in Dallas.
I'll have to tell you after.
Yeah.
Sure.
Some things.
One of the ones there was on one of the Disney related ones.
There was a somebody asked like hey can anyone get me into Galaxy's Edge tomorrow which is back when they were doing reservations.
And it's like that is a thing to not like who's going to do that.
Right.
With a stranger.
So it's kind of a weird ask.
They the people roasted this poor woman hundred comments long of like oh yeah well how are you also.
Can you call blown you my car too.
And it's like well wait a minute.
Someone's mom who doesn't know anything.
Yeah.
Like why do you even have to like why do you have to humiliate this person on Facebook.
It was an extra ticket like the kind you get at Staples for Raffles where it's like you hold one I'll hold one.
Like oh if I'm not there make sure you listen for my number.
Just hundreds of people lighting this poor woman up.
And it's like I was just asking.
And of course like yeah.
OK.
I just have to read.
This is the original start of my thread.
I said I'm in some baby Yoda groups and this is the post that got me on to the fact that there's drama because I don't pay attention.
I'm not really on Facebook.
It says OK let me make this very clear.
I joined this group for all things baby Yoda babies pets memes etc.
I am leaving because of all the drama and fighting surrounding babies pets etc.
If you don't like it don't comment in caps.
Admins need to take more care of this group.
Tired of the drama.
So I saw that pop up on my feet and I'm like what is happening in this baby Yoda group.
Anyone who talks about drama too much.
I am like you are suspect.
You are not trustworthy.
Yes you perhaps are a participant in the drama.
Perhaps one of the primary participants in the drama.
I'm sorry I just have one more and then I'm going to put this away.
OK so this is in the baby Yoda group.
It literally says baby Yoda posting.
OK baby Yoda is cool but the level of obsession this group has with him is just cringe.
It has 655 comments.
Oh my god.
The group is dedicated to cringe.
You can't call something cringe if the whole point is cringe.
It's all cringe.
It makes me so excited.
Why would liking babies real babies and liking baby Yoda be mutually exclusive.
Why do you have to pick a side between baby Yoda and babies.
Yeah no that doesn't make any sense.
All of these groups are pressure cookers for what's every like anything that's going on in people's brains.
And it's like it can't help but come out.
I mean the country is a little it's we're coming off like there was a news clip recently where someone's like I voted for Amy Klobuchar because I went Eenie Meanie Miney Moe and I'm like that's nuts.
But a large portion of the electorate does that.
Oh I like their last name like oh no.
That's what it drives me.
It drives me that I hear people use Eenie Meanie Miney Moe to pick what they watched first on Disney Plus instead of taking the boogity challenge.
It drives me out of my mind.
I need to watch Mr. Boogity first.
There's some weird movie we've watched.
People are excited about it.
Boogity challenge worked out great.
With educated Disney Plus viewers.
Yes.
I wonder.
I'll have to look into it later but I do wonder if there are like fan page Facebook for rides specifically because obviously there's plenty of Disney and Disneyland.
This is good content for the future.
Yeah.
For like Peter Pan 2 we'll see if we can find specific Facebook groups and see how much drama there is.
If people like the update in 1983 better than they liked it in 2015 maybe.
There was definitely because I'm on like Oh My Disney and like a bunch of those Disney things when the whole Pirates where they switched out the wenches.
There was so much on Instagram no less.
That's not even I mean I guess it's owned by Facebook.
Yeah.
But all the fighting about it I saw on Insta with all the Disney peeps.
It's crazy.
Yeah.
You talked about the Imagineering story early and it's funny how early episodes are like and then they figured out how to make a ghost that was alive and then later episodes and fan backlash and toxic Facebook.
This has to be in the Imagineering.
Boo.
The 2010s are terrible.
Yes.
They're over.
They're over and they were terrible.
They were terrible.
I was going to say.
2020s will be great.
Yeah.
Everything's going to be fine from here on out but that 10 years.
I mean in the 1980s there was a lot of controversy around like Peter Pan in the parks because when they redid Fantasyland I mean you hear Tony Baxter talk about like yeah we really it felt kind of like a gamble to just shut down all this stuff for a long time and then they took out the pirate ship and Skull Rock and like they were thinking maybe they'd move it but then the pirate ship had rotted.
It pretty much just fell apart when they tried to pick it up.
There's a yeah there's a lot more early Disney and a lot more Peter Pan presence with that ship and the rock and now it is down.
Now it is the it is this ride and it's we do we think that they took things from the ship and put them in the ride like lanterns and stuff or is that not true.
They said the yes.
According to yesterworld.
Yes.
They're not sure about lanterns up with that hook there's like one hook like Captain Hook hook that you can see sort of right when the ride starts that they may they thinks was saved from the restaurant.
I think some set dressing.
Yeah.
Okay.
Very mild.
There's nothing like crazy.
There's nothing chicken of the sea branded.
That's what that ship was.
It was a chicken of the sea restaurant.
Oh I didn't I didn't know that.
So I believe so.
Yes.
Wow.
Yeah my mom was I think am I making that up.
No you're right.
You're on.
Trust me.
I will assure you it was definitely chicken of the sea diet that I never lived to see the chicken of the sea to eat a chicken of the sea branded tuna sandwich.
Wow.
And a cup of Folger's coffee and all the goods the good stuff.
Yeah.
And then yeah with a side of Fritos and the and Jemima syrup and all of odd brands in the early days.
Yeah I mean we did live through the 2000s where for a little while they're like well I guess people like wheat bread now and everything was served on like wheat buns like weird plasticky wheat buns.
And then it has swung back.
I mean this is one of the episodes we can't get off on a wheat tangent but I feel like wheat has swung back.
We was like the classier healthier choice for a while.
And now everyone's like well wheat is like Monsanto and that's all processed and we should why bother.
I mean obviously bread is bad now in general but wheat is now I would I'll pick white bread over wheat bread now whereas I used to be like well I'm Mike used to give me such a hard time for buying white bread for buying sourdough bread and I'm an idiot because I don't know what's going on.
I don't know anything about health.
I like the vitamin water.
I thought there was full of vitamins.
I will say like Cheapy Brioche or like the New England style like buns that are like or like Hawaiian sweet rolls cut down the middle.
It's like oh I'd always rather that than something like crappy wheat.
Well you were right. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I formally apologize.
Who knew the wheat bread controversy would be solved on Peter Pan.
Yeah I didn't.
Incredible.
I didn't know.
You really never have to grow up in Neverland.
Peter Pan would be like I don't want to know about all this bread stuff.
I want to be a little boy forever.
They don't really address what the Lost Boys eat.
I mean in Hook they do.
Of course.
They eat candy and ice cream.
They eat a bunch of gloop.
They eat a bunch of colored clay.
Yeah.
There's so many different Peter Pans.
Yeah a ton.
There is a new Peter Pan movie every three years.
I was thinking I was coming into this episode thinking I like the ride a lot.
I'm not that fond of Peter Pan and I rewatched the movie to see like what is my problem with this because I think I'm a little creeped out by some things about it in general.
And I was like but I like the ride.
I like the world.
I like being on a pirate ship and I like going to Skull Rock and I like Captain Hook and I realized what I don't like and it is Peter Pan himself.
Oh interesting.
He is a selfish nuisance.
In my memory he's nothing but horrible to Wendy.
And then I watched it and confirmed this that one of their first interactions is that he shows up and he's like a celebrity to them because they're always telling stories about him.
And then so she's kind of like verbal vomiting because like oh my god I'm talking to the real Peter Pan.
She's going on and on while she's sewing his shadow back.
She's doing work for him and he says wait wait I want to get it right.
Oh she's going on and on and then he's like girls talk too much.
Yeah that is really harsh.
Well get on with it girl.
What is this all he's like women need shopping.
Shut up and sew.
I'm a little boy with a lot of energy.
I need that shadow on me ASAP.
Oh I was going to say his shadow the name of the guy who wrote the game but it's mystery.
He's like Peter Pan read the game and he's negging Wendy.
Oh yes sure sure sure.
I feel like he's not very nice to Tinkerbell either.
No he's not.
He pits them against each other and then she's she whispers or twinkles in his ear and Wendy's like what did what did she say and he says Tick says you're a bitch.
Tick says you're a big ugly girl.
This is awful.
This is why I don't care for I think the world is great.
I think he's terrible he's a boy who never grows up who dresses like an ice dancer all the time.
I don't I think he but I think this is never going to happen but I would like to can we just keep the world and replace the protagonist.
I don't want to see these weird British movies every three years with these creepy boys playing this terrible character.
I'm a big Mr. Smee guy.
Yeah now there we go.
He's a cool guy.
Good in the cartoon good as Bob Hoskins all good.
Oh Bob Hoskins is so great in that role.
While I'm calling for Disney Plus series how about Jason Sheridan is Smee.
Smee?
Like just called Smee?
Young Mr. Smee.
Young Mr. Smee it's before he meets Captain Hook.
Oh my gosh.
Young Smee it's like Young Pope or whatever.
Yes.
Young Sheridan.
Young Smee.
Young Pope.
Jason Sheridan is Young Smee.
I would love that.
Smee is clearly the brains of the operation poor Captain Hook is clearly shell shocked by his insane life.
You know there's a Smee character in The Princess and the Frog.
Do you remember that guy?
He's like the prince's assistant essentially.
Right.
But it is fascinating because it's like what would happen if Smee got to control because that guy sells out the prince.
I can't remember his name right now.
Yeah I don't care.
There's a lot of yeah it is a sort of.
Oh and I guess like sorry.
That's okay.
What's his name from Gaston?
LeFou.
I was going to say something about LeFou.
Oh yeah yeah yeah.
Isn't there's kind of isn't there kind of a bumbling little mermaid isn't there sort of a.
Oh oh.
Somebody's helping Prince Eric right or is that no he's like an older.
No but he's good though Prince Eric is good.
The Sultan is kind of like Smee.
Cogsworth.
Cogsworth is type two.
Yes little stuffy.
Bumbling.
Low status guy.
Who are very short.
Short.
The Queen's what the King and Alice in Wonderland.
Like that like that.
Next to the handsome playmaker or whatever.
Yeah.
Is Captain Hook handsome?
He no.
I just it was a thought I had.
I think Dustin Hoffman.
In the movie in Hook he is.
In Hook.
Yeah.
Isn't Jackman Hook in a movie?
Jackman I think is Hook.
Yeah.
He's not Pan he's Hook.
And Christopher Walken was in the musical the live musical.
That was bong.
Who is the hottest Hook?
It's Hoffman.
Yeah.
Are we forgetting some though?
I'm sure.
Or is it live action?
No in the other one.
Yeah.
Is it the animated one?
Is the animated one to anyone hotter than Hoffman?
I bet there are a lot of people who would say animated.
Yeah.
If you consider height the issue like if you think he's tall.
He is tall for everyone that's saying that they want tall in their bios or whatever.
But I'm realizing now Jason I feel bad because you're a shorter man and they're all the shorter
characters are all these bumbling snively often with like a like a much taller wife
who's mean to them.
Scott well look I just want to work.
That's fine.
You can be the first empowered Smee.
I don't want a partner who's mean to me.
I don't mind if they're taller than me.
That's usually been my dating experience.
That's fine.
Young Smee can.
I'm secure about that.
Young Smee is a reimagining of the legend of Smee too.
So he can be a different.
We don't have to go down the path.
This is going to be a Smee with agency.
Smee with agency.
Yeah I mean I've got to get jacked.
I got to get jacked.
Young Smee.
I got to get jacked to do some of these run Disney run universal events.
That's how you train.
And if I get jacked enough finally we can have a canon short Wolverine.
Wolverine in the comic books is five three.
I'm five one and a half.
So getting there.
Rod Serling.
I'm five four and I always remind people Rod Serling is five four.
Really?
I always thought he was a tall one.
Yeah.
And also I was going to say there's a very Smee like character in everyone's favorite
which is Time Enough At Last with Bridget Meredith where he steps on his glasses end
of the world and his wife is awful to him.
She is so mean.
Yeah and I'm like he didn't deserve what happened.
I don't know if anyone realizes at the end when they're like oh my God and then he all
he wants to do is read and when he finally gets to he steps on his glasses and it's like
no but he was nice the entire time and they were all shitty to him.
All he wanted to do was read and they made him feel like a dork.
So it doesn't make sense.
What Rod Serling is trying to say is life is unfair especially if you're a dork.
Jordan Peele I am available to do a remake of Time Enough At Last as well.
But anyway that was a very Smee like character.
Yes.
I'm curious I like that I want to know hottest hook but I also want to know hottest short
king.
Of all of these guys of all of these little.
It's uncouth to nominate yourself.
Jason number one for casting.
Hot short king Jason Sheridan number one number two Wolverine.
Can we put fictional character with.
But actually it's huge how tall is Hugh Jackman.
Well but that's the thing Wolverine in the movie is very tall but it's Hugh Jackman not
as tall.
I think he's like 5'10 or 5'11 maybe taller.
I think Tom Cruise is also 5'4.
There's actually like a list it makes me feel good.
I have like a list of all the celebrities that are also my height.
Whoa I am curious below the list.
I think it's bizarre that Jackman has been tall hook and small Wolverine.
Oh yeah good point.
He's 6'2 by the way he's tall.
Oh he's tall.
Never mind.
OK so Dustin Hoffman is my height he's 5'4.
What?
Wow you're a hooks height.
You're a hook.
Well he really commanded that in a way.
See it's all about your personality.
Personality the way they shoot it.
Tom Cruise, Jet Li, Ben Stiller and Charlie Chaplin.
Stars.
Wow.
Ben Stiller is that?
And Seth Green.
Did I say that?
Yeah.
Wow that's a good line up.
That's pretty good.
So we've come up with a couple different shows here today.
I feel very productive on this one.
Yeah yeah yeah.
A lot of show ideas.
Let's make sure we cover.
We should start winding it down.
So besides show ideas Hot Short Kings.
Yeah yeah.
Hot Short Kings.
I think I'm the most curious to give some love to.
I mean I don't want to discount Wolverine or Jason.
But I want to give some love to one of these short kings who has a big tall wife who's mean to them.
Within those characters who's the hottest.
Let's make them feel better.
Oh OK.
I see what you're saying.
This is tough because some of these characters are like a foot tall.
But I don't even have a front runner.
I have to think about this.
Audience tell us.
Audience will tell us.
How does Short King.
And it can be Jason.
I feel like I should mention we haven't really talked about the crocodile.
Great.
I like the crocodile.
I think I used to be scared of him as a kid because he's scary and a hook like he's mounted.
But then he does eat Dustin Hoffman at the end.
But like I think I was even a little nervous about him at the ride.
But as I got a little older he's like oh no the enemy of our enemy is our friend like the crocodile is good.
Another thing that they use that design it looks like in Princess and the Frog with that.
Very similar.
Yes.
That's a gator.
But like yeah.
Yeah they're in the same like family.
They're big happy dudes.
Yes.
They like clap and whatnot.
He's very humanistic.
Hrugarius perhaps.
In all of the in all of the Peter Pan's worldwide the scene of hook with his legs on either side of the the crocodiles jaws is wonderful.
Yeah I was going to say like all of these scenes at the end I like when they're on the pirate ship.
I like it feels like I can I probably could touch all their faces if I wanted to like it's so close.
And last time I was on it I was like this feels too close and I'm surprised it's not happened or somebody like knocks hook off of the crocodile or like puts his foot out and does it.
Banned forever.
Yes or like yeah had like an umbrella because you can bring an umbrella on the ride.
Easily smack people ideas.
You're OK.
I should probably edit this out.
Lose these because then I'll be it'll be traced back to me and then they'll be able to source.
We know who planted the idea.
There's a rash of umbrella hits to the face to Captain Hook and it's all because I just said that this was a Manchurian candidate situation.
They were patsy's and I intended them with this episode.
I accepted them.
I tended them.
I'd like to give credit to the the again all these some of these scenes you think have always been there.
It came in much later and that the sword fight on the mass.
Yeah.
Between Peter and Captain Hook was a Disney World invention and then added later.
Yes.
Disneyland.
But that feels like it always should have been there and Disney World did it first.
And it's very good.
And the mermaid lagoon was Disney World first and then they added it to Disneyland later.
That is speaking of mermaids unique to the Paris one.
It seems like the Paris one ends in a seed, which is like full size sexy lady.
So the French folks, the French.
This was another problem I had with the film where Peter shows up and all of the mermaids just swooning over him.
They just like it's their voices are like orgasmic like, oh, Peter.
And he's like, hey, girls, want to hear about my sword fights?
And like, why would they be?
They're all like pushing each other away to like, no, me, I want to be, you know, women, you love a grown man.
You love a man who's a little boy forever, who wears a little hat with a feather.
Well, that's just how guys like back then it was like women were for you.
Like the world is yours and women are specifically made for you.
I mean, it's true.
That's like, sure.
And that's why it was such a big deal.
I mean, I talked with Pedro Herra, who's Bell, like it was such a big deal.
Her character was totally different.
She was like, get married me?
No.
Like, you know, and she eventually fell for a prince who was ugly.
Apparently, I thought he was very cute.
But like, you know, she really fell in love with her heart, not her eyes.
But yeah, she read and that's what made her weird.
And it was just a book.
Yeah.
These ideas.
So Peter Pan is kind of like, you know, leftover from that world where it was like, this is, you know, a little what would a little boy going through puberty want?
Like half naked women and like sword fights and like a following of like little pudgy kids that like look up to him.
You know, I know two women who I make fight over who gets me and then a different group of five women who also fight over me.
OK, pretty much everybody's looking at me at all times.
God is motion capture pan and a new Disney Peter Pan.
Oh, yeah.
So you'll be a little boy, but you'll have the balls on your.
No, no, no.
I don't want to move like that.
You have to.
I don't want to have to be in a little hat.
You have to be.
No, I'm not.
This this show idea is canceled.
All right.
Jason will do it.
I was going to say in several adaptations, they've had a girl play that part just because I end up looking, you know, mainly when boys get to that age, they are kind of transitioning so they don't sound exactly and look as like little twinkish as he is.
He's very twinkie.
And and I would honestly rather see that.
I'd rather see a queer girl that's like, you know, oh, I have all these women that love me.
You know, like that could get updated.
Well, on the stage traditionally.
Yeah.
Peter Pan.
And Alison Williams was Peter Pan.
Right.
In the last NBC.
Yeah.
All right.
So fine.
Scott isn't going to do it.
You're off the hook.
All right.
I do.
More progressive if I don't.
Good excuse.
If we're talking, you know, children, I do have a request from the listeners, a call for art in the queue for the for Peter Pan's flight in Florida.
There's these darling little portraits.
If someone could draw us in this style, that would really make my day.
I'll post this on the Twitter, sending out a call for this to all of our talented artists.
I think that take precedent over drawing you as young Smee.
I mean, also do that.
But maybe live hand in hand.
Seems like I haven't.
I must have been drawn.
Little Michael there with the little hat.
Yeah, all of them are there Sunday best.
They're in their Sunday best when you get you sit for a picture.
Yeah.
Well, draw me however you want.
She's not in a feathered hat.
But I'm causing it to happen.
Yeah, I know.
There's going to be some horrible Peter Pan art that comes out.
Maybe don't hang on.
I secretly.
This is the Streisand effect.
I just made it happen.
Send it to me.
No, no, no.
I'll set up a secret email called Scott is pan at Gmail dot com.
Email that email address with your pictures of Scott as pan.
I will raise Scott is pan.
That's the podcast, the ride on sensor.
Yeah, we can talk about all the forbidden pans.
You know, I am mostly out of my notes.
The last thing I'll say is that the volcano near in the Neverland scene, it's that's like the volcano.
It's that's like bubbling.
It's just tiny styrofoam balls and there's air blowing on it.
That's how they get the effect.
Very cool.
Oh, oh, is that closing thoughts from you?
Don't do anything to the captain.
Don't smell him with an umbrella.
No, and just like I still am such a fan of the London town.
Yeah.
Fly over and the kids landing on the clock tower hand.
Oh, that's very cool.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
And those little projection enhancements of all.
There's a lot of projection going on in Shanghai.
It's also nice.
It's a lot of the sword fight happens like going screen to screen and then out of the
math, the mast with projections and I don't know all the recent imagineers have done such
great jobs with all these reds.
It's such a perfect example of I mean, they kind of do it with other rides, but it seems
like this one gets almost the most like incremental love out of every ride because you think like
if we've talked about Haunted Mansion, like there's definitely things you could do to
plus that up and make some effects cooler, but it feels like pan.
They're all like everyone's obsessed with pan and like perfecting pan.
Yeah.
You know, in a fun way.
It's kind of everyone's favorite.
Although I have a theory that you're either a toad person or a pan.
Well, you both said you both said and I said technically I think I like pan better, but
I love toad.
Yeah.
I think toad people came to be because the line was too long.
So then they were like, well, I just got to go on toad then and then you're just like keep riding that ride every time you come.
It does make it more appealing.
And I did in Japan get to because of rain.
I got to achieve the dream of a zero weight Peter Pan's flight, which was wonderful and transcendent.
And yeah, try to go when it's raining like crazy and maybe you'll get on this ride in a reasonable amount of time.
One of the best descriptions of pan, of course, and Tony Baxter always talks about this quote, surprisingly well preserved in a lot of places.
Ray Bradbury sent Walt Disney a note saying, I will be eternally grateful today.
I flew out of a child's bedroom window in a pirate galleon on my way to the stars.
It had nothing to do with the ride either.
It was a bit of a character.
Geez.
Well, that sounds a fun day for me as you survive podcasts, the ride.
Thanks for being here.
That was a blessed of a topic.
Let's exit through the gift shop.
Is there anything you'd like to plug?
Yeah, my podcast, Nerdificent, it's wherever you get your podcast.
You can follow me at Ms. Danny Fernandez.
It's M S D A N I F E R N A N D E Z.
And oh, I have a book.
I'm in a book on audible.
Well, you can also get it in paperback.
It's called The Good Immigrant.
It's a collection of essays from actors and writers of color.
There's a UK edition and then we did an American edition.
So it's 26 writers reflect on America.
And you can listen to me read my essay on audible.
Cool. Great.
Check it out.
And of course, sign up for any and all Baby Yoda groups.
Just start clicking on them.
If you have Ralph in other countries, please send me my character saying my name in different languages.
Geez, that's great.
Yes.
You need a super cut of that.
Yeah, we have.
I've looked at the things.
There are people in other countries listening.
So if you have that Blu-ray or something, yes, send a little clip.
Yeah, that's fun.
I think I technically could also just turn the language setting on my.
This is more fun, though.
This is more interactive.
It's true.
You need the pal.
You need the pal copy.
Oh, yeah.
You'll see specific.
Yeah.
True.
So yeah.
And as for us, follow us on Twitter, Instagram and Facebook and subscribe to podcast thread.
The second gate at Patreon dot com slash podcast.
The ride full Fabio Goose incident.
So to come and yeah, just remember that hashtag Scott is pants.
God damn it.
Just remember how did I've gotten off easy lately?
I think I'm going to have to make the email address.
Got his pan at Gmail.
As the darling children.
If it's a separate email that I don't have to look at, then yeah, full send them to send them to Mike.
You guys creep out with these horrible photos.
I'll figure out a way when to spring it on you at the worst possible time.
So, yeah, don't send it to be on stage.
It'll be on a stage somewhere.
Don't send it to Twitter.
Don't even let him know.
He'll forget about it after this record and then send it.
Yeah, email.
Side note, we've come to a decision that we are our live recording career is over.
There will be no more live shows.
I will no longer be sorting.
Sorry, I think you're cutting out.
I think your mic is cutting out.
That's the only just oh, yes, got your mic is broken.
I wait.
Yeah, you're not.
I can't hear you.
That's too bad.
All right.
Well, anyway, Scott is pan at Gmail.
Jason, you have anything to say?
No, draw.
Yeah, give us those short kings.
Draw some darling children.
Scott is pan.
Most importantly, Scott is got his pan.
Forever.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts.com and subscribe to our shows
on Apple podcasts, Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram at
forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.