Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast is not meant to offend any religious listeners, but we're
certainly okay if it offends any crooked televangelists.
If you are sensitive to goth satans, chickens rising from the dead, or major themed mini-golf,
do not proceed into the Holy Land experience on podcast The Ride.
A very solemn Good Friday to you all.
Welcome to podcast The Reverent Ride.
I'm somber Scott Gardner, joined by mournful Mike Carlson.
Hello, I'm Michael.
Thank you for joining us, Michael, and also a quite joyless Jason Sheridan.
Forgive us, Father, for we know not what we do.
We know not what we do.
We know exactly what we do, I suppose.
We know not what those people thousands of years ago did to Jesus our Lord.
It is Good Friday, if you're listening to this, on the day that it is released, and I'm being
especially sad in keeping with my parents' wishes as I grew up.
As I may have mentioned long ago on the show, they always told me that I needed to be very
sad on Good Friday because that's the day that Jesus died, particularly peak sadness
from noon to three because those were the hours that the events of the Passion took
place.
While we do owe a theme park podcast today, it's going to be as mournful as I had to be
as a child.
Scott, can I ask a question?
I sense I am not I was not raised nearly as religiously.
Was it Western Time?
Was it Pacific Time?
One to three? Or were you just it was that sort of a symbolic
Yeah, it was a symbolic time.
Are you on Jerusalem time?
Were you on Judea?
The Judea time zone?
I don't know. I mean, yes, that's a very good point.
And I was not raised in the kind of religious way where I think that Jesus lived in Utah.
So it was not it was not mountain time.
I think it's, you know, it's a very good point.
You have to switch it to New Year's rules, I think.
Right.
We have midnight.
You know, it's not it's New Year's one time zone at a time.
And Jesus suffered one time zone at a time.
Right. I'm not trying to be a wise acre here or anything.
I'm just I was just asking questions.
I'm just asking questions like I often do on the show.
I'll be the wise acre, as usual.
So I was raised Presbyterian, but like a very chill, like kind of Protestant ism.
Like there's branches of Presbyterianism that deal a lot with Calvinism, which says,
like, when you're born, it's already pre-decided that you are good or bad.
And we didn't really get into any of that.
It was more like Church on the Simpsons or whatever, where they just went every Sunday.
And our pastors were usually pretty chill and would go to great lengths to try to fit
topical thing, like not scary topical news stuff.
But like, you know, I was at the mall this weekend and I.
I saw kids having a good time together and it reminded me of the apostles, you know,
like that kind of shit.
They were always talking about how they were at the ball.
It wasn't like Jeannie at California Adventure when he would be like, well, I was watching
Snooki on the television and she reminded me.
I, you know, I think every now and then they'd be like, you know, I'm no.
Yeah, I'm no Snooki like, you know, a little bit, a little bit.
He was around when you were a kid.
Yeah.
Whoever Snooki was when you were a child.
I yeah, like Tonya Harding, Lorraine Bobbitt.
Yeah, was it Lorraine? Yeah, I was watching Lorraine Bobbitt on the television the other night.
And I, I feel like even that would have been like too bawdy.
My main memories of Church was a lot of nice older people who occasionally would get very
frustrated by like, can you believe who's at Deacon now?
Like, you know, that sort of like inner inner inner personal politics sort of of stuff.
But I don't think I ever had the big rebellion against like the big like a lot of people
our age, I feel like, you know, bought a Richard Dawkins or who was the other who was the
other shithead? The one who died?
Hitchens, Christopher Hitchens.
Yeah, we get those like I never went in for that garbage.
Well, don't don't forget that today's topic that there was a scene filmed at the Holy
Land Experience in Orlando at in Bill Maher's documentary, Religious.
I did forget that.
I also I actually also forgot that.
But once you said a scene filmed, I knew exactly how that sentence was going to end.
Bill Maher meets Jesus.
I mean, that's cool. That's your trailer right there.
Yeah, that's highly absurd.
I have not seen Bill Maher's Religious.
I haven't. I mean, he's a scumbag, too.
That was my thinking in not rewatching it for this episode.
As much as I wanted to experience all Holy Land Experience media, I didn't watch the
Bill Maher clip because I don't hate myself.
Yeah. Yeah, fair.
I the only thing we really did on Good Friday was just not eat meat and not the whole
month. Just Good Friday.
That that sticks out in my mind.
And the other thing that sticks out, you know, because you said like, yes, it's a
somber. It's Good Friday.
I was very concerned. Yes.
Were we being sacrilegious in this episode?
But then the freaks who the multiple freaks who have owned this theme park.
This might be the most sacrilegious thing I've ever seen.
This establishment.
It kind of the entire thing is what Jesus would have torn down, you know, everybody
selling their wares in the church.
You know, if he got into that big rage fit, tearing apart the merchandise stands or
whatever that was.
Yeah, he'd go ape shit at the Holy Land Experience.
Oh, owners who I believe would often say that Jesus wants you to be rich.
I believe that was the sentiment.
So probably still is what you're talking about, Michael, is called the prosperity
gospel. And this is a big thing with televangelists.
Now, yes, I you know what?
Let's establish again.
Yes, we're talking about the Holy Land Experience in Orlando, the now pretty much
defunct Holy Land Experience because they fired everyone back in February.
They fired everyone before it became trendy to fire everyone.
What was the covid-19 and all?
But even before several months before, yeah, they had pretty much like shut down
operations and the people they fired were all the people in the shows.
And I think they're bread and butter are the shows because if you've never been to
this place or don't know anything about this place, there's no rides.
There's no 3D movies there.
You know, it's it's it's shows, it's passion plays and stuff.
So you get rid of the actors and you got nothing.
Yeah, so that means they would have had to fire multiple Jesus's.
And I feel like they wouldn't have been excited to turn the other cheek when they
were getting fired.
Because I know, I mean, there's a circuit, there's a circuit, there's a scene in
flow like people make careers working in the parks in Florida.
And like, I'm sure plenty of people who worked here were just, you know, actors
were just professional actors.
I think so.
I know. So I even there was a a vice article that I looked at about this place that
made mention of that one of the primary Jesus's that they use there had
transferred. He was originally led to Orlando to be an actor and worked for
several years as Gaston at MGM Studios.
So, yeah, somebody moved from from Gaston to Jesus and sometimes in a shortage of
actors would for the day play Satan.
Oh, my gosh. Yeah, same as a guy.
I'm not going to say I'm not going to say OMG with Geo.
I'm going to say gosh today, by the way.
That's a declaration. Oh, got it.
That's good. I appreciate that for Good Friday.
Just for today, I was going to say with the people playing Jesus, is it all fake
beards? Do we know this?
The picture I saw in the I think it was the Tampa Bay Times looked like a pretty
real beard like he had grown the long hair and grown the beard.
I could be wrong, but that's pretty good.
Yeah, you have to really commit to that character.
You can't you can't jump around playing Jesus and then go over into the into the
Disney parks. I don't know who that was.
There a bearded character even they would allow you to play.
Well, I can't flame rider from Tangled kind of has that like 2000 shins strap
kind of. Yeah, but that's not that's not Jesus.
Jesus doesn't know that Jesus.
No. Who's the most Christ like Disney character?
That's a good point. Does anybody?
Yeah. Do we have long hair and facial hair on anybody?
I mean, I'm trying to think like Christ like looks wise.
Huh? That's a good question.
I mean, because we're not talking personality wise, it's obviously Mickey Mouse.
Well, I was going to say Scrooge McDuck.
It's the most Christ like.
Yes, because he has a lot of money and obviously he helps everyone with his money.
I'm assuming. Yeah, but I mean, it's more likely a camel's got to get through the eye
of the needle than Scrooge is going to, you know.
All right. Good point.
I wait. I have some I have some thoughts.
I Google Disney character beard.
And besides just a strange trend of people putting beards on characters like Jasmine
and Ariel, the characters with beards, we got Triton.
We OK, we got.
Oh, and somebody did a Photoshop of Triton without a beard.
And he looks exactly like Jay Leno.
Whoa, really? Yeah.
The chin they filled in for him is.
Yes. Yeah.
Just look at Disney character beard.
You'll see it. So Leno-esque.
You'll see a little a little Bill Clinton, too.
May you know, maybe even a little more Bill Clinton, but big gray eyebrows.
Yeah, maybe maybe more Leno body wise.
I think Leno is in better shape than Clinton.
And and obviously Triton is ripped.
Oh, yeah, he does. You're right.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, doesn't he?
Yeah. So now, you know, yeah, you shave that beard off of Triton and he's Jay Leno.
And on the ride, though, of course, we've talked about this.
He is jacked and he looks like young and handsome on that ride.
And this Little Mermaid ride.
I can't help but stop and stare at that six pack, 12 pack.
It's a big pack.
It's at least six, if not eight.
Who else with beards? Zeus.
I don't think I don't think we got a Zeus walk around in the parks anywhere. No.
Yeah. Does Mufasa technically have a beard?
I guess it gets complicated when you get into the animal kingdom.
Yeah, but that's not going to work.
That's not going to you're not going to be able to apply a human beard
to a Mufasa walk around.
Now, very odd.
And thank God, by the way, that it's just plush looking characters
that they haven't like put on that.
I'm so glad that we don't have Zubali zoos walking around
the Disney parks like cats level, a bunch of fur taped to people's faces.
I don't want to assume animals.
I don't want those at Disney parks, but I do want them somewhere.
And I don't know where maybe it's Halloween Horror Nights.
Maybe there's a Zubali zoo, Halloween Horror Nights maze.
I mean, that honestly, now that I say it is a great idea.
Well, cats universal.
The oh, good point.
Mays at Halloween Horror Nights would be.
Oh, my gosh. Wow.
Oh, I said, oh, my gosh. Oh, my gosh. It'd be huge.
Yeah. Wow. That's such a good idea.
And like Ghostbusters, Ghostbusters is like, you know,
it has got scary elements, but mostly a comedy.
And they did a maze last year.
If there's ever if there's ever a Halloween Horror Nights again,
if there's a theme park open,
cats should definitely be on the list for those mazes. Geez.
Yeah, that's Instagram City.
I mean, everybody just embracing the the frighteningness of cats, admitting it.
And then like it'd be fun to just acknowledge that like, you know,
like to like litter the the the maze of the set or whatever
with unwanted prints of cats or just, you know, the decaying sets
because nobody nobody wants to touch them again.
They're all cursed items.
Oh, yeah. Wow. That would be the hit.
That would be the hit, honestly. Yeah. Yeah.
They got to do it. Love that. Yeah. Yeah.
All right. We're just giving that out for free.
Yeah. Do your cat's maze.
Embrace the embrace the fright and amaze.
I don't think it's they'd have to buy the rights to this,
but amaze with original Sonic.
Just do Sonic with the teeth with the teeth.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
They should just give a lot of I mean, they should just be amazed
with like a random assortment of cartoon characters with those teeth.
Like whatever. Yeah.
That's the thing I've seen online where people do that face
app where they put the teeth on the Disney characters, the human teeth.
What's the group?
What's the what's the name of the group that owns the all the comic strips
on Toon Lagoon?
Oh, is that King Features?
King's Features features
sending a kid. Yeah.
King Features Syndicate maze, but all with human teeth.
So like Beetle Bailey, but then with like actual human teeth.
And that's in the maze because they have they obviously have a deal with Universal.
Does he not have to?
You're just saying with like realistic teeth.
Yeah, realistic teeth and Heathcliff with realistic teeth.
Who else? I mean, there's a lot of Marmaduke with real human teeth.
Um, yeah, I just Googled Beetle Bailey teeth
just kind of without thinking while you were talking.
And there's there's a lot of results.
He's like dealt there's there's dental work comes up frequently in Beetle Bailey.
Does he have those rounded teeth? Am I wrong?
No, they have just kind of like dumb like squares and only like three of them, you know.
Oh, OK, I got it.
Well, he's he'll have human teeth soon enough.
Is Beetle Bailey the chubbier one? Who is Beetle Bailey?
No, no, he's skinny.
He's skinny. The chef is the chubby one.
That's who I'm looking at with a green chef's hat.
Yeah. OK.
Beetle was Beetle Bailey.
Was he a rip off of Gomer Pyle or was he based or was Gomer Pyle based on him?
You know, it's hard to tell.
You know, everyone had funny stories from the war days.
So so you think it was all just based on funny war stories?
Got it. They were all they were both derived from the same source.
I think so. Yeah.
Well, we'll do that on the Jim Neighbors slash Beetle Bailey episode.
And by the way, who you referred to as the chef, we're talking about Sergeant Snorkel.
It is. What do you mean, chef?
Isn't he a chef?
He's got a hat that's kind of like a chef's hat.
Oh, that's what I think.
But Beetle Bailey is constant.
Like he's always being punished by peeling potatoes.
I think I just conflated the two.
Yeah.
I don't know where Sergeant Snorkel works on the base or whatever.
So it could be. Yeah, not sure.
Well, again, a thing that we'll get to because we have nothing but time.
But Sergeant Snorkel is actually he ends up getting killed by Vincent D'Onofrio.
Old metal jacket.
That's just metal jacket.
They went very realistic with the blood just for that one,
just for that one, Beetle Bailey.
And he did have human teeth in that one, too.
That they identified him.
Oh, dear. Oh, my gosh.
This is getting upsetting.
We better switch it back to let's let's go back to a holy place, to the to the holy land.
As we said, it's you know, it's Easter weekend right now.
It'll be Easter very soon.
And I I thought it'd be fun to cover a religious park.
There's a couple of those. I wasn't sure which was which.
You know, at some point, I'd love to get to the the Jim Baker Park
that still sits abandoned wherever that is.
I'd love to do that one.
But this one felt relevant because all year it's been teetering on,
is this going to is this going to stay open or not?
It feels relevant to me personally, too, because I don't think I knew it existed.
But when we all went to Orlando a couple of months ago, we passed by it a few times
because it's it's pretty close to Universal Studios.
You're definitely seeing it off the side of the road
if you're going to Universal or to the Orlando airport.
Yeah. Yeah.
And there's like apartments and stuff close,
but there's a target across the street from this place.
It's right in the mix.
Yeah. The problem is, we really like you need like three weeks in Orlando.
That's the the issue is like I was there for like
we were there for like five days.
You got to hit all the big stuff, but you need an extra week for stuff like this.
And honestly, as theme park journalists, we should have gone there.
We who knew suggested it, but I think our our like swing day,
we kind of used to find our street in Margarita Village.
Yes, for sure. No regrets there.
No, no regrets.
And of course, like, who knows how long that'll be there.
So we needed to get there then. Yeah.
Oh, yeah. How are they doing in virus world?
Yeah, I mean, it might be fine because it's empty.
So yeah, boy, it's eerie.
I've been people have been sending me those helicopter shots of
seeing Margaritaville, Orlando, and nobody's walking around.
Construction has just stopped.
So off putting me staying inside, there's no sign that anyone actually lives there.
So weird. There's nobody in bonkers.
There's no line waiting to get into bonkers.
There's nobody. I think they I hate to say it.
I think they may have ended the influencer program at Island H2O Live.
We might not get to sponsor an influencer, and it's entirely because of the virus
and certainly would not have just happened in a week anyway.
Yeah. What if they get like a big amount of bailout money from the government
that allows them to continue and they blame because they blame everything on the virus.
But in reality, Michael, it's funny you say that because the Holy Land
website does have a banner at the top saying like due to Corona,
we're going to be closed from March 10th to April 14th.
And I can't help but think that's not accurate.
I mean, obviously, it's too soon to reopen.
But also, like, I feel like after you fire everyone,
you can't really put up warnings like that. Right.
Well, I mean, what does that really mean?
That means that they can't open and like you can't go to the restaurant or the gift shop, really.
Is there a restaurant? Right.
There's four restaurants. Yeah.
Yeah. And I mean, I think they would probably reopen the.
Is it I believe it's called the Church of All Nations?
It's got a very unsettling cross logo.
Coen Coen Church of All Nations.
It looks real like handmade.
It's still well, and one of the restaurants is related to that.
And it's next to it.
So it's called Coen Bistro.
And we'll we'll get to the restaurants later.
I will get to the restaurant because there is a really good one.
Oh, good, good. OK, OK.
I think maybe we owe just a really
cliffhanger explanation of what this place is.
I don't even feel qualified to do it exactly.
I mean, there's when you look at it from the side of the road, a lot of it is very
gaudy and palatial.
But if you actually go into this themed experience,
they sometimes kind of called a theme park.
But as I said, there's no rides.
I don't know how accurate that is.
But a lot of it is recreating
the you know, the old the old Bible world.
What city are we talking Jerusalem?
Jude, I I forget what year I did have it, but it's Judea.
OK, I see. Uh huh.
Yeah, because they have I was just going to say they.
It says there's a there's a thing that says on the map.
I'm looking at the map now and one of the exhibits or whatever you would call it,
Jerusalem model AD66.
But I don't know if that's the whole I don't think that's actually representative
of the entire land.
No, that's like a tabletop model.
That's just a model of Jerusalem.
AD66. Oh, I have it.
It is it's recreates the architecture and themes of the ancient city of Jerusalem
in first century Judea,
which one of the articles I read pointed out how that requires people to be the
theme requires all the employees who used to be there to like, you know,
where a lot of, you know, very intense, thick, old fashioned headwear,
like everybody's head is is wrapped up.
And that includes when it's, you know, the dead heat of August,
the guy at the like the coffee shop has to have his his head wrapped up a bunch of
times, just sweating bullets.
So fun place to work.
Yeah, I'll say this.
I don't think the costumes are convenient for the actors, but the costuming is very
good. I mean, there's a lot of great seamstresses down in Orlando's, you know,
people who make costumes and all.
So that makes sense to me that they went all out on the costuming.
Yes, that's all that's all pretty strong.
There's maybe some some squabbling you could do about Satan's wardrobe.
But we'll get to that a little bit.
But so, yeah, you got to know you.
You go there for a couple of hours.
I think like probably a lot of church groups would go out of school groups would go.
And it's, you know, partially you're we're recreating what life was like in the first
century. And then there's a couple of big show venues.
There's a giant indoor one that I think also doubles as a place where they can tape
Praise the Lord because this place is owned by the Trinity Broadcasting Network.
But, you know, we'll cover the history there, but also like an outdoor amphitheater.
So it's it's a lot of live entertainment and then something called the Scriptorium,
which is a collection of biblical related artifacts.
Yeah, I have a lot of questions about the Scriptorium.
Where where did you get a hold of these gang?
And how did you get a hold of these?
Because like, what country what country are these all from?
Because I don't think they're native to central Florida.
Like, you know, you know, Indiana Jones saying stuff belongs in a museum.
I think we've come around now a little more towards like as the years go on, people,
people are a little more going like most of the stuff in the British Museum should be
returned to the countries they was founded.
Well, they didn't. OK, so it looks like it.
This was a preexisting collection by Robert von Campen
that was around, has been around since 1986.
So they like they bought a collection, moved it from Minnesota, sounds like.
OK, where where Jesus may have been, if he was if Jesus was that if all the Jesus
stuff happened in Utah, he might have made it up to Minnesota at some point.
So, yeah, a private collection.
I mean, that feels a little better than like Hobby Lobby pillaging, you know,
artifacts in Iraq.
So better. So.
So for me, who is, you know, was not so raised religious religiously,
this is kind of like a Doc on Dars situation where there are relics
from the past, from the history of the land.
That's sort of what I'm dealing with here.
I think so. Yeah. Yeah.
I didn't look too carefully at what's in the scriptorium, to be honest.
I see. Sorry, scriptorium fans.
If there was an I.G. 88 style robot or anything in there,
I don't I don't believe so.
There are robots around.
I think there is a robot in the scriptorium.
But again, I'll say I want to just do the overview first.
Got it. Got it. Got it. Sorry.
Can you just one one robot?
I'll explain. But I just as we're getting out like headlines and bullet points
about it, I think I think a big thing to say, like we said, it's unlike the,
you know, it's it's really near universal.
It's definitely designed to attract people who were there for for,
you know, for the tourists to try.
And if you're there for a little longer and you're doing your off the beaten
path stuff, your Gator lands and if you're a religious person,
this is a good place to go.
And because of just the way it's designed and that it is a religious place,
this is a a nonprofit tax free
theme park. It somehow qualifies.
It's sometimes described as a theme park, but also is nonprofit and does not pay taxes.
How did they get away with it?
Because they have one free day every year.
Just one. And the lines are out the fucking door.
Sorry, I'm swearing.
Oh, yeah.
I it's yeah.
Yeah, it gets really crazy on the free day.
And besides the free day, it is fifty dollars, fifty dollars,
which they don't pay any taxes.
I mean, they don't pay any taxes on.
Yeah. When it first opened, it was 1750.
Pretty cheap. Wow. Yeah.
They jacked it up to 50.
Oh, my God. I guess in the TBN era,
you're getting that that, you know, you're paying a TBN premium.
I was going to say, like, you know, I was just start to compare.
I initially when I saw that I was going to be like, oh, that's crazy.
And then like, you know, there's I have some maybe opinions on tax
exempt status for certain institutions that get a ton of money.
And where does that money go anyway?
That being said, there's a lot of stuff Disneyland doesn't pay taxes on in Anaheim.
Like, are you mean our church? Yes.
They are all good. Go for it.
They had the city of Anaheim build that parking structure
and they pay like a dollar to like,
I think I forget what it is like.
Disney owns it, right?
But they had Anaheim buy like pay for it and then Disney collects all the money
they make from the parking structure, I believe.
Yeah, something like that.
Something like that.
Anyway, I'm not saying I'm not saying Holy Land is off the hook for something like this.
I'm just saying, oh, wait a minute.
OK, yeah, that's all a bummer, I guess.
But I still I found it very moving when the white smoke was released from
from Cinderella's Castle to anoint Bob Chapek
and say goodbye to Pope Bob Iger the third.
It's a good yes. We all well, we were all we were all outside.
We were waiting, bated breath.
We all cried.
We all we all wiped.
We all cried and then wiped our faces with towels and saw Christ's face in each towel.
We were wearing our religious garments, which were retro Epcot shirts.
Basically the same thing.
I said Christ, I meant Triton.
We all saw Triton's face in our.
Oh, yeah, yeah. The Shroud of Triton.
Yes. Easy to confuse.
Yeah, really very strange place, this place, and that they're able to
to operate it that way.
It's it's been around since when.
When did it get to when did it get built?
Was it the 90s sometime?
2001. Oh, not until 2001.
OK, yeah. Property purchased in 89 and nothing was there until 2001.
Nothing was there until 2001.
And it was it was opened by a man named Marvin Rosenthal,
who was the founder of a group called Zion's Hope, which
the L.A. Times says strives to convert Jewish people to Christianity.
This was a fun flashback.
You know, you haven't heard about the Jews for Jesus a lot in the 20 in the 2000s.
You know, is a but the Jewish Defense League
was not wild about this guy and this organization and this theme park.
When it opened the same article,
Marvin Rosenthal was quoted as saying otherwise.
Are we targeting Jewish people with any kind of exclusivity?
The answer is absolutely no.
Nor do we believe that we are in the conversion business, said Rosenthal.
But for the first visitors to the park, followers of Rosenthal for years,
the exact opposite is true.
There are people coming to Christ through this ministry, said D.
Locklear, who added that Jews are the primary target.
Yes, that's mainly what he's trying to do is to try to reach the Jewish people.
So kind of a weird way to open a theme park.
A theme park meant for Jewish people to go to.
And hopefully by the end of the day, they have seen the Jewish people's
role in biblical events and gone, well, there's so many Jews in all these stories.
Maybe I should just be around also.
Yes, I'm a Christian now. Yeah.
Do you think there's one person that was converted from this?
I heard a story of the exact opposite of someone who had gone to Israel
and had been very moved at the Wailing Wall,
very holy site where people pray.
And the replica Wailing Wall
was so shitty at the Holy Land, they were very upset.
And, you know, not to not to jump around too much, but yes,
there's a replica Wailing Wall at this place where you.
And it looks like shit.
I know we say there's no bad fake rocks, but it looks like shit.
So the Wailing Wall would not have made it to the final four last year.
No, even now that we know about this place.
No, I don't think it's in there.
And I would not nominate the rock that moves out of the way
so Lazarus can come out of his tomb.
I'm not I'm not putting that one in there either.
Yeah, there's a there's a fake Wailing Wall.
But you like the real Wailing Wall,
you write prayers onto pieces of paper and slip them into the cracks.
And then the Holy Land experience gathers all of the prayer slips
and sends them to Jerusalem, where volunteers insert them
into the real Western Wall.
Insane that you can't enter office envelope prayers to the Wailing.
What the hell?
There should be like a bank pneumatic tube that takes it from Orlando
to the actual Wailing Wall.
It may as well be.
So that means like people they got to send somebody from Orlando
once a month has to fly to Jerusalem with a huge bag of slips.
Like you see people, you know, it's a very emotional experience for them.
And they're writing their note and praying for their loved one.
And then some guy walks up with several huge garbage bags
make way out of the way.
Letters to letters to Santa Claus.
Here's my question, though.
Do we have any proof that these actually make it?
No, no, no way.
These things get dumped right in the trash.
Let's be honest. Yeah.
Straight in the right behind the Holy Land experience into the marsh of Orlando.
The people who run this place seem like the type that they wouldn't pay for dumpsters.
They would just wait until Target closed and then Jimmy Thur's open like
nothing seems above board about this place.
I the other the other thing to consider, I don't think there
is there a replica of the Temple Mount
in this park, which is is adjacent to the Wailing Wall
in Jerusalem.
And it is a holy site for Christians, Jews and Muslims.
But I have to imagine this park, if it mentions it, does not do a good job
about talking about the other valid or, you know, the other important world religions.
You know, that would be a good guess.
I would I would venture.
But I don't have a confirmation of that.
Yeah, probably not so concerned with representation.
I wouldn't imagine.
I also say I don't know the the exact borders of where the Wailing Wall falls.
So when I said that person went to, I guess I should have said that person went to Jerusalem.
I please do not yell at me if I got the borders wrong.
We may be getting things wrong left and right.
Keep in mind, this is not a journalism podcast.
Yes, I do not know what good tides Jared Kushner has done this week
for the borders of Israel and Palestine.
Has he fixed it yet?
We might be it's we're recording this a couple like a week or so out.
So forgive us if it's out of date and Jared fix the Middle East.
Yeah, he's fixing Corona.
He's that's he's he can do both, though.
He's a Wunder kind.
Sure. Yeah, for sure.
So Marvin Rosenthal runs it for a while.
And I don't know a lot about what was happening then or how which which of the structures
and attractions were there then.
But in 2007, this place was taken over by TBN, the Trinity Broadcast Network,
which I don't know how exactly anybody's watching TBN today
because I don't have cable anymore for me in my head, a cable
mainstay, maybe not even cable.
You might have even you might have gotten it at one point, just like a regular channel.
But I definitely recall this just being so ubiquitous on TV,
not that my parents were watching it or anything.
It's you know, it's not a Catholic station.
And even they raised me in sort of a way like, yeah, these people are kind of quacks.
You know, so I wasn't super raised with this.
But I I do remember TBN on so aggressively, though.
I believe you can you can stream it on the Internet now for free.
Oh, for sure. Yeah.
And then it's odd. It is still carried by a lot of cable providers.
And yeah, they they believe me, if you go to the website,
you'll be able to find
all sorts of information about where to watch TBN.
Well, and I'm pretty sure people in the low 20s, high teens,
you'll probably come across a grip of televangelist.
I think so, yes.
And I could be wrong not to get on this tear again, but I believe TBN
is the home of my favorite talk show, Huckabee.
I'm pretty sure that's where Huckabee emanates.
Yeah, let me double.
I think so. Is that OAN?
Is that one America News?
Could be. Could be.
I forget. Huckabee is listed as a personality for TBN.
They list such they have like the big pastors like Rick Warren or Joel
Osteen, the Grahams, Billy and Franklin Graham.
Billy Graham, you might remember from telling Richard Nixon to bomb
the dykes in North Korea, which would have potentially resulted
in a million dead and the destruction of a country's economy.
Oh, but yeah, that that kind of came.
But Billy Graham, complicated man, also bailed Martin Luther
King out of jail once.
Billy Graham was very like they called him the people's pastor.
My grandmother loved him.
He was very, very media savvy.
But a weird guy, Franklin Graham
is in charge of a medical group, one of the medical groups
that has set up the field hospital in Central Park for Corona.
OK, and they are for making doctors sign
religious declarations that they believe homosexuality is a sin.
So you're talking about really? Yeah.
Oh, no.
Uh, this what is that?
That organization is also has Zion in the name.
Sorry, I got a bunch of links about the Graham family open.
Volunteers have to agree that transgender people don't exist.
Same sex marriage is a sin and gay people should be celibate
or risk damnation and eternal punishment.
No, no, no, no, no. Excuse me.
Samaritan's Purse, an evangelical Christian group.
That he is in charge of.
It's one of the people I believe in New York Hospital,
one of the groups mainly running that.
But this group is also involved in that field hospital.
Dear God, you want to change the topic right now
and make the rest of this episode about like creamsicles or something?
Yes, please. This is terrible.
Dear God. Now, hold on.
You don't think TBN, which once had a host say,
get Jesus on that credit card.
You don't think that's cool?
Well, I think TBN is very cool.
And I I actually have a personal story to tell about TBN
and its its flagship show, Praise the Lord,
which is able to be taped at the the Holy Land Experience.
So the in the night when was this?
This was, you know, the late 90s, I used to my family hung out in Newport Beach
a lot in Orange County.
And whenever we were driving down there on the 405,
very near the Mall South Coast Plaza and probably about 20 minutes south of Disneyland,
we we would on the 405 see this really crazy,
gaudy palace on the side of the road.
And if anyone listening is from Orange County, you definitely know this
as the headquarters of TBN.
A really bizarre to look at looks.
They do a good job with Christmas lights if you're driving down there at night.
During the Christmas season.
But we always pass by this and like, oh, weird.
What is that? Oh, it's TBN.
And it's like if you look at the photos of its offices,
it's just an office building in a TV studio that has the like
gross Trump idea of opulence.
It's like, you know, it's it's fountains and gold trim and paintings everywhere.
You can jam a painting.
There's big crazy thrones in the bathroom and, you know,
sheriffs pissing and fountains everywhere.
It's so crazy.
And I always wanted to go.
And I'd watch TBN and watch kind of like the kookier
televangelists, you know, people will be will be talking about
in relation to the Holy Land experience.
And and sometimes you'd see like, oh, you know, praise the Lord tapings are free.
And sometimes there are celebrity guests.
And I'm no, I'm like, oh, my God, I got to go to a praise the Lord taping.
And it just seemed like, oh, this could be a fun in between
activity for me and my mom, who is a very religious person,
but also knows like televangelists are kind of silly.
And we can go laugh at it a little, but also it'll be a religious thing.
And so let's be respectful and let's dress nice.
And then me, who we already was like this kitchmeister in middle school.
So I called and like, we got to go.
And I remember like nice old lady answers the phone and
all the next taping is on Tuesday.
OK, sounds good.
And do you know if there'll be any guests at that taping?
And she said, why? Yes.
That episode will have Tia and Tamara Mowry and Hammer.
Oh, I thought it was going to be some fake celebrities.
Hammer, I get to go to for free to a palace and see Hammer.
So I am psyched.
This was so fun to do.
I mean, the thing itself was exceedingly boring.
But I got Hammer's autograph.
I mean, wow, incredible.
Is what I like.
I like we'd leave.
He was on one side of a little, you know, like marble gate or whatever.
And I couldn't got his autograph.
So that was all really exciting.
I discovered our friend Ryan Perez also at some point went to a Praise
the Lord taping. And we had the we're talking about this.
We had the same memory of how no one was there.
So they had to scrunch all the audience member.
You know, it's it's a insane theater meant for 200 people.
And they have to jam the 30 who were there into like one little space
to make it look like it's full.
So I was I was fondly recalling all this and realized like,
wait a minute, I've never attempted to find that episode of Praise the Lord.
And especially to see if it ever cuts to me in the audience.
And I did some searching and I found the episode.
The full two hours is uploaded to YouTube.
And it is from July 14th, 1999.
You can look it up yourself. You can watch Hammer.
Hammer does not perform. He just talks.
But you do get a lot of performances by someone named Clifton Davis.
And I didn't know who that was.
I just like watching, you know, seven songs worth of a law.
And this is boring.
But then I discovered the guy who was hosting that episode
wrote The Jackson Fives Never Can Say Goodbye.
It's a guy named Clifton Davis, who's the star of the show. Amen.
So I was a little more like, oh, my God, I got to see that guy perform.
That's weird. So I scoured the entire two hours.
And I was mostly disappointed and it would cut to the audience.
And like I could tell I could see my mom, but not me.
There'd be a pillar just right in front of me.
But I did find a single shot.
And if you guys check your text messages and I'll post this on Twitter to
I found the one shot in the two hours where you can see me.
So we'll throw that up on Twitter.
You get a little bit of Clifton Davis hitting the last note.
And then I hear I hear you guys playing it. Great.
Oh, yeah, I see. Oh, yeah. Yeah.
There we are. Hallelujah.
My mom, I feel like, is in shoulder pad city.
She's she's dressed in the night. Unbelievable.
Yeah. Yeah.
Very excited to find that.
I've been saving that till it till we talked about some religious stuff.
So, yeah. Hey, I'm I'm a praise the Lord supporter.
I know all about it.
You tie the 10 percent.
Hey, if they if they put hammer in front of me, I'll I'll tie it wherever they need.
I wish he did. Can't touch this, though.
Oh, yeah, of course.
Or pray the Prince sampling.
Oh, yeah, yeah. Religious.
I guess that would have been more appropriate.
Or if they or I mean, the ultimate would have been some, you know,
religious themed scrub of his dirty gangster era song, Pumps in a Bump.
I don't know what I don't know what religious rhymes, you know,
hosts and a cup, maybe
like communion wafers and wine.
Hosts and a cup.
I want the priest with the host in a cup.
Seats in a seat in the pews.
Get on your feet.
Seats in the pews.
It's in the pews.
Seats.
Oh, seats. Yes, that's right.
But they were I think any religious listeners appreciate our use of seats
rather than dirty or words for yes, for.
Yeah, yeah, absolutely.
So anyway, I believe they still.
That's great.
I think they still list Hammer under their like secular
personality hammer, Mike Huckabee and of course, Kirk Cameron.
Well, we call them secular.
Well, like the I am describing the list as like here.
The Wikipedia had the list of pastors and then the list of like more
personality kind of hosts.
I see. Gotcha.
So there's still I guess just because they aren't like
they aren't ordained.
Yeah. Although is hammer a camera is a minister, right?
Yeah, I mean, you know, they they actually all three of them
might be ordained for all I know.
But I feel like her camera goes pretty far.
OK, so I started to say a little earlier, the whole thing about TBN,
which they they claim this isn't their main thing,
but it's kind of their main thing is what's known as the prosperity gospel.
Again, this is a different L.A.
Times article, the prosperity gospel is rooted in the idea that God wants
Christians to prosper and that believers have the right to ask him for financial gifts.
TBN has woven this notion into its round the clock programming,
as well as thousands of fundraising letters it mails every day.
So that's why you see people saying things like put Jesus on the credit card
or if you're broke, that's all the more reason to send us money
because God will pay you back tenfold.
Right. No, I don't think that's the best idea.
Like, I'm not I don't begrudge anyone their faith, but yeah, no, this
this stuff sucks. Like, this is bad. Don't do this.
It does. I kind of like that in this case, because of this park
that people's donations led directly to,
you know, an animatronic of an old theologian or to a or to a laser show.
I mean, I guess that's not good, but, you know, usually donations.
That's better. Yeah.
But, you know, yeah, your donations.
I hope people got repaid tenfold in lasers, too.
Yeah. And not the people who paid for Jan Crouch's private jets.
God. So, yeah, Jan Crouch,
one of the main people behind TBN and one of the main hosts.
Praise the Lord.
The director and CEO of the Holy Land Experience.
And if you're wondering, is Jan Crouch the big pink haired lady?
Yes, that is the big pink haired lady.
You know who I'm talking about, if you've ever flipped on TBN for a second.
Yes, she's the pink hair.
I was reading, I believe her origin story has something along the lines of
she a chicken got hit and almost died, but then she prayed and it was resurrected.
Yeah, I have that.
She was she was 12 years old.
Her chicken got hit by a car.
One of its eyes was dangling out of its socket and then she prayed.
And then the bird recovered.
Yeah, so that's the sort of like that's, I guess, how you justify.
Well, obviously, she has an experience
that like would justify that she has this deep connection to the Lord.
Yeah. So then with this,
if the basis of her faith is on bringing chickens back to life,
then how does she justify selling chick filet at the Holy Land Experience?
That's one of the first.
Yeah, there's a Daily Beast article about this, and that's one of the first things
they say in there is that as soon as you walk in, you can get chick filet
or a naked juice.
Really weird. I think the chick filet is in like a Greek thing.
It's like what used to be the front of a Mediterranean restaurant.
And now you just get chick filet there.
Yeah. And I think not fresh chick filet.
Like if you drove probably half a mile away,
you would get new current chick filet.
But instead, at the Holy Land Experience, you're getting three day old chick filet.
That's also right by the coffee establishment. Holy coffee.
What is that? Is that a pun or not?
I don't know. I don't know the answer to that.
I don't know what their thinking was behind it.
Well, the best restaurant, my favorite restaurant, is called Last Snack.
That is that's actually pretty funny.
And the picture on the website is just a big hot dog.
So, well, you know why I like it.
But like and then you got Martha's Kitchen.
That's got a big turkey leg picture.
Then Esther's Banquet Hall, which is just a picture of a burger.
A really crappy, really awful.
You know, all that stuff about food styling about, all right,
you prop it up with the cardboard and, you know, you may put a little fake
glue glisten on it that looks like it's shining or something.
They just didn't do any of it.
This is the most this is like if McDonald's just took photos of the real food.
Yes. Like if it was just like an iPhone, an old generation iPhone photo
of like the actual like hamburger, you would get it like 11 p.m.
Should we arrange this burger to be symmetrical?
No, I don't worry about it.
No, it doesn't matter. It's fine.
I have I have I have done a few fast food commercials and the way they shoot those.
It's it's insane.
It's like you can't have anything like squirting out of it.
You can't have any sort of it just has to look truly perfect.
Like I had to bite into a Wendy's chicken sandwich and the avocado like couldn't
like couldn't encroach on certain parts of the lettuce and the bun.
While the bite was happening.
Wow. Wow. Weird like border rules seeming.
Yes. Yes. Very similar to what's going on in the Middle East.
Yes. If that's what you're going.
We do. Yes. Do not encroach.
That's that's bizarre.
Did you learn anything about how like, you know, that, you know, lettuce is actually this or,
you know, the tomatoes are plastic or is there some some revelation?
No, just a woman in gloves with like about 50 different chicken sandwiches,
like sternly telling me what to do and me not really having many questions.
Hmm. The Stern Burger Lady.
I've I found a listing for I think when I referred to a Mediterranean restaurant
that is now just a Chick-fil-A, I think maybe what it might have been before.
I found this in kind of an older guidebook.
There was something called the Oasis Palms Cafe.
And I think this might be this is what we're looking for,
because I'm sure we all checked around to see like where are there like themed item names?
Because that's that's what you want in in any themed restaurant scenario.
And almost not at all in Martha's Kitchen or Last Snack or any of those.
But we got them at the Oasis Palms Cafe, the sadly retired Oasis Palms Cafe.
Let's see. Goliath burgers like that.
Jaffa hot dogs.
Anyone know what Jaffa refers to?
I don't. Jaffa was a place with a location, I believe.
Yeah, I just typed it into Google and it's all news results about like riots
and people dying in Jaffa.
So anyway, you can get a hot dog.
It's themed after it.
Oasis chicken,
Bedouin beef, Tabgha tuna.
That's another word I don't know.
Is that a city?
Do we know or is it a or is it a type of what is the type of tuna?
Could be. Yeah.
Tabgha is a place that is a sea of Galilee adjacent place.
Arabian chicken, Centurion salad.
That might be the winner for me.
That is good. Yeah.
Shepherd soup.
Does that mean it's lamb soup for?
Hmm.
Not sure.
It doesn't it doesn't.
Yeah, not shepherd's pie.
Right. That's yeah, that's what I'm familiar with, of course.
And then Caesar's delight.
I'm confused by that.
Is that a Caesar salad or is that just something else that Caesar would have liked?
Is it is that Caesar have like a familiar is there like is it kind of like the Walt
Scotch mist, like Caesar's favorite meal?
Is that documented anywhere?
Yeah. Which back then is what?
Like some grapes with flies on them.
Yeah. Well, but like less flies, less flies.
Yes. Like a peasant would have to eat like, you know,
20 to 23 flies per pile of grapes.
But Caesar would only have like four.
They'd pick them out for him.
I've got a good sense of historical food, I think.
But it's recreated for you here at the Holy Land Experience.
I had not to move completely past Jan Crouch.
She because she got a lot of damage done in all her time in Orlando.
There was a lot of accusations of misappropriating network funds,
expensive homes, private jets, massive custom wigs,
a hundred thousand dollar air conditioned mobile home solely for her dogs.
For well, like this as universal fans,
for nearly two years, she rented adjoining rooms for herself
and her two Maltese dogs at the Lowe's Portofino Bay Hotel.
While she was building, it says while she was building
the Holy Land Experience, it was built, she's bought it.
So I don't know what she's talking about.
And which, by the way, I mean, again, if you can get it,
if you have the means, I think we'd all love to hang out with a couple
dogs at the Portofino Bay for two years.
Oh, yeah. Especially religious dogs.
Blessed dogs. Yes. Yeah.
It is the most expensive hotel at Universal.
So and very close to this area.
Was she more of it was Jan more of a universal person or a Disney person?
I guess universal.
But I guess it's maybe just proximity by living there.
And that's proximity.
I also asked earlier,
who is the most Christ like Disney character?
Do we have a character if we if we remind ourselves what Jan Crouch looks like?
Does it does it does she strike you as being similar to any any Disney walkarounds?
She's I guess maybe my knee jerk is Cruella DeVille.
Yeah, this she she doesn't look like this, but honestly,
the first cartoon character that jumps into my mind is the woman,
the bad guy woman in the Chipmunks movie.
I know that's not completely the looks right, but I feel like the vibe is similar.
What was that character's name?
I don't know the game of the character, but I will never forget
just the way they drew those human characters in that chipmunks movie.
Oh, way too like rotoscopy.
I like to like drawn right on top.
And yeah, very disturbing. Absolutely.
I'll send a photo.
Miss Miller is the name.
Yes. Yeah.
I believe that the Chipmunks are in her custody.
Here's the photo incoming.
If Jason, if you know, Jason, you know, I'm talking about.
I believe I do.
Wait, Miss Miller isn't the villain, is she?
Does she just make it?
Miller is.
Mrs. Miller is like the like nice, but like maybe a little dopey.
Oh, I messed up. OK. Yeah, it's not.
Who's the villain then?
Well, these two people, this is just the first Steins.
I guess it's the further two people, this a man and a woman.
Claudia and Klaus Ferkstein.
Yeah. Do you have a picture of them?
I will soon.
All right. I think I got I think I got it here.
Yeah, here we go.
It's going to send twice.
You're going to get two pictures of the Klaus Steins. Mm hmm.
The first Steins, Klaus is the first name.
I see. OK.
Mm hmm.
I'm excited. Yeah.
Yes. Yes. Oh, yeah.
She has kind of the Joan Crawford hair a little bit.
It's not they don't look exactly like her, but that I don't know.
That was the character that jumped in my mind.
Yeah, that's a pretty cool.
I I don't I think I did not look closely at the pictures of the crouches.
So I am just getting the full Jan Crouch hair experience
on Google right now.
And the rich are so dull.
The rich are so gaudy like
it's like Medusa from the Marvel universe, the inhuman
with the giant hair that she could use as a weapon.
Yeah, she does not. Yeah.
I mean, like it's like almost like she saw Dolly Parton
and was like, I'm going to do it my way, but then like had no actual style or anything.
I think I'm sure there are exceptions to this rule.
And tell me if you can think of them.
Dolly herself might be.
But I feel like colored hair
past 65 is a dicey area.
Hmm. You mean on natural like in like a purple, which is not a natural color.
Yes. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I don't know.
But I somebody might be able to point out a very good example of somebody
who's very cool with bizarre wig colors at an older age.
Yeah, I can't off the top of my head, Jason. Yeah.
Well, as punk rockers age, like I'll be cool.
I'd be cool with it if like Kim Gordon was doing it.
You know, sure.
You have to have like red. You have to have some cred.
Yeah. Mm hmm.
But if it's just because like, you know, because I'm fun,
because I got I got spirit.
I don't know how I feel about that.
She's very confusing also, because when you sometimes when you say
the lady with the crazy hair, the religious, the televangelist
lady, the crazy air, you're tempted to think that's Tammy Faye Baker.
Like it was easy for me to confuse these two.
And and now it's that just makes it a type.
I don't know if there are other crazy wig televangelists like this.
There probably are, but just like of the five famous ones,
two of them are crazy wig ladies.
Yes. I mean, Tammy Faye is the name recognition because I did not.
I'm sure I've seen a picture of Jan before, but I was not.
I wouldn't have known her name.
I don't think I did either. No, no.
Now we know it would be interesting, like the sort of like
maybe like local regional version version of this.
Are there like 50 crazy hair wig ladies
trying to be the next Tammy Faye or Jan?
I'm not sure, but that's a reality show I would enjoy watching.
Yes, I think that's a good idea.
Well, again, we're giving these things away for free.
Just looking at her, I feel like Jan probably definitely terrorized
the room service waitstaff at the Portofino, right?
Like she was definitely a pill.
There's no way.
Where's my wedding woodpecker pancakes?
I would imagine.
I mean, look, there's there's some really dark stuff
if you really want to go down a rabbit hole, which I don't.
I don't. Yes.
Up to you if you want to Google Jan Crouch lawsuit.
It's so bad. I don't want to devote the show to it, but she's like she's horrible.
I will not feel bad about shitting on her poorly themed coffee stand.
Yeah, it's the least she deserves.
Only coffee is stupid.
Also, I had an affair with a Holy Land Experience employee.
Lots of fun stuff going on on the plus side.
On the brighter side, I believe that this place was designed by a place called
ITEC Entertainment that, according to their website, also designed Marvel Mania.
Yeah. I mean, you could feel you can feel the DNA.
You can feel it, I think, if you look at some of the photos.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, absolutely.
And her resemblance to Medusa might have helped
the ITEC get on board.
And also the like, if you look at the map for like the layout,
it is so funny because it's clearly like done by a theme park designer.
Like it's it looks exactly like like if it didn't have a religious aspect
to the map, you'd be like, oh, yeah, this is some sort of theme park. Got it.
Yeah. Yeah, I like the water feature.
The landscape architecture looks nice.
I would feel very stressed out if I had to be the guy
who had to keep up the he is risen
floral arrangement every day.
That feels like too much pressure. Mm hmm.
Yeah. Keeping flowers alive, like making Jesus be reborn over and over.
I'm already it's very warm in this room, so I'm forgetting.
Did we actually go through a list of everything on the map yet?
Not yet. No.
Yeah. Maybe it's time to talk about what you do at the Holy Land experience.
Yeah, because it kind of breaks down to shows and exhibits. Mm hmm.
Are we are we going to the list or do we just want to call out?
I think well, yeah.
I mean, there's one thing I just want to say first.
It's number 11 on the map and it's smile of a child adventure land.
I didn't want to take a screen grab of that
because I was afraid I'd get on a list.
Well, I'm sure as we're doing this through Zoom, we have now been placed
on various lists by the spyware inside it.
But I will look with the context of we have to talk about it.
We have to talk about the smile of a child.
Yeah, I know a little about what's in there.
I mean, the the one that really jumps out is that
there is a little exhibit where you go inside
the whale that swallowed Jonah. Right.
And it seems like up on the in his innards,
like kind of up on his stomach wall linings, there's
he's also swallowed an octopus and a starfish.
And don't quote me on this, but it seems like they have mouths that that would move
like they look like kind of flappy mouths like the the Tiki masks
in the in the Enchant Tiki room.
Yes, that is that's there.
You can play miniature golf.
Well, I think what I was I figured out the entomology here.
I think it was just a it was just like walk arounds and there wasn't anything
to like tactile to do.
So I think they added mini golf as like something to do.
And so now you can I believe now you put through the whale's belly.
They like left everything.
Oh, I see. I see. And turned it into mini golf.
Wait really quick before you say it, because we're going to we need to say
the name of the mini golf.
One video I saw where you go into the whale's belly.
You hear a voice.
And I don't know if it was Jonah or a starfish or what it is.
But this gives you the kind of the tenor of the smile of a child area
that I just heard, like a very silly cartoon voice say, God, my father,
forgive my stubbornness.
The funnest place for kids in Orlando by far.
Hey, kids, come to the park.
Ask for forgiveness from God.
Forgive me for coloring out of the lines at the coloring station
at the smile of a child adventure land.
I did not finish my terrible hamburger at Esther's banquet hall.
Forgive me for going over par at the Trinity mini golf.
Yeah.
That's what it's called, the Trinity mini golf.
Trin-i-t-e-e mini golf.
A mini golf place where the hole that I saw involved,
you know, the obstacles kind of along the way are barnyard animals,
donkey and such.
And then at the end, right, right behind the hole
is a manger with the baby Jesus and Joseph and Mary around.
So if you overshot it, if you hit really, really hard,
you would just smack newborn baby Jesus right in the face.
Yes, you have to be very careful on this thing, because, yeah,
if you were to hit it like a drive, you could knock Joseph's head right off.
Like these flats don't even look that straw.
Like, they don't look like they could withstand.
So if a kid like, say, you know, you know, like it's one of those kids
that like extra aggressive, that like hits the ball too hard,
could do real damage here.
You really could.
And I would wait if I had done this
and somehow damaged the Holy Family, I think I would have wept and wept.
I'm going to hell. I killed Joseph.
And then they'd like the people, also the workers,
that would probably been like, you're right.
Yes, that's right. We're very sorry, son.
Yeah, you're going to need to say 200 Hail Marys and eat five
last snack hot dogs.
Mustard can't save you now.
Where's your relish now?
Is your relish now, Jesus?
There is there is one where you're supposed to hit Goliath with a golf ball.
You like want to. It's like David and the slingshot.
There's also a smile of a child theater.
Did you OK, wait, did you find the shows here?
No, no, go for it.
I believe it's the Roman soldier training camp.
No. Yeah. Yeah.
Jason, you found that?
Yeah, I was going to say the the the smile of a child play area.
Not the only thing for kids, because you can go to the Roman
soldier training camp and unleash your inner warrior
as you enlist in our Roman soldier training camp.
Give us your loudest war cry and show us if you got what it takes
to be a certified defender of Rome.
That's wild.
Whoa.
Do we want to be Roman soldiers?
Like, what point did Roman soldiers shift from
pagan gods to Christianity?
Because, yeah, when didn't they hurt Jesus?
Yeah. Yeah. What?
I don't. Yeah. Do they like teach you to like, all right, here's a stab a hand.
Like, you don't want to be them, do you?
The flattening of history.
My my religious education did not do a good job about like
contextualizing what was going on in the world and like who was ruling
what parts of it at the time, you know.
Yeah. Yeah.
I'm an idiot when it comes to this.
I've just sent you a photo from this this
like pamphlet I'm looking at with all the shows that has a picture of a Jesus
that looks very close to Will Forte.
Yes.
Well, bless you.
He really does.
It could be like, could be.
Did he do a run at
once this photo?
Yeah, he was actually discovered for SNL at the at the Smile of a Child Theater.
Lauren and Marcy Klein go down to the Smile of a Child Theater
once a year to see all the talent, the Jesus talent.
You know, we ask them for three characters and too many of them
just do Jesus, Satan and Lazarus and, you know, just variety is what we're after.
I swear, if I see another fucking Mary Magdalene.
Since you bring that up,
I feel like a lot of Mary Magdalene in this park, right?
I don't I don't recall.
Well, she shows up at
OK, which show is it?
Simeon's House to watch Jesus's feet.
She shows up at Lazarus's house
because she is Lazarus's sister, I believe.
Is that right?
I think I think I read that
Lazarus House is the one that struck me the most just because of this description
that's on the website, multiple locations.
Visit Lazarus's home and meet his beloved sisters,
witness the unique dynamic of this family.
And I don't know what it is.
That phrase has just been ringing in my head for days.
Like visit Lazarus's house, meet his sisters,
witness the unique dynamic of this family.
It's really it's a lot of nothing, huh?
A unique family dynamic.
I think the family dynamic is they yell at Mary Magdalene
for being a sinner.
Right. Am I wrong?
Possibly could be sounds right.
Could be. I'm looking at this and there's a longer description
that says enjoy live singing in a comical twist on one of the Bible's well known stories.
Oh, so I'm not you know, maybe there maybe there's a little improv.
Maybe they ask for a word in the middle of the show.
They also call her Maria Magdalene or Maria Magdalena,
which I know is I think it's some translations call her that.
And if you need to make a telephone call in Lazarus's house,
use the Dan. Yeah.
If you come back to life and need to make a telephone call to say you're alive,
you've risen from the dead. Use the Dan.
The shows at Lazarus's house are so good,
it'll have you coming back again and again.
Is it hot outside?
A little air condition sitting Lazarus's house will bring you back to life.
The coolest cave in town.
Coolest cave in town.
But it's like it's like carousel of progress.
Yeah, you can go there and sit down and get air conditioned 20 for 20 minutes.
I would hopefully.
And he lists all the inventions they don't have yet.
Washing machines. Nope.
Automatic air dryers. Not in our dreams.
Quibi. No way.
Do you realize this episode is the first post Quibi episode?
Oh, yeah, you're right.
Wow. We did. I mean, that means what that means is no one's listening.
We're talking to no one because everyone is quibbling right now.
That's a good point. That's that's that's a bummer.
This is going to sit on listen to for for years. What are we doing?
Let's just give up. It's a good man.
It's fine that we're getting all these things about the Holy Land wrong.
Yeah, no one's going to hear it.
Judge Chrissy Teigen is going to put us in solitary.
And then Chance the Rapper is going to punk our asses.
We would be so lucky to get punked by Chance the Rapper.
Oh, as long as he's got that hat.
As long as he's got that hat on.
It was a being punking was a luxury only available in pre virus times.
Now, the vast majority of punkings
are considered gatherings of more than 10 people.
So
you could still do a zoom punking.
The ultimate punk would be
to reveal that there's like 200 people hiding in your house
and they all come out and cough.
Oh, yeah. What a what a hilarious punk.
Ha ha ha. You got me.
Well, in terms of perhaps disappointing attractions,
one of these articles I read, forgive me for not knowing the name of the book,
but it's called The Ripper.
One of these articles I read, forgive me for not knowing the source,
but they phrased it beautifully.
Number 18 whipping post was just a wooden post
with a cardboard cut out of a bloody Jesus being whipped to red paint,
literally smeared all over it.
Whipping post fun whipping post.
Where was that?
Thank you.
It was number 18 at the time.
I don't know if it was in the script or next to you or in the smile.
Probably not in the smile of a child area, but no, I would hope not.
But the child, the children can still go to the scriptorium,
and I'm sure they would.
Yeah.
There was another fun sounding one is the day in the life,
a day in the life of a monk, which is just it's just a room with an empty cot.
What? Just a small little room.
It's not minimal because we had no money.
It's minimal because that's how the monks lived.
You see, would you could you go in there for like a day or a week?
I assume they wanted you in and out, though, because they had moved people.
Yeah, I don't think so.
I don't think you can room and board in the in the monk room.
This is the monk in the life.
This is the monk's home and meet his beloved cot.
Witness the unique dynamic of his job.
His beloved cot.
That's my that's it.
So I thought you were reading realistic enough.
Yeah, really?
One man in the cot, he loved dear.
I was just swapping in the monk's specifics,
swapping out laser specific, swapping in monk's specifics.
Sure.
I couldn't find a lot of information about the Ark of the Covenant,
smoke and laser laser show.
Yeah, I know there was.
Did you look for a video?
No, videos are a little sparing for this entire thing.
I do know video policy or anything.
Like do they say not to do video?
Probably.
Guys, I'm just like looking at the
like map a little more or the one one of the pages of the map.
And it did not dawn on me that the Empire
and the Kingdom is a three part show at 1230, 215 and 315.
And the parts range from 40 minutes to 45 minutes.
Oh, that's it. Yeah, you're right.
That's interesting.
So it's it's it's not the same show over and over again during the day.
No, you follow Peter's journey through Rome.
Interesting.
Oh, wait, wait a minute.
The park closes seems to close around six o'clock every day.
But the resurrection of Lazarus is at 525.
So that's the equivalent of a Renaissance fair
that has a joust as the last thing of the day.
Is that the big is that the phantasmic?
Is that the fireworks show is Lazarus rising?
Well, I think the phantasmic is the passion.
That's obviously the main draw.
Oh, right, right, right, right.
And they highly encourage everybody to see the passion.
And, you know, even if you're experiencing another exhibit,
I think they tell you, you know, the passion is beginning right now.
So they really they really try to push everyone to that.
What time is the passion?
Well, if it's like the hours that I had to be sad, then it's from 12 to three.
Which those those hours, Jason, you just listed were kind of in that window.
Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, it looked pretty like during the day to me.
And it was funny watching.
I did. There is some sparing video of the of the passion show.
And, you know, because it's this little, you know,
Middle Eastern town and there's like, you know,
here's this little structure and some scenes happen up there.
And then there's there's fighting and you're watching it in stands.
It all reminded me so much of the Indiana Jones stunt spectacular.
Oh, and actually, I just realized, including the abuse of whips.
In this case, for much darker purpose.
Yeah, that's a good point.
Yeah, yeah. They have to like coordinate the sound effects like, you know,
it's all the stuff you have to do in any theme park, you know, in the Waterworld
show, you have to like make all the gun sound effects or whatever.
So somebody's got to be watching the watching the guys whip
and hitting the catcher every time.
I mean, it would have gotten a lot more.
It would have got a lot more guests if Indiana, like one of the Romans,
had thrown off their their garb and it had been Indiana.
Jesus, we got to get out of here.
Do you have any idea what they're going to do to you, Jesus?
And who are you?
I'm from the future.
I time travel in part five.
You'll see. You'll see.
It comes out in 2030.
Marion or Mary or Marie, whatever your name is, come on.
I'm 90 years old.
I will say this, all the pictures of the live shows,
they look like they're pretty well produced.
Definitely. Maybe maybe maybe it's deceptive in just
they've obviously taken pictures that look good, but it doesn't look chintzy.
I will say that.
No, I think I think it's plenty well done.
Yeah, you're getting a show.
You're getting I'm just saying, I think, you know, to give it a compliment,
you're getting a show, at least.
Yeah, it feels like certainly.
I also let me do really let me do another specific quote here,
because this really I mean, this explains Holy Land experience
better than than anything I've seen.
Atlas Obscura framed it as thus at Orlando's Holy Land experience.
Jesus is crucified daily for your viewing pleasure.
It's really strange.
It's definitely very strange.
And again, like I said, there's this whip sound effects and they at every
step at every station of the cross where he is, he is abused and tortured.
He gets bloodier and bloodier. It's crazy.
This is the thing that they actively encourage kids to come to.
And it's it is just a full on really gory passion, just like the film is.
It is gorier than any horror nights thing.
The picture I saw, at least.
Sorry, I was going to say you could also meet the living Christ
at the miracle of the upper room.
Did you guys come across that?
Not sure I did. No, I didn't.
It's offered four times a day.
It's about 15 minutes and participants in this experience
participate in a communion service with an actor playing Jesus.
Huh? Yes, yes.
And I saw somewhere that you get
you get a wafer or a little piece of bread or something,
and then you get like grape juice.
Yes, Protestants use grape juice. That's correct.
OK, yeah.
So Protestantism, not for me, clearly.
So there's multiple we were saying there's multiple Jesuses.
Is it is it a situation, though, where like when you're in Disneyland
and you see, oh, there's Mickey in a tuxedo,
but then there's Mickey in his regular clothes.
And then like, is there ever like our kids going to be a little confused
if they see different Jesuses during the day?
I have to imagine they would be.
Yeah. And is it do you go by San Francisco?
You go by Santa rules and one of them's Jesus's helper.
You're right. Is that yeah, when the kid gets a little older, is it like,
well, that one's beard is bigger than the other one.
That one's taller.
Like that's not the same.
The same one covered in blood is not the same one that I met and got away from.
That nice man gave us a snack earlier.
And now those mean men are beating him up within to within an inch of his life.
Mom, can we go back and see Muppet Vision 3D instead?
No, we cannot.
I and speaking of important and importance, the I think the
the most important act that occurs at the Holy Land Experience.
This is so crazy.
I cannot believe this is true.
Kind of related to the have a community having communion with Jesus.
I mean, I had to check multiple sources to discover if this was real and it is.
OK, the sermon on the Mount occurs.
That's another like mini show that Jesus does.
After delivering a brief speech and pronouncing a blessing
on what appeared to be plastic loaves and fishes,
Jesus solicits costume cast members to feed the crowd
in lieu of real bread and fish.
Jesus's disciples deposit a handful of processed cheddar goldfish
crackers into each visitor's hand.
I can't believe that's real.
They don't give you fish.
They give you goldfish crackers.
That is that's where like, you know, budget like budget
and maybe like health concerns like really get in the way of making something authentic.
I think so. Yeah, it's OK.
It's really important for authenticity that everybody wear like really
heavy fabric on their head.
But we can just give everybody, you know, pizza flavored goldfish.
I mean, I guess, yeah, I guess I wonder if I wonder if it's always been that.
I wonder if they ever actually tried to do the real thing.
Well, look, you got to think about the wholesale rates here.
OK, you're going to your money's going to go a lot farther getting wholesale
processed goldfish than trying to buy cans and cans of sardines
to give everyone a little fish, you know.
Yes, yes. I mean, yes. Budget concerns.
Oh, sardines, dear God.
Yeah, that's fine.
Let's stick with the goldfish.
Jason, do you like sardines?
I do like sardines. Yeah.
But a bunch of canned fish when we all start going crazy at the grocery store
about canned smoked oysters about sardines.
Canned smoked oysters.
I don't know about oysters.
We always had smoked oysters growing out.
Wow. I do like sardines, actually.
I think it's an underrated.
I think I liked it also because Michelangelo would put it on a pizza
and I wanted to be like him.
Yeah, I like you can.
If you if you cook them in the pan a little, if they're already in olive oil,
you cook them in a pan, toss in some tomato sauce, serve it over pasta.
Delicious.
Also, as I eat less meat, as I get older, it is just crazy.
There is just literally like a whole fish.
What do you think is the most
if we're going for accuracy, what how do we make the goldfish more?
If it's just plain cheddar, I don't know.
I mean, first of all, you're going to want the mouth.
Do all the goldfish have mouths at this point or are some of them still just plain?
Oh, that's a good question.
I don't know. I haven't had goldfish crackers in a long time.
I haven't either.
I should treat myself to a quarantine treat.
But I'm trying to think.
I mean, what's like the fishiest goldfish?
Are the like I'm looking at their varieties and like, you know,
s'mores flavored goldfish grams.
What flavor blasted extra cheddar jacked?
I don't know. They don't have really have like a fish.
They don't have like a salmon flavored goldfish cracker, do they?
It doesn't look like they do.
No, there's no goldfish products that offer
the taste of fish besides the shape of fish.
Well, I found a I think it's probably fan.
It's a Etsy type thing.
But there's a goldfish crackers sweatshirt that I think Jason should get.
Oh, yes, I mean that is it just the logo?
What's going on with it?
I'll send it right now.
Jacked might be good because everyone's jacked to enter
the kingdom of heaven when they accept Christ's blessings.
Well, and a cracker being blasted with that much
jacked, that much jacked cheddar.
I mean, that seems like a miracle that only Christ could achieve.
Maybe this maybe look, maybe it's the maybe you don't even have
to have it be fish, maybe it's literally just in the morning.
All of the goldfish crackers are blessed by a priest.
Yeah, that would that would suffice. Yeah. Yeah.
In the way the way the wafers become the body of Christ,
the goldfish crackers become the bodies of real fish.
Yeah, exactly. Yeah.
So that makes sense.
This apparently doesn't actually say goldfish.
It has a different it has a different name on it,
but it's basically the crackers and you'll see it.
I just sent it.
So I'm guessing it just is black.
I'm guessing they maybe they bless maybe that maybe.
So all the food is blessed in the morning.
The chick filet is blessed.
The naked juices are blessed.
Caesar's favorite food item is blessed.
Whatever that was.
God's tidings upon this citrus sea monster.
Right. This Coke Zero Mountain Dew Baja Blast
turn water into Mountain Dew Baja Blast.
The many daily miracles here at Holy Land Experience.
I am another
another daily miracle is the defeat of Satan
within the passion performance.
And this, you know, I again, I really regret that there isn't more good video
or photographs because
I saw several sources alluding to that their Satan
is kind of a well to quote.
This is from Jacob Silverman and the Baffler.
The Satan of the Holy Land Experience is a marvelous creation
knitted out in or kitted out, I guess, in ripped leather,
a tank top, runny eyeliner and chains.
They're like it's like a like a hot topic.
Satan, I think it's like it is like a modern.
It's like what they would cast in like a made for TV movie
where it's like modern day Satan.
Yeah, absolutely.
I think this it seems like their Satan could play in the Hollywood vampires.
Alice Cooper, Johnny Depp, Satan.
Johnny Depp, Satan.
Is that still sort of if if like we're doing like a psychoanalysis
of the people who put that together, are they still scared of like
aging in their 60s, rock and rollers, 60s in their 60s and 70s, rock and rollers?
Yeah, do they think that the rock stars are still like
putting backwards messages in the music?
Yeah, that might that's what I'm getting at.
It's like, well, Ozzy Osbourne is public enemy number one still to this day.
Like they've got an old school way of thinking.
And they're like, well, there's no better representation of state
of modern Satan than Ozzy.
I think so.
Yeah, I think there's definitely people on this earth who are like
a thousand percent on board with everything Trump is doing,
but they're still really mad about Bart Simpson.
Right.
Alice Cooper throwing up the devil's side, like the or the,
you know, devil horns with his hand is still.
They're just mad because he's a man who wears eyeliner.
Yes. Also, his name is Alice.
Woman's name.
God does not want the genders to be confused.
He doesn't know how to classify them once they arrive at Heaven's Gate.
Meanwhile, like all these guys have done like Citibank commercials for credit cards.
Like they're so far from.
Alice Cooper is the right wing is guy.
And the crouches, the people behind it are the most deviant psychopaths,
the most upsetting lawsuits and affairs and money laundering.
Like, yeah, got to watch out for kids listening to monkey's records.
The true danger is anyone who dresses like Adam Lambert.
Oh, yeah.
Chains, little spikes on a wristband.
Not in the kingdom of heaven.
Kids today have 21 pilots,
but they should only have one pilot and his name is Jesus Christ.
You really, Jason, you should write sermons for these people.
I should write sermons for them.
You'd make a little yeah, make a little money, make a little side money.
The apparently then what happens is that this
this goth Satan gets just walks up to Jesus and they just start punching each other.
It's just a just a fist fight.
And then and then Jesus wins, of course.
And that makes sense because I think he has been training as evidenced by a photo,
which I'll try to take quick and send to you guys where he it's a
the corner of a boxing ring and Jesus is shirtless
and in just shorts and his boxing gloves are hanging off of his arm.
And he is super ripped, really well backlit.
That's kind of true.
That's one thing that makes Jesus always in every every painting and everything.
He always finds his light.
That's how you know he's special.
But he was a star. He knew.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. He he knows he knows his best side.
He knows where his hair looks the most luxurious.
But yeah, check out this photo.
Jesus hanging out in the corner of the ring and the the the the side of the ring.
It says Savior down the side.
So in this painting, you can get Jesus like boxes.
He trains. That's weird.
Really strange. Yeah.
Especially weird in the show that Jesus defeats Satan
Satan by biting a chunk of his ear off.
Well, they wanted it to be topical.
Yes, but they never cut it out.
They never cut it out.
They tried doing a bit where Jesus hits him with a steel chair,
but they messed it up and messed up the guys back so they couldn't do that anymore.
You know what I will say, though?
This is there's still more like activity going on here than in Galaxy's Edge.
There's still more fighting and action that the fans demand here.
Then, you know, Kylo Ren walks around, but he never fights Ray.
Yeah. So I give them kudos.
I give them credit. Yeah.
Which is is funny, because if Bob Chaypack had followed the prosperity
doctrine, the prosperity gospel and just put that little extra money
to the people mover system, it would have paid off tenfold.
And he wouldn't have had to take a 50% pay cut
during these hard economic times.
If you're saying that if he had put that third ride into Galaxy's Edge,
he would have been able to have his full salary during the coronavirus outbreak.
Yes. As like they say, the Holy Land experience, karma is a bitch.
Another great mode you can see Jesus in is there's a cardboard cutout
where he's just he's riding a big motorcycle.
He's riding a big hog.
Yes, I know. That's wild.
Yeah. Yeah.
And he's got angel wings.
Why? Jesus has and Jesus isn't an angel.
I mean, he's a lot of things, but he's not an angel.
They may as well have like the buddy Christ from dogma.
It's exactly like that.
He's pointing. He's smiling a big smile and pointing.
It's really wild.
Yeah, I don't know what the thinking is.
Is this like what we have, you know, because like,
I guess we read that there's a little humor in the Lazarus show.
So is this like, you know what? We have fun, too.
Jesus has fun.
It's not all blood and guts.
Not too much fun, though.
Not too much fun.
But some fun.
Some some fun, some fun.
Firmly in the category of some fun is the one
animatronic that I could find evidence of at the Holy Land Experience.
And is it, you know, one of our our buddies from the Bible?
Is it Noah? Is it Abraham?
Or is it the scary snake for the bother Danimeneve?
No, better.
It is an animatronic of John Wycliffe,
the 14th century English theologian, of course.
And you can listen to him explain
how he translated the Bible from Latin to English in 1382.
Oh, oh, OK.
As my son, you don't seem especially excited to meet John Wycliffe.
Oh, no, I am.
Well, oh, very good.
I'm glad you're excited. Sit down.
He has 25 minutes worth of explanation
of translating from language to language.
He knows many languages. He'll tell you all about it.
These shows are so long.
Yeah, yeah, they're all I mean, well, if that doesn't sound interesting.
He is wearing like a floppy Magellan kind of hat.
So, oh, OK. Yes.
All right. I'm back on board.
Sit down. We're good.
Now we're going for your own safety.
We have to buckle you in.
So strap in and the straps will only come loose automatically 25 minutes from now.
Are there straps?
I know. Hopefully so.
But again, you have to ask.
Yeah, it's hard to tell in any of these places.
Yeah. So go here. Go see John Wycliffe.
Go. You can go operate a claw machine.
That's a fun thing for a kid to do.
And your ward may be a prayer bear.
Yes. Oh, I love the prayer bears.
They have a little like couch, like a kangaroo, and you slip a little prayer inside.
Do you speaking of like prayer bears and plush, do we know about the camel?
No, I don't.
Nope. Go on.
OK. Well, I was looking through eBay at different merch,
and I believe the whole they it's a little bit hard to tell
if it's like from Trinity Broadcasting specifically,
or they just like I'm not sure where the origin of the camel is.
But there's a camel named Quaboo Q.A.B.O.O.
the camel, and he is available at the Holy Land Experience.
But I think you also can probably get him on maybe like a home shopping network.
I think if you actually pledge, you can get Quaboo the camel.
But he's a very cute camel.
And he is you can get you can get a version of him on eBay for fifty dollars.
Wow. And incidentally, I would like to congratulate
Jeffrey Katzenberg on the launch of Quaboo.
Yes, we're very excited about the Quaboo series.
Quaboo of the pride.
There's various there's like
it's interesting looking at the merch, too, on eBay,
because it's like there's sort of one off things.
I'll see like lamb sheep plush soft toy.
It looks very dirty, though.
It looks I mean, I mean, like just like covered in soot.
Like it's ashes. It's Ash Wednesday.
Right. But they have, you know, pins like pewter pins.
They have decorative glasses.
They have candle frankincense and myrrh handpoured Christian faith candles.
Wow. So you can spend a lot of money at the Holy Land Experience.
Yes. And then there's also just, you know,
a lot of T-shirts, which, you know, maybe we want to get one or two.
Yeah, sure. You think Quaboo is kind of the item to get?
I think he seems like the number one.
But I think he I just want to I need to do a little more investigating
and seeing if he's more of a Trinity icon than an actual Holy Land icon.
Oh, OK. OK. Yeah.
That's what I'm suspecting is that he might be more of a Trinity mascot,
which I'm less excited about.
He's a look. He's a cute camel. Cute camels, a cute camel.
But I want to make sure he's more associated with a theme park.
And I have a suspicion he's a little bit more Trinity based.
Yeah. You want him to be original theme park.
I.P. Absolutely. Right.
And when this folds, I would have liked to own Quaboo
when this park closes for good.
I feel like everything's up for sale soon. Right.
I think you get a steal on Quaboo.
I think everything maybe in America is up for sale soon.
To to negative here.
I wonder what have we not discussed?
Oh, one thing I missed about the devil is that
it's at some point in time.
This quote, this one, the Vice article, they
they did break the reality.
They break the fourth wall with the devil a little bit.
And somebody explains that now this is this his name is Eric.
He's just an actor.
I say this because a couple of weeks ago, we had a woman slap the devil.
Well, my people get so invested in it and the devil's being mean to Jesus.
Some people would walk up and how dare you beat him up?
What's really funny about that, like we've heard stories and I still don't know.
I haven't heard firsthand, but we've heard stories of like,
oh, they had to take Captain Jack out of the park because women were flashing him.
Like I've heard that before.
I don't know if that's just sort of an urban legend.
But if people thought because because the reason being people like
associated him with Johnny Depp so much, they needed to flash Johnny Depp.
So I like the idea that they would go up to who they think is Satan
and just slap him and not try to murder him, not to try to destroy him.
Yeah, they believe enough that he is the devil.
This is the devil right here.
But I just want to, you know, just just give him a little warning.
You're yes, like like, yeah, like you're challenging him to a duel.
Hit him with a little glove. You jerk.
You are very uncouth, sir.
I've read about some of the things you've done over the years and I do not approve.
Does that mean there's like supporters of the devil to like are there
hashtag devil innocent supporters as there are with John?
Free the devil.
Oh, yeah, I'm sure there are.
I would be interested.
Is there any like kind of like edgy teens that go here
just to go see the devil every day because they love the devil and cheer him on?
Yeah, he needs he needs our support.
Yeah, they're like they're devil stands.
Do you think devil worshippers petition the Holy Land experience
to sometimes let him win like the Washington generals?
I would imagine, yeah, they should.
They should like once once a year, like they do with the free admission,
they should let the devil win.
It's only fair, you know, there's no stakes if Jesus always wins.
Right. You need you need to have that possibility that the devil will win
for that drama, because if not, you know where the story is going to how it's going to end.
And you guys, your big wrestling fans, you love a good heel.
I mean, if they want this to be a good show,
you got to build up the heel to be a significant challenger to the face.
So, yes, sometimes the heel has to win in order to make him or her more of a threat.
Yeah, that is what I thought of when you said someone slapped the devil,
is that someone pulled a gun on who was it, Mike?
Was it the ultimate warrior back in the 80s?
Oh, my God. I a lot of wrestlers have a story in the 70s and 80s
about getting a gun pulled on them because people thought that was all like
they were actual villains.
They were actually that mean and cruel.
Well, I think Andy Kaufman had a lot of what they like people really angry at him
when he was feuding with Lawler.
I don't know that he had a gun.
Oh, yeah. I think a lot of those people.
The idea was you would rile up a crowd so much that you would have to run to your car
so they wouldn't kick the shit out of you.
Wow. Well, so I mean, that speaks to the quality of the devil performance
that they were buying it that much.
Yes. Right. Yes. Yeah.
They're edgy. Yeah.
And there's a lot of wrestling in Orlando.
So he should like, you know, he should do a little speech.
It's a like tonight. I'm taking on the ultimate warrior.
Mm hmm. Well, the devil could pop into any of the different wrestling
taping in Orlando.
Yeah. Yeah. This is the best merger worlds they could do.
Get the Holy Land experience devil
in the in the next raw is really raw tape there.
No, that's on the road.
But there's an NXT tapes there.
And it's a term. OK. OK.
Impact. Oh, no. Impact might tape in Canada.
Anyway, I don't know. He's going to need work.
So, yeah, when you get the devil up for grabs,
wrestling, take note.
Or you can just like join a
cover, a black Sabbath cover band.
Either way, he's already he already dresses the part.
Yes, he can bring his own eyeliner.
Yeah, exactly.
Um, I what a place.
My God. My my God.
My gosh. My gosh.
My gosh.
Are we going to miss it if it if it does not fully come back?
I wish we went.
I do wish we went.
So I will miss not having gone.
50 bucks.
50 bucks is as rough, though, I'll say.
I don't mind not paying 50 dollars.
I could have sent an email.
We could have seen what we could have done.
But when they have like asked us to make it a donation,
like it's it's against the Lord's will to get press comps.
That's a good question.
But if we said Patreon exclusive episode.
Perhaps this is Patreon.
Yeah, it is. Right. That's what we're doing.
No, no.
No, it's regular.
It's the main feed right now.
I'll cut it out.
I'll cut the.
Whatever.
We don't know what we don't know what day it is.
We don't know what we're doing.
Truly from being in this room, I had the door closed
and I literally felt like I've been losing my mind
the whole time we're recording.
I need to figure out an air circulation in here.
It's getting hot for me, too.
Well, hey, no one's making us do it.
We could we could end any time.
Any final thoughts about the Holy Land experience?
I just again, I wish I went.
I wish I went.
Again, I wish I went.
I wish honestly I wish that they had poured more money
from Trinity Broadcasting into this
because it feels like Trinity has a ton of money
and they should have really upgraded.
Let's get a ride in there.
Let's get more animatronics.
Let's up the production even more.
Let's you know, let's make it a five part series,
not a three part series.
I forget which show that was.
I just wish the budget was higher.
I just wish they really went nuts
and it was like much more of an epic like shutting down now.
Yeah, yeah.
That they yeah, that they would go all out.
I mean, the opportunity to have like full on religious dark rides.
They definitely have not really made good on that that possibility.
And if this is all we're going to get,
this is kind of the biggest religious theme park.
Definitely, definitely a bit of a letdown.
Unless there's things we don't know about
that have had full on religious dark rides.
Yeah, but I don't I think we've we've asked before
and no one's produced an example.
So they should license the journey to Jerusalem thing
from the the pavilion at Epcot, the Millennium.
Oh, yes, that's floating around somewhere.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
Yeah, we talked about that on the second gate.
There was a weird ride where you go to Jerusalem.
Yeah, that's like begging to be here from the Millennium village,
although that might be a little too not Jews for Jesus see enough for the for this gang.
Like that might be a little too like, well, OK, that's the first half of our book.
But the second half is where the real ticket is.
You know, that's where your real ticket to ride is right in the heavens.
I don't know.
We've talked about what religious rides might be, I guess, before.
Is there something from Jesus's life that would make an especially good
maybe if maybe some kind of like bumper car scenario where, you know,
that they were he's like getting rid of the shopkeepers in the temple
where you're like mowing over shopkeepers in a Mr. Toad madcap fashion.
Oh, that's good. Huh?
Like 40 days and 40 nights in the desert.
There's there's so many water ride opportunities.
Noah's Ark, Jesus walking on water.
I feel like those are givens. Yeah, right.
I think there should be there should be more of a of a crucifixion.
It should be really like it doesn't go far enough here is what I'm saying.
They should really like you should get like you should have that sheet like at the front row of a Gallagher concert.
Like really the blood, I'm saying. Oh, I see. Oh, the blood.
Oh, gotcha. Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, they should provide that just as a courtesy. Yes.
And they should have Gallagher do it.
Like doing so many people do special runs as the devil this month. Gallagher.
Yeah, you got a super. Yeah, you get like like older road like Jimmy JJ Walker.
They'll do it one month. Yeah.
Carrot top. Carrot top. Sure. Props involved in that one.
That'll be kind of a sillier crucifixion. Yeah, but that's OK.
Again, they have a sense of humor. So that's why you get these these guests.
Satan's and Jesus. Yeah, I guess they're going to want to be Jesus's hammer.
Obviously, hammers around hammer doing a stint as Jesus and doing his little hammer dance,
his parachute pants dance on water. Oh, wow. There we go.
He not only survives the crucifixion, but he comes back to hammer dance
because he is too legit to quit. Yeah.
And that's such a great guy. Somebody's going to draw that.
Yes, please. Yes. Yes. Yes.
The hashtag Jesus is hammer or hammer is Jesus. Hammer is Jesus.
But for now, what's the worst that could happen?
We're already in the middle of a plague.
If we do something sacrilegious, we're going to get another plague.
I think Jason, Jason, daring the Lord now.
This is we're causing it by doing this episode at all.
It's I'm sorry, everyone. It's no, we're calling out the money lenders in the temple.
We're overturning the tables now with these hypocrites.
That's correct. We did.
And I don't think it'll be a problem anymore because we yeah.
Yeah. They look a whole experience.
I think it's safe to assume willfully close in the near future.
You know, maybe it was the virus. Maybe it was them firing everybody.
But who's to say podcast wasn't wasn't part of that?
Don't mess with us. We'll take we'll take a little credit.
Yep. Yep. So get on our good side and offer us comps.
If you hear we're coming to Orlando. Fly us in.
Fly us in on a private on your private jets.
Put us up at the Portofino Bay Hotel with two Maltese dogs.
Yes, please. And then please like sterilize the planes before.
Yes, that would help. Yes, please. More important than holy water.
Sterilize. It would be funny if they send us like three coach tickets.
Hey, when this is all over, we are the episode.
We want to make you happy. And they're like, no, no, no, no, no.
Now you're coming now.
Yeah, coach tickets are fifty dollars. Right.
All right. Well, yeah, we'll revisit this if they do give us comps.
That truly is the way into the kingdom of heaven, giving podcasters comps.
But but for now, you know what? It's just for changing up the ending.
I will say podcast. The riot has ended.
Let us go in peace to love and serve Jan Crouch for more.
For more podcast, the ride visit the Holy Trinity, Twitter, Instagram and Facebook.
And for only five dollars a month, you can pass into the kingdom of podcast.
The ride, the second gate.
All are welcome for three bonus episodes every month at Patreon dot com slash podcast.
The ride. Put the second gate on a credit card.
Yeah, it's considered a write off, right?
Just like this park. I think it is.
Yeah, I know. Yeah.
So think of it as a religious donation.
If Florida can have tax exempt status for locations that display biblical artifacts,
California should have a law that podcasters get all sorts of tax tax exempt,
you know, benefits.
We're keeping this economy of California afloat.
Anyone who wasn't a podcaster before the virus certainly is now.
So and they're also good.
They're all great. And yeah, you know, you know, I usually I just like to plug what we're doing.
But I, you know, in the spirit of Easter kindness, we should promote another podcast
and say, please go check out the podcast.
I wish it promoted another podcast and say, please go check out Zach Braff
and Donald Faison's Scrubs Revisited podcast.
That also will assure your passage into the into the kingdom of heaven.
I would like to also announce Jason Sheridan and I are doing a podcast where we revisit old heralds that we did.
Oh, God. Don't we do that enough when we hang out?
Yeah, now we're recording it.
This is this is the content we need.
This is what will cheer up everyone in these troubled times.
Do you think also I don't know, no spoilers, but do you think that your guys
I know you guys were real bros in a lot of your heralds, but is your real life broship going to kind of come out in this podcast, too?
I would think that everyone will be able to finally experience our real life broship in their living room.
So, yes, I guess the answer is yes.
That's sort of that's a mission statement.
It's just I have it.
I have it written down right here.
It's just so it's so crazy that you guys played friends in improv shows and our friends in real life.
I agree.
And we're so happy to bring it to people's, you know, podcatchers.
Thanks to gambling online dot com.
Check out gambling online dot com.
The website where you gamble on the Internet.
We really are happy with our partners at gambling online dot com.
We like them.
All right.
Well, happy Easter weekend, everyone.
A very solemn remainder of your Good Friday to you.
And thanks for listening.
Be back for more next week.
Forever.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Baum, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts dot com and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.