Five, four, three, two, one.
Bright Light City, gonna set my soul,
gonna set my soul on fire.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, The Second Gate.
I'm Jason Sheridan, here as always with Mike Carlson.
I'm here, Viva Las Vegas indeed.
And Scott Kierdner.
I'm leaving Las Vegas.
How does that, that's a Sheryl Crow song.
It's not really a big one.
Switched it up.
I don't know any lyrics beyond that, but I did what I could.
What other Vegas songs are there?
A lot, I think.
Yeah, probably.
This Viva Las Vegas is if you ever rock Vegas.
Right.
So you're freshly back.
Freshly back from Vegas.
Vegas vacation.
A Vegas vacation.
Of course.
Yeah.
So did you end up feeling more like Rusty Griswold,
scoring big on all the tables,
pretending to be Nick Papagiorgio,
or did you feel like Sid Caesar having a heart attack?
Oh.
Well, that's interesting.
Like Vegas, you know, it's the highs to highs
and the lowest to lows, you know?
So a little bit of both.
So you're saying you were up like $5 million
and then you were like, you know, like strung out with a hooker
in a $5 hotel room?
Well, not quite, not quite.
A little uncomfortable and grumpy.
Before we get to the main topic, let's just go through the trip.
Tell us how you got there, all that type of stuff.
How I got there.
Okay, so because this is, we're going to talk about the M&M store
and the 3D movie within the M&M store.
Yes.
But I lost my M in Vegas.
The primary.
Rolls off the tongue.
Just hits the ear like a beautiful symphony.
But yeah, this is also a little travelogue.
Yes.
Like my adventure on the Queen Mary.
Right.
What did you, what were you?
I said just a little bit.
What did you do?
You flew out there.
I flew out to Vegas.
Yeah, I went to Vegas for a few days.
You were not alone.
I was not alone as you guys and I've been seeing someone
for a little while now.
Yeah, a while, yes.
And we went to Vegas together, went on a little trip, flew in,
flew in and out, beautiful McCarran Airport.
Meant to look up exactly what crimes McCarran did.
McCarran, a notoriously corrupt Nevada politician
that the airport is named after.
Right.
That's okay.
There's plenty of corrupt people that airports
have been named after, I assume.
And full credit to her because she, you know,
we stayed at the Park MGM, which you have stayed at before.
Two times, yes.
Yeah.
And she, there is, so there are these apps,
these slot machine apps you can play on your iPhone
called MyVegas.
And she had been playing these for a while and had enough
that we like got a free night and I would like claim
two free drinks somewhere and a free appetizer.
I mean, this sounds like heaven.
This sounds like the perfect setup for a vacation.
I love it.
So, but, you know, so we went and most importantly,
she also picked great seats for David Copperfield,
Live the Impossible.
Yeah.
Yes.
And if you don't recall this, then we did an episode
about David Copperfield's insane show at the MGM Grand.
Mike and I had seen it and we were mainly describing it
to Jason who had not seen it.
Now you have seen it.
You've experienced Live the Impossible.
And kind of I've been talking about like, oh, we should go,
we should go to Vegas.
She had never been to Vegas before.
And I've been a couple of times.
But that kind of lit the fire under my ass.
I was like, well, if we go, we have to see Copperfield.
Yeah.
Of course.
And as I was saying, because I, that's, that's where my
response video was filmed.
Right in front of the Copperfield Theater in the MGM Grand.
Next to the Blue 32 statue.
Yeah.
To the Chay Pack.
Succession news.
Yeah.
And Jason Willner texted me after he saw that and he said,
what did you think of the show?
And I said, it was the greatest theatrical experience of my life.
Yeah.
It is really, so I don't think I was fully prepared.
Even with you heard beat by beat.
Beat by beat.
But I, and I have to give the man credit because it's a very
interestingly paced show.
It is, I mean, I kept saying the whole thing.
I was reminded about Vegas.
A couple of things.
One, they, there are parts of Vegas.
Uh, like our main chunk of this episode is like, if you build a
theme park infrastructure and went, okay, we will come back to
check on this.
Never.
Uh, and then there are other parts where it's design elements that
you kind of, you kind of recognize that this is art.
Oh, David Hockney did this, but he drew it on an iPad and now it's
rejected on a screen and a lot of it, um, where it's like, oh, the
aesthetic is all aesthetics.
There's a lot of hanging glass everywhere.
There's a lot of hanging silver rock.
Like you recognize it, but it's, it's just overwhelming.
It looks good in the concept art, but once everything's been barfed on
and there's like, you know, plastic yard glasses littered everywhere.
What people say theme parks are the simulation of reality, like
simulation.
Oh, it's so fake Vegas kind of it.
And I don't mean that like as a derogatory, but it is, it is very
overwhelming.
I mean, I got back in two days later, we were at fries doing the fries
event and I was still mentally like, we were questioning this because you
were there and you were like, look, I'm just still exhausted.
I've been to vape, but it was like this two day.
That's a lot of days to recover from a no time zone shift.
You seem like you're still recovering now.
I'm still a little grog.
But why, why I think it was just, there's just so much mental stimuli.
There's so much sound and lights.
There's so much of everything lights.
There's too many lights.
Yeah.
Do you not think Las Vegas is overwhelming?
It is, but I'm I bounce back the next day.
I'm not like, oh, it is funny.
I mean, I got back from Vegas the week and a half ago.
The, I don't know when, which episode will come out first.
You were saying though, you napped immediately in Vegas.
Well, I didn't feel very, we took the first flight out.
And so I was like, seven AM, something like that.
Yeah.
And so like, I was like, I'm not going to do this.
And so like, I was up to like, you know, get dressed and like,
get in a lift and every like four 30 in the morning and stuff.
Sure.
You flew out of Burbank.
It did fly out of Burbank, which is a smaller airport.
And it's very cool because you get to walk on the tarmac.
Like, it's very, yeah.
Pan Am or something.
Yeah.
So getting into Vegas at like nine 30 in the morning, checking in,
dropping the bags and making a beeline for the M and M store.
You went, that was the first thing you did.
Very first thing.
And I have a suspicion here.
I have a suspicion that in a more relaxed state, you would have enjoyed this
experience a little more.
Well, I did enjoy a chunk of the experience.
I mean, I had a great time in Vegas.
I had a great time.
I just did not sleep.
I prefer, I read,
I like a lot better because you just kind of like zonk out on the flight,
but like I never sleep well if I have to get on like a seven AM flight.
I just feel awful.
And then I, it's the same time I were like, well,
maybe a cup of coffee will make me feel bad.
It just makes me feel a hundred times worse.
I would completely understand what you're saying.
If I hadn't seen evidence, the contrary, when we went to Orlando,
Orlando is a different animal for you.
I slept like a baby at your house.
We only slept for like five hours before we had to get up.
Yeah. But we were, you know, you have that juice, that show juice,
that positive vibe.
That makes me more tired because the adrenaline's going from the show.
And then when you wake up in the morning, you're like, ah, now I'm like,
I'm depleted.
I mean that, I mean, that might also just be that like Orlando,
the Orlando magic, you know, as they say,
it's just interesting.
He said as a basketball team,
I'm like, oh, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like,
I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like,
As a basketball team says, it's interesting because you're saying I got up early
for a flight and it devastated me. And I had to take a nap.
Did not feel well.
And but in Orlando, we slept for our excuse.
In Schomburg, we slept for about five hours.
We got on a I mean, not as quite early, but it was still like,
the turnaround was like five hours we were up and then we were going.
And I think I just knew I was going to Orlando.
I'll get a nap or two in.
And don't get me wrong.
Yeah, I and I like Vegas, but like it was also cold.
And that's true.
A little cold.
Like I don't the desert isn't my fell last a few days in the desert,
but it's not my favorite.
Right.
Vegas doesn't give you strength.
Orlando gives you strength.
That's my hypothesis.
I did walk like seven miles a day in Vegas.
Like you walk a lot.
You walk so much in our land.
We check phones and it was like twice.
We all walked a ton and you walked like double amount and you were fine.
You were rare and go like you were, you know,
that Orlando feeling that's what I'm I'm just it's interesting because I think
just Vegas, the feeling exhausts you in general.
Whereas Orlando, I think you're like, you are just energized.
I mean, look, I found some very relaxing.
It was a little too cold for the pool, but like half of the Bellagio is just
nice alcoves with couches like pleasant views into the courtyards and like
artwork everywhere.
So you take a seat, you know, you have some slushes.
We kind of did the we did the slot.
A lot of places doing the night like slushes in Vegas are very popular,
but like best friend, we went to the Roy Choi, LA celebrity chef,
Roy Choi has a restaurant and they have like nicer versions of the classic
like Tuesday, like a green apple slush in a little cup.
We had like a ginger and Jameson one and we had a Hennessy and Coke one.
Did you like the food?
The food was great.
Yeah.
I mean, I was I thought it would be different, but it's like his hit.
It's like kids like Korean barbecue tacos, rice and sure.
It was very good.
This is all nice, but I'm a little when are we going to get to the fireworks
factory?
I think that's my favorite.
I love this thing.
I have a feeling you guys don't love this thing as much as me.
I'm just saying I want to get to it someday.
No, it's fine.
I know we'll get to it.
So I hit the hit the quick highlights and then we'll do a little copper field
and then we'll get to it.
Sure.
Thank you, Mike.
You're welcome.
Thanks.
A great hotel clearly going for younger people.
Italy.
I mean, incredible.
Scott, you you eat Italy.
It's amazing.
Italy is like how would you describe it?
It's like a block long Italian market with lots of stalls and everything's very
free.
You can get a big pile of pretty cheap food, like really good meats and cheese,
but like for pretty cheap and cheap stuff started to find in Vegas.
Oh, it's not hard to find, but it's like garbage.
This is like quality food for cheap.
And when you are like have a meal where it's like, oh, let's just go eat at the
hotel.
When your options are like pizza and fresh pasta places stay open pretty late.
There's one stall that's just doing pizza slices and 3 a.m.
if you want.
Yeah.
And the tell us stuffed fried dough like on the night.
Were you up?
How late were you up every night?
Two or three one night we went to on the record, which is like the speakeasy kind
of yes.
I've been I've been multiple times.
Tenders told us like, oh, it's not a club and it's like after 10 minutes it's a
club.
It's a night.
It's too.
I'll ask about 30 minutes because it was just so much.
Well, there are there are little areas that you can go and then aren't as intense.
There's like an outdoor ish area there.
I mean, it's not really.
Okay.
Maybe it was a very crowded night.
And then there's the secret room there as well.
Very cool.
That's where there's a wall.
That's a fake thing.
And it's a door and you go in and it's a little speakeasy room.
I'm just watching my beloved red and yellow melts.
They're just melting in the desert.
Oh, hey, hey, private room or do this is the thing.
It was very, very, very, very, uh, yeah.
Uh, Italy.
Hi, Marks.
Uh, is very funny because it's across the street from the MGM Graham.
What's very nice hotel.
Park MGM.
Nice.
Clearly going for a younger crowd.
There's no buffet.
The food's all pretty good.
Yeah.
A reasonable size, casino floor, not overwhelming.
A tram, a free people mover, a tram that'll take you up to the Bellagio.
That is great.
And gambling.
Yeah.
Slots.
Uh, we really liked, uh, my girlfriend won like 80 bucks on the Britney Spears slot,
which is so fun.
It's got the bass vibrations.
It's blasting clips.
So the music video, I won $80 and I'm like, show my slot machine.
We saw that was always occupied.
Cause it's now they have a fun thing where like there's a computer console and you can
play a fake video game while you're doing the slots.
So there's like extra elements of just then the normal, like you pull the slot and you
don't understand what the amounts mean.
Now it feels like you're actually doing something else.
You're probably, it's just a fake thing, but still it's fun.
We were both kind of up and down on the virtual blackjack where it's like the fake dealer
and sure no one's yelling at you.
Uh, that's fun.
Uh, I don't know.
I probably broke even.
Oh, we, I don't know.
All right.
I just put a little in the slots or, um,
You did not see Aerosmith and the deuces are wild tour.
We did not see and Gaga was not there.
Uh, neither of them were there, but we saw Copperfield.
Yes.
Now do I have some Copperfield observations written down and I have some questions and
I was thinking you guys could ask me some questions of like, did he still do this, that
sort of thing?
Because I feel like,
I think he does most of the things.
I think it's just the order in which he does it.
Are we still shaking your tail feather?
Do we still have a duck that is walking around to shake your tail feather?
Uh, no.
Tail feathers are not being shaken.
There was no duck.
Whoa.
Okay.
Duck is out because it was really a fragment of a previous thing.
Yeah.
I think that didn't make sense already.
So that's probably a good trim though.
I missed the duck.
All right.
Skeleton, the skeleton of the dinosaur.
Of course.
That's a big fan.
Of course it was not in our show.
That was not in yours.
Not in mine, but in Scott's and on most people that go see the skeleton.
It was probably broken that night.
The skeleton is after he waves to his, does the symbol to his father.
Right.
So we are back to it.
It culminates in, in skeleton.
I think because he, that is clearly just video editing.
Like that's just a trick.
That's just, you edited a movie and I think he was like, and one last thing, one last
bit of the impossible, because that is what I was really impressed by in the show.
The first half is kind of a standard magic show with a lot of like, Oh, wow.
Like he makes, he appears on a motorcycle and then he appears on a Lincoln.
How checked out was he?
I, I was hard to tell cause he was doing kind of like the snide delivery, the like toss
off like Jesus Christ, come on.
Like he, that's the persona and I, I want, I have to go back and watch a TV specialist
cause I was like, I don't remember him being the sticky and the TV specials cause he was
kind of like winking at the audience a lot.
Like were there people from out of town that didn't speak English that he would goof on?
I think one person maybe from Albania.
Of course.
They're all plant.
I'm convinced they're all plants.
I was convinced the person blue 32, which incredible RC.
We were maybe 10 feet away from blue 32 coming out of the case.
You don't know.
And you hadn't heard the other patron episode blue 32 is a little blue alien that met David
Copperfield's father when David Copperfield's father worked at area 51.
And there's a lot of story that we got into on that other episode.
But if you're behind this paywall, you can go back and listen to that.
He is a being of pure love.
His message is love.
And he also loves fucking poon.
Yes.
He is a big old horn dog.
As I was watching the show, I forgot he is crass and horny in addition to giving a message
of love.
She likes hot.
She's hot, David.
But watching him like wiggle around and then they put some on the box and he's like a little
robot.
Still get lucky.
We changed the song.
Does it get lucky?
Uh, I, I think when he's like the mayor Pete dance, they made it topical.
Is that what he taught?
He does this thing where he's like, oh, my old flame, you still stripping and it's an
old lady.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm convinced.
I'm convinced they're a plan.
The lady's not there.
There's no lady.
It's just a shot.
Okay.
That's what I was trying to figure out too.
Cause I realized at a certain point, cause he did the like turning a tissue into a rose.
Yeah.
Six feet behind us.
Like we were front row center.
Like we were almost underneath the UFO.
Yeah.
And get good seats for this is not the priciest thing to get really good seats.
It's on par with other Vegas shows and cheaper than like big musical acts.
Uh, I realized watching that though, like the cameras have a monitor on the front so
he can see what in theory you would think what's being filmed, but I'm trying to think
if it's, if he is seeing what's on the screens.
Cause I think sometimes that's a live feed from those cameras.
And sometimes I think it's old video.
It's like shot videos and he's just so precise with his movements and where's the same outfit
every night.
Yes.
He does.
He's filmed in advance.
Uh, when you guys saw it, did he play a clip of the Meek Mill Rick Ross song, black magic?
I don't think that goes David Copperfield, David Copperfield.
No, no, no, no.
Maybach music track that they sample.
Wow.
In between what, uh, Oh sugar sugar.
You can't hurry love.
Um, what were the, I'm a believer he's playing all of these songs and then it cuts to an
excerpt as people are filing it of the Maybach music song.
Wow.
You got to see this again to see the updated version.
It looks like there's a video where Rick Ross brings out David Copperfield to this song.
Copperfield is hung out with Rick Ross.
Wow.
Whoa.
Oh boy.
That's crazy.
This is exciting.
Uh, uh, Ooh, Hey here.
Just, just, just so you see it, just to see these folks together.
Oh my gosh.
Yes.
Very good.
This is excellent wrapping.
Yeah.
I have to say this is some of the best wrapping I've ever seen.
Haha.
What's your name Rick?
Okay, Rick.
Okay.
So Rick and Rick has a beard.
All right.
Rick with the beard now.
Why keep your hands on the handkerchief and uh,
So I should say after the show, we went out into the lobby and asked, and I feel like
one of you also asked this, is that statue of blue 32?
Cause there's blue 32 above the bar and the merch stand.
Is that for sale?
And we were told, no, that's from David's private collection.
Whoa.
Or David's personal collection.
And I said, do you get asked that a lot?
And she just nodded yes.
The only merch besides a t-shirt with his face on it and the blue 32 fanny pack available
for sale was like a logo t-shirt for the Island.
Musha K.
Yeah.
Oh, you can buy Musha K merch.
You can buy a Musha K merch.
Wow.
And also if you haven't heard the episode, yeah, this is, well, it's his, it's his Island
where monkeys someday will do things for you.
Yeah.
They'll hug, they'll hug you.
I believe they'll crawl over you and give you love.
Wow.
Yeah.
Love.
Love David.
Monkey love David.
That's exciting.
Wow.
But I mean, you were in, even though you knew it all.
So this is good because if listeners listen to our episode and they don't want to go to
the show, so they think it's spoilers that maybe it doesn't matter.
Maybe the experience.
Yeah.
It's all other thing to see it in person.
Because again, like this sort of stuff, even if you see like a touring magic act, like
It's a pretty, I was surprised by how kind of intimate the theater was.
It was smaller than I was expecting.
Everything was much closer than I was expecting.
It's not a room you expect a UFO.
You expect a goddamn UFO to be in.
Jesus Christ.
Like he kept, he would give like an instruction real fast.
And when someone didn't get it, he would go, Jesus Christ, come on.
Like, and it was the right amount of body for like that kind of out of town audience.
But it's either all plants.
I'm convinced they're all plants.
And he goes, Jesus Christ, come on.
And like it's the same bit with almost everybody where they don't know what he's doing and
he's making fun of them.
I mean, it's all Mr. I mean, halfway through the first half is a traditional magic show.
And then halfway through he turns to like, and this is a magic inspired story where it
becomes much more play like.
How is that?
How great is that moment when you realize, oh, here's the turn.
Here's the turn.
Sit down everyone.
I imagine my father's warehouse, my father's secret warehouse and the things he left me.
I mean, it's just so you're like, oh, you're not.
This isn't quite magic.
That's a puppet.
Although blue 32 does appear, you know, I mean, it in and of itself is magically realistic
electronics.
A guy, an audience, a person helps with the thing whose sister had passed.
Was that in your shows?
That's always there.
They're always helping.
Fake.
Yep.
Yeah.
Fake.
Is it possible?
Oh, what are you playing?
This is black magic.
OK.
Hmm.
I'm going to have to plug that into the episode there.
Yep.
Yes.
The idea.
So so he has a fictional scenario where someone's sister died and they get to do magic.
The brother gets to do magic in honor of the sister, but it happens every show, every show.
So ridiculous.
A lot of siblings die.
You get the email.
Yes.
So we all have the email now.
And mine, of course, had the skeleton in it.
They didn't even take it out.
Oh, wow.
They didn't even.
Because, yeah, so basically before the show, you put your phone in a box.
They say like, you'll get an email and it's like they send you an email already and they
said, don't look at it yet.
And then when at the end, it'll say it says everything that happened during the show.
So it has all the specifics and it has everything that happened.
But they didn't bother to take the skeleton out of our email.
So it's just in the email.
Right.
So I'll be honest, the illusion was a bit broken for us when you're reading a letter
that's describing what you saw.
Right.
It is not what you saw.
Yes.
I forget.
There was one moment where I was like, I think that video is not a lot like I would.
There's one or two where we caught.
I mean, we're close enough.
Jane was like, I think I see a drone holding up the UFO.
Like the like, oh, is that what it is?
Or that like there might the corners might be the propeller like, but we weren't sure
we weren't 100% sure.
Regardless, it does go pitch black.
And then suddenly there's a giant UFO.
No matter how it's operated.
It's very, very impressive.
Sad though that blue 32 has to see his family one last time to say goodbye.
I don't know that that part was thought out very well.
Well, he died.
We can't rehash this, but I'm going to, he's going to die.
And then he doesn't die.
I guess he's going to die.
David, David, a time stone.
Yeah, the time stone.
Once you get time stones involved, you only get so many.
And if your hearts, if your time stones start failing or you give some away to a friend
and that's the end of you, then your clock, your clock's running out.
Very simple, David.
David, very simple.
I used to have 10 time stones and eight of them.
I gambled away and one of them, I just drink too much and it's shriveled up.
Thus you're getting my last.
So that's the end of me.
I should have been smarter about all this.
You know, I know about love, but I don't know about time stone management.
This is if this sounds crazy, this is the show.
Like this is basically the show.
Only in Vegas.
Yeah.
You know, only in Vegas.
He's cradling him like the Christ child.
He does cradle him lovingly.
As he does, he intones about love and they didn't listen.
Only you loved me.
You cocoon me in your arms.
And David is like tossing the lines off as if he's just doing the rest of the show.
Sorry, they've danced to you.
Human beings are heathens.
You never know the depths of cruelty that the human race can sink to and they crucified
you.
You're thrown in the trash pile of life.
Soon you'll be a corpse.
Oh, well.
La da da da.
And here we go.
You got to give him credit.
Kind of predicted Baby Yoda before Baby Yoda though.
It is very Baby Yoda.
It's protecting a child.
Yeah, the child.
An important mission.
Yeah.
He probably got pissed when he saw the Mandalorian.
I pitted through something through the TV.
And you're telling me everyone in the world loves this.
And yet no one.
I don't know.
They just, you know, reveal it all at once.
It's just available everywhere.
Everyone's watching it.
There's shirts of it.
There's there's no suspense.
I've kept blue off of merchandise.
I've made it.
You can't see his picture anywhere.
That's the way to build suspense.
You don't have to be an M life member to see Baby Yoda.
Check the records.
Mr. Mr. John Favreau must have been in the audience for one of my performances.
Check the record.
He must.
He must have stolen this from me.
He's of course saying that.
He's of course saying that to monkeys on the island of Muzhike.
Fetch the tapes.
Monkeys are going through trying to figure out if John Favreau ever was there.
It's the wrong night.
No, not the political speech writer, John Favreau, the swingers guy, the other one,
the heavier one.
He's lost a lot of weight, but he's still a little.
Come on, Roy.
Joy's best friend.
Don't you monkeys know how to scan footage?
God, how am I ever going to unleash you to give love to my customers?
And you didn't settle my lawsuit.
It's the last time I hire monkey attorneys.
It's a pretty good show, honestly, of Copperfield on an island with all monkeys.
Only monkey cast.
It's sort of a cast away where he's the only one talking.
Yeah, you know, you do get emotion out of the monkeys.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. You fall in love with the monkeys and they're not treated well.
They got to get him on Quibi.
You know, we got to get some more magic on these.
I think Netflix is one or two magic things, but they don't promote them a lot.
Well, if they can't get him, they get Lance Burton, who's already a content creator.
Well, yeah, like his restaurant.
Just slide it down to Lance Burton.
Lance, I don't know. Lance Burton.
Yeah, Lance Burton is made, of course, the movie Billy Toppett.
Anyway, really, we got to go.
We got to do it soon.
Yeah. Well, so I mean, that was that's kind of the long and short of it.
Yeah. I'm glad you're part of the club now.
And if we're if we're talking about nonplussed performances,
then that is a perfect segue into the realm of the professor,
which is the M&M's store on the strip in Las Vegas.
And it's mainly the 3D movie within.
I lost my M in Vegas.
And that's where you're in the store and you're watching the movie.
But within that, also, you're in the M&M's lab, M&M's laboratory.
I you know, but before that,
so if you if you've never been to this thing or if you don't know where it is
or how to get to if you're so if you're staying in Vegas, it's close to the MGM.
MGM is probably the main hotel that is close to it's part of something called
the Showcase Mall, which is an incredibly confusing complex.
I was trying to find a movie theater there and got way lost.
I'm on a sky bridge that leads to nothing.
And the Coca Cola store is part of that.
Yeah, the Coca Cola store is a few doors down.
The landmark is a hundred foot tall Coke bottle.
Right.
This this mall is pretty in general.
This is like a hub of the kind of dumb nonsense that we like with that.
With like, OK, right now, 100 foot Coke bottle.
There's Denny's in there.
Yep. There's a hard rock cafe.
You know, still now let's hold on there.
I you can't undersell that part of the complex.
Because you go over if you go from Park MGM, the other side of the street,
like where New York, New York and Park MGM are.
You cross a bridge over Las Vegas Boulevard.
And the first thing you are greeted by is a three story building.
Denny's on the bottom floor.
Hard rock on the top to kind of a fall from grace for the hard rock.
Like kind of the upstairs neighbors to upstairs neighbors.
It's kind of obscured the sign by the sky bridge.
And like it's competing for attention for like a sketchers
logo and a marshal and Ross Marshall.
It is the boringest.
Or this they have this this amazing real estate and it's just a Ross there.
That strip was like that was the first thing we did after we dropped our bags
was go over to the M&M store and I'm like, it's nine in the morning.
Like, this is too much. This is too much.
I was like, this is sad.
Our hotel is so nice.
And MGM is nice.
I was like, this strip is so odd.
And then we walked into the M&M store and that smell.
Oh, my God. You warned me.
But I was not feeling very good.
And I was like, we got to see this movie.
We got to get it.
And then you're rushing through the smell like it's like it's carbon monoxide.
The smell is like trying to breathe it in.
Hurry. Where is it? Fourth floor all the way up.
Oh, God. I mean, by the time I got out to the fourth floor, I was like,
I feel like I'm going to be sick.
I was going to tip out of the fourth floor down on fall down onto the strip.
I was a window.
It's like whatever canister smell canister they were using for their fake
chocolate smell in the M&M store.
It's like mildew started growing.
Like it's it's just it's like off.
It's like something's wrong with the smell.
It ran out in 2000.
And now it's just like the specks of chocolate and Legionnaires disease.
Or it's like if if like
somebody does left a pile of M&M's behind like a heater in there
and no one's found it.
And it's just like it sort of made it the smell part of the heating system.
No, it's yellow's corpse.
Yeah. Yes.
It's running away for years.
Yes. The M&M's 5000 couldn't find them.
No one could hear his high radiator.
Constant screams.
Now, the theater does not smell.
No, no. It does not go into the theater, which is a godsend.
Yes. So you're I mean, there's not a lot to say about the M&M store itself.
There is a fund.
Once you get to the fourth floor, this is where the attractions are,
because it also forget if it's still there.
Maybe you could tell if there's like a race car that's M&M's branded.
And I have pictures with M's who are in like NASCAR racing gear.
So that's potentially something that's happening up there or used to.
I don't recall.
I think there was more like put your face on M&M's.
Sure. I mean, obviously, personalized.
Yeah. Which I think the cheapest thing you go by was like twenty two dollars
because you have to fill a contraption with the personalized M&M's.
And it only makes sense.
Buying two candies.
Yeah, that's that should be.
That should only cost me but 15 cents.
The one floor is just like fill up a thing like big tubes of M&M's that you could fill.
I mean, it was a very it's a very thorough story.
If you like M&M's. Yeah.
And I'm a big peanut M&M guy.
Mm hmm. Really?
You like your top?
I think that's my top.
Like, Crafts are if you're on set, if I'm on set, like there's
I'm there's a very good chance I'm wired on coffee and peanut M&M's.
Just way to way to ground to shoot.
Wired.
Scott, what's your preference?
I think I like, I mean, regular, but then within that holiday,
the holiday ones make me happy.
Interesting. I like just a red and green.
OK, but like the norm, those are the normal flavor.
But you like the festive, the festive nature.
Yeah. I feel like I go regular or peanut butter.
Peanut butter is solid.
Peanut butter is very good. Sure, sure.
So you're you're heading up to this movie theater.
I didn't know about any of this.
Now it's a thing I tell everybody.
Oh, you're going to Vegas.
You got to go to the M&M store movie.
But I didn't know.
We just stumbled into it.
I just saw some signage that said free 4D movie.
Yes. Oh, man.
You're kidding me.
I read that the first time we went to, I was on such a high
because the strange in I had, I was able to get a free meal,
including drinks at the Fat Burger on the strip.
Well, I had a big old beer and the Fat Burger people could not have been nicer.
I was just on the high from this experience.
Sandal and a nice little beer buzz.
So I was I was having a great day.
This is what I think might factor into because you're there.
You're stressed out early in the morning.
You're sleepless. Me, I'm like, I just had a beer.
I'm I'm feeling fine.
I'm in heaven.
I took a quick nap.
Bye, biker resigned.
And then we had pizza at Italy and I felt like a million bucks.
OK, so my thing about the thing I like about Vegas,
you can do whatever you want at any given time.
You can probably find where and whatever your heart desires.
You can nap.
You can nap on the other side of the bed.
You can ride a free tram just back and forth.
So it goes to insane real estate.
Now, the largest, the largest
privately funded real estate project in the country,
the city center area.
Oh, that'll be interesting.
I like it in there.
Yeah. So yeah.
So in my way, like 40 movie.
Oh, my God, I got it.
I don't think I even noticed the smell to the degree that you guys.
That's what's interesting.
We've talked about this before.
It doesn't seem like you registered the smell.
I think the way Jason was in Orlando where he's ignoring any problem that exists,
I think I was I'm maybe a little more I was
I was pretty psyched in Vegas.
Also, give me a beer and I'm I'm I'm a thousand percent.
I'm feeling great.
It's not rushing up the stairs.
I don't notice this at all.
The smell was so bad, I'm sure it knocks down my enjoyment of anything in the store.
I know is horrible.
Horrible. OK, you were it was very early for you.
Beer for you was I did I have a beer in me or anything?
Yes. No, I know.
I think it was in the middle of the day.
I don't think we had anything to drink.
This is, I think, the crucial.
You have to be a little bit buzzed to love.
And because also the same day after that, I had a bunch of time to kill.
I never been to the movie theater there.
And we ended up seeing in that same complex Jurassic World.
And I think from that good mood, I didn't think Jurassic World was dogshit.
Oh, I remember this. You were like, we liked it.
We had a good time. You got to have fun.
Yeah, I don't know.
And I think it was all I think it was that beer talking.
Wow. That was more fun.
It was more fun to be in a loving mood.
Sure. Yeah, I liked it.
I liked it more when I watched it, like with the Christmas tree
on with the whole family like that was that was fun. Sure.
So, you know, I'm racing up the stairs and on the on the way up,
you're seeing movie posters because you're going to see M and yellow
or M and yellow, red and yellow, who you love from the commercials.
And they're going to be in their own movie, their own non feature length film,
their own nine minute film.
Sounds great to me.
And then you get a little taste of like what other movies would be that they're in,
including M's in Black,
which has the tagline protecting the earth from the scum of the candy bowl.
Not to be confused with women in black, too,
which we found at Fry's Electronics with the tagline, skip ahead,
protecting the earth from the come of the universe.
I might still prefer women in black, too,
but still happy to see a little men in black nod.
I and you know, and this is also a good reminder that you're going to see
you're see, you know, the characters from this Christmas ad
that is the perennial Christmas ad that will never go away.
It's this and the Cadbury Easter.
Yeah, for that, they will never refilm. Yes. Right.
But that one with Santa where Santa faints, he does exist.
I do exist.
And I think you always forget about that.
Who the you guys know offhand who the M&Ms are.
I do. Yes. Yeah.
Voiced over great Billy West, one of the greatest ever.
And J.K. Simmons is yellow.
I forget that fact a lot.
It's so it's it's so not his usual character.
But he has done like he was in Guys and Dolls in the like 90s
revival with Nathan Lane.
Was he? He was one of the supporting guys.
Yeah, he's one of those guys.
Now you go back and see him and like, you know, little character.
It's like it's like when you go back and see Giamatti in smaller roles
and you forget like you didn't think this guy would be the main star of movies
at some point in time.
If you add up that he's that he's in this Christmas
bad that will never go away.
And he's farmed. He's the farmer's guy. Yes.
I mean, I wondered this about somebody, Seth McFarlane, in a recent episode is
does J.K. Simmons have one billion dollars?
It's possible. Yes. At this point.
And not not for that reason, but I was going to ask you this, Mike.
Do you consider J.K. Simmons an enemy because he's farmers
and you are team Allstate from your.
Well, I'm not look, I'm not under I'm not getting paid by Allstate anymore.
So I'm open to the highest bidder.
I'm willing to flip now like the spring like spring guy.
If they want, they should just refilm the Allstate commercial
I was in for progressive.
Well, let's do it.
Let's stick it to Allstate for not keep continuing to pay me free money.
You turn the camera.
It's me, the guy who the Hayes Burt voiced woman.
Right. Bested.
Yeah. So now I'm here for progressive.
It'll be just as big of a campaign because that's spring.
I still go and they're still they're doing that.
He is truly firmly the face of sprint.
It's wild. Yeah. Yeah.
So now let's flip, Mike.
Let's put any insurance company. Yeah.
Geico's revisiting old ads.
Why not visiting revisit?
Not there. Yes. Yeah, I agree.
So no, I'm well, I'm willing to get on the farmer's team.
Yeah. Yeah. He needs a sidekick.
And it's me.
His bumbling like your your your papers, sir.
Yeah. And then he's always like tour, looking around a museum or something.
Yes. And you like trip the floors to slick and you slip and fall.
Yeah. You can be mean to me. That'll be funny. Yeah.
I wanted to go full whiplash on the other insurance company.
Not by tempo.
No, I don't.
Oh, so you wait in line.
And one thing I will say, was it a little crowded for you for either of you?
Well, I went to the first show of the day and we were the first ones in line
where we're like, when is it? Oh, thank God.
It starts in 10 minutes.
Are you saying there was a crowded in the theater? Yeah.
No. See, I've been and my friend,
Siler and Kio just went the pacts full room and we'll go with a full room, too.
Like there are times I think depending on when you go who again, maybe I've just
I'm just glass half full on this thing. Yeah, I've seen packed psyched audience.
Psyched to be there.
There were like six, seven people in with us.
Maybe there was like 10 other people. I mean, there was a decent.
I've done it with less, but I've definitely done it where they can't like
people have to wait for the next show because there's so many in there.
My memory is that there's a child screaming before we started.
Yeah, that was a child screaming.
Oh, yes. I think there's a fourth floor that I kept going.
The smell is oh my God.
The smell is insane.
And there's a child screaming.
There's like a couple of people in line.
People would I feel like we there were people wandered up and like
they would explain to them what the like this is a 40 movie and they'd go, OK.
And they turn around and didn't go in line.
They want to pass down mad.
You got to if you went in Rome, you got to check it out.
Hey, I agree.
So you're you get into the theater and realize this is more than a movie theater.
This is a laboratory.
You're you're at the M&M's Academy, not unlike the farmers.
Yeah, this is this is a place of education.
It's like the X-Men's Mansion, the Xavier School for Gifted Candy.
Oh, so this is officially the M&M's Academy.
The room that you're in.
Yeah. Is the M&M's.
I don't know if any of the rest of the store is the M&M's Academy. Right.
And there's no pre-show to lead you in or a sign that tells you
you're in the M&M's Academy.
Yeah. And it's that's just in that space is where that reality exists.
Because I think it's right outside that they have this big like
3D sort of display of the M&M's and like suits.
And it's like Las Vegas plastic.
They're they're like the Rat Pack, what you're showing.
Yeah. So it doesn't.
And that's me. I went with them.
It doesn't ease.
It doesn't ease you into the narrative.
No, not really. You just go in there.
Then pre-show. There's no world building.
Yeah. So it's a shock that you end up at an academy,
which is a science lab primarily.
And even when you walk in the room, you're not sure what you're looking at
because there's like computer panels and flashing lights,
especially this one little space on the side with kind of a
it looks like a test tube or a big, big tube or door or something.
And, you know, full, big, bright light bulbs all the way around.
And that's the space that your host steps into.
And this is where I felt this is mainly the movie.
I could take her leave parts of it, the story or it smells whatever.
But I just fell in love with when it begins and it and, you know,
there's a range of who you could get as part of this experience.
But when we saw the first time, the most nonplussed teenager walks in
in a lab coat and and says, Hello, welcome to my laboratory.
I am the professor.
And seeing a teenager declare that they are the professor
just made me so happy.
And you could see videos where people are giving it a little more.
But even giving it more is just so no one.
No one doing this looks like they would be called the professor. No.
My professor seemed like he was about to cry.
I was not sure if he was supposed to be.
I was not sure.
I saw he was wearing a lab coat, which he immediately ripped a pocket.
Like the pocket lab.
He went, no, it's my pocket.
I hate that.
It was like, what?
I think you might have gotten the professor.
Sounds like your professor was the best.
But he wouldn't put the headset mic.
He just had it like around his neck.
So we couldn't really hear him that well.
Like it's one of the headset mics can be rough in general.
They could sometimes just be faintly attaching to the to like
the quietest speaker ever. Yeah.
And that's that's the case here.
Yes, a professor in a headset mic.
Do you do you have a recollection about your professor?
I do. He he was fine.
It wasn't it wasn't anything.
It was neither here nor there.
It was neither here nor there, which I think did color our viewing of it.
Because it is fun that a guy in a lab coat comes in, but he wasn't like
he wasn't an Emmett Brown type.
He wasn't like a 15 year old who couldn't deliver lines.
So it was just like, oh, yeah.
Hello, I'm the professor.
The last time we went, I took a video and the guy really had it.
The guy was really good.
Aside from the age being wrong, he's probably like 22.
It just is not enough time for someone to be a become a professor unless.
Yeah, you need the house or type.
Yeah, you need someone who looks like the guy who played Professor
Keane being from the Richie Richie Rich movie is that in one of those films,
that is Eugene Levy.
It's not in the first one.
I believe in the straight to video Christmas wish.
That's Eugene Levy.
It is Eugene. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I forget the guy's name.
You know, I'm talking about in the first and the Macaulay Culkin, Richie Rich.
It in the in our call.
I don't know. But yes, he's got to be like he's got to be stately.
He's got to be stiff. But this guy was definitely gay.
And there's like clearly a range where they can do a bigger like,
allow me to introduce myself.
I am the professor.
But the main dialogue and I'd prefer to do it as the first one I saw.
Yeah, please. You never forget your first professor.
Hello. Welcome to my laboratory.
I am a professor and I'm here to introduce my brand new invention.
This is a truck and look at Eminem's all over the world.
It's been very like that's that theme park voice.
That is like announcement theme park voice when the person doesn't have like a take on it.
It's similar to I'm sure I've said this before the show before.
But when I the maybe the only time I ever saw the movie Golden Dreams,
that was in the this what is now location of Little Mermaid,
that a nonplussed teenager said, please gather our belongings,
including your dreams and exit as a writer of the theater.
Didn't register as a joke or anything.
Just said so dead inside.
Oh, you got a custodial here.
We got a dream clean up some other dreams.
I'm not telling you, please.
Spilled especially high.
I'm not going to make it to Broadway.
I'm not going to be a dancer.
A lot of dreams got spilled in that Chippendale Acorn Treehouse in Toontown.
Our kids have some so many dreams in here.
So, yes, so this is the premise that you are in the academy
and there's an invention that it's called.
Ladies and gentlemen, boys and girls, I give you the M&M's 5000.
The M&M's 5000, which has the ability to locate any M&M,
right, wherever it is in the world.
So it is like X-Men.
It's like Cerebro, which is Professor X computer
that he uses to track all the mutants in the world.
And he puts it on. That's his helmet.
You've ever seen Patrick Stewart with the helmet like thing he puts on.
That is Cerebro, which tracks all the mutants in the world.
This is all. So there's a lot of X-Men.
Yes, I believe. Yes, it feels like that.
When did the first X-Men movie come out?
2000.
Yes, well ahead of it.
I believe this experience opened in 1999.
It opened in 99.
It won a FIA in 1999.
Good. Yes.
It could. I mean, Cerebro is all of the mythology has been around.
This could be a comic. Yeah.
And there's the animated series was on very much around the same time.
Huge in the 90s.
Probably was. It could have been or not.
Before that, you know, Red and Yellow were supposed to be here today,
but I can't find them anywhere.
So let's get started without them.
So then they power up a machine and you're watching kind of like,
you know, early, you know, rudimentary 3D animation
showing you this lab and this big it's
just generic sort of zips and zaps kind of machine.
Once they tap into it, there's a big scan of the world.
And we're going to find Red and Yellow and get them in here
because that's who you're there to see.
Of course, how's Red and Yellow?
And it happens to track them to elsewhere in Las Vegas at,
you know, at a generic casino, the Casino Generico.
It's unlabeled.
I've been blown up by this point.
Yes, it's been long, long since demolished.
Yeah, yeah. Exploded.
And they are at a
roulette table there.
Yeah, yeah, it's a roulette table.
They're placing bets that you get a shot.
And I forgot this to last time I went.
You get a shot of the dealer.
The dealer is played by an actor named Dave Rubrick,
who is the host of Supermarket Sweep.
Yes, we squealed with delight. Yeah.
Yes, we were very that was maybe the highlight of the whole thing.
Yeah. I'm glad you're equally fond of Dave Rubrick.
Yes, he's like he's not as human as Regis,
but he's still got his charm.
You know what I mean? Is that right?
The kind of yeah, Regis type.
He's like sort of an inoffensive host kind of guy.
There's like nothing going on there, but that's I don't mean that as an insult.
No, I don't mean it as a pleasant.
Yeah, I could not tell you any characteristics of him.
Nice, good. He seems nice.
And I like him. Yes, but he's good, likeable.
Yeah, but he doesn't have any personality.
Really? But I mean, more personality than some of these actors
may be playing the professor.
I guess. Yeah, I guess.
I take that back. There's personality there.
I'm very fond of Dave Ruprecht.
I'd love to have Dave Ruprecht on the show.
You know, it might be fun to talk to who is the writer of this film.
Do you know who wrote this film? Yeah, I did.
That was what surprised me.
Yes. A person not that far a person, a fairly reachable person.
Here to fill us in. Yeah.
David Cobb, whose current title is principal of creative development
at the Thinkwell Group, who you've mentioned on the show before.
She's on Twitter, very active theme park Twitter person.
Yeah. Who I was looking up other credits,
wrote the Borg invasion at the Star Trek experience elsewhere in Vegas.
Got a Thea for that.
Well, yes. Multi Thea winner David.
David C Cobb wrote the pre show for T2 3D, which if that means the thing
where Shaq gets the free throw and the claw and the doctor
performing the surgery on the beach, that's a if he wrote that.
Oh, my God. Just that.
And it's a legend.
And the short in Men in Black Alien Attack.
The Goofus and Gallant sort of thing. Right.
Yeah, that's a hell of a filmography.
So he was working on Warner Brothers, Dubai.
Yes. Warner Brothers recently.
OK, OK. Also got a Thea for Caesar's Magical Empire,
which I think was the show Fountain Show.
I think it's the fountain show, which I get running because I walked by it
and I couldn't tell don't do as much as they used to.
The statues come to life, but I think there used to be a more involved show
and maybe even like then you went into a room and there was a bigger
40. OK, yeah, I believe.
So, God, this guy was the king of Vegas.
They entertainment now the king of Dubai themed entertainment.
We have to talk to this man. Let's try to talk to this man.
So the M&M's 5000 turns on, they find Dave Rubrecht.
Red is trying. Red's up, I think, and they're ignoring
their responsibilities back at the lab.
They're not saying hello to us, which they should be.
Red is getting greedy.
They're being like kind of lascivious, like they're a little bit like
they're a little routier than they are.
Really? Also a little more textured.
Yeah. Footage.
The texture looks nice.
The film quality, it's like rich film.
It's clearly film. Yeah, we film.
And I have some thoughts on that, but I'll keep describing the plot.
Yeah, I keep going. Why it was so.
OK, OK. But the.
Yeah, they are pretty jerky.
I was realizing, like, if I if I try to talk like him,
what's that line from there?
Like, I don't know. I never met the guy. Right.
It's just going to be we Chuck and Leno and the
blue 32, 32.
That's that's that book voice.
But he is pretty sleazy because he's like he's gambling instead of working.
And then this is the height of his sleaziness.
This is like putting your baby on the table.
This is like a precious watch your grandfather gave you.
You gamble with that.
He takes his only belonging.
I imagine if you're the writer of this, if you're David Cobb, you're like,
what do I have nothing to what do the M&Ms have that I could draw from?
Well, there's one thing on their body and it is the M.
So he peels off his M and puts it on red.
Put it on red.
And they spin the wheel and it is black and and he loses his M.
His M is cruelly, callously shoved into that little slot where all the money goes.
Yeah, it's kind of upsetting.
It's like taking your nose off your face and putting it on the table or something.
Like it feels like a part of him. Like, yeah.
Yeah. It's not just a shirt.
He's like, yeah, I got to get that back.
He doesn't seem like it is to get it.
Yellow seems more concerned about getting it back.
Like he knows the rules of being an M&M better than red does. Right.
Yeah. Yeah. That's your soul.
You can't go more than 30 minutes without that.
God won't be able to find you.
He'll melt. He'll disappear like back to the future.
You've forgotten.
So then the entire time the professor is protesting all this and like, no, red,
what are you doing? No, I shouldn't be doing that.
And then beams them to the lab, beams them in the lab.
Now they're upset. They're in an addled state.
And then we got to get that M back.
So they has this work.
Oh, I think the professor says you look like a skittle and then says, I'm out of here.
You guys figure it out.
Leaves the rest of it. You're just watching a movie.
There's like wind in the theater.
There's some effects like that.
Yeah, that's pretty fun.
It is fun.
It does feel like 4D right there.
They just turn the air on like real powerfully.
Pretty much.
I mean, it's still good.
I know. Get me wrong.
That's why the chocolate smell won't leave is that all the ventilation in the building
goes straight to the right.
Right. The Academy is sucking up all that.
Literally sucking it up.
And then then I get Aaron and I were talking about this, how, you know, an alcohol
might factor into this, but we're seeing every time we've sat down to do this,
we don't remember what happens.
We're very fond of it.
But yet we're surprised by Dave Rubrecked every time.
We do not remember that it becomes about going to the Department of Lost and Found.
I can't get this out of my mind this night.
I meant to look up.
Yeah, because then they go.
Then they're kind of they sucked out again.
Yes. I get fuzzy on why or.
Yeah, they go to like a limbo ask hell.
It reminds me honestly of like the Minion Mayhem
ride at Universal in a little way, not aesthetically, but in the same
like there's stuff happening and they have to like dodge it.
And it's it's all coming at you so fast and furious.
You don't know what. Yeah, I probably couldn't tell you what happens in Minion Mayhem.
Well, you go through Groo's secret.
I know that because I know the broad strokes of it.
It was a fart gun, but it smells like a banana.
And I know you bump into them at one point and they all become a big minion thing at once.
Yeah, which actually kind of happens here.
Similarly, is there is a similar thing to that, right?
There's a similar thing in this. Oh, yes.
Yeah, so that's why I think it's yeah, there's a few similar beats.
So we're at the we're at the Department of Lost and Found.
That's where he has to go to find his M.
And it's like a scary guy.
This feels like a very 70s movie.
Chitty Chitty Bang Bang kind of thing.
Yeah, a guy in big glasses and he's very judgmental.
And yeah, a lot of doors that lead to different lost things.
And he says that he asks, what do you need?
It's an M like, well, that's not animal, vegetable or mineral.
That's not classifiable.
So where so that means that it has to go to the scariest place of all.
Lost causes.
And then there's a big, gratingly loud scream.
They make a runner of playing this so many times, so many.
And it's yellow. It's yellow screaming.
But it's also extremely like sound effect.
Like that. I think that's I recognize it from sound effects library.
It is like a will. Is it the will?
It's not. It's not.
But it's like a famous.
It feels more like a woman's shriek.
OK. Yeah.
Which I believe is supposed to be the running joke.
It's like yellow. He has a very good voice.
But then, yeah, really, I don't even want to attempt one.
I don't want to blow out the mics that they put a lot of if I have a criticism.
It's a big if I think they lean on the screen.
They lean on the screen and it's very loud.
It's very, very loud.
Then they had to walk through the hallways from like the crazy bureaucracy
from Brazil, like they're in the Brazil building.
There's like some good set pieces in this.
That is what is impressive about it.
The sock bar, the horrifying socks.
Well, that's where we go.
We're looking at different.
There's different rooms, lost sheep, lost boys, lost time, lost sleep.
And then we end up at the lost sock lounge.
Right.
Is where all the single socks that came out of the dryer go.
And they're single and ready to mingle.
Yes, they're all really thirsty.
Thirsty socks.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
And that's where we end up with a love interest for yellow.
A yellow sock.
Jason seems like you're pretty fond of this component.
I I was just where these CGI were these stop motion.
I was trying to figure out.
I find that a little interesting.
Yeah.
You can't quite tell what's going on.
This is an interesting 40 movie.
The movie looks better than most movies in the last 10 years, I feel like.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's like a more good CGI and film.
Yeah, it is like a much more distinct style than most like mainstream movies.
And with that, we as Brazil and Chitty Chitty Bang.
It is right.
Yeah, there's like something like visually and setting wise going on here.
There's like a vibe, like stuff.
Mainstream movies are missing oftentimes, like a vibe
or like it's like a specific.
I'm glad I totally agree.
There is a distinct vibe of I lost my image.
Yes.
And you know, the kinds of the visual language.
They.
Yeah, yes, for sure.
Hell, yeah.
Did did Roger Deakins?
Does he the DP on this?
Do we know?
Well, I can tell you that I'll tell you about the DP.
It's a it's a pretty impressive DP.
The guy's name is Isadore Manic Mankowski,
and he is one of the strangest DP filmographies I've ever heard.
The Muppet movie, the original Muppet movie.
So that's the guy who shot that.
Jazz singer, the Neil Diamond version.
Oh, wow.
Sevenies was this guy.
He shot the TV movie Ewoks, the Battle for Endor.
Yeah, uh huh.
He is a Star Wars guy.
Wow.
Uh, in that respect, better off dead.
He shot the Harry Anderson absent minded professor for the magical world of Disney.
He shot a movie called Skin Deep with John Ritter that I'm very fond of.
I've never seen it.
It's I really like it.
A little kind of hidden gem.
Blake Edwards, I believe.
And the movie She Cried No, a TV movie of the week where Candice
Cameron is being harassed by Mark Paul Gosselaar.
Wow.
That's like a top tier good lifetime movie, like really watchable.
Watching him play dark is really interesting.
Right.
So crazy lineup.
But also, I think the reason he's part of this, he was not the credited DP, but a
he lent 3D expertise or I guess,
mainly more Muppet expertise to Muppet Vision 3D.
They got a very light like they actually was a 3D expert and then he has done
Muppets before, so they kind of worked in tandem to shoot Muppet Vision 3D.
Wow.
He acts and I know all this because there was a book about I just in Googling his
name discovered a book about 3D filmmaking where it seems like the
interviewer wants to keep it on track to I Lost My M in Vegas, much like me with
the episode.
He's like, let's go back to the Vegas movie, though.
And it seems like he does not really want to talk about it.
The interviewer had probably had a beer at Fatburger before.
It has to be that.
Putsy in the mood for M's.
Which I didn't remember.
This is the very first thing I did in Vegas.
The next day we went, we realized we were across the street from the Taco Bell
Cantina.
Oh, I didn't realize that.
That was fun.
It was, I mean, it was pretty empty all the week.
So that was like, oh, now you're saying this.
I'm like, oh, we should have gone there.
And then go.
I did last time I went straight Italy to that.
That's like ups and downs.
For sure.
Nice food.
And then this fun, stupid thing.
There was a funny story about shooting the first Muppet movie where they have to
build all the sets up really high because of the puppeteers.
And then they have to put actors up on these elevated risers.
But don't forget that the Muppet movie ends with an appearance from Orson Welles.
Yeah.
And thus they had to super reinforce that set because they were worried he was
going to fall through it.
I know this should have been on our fries episode, but I'm remembering now the
manager told me of fries that Marlon Brando, speaking of actors of size,
Marlon Brando was in the Burbank fries and they had to shut it down.
What?
So he could walk around.
They privately closed down.
That's what she told me.
Because he wanted to look at the monsters and everything.
I can't believe I forgot to say that.
Yes.
But we've got to figure out if we can find.
I just remembered it now.
It's got to be pictures.
And that thing is like motorcycle, dude.
It's like young Brando.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
We got to figure that out.
Thank you for.
I mean, I love that you're springing this on me.
Yeah, this is delightful.
This DP also has some bones to pick with Frank Oz because he picked up shooting
after Muppet Vision 3D.
Right. Right. Right.
Yeah.
Henson died and Henson was very specific about it's going to be long shots,
continuous shots like the lab we've right commented on that big deep.
And this guy was like, then Oz came in and shot everything close.
He just like threw this guy who just passed visions that vision out the window.
So he's a little mad at Frank Oz for changing Henson's plan.
Interesting.
I'll come back around to this guy a little bit, but we'll keep moving through this movie.
But that tells you a really good DP.
Excellent.
Yeah.
So a sexy yellow sock is hitting on Yela with all that expertise.
Then he films a sexy yellow sock.
This is fairly disturbing because she gets really flirty.
Yeah. He has a just full on love interest.
And he and then Red's like, hey, come on, love a boy.
But it's all her.
She is just she's pursuing.
It doesn't pay off, though.
No, they don't end up together.
You don't watch them do anything, which would it just consist of him
climbing into the sock?
What happens in the lost sock?
Var stays in the lost sock.
It is. I would like to say my favorite quote of this thing is the way where they
reveal that like, oh, we're not socks.
We're colored candy.
And then there's a record scratch and it gets very quiet.
And then his socks scarily stares straight down the barrel of the camera and says,
You're not socks.
I like that very much.
She oh, she her name is Bobby, by the way.
OK, Bobby Sox.
She shows him the way to an elevator.
They I'm lost here now.
I'm lost in this lost movie.
They have to go to the sock bar to find out where the M would be.
Yeah, this all is very confusing.
Yeah. Yeah. It gets a little fuzzy from here.
And then they they kind of self reflexively.
They kind of know that there's just the beats that they have to hit because they
go up and see a big scary furnace thing, which they call a big scary furnace thing.
It's like an alive monster that's chomping.
Right. It feels very well.
This is where it would end. Right.
The M's going to go into a furnace.
Yeah, it's it's like Toy Story 3. Of course.
Much later, the M's on a conveyor belt.
That's when you discover that they have a they were given a device
earlier that makes time stand still.
So they're they're clock stoppers also.
Yeah. Yeah.
The M's are clock stoppers.
So that's helpful.
But they also have another weapon up their sleeve.
A weapon of mini destruction.
It's time for the secret weapon, the minis, and they fly out towards camera.
And this is wonderful product placement and new product at the time.
At the time, still around.
I mean, they're still around, but I remember them pushing it a lot.
Yeah. Yeah.
Late 90s, minis are at the top of their game.
I like the minis.
Yeah. Sure.
Delicious. You like them as characters?
They're more like a swarm or a hive, kind of a collective entity.
There's no individuals. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
It's like the fish in Finding Nemo make the shapes.
You're right. The minions do it at some point.
They're so small that they're able to form like they all together
form like a helicopter and that helps red fly around.
They form a bugle like to do it.
And they, I don't know, then they get the M back.
What happens? He gets it back and he seems indifferent.
Yeah, he never cared.
And also, there's one shot where I especially like where I think the animation
is good and the texture of the M is also good flapping around.
Yellow is sacrificing himself.
He stretched out on top of a pipe and he's
blowing the M to try to stop it from falling into the furnace.
Yeah. Not his M.
Yeah. Yeah.
Did they? I forget.
Do they actually set something up in it that like he's going to die if he doesn't
have the M? Not really.
It's just like he's like lost a shirt.
Yeah. Yeah.
And it's like a shirt that didn't even care about that much.
And do M's.
Can you repaint one?
Can you have a fake one installed like it's a tooth?
Yeah. Right.
Or do you can you grow one?
Like, will it eventually?
I just like grits his teeth.
Will he grow one?
But maybe it's more like a finger and you don't regrow it.
But then I don't know, get a prosthetic.
I mean, that's that's complicated to do with a finger.
But you would have to think with an M prosthetic M.
That shouldn't be.
It already looks very fake in and of itself.
Well, you would think they were in the academy and the professor.
The professor has to have a solution to this.
It's got to be some kind of stem cell.
Yes.
Yes. Can we are we able to grow like beyond meat?
Can we grow M's artificially in a lab?
Whatever that clinic that Swedish clinic that Quincy Jones goes to
that he talked about in the interview where he said they were going to keep
them alive till 120, the go to that, pull that version of the M&M,
like a clinic for M&M's in Sweden.
In theory, though.
Well, but is it on American soil?
That's the problem because medicine isn't approved as fast in America.
Because that's why you have to go like to Brazil for certain procedures.
Or if you want to get your stem cell injection or mechs.
Yeah.
Wherever Sweden, all these places, they have a little more advanced technology than
we do, but Q should fill him in because he's friends with the M's.
I mean, yes, he knows all the major players in the world.
He's like good friends with the Obamas.
Yeah.
So any you know, he parties with the M's, of course.
So, yeah, there's got to be something.
Yeah.
Help help him out.
Come on, Q.
So then we yeah, we end.
Yeah, you're right. We end up back.
We did it.
M doesn't really care.
And then we're back in the lab where we started.
The professor comes back in.
All right.
Wait, let me take it.
What's all this noise in my lab?
And what have you guys been doing?
They say they found the M.
That's good, Red.
But how did you do that?
We just hit a few buttons and then they do hit buttons again
to demonstrate how they turn the machine on to go have their adventure.
They hit the wrong button.
The wind machine starts blowing again.
And then there's a pretty fun gag, not unlike the special effects stage
that we talked about, where there's like a little blackout thing.
The professor flies through a big flash of light.
Professor flies through a door disappears.
They like obliterated the professor.
Oh, professor dies at the end of the show or there or he's just like he or she is
just like in a limbo state.
So our professor, I have to give him credit because that flash happened
and he was gone and then the exit doors opened and he was there.
Cool.
So I think maybe that's where he puts his panache.
That's where he puts his spin.
Runs around real fast.
Yeah. Good for him.
I like that.
I watched a video on YouTube and at the start, a walk around Red.
The professor was like, get out of here, Red.
We got to start the presentation.
Walk around Red in the lab and he walks out.
What?
Professor's like, then the professor goes into like, all right, well, I can find
any man in the world.
Let's find Red and Yellow.
And that in that presentation, that the implication to me is that Red walks out
of the lab and then immediately hits the tables.
He just like slides down a chute in the MGM Grand Floor.
Human size, human size.
Well, big size.
Yeah.
Wow.
You know what they do say?
Should we look for the professor right after we hit the buffet?
So again, he doesn't care.
He's so self centered.
But that implies that the professor doesn't die.
Yeah, that's true. You're right.
You're right. The professor might they might have like.
They have a device to locate any academic in the world.
I remember when he went.
When he disappeared, I remember when they kill him off.
They killed the professor.
It's true enough that I think a sequel is required and demand.
Well, it certainly it certainly should be.
We should have David out and see if he can talk to the right people.
Boy, if we could talk to him.
Crispy. I mean, you can have Crispy in there.
You can have Carmel in there.
They've had it so many.
And I think this is I think the female care, I think like Brown is.
Let's get Brown in there.
Is Green is a female.
Green and Brown.
Well, yeah.
Well, why are we only dealing with the two?
It's time to flush out the ranks.
Let's get everybody else in there.
Right. I mean, this is green.
Green is they're in the store.
They're in the store.
They're represented there, but they're just not in the film.
Right.
And if if they're going to plus this up or refresh it, they might need to do
some things to be more to the liking of DP Isadore Mankowski.
Of course, again, in this interview, that's all the interviewer wants to talk about.
Tell me about the M&M's film.
Well, that film all together.
Well, that film is not very impressive, frankly.
It was shot with stereo vision and I didn't
particularly care for the quality or the of the lenses or the system.
So he's not happy with that high on it.
And he says, I don't get that voice through this whole quote.
He says, I didn't see the finished film
until a number of years after it was completed.
I went to Vegas to see it.
When I went to see the M&M's film, I was
absolutely horrified because if a 3D film isn't projected properly, it's a waste of time.
I went in there and got a headache right away because the images were out of focus.
I won't disagree with that.
I had a bit of a headache while watching it as well.
That's not a credit you would give it.
That's not. I like the spirit of the movie and the spirit of the professor,
but it's not the best circumstances to watch.
Not the highest optimum viewing.
It was just complete chaos as far as projection is concerned.
I went out and talked to the manager of the theater.
Beyond the fact that I had shot it, I was concerned.
I told him about the fact that it was being projected atrociously.
And it had to be lined up again.
And the audience would not get the full benefit of the production.
He apologized and said he would attend to it.
I don't know if he did that or if the film is even still being shown.
The interviewer says, I believe it still shows.
A friend of mine who went a little while back told me they didn't even take the house lights down.
Oh, no.
Poor Zador.
What a bummer.
I can only imagine as a DP how much that and that's something you're you know,
they aren't still showing the Muppet movie every day.
Right. The jazz singer every day.
This is his only chance to have something playing forever.
And they're they're fucking it up.
You know, get get it a little.
I say give all the professors a little bump, give them a little bump in pay and give them like, hey, guys, let's just run this.
Let's, you know, give them give them a little,
you know, help to be the best professors they can because they clearly have invested in the store.
I mean, you can get any and every color or variety of M&M merchandise like this.
It is very thorough.
But the professor is the ambassador of the Academy.
Yeah. And you walk out of there thinking about your professor.
And yeah, they have to be they got to notch up their performance.
Let's get the guy who played Keen Bean.
That's all I'm saying.
Let's just get him in there.
McShane, very interesting.
Was also in the Tower of Terror movie.
I'm a director.
He's a who's lines anyway.
Yes.
And originally in the British.
Yeah. But if they were to happen, I do think that I miss the general tenor of the current
professor who has that up and down the actual kittens and that I wanted to go
through it as quickly as we possibly can.
Could you do all of our now announcements like that?
I would I would love to
if that's what we're doing.
All right. You survive.
I think so.
Listen, Sean, we'll be back with more of those very soon.
Be sure to check us out on Facebook, Twitter, Instagram.
And for more,
send a podcast or pitch on dot com slash podcast.
Right. Thanks.
Thanks for being here.
Have a podcast day.
There is something so comforting, honestly, about that rhythm from doing all these
experiences over our lives.
Yeah. It feels very nice to do.
I feel relaxed.
Yeah. And I don't have to put that much energy into it.
No, not having to enunciate.
I feel like I have a particularly I try to enunciate when I speak and I end up
feeling exhausted.
Why?
Maybe from now on and all the rest of the episode, should I just take it down?
Not now.
Worry about hitting those T's and F's.
Just kind of try to breeze through those words as smoothly as I can.
One whole episode just to try that.
That whole.
Arbitrary. It's not about this or anything else.
No, no, no. Of course not.
Yeah.
Similarly, that was one of the reasons I think it took me a second.
Then I realized it.
Park MGM is pain it
inadvertently.
The color they have chosen for a lot of it is similar to Disney's Go Away Green
that they paint on things that they want you to just pleasantly
fade into the scenery and to the background.
What if the plot of the next one is that green ends up in a place with a lot of
Go Away Green and they can't find her?
It overpowers the machine.
That's good.
Yeah.
And she ends up feeling bad about herself.
Like, why do I have the color that everyone wants to go away?
Yeah.
I mean, look, we're going to make the sequel to this.
We'll just get it then.
We will hire Isadore and we'll make sure to shot to his liking on the perfect.
Oh, yeah.
Old film, not on this stereo vision that fucked him over.
So right.
Well, thanks.
Thanks for listening, Jason.
Glad you had a good time.
Glad you're part of the Blue 32 family now.
I love it.
Yeah, to go back.
And thanks for watching this film that I care about deeply.
And next time, do it with one fat burger beer.
One fat burger beer, a good night's sleep.
In fact, that's what Isadore should have done, too.
He would have given a shit about the alignment.
So Isadore, grab a beer.
See you next time.
Bye.