Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast contains banana allergy
experiments, the universe hopping abilities
of Michigan J. Fraud, and a mysterious question,
who are the Centaur children?
Brett Davis joins us as we tackle
Universal's Kongfrontation today on Podcast The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the podcast about theme parks,
where at least two of the hosts today
have some major banana breath.
I'm Scott Garner, joined by Mike Carlson.
Hell yeah, I'm one of the two.
Yeah, we were literally just eating bananas
before we recorded, can you believe it?
Not for show either, I just hadn't eaten anything today.
Same for me.
Obviously it's a quick meal, or not a meal,
but a quick snack, I guess, a quick burst of energy.
Yeah, portable.
We found out Jason Sheridan, who's here,
does not have banana breath.
No, if I eat solely a banana first thing in the morning,
I get a tummy ache.
I can have it with cereal, or I can have it with.
The most persnickety stomach in podcasting.
That's interesting, I think I have a mild banana allergy.
Okay.
Because I have a little cough sometimes
after I have a banana.
Interesting.
And a past guest, Marissa Strickland,
was like, maybe you have a really mild allergy to bananas.
I don't know, can I test that?
Is that an allergy test I can do?
Yeah, I think you can do an allergy test
for most common items.
But isn't it just like rub it on your back?
I think they prick something on it.
And then put a little banana into my.
There's some you can do with blood tests.
Right.
But I think the prick test is they just put it like,
whatever the item is on your skin
and see if you're allergic.
Basically, yep.
Are you gonna freak out in this episode?
No, I'm not, I'm just saying, I can do this at home, can't I?
Just put a banana on my skin and see if I get a rash?
Do you still have one in the house,
or did you eat the last one?
I do, do you want me to go do it?
Yeah, maybe while I introduce our guest,
why don't you go get a banana and rub it on your skin?
I'll rub it on my skin and see you at the end in 90 minutes
if it's a rash.
Wow, we usually don't have such cliffhangers,
that's exciting.
All right, while Mike grabs a banana,
we're happy to be joined by Forever Dog family member
from the podcast for laundry
and the National Lampoon Radio Hour, Brett Davis is here.
Hey, it's a true honor to be here.
Oh, geez, thanks, thanks for being here
and for taking up some of your trip from New York
to come over here.
I'm a big fan of the show.
Oh, thank you.
I'm happy to hear that.
Very flattered to be asked.
Oh, geez, absolutely.
Yes, and well, so you're out from New York for a little bit.
I know, because I saw you before,
a little bit of city walk time.
What'd you think?
Did it live up to your expectation?
Was it the best, has it been the best thing
of the trip so far?
Yeah, I think it's been the best thing of the trip.
I marveled at Jurassic Parking.
I sat and just stared at that giant screen
playing the worst music videos I've ever seen.
That's very true, I know.
And it's not like it's the top 10 hits of right now
and you're going like,
I guess I don't know what the kids are into.
You don't know what any of it is.
Yeah, well, the one I did pay attention to a lot
was Weezer's doing take on me now.
They're just an 80s cover bit.
Oh, this is perfect while Mike is off Mike.
Fantastic, yes, this Weezer shit.
Everyone on Mike agrees that the new Weezer,
the 80s Weezer covers are the worst things
that have ever happened and let's change topic
before Mike gets back to the microphone.
I'd argue they're not the worst things,
but it is pretty just shrug-worthy.
It's mainly that.
Yeah, you're right that maybe not specifically terrible,
but why?
They're just like, it's like the Gus Van Zant psycho.
Why did this happen?
It's just, we're just gonna do the exact same thing,
but with slightly less charisma.
They had Finn Wolfhardt play,
like he was the lead singer of this 80s band.
So more Finn Wolfhardt 80,
that's like, this is another iteration of that is his schtick
because he's just today's kid who's also an 80s.
Born in like 1998 or 2003 or whatever he was born in.
No idea how old this person is.
The music video that I always saw a lot playing up there
was the Coldplay music video with CGI apes
that I did not realize was Coldplay.
I've never seen CGI apes.
Yeah, like a whole crew of CGI apes dancing to a song.
I forget whether it's from Milo Zyloto
or another one.
Mike, do you know what?
What's the song?
Viva la Vida, I don't know the song.
Viva la Vida is from Milo Zyloto, yes.
How are we managing to talk about anything
but that you right now are rubbing little banana bits
onto your palm?
Well, the back of my hand.
Oh yes, sorry, that's the opposite of a palm.
Well, I was just, cause everyone was just, you know,
I was just trying to figure out the best way to do it.
I think this is good.
I don't want it to be like getting the couch dirty,
but that's enough banana residue
to see if there's a breakout.
I think I thought this has been such a delicate process
and I think I thought you were just gonna take a banana
and just rub it whole really fast.
Do you want me to go back and do that?
No, no, no, I think this is fine,
but you did it very medically.
You did it, it's a little dab and then you
Really, if I just- Some gauze on it.
If I start gesticulating wildly,
I don't wanna rub banana on the couch.
Mm-hmm, does it smell like banana on your hand now?
Yeah, my hand smells like banana right now.
So like you're engulfed in banana bread.
Yeah.
I also like isn't going to like answer
a few of digestion issues on bananas.
Well, but I don't think that it's not digestion issues.
It's like some sort of like my body rejects it a little bit
because the cough would suggest not a digestion issue.
It would suggest there's something that incompatible.
Am I wrong here?
Kind of like- I have no idea.
I don't have an upset stomach when I have a banana
is what I'm saying.
So I don't think it's digestion.
I think it's simply a mild allergy
if it indeed is an allergy.
You might end up in 90 minutes where you might look
and you have a big Donald Duck kind of bump
on the back of your hand.
It's very possible.
Possibly you'll have to take me to the hospital.
We don't know.
I've never rubbed a banana on my hand before.
Well then if so, so there may be an edit at some point
where we, because we have to get to 90 minutes minimum,
if not two hours, if not two and a half hours.
So we cannot cut it off short.
So there may be an edit and that's where we will have
taking you to the hospital.
Brett, you have to stay with us.
Oh yeah, I'm gonna be at the hospital talking about-
Take the-
Well, it is like a thematic for us though,
because the big hospital in Burbank is Providence St. Joe's,
which is next to the Disney lot
and is the hospital Walt Disney died in.
Oh wow, okay.
We have all, yes, we haven't said this out loud I think,
but we all have a sort of a wish to die at that hospital.
That's sort of what we want.
Would it be too much of a stretch to do an episode
dedicated to that hospital?
Oh, not at all.
No, no, please.
Absolutely not.
Come next week.
Well, yeah, first things first, we have to get in there,
which maybe will happen today.
Yeah.
And then yeah, let's find the bed.
We've been to the, I don't know if,
well you've been out here,
there's this restaurant, the Tam O' Shanter,
which is where, like he, Walt went there all the time.
He had a table there.
We've sat at the wall.
I actually have, I've just passed by the Walt table.
All right, so there's the Walt table.
We got to find the Walt hospital bed.
Oh my God, yeah, you think they have the same bed there
and there's like, it's like a little tribute to them?
Oh yeah.
And if you get brought in there in the ER
and they're like, oh, and you're like dying,
but you're like, oh, I got the Walt room.
Got the Walt bed.
The bed is really bad.
This old bed.
Or yeah, there's just like an old,
like it's an old room.
You're walking through and there's like a brown room,
weirdly.
What is this?
They haven't updated anything.
Smells like cigarettes.
Same dust.
Very mixed feelings, because it's like,
oh, this is historic, but also like, they didn't save him.
So like, that doesn't make me optimistic.
You're getting like out of the ambulance
and people are like screaming at each other
what's wrong with you and what they need to check,
like your blood pressure.
And you're like, excuse me, it would be possible.
I can't get it.
In the Walt room?
I don't mean to, it's okay if not,
but if it's not too crowded.
I'm gonna turn the front facing camera on on my phone.
They're like, no, sorry.
And you're like, well, did Roy die here?
Is Roy's bed available?
Did Annie Disney's?
Then you get it, then you're filming a YouTube video.
What up fam?
Dying like, this is dying like Walt.
Mike and I were at something lately
and we started to do a video and I jokingly said like,
what up fam?
Like sort of the like, fake YouTubey reviewer stuff.
And then someone on the other side of the table
about five minutes later started doing it sincerely.
And I immediately was like, oh my God, I feel so bad
that it's clearly doing it as a bit.
I don't think those people knew we were doing it
with any irony.
Okay, okay, that's fine.
And we didn't do it after they did it.
I think they were just like, oh, another YouTuber.
Yikes.
And they probably were like, honestly,
he could use some more energy.
He wasn't doing that.
You gotta really dive into that what up fam.
Yeah, cause they did it much more energetically.
I think we're all right.
This is a, it is totally okay if you don't have an answer
to this question because this is a very specific question
and one I'd never considered till right now.
Have you ever, is there a dream hospital
you would like to die at?
Hmm.
You know, I don't contemplate death that much,
let alone where specifically I'd like it to happen
if it's a hospital situation.
Yeah, this is if we're lucky enough to be,
to have some help.
Yeah, I always say I wanna die in a tour bus crash.
I think it's the most taller way to go.
Oh sure.
And if I have my, there's 20th anniversary tour,
the Dane Cook Tourgasm bus crash.
But that's a few years away.
Now is that because you've been accepted
into the Dane Cook Tourgasm lineup
or because you're just like hanging out with them?
You know, I think I'd be part of the brotherhood.
I mean, I hope, I wish this for you, absolutely.
When is the original Tourgasm?
When was it?
So how many years are we away from 20?
2006, right?
That was peak Cook.
Yeah, so not far, we're not far.
For clarification though, his current tour,
I know for a fact is called the Tell It Like It Is Tour.
Oh really?
Tell It Like It Is Tour.
Oh, he's finally being honest?
Okay, cool.
I was at a, I ate at the Boston Market
behind him 10 years ago.
I was eating alone and someone was talking about Dane Cook
and I turned around and it was Dane Cook.
He was like, yeah man, and like, you know,
somebody was like, yeah, that's just Dane, man.
That's just Dane Cook and I turned around
and I was like, it is Dane Cook.
And like, we were like, there were four people in there,
three people including him at his table and me
at my table right behind him.
Wow, wow.
All right, I'm no longer impressed by Walt's table
at the Tamoshanter.
You've seen Dane's table at the Boston Market.
Which I believe is gone?
It is closed.
Yeah.
No, we should have gone in there
and seen if we could preserve it beforehand,
but we can't now.
At least the plaque?
You know, I don't think there was.
I did have many meals in that Boston Market 10 years ago.
But I don't think anyone.
Any meals at the Boston Market?
I used to be, I PA'd at the ranch.
Oh, you were at the Warner Ranch.
At the Warner Ranch, yeah.
The Warner Ranch, for people who don't live here
have never been lucky enough to work on these lots.
The Warner Ranch is where the Friends opening sequence
was filmed.
The Fountain.
That's where the real Friends fountain.
Yeah. Yeah.
And much of the music man.
Really, there?
Yeah.
Is that right?
I didn't know that.
I believe so.
The movie version, yeah, from the 60s.
I walked around the lot and I found the old giant WB sign
that they used to use in those promos.
You remember like Michigan J. Frog
would be like animated in the corner
and then you would see like this crazy lit WB sign
that they would do like all these angles around
for their like bumpers.
It was sitting, at least it was there 10 years ago,
just sitting back there on the lot.
Just decaying?
Yes, just decaying.
I really recommend anyone that is at least peaked by this
to go and watch all of those old Michigan J. Frogs
like bumpers.
They are insane.
And it's like this weird shared universe
where like all of the actors
and like some of the cartoons know each other.
And like you'll get like Superman interacting
with like Jackie.
And like, yeah, it's just this weird world
like John Witherspoon talking to like James Vanderbeek.
It's very strange.
He would bring Cameron and like Marvin the Martian.
Yeah.
That sort of.
Cause when he bridged the gap between like WB kids
and the WB network, like the prime time.
Michigan J. Frog could walk in all worlds.
Yeah.
It's like the day walker.
It's like the lead.
Will we do an episode on just Michigan J. Frog?
Yes.
Yes, sure.
Can you Skype me in for that?
Yeah, of course.
Oh yeah.
Yeah, I'll be like, yeah.
You know, this was, I gotta see if it,
is it in my notes for,
I was trying to remember why this came up.
And I think it's because we just,
I don't know if it's out by now,
but we did an episode about the roller coaster
Kingda Ka with Dan Klein.
And for some reason,
I think that is why I found out that there was some song,
or was this because, wait a minute,
this might be because I was looking up the Six Flags song,
the Venga Boys.
I don't remember why,
but I discovered through all of this research
that there was a commercial for the
Sylvester Tweety mysteries,
which was in Kids W.
I remember that.
Where there was a, just in the promo,
the Wikipedia noted that in the promo,
Tweety like raps to the Venga Boys song,
something like that.
And he said, the phrase he says is like,
gotta get that putty.
Give me that putty, give me that putty.
And if you're a podcast completist,
and you are aware of the work of our friend Bug Mane,
Buzz Buzz, Skittle Skattle,
give me that putty sauce.
I just really jumped out at me.
The rapping about putty.
I was meaning to mention this to you guys.
Putty cat is what-
Yes, he calls him putty cat.
He would call Sylvester.
So that it is from Tweety Bird,
but did you have a clip of it?
I don't, after I discovered this,
I was looking up as many Sylvester Tweety mysteries
promos as I could find.
I'm sure a listener knows exactly what it is
and will tweet it at us right now
as they're listening to this.
We're going to the Paley Center right after this.
We have to find these promos.
Oh, here it is, okay, yes.
Well, it's because I was gonna, I'll do this now.
I wanted in that episode to propose that we do,
I don't know why this hasn't occurred to us yet.
When are we gonna do a full second gate episode
about Mr. Six?
Oh, of course.
The old, the Six Flags old man.
That is an epic.
Yes, so let's get that up there.
What an original name.
That's his name.
Could have been Mr. Flags, but instead it's Mr. Six.
So that, thinking about Mr. Six led me to the official
Wikipedia for the Vengabus.
And in the section in popular culture,
which needs additional citations for verification,
it says this song is used for promos
on Sylvester and Tweety mysteries,
and I'm sorry I was wrong, it's We Wike Da Poodie.
We wike, we wike da Poodie.
Why is he saying?
Buz, buz.
Didn't they fight?
Didn't Sylvester and Tweety fight?
I believe by the mysteries,
they were working together. Oh, I guess they were teamed up.
They were working together.
Oh, the Wikely pair, yes, yeah.
And they had to put their differences.
They had a common enemy, unsolved homicides.
That he had to get to the bottom of.
And then they caused all of America
to have a common interest.
This potter's field, we're getting to the bottom.
We're getting justice for everyone
buried in this potter's field.
Sorry, I'm just glad you unlocked all this in my brain.
It's been buzzing around for the last,
it's been buzzing around for the last month.
So if you're interested in Poodie,
subscribe to Podcast Thride, The Second Gate.
No one liked it, you both just got the most stern faces.
Well, I'm thinking about Mr. Six now.
It's always nice to be thinking about Mr. Six.
Is there more than one Mr. Six?
I think it was in the commercials,
always played by the same guy.
Okay, I had a hunch when Ronald changes.
You're like, wait a minute.
I felt like one year they had a separate Mr. Six.
They might have, but I believe the original Mr. Six,
and I don't wanna say too much
because obviously we should save this for the episode.
But what I discovered about Mr. Six
is that Mr. Six is hot.
Yes, the real man.
Was I reading about him a week ago?
Yes.
How has this not gotten in the air before?
We briefly brought him up, I think,
but for whatever reason we haven't.
There's only one, he wasn't like an old man
they had to replace, basically, that's all I'll say.
He didn't pass away?
He didn't pass away.
In which case.
Can I see the Mr. Six room, please?
Yeah.
Now you have an answer, you should die
where Mr. Six died. Oh my God.
Yeah, he's a stud.
I just showed, I can't turn it all the way around.
Jason just saw Mr. Six.
The real, yes.
Does that make you? The little tease,
the real Mr. Six actor was like a hunky dude.
Okay, I believe that.
Here, I'll show it from my phone, can you see that?
Oh yeah.
Ripped guns.
Yeah, that was Mr. Six.
Anyways, we'll get on this, Six will come soon.
Six will come.
Six will come soon.
So anyways, oh boy, I'm delighted by all that,
but let's get down,
because hey, we're covering a huge thing right now,
and I'm so glad you wanted to talk about this.
Confrontation, and I love the specificity
of you bringing this up,
because clearly confrontation
equals the very specific ride in Florida,
and not just all of King Kong in the parks,
which there is so much.
Why confrontation?
What's the attachment there?
Well, it was my favorite ride.
As a kid, they'd have that scrolling Universal Studios ad
where it's just. On the tapes?
It was on the tapes.
Yes, inside the letters, one of my favorite things.
Yeah, where you'd have the words Universal Studios,
and then you'd see King Kong, you'd see the Out of Time car,
you'd see all of these things.
Jaws jumping out, Yogi and Boo Boo,
yeah.
Hitchcock walking into the silhouette.
You can ride the movies, unbelievable,
and I never got to go as a little kid until I was 12,
so I had a slightly adulter appreciation of it.
Every kid had gone to Universal,
all I wanted to do was ride this King Kong ride,
because that's the one that stuck out in the ad for me.
I loved King Kong as a kid.
I remember renting Son of Kong and Mighty Joe Young,
and these movies are not meant for six-year-olds.
Yeah, some of those Kong movies are really violent.
King Kong versus Godzilla is very weird.
So King Kong was like, that was the,
I was going to Disney, I was going everywhere,
but King Kong was the main attraction for this whole trip.
Wow, sure.
And probably at 12, you're chasing thrills a little more.
Yeah.
You want something scary.
It's a little scary, but once I realized
I could deal with it, I rode the thing three times.
Wow.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's a good, this was a really epic attraction.
And like, I mean, it's not scary
in the thrill ride way of scary.
It's just like, it's not even just the ape necessarily.
I think just the general veneer of it,
the fact that you're in this grimy subway station
for so much of it.
Yeah.
It's terrifying.
Yeah, 70s New York, the recreation of 70s New York,
you're going through a queue.
You may know from Joker.
Yes.
Sure.
No other films.
It's almost a character.
The queue just filled with graffiti.
Like they had actual graffiti artists graffiti the place,
and then of course people just added their own graffiti
over the years.
Cool.
I remember seeing like a curse maybe on the wall.
Yes.
Which is insane to see it, universal.
That's pretty cool that they like,
almost encouraged people to head to that tapestry.
But yeah, this could have been any,
this could have been like a, you know,
dressed up, now they have a cleaned up version of New York
with the Jimmy Fallon ride.
It's cool that they had like grimy, shitty,
Ed Koch New York.
Ed Koch does not appear on the ride, right?
I don't believe so.
No.
They have a real news anchor in it,
like an actual New York news anchor doing like,
evacuate, get out of here.
Yeah.
In the ride video.
You know, I went 1998 and he was still on TV.
So it was very kind of cool to see that.
Oh wow.
Was he the news anchor you grew up watching?
Yeah, he was on, I wouldn't say grew up watching.
He taught you everything you knew?
Yeah.
Mom, mom, the nightly news is on.
Mr. Rogers, this guy, Rollin' Smith.
Rollin' Smith.
He looked a little like a Vulcan.
Yes, thick eyebrows.
Yeah, very like a stern presence.
He was on the UPN affiliate.
I'm sure he was on like a major one
and then got bumped down over the years to UPN.
Most likely.
But yeah, he was the 10 o'clock news guy.
Wow, wow.
Was he New York or New Jersey?
I think the UPN one might have been based out of Secaucus.
Nice.
It's kind of been a big bump down.
They would play weird like New Jersey,
like shots of like New Jersey parks
at like a weird times of the day
when they just didn't have a commercial to play.
But yeah, it was the New York area.
Sure, yeah, yeah.
Affiliate.
I am very fond of Rollin' Smith also
because he was, it's not the same video.
So they got him twice because he also was the host
of the Tram Tour attraction.
And if you don't know the full breakdown,
King Kong was a stop on the Universal Tram Tour
and like a huge step up for them.
They had done Jaws and that was great,
but like the technological advance
to have that King Kong robot just really like
took the studio tour into the next, into another gear.
Then when Universal Studios Florida opened in 1990,
they turned it into this full blown huge attraction
in and of itself.
And Rollin' Smith was on both.
And I was like, let me look up some Rollin' Smith stuff.
Rollin' Smith has this odd, like a part of,
oddly Star Wars lore and a very specific Star Wars lore.
I'd never heard of any of this.
That the Star Wars holiday special
the tape that it was mainly distributed on,
because Star Wars holiday special lived as a,
people trade in tapes like this bizarre
can you believe this thing taped off TV.
And the main tape that was distributed,
like that people traded around,
had a very brief clip of him at the very beginning
doing a five second tease for what's on the news that night.
And his phrase was fighting the frizzies at 11.
Which presumably fighting the frizzies,
I don't think, I don't know that anyone ever saw
the actual story, but I think fighting the frizzies
has something to do with hair care.
I guess, maybe, we don't know,
unless there were creatures called the frizzies out.
Yeah, was this an in universe news probe look?
Oh, it's some like deep Star Wars thing
that we don't know about.
It's like wearing a robe.
A little Star Wars news teases is a very good idea.
The Empire Strikes Back at 11.
George would have put the frizzies in his sequel trilogy.
It was gonna be all about the frizzies.
It was gonna be about the frizzies.
They fight the force, they're little bad guys.
They're smaller than atoms.
The frizzies are very small.
But fighting the frizzies also has this odd,
what kind of has sustained that phrase in pop culture
is that one of the first episodes of South Park,
Mr. Hankey's Christmas Classics in 1999,
because it's an old holiday special,
they started it with a shot of their editor
dressed up like Roland Smith saying,
fighting the frizzies at 11.
Really?
Yeah. Wow.
The South Park guys tributed this very specific sliver
of this news tease on VHS's tape.tv.
I can picture that as you're saying.
Yeah, it does ring a bell.
I can picture that episode.
And he looks like it, they gave him a stash.
It's a wonderful little clip.
Those are all on YouTube.
So, I mean, most news anchors, I don't feel,
have this amount of lore.
This guy is the King Kong news anchor
and fighting the frizzies.
Pretty major stuff.
And probably he's like a good journalist.
Whatever.
Or donated to causes or something.
Sure, who cares.
I mean, now it would be Pat Kiernan,
who's the New York One anchor and is just in everything.
Oh, okay.
He's in every Marvel movie.
Like anytime you just need a New York anchor
and don't wanna shell out to NBC or CBS,
you just get him and he'll say anything.
Like, vampires on the loose.
It's just like, that's his bread and butter now
as far as New York people go.
Oh, wow.
Okay.
I like those game news anchors.
Yeah, I think he also hosts trivia at a bar somewhere.
Wow.
Nice.
He's everywhere.
We have a weatherman here in Los Angeles
named Fritz Coleman, who also considers himself
a bit of a funny man.
Like does stand out sometimes.
Does he?
Fritz Coleman?
He had a one man show running
at the Gary Marshall Theater in Burbank for a while.
Really?
Yeah.
He's a Burbank fixture because I have seen him
several times at the Bob's Big Boy Starbucks,
which is essentially pretty much in the same block
as the Gary Marshall Theater and the Boston Market.
Yeah, that we were talking about earlier.
I love how many locals we're talking about.
Toluca Lake, Burbank, like really coming through today.
Five minutes from the hospital, Walt died.
Wow.
So in the same, we could go see the Fritz table,
the Dane table and the Walt bed.
Yep.
It would take a half hour.
Damn, let's do it.
This is dangerously off topic,
but he's not the Mr. Wacky guy, right?
No.
Okay.
What's Mr. Wacky?
It's a video where they're,
it's like a morning news weekend and they're like,
well, what's going on at this parking lot?
And it's like, well, we've gotten a big inflatable slide.
It's just a bunch of like very tired volunteers,
first thing in the morning.
And they meet,
this anchor's doing the worst possible job
anyone's ever done in doing like a fun segment.
And so I've heard that he's, you know,
he's bombed a few of these.
Oh, okay.
Oh, interesting.
Wait, so why Mr. Wacky?
Is it this video?
Yeah.
It looks like that's San Diego.
Oh, okay.
Nevermind then.
Yeah, but I do wanna watch this.
It's really, really great.
I really recommend everyone watch it.
When you first, I was wondering why Mr. Wacky
sounded familiar to me and I was like,
that's not what Robin Williams calls his penis, is it?
No, that's Mr. Happy.
I'd say Mr. Happy, yeah.
Oh, Mr. Wacky, ho.
You could imagine maybe once in a while
he called it Mr. Wacky.
He might've tried that out as an alternate name.
Mr. Wacky is the best comedy sketch
that's ever happened in real life.
I'll say that much.
Wow, okay, okay.
I will.
Yeah, we have to look at this.
Okay, so, back to Kong.
Roland Smith, great job, great work.
Yeah.
You know who else acts in this ride?
There's a lot of VO and a lot of the SWAT team voices
and everything.
Ron Knight, who is also the voice
of our favorite theme park character, Botanicus.
He also has voices in Jaws, apparently.
I've made an effort to try to get him on the show.
Yeah, what happened with that again?
Or is there no response?
He did respond in an interesting cryptic manner.
It was like teasing stories that he has.
And then he never responded again.
So I don't know.
I really like to talk to Ron Knight.
Do we have to interview Cotswinkle too?
Who did respond to me?
Botanicus is his creator.
Oh, oh.
The author.
The author of The Green Planet.
He created all the ET ancillary characters
and the characters from the ride.
This man, William Cotswinkle.
Did you make it to,
are you fond of the ET adventure as well
from those, from Florida trips?
That's a close second of the worst things
I was excited about.
I didn't know that this was a sequel,
but yeah, that was unbelievable.
Yeah, there's a book,
he wrote a book in the 80s called The Green Planet
and that's where most of the lore from the ride comes about.
We did a whole Patreon on Botanicus and all this lore,
but I emailed him.
And just as a little spoiler from that Patreon episode,
he emailed back and he said,
I asked him if he created Botanicus and he said,
dear Mike, thanks for your email,
except for ET himself,
I created all the characters
in the book of The Green Planet
and that includes Botanicus.
Good luck with your podcasts.
Best wishes from ET and me, Bill.
Wow.
Which is like, does he also think I'm 12?
I like that ET also gave me a best wish,
but also it was.
I don't know that he had the authority
to speak on behalf of ET.
That's questionable.
I could send this to Amblin
and Spielberg would sue his ass like crazy.
ET did not authorize this hello.
ET does not wish you well on your podcasts, 12 year old boy.
Nonsense, he loves us.
He said, the last time I went on the ride,
he actually said my name.
But I have Kotzwinkle's email now.
Wow.
So.
Kotzwinkle.
If you can get the voice,
if we can get an interview with him,
combine it with an interview with Kotzwinkle.
Boy.
Can we speak to Botanicus?
He's Botanicus with you right now?
It's Botanicus' favorite curse word.
And then he's like, oh, you could speak to ET too.
It's like, no, no, no.
No, no, no.
Shit from the movies, we don't care about that.
Yeah.
Okay.
Kong, very popular.
This ride, very popular.
Yeah.
Long lines, usually.
Prone to breaking down.
Lot of moving pieces, helicopters,
multiple Kongs, a very unique suspended ride.
This is like a very, much larger scale kind of Peter Pan
like hanging from the ceiling.
To the point I found out this was replaced
by Revenge of the Mummy in 2004.
The tracks are still in the ceiling
because they built the tracks for Kong into the building.
And it is too difficult to remove them.
So they just left them up there.
So it's possible.
I mean.
Bring them back.
Yeah.
Or just put the Kong vehicles and have it go
with the coaster.
Oh, sure.
Could you do.
Concurrent rides.
Intervals, just intervals.
Roosevelt Island tram ride.
Yeah.
Haunted pyramid.
It's like the Indiana Jones,
what they were gonna do with two rides at once.
Remember they were gonna have them go through
like the people mover or something.
Yeah, why not?
Yeah.
Well, I mean, yeah.
Well, you say why not?
We don't have to look at the mat,
like the actual blueprints to see if that's impossible.
That'd work.
It would work.
Fill those like, you know, Roosevelt tram rides
with like hard hats with crowbars going like,
you don't.
You don't mess with Brendan Fraser in Motaps.
You mess with them, you mess with all of us.
Spider-Man ending.
Yeah.
Actually, though that's a good thing to say
that this is like to make all of these,
cause there's universal Florida open with three attractions
that were all based on the tram tour.
And thus they all like there had to be three separate rides
that essentially had tram-esque ride vehicles.
And they went a lot bigger.
Yeah.
And they were big because they had to make it,
they were competing with Disney on Disney's turf.
Uh-huh.
But so it's, you know, it's boats and draws.
It's a subway car in earthquake.
And then in this, it's the Roosevelt Island Expressway.
As a New Yorker, do you have any experience
with the Roosevelt Island Expressway?
Yeah, it's a great ride.
It's just this, a swipe of the Metro card.
Okay.
And you get to fly over the city.
I think I liked it because I liked King Kong so much.
Right.
And then you go to the, like a weird little island
that doesn't feel like it should exist.
That's what's there on the other side?
Roosevelt Island is like a very small,
like you could walk across it lengthwise
in like five minutes, if that.
And then it's got some restaurants
and it's got some campuses for, you know, Verizon
and like I think a college is there.
It's just a very, it's a weird anomaly
of no reason to go there unless you happen to work
in these places or whatever, but it's a fun ride.
Some people live there.
There are apartment buildings.
There is some apartment buildings there,
which is also strange.
Yeah, it's just a big mystery why it exists.
And you could really only get to it,
well, you could get to it by bridge, I don't know.
I read an article, like in the last 10 years,
like in the New, like the Times or Buzzfeed,
like big places where they were still like,
we don't quite understand Roosevelt Island.
Like it was a feature on Roosevelt Island,
but they're like, it's even among New Yorkers.
It's a conundrum.
It feels like you're in a different city.
Yeah.
There's like bridges very close by.
It's just a strange place.
And then now that they've got all these like campuses
that moved in, there's like this kind of like
AstroTurfie field and it's just got a strange vibe
all around.
Could it work as an evacuation spot
if a giant ape invaded New York?
Well, that's the big question.
I'm not really sure what he's doing over there.
It's as baffling as why any people would be there.
Or why you enter Penn Station,
you wind up taking a Roosevelt Island tram,
which is about 30 blocks away.
Oh, I didn't think about that.
This is also a little strange inconsistency.
Yeah, yeah, right, right.
Weird.
I like that in putting in the mummy attraction
that they didn't have to change the exterior too much.
They put that kind of like gold museum type overlay,
but that the exterior's fantastic.
Yes.
I'm really glad that didn't have to come down.
And all of it in theory,
because originally Universal,
the idea was that you could use all of these as sets.
Right.
Like you could shoot movies here,
but I don't think anyone ever did.
What's the most prominent thing
that was shot at Universal Florida?
Is it the Jimmy Buffett,
or no, that was out here.
There's a bigger music video.
Or is Fruitcakes here?
No, Fruitcakes was Florida.
That's Florida, yeah.
Jimmy Buffett shot one of his most famous music videos,
Fruitcakes, the song Fruitcakes, at Universal Florida.
Universal Florida.
Universal Florida is doing a lot of heavy lifting.
Yeah.
One of his most, how would you dispute
one of his most famous?
What is his most famous?
Also, how many music videos does he have?
My statement stands.
One of his most famous.
He wasn't really doing a ton in music video era.
So he didn't have his November rain.
Five O'Clock somewhere,
but I think of that as more an Alan Jackson music video.
It is.
That he makes an appearance in.
Yes, it is.
I agree.
But yeah, what is the most prominent thing
he shot at Universal Florida?
I think there's a Creed music video
where they filled the New York streets with water.
Yes.
Right, with a rowboat?
Yes, you're right.
Yeah.
What is it?
Is it my sacrifice?
I think so.
It's the one that's like,
brrrr, brrrr, brrrr, brrrr.
Brrrr, brrrr, brrrr, brrrr.
Mm-hmm.
That doesn't narrow it down.
I know that's, I think only one's like that.
Okay, so Riot itself.
Yeah, all right, I really like that line.
Really like, I like how there's real movie posters
in there.
Yes.
For like Kramer versus Kramer,
that like kind of, and Rocky, I believe.
I believe they would rotate those.
I believe I came across on that,
and said they would update those with current movies.
Even though the footage was always the 70s,
because this is primarily based on the 76 King Kong,
which starred Jeff Bridges, Jessica Lange,
and Charles Grodin.
And that's still, I do not,
I have only seen clips of this movie.
I've never sat and watched it.
I really like the clip that they show
in the line for the ride,
where you're looking at the subway car's POV,
as it careens into King Kong's palm.
Yeah.
Like he catches it, essentially.
I think I know, yeah, I've never seen the movie either.
It does sound like, people like it a lot.
It was a big hit, Dino De Laurentiis produced,
which comes-
I feel like everybody hated this movie.
I feel like I've only heard shit about this movie.
Money-wise, it did well.
Kind of notorious now, though,
because Kong doesn't climb the Empire State Building,
he climbed the World Trade Center.
And I guess Dino De Laurentiis had the rights,
or had something,
they made a sequel called King Kong Lives in 86.
Yes, now that I have seen.
I was trying to remember the plot.
I believe it is a story about King Kong having to get,
give a, he's involved in a heart transplant operation.
He's performing the surgery?
No.
Or he needs one.
I believe, if I'm remembering correctly,
that a giant mechanical heart is built,
and they have to take King Kong's heart out,
replace it, and put it in a huge tank.
And we end up somewhere with King Kong being in love.
What?
There's a love story.
This all, again, all of these movies I saw
when I was six years old,
barely comprehending anything,
and it's like, oh, cool, King Kong movie.
And then he's like sick for most of it.
Yeah, he's in a coma.
And in love for the rest of it.
It seems like it starts with him,
like they're like, okay, so he fell off
the World Trade Center, he's alive in a coma,
and scientists are studying him.
This movie was not a success.
None of the actors came back.
Do you know De Laurentiis?
And the director came back, John Gillerman,
who apparently was a real hard ass.
His Wikipedia basically goes like,
no matter what he was making, he was very strict.
He was very intense, it seems like.
I think this movie has a part where
King Kong sees a giant crocodile,
and they have a shot of a crocodile,
and he kind of lights up, mm,
and then it cuts to a wide of the guy in the suit
picking up a lizard,
what is clearly, they're trying to do a scale thing.
Okay.
And then that's supposed to be a crocodile,
and he drops it into his mouth,
and then I believe it cuts to just full crocodile bones
just being tossed onto a pile of lots of crocodile bones.
So he's eating a normal size crocodile, basically?
It's just large for us.
Yeah, but there's no question when it cuts to the guy
in the suit, it's like a little gecko or something.
But you're saying it's real,
they found a real panfibian or lizard or something.
Yeah, yeah, I have to go into my tape of it.
I know there's a couple parts of this movie
that are funny as shit.
Oh man.
Oh sorry, I'm gonna go.
I was just gonna add to the movie
it's based on the King Kong from the 70s.
70s, right?
Yeah, 76.
There was a, what I remember is funny,
but again, haven't watched it in years,
funny post-911 SNL sketch.
Yes, I know this.
This particular film where they're showing
a post-911 edited version,
and it's like, instead of going up the World Trade Center,
oh no, he's climbing up the Chrysler building.
And then it cuts to a bunch of new scenes
with the worst actors you've ever seen,
and then they delay the information that the actors,
then they cut to a station break,
and the actors you've been watching
are the news anchors for the station
who now are improvising a new ending to King Kong,
and incorporating the other things the station owns,
like Superman, like if they look out the window,
look, Superman, he's heading for Kong.
Oh no, he's gonna attack that bar.
Cut some cheers.
Cheers.
That's one of those end of show unarchived sketches
I'm glad you brought up,
because there's some of those things,
if nobody saved them, it feels like a fever dream,
like it didn't happen.
I don't think, yeah, I don't think you've seen it.
I've only seen the Kong sketch with the boner.
Oh, that's a great sketch.
Which is also a good sketch.
I really like that sketch.
Let's get it out of here.
You're shaking the shit.
Oh yes, yes.
And we're calling as an erection in the building.
Yeah.
Just so funny that they can cut to that,
and it's not a problem,
because they don't show the head or the balls,
or it's just a big furry thing.
You can show that on TV.
Oh yeah.
It's not a problem.
Yeah.
Oh, good job, SNL.
Some great Kong sketches.
Great Kong sketches.
Okay, wait, so what have we not said?
Okay, oh, well the ride vehicle,
I really like how the,
yeah, that suspended nature of it,
and how it's this weird accordion,
if you watch video of it,
it's a big zigzag X kind of pattern,
which allows for it to do dips and die.
And I guess the crux of this ride,
when they, not Imagineers, but Universal Ears,
whatever you call them,
we're talking about, okay, it's so huge on the tour,
we gotta bring it to Florida,
how do we make it bigger and better?
Well, what if King Kong actually picked up your tram
and threw it?
And that's kind of what it leads to,
it's the climax.
Yeah, it's crazy.
I'm, is there anything else like this at the moment?
Like anything that's a suspended ride,
it's like Peter Pan, it's Peter Pan.
ET.
ET technically.
Yeah, you're right, ET.
20,000 leagues in Tokyo.
That's true, yeah.
But nothing like this aggressive.
Yeah.
No.
And it's huge, yeah.
And it's big.
And there are like two story buildings too,
that like you're kind of.
Yeah, they're really big.
Maybe three story, like it's a very large ride.
Where I live in Brooklyn, I'm in Bushwick,
and they have kind of like two story high train platforms,
and I like it because it reminds me a little bit of King Kong.
Wow, I love how it's like part of your New York,
it's a self mythology.
It was very impactful for me.
Do you ever imagine like you're walking along
and you like kind of just like drift off
and imagine Kong climbing a building?
Oh, I see him.
Yeah, I see him.
You see him, yeah.
Sure.
I see him in your heart.
If a newscopter, if you see a copter in the sky,
it's like, well, they're gonna be a pain in the ass.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't know if I've ever seen a newscopter in New York,
to be fair.
There's a section of the 110 when you're going downtown
to like towards the 10,
and there's a lot of building, high rise buildings,
and I do admit, I've probably said it to you
and it's very embarrassing.
I oftentimes picture Galactus from the Fantastic Four
as if he was to scale with the buildings.
I'm like, what?
You've never said that to me.
Like this is a common thing my brain does as we're going,
because like that's the most like height you get
in Los Angeles really is when you're going down the 110.
So like I'm like, what if he was real?
And Galactus by the way, is a giant Jack Kirby designed man,
he's a God, I guess, sort of a God character.
He's the eater of worlds,
and he comes down and he like eats planets.
So anyway, I'm saying I do that bizarre thing
I just made a comment about.
The tunnels to Toontown in Roger Rabbit
is like one of the worst exits like in LA.
Oh yeah.
Oh yeah, yeah.
I mean, that's a fun thing to go like,
oh, this is the tunnel they had to go through
to get to Toontown, but like it's like,
you have to pretty much slow your car down
from like 60 miles an hour to like 20 miles an hour
to make a 90 degree like exit.
And it's built into a hill.
Yeah.
It's like you're doing like a race.
We can talk about bad weird freeway stuff later.
But that's really nice that you like, you know,
cause like sometimes you gotta go downtown for,
I don't know, you haven't gone to court.
I was gonna say like,
you have to go downtown for unpleasant things.
What am I talking about?
Sure you did.
Yeah.
Have you, yeah, well, is that true?
I've never done jury duty.
I have a system I think I have to beat it.
Oh.
That's in your checking wheelhouse.
It is, yeah.
How to defeat jury duty.
I've only really been called once.
Oh, you know what?
I'll just say it here.
This is not some secret.
Like everyone try it.
If anyone is listening to this,
if anyone listens to every podcast
to try to find potential juries.
Yeah.
And I'm not doing anything wrong.
People who have been escorted jury duty.
There's nothing I'm doing that's wrong
or would get me in trouble.
My system is what they have at least in Los Angeles
is you're supposed to call in.
Once you get like served or whatever a notice,
it says call in the night before
and we'll tell you if we need you.
So what I did was it says like call from whatever,
eight to midnight.
I call it 1159.
Theory wise that they fill up the juries
as the night goes on.
Cause it can't be truly random
because you would, you know,
you would be filled up already.
Like there's no way they would just reject
the first 10 people.
Cause how do they know for sure
everybody's gonna call in?
Yeah.
So they have to fill people up.
So you call in at the last possible second
and I did it and I never got called.
Could be a coincidence.
I don't know.
Try it in Los Angeles.
If you've been given a letter
that says you have jury duty.
I'm interested to see,
cause I've had other people do it with success,
but I'm not declaring it a full victory yet.
I was, as you were saying all that,
I was flashing to your plan of how to defeat
the dreaded parking garages at City Walk.
The like the canceling the movie tickets
the moment that you arrive.
Have you done that plan since?
No, I haven't done that plan since.
I have recommended it.
That would probably get me in trouble.
If there are universal people listening,
they will not like that.
The plan to buy a movie ticket,
get the discounted parking
and then cancel your movie ticket.
So you're more afraid of the universal people
than the city.
Yeah, well honestly yes.
I'm sure they're more on top of things.
I'm sure they're policing more vigilantly.
You remember Jason was afraid of them
when we suggest recording at City Walk.
He didn't want to get arrested.
Yes.
Well yeah.
We were involving a hypothetical scenario.
We were involved in a lot less events
where like there's just,
I guess now at parks they just expect people
to be vlogging and like carrying.
But we were describing a scenario
where we stole the Blues Brothers car
with the big megaphone and did a bum rush live show
and you were like mad about that idea of doing that.
I don't remember that.
I do.
No memory.
Back to Kong.
To make this ride vehicle,
to test the height dynamics
and the idea that Kong would drop you.
Somehow this led to the,
we gotta start,
we have to come up with an official name
of what universal Imagineers are called.
It's universal creative.
Okay so talking about the ride mechanism itself,
to test the idea that you would get dropped somehow by Kong
and how was that going to work.
In figuring out options for this,
the universal creative person,
is it Peter Alexander?
Peter Alexander.
Alexander and I think you have it in front of you too.
This book we cite sometimes universal versus Disney
by Sam Genoway.
This story is in this book where he,
this guy, they wanna test some harness thing
and nobody volunteers,
nobody's willing to do it
so the main guy in charge of this ride says,
I don't know, I'll give it a shot.
So they go into a sound stage at universal Hollywood.
He gets up on wires and they test the thing
and it seems like it's gonna work
but then a miscommunication caused the engineers
to drop him at full free fall
then jerk him to a sudden stop about three feet
from the cement stage floor
resulting in a double hernia operation some months later.
This is a guy who thought of the idea
what if Kong dropped you
then he had to have a double hernia
because of, because he lived his dream.
He flew like a tram.
That was kind of how they scaled,
okay so less intense of a drop.
Less of a drop.
Because it wasn't that intense.
I don't recall this part being super scary.
It's not some Tower of Terror type drop.
No I don't remember a lot of restraints on this.
I mean it does, it did a good job at simulating that
he picked you up and dropped you
and then a police helicopter with a Gatling gun
scares him off.
Hit him.
It's like, it seems to me like it reminds me of the,
like when they're talking about Indiana Jones
when they're like we wanted to make a ride vehicle
that was, you know, like was gonna give you
like shaking essentially so you would feel like
much scarier, like in a much scarier situation.
So it's like you're building like,
it's a normal thing they've done before
where you're suspended but then they're like
trying to figure out how to like jerk your brain around.
I guess so, yeah yeah.
But it wasn't, I honestly, I never went on this ride.
Oh you haven't talked about that.
I never experienced.
Oh okay, oh geez.
Did you skip it?
We didn't really go to Universal until I was like older.
And was it gone by then?
I believe it was gone by then.
Because this was gone in like 2002?
Yeah.
That's a great one we went.
Left in 2002 along with the Fantastic World of Hanna
Barbera also closed in 2002.
Another fun ride.
That's a fun one.
Yeah.
That might have been my first of the day.
Oh that's a good one.
Yeah yeah yeah.
Yeah you kind of hit a fork and then you either go
straight up towards where Hanna Barbera is
or you go the right like towards Lucy.
Yeah.
That used to be the choice.
Ooh, the Lucy exhibit, it just came back to me
that I spent an inordinate amount of time there.
As a kid I was a big I Love Lucy fan.
Me as well, yeah.
So I was like genuinely interested in the layout
of the stage and stuff and the miniatures.
But then also I remember walking outside
and my grandma was deep in conversation
with a man in a wheelchair in full kiss makeup.
He's in a wheelchair.
Like wearing a kiss shirt.
And in.
And like Gene Simmons like paint.
Whoa.
I don't know if like they ever like
I don't think she knows what kiss is.
That seems like if you were a grandma at that time
you would have missed that part of culture.
And that wasn't an employee.
Not an employee.
Yeah.
Whoa.
I wonder what they were talking about.
I couldn't imagine.
My grandma was like a pretty like conservative person.
Can't imagine her just starting a conversation
with a man in like kiss makeup.
Yeah.
Was there a kiss based event anywhere?
I don't think so.
Cause I remember thinking about that
and I'm like well there must be like a concert here
or something and I don't think there was.
Wow.
Nor was it an ICP event.
It was not an ICP event.
I was down with the clown back then
so I would have been a little more excited.
But if anyone knows what it was going on
around spring 98.
Let a ninja know.
Yeah.
Well I don't think the ICP was there.
I think it's safe to say that there wasn't an ICP concert.
You're too interested.
1998 Lucille Ball and Shaggy Too Dope.
Yeah.
This guy who I brought up, Peter Alexander,
I kept going down the rabbit hole with
because when I was,
he's an interesting figure
and seemed involved in the Jaws attraction
and the E.T. adventures.
Definitely factored into things we've talked about before.
And in Googling him, just like oh yeah okay so King Kong
and he has his own company now okay.
And Scientologist okay.
Oh what?
Whoa.
He is an escaped Scientologist.
He made it out and speaks at events frequently about,
he basically, this guy was like royalty in Florida
because one of the best jobs in Florida you could have
is building all the main universal rides.
And when he was doing it in the early 90s,
he was still full fledged Scientologist
and still lives in Florida.
He's like the king of Tampa.
Wow.
Clear water is down there.
Him and Bubba the Love Sponge.
They tried for years to get Bubba the Love Sponge.
I'm fine man, my head's great.
Is this what you were alluding to last night?
Yes.
Having about him?
The oddity about this guy.
I had something else about this guy.
What's your thing?
So he went on to form a company called.
Totally Fun.
Yeah Totally Fun.
And one of his jobs after making all these universal rides,
Totally Fun made a pilot for Nickelodeon that did not go.
And then he wrote the treatment and drew concept sketches
for one that did go.
Nickelodeon Guts.
Guts.
Wow.
Do ya have it?
Yeah.
Yeah, crazy.
This guy's a legend.
This guy thought of all these rides,
thought of the drop in the King Kong ride,
was injured himself trying it.
Then invented Guts, then escaped Scientology,
which by his own quote, he said,
he made it all the way, he made it up to all the levels.
He made it up to OT seven or whatever.
Wow.
I'm the Scientology agro-craig.
He got to the very top.
He got the final crystal off the top.
Wow.
And he gave an interview where he said,
once I figured out it was all about aliens and stuff,
then I'm looking around the world and going,
well I'm not seeing any aliens.
What am I doing?
And by that point in time, he had given a million dollars
of his own money to the Church of Scientology.
Whoa.
He just had the sudden, what was any of this?
He got into it in that very slow way
that people get into it where it's very self-helpy
and all these classes and they're helping me.
And then just realized, oh, I didn't,
it crept up on me, this is a cult, what was I doing?
And he decided to do something about it.
He's gonna share his story
and not just go talk at events, which he does,
he's going to, in a narrative form, tell his story,
which he did in a film in 2001 called The Prophet,
the name of the CNBC show that we enjoy very much.
And it is also a 2001 anti-Scientology film
made by the guy who did the King Kong ride.
In this film, an author who's kind of gone off as rocker
named L. Conrad Powers has become the leader
of an organization called
the Church of Scientific Spiritualism,
which lures people in with the promise of self-help
and these tests that they perform involving mind meters.
Okay.
And this film.
So, you may as well call it schmoy and schmology.
Why did Paul Thomas Anderson even bother
with the master after this?
It's been done, dude.
And the Shamwell guy did the same thing.
What? Really?
Yeah, he took his Shamwell money and like,
I don't know if he made a movie.
I know he took money and made a movie
and then also used the money to fight Scientology.
Wow.
Wait a minute, the guy,
because is the Shamwell guy the guy
who made the underground comedy movie?
Yes, Vince Offer.
Vince Offer, yes.
That thing that they used to advertise on cable?
Yeah.
The underground comedy?
Wow.
That's how he got involved in the Shamwell
and the Slap Chop is that he was,
he so successfully sold this weird little movie
via infomercials that infomercial people approached him
and were like, you got something.
Why don't we put you on camera and sure,
but before you know it, he's the Slap Chop guy.
And he was a Scientologist?
I've never heard any of this.
Yeah, any declared war.
Whoa.
And we don't, we have to figure out
the machinations of that war.
He didn't, but he's done something.
Right.
That's amazing.
Wow, good for Vince Offer.
A flawed hero.
It's not a full endorser.
Yeah, doesn't he get, he was in some trouble, right?
Yeah.
There were some messes he could not clean up.
Also mentioning Nickelodeon Guts, I was like,
that must be the most popular thing filmed
at Universal Orlando.
Maybe so.
But then I looked it up.
We've got a family feud with Steve Harvey.
Whoa.
Oh, cool.
Yeah.
Certain episodes of Deal or No Deal on CNBC.
Right.
Very good.
And then total nonstop action wrestling.
Oh yeah.
And WCW Monday Nitro.
Yep.
Portions of Fear Factor and major scenes
of the movie Parenthood.
That's right, that was the arbitrary one they chose.
They were like, something has to come filmed here
so we can say something filmed here.
Right.
And it was that, because that was in the early 90s.
They don't even have Jimmy Buffett's food cakes
on that list.
Yeah, no, I didn't see it on there.
Hold on, Gliss is this.
Oh, and The Tonight Show, if that counts.
The Tonight Show, yes, they did some weeks there.
Yeah, most studio-based NBC Comcast-owned properties
will do a few days in Universal a year.
I think Ellen does, that's Warner Brothers.
Every one of those shows does a few days
at Universal every year.
Today's Show, that's what it's named.
Sure, sure.
Really quick, but just before I move on from The Profit,
The Profit is available entirely on YouTube.
This is a film that Scientology fought into the ground.
They aired it, they showed it at theaters
in Clearwater, Florida to fuck with Scientology
in their own backyard, and they called it,
we call this thing the lack of profit,
that's what we say it is.
And they disparaged the film and they said,
it looks like it was shot on somebody's home video camera.
And I gotta go with Scientology on that one.
And there is a part, I didn't watch the full film
because I barely found out about this,
but I did put on, there's a part where it zooms
into a dying El Conrad powers.
Oh my God.
And this is like Halloween store makeup.
This is like, they slap a gray wig on him.
A couple, all right, how do we show that he's old?
Lines, let's put a line on his face.
Do you think this is on par with the slightly teased
Lance Burton movie that we talked about
on the David Copperfield Patreon, Billy Toppett.
The very cheap looking Lance Burton movie
about a magician named Billy Toppett.
We haven't done Billy Toppett yet.
We haven't.
We gotta do a film series, Billy Toppett.
That's what I'm getting at.
The profit and the underground comedy.
Available for unrated version, $3 on Amazon right now.
So when I order my copy of, what's the TV show,
what's the DreamWorks TV show?
Father of the Pride.
Yeah, we gotta do that too.
An Amazon cart with Father of the Pride
and underground comedy movie,
and then the FBI will be at my house very quickly.
Billy Toppett, master magician.
Oh my God.
Jesus, the cover.
You've never shown us that.
Yeah.
We watched the trailer before.
Garbage.
It's no Burt Wonderstone.
Peter Alexander also has the Spielberg connection.
I came across a few different things.
One is saying that the Universal versus Disney book
says that Spielberg hired Alexander
after all the rides were open.
One video online was saying he was so impressed by Kong
on the studio tour that he tasked Peter Alexander with,
all right, think of some back to the future ideas
for a ride.
Oh, huh.
But while we're talking Spielberg,
there's that famous story that Spielberg
did not wanna do the big drop on Jurassic Park
because he's scared of heights.
And that was not the first time he pulled that
because he came to Universal Orlando before it opened.
And apparently they say in the book,
Spielberg was not fond of heights
and suggested that he wait for his guests
at the exit of Kongfrontation.
Like Killjoy.
Yeah.
Yeah, geez.
He wouldn't even do Kongfrontation.
Wow.
Feels on par with me though, not long ago.
I feel like a kindred spirit within.
If he was on the podcast regularly,
he would have worked up to it.
Yeah.
And now he could do it.
Spielberg's just not being conditioned like I am.
Yeah.
The book also makes a point to point out.
They were having a lot of troubles with Jaws and Kong
when it first opened.
There was no way to be certain that Kong
would not malfunction and stick his hand into the tram car
and nail somebody in the third row
or that the tram car would not break off Kong's hand
in the process.
Wow.
Jesus.
What?
It might have just reached in and.
Wow.
So probably for the best, Steven sat it out.
Yikes.
Yeah, I read that on opening day
that all of the mechanized stuff broke
and they were just operating it practically.
So like all day on opening day,
there were just people in the control room
just doing it live.
Fuck it, we'll do it live.
That's like if there were like 100 people
doing Pirates of the Caribbean
and they just had to be there all day
like puppeting the mouths essentially.
God.
Making the woman chase the man with the rolling pin.
Geez.
Like, I'm bored.
I'm gonna make him do a jerk off gesture.
Who cares?
All right, now I'm feeling good.
I'm gonna make him do the hang 10 sign.
Hang loose.
Could you make him talk?
If they could manually do it, could you like,
you could make him talk and play it over the loudspeaker.
Oh yeah, probably.
He thinks everybody by name.
Oh my God, that would be the greatest.
Good my, Brett.
This is gonna have to be quick.
The vehicle is much bigger.
If you're struggling with your life,
you may have what are called feet
and strapped in your body.
What, these are buildings?
I thought they were Kong sized E-meters.
I'm just trying to get my head straight.
Wow, we gotta find out if that's possible to like manually,
I guess it has to be,
manually program all these robots.
Sure, but they're all gone now.
I'm just saying all robots in general on these rides.
I'm saying that opens up the potential.
Could you do Lincoln and truly have somebody
just making the mouth move as they talk
and you have him do a totally different show
at great moments with Mr. Lincoln.
Where he like responds to people and roasts them?
Yeah, he does crowd work.
Look at this guy in the front row.
What a chowder head.
Is this your wife?
What happened lady?
You look as thick headed as the morally corrupt leaders
of the Confederate army.
Well, I think you've made a good case right now
for you being the voice.
Yeah.
All right, I have to do live.
Someone let us know,
we have listeners at work at Disneyland.
Is this possible?
Obviously we can't do it unless we do something very
against the rules, but is it possible?
I just like to know.
Your hat looks silly and not at all like a stovepipe.
Honestly, people would love that if he was like,
it was like turtle talk with crush, but Lincoln.
Yeah.
And he just lightly made fun of you
with only references he would be available to him
at the time he was alive.
So he couldn't do a Rickles roast.
He couldn't call somebody a Nazi in the front row
because he didn't know what that was yet.
He comes from a more innocent time before Nazi.
I guess he could say war.
I'm jealous of Lincoln.
I guess you'd be like, what are you, a Confederate?
What is this guy?
Confederate?
Logs for brains?
In which case I'm a fan of you.
I love logs.
Big fan of logs.
Quickly scanning all the things I know about Lincoln
in my head and I might be out.
He was good.
Sullen.
Sullen, say, he was depressed.
Mellon Colley, he was a sad, sad man.
A couple real quick Kong things.
I always liked the logo.
I thought the logo was real fun.
Oh yeah, all the art associated with it is so great.
And the photo op, you would come down this big ramp
at the end and there was, I don't think my family ever
did the photo op, but there was a giant Kong
and you could get in his hand as if he was picking you up
and get your official Kodak photo op memory.
And it was so, I mean, nowadays people would be lining up
for something like that.
I mean, they wouldn't make any money off it
because everyone would just use their phones, but.
There is a similar thing at, at least in New York,
but probably elsewhere, at Madame Tussauds, similar photo.
Oh, great.
And I know this because I was going to see Knives Out
a few weeks ago.
Went to Times Square and some guys like,
hey, you want to get into Madame Tussauds for free?
Did he say it like that?
Yeah, like quietly.
Like to me and my friend, we kind of looked at each other
and were like, yes.
You come in, you walk around at the end, there's a survey.
You put my name down.
My name's Tyler.
You do that, get in for free.
And then we were like, yeah, deal.
And then he gave the guy the nod and then they waved us in.
We got to explore a mostly empty Madame Tussauds.
Yeah, what's on the more recent end of celebrities in there?
Who'd you see?
Oh, we got, there's a whole Marvel exhibit now.
So Captain Marvel is pretty new.
Kardashians.
Oh, nice.
Greta Gerwig.
Is there a Greta Gerwig?
Is there a Florence, I don't know how to say it.
Florence Poo?
Poo?
I don't know.
I think it's poo.
Is it poo?
Florence Poo?
The cast of Parasite, Poo Dameron.
Oh yeah.
I was gonna say Poo Dameron.
Sure.
Yeah, the thing with Greta though, it's like,
it's Frances Ha.
Yeah, it's Frances.
It's always a few years behind.
Like, I wanna take a picture of Greta Gerwig,
not Frances Ha.
Right.
Yeah.
They have the Safdies, but it's him in good time,
and which in retrospect, it's a little weird.
He was playing kind of the handicapped guy,
and I don't want a picture with that.
Yeah, the 824 section was really funny.
That was packed.
That section was packed.
Yeah.
Oh, souvenir.
This was a big souvenir, I feel.
Stuffed gorilla.
I believe I went to this with my grandparents.
We went, took them to Florida once,
and I believe my, for my cousins who were not there,
I believe my grandfather bought a stuffed Kong.
But I remember that was a big merchandise
when Universal first opened,
was stuffed sharks and stuffed gorillas.
You know what I really like are those
in surrounding stuff and artwork, like you said,
I really like when the billboards that were outside,
if you guys have seen pictures of the billboards
in Florida promoting, and because they had texture,
it was like a weird, too many details, like plastic Kong.
They didn't just do flat billboards.
They were sort of odd and scaly and creepy.
I don't know why I immediately thought of the board game
life with the weird, the mountains
that were like three dimensional.
That's not the best example of what you're talking about,
but that's what popped into my head.
I know what you're talking, I know what you mean.
I like inserting those into the.
Yes, that was very satisfying, we're on the wheel.
Dimensionality.
This in general, I'm very sad that I didn't get to do this
because it feels like the ultimate
Universal ride of the time.
It's got all the different things
that differentiate it from Disney.
It's a little scarier.
It's different tonally than anything.
I guess MGM Studios was opening up
and they were gonna have a gangster hijack your car,
which is the closest, I don't know,
feeling of terror you'd get and danger.
Both of these parks had a lot of real fire,
which is fun.
Real fire.
Hosts in the car, like Jaws, like cast members in the car,
which probably contributed to both those rides downfall
because that's expensive to have people in every car,
although both real people leaders too.
They could get a lot of people throughout.
There were anecdotes about cast members on Jaws,
cast members on King Kong were trying to,
it was competitive to see how many guests
they could get through per hour.
Also on Jaws, they were armed.
Yeah, they were armed.
This would have been helpful on Kong, but.
They weren't expected.
This is an evacuation mission.
They don't expect to be taking a best Kong.
But it feels like the rise of the resistance of the time,
where all of Universal's tricks are in there.
It's the best of everything they can do.
It's possible at the moment.
Yeah, I think it really did push the limits.
Because it broke down all the time.
It broke down a lot, yeah.
But I love that it was big on the tram tour
and then they go, how do we top one Kong, two Kongs.
Skylar, we haven't talked about that.
You get to see two robots.
That's really neat.
I was so, I remember seeing these commercials
and I was so scared of the idea of it.
I wonder if I was six if I would have refused to do it.
I might have.
Because it was scary and when I'm watching these videos,
I go, oh my God, I would have been terrified.
Because we've talked before about,
when did you go on this?
How old were you, Scott?
It might have been down when I was there in the 90s.
I might not have done this till like 99.
Would you have been freaked out with your big things
in a smaller space sphere?
Probably, yes.
That's one of my questions.
Because I have. He's huge.
I've talked about before my fear of giant
car dealership balloons out front as a child.
To the point. Have you talked about that?
Have you? Yeah, have you?
No, I don't know if you have.
You might just hear it so much in your head,
that and Galactus.
I'm thinking about Galactus.
Will Galactus defeat the car dealership balloons?
I'm thinking about Galactus all the time.
I've never mentioned that.
I really have not mentioned that I was afraid
of like big giant balloons before on the show.
No. Wow.
No, really?
Afraid of them.
They're also silly and friendly.
Well, because they were just so big,
they were abnormally, you know,
you don't see a giant inflatable ape
in front of a car dealership.
I would like, I kind of look away.
I would look away in the car when we'd be driving by it.
Wow, much less in giant sunglasses and giant swim trunks.
Yeah, there was right by the,
right by the Rosemont Horizon,
which is now the Allstate Arena.
I remember there was something they were promoting
and there were like seven of them in a row
along the like the expressway.
And God, I was scared.
Even though they were far away,
it wasn't like they were coming up to the car.
But then my dad once, there was one,
there was a giant balloon, just it was balloon shaped
next to the Toys R Us on Gulf Road.
And he made me go up and touch it.
He like, he forced me to like, yeah, get over it.
It mostly worked.
I think I was still a little uncomfortable,
but it did like.
This was a facing fears moment.
Yeah. They touched the balloon.
Yeah, I remember it very, very vividly.
I assume I was like six, seven.
Wow.
Walked up to it and touched it.
I don't know if that's really the best way to do it,
cause it wasn't like I was thinking
it was actually gonna eat me
or that it wasn't real or something.
So I don't know why touching it was.
It's just tackling your fears.
Yeah. Putting your hands on your fears.
He should have just like sat me,
like made me sit there for an hour and stare at it.
Desensitize me to it.
For every tear, I deduct $1,000 from your inheritance.
He should have, I mean, maybe it was a bribe.
Maybe I got bribed that day.
Cause I got bribed for other things,
like scoring a goal in soccer.
Like my dad told me. Was that successful?
I was bad at all sports.
I didn't want to play.
I was on defense.
And then I one day,
I don't know if he like talked to the coach.
They put me in on offense for soccer.
And my dad came up to me before I was about to go in
and said, I will buy you a toy if you score a goal.
And I fucking scored a goal so fast.
It's unbelievable how fast I scored it.
And I got a Ninja Turtle vehicle out of it.
And I was thrilled.
So I wonder if there was some sort of bribe.
I have to ask my dad.
He, and I will say all of our dads
should be bribing us in this way.
I'll get you a toy if you sell a TV show.
Oh my God.
And I just did it.
Yeah.
Honestly, I need the motivation right now.
Sure.
So I'm jealous of not going on it,
but I wonder if I would have been too scared as a kid.
Well, he wasn't inflatable.
I was a little scared.
Now I'm thinking, I was about 10.
So it was like 98.
Yeah.
And I think I was still a little,
I mean, maybe like we were in the vicinity
and I was like, maybe we check out another ride first.
Like, let me build up my.
That's a good move.
Let's go back to Lucy.
Cool, like, for a minute.
Oh man, if they can drive across country,
I can face God.
That's the thing, my wife Erin is extremely fond of,
the game where you drove them across country
by answering trivia questions.
Oh my gosh.
The questions were hard though.
Very specific questions.
They still had it like seven years ago.
And Lindsay took a picture of me excitedly
playing the I Love Lucy game.
Wow.
We haven't talked about the biggest selling point.
Oh yeah.
I remember it, maybe it was even like
in the pamphlet or something,
or on like the Beetlejuice hosted infomercial
that just played on repeat at the hotel.
Wait, maybe I don't know there was that.
Oh yeah.
Fuck.
That I kept watching and annoyed my family.
Cause he hosted it?
It was like the Beetlejuice actor at the park being like,
you want scares?
Get on jaws.
Like whoa, wait a minute.
He was sort of the MC.
I've never seen this.
Have you seen this?
In which hotels are we talking?
Well there used to be hotels,
not like partner hotels across the highway, right?
I'm gonna say this was at a Days Inn somewhere.
Like whoa.
That had, so they gave all of these hotels,
Beetlejuice videos?
An in hotel chat when I got like stuck
in Vegas once, like this no name hotel had like
the Vegas channel, which was very much like a theme park.
So I think like,
These can exist.
There can be like the Disney channel
and the universal info channel.
Okay, okay.
It was just like for tourism.
Oh man.
So Beetlejuice told you about everything?
Yeah.
I wanna see this really bad.
He set the groundwork for my excitement.
Wow.
He was kind of the master of the ceremony.
Original universal, I feel like.
So he'd tell you about Kong though.
So he said Kong, and I remember this was a big selling point
was the banana breath.
Oh wait, that was the opening joke
and then we haven't talked about it.
Yeah, yeah.
Smell that banana breath.
Which the one here did too
and I smelled it on the daily when I worked there.
It's great.
That is a lot of fun.
It's a really smart idea.
They didn't have to think of it.
They could have missed that.
But it's really funny.
I mean, yeah.
Like they, yeah.
There was nothing, there was no banana smell
anywhere out before this, right?
They really innovated with banana breath.
I think so. Yeah.
There may not have been a ton of theme park smells
up until this point.
Did this innovate the theme park smell?
I think they had to go to a fragrance distributor.
Like they had to go to someone who sold scents
to like get this scent.
Interesting. And then get it in bulk.
Like it's artificial banana smell.
Yeah. Yeah.
Which is odd.
Because bananas don't really smell like anything.
Right, but did you ever have the Nesquik banana flavor
like I did as a child?
Yeah.
You'd have those like little,
they came in like a very satisfying like metal or like tin
and you'd scoop out a scoop of it.
We had it in strawberry and banana
and you put it in your milk
and it was the most artificial banana smell possible.
Yeah. It's like fake watermelon.
That kind of like flavor.
There's fake banana.
I guess a lot of bananas together have a smell
but not like one.
Speaking of which, how's your hand doing?
My hand is, there is no sign of anything going on
in the banana spot.
Does it smell like bananas?
Yes.
Wow.
Oh. So they do have a smell.
They do have a smell. They do.
But it's not like the Runtz candy version of banana.
It's more of a, it's a subtle, it's a more subtle smell.
Yeah.
So I'm not an idiot
but why would Kong's breath smell like bananas?
Yeah.
You know.
We need a train and a helicopter.
It's not like motor oil.
Requires a lot.
Ripping apart crocodiles or something you said, right?
So, well, where in the timeline is it?
Has he been made to perform in the show?
Right.
As, when he was backstage at the show,
did they, was there crafty?
Was there like a big pile of bananas?
Blue almonds.
They put out a lot of things for him.
You know, they had, they had barbecue chips
and the trail mix.
But like.
A little last sprint just in case.
Yeah.
I don't like, yeah, with somebody on,
like the amount of bananas he'd have to have
to feel satiated would be insane.
You'd have to have somebody peeling the bananas.
Or did he eat them with the peel?
I guess his digestive system can handle the peel.
Probably.
He can just eat a crocodile.
Jason's digestive system can't handle a regular banana.
Well, I just need a little toast or a little cereal first
to prime the pump.
Prime the pump.
Prime the tummy pump.
You can't have just a banana in there in the morning.
It's so much sugar immediately, I feel like.
Could you have like a strawberry first thing?
I think that'd be fine.
What else is on your list?
What can't you have?
What's on the no-no list?
I don't know.
No, no, no, no.
I don't have bananas no more.
Hmm, I'm trying to think.
I mean, some mornings it's like I wake up
and something savory sounds disgusting to me.
But some mornings something sweet sounds disgusting to me.
But that's more of like a taste thing
than like a this will fuck me up sort of thing.
But a banana would fuck you up.
But it sounds like a banana is the one rule you have.
No bananas first.
No bananas first, yo.
But anything else is on the table.
You would eat like a pancake or a chocolate chip pancake?
Sure.
Cold?
Well, as long as I have caffeine to balance it out.
I think the sugar.
I think too much sugar early in the morning.
Do you put a lot of sugar and cream in a coffee?
No.
Not at all?
No, maybe I'll get a vanilla latte, but only one pump.
Would you eat a piece of cake first thing?
Yes.
But that's incredibly sugary.
I need a cup of coffee to balance out the sugar.
So balance it out the banana with coffee.
Yeah, yeah, that would probably work.
But I would need to have some of the coffee first.
No question about the cake.
The cake is the flaw in this.
Up till that I think I was with you.
But if it's the cake.
I think, well, I think the wonders of sugar processing,
probably.
So the raw sugar.
Yeah, the fiber, the stuff from the earth.
I needed a little more.
We need a listener to weigh in on this.
Is there scientific evidence, what Jason's saying,
that banana sugar would be rarer and more tumultuous
inside Jason's stomach?
It's the morning.
I can't have all that real sugar shit.
Give me cake.
Give me a sheet cake.
I have one real little thing.
Breakfast sheet cake.
So here's a thing for our theoretical movie series.
The Magic of the Movies Souvenir VHS cassette,
which they would sell at Universal Florida,
and I believe Universal Hollywood too.
Hosted by John Forsythe.
Oh, yes.
Well, I love this.
This is my favorite tape.
It was back when there was a very short window
where theme parks would be like, here's a souvenir VHS
to remember your trip.
It is $40.
Now it is free on YouTube.
I scrolled through to find, when does he talk about Kong?
And how does he talk about Kong?
So of course, the Kong footage is that very stylized,
like Kong squatting at you and the tram and the helicopters.
But John Forsythe setting it up is just
him talking about the thrills of Kong
while he is on a slowly drifting boat.
He's on a boat in the middle of the water in Universal Florida.
And it's like a two-tier boat.
He is in the galley.
He's in the living room area of this boat
that is either on a rope at the dock
or just in the middle of it.
And it's just kind of drift.
You see the background just drifting.
And John Forsythe, who is old at this point,
is just setting up Kong.
But there's no context.
He's just on a slowly drifting boat.
When you're thinking about the movies,
you don't notice where you are, why you're drifting,
where to, if the boat was sinking.
I wouldn't even give it a thought.
But I mean, that VHS, I truly am wondering,
was this directed for children to remember their trip?
Or was it more for the era of the last remnants
of people making slides and giving,
here's, you gotta look at the slides from my trip.
Was the John Forsythe VHS for very old people
who were used to seeing slides
of friends and loved ones' journeys?
John Forsythe involvement is maybe a hint.
I think so.
Like I maybe would have chosen Beetlejuice
if given the choice of MCs.
Far too crass.
I definitely have watched that
and probably wanted the VHS as a kid.
Yeah. Yeah, I definitely eyeballed it.
I might not have known it was there.
I was a big fan of the movie side of Universal Studios.
Like I loved the Hitchcock exhibit.
I was really into that.
I obviously loved the Lucy thing.
All of those kind of attractions really appealed to me.
It was like a nerdy tenor.
What that led to was just a generation of people
who are weirdos in the entertainment industry,
who are comedians.
Yeah.
Yeah, it spoke to us.
Murder She Wrote, you see the Murder She Wrote show?
Or was it Hercules and Xena by the time you were?
It was Hercules and Xena.
I was not even, I didn't just watch the show,
I was part of it.
Damn, whoa.
We haven't talked about Hercules and Xena at all.
I was a centaur child.
I was the centaur child.
Whoa.
Yeah.
Okay.
The centaur children have found each other.
A late reveal in the episode.
Whoa.
I also at this time, I loved,
like it was my favorite thing on TV,
the action pack of Hercules and Xena.
Wow.
I loved it so much.
It was such a thrill to be part of that world.
Wow.
The centaur children.
The two centaur children.
From across the country,
they managed to find each other.
I've never seen the show though.
What did the centaur children do?
I think we just celebrated.
I remember going, woo.
Well, someone was attacking Hercules and Xena
and then there's footage of centaur shooting crossbows.
Yeah.
And then it cut to two adult centaurs and a centaur child
and Hercules and Xena are like, thanks.
And then it cuts to us in front of a green screen.
Yes, we killed that man.
We killed that man to help you.
Oh my God.
Oh, both of you, wow.
I mean, these Hercules and Xena crossovers,
they didn't come, there was once in a blue moon.
It was a big deal when they meet again.
Yeah.
And you got to be part of one.
I got to be part of it.
You're part of the universe now.
Wow, that's amazing.
What if you had just been in it
and you didn't know what the context was gonna be?
It's gonna cut to you and then you wave and celebrate.
And then if what that ended up being is like,
Hercules and Xena got slaughtered,
just wrecked and their bodies are dead.
Oh no.
And then the villain gives you a thumbs up
and you're supposed to like, yay.
Their blood is on our hands.
And right before it cuts to you,
they like throw a little blood on you.
No, no.
Thank you centaur children.
You finally banished those bastards to hell
where they belong.
Take me back to Mills driving.
I need a milkshake to calm down.
But not a banana if it's the morning.
They should have sold videos of that.
That's a big thing they didn't do.
They didn't give us like anything.
Like I thought I'd get a video at the end.
Yeah, the MGM studios version
when they would have you been like
being the soap opera and stuff.
They didn't sell a video to that either I don't think.
It seemed like such a missed opportunity.
Someone be inserted into home improvement episode.
Oh.
Disney World.
Yeah.
That was a Disney World thing.
What did you guys wear to be centaur children?
There was some armor.
I'm sure I was also wearing maybe like a bugle boy
sleeveless shirt.
Was it wig?
That was my style.
Yeah, like a long haired wig maybe.
Guys, both of you Halloween idea for this year.
Oh yeah.
You made it.
Send tweet pictures at each other.
The boys are back in town.
Centaur boys are back in town.
Forever Dogs Halloween promotion.
Yeah.
It's two different O's on two different coasts.
Just the centaurs.
Should really change the name of the podcast network
to Forever Centaur.
Oh yeah, yeah.
Forever Centaur.
Any final thoughts about Kong?
About anything while you have the mic?
It was the most exciting week of my life
until I was maybe 18 and had a car
and was kissing people and graduating school.
It was such a big trip for me
because it had been built up and other kids got to do it.
So by the time I was 10 and doing it, it was huge.
And King Kong was the centerpiece of it.
Man, hell yeah.
There's entire years of my life missing.
I don't remember a day.
I don't remember what school was like.
I remember every second of the Disney or Universal trips.
I had all the, I would take every, any like free thing
like I had and I would just look over again reminiscing.
Yeah, it was such a fun time to be, yeah.
And it was pre-Islands of Adventure.
They're still using that neon sign logo.
It's just like aesthetically really still in the head.
Man, hell yeah, absolutely.
Well, Centaur Child, Brett Davis,
You Survived Podcast, The Ride.
What a blast.
Thanks so much.
And let's exit through the gift shop
with the King Kong photo op.
Is there anything you'd like to plug?
Check out the podcast for laundry on Forever Dog,
the National Lampoon Radio Hour on Forever Dog.
Did a weird TV show for a while
called The Special Without Brett Davis.
That's still up there.
And there's like, that's on YouTube.
And it's on YouTube, yeah.
You can watch moments for that, wonderful.
I know, Brett Davis, RIP on social media.
Cool, cool, all right.
And as from us, as from us,
for more Podcast, The Ride, follow us on Twitter,
Instagram, and Facebook, and three bonus episodes
every month if you sign up for Podcast, The Ride,
the second gate at patreon.com slash podcast, the ride.
Mr. Six episode, certainly coming soon.
Lucy tribute coming soon.
Yeah, this one's really looming now.
The Lucy one, I think we promised
a two and a half hour episode.
I'm not sure that we have, but you clearly did just now.
We might have to do a retreat to prepare for that.
We might have to go to Big Bear or something.
Yes, I think.
And run out of house.
We gotta drive across the country from New York to LA.
Oh, yeah.
We have to find William Folly's relatives.
We have to, like how we found Cotswinkle
and the guy who did Botanicus.
We need to find the great, great grandson of Bill Frolly.
You wanna ask about who?
Bill?
Forget about Bill, that old son of a bitch.
No way he had any kids, right?
I don't think so.
I believe he had.
Not on purpose.
Yeah, no, not on purpose.
See, where he'd be.
Damn it, I'd have it again.
He seemed like he'd be put out by it accidentally.
He seemed to be put out by the act.
He doesn't seem like a guy
who would love the act of lovemaking, no.
Also presumably dead before either of these Lucy zippers.
Oh, yeah, he died a couple years.
He was on My Three Sons for a couple seasons
and then he got replaced because he was ailing
and then he was dead pretty soon.
And he was 25 years older than the rest of them.
Walked outside of his apartment building
and died on the sidewalk.
Yeah, he like lives in a one-bedroom apartment still.
The same efficiency apartment for years and years.
I forget which one, I used to know which one.
We need to find it.
We gotta go.
We gotta find the apartment,
we gotta find the hospital bed he died in as well.
I wanna die in now.
Or the sidewalk he died on,
depending on where it actually happened,
where the expiring happened.
It depends on what part of town I'm in.
Is this LA we're talking about?
The Boulevard.
Oh yeah, it's like by Paramount, I think.
I think his apartment was right around there.
Oh really?
Yeah.
Yeah, go find it.
So that we know in advance.
All right, if we're on one side of the hill,
take me to the walled bed.
If I'm on the other side of the hill,
The Frawley sidewalk.
The Frawley, I wanna die on the Frawley sidewalk.
Which piece of cement did Bill Frawley die on?
Excuse, yeah, police man walk.
Officer, hey, do you know?
Where's that, hi, where's that famous sidewalk in Hollywood?
With the stars?
No, no, no, hell no, I don't wanna see that shit.
Take me to where Bill Frawley collapsed and died.
That would be the tour I would start in Hollywood.
I would drive people around in a van.
It would be mostly about Bill Frawley things.
You'd start at the apartment building
then drive up the sidewalk slightly.
All right, get it out.
All right.
Yeah.
Tour's over.
Also, if Kiss Makeup Guy is out there,
please reach me.
Yeah, I'm serious.
He kinda look like Harry Knowles, if that helps.
I don't know how much that nervous it is.
Harry Knowles with the little Jane Simmons makeup.
So this has been a great mystery in my life.
Wow, wow, an old family friend, yes.
Let's make the reunion happen
just like the Centaur Chaud reunion.
Thanks for listening everybody.
Fighting the frizzies at 11.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a Forever Dog production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Silio, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts,
please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple Podcasts, Spotify,
or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news
by following us on Twitter and Instagram,
at Forever Dog Team, and liking our page on Facebook.