Hey, this is a little Patreon bonus.
We're finalizing the brackets for the fake smell final four.
And I wanted to pose a question that I thought might be funny enough for the episode, but
and we'll see, maybe this is nothing.
Genuine question.
Are we sure there was a fart smell in Shrek 4D?
I'm not sure that there is one because I don't remember, but it feels like...
We have a category at this point that is fart versus fart.
And I'm not totally sure that there was a fart.
He definitely farts in the movie.
Yes. But I'm Googling it and I'm not finding a lot.
But Jason, I think this is your suggestion, so you might know better.
Yeah, I could have Mandela affected myself.
I think maybe if anything, there was like a spray.
You mean, wait a minute, maybe they spray air jet instead of a smell.
Yeah. Yeah. I don't remember a fart smell on it.
It feels right.
It does. And I really like our category of fart versus fart.
But there's maybe a logistical error here.
And also, if you think about I believe now currently the suggestion
and I hate to pick this apart because I really like that we have fart versus fart.
Right. But I also believe that fart in Despicable Me, Minion Mayhem,
is a fart gun that once fired is actually the smell of banana.
I believe you're correct. Yeah.
So it might be incorrect to say I think there may be a fallacy in both farts.
Well, but you could call it a banana fart, I guess.
But it doesn't. You're right. A pure fart maybe doesn't exist.
The closest thing is honestly like skunk, I think, if we're talking pure smell
from figment. Yeah. Which is I think is in there.
I think maybe what I may be thinking is that
what is currently listed in the pre list as Despicable Me
fart should maybe become
classified as banana and go up against King Kong's banana breath.
Oh, that's good. Yeah, let's do that.
Let's start with that. Yeah. OK.
That might be it.
Maybe this is this is just a little like five minute fragment.
Is there anything else we want to hash out before we get to the list?
We can recap some of this on the episode, but yeah.
Should we just a little peek behind the curtain?
Hmm. Good question.
I hate that we it makes me upset that there potentially was not an actual fart.
Yeah. On any. And if we're wrong, tell us.
Oh, my God. For wrong. It's over.
And if there is a part that we're unaware of.
Yeah. Yeah. Huh.
So I think should we dock points from Jason already for this for
we're competing now, we're competing within the there's ways we can win.
Well, fake smell final four. I guess you're right.
That's true. We're not really.
I mean, I don't mind it.
I just now we have a really more complicated.
Jason's vote counts 75 percent and ours counts 100.
Well, this is some this is gerrymandering.
This is some Iowa cockatoo.
I don't want to do that. Yeah.
Oh, you were at that birthday party, Mike,
which birthday party of the app developers.
Oh, yeah. I know you were there with the other scumbag.
Shadow. But that's just but he might knew Tommy Vitor.
You know, you got to.
I am on the website.
Your friends. I am listed on the website.
I sit on a couple boards. OK.
So don't fucking get mad at me.
Sit on some boards. I'm on like seven boards.
It doesn't take up much time. I understand.
It's fun to be on the board. It's fun.
I get 50 grand a month from each board.
Just for having my name be on it.
Does the know, guys, is the fake smell
final for voting app working for everybody is is shade working for everyone?
Yeah. Let us know.
I would be shocked if it's not.
I sit on the board of that, too.
And we tested it once.
So I think it'll be fine.
I'm you see, I'm on the I'm on the board of of glint,
which is really the opposite.
I'm on the board.
A is like a shadow on glint is like if there's too much sun.
Yeah, we want to be fully exposed.
We want everyone to know we don't want any shadow type problems.
We want everyone to be in the glint.
I'm on the board of glare,
hmm, which is one where it's sort of like over.
You want like a big blast of it, whatever we're making.
You want a blast of it in your face.
I'm not concerned that glint and glare can't exist in the same marketplace.
And you got you guys are prelaunch, right?
Because we're like we're in Blanche prep.
Yeah, we're prelaunch right now.
Honestly, I don't know what's happening because I just sit on the board.
I'm not one of the developers.
No, I don't. I'm not making the app.
God, no, I don't know anything about making apps.
Yeah. So I do that.
And we're working on a couple of things.
We're working on an app where you there's different birds
and then they fly up and down and then they get little like peanuts and stuff.
And then you get points suspiciously like Flappy Bird.
Hmm. Does it? OK.
No, it's it's Flapp Flapping Bird.
It's totally Flapping Bird. Yeah. Yeah.
All right. Well, we can start out the rest of this off, Mike.
I just wanted to loop you guys in on the on the decision
and let us know if you have a problem with it. Yeah.
All right. Thanks. Bye.