Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, the second gate today containing
one of the stupidest experiments in the history of Podcast the Ride.
I'm Scott Gardner going boldly where no man should ever go.
Joined via satellite by Jason Sheridan.
Yeah, I'm here.
And Mike Carlson.
I am here and I am terrified.
The brave three, we really are like the Apollo 13 astronauts.
We may regret boarding this mission or contemplating it, the hubris involved.
Because what you're hearing right now is the Father of the Pride episode.
And we'll talk about what Father of the Pride is, but the, you know,
we've talked about doing this for a long time.
And for some reason we landed on rather than let's just kind of like be vaguely
aware of the show and, you know, kind of poke fun at some highlights of it.
We landed on that we will be watching the series in its entirety.
Yeah, I bought the DVD a number of months ago and because we said we were going to do this
and I was fully prepared for like the days leading up to it.
I just watched like two or three at a time.
But then the world changed and we, Scott, I think it was your idea to watch them all in one day
and check in on each other.
I mean, it seemed like we were always heading to something like,
I feel like in my head all of the discussion of this has been that we would have to watch the entire series.
And then the rise of coronavirus, yes, caused this to be a necessity, I feel.
There's no choice, right?
I can't see how we have a choice here.
Yeah, no, we're powerless to stop this.
It's one of the, yes, there's ways that the world has changed indelibly.
And one of them is that for sure we have to do all this in one day, check in from our separate apartments.
Now, one good thing about it is that I think it would have been a little hellish to do this in person.
I think we would have gotten truly sick of each other.
And the way, doing it via satellite means we can have snacks, we can take a little break,
be with our significant others, we can watch it all in our underwear if we want.
Yeah, I think this is going to be a lot more comfortable.
I don't know, it might be a higher chance that we go completely mad, some sort of internalized madness.
Yes.
Like if we're not, I mean, I guess, yeah, there'll be a significant other route,
but I don't know if I'm going to make Lindsay watch this with me.
I don't think I am.
So I may just melt down alone on the couch is what I'm saying.
Sure.
Would you say you might be feeling like Larry when his father-in-law, Sarmati, moves in?
All right.
As far as characters go, if that's a reference to the show we're about to watch, I don't know those characters.
I know there's a character named Blake.
I've seen Blake. Is that correct, Jason? Blake?
I think there's a Blake.
I should say there's a shocking number of characters with known actors voicing them.
It's an incredible voice cast.
It's a truly robust, I feel like I'm cheating by having the Wikipedia in front of me.
I think we all know John Goodman is the star,
but I'm being reminded by the Wikipedia that Carl Reiner is in this series.
I want to be surprised, but I do have the Wikipedia open and I see something about Darryl Hannah.
Darryl Hannah, I think we may be looking at a CGI Kelsey Grammer coming at some point.
Oh my God.
The random one that I flipped to has that, yes.
I mean, maybe if we're getting into it, yeah, maybe this is a good time to say we wanted to check.
We haven't started this yet.
That's why our plan was to check in right at the top where this is as good of spirits as we're going to be in this episode.
I thought we would just kind of corral all of the information that we know about this show.
Now, the reason that I think it's memorable and why it came up the first time on the show is that
this show aired on NBC from 2004 to 2005.
It was a single season show.
I forget how many aired exactly.
It aired for the first time in 2004.
The show was being prepped for a number of years.
According to Wikipedia, Jeffrey Katzenberg, the king of Quibi himself,
had this idea when he visited Siegfried and Roy's secret garden in 2002.
So, 2002, they had the idea.
2004, it airs.
In 2003, Roy is attacked by one of his own white lions,
and they are still very deep budget-wise into this show.
They are committed to it.
It is far too late to stop it.
So, they now, in 2004, had to air a series about the lions of two characters,
one of whom in real life was mauled by one of the lions.
Yes, and Siegfried encouraged them.
They pumped the brakes, and they're like,
can we not do this anymore?
And Siegfried said, no, we need to push ahead.
This is important to us.
This is important to Roy.
Was the...
Okay, so, wait.
Was a lion that attacked Roy?
Yes.
Yes?
And was it that...
It was not Montecore.
Montecore was the tiger.
I don't think that Montecore is reflected in the series.
I think it is all fictional lions.
All right, that's, first of all, that's one huge strike against this show.
It's crazy.
See, I'm seeing White Tiger, that mauled Roy Horn, here, and it's Montecore.
So, it was a tiger, but the show is about lions.
I guess.
I mean, as far...
Again, I don't know much about the show, but I see, yes.
380-pound White Tiger is Montecore, and that's the one who was involved in the attack.
Do we think they changed it to lions just to put some distance?
I don't know.
It's a good question.
I mean, I assume they had a lot of different types of animals in the secret garden that
they apparently have in Las Vegas.
I assume it's in Las Vegas.
Well, they have a lot of everything.
Like, reading about the production, they made a lot of sets, you know, in the computer.
They made a lot of sets, a lot of props, a lot of original characters.
And back in the early 2000s, that took an obscene amount of manpower and processing power to do CGI.
That was probably some of the rationale behind, we can't cancel this thing.
Yeah, because it was like...
Yeah, they had built so many assets.
I may have mentioned, I don't want to remind people his name in case he doesn't want to be associated with this,
but I do know someone who wrote to, for some extent, an onfather of the pride.
And he joined kind of late in the process.
And what he said was that were just like, he was showing the assets and it's just thousands and thousands of sets
and characters and animals, many of which weren't used.
It was all rewritten so much that it was all thrown away.
So what we're going to see is, you know, 10% of what was built for Father of the Pride.
So maybe Montecori was involved before and they got him out of there?
Could have been, could have changed his name.
I went on the Wikipedia, I did a little search for Tiger without trying to find out too much.
And there is a Tiger character played by John O'Hurley, one of my favorite voice actors and a wonderful guy.
He plays a character named Blake, who is a Tiger.
So that is, yes, Blake that you mentioned is a Tiger and he is a rival of Larry played by John Goodman.
I don't want to find out much more, but so there's like there's lion Tiger combativeness, apparently, in this series.
So could perhaps Blake was like an analogous Montecori?
Definitely could.
I think it's best for us to assume that he is Montecori and that all of the actions that we watch him do in the show are reflective of Montecori.
I will not call Blake Blake. I will call him Montecori.
We all know.
So if you catch me saying Blake, correct me, please, because Montecori, I would like to think of it as Montecori.
I would like to think of him as Montecori.
Do you do you guys know?
And do you guys know, like, really like what the setting of the show is?
Like, if do we have any idea what a home base is at this point?
I do know.
I don't. I do not know.
I assume it's like I assume it's like their house.
I assume it's like a big like palatial mansion in the deserts of Las Vegas.
I don't know.
Well, do you want to know?
No, I will find out is what we'll find out.
I'm just like sussing out everyone's awareness of the series.
I think what else do we do?
We know. I mean, we when the first time we talked about it on the show and I cannot remember why, but I know we discussed that that we're pretty confident that donkey from Shrek shows up in the show, that it ties the Father of the Pride does take place in the Shrek averse.
Yeah, I don't want to spoil anything, but I believe he shows up in the episode solely titled Donkey.
Oh, wow.
That would add up.
So he's a big part of it.
He's a get. He's a big get.
Yeah.
Shrek characters for Fergal, Farkas and Felicia, perhaps.
Oh, this is way before they were even a twinkle in Shrek's eye.
Oh, yeah. Good point.
Good point.
That's I guess another important thing to note is that this very expensive series was done in the wake of Shrek mania and that Katzenberg was a golden boy and they're just throwing money as much as we can possibly throw at him to do this show as soon he will be post to the launch of Quibi.
You may be hearing this after the launch of Quibi, and by that point we will.
Everyone listening will have every Quibi show memorized.
You will have watched every Daily Essential many times over because we are as ravenous as lions and tigers for Quibi content during this boring quarantine of Penta.
We're really the caged animals.
I think we might be able to relate to Larry, especially well.
We're all in cages.
No, Larry's the lion.
Oh, Larry. Sorry, sorry.
Yeah, but yes, Montecore.
Yeah. Are we all going to be like Montecore and and like let our rage loose on this series by the time we've watched 13 of them?
Well, I like to think of the way when Roy, because after the fact Roy started to do some, you know, like damage control and say that Montecore was actually just trying to help him.
So I'd like to think that I'm going to be more helpful in this situation than rageful, but we'll see.
It's hard to know.
I would guess some rage on at least one of our parts.
And maybe we should explain how we're going to do this.
We're going to take it four at a time.
We're going to break it up.
You know, it's sort of like the imagine us.
This is the podcast equivalent of the climb and free solo.
And we're, you know, we're going to like make it to a summit, make it through the various pitches.
Let's think of the episodes as pitches climbing a cliff wall.
And we're going to do one through four and then we're going to rest.
And by rest, I mean, we're going to podcast about it for a little while and then go back and do five through eight.
And then and then the final leg, the most harrowing, we're going to close with five.
We're going to do episodes nine through 13.
But there's there's some confusion in this because Mike and I will be going off of YouTube links.
And if you want to follow along at home, you can also look it up on YouTube and we'll tell you what episodes we're doing.
Jason's going off the DVD.
And that's creating some chaos in terms of which episodes we watch and what is the true order of Father of the Pride?
Yeah, it seems like I mean, on Wikipedia, the list, the episode list, I think might be based off the DVD run order,
because if you look on that chart, it is not the list of air date order.
Now, this said that used to be a very common TV thing that would just air episodes out of order.
And then especially with new shows, they'd air episodes out of order and then be shocked that these shows weren't a big hit.
I feel like so many shows where it's like, oh, that was a fun one or two season show.
It's like, yeah, but then they just started airing the episodes in whatever order and they wouldn't make sense.
Hmm. Hmm. That sounds like a problem. Well, so do we so we probably need to like check in here.
Well, this is so confusing. I'm looking at the Wikipedia original pilot and then it says, no, this episode wasn't aired on US television.
So where do we go? That episode was not aired on US television.
And the Siegfried and Roy fantasy experience movie episode was not aired on US television.
And then the episode titled The Lost Tale was never animated and is solely a storyboarded, you know, animatic on the DVD.
So Lost Tale is off the table. We already said that.
I think it has to be. If you if Jason, if you'd been able to deliver the DVD to us and like so that we could all rip it and then watch The Lost Tale.
But we didn't have the foresight that, you know, the corona got out and we just we just had to act.
So we are stuck with the YouTube links. Yeah, I'm should we go through the names?
Is that like, is that what we should do to make sure because I want to make sure I think the names, the episode names you mean?
Yeah, yeah, sorry. Yes. OK.
OK, well, yeah, so let's just let's just decide what we're watching for block one.
Yes. Why don't you let's maybe you have to dictate it as the keeper of the cleanest copy.
Well, do you have the can you see that the user who uploaded all the YouTube ones?
I just want to make sure all of the ones that I'm seeing are available.
That's that's a good point. Yes. We shouldn't name something that we don't have.
OK, I am. Yeah, the user is Top Tunes and there's he certainly has a lot,
but the order seems wildly different than the Wikipedia.
So, yeah, tell us and we'll make sure we got them all.
Well, do you have original pilot? Does he have original pilot?
I don't know that we if it's just called that, I don't know that we have it.
I think Top Tunes, because I looked at him earlier, I think he may have listed it in.
He might have it as air date because he does he have episode one is what's black, white and depressed all over.
Yes, correct. And that is episode two.
Larry's debut and sweet Darryl Hannah, too. That's correct.
OK, and then that would mean episode three is probably catnip and trust.
Yes. Yes. Catnip and trust number three is the name.
Yeah. Do you approve of this order or is this wildly different than what you're seeing?
Well, so on the original on the DVD menu, it kind of grows, goes in, I guess, the order of production.
They have original pilot Sam Roddy moves in catnip and trust.
But then they have one man's meat is another man's girlfriend.
And then what's black and white and depressed all over.
So I think for the sake of trying to replicate what 2004 America was like, we should go in the air date order, which I again think is Top Tunes is order.
So why don't we say for the first block, it'll be what's black, white and depressed all over.
Great. Then Larry's debut and sweet Darryl Hannah, too.
Great. Go ahead. And then catnip and trust.
Catnip and trust. Yeah, I've been trust.
And then and the revolution continues.
OK. OK.
Revolution continues.
So that will be our order if you're following along with it for some I think.
How many of the people listening to this Patreon, you know, it's like getting close to 2000 people.
But how many you think I want to say like five people might be doing this along with us.
Mm hmm. So I'm like, right.
Most people will say, yeah, you know what?
I'll hear what they say about it before I make a decision.
Yeah, I'm sure by the end we'll have our highlights of like our our phases, you know.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. So we can give you a Cliff Notes version and the ideal order, much as you would with with with Star Wars or with Twin Peaks.
All the great pieces of art will be able to do it with Father of the Pride.
We may have our own preferred order, I think, by the time this is done.
Yeah, yeah, we'll confer on that.
And of course, we already have our preferred naming system, which is that Blake is Montecor.
Blake is Montecor. Yes.
Blake is Montecor. And I'll put this on the table.
Like, I'm not married to this, but like if if one of our breaks is like an extended lunch break, maybe I will I will suffer.
Like maybe I will suffer and fall on the sword and watch the additional two unaired ones.
Jesus. Just wait, wait a minute.
Hold on. I think I know what's going on here.
You want that lunch break to be longer than a normal lunch break.
So you've stuck to TV shows lengths in there.
So you get an extra hour of lunch.
Well, these TV shows aren't very long.
And also 35 minutes of lunch.
I wouldn't say I have the biggest appetite at the moment.
All right. Fair enough.
But also, if we're just like, let's get this done, I don't have to do that.
We'll discuss this. I can give an update on another episode or something.
We'll see how we're doing.
The first four might dictate how much more how much you want to watch more of this.
That may be one more question before we start.
Mike, you said you probably not going to make Lindsay do it.
I think so far the plan is for Aaron, my wife, to do this in solidarity with me.
And that's the plan because there is jack shit else to do in this world.
So I think she's going to she's going to join.
That's the plan now. But I could see her bending very quickly once she sees the quality of the CGI.
Yeah. So, yeah, we'll we'll update you on on on viewing patterns.
Yeah, I my girlfriend, Jane, is watching this with me.
She has decided to do this journey with me to nice to nice to have support.
Is she excited? Are you excited?
Yeah, because I'm pretty stoned.
She says she says yes, because she's stoned.
That'll help. That will certainly help.
OK, then, well, gentlemen, we'll let's all talk.
We'll figure out it. So let's just text each other when we're heading towards the end.
But I'll talk to you soon.
I'll see you see on the other side of the moon here.
We should at the summit. All right. Great.
And break, break.
Well, we're back.
We haven't talked at all.
Let me just say this.
I'd like to quote the downtown Disney ordeal theme and just say, why do we do this to ourselves?
This is what no one was even like asking for this one really or for this to be done in this way.
I well, I mean, yeah, not in this way.
I think somebody actually I was just Twitch streaming yesterday.
I was playing a video game.
Somebody did ask for Father of the Pride.
But no one said why you should punish yourself with Father of the Pride in a short amount of time.
Mm hmm. But when the alternate option is Twitch streaming, you know, look, we're all the bar of how we can entertain ourselves has been significantly lowered.
And I don't know. I think, you know, why not attempts to really rapidly rot our brains?
Yeah, for sure.
Yeah. I do want to get ahead.
I do have to apologize.
The last episode we watched in this block and the revolution continues, I believe it was called the lobster one that that technically aired after donkey.
I had the air dates transposed on that.
So the first block in episode the first episode in block two that we're going to watch would actually be the fourth episode airing in sequence.
That said, I think it worked out because at least we have something to look forward to going into block two.
That's a good point. Yes, because I need a little bit of a I need a little bit of a boost here to get me into block two, I think.
So don't you definitely I'm definitely lagging.
And even though, you know, usually hearing Danny DeVito would be considered a treat.
I don't know that it really gave me the bump that I need.
That might have been the worst one. I think of these four.
I struggled the most through that one.
But I bet you know, why don't we let's go through it in order, I suppose.
Starting with I don't have the full title in front of me, black and white and what?
Black, white and depressed all over.
It's bleak. It's bleak and like.
Well, that was that that was the Panda one. But was that the was that the first one?
That was the first one I watched. That was the very first one that aired.
Oh, did I watch? Did I? I didn't. Did I watch them out of order?
Well, we look we spelled it out. Jason really, at least all that out.
So it's on you if you did.
What's black, white and depressed all over was the first one to air in August 2004.
That said, I think of fitting one to air from what I read because they bombarded the airways
with commercials for this show during the Summer Olympics that year.
And apparently a lot of the commercials were about the animals being horny.
And this episode certainly lived up to that promise.
Did you not see an episode about horny pandas, Mike?
No, no, I saw it. I watched it. I just think I watched it out of order.
Oh, I see. That's OK. Yeah, I think we're all right. OK.
I think that was kind of a big revelation on my part that I didn't know.
I think I thought this was a little bit more in the Shrek zone where it was for families,
but kind of a little bit, as we love to say, bawdy.
And instead, what we found is it is a very edgy show.
It's like about fucking a lot. Yeah, it's a very horny show.
I guess we should also say what it's about now that we know.
Yeah, that's yes. Yeah. The bigger primer. Yeah.
So, so, yeah, so it's a horny show for adults about John Goodman as a lion named Larry
and his wife, Cheryl Hines. And I'm blanking on her name already.
I have it written down. What's the wife, the lion wife's name?
Can somebody help me here? I don't remember either.
And I'll tell you why, because I was so distracted by hearing Cheryl Hines' voice say Larry.
My first note is was this was where they like, you know, we can do like kind of an inception thing
and make people like this if people hear Cheryl say Larry, like on Curb Your Enthusiasm.
My first note just says the lions are horny.
You're paying very close attention. Yes.
My second note just says, quote, good wife time.
Larry says the phrase, I still I can still have some good wife time if I get home now.
Cheryl's character's name is Kate. Kate.
I was hoping Helen, but it's Kate.
The only other time I can remember one character, like an actor saying the name of a character in a movie
that's the same name as a character he played in the movie.
Excuse me, a character he was addressing in a different movie is when Michael Douglas has to keep saying Scott in Ant-Man.
And of course, he has to say Scott a lot in Behind the Candelabra.
Scott. Scott. Scott. What's wrong, Scott?
So when he's talking to Paul Rudd and he says Scott, I just would flash back to Behind the Candelabra.
This isn't with names, but the names of the characters.
I think I got a laugh in the theater when I saw it.
But when I saw Dark Knight Rises and Liam Neeson shows up and I think everyone forgot Liam Neeson was ever in the Batman movies
because Batman Begins had been so long ago and he says something in the movie about like she was taken from me.
He really enunciates taken and it really took everyone out of it.
Just use a different word.
Stolen, removed. Just go to the thesaurus.com.
There's no reason he has to say taken. Right.
Unless it was on purpose.
Could have been. I guess to Inception.
And this is from the maker of Inception.
Yeah. So that's true.
I think you're onto something with your theory, Mike.
Yeah, you're right about the.
Well, OK, so it's the two of them.
And then they've got kids and one of them is in the movie.
Yeah, he really likes Lord of the Rings, which pays off to much comedic effect.
And a younger daughter is kind of unruly and, you know, dating and doing drugs, including lady in one of these dating someone with a child, even though she's 16.
Jesus Christ.
But the end, you know, it throws it off.
So that's at least that's how I wrote it off in my head as being OK.
Some very confusing.
I don't want to say racial politics.
I guess I'll say racial mapping really pops in this one in that, like, there's a lot of racial mapping in this one.
I guess I'll say racial mapping really pops in this one in that, like, there's an elephant with an Indian accent, but all of the pandas have like names like Foo, Lin and Bong Bong, but are voiced by Lisa Kudrow and Andy Richter.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
There's a slave name joke like that's my slave name.
That's my first thing he says.
Yeah, there there is some weird shit in this.
I mean, you said it quickly, but like Foo Lin is obviously fooling.
I mean, right. Like, that's that's the joke is like it's like something from like that 1950s like old movie.
Yeah, like an Asian name.
Yeah, yeah, that it would be another word.
Yeah, that's pretty it's pretty rough.
Bong Bong, that's my slave name.
This is how they wanted to present themselves to America.
Can I also say this is 6.8 on IMDB. That's far too high.
Yeah, how is it so high?
I don't this is the when it premiered this one the week this was the most watched show of the week.
She is wow.
And the ratings apparently quickly fell off, often interrupted apparently by 2004 election coverage and debates and such.
I was going to save this for the episode after which they pulled it from the lineup because they kind of they skipped it.
They skipped this show for November sweeps.
They said we want to really keep the ratings good for this November this month in November.
This show can't be a blight on our schedule.
And the one that last aired in October before they dumped the rest in December only was watched by six point six million people.
I wanted to compare this to 2020.
And I was thinking about what does NBC have now?
I mean, well, they are.
Which feels like about as big of a phenomenon as there could possibly that definitely feels like event viewing in 2020.
Everyone's talking about it.
This is us gets a weekly average of six point four million.
Well, oh, my God, wow.
Eating show about a lion and a guy who got mauled did better than this is us today.
Wow. They would kill for a hit like Father of the Pride today.
The glory days of Father of the Bride long past.
It's like if you look at the ratings for like, you know, the Magic Hour or the Chevy Chase talk show, like they were just incredible.
Oh, yeah. They were just like, you know, doing the Super Bowl numbers now.
Yeah, really? Yeah.
These like the steadily nose diving Oscars every year just gets worse and worse.
And I, yeah, it's yeah, if only it could have been if it could only get to the level of Kenan Iver Wayans talk show vibe.
No, he wasn't. No, I'm sorry.
Sinbad was a vibe. Kenan Iver Wayans had the Kenan Iver Wayans show.
I almost that was really look, I blame it on watching too much Father of the Pride today.
Of course, I know what all the bad 90s stardust work and they had 25 million viewers a night.
They were always in trouble. Everyone was always mad about 25, only 25 million.
You're fired.
I am going to be so tired by the end of this viewing.
I'm going to I lasted two episodes without my phone and I said, you know what, I'm going to sit here and I'm going to watch.
I'll put a note down once in a while.
And by episode three, I was like, I got to get on my phone at least a little.
I don't know. I need to.
I'd rather be looking at very distressing statistics about the virus.
I got to look at live updated numbers to scare and depress me.
You have to watch the live climb of the graph to distract me from Father of the Pride.
A nice, nice distraction from this cartoon.
I halfway through the second episode, I just started handwriting out the air dates of the remaining episode
because I'm like, oh, I'd rather just organize a list than watch this.
That gives us my full attention.
You know, it gets hard to pay attention to also because while there is a bevy of different animals,
there's like a little squirrel or something pops in all the time and there's, you know,
there's like a little snail snack.
Yeah. Squirrel by played by Orlando Jones.
Yeah. Jones. Yeah.
He's in there. There's, you know, there's a snail in one of these.
So they vary it up a little.
But for the vast majority of it is either white lions or white tigers.
And it gets really difficult to tell them apart.
Now we did get an answer.
There is a rivalry between the lions and tigers.
So they do explain that there are white lions and white tigers.
I think, you know what, talking about Siegfried and Roy, I was a bit confused.
I always thought it was mostly a tiger show.
I had never seen Siegfried and Roy like many of people around the world.
I was captivated by the idea of them and the idea of the show.
But I was really thinking it was just tigers and not lions.
But apparently the show was like a bunch of lions and a bunch of tigers together.
So either of you seen Siegfried and Roy? I don't think Jason has.
Live? Yeah.
No, I've seen the like TV specials.
Right. Scott, have you seen Siegfried and Roy live ever?
No, no, no, I never got to see them.
OK. Yeah, I definitely visited like the lion habitat in the Mirage.
The Mirage heavily brands each episode of the show.
Yes, there's a lot of branding. Yeah.
You're referring to the secret gardens.
Yes, that's that's we should say that's where they they live.
We're kind of wondering if it's about like a house or a cave.
And it's it's sort of both. It's kind of the middle of both.
Yeah. Yes. And if I could if I can explain the opening credits and the theme song real quick.
It's the song Viva Las Vegas sung by John Goodman as you're going through like a reboot.
The CGI cartoon from the 90s level of CGI Las Vegas.
Yeah. I mean, maybe a little bit better than reboot.
A little. Yeah, that's about as good of a critics quote as you could give it.
Yes. As you pass by again, the very clear logo of every MGM resort on the strip and no others.
It threw me for a loop because in my just awful taste in quarantine boredom viewing.
Recently, I watched the Flintstones Viva Rock Vegas, which has several performances of Viva Las Vegas with one key change.
And I think you know what it is.
But it was jarring for me to hear John Goodman singing it because John Goodman is not in Viva Rock Vegas.
Right. Do you think this was part of the pitch?
He was so regretful about not doing the sequel and not getting to go to Rock Vegas that they said, well, now you got to actually like you got to your wish fulfillment.
You'll get to like right or wrong in the history of your career.
And he was like, that does sound good. I'd like to do that. Thank you.
Always wanted to sing that song.
Well, he was looking at this is this was a he had just come off Blues Brothers 2000 a couple of years prior.
So he was in a singing mood.
He always is. Yeah.
I actually I've let the opening play every time just because it's I it's more pleasant than watching them talk and hearing them talk about sex and just the like barrage of quips that fills every spare second of this series.
Dated quips, I want to say, like in the first episode, this sad female panda is referred called crazy bitch and fat middle aged virgin.
I believe directed at one character.
The other character also shamed for being a virgin panda.
It doesn't Carl Reiner's character Samadhi.
Did you say that harsh to her?
I believe so.
And she likes it.
So are very crude, but probably the most horny.
He's an old man.
He's very horny and he says inappropriate things.
He's he's not PC.
I think I think a lot of the right wing in the country today would be big Saramati fans because he doesn't let the PC police tell him what to do.
You know, he's he's kind of out of step with the world, even the world of the of Larry and the younger lions.
He's clearly a relic from another era.
But then you finally see him with somebody like correctly matched to him.
He gets he has like a girlfriend who is voiced by Jennifer Coolidge, who as many of her characters are is, you know, kind of a dummy, kind of a dingbat.
And he she she gets easily confused about something and he's like, you're the perfect woman.
You know, he like loves is just airbrained as a lioness can be.
I could see Saramati on a Ben Shapiro show.
I could see him on Huckabee.
I could see him really I could see him like really liking what like the Proud Boys are doing.
Like I could see him everywhere.
I think that stand up snail would probably be there's a snail who's a stand up comedian.
And Larry the lion makes a very tame comment about his material and the snail goes, you're gay.
And I was like, whoa, yeah, jaw dropping.
So many of these jokes are so upsetting, even for the times.
It's like, whoa, that's not OK.
Come on.
Really, Steven, with the sex jokes in the in the pretty early, I still was surprised when in a pretty quick succession, they said crap, slutty and bitch.
Yeah, yeah, this show is to first of all, obviously, it's it's problematic, but also just the language is maybe too much for our sensibilities.
We had the same thing you did, Scott, were like I knew it was a prime time TV show, but we were really like, oh my God.
Yeah, this is not this is another level from like Shrek, like, oh, he farts or like, oh, there's a matrix joke like we were just like, ah, I also don't think like we did prime time shows in 2004 say bitch a lot.
I know it's like question.
Yeah, I don't think so.
So like maybe whatever aired at nine thirty, like one network would have like one one network would have one show a year where it's like, well, this one's a little little crass.
This show should have been like on Cinemax.
This is like one of the dirtiest shows I've ever seen.
Yeah.
I mean, I guess all the animals are nude, but like other than like graphic sex, I wouldn't be surprised.
I mean, I all bets are off with what they're going to say on these next few episodes.
There's a they use the word whore like because the well the character now who he realizes is who we will be deeming Montecore the portrayal of the tiger did the mauling is voiced by John O'Hurley.
He he says I'm a whore in the way of like wanting the spotlight like he can't resist the spotlight.
He just loves attention leads an attention whore.
But then that leads to him saying like, yeah, and you wouldn't slap a whore, would you?
It's really I try to be, you know, I try to not have steam coming out of my ears on stuff on this show if I can.
But I think I think I am offended by Father of the Bride.
You know what? You know what joke offended me?
I know we're jumping around here now.
Yeah, we don't have to one by one.
It was a cover all through when when the Tigers are inside the house and they kind of let themselves in a Blake, a Montecore and his wife and then Larry and Kate.
And then they say like, I forget who says it, but somebody goes like, oh, what a nice surprise.
And Larry goes, yeah, like when the gas wears off and the dentist is buckling his pants.
Oh, oh, I miss that one.
Oh, no, I rewound it because I went, what?
Geez.
And I guess the joke is like, that's bad because they don't want to see the Tigers.
But I'll be honest with you, the company doesn't always land perfectly on Father of the Pride.
I mean, let's not even look.
Maybe there were rumors at the top, but see the whole second episode has a major plotline about a CGI Matt Lauer, who is called non threat.
I mean, there's a there's a great now you can pull it out of its context quote from either Siegfried or Roy.
Or is it now because they kind of hate him through it.
I'm not sure who says it, but there is the phrase I have had it up to here with you besmirching the good name of Matt Lauer.
I.
They they couldn't have known they couldn't have known what was happening.
They yeah, I don't think it was rumored then I know who's who's to know.
I mean, honestly, they probably all the top people already knew, but they just weren't saying anything.
That's usually what happens with all this stuff.
But this is typically I mean, this is a real product of like NBC, like cross promoting itself, which was really bad in the arts.
Like, oh, cool. Look, everyone, Matt Lauer's on this.
The next episode had a lot of what I believe the term is integrated marketing where you have products in the shows because that was just like a 20 minute long 7-eleven ad.
Yes. So OK, so let's let's talk a little bit about how they portray Siegfried and Roy.
They're sort of like side characters in a way, like kind of goofy comic relief side characters that do like they they live like by the animals because the animals are like kind of in their backyard.
But they're sort of just like cartoon character versions of Siegfried and Roy and they go on like little wacky jaunts, especially when they go to 7-eleven because there's one of them is thirsty, I believe.
I was confused why they were there.
I think I was watching a commercial and it's like, are you thirsty?
He's like, I told you I am.
And it's like that's that's the oh, that's the impetus for them going to 7-eleven and then ultimately working a shift there.
Yeah.
Which I'll say, like, I don't hate the premise of Siegfried and Roy working at a 7-eleven.
I also will say I don't actually hate the premise of this show.
It's kind of a funny idea.
I will give it to Jeffrey Katzenberg.
It's not a bad idea for a show that I'll be positive there.
Have we said to Jeffrey Katzenberg gets the created by credit?
Yes, he does.
It's really jarring when that comes up.
The created by created by Jeffrey Katzenberg.
You just don't you picture the creator being someone who would actually be able to write a joke or something.
Yeah, that would help.
I think the I should say the behind the scenes stuff that I know that then the the next credit is developed by and I think this is the guy who was actually doing the nuts and bolts of it.
A guy named Jonathan Groff, who was the head writer of Late Night with Conan O'Brien from ninety five to two thousand and extremely well regarded in that time and what he did there and what he's done elsewhere since.
I like all I've ever heard is that this Jonathan Groff is great.
And this show is a real proof that when you're just handed an idea by Jeffrey Katzenberg that even some of the funniest writers could not working their hardest and who were their brains at full capacity still cannot fully polish it dirt.
I would I would love to know like the full Tom Shales book about the making of this should come up like somebody should do an oral history of this because you know the notes were just like I don't want to use the word it's overused but the notes were epic.
Well, here's here's one of the one other bit of buying the scenes knowledge as I said I've been I've been texting my my friends not Jonathan Groff but I just said Tommy Blotcher this writer a very funny writer ended up like was pulled in he made me work to like here and there consulted on the show a little bit like as it was pretty deep in production.
I think it was like we were you know that point where you're limited we've already animated so much we spent so much money.
There's only so much we can do but just can you watch what we've done so far and see what you think and he before I these episodes even started I texted him about it and he said well I remember them showing me a bunch and the only thing I liked at all was Siegfried and Roy.
These guys are kind of funny and there was some scene where they were in a 7-Eleven or something and I was like that's okay you just make the show way more about them like I know they're the scene stealers or just push Siegfried and Roy there's so much more interesting than these lions and them being these
way 20 euro guys in a you know mundane place like a 7-Eleven that's all right maybe do more like that and they were like yeah you know I think so I think we will do more like that so the show from then on became more Siegfried and Roy focused and then Roy and I was like I'm going to do more like that.
So they were like in the process of more Roy the way that people have spoken this needs more Roy and then insane.
Yeah well Siegfried and Roy do not do their own voices.
No.
But we're in voices.
Yeah.
I think that's what they were doing.
Well Siegfried and Roy do not do their own voices.
No.
But we're involved in the show.
Right.
And I you know you got to give it you got to give it up to them they're they're getting goofed on a light like lightly goofed on and they were obviously game for that.
Yeah.
I too will to be willing to be.
They don't seem to have noted it to death in terms of like we can't look stupid and they're a little fun but also kind of exhausting.
I don't like the voices are not my favorite.
I don't know if they're the highlights.
I'm still not they can't save it you know.
Well look I agree with you.
I was just trying to be positive and say that I like them OK.
And if we're looking for if we're looking for the highlights you know what here do one of the I didn't know this existed before this episode and I think I watched 7-Eleven first when there's a scene where one of them like retrofits the Coke or Pepsi machine to play music and shoot
lasers and fog and there's a song that plays and I'm sure Scott has Scott knew this song before and I certainly did I may have heard it but I had to look it up and went oh yeah OK.
And it is of course the theme Siegfried and Roy's like theme song in real life essentially in their Las Vegas show and it's called is it called Siegfried and Roy.
No the song is called Mind is the Magic.
Oh right right Mind is the Magic and it is of course by Michael Jackson.
Yeah.
They use it.
This is a song that plays like three times every episode that they use every episode every time they walk into a room like yes.
Yes.
The logic of the Siegfried and Roy characters really starts with like Looney Tunes kind of logic but then just becomes like it's like bad it's like early 2000 like webcomic stuff where people are like talking about video games and that the in the last panel someone's got like a sword like it's just like look folks it's it's funny because it's random you see.
A little bit.
Yeah.
I heard some story.
This this might be really super game of telephone but I feel like I heard somewhere that he Michael Jackson was obsessed with Siegfried and Roy wrote them a song just like out of the you know nobody asked him to is just like here I made you a theme song which they used and then he like you know brought it to them and like oh thank you so much and then he you know came to the show again and again and again and was at the show so much that Siegfried and Roy
were kind of like maybe if we get Michael out of here he's he's hanging around a lot.
They were like trying to get away from him.
Like this guy's a friggin weirdo.
As they're like surrounded by tigers and sparkles.
This weirdo is ruining our vibe.
I can't concentrate he's in the front row.
He's staring at me and it creeps me the fuck out.
He dresses like a freak.
Correct me if I'm wrong to Siegfried and Roy by like 2002 or so.
Still very successful I'm assuming doing a Vegas residency but we're not like on TV every month anymore right like.
No.
Were they ever on TV every month.
Or like at least every few like a Copperfield Lance Burton and Siegfried and Roy were like the TV magicians right.
I really I don't remember watching Siegfried and Roy specials on TV but I do think they had they had to have a couple right.
I'm not sure.
And when you said Lance Burton you're talking about the star of Billy Toppett.
Billy Toppett yeah.
Our next torture.
Your next self inflicted torture.
I'm looking by the way at if you Google image Michael Jackson mind is the magic you'll end up on a photo of Siegfried and Roy helping Michael Jackson feed a baby tiger with a bottle.
Geez.
I don't think I've seen that.
I don't need to look at it.
I don't need to see that.
You can you can imagine it.
No I don't know.
It's even the fact that that Katzenberg wanted to do a show about this all of a sudden it is such a like rich person idea like you know I was hanging out with Siegfried and Roy and like no one did something no one was doing or thinking about in 2002.
Right.
You know what I think we should make a show about David Geffen's anthropomorphic boat.
You're like oh yeah okay that's everyone can relate to a expensive boat.
If we're worried about the Kevin Spacey episode getting us killed David Geffen episode will.
Oh my gosh.
Surely be the final podcast.
Yeah we're not doing that.
I love David Geffen.
He's great guy David Geffen has given us a lot of great music over the years.
He's the G and Dreamworks SKG.
Yes.
God bless you David.
But let's get back to the K a little bit.
Yeah yeah yeah.
I.
What have we what have we missed in this.
This is a cat.
I feel catnip.
Yeah.
When they realize.
When they.
She.
Yeah there's a cat has a drug problem and it's a little green baggy and you're like oh what's it going to be and when they say catnip I moaned really loud.
That was still probably the best of the four episodes I would say.
Maybe we'll add a seven eleven runner.
The seven eleven runner.
The seven eleven runner is the best thing so far.
So that episode is the best.
And it was nice to be reminded of products that we like like seeing the perfect big gulp logo and like the Sony just like seeing the just you know I get used to on a show like The Simpsons to seeing you know some funny drugs.
Or some funny joke or one of my favorite logos should be and I get confused.
Where are we.
Yeah.
I see Mountain Dew so featured so well.
It's very relaxing.
There was the one gag where they were just showing an old talk show bit about fondue.
That was all right.
That was kind of funny weird non sequitur.
Who was in that who was in the clip again.
Was it.
Oh God I forget who that was.
Barbara Streisand in that clip or no.
No Barbara Walters.
Thank you.
Barbara Streisand is in the other episode.
Barbara Streisand who what other real people.
Lauer's in it does his voice.
Streisand's not Streisand obviously.
Dick Traney is not Dick Traney.
The chainsaw.
They call him the chainsaw.
Yeah.
James Brolin is in right because Mary DeBarbara Streisand.
That's James Brolin.
Am I wrong.
Oh right.
Yeah.
He's in there.
He gets like a little bit of something to do but not much.
Yeah.
They're not them.
They're not playing themselves.
No.
They're being they're being parodied I guess.
They're in an episode called and the revolution continues that in which Danny Devito plays
Emerson an activist lobster who is fighting for different kinds of animal rights.
I mean really it's just kind of general you know like not letting you know the the the
the upper class oppress us and it's it's kind of like an animal unionized.
Plot and John Goodman's reaction throughout is like would you shut up get a hobby.
This is true.
I mean look they're trying to pad like we could be in unions.
We know we know what maybe the opinion is of the higher ups trying to make of course
the very relatable everyman hero Larry show his distrust for these type of hits.
Show his distrust for these type of hippies who want to unionize and want to give more
power to labor you know.
Yeah.
Well when you're dealing with a movie or a TV show you know there's union rules about
that.
But when it's a quibi you know who's to say.
Yes.
All bets are off.
I mean who's to say we need to work with unions in any regard.
And they have a fair argument there.
Mm hmm.
Yes.
I was going to tell a story about a friend of mine who was going to be working on a quibi
and then this whole thing happened and the writers guild or excuse me the editors guild
wouldn't cover health insurance or anything because it was not technically the contract
for a regular TV show.
It was the contract for a quibi show.
So he didn't get any of the benefits that he would have gotten because of quibi anyway.
Cool.
That's a cool thing.
And also this is coming from the brain trust that made the show Father of the Pride.
So it's all cool.
Also who said part of your world should be cut from Little Mermaid.
So there is a lot of good stuff.
My good stuff happening here.
You know he gave us a show with gay rabbits.
It sounds like the voice of Bender from Futurama.
I think.
Yeah.
He does a very like Lamont and I or what like a guy.
Life partner joke.
There's a this had no aquatic access joke like a like a wheelchair ramp kind of very
strange very like oh OK that's not good.
That's not good.
Probably wasn't cool back then let alone now.
Different time 2004.
Six.
I mean it is it is 16 years ago years ago but it's not I mean yeah lifetime ago.
Yeah I'm watching.
Hello.
No God.
I was gonna say I just clicked on a YouTube thing called Siegfried and Roy the Magic Returns
and within a minute Steve Wynn is doing an interview of another guy who we probably shouldn't
do an episode about but I love to do an episode about Steve Wynn.
I mean his commercials as a big fan.
Yeah.
His feud with Joe Francis.
The girl's gone wild man.
Oh yeah.
Talk about that too.
There's a lot of rights.
There's a lot of right material.
The war for the shore.
The war between Trump and win for Atlantic City which Trump won and then practically
torpedoed the city a few years later when all his casinos went under.
Don't worry.
Steve Wynn still a big fan of big friend and supporter of the president.
Yeah.
Still still on the Republican National Committee.
So yeah Steve Wynn episode.
We'll figure it out.
Yes absolutely.
I should mention that around episode four you know if you if you can if you're surprised
that Emerson the activist lobster did not quite hold my attention that episode four was around
where I started like Googling other stuff and not not focusing on the plot so much.
And that's where I discovered that Father of the Pride was honored with the Ursa Major
Award in 2004.
Do you guys know what the Ursa Major Award is.
I don't.
That's it.
Tell us.
That's an award that's given out at furry conventions.
Oh good.
I discovered this on there's a pretty dense Father of the Pride area on wiki fur dot com.
And so it won best anthropomorphic dramatic series in 2004.
So you know they award important works that involve I guess you know furry characters who walk on their hind legs.
So you know throughout this I might kind of be just checking in on what else you know what else the Ursa's felt it fit to honor.
Actually 2004 a big year for Katzenberg because at Anthrocon 2005 best series was Father of the Pride and best motion picture Shrek 2.
Wow.
Anthro, Anthrocon?
Anthrocon 2005.
There's they it's always called the Ursa Awards but it's always a different event.
It used to be Con Fur-ence but then since then it's been Morphicon.
It's been All Fur Fun.
It's what the Fur 2016.
So you know I'll be checking out the rest of the history of the Ursa's throughout this.
I'll say this we've championed a lot of anthropomorphic animal characters on this show and I would like an official invitation to come to this convention.
I think we should be there.
I think we should be hosting panels.
I don't need any like sexual element to the anthropomorphic animals or the love for them.
But I do believe we should have a presence there at Anthrocon or whatever it's going to be called.
Sure.
Sure I respect and fear the fairy community so I'd happily make an appearance.
Their taste lines up with us a lot because you know they gave best anthropomorphic motion picture 2009 to Avatar.
Yes.
In 2017 best motion picture Guardians of the Galaxy volume 2.
Alright.
Yeah.
Hey they're they're honoring me at a convention.
What kind of convention?
Oh I heard about this convention.
But you know what Rockets a freak.
I'll be here with bells on.
I don't care if it's a real rabbit or a person dressed up as a rabbit.
Don't make no difference to me.
I should pick a safe word huh.
How about my hands don't scan.
That's his password like that's his password for all of his stuff on his computer like he just uses that for everything in his life.
Hey give Rockets some credit.
Sometimes it's my hands don't scan one two three.
And sometimes it's gantry lift.
Oftentimes it's just gantry lift.
Gantry lift but the A is a four.
So that's how they that's how I keep them out.
That's how my password goes from weak to mildly weak.
And not strong.
Rockets always gets that bar to orange.
I don't keep it at red.
You think I'm stupid.
I'm smart.
All right we're talking too much.
We have to watch this show.
Let's let's keep going.
Okay so yes you Jason in this episode you're the you're the father keeper.
Tell us where we're going to go next.
Well okay so block to donkey.
So we're starting on a high note.
One of our friends make an appearance.
Second episode possession.
Third episode I believe it's called one man's meat is another man's girlfriend.
I don't care for that.
And then an episode called rehabilitation.
So and to put these all in perspective.
So donkey aired September 21st of 2004 possession aired October 12th.
One man's meat aired October 26th and then a long break rehabilitation aired December 21st.
So OK.
So the first three aired before the reelection of George W. Bush.
And then there was we knew the last ones all aired in firmly in a Bush Bush second term.
Yeah and then the air dates get even funnier in the final block of the day.
Great.
Good tease.
All right.
Meet you back here in a couple of grueling hours.
Fantastic.
Goodbye.
OK bye.
And we're back.
Unfortunately we're all here.
We left into these let's get into these hate crimes.
We left in the last one and then it is like all right back to it right back down on the couch immediately.
It's a bunch of lions all ogling a young lion's butt just instantly straight back to gross and it only got worse from there.
Yeah I am.
I think we were saying a little I am so sleepy right now.
I've gotten so tired in the last hour and a half.
And also I keep getting taunted by YouTube with much better videos.
And when I say like because I'm watching I've watched these of this last four on my phone.
So I'm getting all these suggestions under the video I'm watching like listen to the 22 minute soundtrack for a Tokyo Disney show called Minnie's Tropical Splash from 2016.
And I'm like I would like to listen to this 22 minutes of Minnie's Tropical Splash but I can't.
I'd rather listen to that 45 minute Bob Dylan song than watch more of the show.
Oh man I haven't listened to that yet.
I got to listen.
I will not but if somehow I was given a choice but I don't think I do have that choice.
Unless you'll let me so unless I can work out a deal with you guys that instead of watching two of these I can listen to the Bob Dylan song and report on it.
The JFK one?
Yeah.
Can we make deals?
Can we make deals to not have to do one episode but we have to do a different homework assignment?
You know this is the kind of eye jinks that like Larry and his friend Snack get up to.
Wait wait.
All right here's here's what we should do.
We each don't have to watch one.
We each can say no to one of the next five episodes.
But we have to be assigned a different video by another by one of us to watch in its place.
Oh so then is it still a choice or do you have to watch the other thing?
Let's you know what here in the interest of time I will say you can pick one episode you don't have to watch but you do have to listen to the Bob Dylan song and report it back to us.
All right I will I will take that deal and is that on the episode of my choosing?
Can I do it based on the episode titles?
Yes.
Do it on the episode titles and then we'll go around and each one of us won't have to watch one.
But you'll you get the first pick for which episode you don't have to watch of the next five in the block.
Oh wow okay okay thanks.
But so we need to think of punishments for for each other then?
For me and Jason.
Now Jason and I have to have so unless Jason wants to do all five.
Well yeah I'm going to say I have to see this through.
I have to I have to see them all but Mike I'll give you the option if there's some other thing you would rather do.
I absolutely would rather do anything else.
Please give me an assignment.
But it's got to be punishing to some extent because I don't want to hear that Bob Dylan song.
It has to be something you don't want to do.
So we got to think we got to think on that.
Maybe if we all talk and if Jason I kind of trade focus on that.
So we like because if the fouls are the faster we get through this discussion the faster we're done with all of it.
Well let's have the discussion if something pops into your head while we're talking you can throw it at me at the end.
Okay.
Gotcha.
Okay okay.
So let me start with you know I'll start with the this just an observation.
So this run of episodes it's a lot of sitcom go tos.
Character has to lose weight.
Character is laid up with an injury but he's actually faking.
Bring your parents to school day.
We never do anything fun anymore dear.
And they really transform those tropes into a slog just a really paid full like upsetting experience.
This makes the first four we watch look like masterpiece.
These were especially bad.
I will say I think donkey is good.
I think donkey if we're on the sliding scale donkey is easily the best one.
Yes.
Yeah it is really nice to hear Eddie Murphy no matter what he is better than anything else.
Yeah.
I did not I don't I did not care for donkey's kind of his stunt double.
He's like campy.
So there are so many weird gay jokes in this show.
Like it seems like when they couldn't think of something they would just make a just out of nowhere gay joke.
It is every single episode with such like veracity.
I can't believe this might be the most homophobic series in history.
By the way when I say I think the donkey episode is the best I am not sanctioning each joke in the episode.
No I know I know I didn't think you were.
Yeah.
So you're saying you didn't like when somebody mentioned Justin Timberlake and then Larry the funny lion said is he into dudes.
What's going on there.
I did not like that joke.
I will say that I was not I was not hooting and hollering.
John Goodman was had to say this while he is work that day was to wonder if Timberlake is gay.
Yes.
The worst thing that anyone could be.
What is that I don't understand.
And it's the next episode where the grandpa thinks the son is gay.
Yes.
Yeah.
It's all of them to some extent.
Even the daughter makes a joke under her breath about like oh that's a little gay.
Like what is going on.
Is every character that's making these jokes.
And I haven't watched the episode of The Simpsons where Homer thinks Bart is gay.
But in my mind that episode is more about a close minded person being opened up to like his own prejudices a little bit.
Am I wrong.
That episode is like years prior to this too.
Yes.
Years and years before and Homer learns a lesson and gets closer to his son.
Like yeah there are some redeeming elements of that.
Sure.
But that's not what that's not what's happening.
This is the show is so it's so crazy that there's there's slurs that I have I've never heard before.
It's like taught me gay slurs that I've never heard in any I know what you're talking about.
Yeah I don't know that I want to say it even.
But how in the world how can a CGI something that we until right now thought like they try to do kind of an ill-fated trick as a show.
Let's go laugh at who knew it would illuminate slurs.
I didn't know it's yeah.
I and it's like I'm trying to think like once in a while on like stuff from the 90s or like I go oh shoot that's that didn't age well.
This is every couple of minutes.
This is every minute every two minutes.
It's it's unbelievable and I don't I really am now that we've watched so much of this it's like why didn't you guys just make something that like totally was like Shrek.
Like I don't there's no reason there's no audience more for this.
Why would you be less like Shrek the biggest hit the most surprise like across the board said in years like we're not really going to do the whole Shrek thing.
Why not?
You should then families are watching like imagine people tuning in and like like a family and around this like a like a young boy who's like probably just discovered that he's gay.
He goes and watches this show and like oh God and he like stays closeted for longer because the show was mean to him.
This is the least for families thing ever.
It is it is why I mean it is wild.
I really I didn't expect this element.
This is the most surprising element of the show to me.
It is truly infuriating and even if we when we aren't dealing in gay slurs which every episode does then there'll be some other thing like I wrote to this some phrase about I wouldn't go to that Southern Fried Hags bitchfest.
Why do they say so much?
So much.
So bad.
It is wild.
You could really teach this like they need they need to have like if they ever show this anywhere ever again they need to have like one of those messages before it of like you know it was a different time.
And this was acceptable humor.
And really though of course like it really wasn't acceptable humor for the time.
No.
But you know.
There really should be warnings.
This season was like when Queer Eye for the Straight Guy blew up.
Like we've got like a major influx of gay culture that's very popular.
Why on just up the up the dial on NBC?
Why are they so mad?
Look there's a lot of confusing things happening in this show.
The donkey episode features the Siegfried and Roy storyline where I have to give them credit this is kind of a clever idea that Siegfried and Roy are protesting a small business because it is not a good corporate.
That's kind of funny.
And then Siegfried fucks grandma to like get her to change her ways.
Like that's kind of weird.
I'm kind of that's funny.
The premise is Siegfried and Roy are upset because some sort of small business has moved on the Las Vegas strip and they don't like that.
They like everything being like corporately owned.
So it's very it is I was like oh this is a very funny idea.
I like this idea.
And then they just quickly get out of it by having Siegfried have sex with an old woman who owns the bed and breakfast and it turns into like a horrible casino type of place.
Yeah there's also in this episode a joke about oh Larry yells at a pig the pig agent or manager that you people killed mama Cass.
That was very confusing.
And then they step back the joke in a meta way for too long.
Yeah.
It's yeah I'm getting ahead of my there's so much happening in the donkey episode.
Yeah we can we can focus on on donkey for a little bit.
You know maybe to brighten the mood I can say one thing that I liked which is that it's about the Larry's son who I don't know the name of just by watching eight episodes of the show.
The hunter I think it's hunter.
It's hunter.
Hunter.
So Hunter is at there's like a parents day like a show and tell where your parents talk about their job and the the John O'Hurley eventual mauler tiger cheats essentially but he doesn't really talk about himself.
He brings in his pal the MGM lion and the MGM lion puts the crest around his head and does the roar like the exact roar from the opening of all the MGM movies and and the kids go nuts and he does it again.
I liked that.
I liked that because maybe partially because it reminded me of entertainment that I enjoy more that begins with the MGM logo.
I enjoy that.
And I like that everyone calls him donkey from Shrek like everyone uses the phrases normal people use donkey from Shrek MGM lion like.
Well yeah when it happened when the when is when Kate tells Larry that donkey is in town or I think that's what happens he goes donkey from Shrek.
Yes.
Which so we should note that that though donkey from Shrek is in this episode it's one of those scenarios where he's a celebrity rather than he it's not he's not from we're assuming that he played himself in the movie and he's visiting in like a celebrity way.
He's shooting a commercial in Las Vegas.
That's correct.
Yes a car commercial.
Donkey from Shrek.
Specifically a Japanese SUV commercial and donkey says he will not get in the SUV because he's concerned because they roll over which is a very 2004 joke a lot of a lot of worry about SUV rollovers back then.
Oh I didn't even that didn't register with me oh my god.
Yeah you end up in this weird zone.
Well well first of all you know another part that I liked that made me hopeful for block the two here but and then my hopes faded but when donkeys finally revealed and all stars playing like it's a song that was wonderful.
Yes, that made me very happy.
All star plays wherever he goes.
And he has some self reflexive dialogue where he says babe but tell your tell your boy Shrek 3 is coming out in 2006.
That was good.
I like that.
Did enjoy that.
Then I less enjoyed what Jason alluded to which is that donkey refuses to it says oh so the MGM lion Larry has to compete with that like how can I impress my son's class and he lies.
And he says these friends with donkey from Shrek and so then he like how am I going to find donkey from Shrek and he does so by walking right up to him in the next scene because when donkey walks through his town.
There's no particular struggle to find donkey.
It's just a logistics issue is manager says no.
So instead he finds donkeys stunt double who has a very list be gay voice.
Wonderful.
Once again that's the great comedy of Father of the Pride.
So it's like don't talk as long as you don't talk then we'll get through this and all it'll make sense and we'll show and tell.
That was all very painful to watch but you guys happen to catch an interesting name in the credits that was the voice of donkey stunt double.
I did not.
Donkeys stunt double was voiced by Reeve Kearney.
Do you know offhand Reeve Kearney is.
He's a boy who fell from the sky.
Spider man in Spider-Man turn off the dark is the voice of the gay donkey look alike which I should mention Reeve Kearney.
We haven't talked about this Reeve Kearney has remained very relevant on Broadway because he's in Hadestown.
And do you know who else is in Hadestown.
The guy who played the Green Goblin.
Yes.
This is an extremely popular play.
It's Spider-Man and Green Goblin together again.
Well yeah they both are big stars on Broadway.
Yeah yeah usually relevant.
So anyway I guess I felt better about this horrible scene knowing there was a connection to Spider-Man turn off the dark.
When Broadway opens again in a year and a half we really got to go see Hadestown.
And then just yell do the Goblin.
Make a topical joke.
What kind of circus tragedy is this.
So anyway what are your guys thoughts on Donkey though.
About the I like seeing Donkey.
I kind of like the bit with his manager.
His manager is a pig and I kind of like the bit where Larry has to go.
He goes can you come to my kids school and Donkey is like of course go talk to my manager.
And she goes not going to happen.
And then he keeps saying yes.
And it felt like a very Larry Sanders style joke about like you can't you know you got to talk to the person in charge.
And the person that's actually the celebrity doesn't have to deal with saying no.
I kind of like that bit.
That was a well observed yeah.
There's a weird bit or there's a weird line when Larry says to the pig manager nice nipples.
Yeah that's weird.
It's not the last.
There's another episode where he brings up someone's nipples.
There's a lot of nipple talk I feel.
A lot of nipple talk.
When all the female characters have just these wide shapely hips.
It's very very unnerving.
Everything in this show.
I was just going to say like as I was watching I noticed everything in this show is somehow very smooth but angular at the same time.
And it's upsetting.
It creates an unease.
It's just nothing's very emotive but they're trying with like probably the best technology at the at Hollywood's disposal at their time.
But yeah it looks like shit 16 years later.
It's really awful.
I've tried to get through this while the kind of kind of absorbing the plots without looking at the screen very often.
Just in my periphery.
Mm hmm.
Yeah it's.
So I don't know I think I've said all I've had to say about donkey the episode donkey but.
I think we can keep moving as fast as anyone wants to.
Well let me just say I just wrote down the phrase this is upsetting and I don't remember what that was in reference to.
It could really it was under my donkey notes but it could apply to most of these episodes.
I wrote down the phrase this shows so bad I can't believe I'm not interviewing to write on it.
It's surprising it's not coming back surprising it hasn't come back yet.
For Quibi yeah.
Give it time.
Obviously I mean you know what can I say big fan of the original.
I love the you know that the old man lion whose name is Sar modi Sar modi.
I love obviously big Sar modi fan and just God bless the car.
Reiner's still here with us to voice Sar modi.
Don't have to replace him.
That is insane.
I would like that he was I believe he was 82 years old when he voiced to the show in 2004 and he is still alive.
He's 90 years.
Incredible.
That is great.
That is what you like.
Betty White.
Oh yeah.
I'm also still great great.
So that's some good news.
Yeah.
Good entertainers and good health.
You got to feel good about that even if you don't feel good at all about the show they participated in a long time ago.
Yeah.
Gotta feel good about that.
My question here real quick about the logistics or like the the reality of the show.
The characters Larry Kate and then their her dad's name is Sar modi.
Why aren't the characters all fun names like Montecore like isn't it.
Wouldn't it be better if they were all like like like like lavish named eccentric like Siegfried and Roy.
Wouldn't that make sense.
They were like exotic tigers or exotic.
So yeah and you know them being sort of like snooty stuck up or they're being a mix the one you know like there could be a real green acres thing here.
They're like you know one of them could sound like a Gabor and and then you know mixed with a more down to the salt of the earth.
John Goodman guy like one of them being a yes darling like that.
That's more fun right.
More fun.
I agree.
I mean just like white lions are not generally American I guess is what I'm saying.
I guess I guess the idea being they were probably raised here but then Carl Reiner should have an accent of some kind.
Yeah the only only old ones are all they're all like old Jewish actors.
There's like nobody's from Africa or any there the places where these lions would probably come from.
Right.
So however that is licensed to get in.
I don't like anything they're doing but again hearing Gary Marshall and Dom DeLuise I'm reminded of other things that I like that they're part of.
That's true.
I'm not saying I don't want Dom DeLuise to be involved because of course I do.
Always in anything.
From a conceptual standpoint these are these are questions I have.
Anyway.
They spent so much money on guest stars for the show.
Yeah Eddie Murphy just just that.
What a get what a cue that Eddie Murphy was doing something on primetime that night and no one ever wants to think about it again.
I wonder we got to find out how much he made.
Yeah or unless it was just he just got like swindled as part of some Shrek package deal.
Oh yeah maybe.
Part of the Shrek 3 deal maybe.
I think maybe.
I have some little nitpicks actually there are a lot of these Aaron's nitpicks because she's she's paying better attention than I am.
There's some some lion where the guy who's obviously the voice of Bender from Futurama says you can you can watch me lunch and but the scene is at night.
So they should have they should have noted that one better.
And then also there's like I lit up at this one part because there's a bottle of wine that you know that made me think about wine and that is it you know what right now it's three 30s it too early to drink some wine to get through the rest of this.
I don't I don't think so necessarily.
I don't think so.
Quarantine there are no rules in quarantine.
Yeah I can have a big bowl of wine for breakfast.
That's right.
But there's a bottle is a really clearly labeled bottle of 1997 Cabernet Sauvignon and then in the next episode the same bottle appears it's just such a like specific year and variety so you see it sticks in your head sticks in your head but that the label is you see the label and then it's read as a Shiraz is a totally different type.
So they shouldn't like I get reusing props but they change the wine name.
Yeah, I did not notice that detail. I've been noticing all the mirage logos on everything which is very funny so many so many mirage logos.
Yeah, I was everywhere which is kind of like, I'm sure they were, I'm sure it's there for the practical reason of synergy. But it's kind of funny that mirage is everything.
Yeah, I did you kind of like that. Yeah, you're watching just casino ads.
Night after night.
I also wait the you know we don't like glaze past with the use of the wine is that there's there's an episode one of these there's a lot of stuff at a bar, and all these animals are just drinking human wine.
Yes.
Yes, I don't like liquor and beer and martinis in the opening there's a beer can all the time. Yeah, it's about a bunch of alcoholic animals.
If they had done the analogous like catnip to weed thing what wouldn't there be an animal version of alcohol. You'd think.
Yeah, if they don't smoke weed because I'm amazed they didn't just do that just it's just animals getting high.
What would it do that.
2004 I was just going to say like maybe on prime time TV they couldn't do any weed jokes, they could do a bunch of homophobic joke sure but weed.
You can't say we're not television in 2004 that's pretty far yeah yeah I don't know what would what animals respond to like alcohol, the tranquilizers.
This is a big glass tranquilizer.
They did a little of that earlier, little of that.
So you can say that.
I mean, a lot of this feels like really limited imagination like limited executive imagination of like well if it's a sitcom you got to have a nuclear family.
You got to have the bar and the job and the school and it's like I don't remember is the public really that dumb or is it just you keep shoveling the same slop you know if it's just like well it's a cop show or a firefighter show or lawyer show or a family show.
There's a show about lions who perform in a fancy show covered in diamonds.
Why is it still just a house in a bar.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah why yeah why aren't they like, like a bunch of animals like hanging out on the strip.
Yes, Vegas is right there.
It's like a fence, and we know the strip the literal strip is behind the fence, and we never get to go.
There's a bunch of weird stuff they could get up to on the strip and all the weirds like what are the other animals in Vegas but like they're confined to this other world.
Yeah, like part zoo and part. And if yeah if they were like we're in the casinos and then everybody would just assume they were like imagining it because they're so drunk or so high, like everybody is like wiping their eyes like an old 40s movie drunk and like boy now I've seen it.
Oh Vegas. Boy, what happens here. Easy.
Yeah, the circ they get talked to the Cirque du Soleil maybe maybe I'm getting ahead of myself maybe we're really going to open it up in these next five episodes and they're going to get out there and mingle with like the cast of, they see Zumanity they see the cast of the Cirque du Soleil show Zumanity which is the sexy animal show, and they get confused, you know they think these are actual animals but they're people.
That's a good plot.
You know, there's a lot of horniness in this show and just a few miles up the strip. One of the horniest creatures on the strip lives, David Copperfield's pal blue 32. Oh my god can you imagine dating the daughter blue date blue dates, whatever her name is.
David Copperfield gets a shout out. He does get a shout out in this.
They refer to the good. He's not the good kind of lady killer like Billy Dee Williams or David Copperfield.
Not the term I would use to describe David Copperfield.
Allegedly allegedly parody parody.
Probably not what you should say about Billy Dee either. Just take a Google, just take a quick Google. Oh, oh no.
Oh god. Yeah, I just, you know, maybe it's a more a character we met like, I guess, you know, who's best paired with blue 32.
It seems like that there was a little like squirrel or something that didn't get along too well with the snack.
Maybe maybe she could cook up with blue.
That's good. Whatever that character's name is. Yes, I agree. Making love, Larry.
I don't. We should probably head back in for the final round.
I know we should, but not without mentioning that it's not all downhill from Eddie Murphy.
There's a there's an exciting cameo in one of these episodes from Peter Fonda.
It was Peter Fonda. I mean, that's who they refer to him. I don't know if he did his own voice.
I don't know if he did his voice. Yeah, he literally like that's the episode where they're working Larry too hard.
So he fakes an injury. And one of the working things is he has to go out and hang out with Roy and Peter Fonda.
And Peter Fonda says, where's the bong? Like, it's like, come on.
Are we still mystified by Peter Fonda in 2004?
That reminded me of the first time Peter Fonda came up on the show when he opened the Harley store at City Walk and said, are you ready to start partying?
Maybe happy to go back to that.
Peter Fonda was just making like easy rider based cameos for like decades, I guess, because that's what this is.
Like he's got Larry's got like a do-rag, an American flag do-rag on. Right? That's the same episode.
Oh, yes. That's it. Yeah, I think so. That's right.
In the previous episode, of course, One Man's Meet is Another Man's Girlfriend, a very upsetting title.
You had Arlie Emery as a fitness drill instructor rabbit. That was cute.
The famous always a drill instructor, Ermi, I think it's Arlie Ermi.
From Toy Story. If we're ready to assign the episodes, I have an idea of something of sort of equivalent length that could be Mike's alternate entertainment.
Will he suffer?
Well, I'm worried it won't be enough, but it does sound it sounds like suffering to me.
I'll say. But I guess I'm worried I'm I mean, I might have more fun listening to the Bob Dylan song, too.
There's always a chance with these alternate options. Right.
Though it is a little bit longer. You could just watch an equivalent amount, I suppose.
Inspired by Peter Fonda's appearance in this episode and the reference to the film that he's in, Yuli's Gold.
I thought that maybe you could instead of watching one of these five episodes, you could watch a 1998 interview with Peter Fonda on Charlie Rose,
where he discusses his role as a beekeeper in Yuli's Gold and his memoir, Don't Tell Dad.
All right. I accept that. I accept that as my alternative.
I mean, I look, I honestly it sounds it sounds really good compared to what you guys are what Jason's going to have to do.
So guys lived an interesting life. Probably a good day about his memoir film legend.
He was an easy rider. Did you hear motorcycles?
I'm reading the transcript, you know, they're talking about dirty Mary, crazy Larry.
And he just won a film critic circle award.
1998 was a big time for Peter. So I'm excited to send you back to that era with him.
That's great, Jason. Let's let's.
The last thing I wanted to say was that there was a bunch of like weird jokes about like people cutting themselves and like like weird upsetting like suicide jokes that weren't funny.
Yeah, there was a really like there was an odd Kirstie Alley fat joke that then the characters like, why did I make that joke?
That's a Siegfried and Roy drinking in the lobby of the Betty Ford Center was one of the grimest psych acts I've ever seen.
Yeah, yeah, I don't. All right. That's unless you got something else. Let's do the next episode.
So it's Jason. All right. So this is where the episodes start to get even stranger.
So let me read you off the OK. So the first three, I'm going to tell you the titles together.
And there's a reason I'm doing that. So our money moves in is one.
Then there's another episode called Road Trip.
And then there's another episode called the Thanksgiving episode.
Now, you're probably going, oh, I know when that one aired, but you're wrong.
All three of those aired the same night, December 28th, 2004.
You know, New Year's, the week between Christmas and New Year's, when new shows don't typically air.
Well, they did the burn off. They did the one night burn off.
Then there's an episode called Stage Fright, which on the DVD they refer to as an alternate pilot.
Stage Fright is the last episode to air in the United States that aired May 27th, 2005.
And then the very last full episode, the Siegfried and Roy fantasy experience movie never aired in America.
It only aired in the UK and it's on the DVD. It is on that YouTube playlist.
So I'll leave it to you guys if you would like to choose from those titles what you want to skip.
Do you have a knee jerk?
I would like to skip Sarmati Moves In because Sarmati is so unpleasant.
I'm really, I'm really sick of Sarmati.
I, yeah, that's a really good pick.
So I think I'm going to need the break the most later on.
So I'm going to I'm going to cancel that stage fright and come back for the Siegfried and Roy fantasy experience movie.
Though I don't think I'm going to like any of these episodes.
I do know in advance that the Thanksgiving episode and Siegfried and Roy fantasy experience both have writing credits from David Goodman,
the head of the WGA who has led a fight that I believe in leaving the agents and the ATA.
And he's very good and funny in these meetings and just seems like a good guy.
So in support and solidarity with David Goodman, I'm going to watch both of his episodes and I will skip stage fright.
OK.
All right. So, Mike, I will email you Charlie Rose's 1998 interview with Peter Fonda, which you'll get to first.
It would seem I will listen to this inscrutable Bob Dylan song.
And we I don't think the reports have to be very lengthy, but, you know, we should say make sure we should show our work, make sure that we did actually check these things out.
All right. I'm also going to eat something so I don't pass out.
Yes, sure. OK, so we'll be looser on the return time.
But for you, the audience, it'll happen in just a moment. Bye bye. Bye.
Well, welcome back, everyone.
We've completed the gauntlet, finished the series, and I'm going to go ahead and say, much to my surprise,
that last block of episodes were the most pleasant of them all.
Am I crazy? Am I wrong? You guys seem surprised that I am surprised.
Yeah, I look, I missed one of them.
The last one I did like more, but, you know, it's still very relatively speaking.
I'll say this. There's two. There's two jokes. One is in the one with David Spade is the Fox.
First of all, I kind of thought Spade was OK as the Fox. I kind of like that character.
He he says he's going to like take care of something and he's going to distract a bus and he like stops in front of the bus as if it's like he's going to make it stop.
And then the bus rolls over him. Pretty good gag. That was a good gag.
Yeah. And there's a joke later. I forget which episode.
Oh, I think it's the it's the Kelsey Grammer one where one of Siegfried Roy tells Kelsey Grammer that as a child,
his dad made him watch a son of music and root against the von Trapps.
Yeah, that's a good joke. I like that joke. That's a solid joke.
Other than that, I don't know. It wasn't that much different than the rest.
I thought these were less hateful overall.
The Thanksgiving one. Well, OK, the Thanksgiving one did not land. Yeah, the Thanksgiving. OK.
But the Thanksgiving one is maybe the worst one of all of them.
That is probably the it it.
But don't you think it was trying something?
I guess it was trying something.
It really ate shit every single place it tried to go.
That episode was so unpleasant. Extreme. That's that's the word.
Yeah. Yeah. You watched that one, right? That was that was still on my list.
Yeah, it was sort of a the what's your name?
I already don't remember her name.
Karen Kate Kate Kate.
Cheryl Hines is running for president of the PTA
and finds that there's like a block of voters that she has to please or she offends them or something.
And that's the that's turkeys.
She says all turkeys look alike. That's OK.
Yeah. But it was so confusing.
The metaphor got so confusing at some point.
Like it didn't really mean did you.
Jason, did you get high in between the last time you recorded it now?
OK, I'm drinking a beer and and and I took a few puffs out of a.
Yeah, we figured it out.
What is the missing element that made it more?
No, I thought something Thanksgiving was the worst.
But like I thought stage fright, the one was Kelsey Grammer.
So that's what the DVD says.
That is the reworked pilot.
So I think that was supposed to.
I think the intent of the show was that that would be the first one.
And then the second one would be Sam Roddy moves in, which somewhere along these episodes,
I think they started pronouncing his name differently.
Am I crazy?
You you could have said anything and I would have gone, oh, yeah, OK.
And I've said his name like three or four times already.
I don't remember it.
Or Moody's Sarmo.
I think storyline wise, it would make more sense that he retires and then he moves in with the family.
It was just happening without explanation.
Like suddenly, like we've seen him there before.
Right. I think those were meant to be the first two episodes and then shit aired.
Fucked up, you know.
That's a good description of the entire series.
Shit.
I fucked up, yo.
But the Siegfried and Roy fantasy experience movie had a I like the gag where they there's one bulb out in their giant sign
and they skydive out of a helicopter to fix it.
Oh, yeah, that's all right.
I like the commercial for the competing magician.
I like that, too.
That was good.
That was finally something good.
And I like that they're performing at a casino called the Fandango.
I think that's a really good approximation of a casino name.
I agree with that.
But then also, I don't tell me if I'm wrong.
I don't think there is a single one that didn't fulfill the the the father of the pride base of having a homophobic joke.
I think every single one had had one at least, if not way more.
I think that's correct.
I think one or two of these later ones did not.
Maybe I all I know is that I did like this one more for the most part.
And then right at the end, they got like, oh, they just checked them off.
There's the gay one. There's a trans joke.
And then that one is about, yeah, Kate is in like a women's group and Larry is wondering what's going on, what crazy ideas are they putting in her head?
And right at the end of the episode, he charges into the women's group meeting and says, give me back my wife, you crazy lesbians.
Yeah, yeah, that's true.
OK, yeah, that wasn't great.
But I like seeing that same bottle of wine again.
It was nice to see it for a third time.
And I love that this episode was a good chance to reference Bill friggin Murray.
All we was a big Larry's plan with all of his buddies, like his orangutan friend and everybody else is there.
All the guys are going to get together and watch all their favorite Bill Murray movies.
Let me tell you, if Bill Murray is referenced, that's all I need.
No more jokes needed. No more content needed.
Say the name and I'm satisfied.
You love it and you go deep like you're a broken flowers guy, you know.
Well, he doesn't need broken flowers.
He just needs a picture of that icon of partying and chilling out.
That's all you need.
You just need like a reddish t-shirt.
Give me meatballs. Give me.
Let me see that floppy caddy shag hat.
That's that's all I need, man.
He's the king of the bros.
Dolly Llama.
He carried for him.
Yeah, the dolly Murray in Murray, we trust.
I think so.
I would say that's right.
I'm a Murray bro.
Murray or bust.
I call him like like my boy Danny A.
I like to call him the Murray Kane.
That's what Danny Danny Ackroyd calls him.
Oh, boy.
Murray Kane.
And that's what his friends call him is Danny Ackroyd.
So you feel like like a friend there.
They're all their friends.
The one where OK, the episode now we're getting all over the place here.
Can you have a work where Larry's wife, Kate goes and goes to a women's group is like the most sitcommy.
Homer Simpson ripoff episode that I just so I just oh, I checked out.
You must have been having a fun party over there, Jason.
I don't know what you must have been like really comparably.
I just thought the second block of episodes was so grim that there was the slightly more competence.
I guess I was just so drained after the second block, the slight appearance of competence in a couple of these episodes.
Perked me up.
Well, look, dear listeners, when you watch all 13 of these episodes, you'll have to let us know.
Did you find the last five more competent or is CGI, CGI, Kelsey Grammer and cat cat.
But didn't look very good.
No, but it but was Kelsey Grammer.
That was his voice.
Unlike CGI Martin Scorsese, which was clearly not.
I just feel like you got CGI, Kelsey Grammer.
They don't really do much with him.
That's true.
I can't believe of all the ones that I sat out that the one that I arbitrarily said out that was the one with a creepy CGI, Kelsey Grammer.
Yeah, I really fucked up.
That's a tragedy.
Although it's not because the episode was not good.
OK, which one did you sit out?
What's his name?
The old man on the stage.
The state's are moody moves in.
Moody moves in.
I have the least I I left my body in now.
I don't I have no idea.
I really don't know.
I it's early.
Somebody in it says, I know you won't come here without my money.
Beotch.
I know that about it.
They explain how they get the rug.
They explain how they get the zebra rug.
Is that in other episodes?
And then this does appear in other episodes.
That's right.
So there's a rug.
There's a rug the entire time.
But then oddly nine episodes in, you find out why they have a rug because they aired in a bizarre order.
Yes, I believe so.
This episode also features snack, kind of gets tossed or is running away.
He he runs over three women lying on rafts in a pool and each woman's bosom plays the NBC jiggle.
Ding ding ding ding ding ding.
Fuck that shit.
Garbage all garbage.
I don't want to jump.
I'm all over the place.
I'm now I'm just mad now looking through my notes in my picture.
I took pictures of the show.
They're like the joke of like the turkeys are coming over and then the old man is really racist against turkeys and then they're about to feed him corn and he's like, no, that's a stereotype.
But then the turkeys like corn afterward.
They're like, I guess they like corn.
And then the old man accuses the turkeys of stealing his watch.
Excuse me.
Saramati accuses the turkeys of stealing his watch.
But then they did steal his watch at the end.
Like the whole episode, that's the sucks so bad.
It's so bad.
Principal appears to be Tress McNeil.
Is that right?
I believe that's right.
Yes. Sounds like Lindsay Nagle.
Yeah.
There's a James Carville turtle.
Huh?
That was I didn't catch that metaphor at all.
I thought that was like they were doing a James Carville voice.
I don't know.
That episode was such a mess.
It was the turkeys are kind of stand ins for for Jewish people at times,
but also Mexicans, but also Native Americans.
Like it's all it's it changes and bends what exactly they're a metaphor for.
And then are they good or are they bad?
And they're sort of all at once.
And they accused the turkish appearance.
So they go like, yeah, you know, the white man took the land from the Native American,
but the Native American took it from the turkey.
You're like, oh, my God, what is what are we doing here?
I'm worried.
What is the more that we talk about this episode?
It's someone that will say a quote that's just from the show.
And then someone will just snip only that.
And then we'll get we'll get Shane Gillis.
Then where it'll be a wrongful Shane Gillis thing.
Well, right. I mean, his wasn't taken out of context.
It was. No, I'm saying it's an incorrect being incorrect.
Shane Gillis thing, which is was correct.
When like you'll have to like distance yourself from me online.
Yeah, we're all going to have to do it because we watched the show.
They're going to stitch together a bunch of stuff.
Somebody else stitched together me saying it was wrong to get rid of Shane Gillis.
I just said it. I just volunteered it.
What am I doing? The longer I talk, the more we're all providing cancelable quotes.
I mean, the weirdest part is that Mike substitute watch
the fine print on Mike watching that interview is that he has to do a long segment
about how Charlie Rose was robbed and he's actually innocent.
Right, Michael? You agree to that?
No, I did not agree to that. That was not part of the deal.
You said I am the head of the Charlie Rose Innocence Project.
I have not. I know. I disavow any knowledge of the Charlie Rose Innocence Project.
They're going to just say somebody's going to clip out this and just I avow the Charlie Rose Innocence Project.
Oh, I do not avow. I do not avow. We're screwed.
I'm about to go ahead.
I was going to how about Larry on the no his wife's and his anniversary when he loves to put on a Jimi Hendrix wig
and play Jimi Hendrix music. That's the thing he does.
He wears a wig that looks like Jimi Hendrix's hair.
And they cleared the songs that like clear the pain for Jimi Hendrix music.
They cleared the songs.
But what about the Ghostbusters sound alike song that plays over the credits?
That's not that one. No, they didn't do that.
They didn't clear that with the logins.
What with all these Jimi Hendrix song clearances, you know, you don't wonder how the math sorted out to where each episode cost two point five million dollars.
Hmm. I wonder. God.
There's a broader issue in a lot of episodes.
And again, I credit Aaron with this observation.
How come so they were soon as Siegfried and Roy show up anywhere, they all they dropped to all fours.
Right. That's that's kind of the premise that they all stand on hind legs.
But there's sort of a Toy Story thing going on where like they are Rugrats more accurately.
We're like Siegfried and Roy don't know they talk in the way the parents don't know the Rugrats talk.
That's right. So there's this ruse being kept up.
But they like it's always like we got caught like quick on all fours, everyone.
But that's what that happens when Siegfried and Roy walk up and talk to them in front of their homes where they have television sets and furniture.
Why? So they're allowed to have all that.
They all have like recliners and, you know, Wi-Fi routers, but they don't have they can't stand up and talk.
They also always look very indifferent at Siegfried and Roy or mad.
I would say there is no relationship between the animals and Siegfried and Roy.
I mean, the most relationship happens when Snack becomes friendly with Roy on the Thanksgiving episode.
He says his hair smells like home.
Yes, we can snack and also Roy hugs Snack and then he comments on the fact that Snack has a penis as a boner.
It's probably a boner, right?
Because there's like a romantic thing between Snack and Roy.
But then Roy takes another animal as a pet and they play it off like Roy is caught Roy's caught between two lovers.
This show is so weird.
I just wanted to put some stuff in perspective for you guys.
Yes.
Since Scott, you said two to two point five million an episode for the budget of this show.
Yeah. Yeah.
The it appears the average budget for an episode of Mad Men, a very expensive prestige television, was two to three billion.
What?
Yes, that's right.
A show filled with period details and like actors who were multi seasons in like, you know.
Dear Lord.
Oh, my God.
Sometimes the same as Mad Men.
This cost.
Sometimes the same.
Yeah.
May cost more than an episode of Bad Men.
Fuck God.
I think I knew the show was going to be not good, but I didn't think it would be so just abrasive and headache inducing and that there'd be things about erections and pitching tents.
So often and again, I cannot underline enough gay jokes in every single one of them.
Yeah.
Yes.
Why?
I never go to see this coming.
A larger.
Even for again, for the time being, I think it's the show is really just a show that's not going to be a good show.
It's not going to be a good show.
A large about even for again, for the time, a lot to me, like you wouldn't be like, oh, well, that's obviously every show was like that at the time.
It wasn't.
I don't think.
No, I just I've watched shows from before this from the 90s from the 80s.
What?
Like unless things suddenly turned really toxic just for like a year there and we'd go back and watch any like According to Jim is just full of like I mean, maybe that's right.
Yeah.
Well, of all the shows.
Yes.
That one's the most likely.
You picked According to Jim.
I don't know.
It could be every other every other sentence.
But just Jag has a monologue in every episode about keeping those homosexuals out of this.
I really said, no one's ever actually paid attention to Jag before.
That's why you did.
Yes.
All of the show.
That's all the CBS shows we all make fun of.
Who watches this?
It's because touched by an angel is excessively homophobic every time.
Hawaii Five-O is still on the air nine seasons in and it's just full of gay jokes still in 2020.
And I think it's how crass they are in this.
Like, well, you didn't need to fill that time.
Like you could have just ended that scene or just had a non sequitur about something else like it.
Yeah.
Anything else could have been done.
And speaking of doing other things, Mike and I got to take some well-deserved breaks.
Mike, how did you feel about your break time?
Oh, I loved listening to one of the great actors of our of our time, I guess of a different time, talk about making the Oscar nominated Golden Globe nominated winning.
Julie's gold.
Of course, Peter Fonda played Julie Jackson, sort of a reclusive beekeeper.
And I learned a lot about sort of the making of the movie.
I learned I forget that I'm forgetting the director's name, but they referred to him as the gentle bear on set.
And Peter Fonda, he he basically he loves working with this with this director and he would he said he'd love to work with him.
He said he'd carry water on the set.
That's how much he liked working with this guy.
And he was just sort of explaining his process.
You know, he's just he looks smaller is better, he thinks.
And he was talking about his father, the great Henry Fonda, who was a bit of a withholding type, to be very honest, towards the end of their life.
Let's see who the Dan refers to in the book.
His memoir, which is also discussed.
His memoir memoir is discussed and he was a bit withholding when he was a youth.
But toward the end, I think they had a better relationship and he was talking about acting and, you know, playing things more internal, throwing things away.
And it's like how is Dad Henry Fonda threw away the last line of of Grapes of Wrath, which, of course, laid John Steinbeck's work bare for the audience to really absorb it.
And I found this interesting process, a little bit of personal history, show business history.
This is by far the highlight of my day.
I would say without question, but in Saramani moves in Siegfried develops a gambling problem.
He almost blows the whole fortune.
They finally go to a casino floor.
And I'm surprised for a movie that probably got some kickbacks from Vegas or the Mirage MGM company.
They were showing a negative portrayal of gambling.
Hmm. Well, you know, they got they were allowed to get a little irreverent in some of these storylines.
Look, that sounds great. Will I ever watch that?
No, I will say I will never watch that episode.
Never, ever, ever watch Saramani moves in.
I will never watch Saramani moves in.
What if I were to tell you that Dick Cheney is back?
There's another Dick Cheney site gag.
Why is Dick Cheney in so many episodes?
It was just a zeitgeisty reference.
So sticking it to the man.
The reelection committee like slipped them some like we'll cover an episode.
We'll cover an episode for you.
We just got to get our boy in there.
They were probably wondering if we could, you know, like, can we use his likeness?
Is that OK? And then Katzenberg caught wind of it and like, I'm on a boat with him right now.
I'll ask.
Mm hmm. It's OK. It's not going to look like him anyway.
Who gives a shit?
How good do you think our rendering is?
It's going to look like a sim.
I do think you're likely to watch the film Yulis Gold.
If in the next couple of weeks I just happen upon it, if it happens to be like free streaming on crackle or to be, do you know to be?
I do. I do have to be downloaded. Yes.
T-U-B-I to be they have some free movies on there.
I've recently learned if it's if it happened to be streaming, would I throw it on?
Oh, sure. I got news for you, Mike. It's on Hulu.
Is it really?
I almost thought about having you watch 22 arbitrary minutes of it.
And then I realized it'd be more enriching for you to learn about Peter Fonda and his process.
I think you made the right call, but that does not that does not mean I don't want to see the story of Yuli Jackson.
He was a beekeeper.
Why is he reclusive?
He doesn't really get into that so deep, but he did win the Golden Globe for it.
I'll say that.
I mean, that speaks for itself.
In the end, Yuli's gold was the globe.
Mm hmm.
Yuli Jackson, a beekeeper.
Well, I mean, my my experience is skipping road trip.
No, I watched road trip.
Why skip the stage fright?
Skip stage fright.
And Scott, what if I were to tell you you missed another occurrence of the Dick Cheney's like, yes, Dick Cheney was in stage fright.
And Saramadi talks about growing up in Africa, which is even weirder.
He did not.
He did not grow up there.
No.
Yeah.
Saramadi.
Well, I keep thinking it's like Scaramucci in my head.
Sierra, the daughter there.
They OK.
So they're watching.
There's a psych ag where the daughter and the son are watching The Lion King.
And she has filled the son's cone with popcorn.
How about that?
And then he says, what's happening in the movie?
And she says the line Simba was sad.
And then Darth Vader said some made up Africa crap.
So that made it onto network television.
That line.
Father of the pride decided to be higher and mightier than the Lion King.
Get Katzenberg got wind of the what do you mean?
He was going to put a dream jerks in California adventure.
That won't stand.
Time to shit on my old work.
This was the episode that we should have made the big pitch for Eisner to be on.
Yeah, we're going to sink up and watch it with him.
We screwed up.
Eisner should have done all episodes with us.
And he should have watched the Peter Fonda clip or listen to the Bob Dylan song.
And then we should have all gone on here because he would have loved to give us some Katzenberg stuff.
Oh, yeah, that'd be great.
I mean, we should pitch him like Mike.
We're going to call it settling scores with Michael Eisner.
Huh?
He has no venue to do that other than our show.
Yeah.
Yeah, I mean, we'll create a stern like environment where he feels comfortable, you know,
revisiting old feuds.
I also feel very rewarded because like you, Mike, I got to, you know,
sit and hear wisdom from one of the great artists of the 20th century and beyond.
And the song Murder Most Foul Bob Dylan not only relives the JFK assassination,
but also much of the pop culture that shaped him, that shaped America in the 60s and 70s
and via a series of endless couplets for 17 straight minutes over a drone of piano and cello.
We go back, we time travel with Bob and we hear lines like November 12th, 1963,
a day that will live in infamy.
That does sound like Bob Dylan, but it also sounds like Kenan's Pierre Escargot character.
They blew off his head while he was still in the car.
I thought it was sort of Sandler-esque a little bit too.
Oh, yeah, that too.
Oh, yeah, that's a sub.
I do JFK shoot a room.
The one that I made it through the song without stopping until I needed a breather when he I got to the line
the day they blew out the brains of the king.
What are they talking about?
What's that?
What they blew up the brains of the king.
They're talking about who?
The JFK.
Kennedy?
The best guy.
And how long is this song again?
17 minutes and it's lyrics nonstop and it's all like that.
It's very Dr. Seuss.
Which I felt inspired to relive my own history in the same format.
And I decided to try my hand.
You know, I'm no Dylan, but you know, there's a little poet in all of us.
And I decided to see if I could write some murder most foul type lines about what I've experienced today, which father of the pride.
Father of the bride.
Oh, I love it.
Which with this experience today, watching this entire series felt as long as living through the 1960s.
So with that, let me see if I can convey the experience here.
Yeah.
See Sigfried and Roy, the magicians are rich.
Some old here likes to say crappy and bitch lesbian gophers stronger and shimmy Larry likes to wear a wig like Jimmy.
Wig like Jimmy play smash mouth for donkey from Shrek.
Cheryl Hines cashes a paycheck.
Smoking cat nip make the lions all growl.
Father of the pride is a serious most foul.
You have it.
I mean, I think that was all worth it.
And hey, Jimmy and Chaga definitely trust McNeil voices.
That's confirmed.
I think so.
Yeah.
And they made out.
That was a lot of fun.
Yeah.
So there you have it.
I mean, this also it as we record this much 29, 2020, a day that will live in it for me as the worst thing I guess I ever did to ourselves or to the audience.
I think I was in a fuzz bucket, tested my will, tested my relationship.
You know, it's not like you had a great time.
Yeah, you got high on catnip with your girl.
I think I came around with the catnip at the end.
I wish you like the lions could have eaten it from sausages.
I will.
That's you know, that is a good idea.
I should run my once a week trip to the store.
I should pick up some sausages because I don't know what I have.
Once a once a week, you're daring.
You're real daredevil.
Yeah, really.
What do you mean?
No, that's what they're saying.
You're supposed to do.
Oh, that's what they're saying.
Yes.
I'm trying to I'm trying to do it, you know, two or more.
I'm afraid to go outside anyway.
I admire your bravery.
Oh, I've been walking every day.
I haven't done that.
I've been.
I took a walk after all this after Father of the Pride.
That felt good for getting the getting kissed from the sun.
I've never tried.
I don't really think I have the the, you know, grinder type utilities
and the casings probably gross.
Well, I have a suggestion for what to grind up and stick in a sausage.
The DVD.
This four-dollar DVD.
You know, maybe for Twitch, I'll watch the automatic.
I'll watch the automatic and I'll watch the DVD.
I'll watch the DVD.
I'll watch the automatic and the original pilot and do commentary on that.
Not for this.
I'll wait.
I'll wait for the episode to drop and then I'll be like, folks, I got to close the loop.
I got to close the circle.
It's going to drive the OCD part of my brain nuts if I don't finish this DVD.
I was going to say we give this away at a live show, but I'm afraid to put my signature on this item.
Well, that's yeah, that's OK.
We don't have to sign it.
You just mean you don't want and you don't want it to be in someone's home because of you.
I mean that and also just having our names like even just written on it and marker.
Why are we signing it though?
Why are we so we don't have to sign it?
People might ask, you know, someone might add something else.
Yeah, we should probably sign something else.
It's a presumptuous autograph, I feel.
OK, fair enough.
In your scenario, people are like, I demand the three of you sign this.
I would.
If there's like a funny giveaway, be like, hey, would you sign it?
I think that'd be fun.
If I ever saw if I had the copy with me in my car and I ran into Cheryl Hines or Orlando Jones,
maybe I'd have them try to sign it.
But then I think they might like throw smack it out of my hand onto the ground.
We'll have the wait for the DVD to break and then press it against my neck and threaten me
or just go, what are you talking about?
I wasn't in that.
That's a solid move, I think, on the part of anyone involved in this show.
Let's get out of here.
Let's let's let's end this.
You know what I think is funny just as a closing thought?
You know, a lot of the throughout the downtown Disney ordeal, I was trying to reduce things,
get out of things, avoid doing things.
I like how we came up with an escape patch for us to miss some of this and everyone agreed it was fine.
Oh, yeah.
There's no argument.
I was thinking, though, that and we're still in the middle of a quarantine situation here.
I was thinking if after the first few, if we had said like, hey, instead of doing this,
let's throw it out the window and I'll drive down and just review the exteriors of the businesses on Harbor Boulevard.
I would have 100 percent said, you know what?
Let's do that. Let's go do that instead.
Yeah.
This. Yeah, I think we all we all saw the writing on the wall very quickly, very quickly.
And no, no, even amount of funny bit, no even amount of funny bits were going to like make us stick to some sort of some sort of structure to this.
I guess Jason insisted on watching all of it.
And it turns out that the show is going to be a lot of fun.
Jason insisted on watching all of it.
And it turns out he's just one of the biggest fans of the show.
I mean, I, you know, at this point, I would love to ask.
Yeah, I would love to hear from people involved in the show.
I would love to hear more stories because I'm so curious.
I mean, if it's early 2000 Dreamworks coming off of Shrek's like massive success and it's got a huge budget.
How could you how do you say no? How do you say no?
How? I don't know. I I I would never say no to Mr. Katzenberg to Mr. Zigg to Mr. Roy or Mr. Ziegfried.
I would never. But then another question is how do you see a script that on every page contains a gay joke that is gone?
There's such a circuitous lengthy path to get to it.
How do you not take a really thick sharpie and exit out as many times as possible?
Hmm. Yeah, that is also very fair. That's a great question as well.
Who is the script editor on this show? Sarmody?
Could you imagine if you had to work for Sarmody?
Oh, man, that would probably lead to some some tales.
Get out of my office, you dumb bitch.
Never refers to being a lion.
There's so little of the show is about being a lion.
If it had been about lion stuff, I would have loved it.
But it's like my boss is coming over.
My mother's an election to my kid's school.
The night like it's sparingly occasionally accidentally about being a lion.
Yeah, barely about magic shows like hardly any magic.
Yes, but the mind is not the magic when it comes to the show.
Look, here's what's going to happen.
I mean, we've all been through a real psychological journey today,
and we're going to have to sit and recover from this,
just like you, Lee Jackson recovers from a knife wound at the end of the show.
At the end of the film, Uly's gold.
But will be the more enriched for it will grow and will be better people.
That's right.
Uly Jackson.
That's us.
And what you're listening to right now is you is Uly's gold.
Uly's gold, the gold of the three Uly's is what you just heard.
No longer the good boys were referred to as the three Uly's.
And you just endured the three Uly's, the new our new catchphrase,
as that is what we are three solitary in hiding beekeepers.
Making trying to make honey or harvest honey from terrible television shows.
And I hope you enjoyed that honey today.
Dear fucking Lord, let's never do anything like this again.
My least favorite episode.
It's nice to have a definitive.
I think for sure I would say 100 percent.
This is the first episode we've ever done.
If you would like to watch Father of the Pride, retrain your brain to do anything else.
What's the order? What's the correct order?
And I think the order is none.
The order is if you happen upon it,
maybe the order is go to YouTube, look up the episodes on the channel TopTunes,
report the top tunes to YouTube for crimes against humanity.
We'll get all these episodes removed.
Copyright strike. Take down notice.
I don't like to be a narc on copyright issues, but in this case, yes,
something must be done. The government must be alerted.
Yes, everything I think everything you can get out of this show.
There's one JPEG of like donkey standing next to Larry the lion.
That's what you need. You just need that JPEG.
You just. Well, I have I have one picture of Kelsey Grammer that I captured on my phone.
I mean, that's good. Yeah. I mean, that's that's all right, too.
You'd like that to become a meme.
Well, definitely. We'll be posting that for sure.
Yes, we need to popularize bizarre, stiff CGI.
Kelsey Grammer, the guy, Kelsey Grammer.
And of course, Martin, you know, he's got those big eyebrows, a precursor to shark tail
precursor to Martin Scorsese showing up at Shark Tale where they got the real guy
and where they got the real guy. More money.
You know, let's never let's not watch that.
Let's not watch anything. Let's take a break.
Let's not record one for like a month and a half.
Yeah, I don't really.
I prefer to not to
restore Kelsey.
I sent you the photo of Kelsey Grammer on your phones.
And that's the last we ever hear from Mike.
That's the last it's a screen grab a Kelsey Grammer.
And then last night when he texted us the Disney Plus page for returned Oz, an upsetting image.
This is a terror. I'm deleting this thread.
This is the end.
Return to Oz compared to the return.
Return to Oz is a masterpiece compared to this.
I don't. I don't doubt that.
I certainly don't doubt that.
And every other episode of podcast the ride is a masterpiece compared to this.
Listen to the rest.
Subscribe. Check us out on Facebook, Twitter, Facebook, Twitter and Instagram.
And yeah, that's it.
Let's get out of here.
All right. All right.
All right. Good riddance.