Forever.
Dog.
Smells.
They're all around us, and they're often talked about and debated.
Is the smell of freshly cut grass better than the smell of baked goods?
Is the smell of a chocolate factory better than the smell of an open sewer?
Eavesdrop on any water cooler in the country, and these are the words and sentences you'll
hear.
But we on Podcast the Ride decided to tackle a less talked about, yet equally important
type of smell.
The fake smell.
The backbone of the olfactory experience in any theme park.
The thing that can make you hungry, make you laugh, or simply make you want to hurl.
Join us today as 16 of the top fake smells in theme park history are pitted against each
other for ultimate fake smell supremacy.
Which fake smells will dissipate quickly?
And which fake smells will linger in our sinuses forever?
It's the fake smell final four on Podcast the Ride.
Ooh, that smell.
It goes a song that no one likes.
But today we will determine which smell in theme park world makes people go ooh the most.
And which make people go you the most.
I'm Scott Gardner, joined by this for this very important event by Mike Carlson.
Hello.
I am here.
And Jason Sheridan.
Hi, I'm here.
And just to clarify, we're talking fake smells.
Yes.
Not actual.
Yeah.
This is the fake smell final four, which we felt like was a worthy follow up to last year's
fake rock final four.
We love these things as long as they are fake.
Because by saying fake, which sounds like a dismissive word, we are tributing the people
who worked hard to create these.
We're honoring the fabrication.
But there's certain smells in theme park world.
I don't think we would quantify as fake smells because they just are the real smell that
exists in that setting.
They weren't crafted.
Do we have some examples of this?
Certain food items like cooking a churro is the churro smell itself.
If there's a fake churro smell, which I do kind of think there are versions of it.
They may be pumping in something to add to what's practically there.
It's unclear sometimes exactly what is fake and real.
I think a lot of times it's fake.
But yes, if you were actually to go up to the churro or say the popcorn stand, you go
up and you can actually smell popcorn because you're right standing there and that's where
the popcorn is.
That is not in this tournament.
That is just food cooking.
That is the side effect of food cooking.
Don't think that counts.
I think maybe the big one that people are going to point out is not in this tournament
is the smell of the Pirates of the Caribbean water.
Because I believe that also to be not a contrived smell, but just an accidental smell that people
are fond of.
Oh yeah.
But I don't think it's calculated.
I don't think at all it's calculated.
Haunan Mansion also is a smell that we all have affection for.
But that's just whatever the building materials.
Yeah, a combination of plastic and age and humanity.
They don't have like a little canister that says old house on it that's blasting in the
smell of old house.
I don't think so, though you never know.
There's a thing.
They're not public with all this stuff either.
So we may be making a big mistake on one of these.
We may be missing out on something.
Somebody is going to be very upset because they're going to say, you know, that thing
you thought is fake, it's real.
Or you're missing out on this thing that's actually fake and you thought it was really
fooled you.
Yeah.
Yes.
Maybe more than the previous might require a recount and like a sort of fact session.
We need to fact check these.
So that's really up to you, the listener, if you know more than we do.
But I feel pretty confident about these 16 that we narrated to that they are contrived
smells, that they are created smells.
I think there's one that may be snuck in and I think we can allow for a little bit of wiggle
room on that one.
OK, interesting.
I'm not trying to know offhand.
Yeah.
Is there anything else we want to say about the formulation of these before we kind of
unveil the 16?
I think I just want to say in case like you're really you don't still know what we're talking
about like at Disney, if you walk down Main Street and you smell something, oftentimes
it's fake.
It's not a real food item.
It's a fake thing.
When you're on a ride, there'll be a blast of something and it'll be a smell that's supposed
to go with what you're seeing.
I just want to fill in in case you don't really don't know what we're talking about.
Smellarize?
Is that the trademark term?
There's technology.
Smellarize?
Really?
So we smell it.
Smellitzers seems to be the mechanism that dispenses the smell in some settings.
I'm not sure every smell that is released is released by a smellitzer, but certainly
some of them are.
Can I have a picture of what Universal might use?
That's true because some of these are universal.
So it's not like Disney has the market cornered on fake smells.
So universal factors in.
And you know what?
Actually it has the official name supposedly of one of the things we're going to do, which
I'm realizing now.
Oh really?
So feel free to correct.
This is all a loose process.
We tried to name these things, but some of the names could be incorrect.
There could be better names that we determine as we go.
Right.
So before what I was just trying to sum up is that we've chosen what we believe are the
top fake smells that you would run into on Main Street, that you would run into on the
top most well-known rides in the country.
Often the most, I think we've also kind of quantified them as the most memorable because
I don't think you would call all these the best, the most pleasant because sometimes
often there's unpleasant smells released.
So these are remarkably unpleasant.
A lot of them are.
There might be some people who think every one of these is unpleasant.
Interesting.
Yeah.
If I get too much of a blast, I have a very sensitive sense of smell and it can really
be irritating.
So people probably are going to wonder how are we judging these?
What are the criteria of which we're deciding?
What are we using in our thought process when we are deciding what is going to be in the
fake smell Final Four and ultimately win the whole tournament?
Yeah, it's obviously extremely official.
We have our list of 12 aspirational smell qualities.
Detail them all now and certainly not just make them up.
Mine is all mathematics.
It's all moneyball.
That's smart.
Moneyball.
Moneyball holds up.
You see moneyball lately?
Yeah.
It was very good.
It's the social network too.
Remember that?
I thought it was like the social network.
Every Bill Simmons, everything on the Bill Simmons network is just, every podcast is
to remind you that moneyball and the social network are good.
I bet because I really like social network and I bet if I went back and rewatched those,
I bet a lot of that still holds up.
Just because, but I also really like David Fincher as a filmmaker.
Sure.
So.
These are not insane opinions.
I'm confused by these podcasts that are like such and such holds up.
And it's like, that's two years ago.
Like Birdman holds, yeah, that was really recent.
Like, are movies supposed to just expire?
After five years.
Or like five months.
Yeah.
A movie from a year ago is still good.
Parasite held up.
I watched it last night.
It held up.
Was that your first viewing?
I never saw it before, but it held up.
It did hold up.
From its Oscar win.
Yes.
It was still good after winning.
Yeah.
Good for Parasite.
You weren't up frustrated with all the reading.
No, I was all right with the reading.
Yeah.
It's fine.
It held up.
That was the winner of the Oscars, a lesser competition than the one that we're currently
engaged in.
Yeah, that's, yes.
Obviously that's on the way down.
These fake something final fours are on the way up.
Yeah.
And this one has three hosts, so it's three times better.
Oh yeah.
That's true.
Zero times three is three.
Three non-controversial hosts.
Yeah.
Controversy free.
Well, we'll see though, because also, yeah, if you go back into past tweets and we've
like said that we didn't like smells that we champion now or vice versa.
Oh yeah.
Delete your tweets now, boys.
Look for your own name and smell and make sure nothing contradicts what we're about
to do.
Yeah.
What are the criteria?
Does anyone have any in mind?
I mean, look, it's going to have to factor into a lot of different things.
Everything's going to be, you know, you're going to see the matchups.
You're going to see what kind of a thing, like what these two, are they, you know, a
ride versus just standing on Main Street.
That's going to factor in.
And obviously you're going to have to adjust based on each lineup.
But in general, I'm going to be judging on if I think that isn't an effectively used
in the place it's at, if it smells like the real thing or makes it improves on the real
thing in any way.
And I will try to divorce myself from just saying, well, this is on a ride I like.
I'm going to try to really just examine it as a piece and then examine the other thing
as a piece.
Oh, like the moment in and of itself.
Yeah.
Although it's hard to totally separate, because it is if it's contributing to an
experience that you're very fond of.
Yes, it's going to be very hard.
There's a couple I already know I'm looking at and it's going to be very hard to just
separate myself from this ride or experience.
Yeah. Yeah.
I think I've been reading this book that Joe Rodie was posting about called Places,
Places of the Heart.
And it's how it's about how humans experience locations, like especially built
locations, constructed places.
And how much are other senses?
Like how much are senses come into play?
And I do think sense is a very it's a very powerful one.
So I think like the the impression it makes some of these I just plain like, like some
of them I will just go on gut.
Like, no, that's great.
Some of these I do not care for.
Yeah. Yeah.
We tried to put ones we don't care for against each other here and there.
Yeah.
But that's just what you're judging it on.
Maybe it's like maybe you almost go the most unpleasant in that regard.
I think creativity has to be taken into account.
I agree with that.
It's like you wouldn't like automatically think to create a smell and incorporate a
smell of this.
Yeah.
You know, if it's just kind of like, well, we put the smell in that should be there.
Can you really reward that?
But sometimes maybe it's atmospheric and it's it's crucial and tied into the place.
Yeah.
I mean, any rules we try to make now, they could all go out the window when push comes
to shove, when we have matchups that we just don't know what to do with.
Yeah.
And it's funny, we that, you know, we do kind of moneyball the first categories a
little bit. We try to make them either like fair fights or like thematically similar.
But, you know, I think that what I found with the fake rock final four last year is
the first categories were a little easier than the second.
Yeah.
The second where total mismatches.
I never thought about having to align these two.
Right.
Like I could I kind of have in my head all of the first round.
But the second, we're just going to be going off the dome.
It's going to be scary.
We're going to be going to try the waters.
I can already call some chaotic energy real chaos.
Because it's radically we're going to end up with so all over the map.
Yeah, I think by the second round, I also will say if I if my memory serves me correct,
you're in for probably the least funny episode of podcast to write all year, the most
taking seriously episode where we're just sitting going, I don't I don't know what to
choose here.
So if you want jokes, tune out.
If you want, if you want a lot of hemming and howling, if you want a lot of just sincere,
God, I can't do that.
I can't I can't do it.
Yeah, there's going to be pauses.
We'll have to leave and go like, you know, climb a mountain and think about the choice
and maybe come back tomorrow.
I don't know if we're going to be seamless for you, the listener, but this might take
us a week.
Yeah.
I mean, just listen to doughboys if you want the laughs because they're not happening.
Sorry.
This isn't funny.
This just isn't funny.
Sorry, it's going to be so unfunny.
It's going to be a real bummer.
Listen off book.
Listen to doughboys.
There's a lot of podcasts that have humor in it.
Not this one and a lot of podcasts that tell you that moneyball holds up.
And if you want, if you're looking for that, we've said it once in this episode, right?
Not a bunch of times.
Right.
We're here to do what we have to do, which is be very nervous about choices with no
stakes whatsoever.
All right.
Nevertheless, I am nervous.
So maybe we dive into the first round and then once you've heard our first 16, we can
talk a little about.
We didn't list off all 16 at once last year, did we?
No, I think we did.
Round by round.
I believe we did it one at a time.
And then we talked about what didn't make it.
Yeah.
Now, if you go to Twitter, unless you're hearing this at midnight and we haven't gotten up
to post it yet, at some point on true, you could look at the whole thing and follow
along with us.
But if you just want to hear, if you want to be surprised, then sure.
Just be surprised with us.
Yeah.
Okay.
Are we ready?
Do we do we sort of like round robin unveiling them?
Yeah, that's good.
You can go first, Scott.
Okay.
All right.
Round one or not round one bracket one.
What do we call the individual bracket one say?
Okay, sure.
All right.
Bracket one stage one bracket one.
These are levels, levels of brackets.
How are we going to do this without somebody keeping us on track?
I wish we have no sweet smells of his vapes.
Oh, man.
Joining us.
Oh, wait, the bracket keeper is here.
It's a different character.
The bracket keeper.
Hey there.
Hey.
Where is Bruce?
Move along.
Okay.
Joke.
No fucking way.
That's not what this is for.
All right.
No bracket key left.
Bracket keeper left.
Get out of here.
All right.
So bracket one.
I almost feel I don't even know if I like the name.
Why don't we just I have the official name of it.
Oh, then let's do it right here.
Wait, then you take it.
Okay.
This is the scent officially named if this is a correct photo, the evergreen
forest from the ET adventure ride in Orlando only existing now.
Who I like.
And I land on much better name evergreen forest.
I was calling it damp forest.
Yeah.
I like damn forest, but this is a little like a kind of a black.
It's called sent air, which is where it comes from.
Supposedly.
This is what somebody posted on a message board saying.
I believe this is what universal users.
Supplier.
Yeah.
Sent air.
Wow.
Evergreen forest.
I have a number on it too.
Nine five six.
Then there's a code that says SWC 10 40.
We'll rank the individual evergreen forests.
Well, we should all skew.
And at this point, maybe we could call them and see if we could each get
one of these and pump it in.
All right.
So services evergreen forest versus African grass from Soren over the world.
Right.
Yeah.
Yes.
From Disney's California version.
You're in Africa and you're flying over the elephants and the animals kind of
scary and away from you.
Yeah.
And of course the evergreen forest, I guess it's in the ride too, but it's
primarily the line.
Yeah.
I think we would say all of the trees and where you meet to botanicals.
Um, now you don't want to skew anything, but it's hard evergreen forest is a strong,
I think it's there's a reason why it's for the first one that we named.
It's definitely one of the like, one of the ones you think of an evergreen
favorite fan favorite versus a young upstart, thrilling, thrilling match in
this competition.
Yeah.
Grassy, both earthy.
Both pleasant.
That's what I felt like a good.
One of the few pleasant brackets.
There is.
I would call a lot of them.
I would call it.
Yeah.
There's a nuance to the African grass smell.
I feel like that's like kind of a, there's like subtlety to the smell.
Cause you could, and I don't know if it's just my brain screwing with me when I
see the visuals of the dirt and the grass, but it feels like I'm smelling both.
It feels like in my head, again, this is a lot of scent can, I'm sure is deceiving
depending on what visual cues you're getting.
But when I see that and I smell it, I do really think, Oh, I'm smelling dirt and
grass.
It's like cut grass, right?
You're smelling cut like a lawnmower cut grass.
Yeah.
Which it's, you know, and it's clever in that regard.
I think, you know, you're going to see Soren on here a couple of times.
It's probably no surprise.
Right.
I really the ride that most prominently uses multiple fake smells.
And I think this is, it is one of the more unique smells that they use.
It's one that you, you know, if you're being kind of dour and grumpy, you might
say, well, they're just blasting in like air freshener and this is not really an
air freshener.
It feels sophisticated when it comes to theme park smells.
Yeah.
It feels like it's maybe the next level of them.
It's very creative and a fun point in the ride.
I feel.
Yes.
I'm going to jump in here, not with counterpoint, but kind of, um, I have a
hand soap from Target that smells just like this at a cost 99 cents.
Oh, so I am knocking points for that.
Okay.
Honestly, I was impressed at how the hand soap captured this smell and, and, and
in that your hands then smell like it.
Do you have a name on that?
Did you buy it for that reason?
Smartly.
That's a smartly.
Smartly?
That's one of their newer house brands.
What's the name of the brand?
Smartly.
Oh, I thought, I got confused.
It's kind of an up and up level.
They have all these fucking house brands now.
It's so hard to keep.
Do you know the specific smell?
That's what I meant to ask.
Flavor.
What do you call it?
Variety?
Or would you call these?
Yeah.
Literally the bottle says smells like a meadow.
Oh, and it smells like dirt.
No, it smells like, like cut grass.
Okay.
Just the cut grass elements.
Just the cut grass.
I see.
I'm going to double check.
Okay.
I would like you washing your hands with a dirt soap.
There's like earth and kind of sense.
That doesn't seem out of the realm of possibility.
Yeah.
So, I mean, there's a lot of the good things you could say about this.
However, I feel this is, I think that African grass is kind of cursed.
I think this is kind of, this is when like the top seed and the lowest seed.
Yeah.
And seed appropriate, what with grass and forests.
But what are you going to do?
This is a juggernaut.
Yeah.
This is a evergreen.
It's evergreen forest.
It's, I mean, it's got to be.
Yeah.
I think that unfortunately I wanted to say some nice things, but how do you possibly not pick?
I should probably.
Yeah.
I, it's just that it's such a, the mood in there, it's such a great line.
It's one of the best lines, cues of all time.
And Botanica is being there.
ET's teacher, in case you're behind.
ET's teacher appears every 10 minutes, maybe.
And it's just a perfect presentation of a wise old, Broto-Azojan appearing.
Which is also if you're behind, what is that?
That is the name of ET's alien.
That's the name of the alien race species that alien, the alien is.
Uh, the whole package is so fantastic and the smell is such a big part of it.
It's excellent place making.
It's really certain.
It's sort of perfect.
Unfortunately.
Yeah.
There's just, you're not going to beat standing in that queue, seeing Botanica's
smelling the evergreen forest.
It's just, it's going to be hard to top.
And it's like, I'm just going to say it's taking, it's looking very good for the
tournament is all I'm saying.
Yeah.
Uh, I don't want to like call it a foregone conclusion because I think there's
some very strong competitors.
We'll see.
The, the, it also is one of those things that when you're older, when it's not
either when the ride was gone, when you haven't thought about theme parks in a
little bit and you're starting to connect with people.
I just remembered a lot of conversations with people like, oh, you grew up around
universal or you went to universal a lot.
Oh, ET adventure, right?
Oh, the smell.
Remember the smell in the line?
Yeah.
Just one of those like slightly deeper cut details that people bring up and
don't think that other people remember.
Do you remember the smell?
Oh my God, the smell.
Yeah.
Just such a, uh, it's a, it's a real franchise.
It's like a UCLA Duke.
You know, it's, it's a big one.
Yeah.
Probably going to be beat around.
I got a little gassy.
Uh, that was it.
I thought you were getting choked up.
Oh, no, no.
It was probably going to go pretty far.
It's probably going to be around.
Yeah.
You really sounded like you were like announcing the death of a president on the
news services today and be held like you just had to, you just got handed the
bulletin tragedy in Dallas.
President Johnson will, uh, the center.
Well, let's, uh, let's keep moving it along.
Then anybody want to, Hey, Mr. Mr.
Sweets.
Maybe, uh, no problem.
Um, all right.
Uh, we have the chocolate smell from Hershey's chocolate world versus the
waffles and vanilla smell outside of, uh, the ice cream shop on main street.
It's probably any, I think they're called different things in the various magic
kingdoms, but I think whatever, wherever you are, uh, the whatever, wherever, uh,
sweets are being sold in a main street, whatever the smell being pumped outside
of that place.
Yeah.
It's a, it's sort of, it ends up being, I think a catchall for trying to get you
to buy sweets of any kind.
It's a confectioners kind of general.
Yes.
Confectioners smell.
And it's the strongest main street smell, I believe my, in my memory, at least
that you have when you walk by, especially the confectionary area, but
they're pumping into other places in the park to make you want sweets.
Yes.
Yeah.
This is the one that I said snuck in because I'm a little conflicted because it is an
ice cream shop next to a confectionary where they make the actual product, but this is
so noticeable.
And it's for sure smell itsers are deployed.
This is like where I'm thinking of, and you can see photos of the little kind of a dot
at circles, the way they're being pumped out of.
And that's like an early one.
That's like a one.
If you're a little kid, I, I'm sure you don't realize that fake.
You're probably possibly an adult and not realizing or, or if not totally fake, then
exaggerated, uh, you know, supported and.
Yeah.
Puffed up.
I mean, a lot of, I grew up going to a lot of like, uh, old fashioned ice cream
parlors that still did the soda fountain and the, you know, waffle press and everything.
At the Jersey shore, there was still a lot that you would sit down and you get it in
the glass, you know, dish and all that sort of thing.
And they definitely had a similar smell because they're like churning out so many
just all day long.
Right.
Yes.
Not always a contrived smell.
No, completely real at the time.
Yeah.
Um, uh, and then versus, I mean, I think there's multiple places where you're, you're
smelling fake chocolate.
And we even talked about the, the tooth some, uh, Emporium at universal studios is a place
where you, where you could smell real strong, like piped in chocolate smell.
Yeah.
But we went with Hershey's chocolate world, which is the ride that's technically not in
the theme park.
No, it's next to the parking lot.
So for a long free ride, Hershey's at one point in time did give tours of the actual
factory.
And then as they expand theme park, they built a visitor center called chocolate world.
That is different than chocolate land.
The soon to open land at the entrance to the theme park.
It's kind of a deescalation in naming, but it looks like it's going to be very nice,
but chocolate world.
I mean, I, it's free for one thing.
It's got restaurants, got lots of candy, different candy shops inside.
There's tastings and educational stuff, but there is a dark ride in it.
And, uh, now a lot of that dark ride is singing cows.
Uh, but it usually used to be mostly simulations of the factory, including large
vats of like chocolate looking goo being stirred.
When there was less cartoony stuff in there, the chocolate smell being piped in is almost
the primary interaction.
It's like a, just a realistic recreation of a factory and just glued in my mind, like
glued in my sense memory in terms of like stuff lodged in my memory of these.
This one might be the strongest.
Would you say, and I have not smelled this particular, I've obviously smelled the
toothsome chocolate.
I've not smelled the Hershey chocolate.
Would you say this is the same smell?
Scott specifically as the M and M world store in Las Vegas?
Uh, huh.
Now I, now is there, is there a fake smell in there in the M and M store?
Yeah.
Yes.
Okay.
So maybe it wasn't on when you were there.
I don't know.
Or I just don't.
I was in such a fog trying to get to the movie.
You would know because it's one of the worst smells.
Oh, okay.
Smell smell.
This is very comfort.
Like this is much more like your mom's baby.
Right.
This smell in the M and M store in Las Vegas, when we were there and did the video,
did the movie, um, was trying to imitate the smell of M and M's.
It smelled like shit.
It smelled the whole three store, four stories or whatever up and down every floor smelled like
this fake M and M smell, but like maybe mildew had gotten in the scent air or something.
There was something stale about it.
It was like stale M and M's that were cooking in the sun where it was wafting through all
four levels, five, whatever it is of the M and M store.
It feels like burnt.
It feels like overcooked.
That would even be too good.
I think like wafting in the sun is more right to me because it like,
you could feel like it would mutate it more, the smell.
Okay.
So it's not all right.
That's more, that's more pleasant.
And a little preview, I guess, of your feelings about the M and M
Vegas movie, which I think Jason, I think hopefully you get a chance to.
I'm on my way soon.
Yeah.
Great.
That's, I'll be staying in that neck of the woods and that is on the list.
That's on the list of things to do.
It's got to be.
Yeah.
There's no way it couldn't be.
Going to Vegas when it's like the cold time of year or the very mild time of year.
So it's like, yeah, what are the indoor activities to do?
Oh, that's a top.
Oh yeah.
You better get there.
Probably ride the death trap monorail.
I don't know if it's a death trap.
The monorail is fine.
Oh, is it?
Okay.
Yeah.
The new monorail.
Is it new?
Isn't there, it's a newish one?
I don't know.
There's a monorail.
I've never had a problem with the monorail.
Like 2006.
I just don't think it goes a lot of places.
Maybe I'm thinking of a different thing.
There's a whole side essentially you can't really get to.
I think it's services pretty particular.
It goes from like MGM to the link, right?
Like that's kind of.
Yeah.
You can get down to, well, you know where it takes you is the Hilton where the Star Trek thing was.
Oh, interesting.
That's one of the furthest outposts.
As a Patreon, we should all get into the link high roller Ferris wheel, but with the open bar.
Oh, the eye.
Yeah.
The eye.
Do you know about this?
That's that the, well, the, I guess I didn't know what it was called.
But you can pay for like an open bar for 45 minutes.
In the Ferris wheel?
In the Ferris wheel.
Whoa.
So you get to just drink an open bar as you go all the way around.
Well, well, well.
Right?
Huh.
Yeah.
So.
Do you have a bartender in here?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Whoa.
And it doesn't seem like it's not crazy.
It's obviously more expensive, but it's not crazy.
It's like $30 a person or something.
Wow.
Which obviously are you going to just like be chugging?
Just crank through.
But still you get like probably a shot or two and a drink.
If everyone had two or three drinks, I mean, that's a short amount of time.
And you go around the thing.
It's Vegas.
Which would stress me out.
I keep looking up stuff like places to go and everywhere is like specials or like well
drinks, 20 ounce pour.
And I'm like, whoa, I thought this was the fancy restaurant.
Or like.
Shitty.
Vodka.
Slushies two for one.
And I'm like, this is the nice restaurant.
Well, that's the ticket to just be.
I think I would be upset.
Like, yeah, I'm not doing it.
Well, we'll get back.
We'll get back to your Vegas.
We'll see.
Yeah.
Do a trip.
Um, so.
Uh, yeah.
Where do we, where do we land here?
I have smelled better chocolate at theme parks, though.
So I won't lump Eminem store in there.
Yeah.
I mean, for me, look, this is no contest.
The vanilla waffle smell is such a fantastic smell.
I associated with Main Street so hard.
I like that chocolate stuff, but vanilla and waffle smell is just the perfect smell.
Is it me?
Like I would miss it if it wasn't there.
Main Street is the most iconic part in any theme park, especially Disneyland's.
It's got to be for me.
The vanilla waffle smell.
Sure.
Jason.
Uh, you know, I'm biased on this one.
I, I, it's again, so glued in my mind.
I have to give it to chocolate world.
Wow.
Tough.
This is a tough round.
Yeah.
I, I don't know that this, my choice will come out the victor.
So like Scott, I'm going to let you break the tie.
Yeah.
That's what I felt.
I figured it would land outside.
I figured it would last.
Um, I'm extremely fond of chocolate world and my, uh, trips there.
My, my trip there as a kid, uh, but for pure iconic reasons, I think you have to go.
Yeah.
Vanilla and waffles.
It's clever the way it's kind of hidden the way it's, uh, you know, that it's, it's luring
you and it's, it's like, uh, the, you know, kind of quiet creativity from the, from the
imagineers.
It feels like a Walt's deployed thing, whether or not it was, it seems very possible.
It could have been, um, yeah, I think you got to go with that.
I am not looking forward to deciding about this second round.
I'll tell you that now.
Evergreen forest versus waffles and vanilla mainstream.
All right.
Two icons.
Oh my God.
Uh, okay.
Do you want to introduce, uh, the next one or am I up?
Introduce?
I think Europe.
Okay.
Uh, number three bracket.
Number three, uh, the orange Grove from horizons versus the orange Grove from Soren over California.
This is orange versus orange.
We're pitting the oranges.
This is a clash of the Titans.
Also to correct ourselves from earlier, Soren over California, Soren around the world.
Soren around the world.
What did I say?
Across the world?
Uh, I think over the world.
Okay.
No way.
So, but this is over California Soren over, over those beautiful California orange groves.
Yes.
That, that part I think is maybe a Camarillo is what that's portraying, which I always find
funny because Camarillo is a place I spent all the time.
I had a good friend out there.
It was like an hour away from where I grew up.
So I ended up in Camarillo a lot and it's just, you know, I've had, I had fun out there,
but a very sleepy place and a very agricultural place.
Yes.
Very suburban outlet malls, outlet malls, very suburban and agricultural, like, like
right next to each other.
Yeah.
And just really always funny to me when you're in the Soren over California line as they bring
back every once in a while and see Palm Springs, Camarillo.
Is so why not just like recita?
Yeah.
A lot of fun golf course.
I really, I mean, maybe it's just the way I go to Palm Springs, but I really don't associate
it with a golf course.
I think plenty of people would.
A lot of tournaments down there and so many of the housing developments are along.
Oh, the housing.
Yeah, that does it.
Yeah.
Oh, and back in the dip in the Bob Hope days.
Sure.
They're down there for, yeah.
We could do a Patreon on all of our personal favorite Soren over California routes
of our landmarks in California where we would want to soar over.
Oh, wow.
Oh, that's like build a Soren.
Yeah.
You each build our own Soren over California specifically.
That's mine would go to recita because of the American, well, the American Legion that's
gone now.
Oh, yeah.
PWG was.
You get to see the vents.
Yeah.
You've all been there.
You guys have been there.
To see where all the sweat is released.
Oh, yeah.
In the air.
It's been destroyed though.
Oh, it's that building is down.
Yeah, it was it was bought by somebody.
Oh, wow.
Anyway, we're talking about an indie wrestling venue essentially.
So it was so in your version, would it release the smell of 200 sweaty men of big bearded
guys in a small room of wine that's turned?
Yeah.
Yes, honestly, that is that would be the smell here.
That's all the alcohol has turned somehow.
Sore over an American Legion hall and you would smell just you just smell like you wanted
to die.
Build a Soren is a good idea.
And you have there are only three smells in total.
Like if we had to build it, do we have to like keep ourselves to three smell?
Like not every scene could have smells.
Yeah, that's yeah, we should we should put the limits of Soren that exist on our own
version.
Same amount of scenes.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's that's nice.
That's a good idea.
So yeah, we got the smell of Camarillo, a famous Camarillo.
Is that where the balloons there to is at the balloon scene?
I think so.
I think that is somewhere else.
Well, there's also balloons in Soren over the world.
Oh, but I think isn't this where or is that like a winery kind of area?
I don't remember.
Yeah, I think that's more NorCal.
I don't recall.
Anyway, versus Horizons.
Yeah.
This is pretty historic stuff.
Was there a ride smell before the Orange Grove and Horizons?
That's a good question.
Yeah, because it's some I was looking at that.
What was the first ride smell?
And I'm not sure.
It might be the oldest one on this list.
I think that's correct.
I think it is.
And it's hard to say when they started pumping in vanilla and waffles, but talking on rides.
Yes.
Well, now.
Sorry.
Yeah, that one is that's an opening day.
That's an opening day when Horizons is not opening day.
Right.
So that might be it.
The last round.
I'm really distracted by whatever this shush was about.
Well, it was this.
Oh, it was the I almost said.
We didn't want to say what it was.
Oh, I said another seat.
Oh, I thought I was being set up for something.
Shucko was going to come in here.
Jason, I got to spring.
16 more on you.
The smell of Casamico's tequila.
Come on out, Randy.
Quality.
Randy's been in my bathroom for 45 minutes.
Um, so I see what you're saying.
There's maybe an older one left.
But so all right.
What's the what's the context of this in the ride?
I went on Horizons, but I don't have it super memorized.
This is like one of the future paths like the like or the the world of the future that
you could be in involved.
This is where the giant machines are harvesting.
Yeah.
Oranges, correct?
OK.
My memory was as hazy, obviously only from video.
Now, do I fully remember or do I think I remember going on the ride?
It's been so long.
It definitely did.
I mean, I may have.
I think I for sure did.
Yeah, I think this is where my memory is starting to fail me because I kind of had to go like,
oh, yeah, yeah, there was oranges.
So there are people for whom if you if you did get to go on this ride alive,
then the oranges are a huge deal.
I think it's one of the things you like about this, right?
No, this is a very important attraction.
And yeah, that was a very, very memorable thing.
But how do you explain for any listeners who don't know?
Because there's listeners who have horizons memorized and like you don't take time to
explain horizons, but there might be people who do.
How do you explain horizons in a sentence?
I got it.
The thing I've always heard that I think really sums it up best is it's sort of like the next
extension of carousel of progress and the original Epcot project of like this is what
this is what mankind can reach.
This is the future.
This is a ride of like it's a ride about future possibility.
Future possibilities of like if technology were to keep going in a similar direction,
this is where we could be and not dissimilar from Spaceship Earth because it's kind of an
ever moving like like constant ride vehicles.
Yes.
Yeah, it was an omnimover, right?
I mean, it's definitely in the same tradition as the carousel of progress in a way too,
where it's like this is the other part of it.
It's like this is where we came from.
This is where we're going.
You sort of can think of it in that way.
I feel like too.
Didn't I say carousel?
Did you say that?
Yeah.
All right.
Well, I'm losing my mind.
That's the thing I've seen pointed at most.
Now that might also have been part of its undoing of like carousel of progress boring.
We already have it.
We don't need.
Let's make people sick going to space here instead.
That's got to be one of the worst.
I think that's a competition we could have is like worst trades.
We're like from quality of attraction to quality of attraction.
On paper, I get it.
Simulate space flight.
Yeah.
At Disney World.
Using real technology.
Real technology.
I even liked it a couple of times when I wrote it.
As I've gotten older, my brain does not care for it.
Yeah.
No, it's unpleasant.
My whole family got off it last time we wrote and we all needed to take a second.
Was Horizons in such bad shape that they had to get rid of it?
Is that in hindsight a big mistake?
Is it a maintenance issue?
Yeah.
Was it like really like, did it look like shit?
What was the deal?
It might've just been a combination of guest satisfaction and how many people were going on it.
Yeah.
Maintenance.
I wonder.
I think there's a swath of people that is us, and I include myself in this,
that just has nothing but warm glow about that ride and rides like it.
Yeah.
I think it's probably a lot of regular folks who don't go to Disney World all the time who
would go on some of those Epcot rides and go, boring, didn't like it.
But like a journey, like energy though, totally understand.
Yeah.
This one though you watch and you go, well wait a minute, did this need to go?
There's robots, there's cool scenes.
Couldn't this have been updated or something?
I don't know.
That's another episode.
There has to have been a way.
We'll do Horizons.
Honestly, I think if they left Horizons and just re like plussed it up a little,
they would not be having to spend so much money to make a new Epcot,
which is just the spirit of old Epcot.
Yeah.
Like the whole premise of this Epcot redo is just like, hey, Epcot will be like it used to be.
Like Epcot will be good and we fucked up.
Sorry.
Yeah.
But it wasn't one of those that just like, you know, where there's nothing redeemable
and it has to go like living with the land.
It's not one of those where, you know, it's just not, there's nothing there.
It is odd though, living with the land.
Scott Fracken.
Scott Fracken-Garretter.
Living with the land, I guess.
He loves to get rid of that land.
He just loves it.
I am an enemy of.
Enemy of Mother Earth.
Tear it up.
We're alive now.
Time to drill.
Yeah.
That's very funny.
I guess because.
Clearly.
Because of the lab.
Because of the labs, they couldn't get rid of living with the land.
But it does feel like that would have been a quicker thing to go than Horizons with robots.
Anyway, again, another episode.
Yeah.
Okay.
We got to decide between these.
I sense that these orange smells were probably the same.
I think it's possible.
Exactly the same.
So that leaves us to, because we'd have to admittedly not just judge specific.
Right.
The smell itself, because we don't have them in front of us.
So we do have to think about context here.
Do context.
Do you guys know already?
Because I'm not totally sure I do.
I'm not sure I do.
I mean, part of it is I am biased of like, it's not coming to me as well from Horizons.
When I think about these experiences.
But that's also just like, well, how old?
I was the oldest I was when I wrote Horizon.
Maybe 14.
Maybe 13.
So it's just not sticking around with me.
But Soarin', I mean, I guess you see orange grows in both.
But maybe the fact that it's footage versus, you know, illustration or mock-ups.
Is it a mural back there, potentially?
Yeah.
Yeah, I don't want the age bias to factor in.
Because I know this, if we were there in the heyday of Horizons more often, I think we'd
be like, it's Horizons all the way.
I definitely did.
And when it comes back, I do the Soarin' Over California still.
And just, it is an, you get a good waft.
It just hits you all of a sudden.
The wave that hits you is very exciting.
And I associate it with like this probably little move that comes with it.
And a little bit of wind hits you.
I think it's an especially exciting moment of that ride.
Yeah.
And I associate that, you know, that ride was the one thing in the original California
adventure that worked.
And this was one of the aspects of it that worked the best.
So to me, when I think of DCA surviving, I think of this orange smell as a big factor.
Yeah.
I have to say you've swayed me.
I was in the fence a little bit, but that's right.
You have to give it to, because it's really, it's the iconic smell.
Can smells be iconic?
The iconic smell of the ride.
It's the signature smell.
I think it's what everybody like my mom would have, like, you know, she'd go, oh, the orange
smell.
I love when the orange smell happens.
I think a combination of the music cue there, the orange smell, and the sound cue of the
sprinklers.
The sprinklers are going off.
That always sticks with me, too.
Such a refreshing, how relaxed do you feel?
Yeah.
I always say this is the most adult ride.
It's like a wine tour of a ride.
Yes.
But tricks, like tricks, this, I think I get more almost is tricked.
The Imagineers talked about in the Imagining story about like, yeah, when we first like
tested it, then you went over the water scenes, people do lift their feet up instinctively.
Right.
Yeah.
It's so nice.
And I also don't know that it paved the way for some of the other entries on this list.
There probably aren't as many.
They probably don't go crazy with the smells as much as they did in the World One without
this orange one working so well.
Jason, are you ruling?
I'm going to go for Soarin'.
I'm going to go for Soarin' too.
I think that's unanimous.
This is a tough one.
This is no Dis of Horizons.
I think people might be a little mad about this one.
Yeah.
But I don't think it's only bias.
I think it's such a strong moment in California and in theme park history.
I agree.
Do not drag my ass.
Mike, do you want to take the next one?
Oh, God.
Oh, yeah, you don't have to.
It is Skunk Smell from Journey into...
I didn't write it down.
It's a Journey into Imagination with Figmen or Journey into Your Imagination.
They renamed these.
The bad one.
The Figmen ride, the bad one.
And then Chili Dog from Stitch's Great Escape.
This is the full unpleasant bracket.
This is unpleasant versus unpleasant.
It's just a matter of which one works the best.
Which unpleasant thing works the best.
What a terrible category.
It's a really...
Yeah, I'm not looking forward to this.
After a very refreshing one where both entries were great.
Skunk, the part where you get hit with Skunk,
you're already at the point in the ride where you are just so cranky about that ride in the way it is now.
Because the ride used to be great and now it's weird.
Now there's a toilet on the ceiling.
That doesn't make any sense.
What does that have to do with imagination, as Tony Baxter said on podcast, the ride?
Famously.
We all know.
As you famously said the last time.
He famously said it.
And then you get hit with that Skunk and it's just like one insult after another.
And then you get hit.
Then you smell that and it's not full on Skunk, but it's close enough to just make you mad.
That new way that Figman is.
Yeah, that's what I'm gonna do.
Yeah, dream finder.
That's like a more grating Olaf.
Okay, in defense of this, I have heard people say, oh, my family would always like,
we would do that all together.
Everyone could get on it.
No one was too short or anything.
That was a thing.
And Figman is there.
A lot of people have affection for Figman.
He's wearing a jacket now.
He's wearing a jacket.
Well, he always had a sweater sometimes.
He has like a track jacket.
He's got a bunch of outfits.
Yeah, urban outfitters.
And people have affection for Stitch, but I can't say I've ever heard anyone go like,
oh, I love Stitch's great escape.
Even the first once or twice I rode that ride and I was like,
there's little elements of Alien Encounter.
I want this to be good.
Yeah.
I don't think I gotta give this one to the skunk because at least my friend Figman is there.
Well, let me before we make the before we lock anything in,
I have to admit I never did Stitch's great escape.
So I never experienced this chili dog.
I have experienced the skunk and I find it to be terribly unpleasant.
Yeah.
I hear what you're saying, Jason, but and it's hard for me to vote for chili dog,
but this here's what I'm thinking is maybe creativity.
It is like thinking of releasing a skunk smell sort of makes sense.
I feel like that's something that might happen in like a kid book where you smell like a scratch
and like, oh, skunk you.
Yes.
Chili dog is pretty original.
Yeah, it's original to a horrible extent.
Can we explain the context is this is this lesser version of Alien Encounter
where a lot of sound effects and like, you know, things are being dripped on you
and it makes you think a scary alien is right in your face.
Right.
And they redid it in this horrible way where Stitch is released into the room
and he's drooling on you and slobbering on you and just, you know, being a menace.
And do you remember the actual moment when this happens?
I don't remember the moment.
I think it's at the very end, isn't it?
I think so.
I don't know.
Somebody's gonna be mad at us again, but it's something around then.
I just know that he's like slobbering and then you smell his food.
Okay.
Essentially.
Do you remember?
I think it's also let's take some we haven't talked about this audience reaction.
Do you have any strong memory of what made people like yell more?
That's the sign with an unpleasant.
It's a good thing.
A good question.
I mean, yeah, that's a good question.
I did this once and I don't remember much of it.
I vaguely remember this, but I don't remember audience reaction.
I remember my reaction to skunk.
That's really the only reaction of the two.
And I'm always displeased with skunk.
Yeah, I think maybe we shouldn't spend too much more time on this
because there's no way it makes it past the next round.
Yes, it's going to go away.
Go with our.
I just go with chili dog because it's less offensive to me.
Oh, oh, I get that's why I thought you were heading to skunk.
Now I feel like I got to decide.
You are going to have to decide again because I'm going chili because I skunk.
I'm just I'm just upset.
I understand Figman is there, but he's like different.
I like his little track jacket, but I just by the end, it's just so I just I'm so displeased
and I can't.
Unfortunately, I guess I was saying I don't want to bring in some sort of personal bias
and nostalgia, but unfortunately I am.
I can't separate it in this instance.
So the chili dog happens like in the middle of the ride.
He eats a chili dog and burps.
Stitch devours a chili cheese dog and burps accompanied by a foul smell effect being released
into the chamber and destroys a cell phone.
And I understand it's not fair because Alien Encounter was a better ride, too.
But as we know from this podcast, I was too scared to go on that.
Yeah, so my affection for it is lower.
Unfortunately, again, I can't I can't pull personal bias out of it.
It almost feels like less of sacrilege.
That's what I'm getting at.
Only a little, but like to take this like really sweet, shirming dark ride and put skunk smell
all over it.
You know what? I have that creativity point.
I'm breaking the tie.
Chili dog.
Wow.
Yeah.
Now, get ready to fucking eat shit chili dog next time around.
But you're done.
I will let it pass.
I can't believe we created a scenario where we had to vote for the stitch chili dog over
anything else.
I would like to say I think we didn't explain the rules that we would have to
if we didn't unanimously vote what we'd have to have to see out of a tiebreaker.
But I will say, Jason, if you feel very strongly, I would like to give or any of us,
give us the opportunity to stand and filibuster a bit to try to change the other people's
opinion.
I think we should keep moving.
I appreciate it.
All right.
Great.
Yeah, I know.
We're going to appreciate it.
This one is maybe the most pleasant.
Yeah, good.
Perfect.
One of the more pleasant ones.
You want to do it?
Yeah, you.
Yeah, this is I don't quite.
We were calling it the Pandora Forest smell from Flight of Passage.
Also, it's also the tropical island smell from Soarin' Around the World.
We made the decision we're going to call that the same thing.
I do think it's the same thing.
And there's a fragrance or a candle that somebody's making that do lump them together.
Yeah.
And then the Taj Mahal floral smell from Soarin' Around the World.
Yeah, we're debating.
Is it more rose?
Is it more jasmine?
I feel like things are calling it rose, but it's hard to say.
It's a pretty unique one.
That's a really nice moment in the new Soarin'.
Yes.
That music is great.
It's like sitar-y.
Yeah.
It's really cool.
That point.
Soarin' coming out strong in this tournament.
I think it was a guarantee.
There's so much, so many great smells in it.
Pandora Forest, though.
And if we are calling this, is it unfairly
making it like a titan?
Because I also thought, let's talk about the tropical moment in Soarin', which is lovely.
Yes.
That's fantastic.
You're in Fiji, I believe.
Yes.
Oh, it's great.
It could be my favorite smell in Soarin' too.
I think it is.
You could argue that that is the best smell in Soarin' too.
Which almost makes me-
You've already decided then.
That's almost me deciding.
And then you toss in that if it is the same thing in Flight of Passage, does anyone want to argue
whether- are there different smells in Flight of Passage?
Because isn't the cave something different?
Yeah.
I've only done it once, so it's hard to say.
Sure.
The Avatar ride, Flight of Passage, is so good, I don't even register that there are fake smells.
I registered this one because this is one of my favorite fake smells, period.
If a hotel has this kind of smell in the lot, or a store immediately endears it to me.
I'm saying there could just be a couple other fake smells that got shot in there that I wouldn't
notice because I'm like, oh, well, I'm in a cave on the back of the Mighty Akron.
I'm not actually-
Feeling the beast breathe between your legs.
I'm feeling the great beast breathe.
Yeah.
I'm just saying that I don't know how many smells are on there.
Do we just know that we don't always have to take it along?
No, I think we know what it is.
All right, Pandoran Forest.
It has to be.
Moving on.
Yeah.
The other one is really good.
I know.
It's very unique too, which you really should get at points, but unfortunately it has
tied to two really great things.
Some of these initial brackets are pretty unfair, and I think with a different-
Yeah.
There's a version of this where all the last four are sore, I think, but that's not where we're at.
We are now at number six, and that is Ginger in Monsters, Inc., Mike and Sully to the Rescue,
one of the longest ride names in the world.
There is a ginger smell when you go into the sushi restaurant in that ride.
Ginger versus ginger bread in Haunted Mansion Holiday, mainly at Disneyland, also Tokyo,
Disneyland.
There is a gingerbread house every year that changes.
I learned from some holiday special that they do a very different house every year
in the ballroom scene on the table.
That is a real gingerbread house, which I didn't realize until watching this special.
It seems possible that that is a contrived plastic thing, but it is in fact edible,
and they do a very good job with it.
Ginger versus gingerbread.
Well, Monsters, Inc. is a weird ride because it's pretty good.
It's obviously reskinned superstar limo, but it is pretty good, and it's a fun thing.
I don't go on it a lot.
It's like the placement of it is weird.
If it's anything over five minutes, I go, I'm not waiting for this.
It's sort of not fair to it because this scene is really nice, the ginger,
whether they go into the sushi place.
Very fun scene, this sort of madcap, she's hiding under the takeout boxes.
I don't know what it is when I'm in that corner of California Adventure when it's like,
oh, you want to go to Monsters, Inc.
I go, nah.
If I think about it, I think it has to do with that area.
It has to do with that queue.
So industrial.
I think it's a similar thing to what we were saying on the Living with the Land episode,
where I think that the area around it influences it unfairly.
It's a great option if you get to the paradox of crowds at California Adventure,
because sometimes you can be in the middle of California Adventure and it's a busy day
and everything is a burden.
All the food is long.
All the rides are long.
And there's like two or three things you can do there.
It's happened to me during spring break.
This was like, well, I came all the way down here.
I'm getting on a ride and I got on this ride.
Right.
I do think it's like kind of got flats outside.
But when I'm thinking about this scene, it's really good.
It's a really, as we just said, it's really fun.
And then they decided to go with ginger over the fake fish smell they could have used.
It's probably for the best.
Probably for the best.
Sushi restaurants don't really smell super like fish, I don't think.
Right.
Depending.
Yeah.
I guess if it's so stacked with like fresh fish.
If you're doing the whole like table thing where the sushi chef is making it for you
while you sit at the bar.
I'll say this, though.
You notice the smell.
I don't think I could have called it out as ginger specifically.
I agree with that.
I think when I read, oh yeah, when I was reading up on smells and it was like, oh,
ginger in that area.
I go, oh, that is ginger.
That's really smart.
That's really original.
I think that's a nice feeling, but I think it's a feeling that doesn't take you all the way
to the end in this tournament.
I agree with this.
I think this in another category is a bit of a sleeper.
I truly really think this is a nice subtle thing because I think you have to award subtlety
in certain ways for just slightly adding to it, but not calling so much attention to it,
which I think is tasteful.
It's a tasteful little addition to this already fun scene.
Yeah.
Gingerbread, the gingerbread house can be overwhelming if you hit it at the right thing.
Points dock to for the presence of actual gingerbread.
Why would you say that?
Well, because it's the item.
It's the actual item.
I don't think that's the smell is not coming from that though.
It's added to it.
Yeah, it's added in, but I'm a little skeptical.
This is an interesting thing with you.
We have only a scratch of service on this.
You don't like it if the actual item is anywhere present.
I like it, but in the context of this tournament,
there's some very nice essence makers.
There's some very nice scent makers who had to work very hard.
Right.
I know that, but I'm saying, and I think we'll talk about it once we're done with this first bracket,
is that if something's around, you don't think it's as impressive if it's possibly partly real.
I'm just verbalizing my thought process on how you pick a victor.
The smell you're smelling is entirely a contrived smell.
I do not think you are smelling that house.
Yes, I think for sure.
I think you're going to be right next to a gingerbread house to smell the gingerbread.
I mean, they make some pretty big ones at the hotels and those smell, but yes.
You can't smell it from across the lobby.
I don't think so.
Do you disagree?
I can't really remember.
You walk into Grand Californian, can you smell the gingerbread house?
I feel like sometimes.
Could they be fake smelling you in the Grand Californian?
They might be.
They're working me.
Yeah, maybe.
They're working you with the smell.
Hotels definitely pump in scents.
The most egregious being the Universal Sheraton, the Universal City has one of the most aggressive.
The Universal Hilton has no scent and the Universal Sheraton has a very potent fragrance.
I didn't notice that when I was drinking alone there several weeks ago.
But if you go, if you walk in looking for you'll find it.
It dissipates when you get towards like the rooms, but it's a little much.
Smell in a telly.
That's telly, baby.
That's the smell.
It's been 25 years.
The smell remains.
Telly.
The smell of robe and bald head oil.
Bald head oil.
Keep it nice and oily, baby.
Ooh, lozier scent to air.
I don't know, Mike, you may have unintentionally swayed my vote though with the subtle day note.
You're allowed to vote however you want.
I might have to toss mine to Ginger.
Okay.
Monster Zinc.
Monster Zinc tics.
I think I'll be in the minority.
The reason I made that point is because this is probably my favorite part of Haunted Mansion Holiday.
When you go into this room and you smell the gingerbread and you see the house,
it's new every year.
It's not the craziest impressive thing.
I find it very charming.
I love the smell of gingerbread.
In any other category, Ginger maybe gets a little sleeper room, but not here because I gotta go
gingerbread.
I love this scene in Haunted Mansion Holiday.
Gingerbread from me as well.
And you know what?
I think this ride needs the support because lately a lot of hatin' on Haunted Mansion Holiday and I
don't understand it.
I could see the point of starting it later, but I think that is
morphed into this monster of it's bad and they shouldn't do it.
Fuck that.
I really like Haunted Mansion Holiday.
We can talk timeline, but it's great.
That's insane to say you don't want it to be done at all.
I've said this before.
Of course, I would.
Yes, if we could do it for two months, great.
The thing is you can't argue with the crowds.
The thing is double the line of normal Haunted Mansion for the five months that it exists.
It's obviously more popular than the regular one.
So if it's like four or five months though, you're about almost getting the same.
If you consider like downtime, it's probably pretty close.
Maybe you get an extra month of regular Haunted Mansion.
I'm just picturing us standing outside and hearing that music that plays outside.
I love it so much.
That little loop, that twinkly, scary, demented kind of.
I think actually, even more so than just the Haunted Mansion,
the Nightmare Before Christmas theming, I think it might be an excuse or a reason
or a justification for going into the Haunted Mansion and really plusing it up.
Because it does feel fresher because it's newer stuff.
Part of it.
I do think that might be part of it.
I know I've said this many times, but that Midsummer Scream panel
where Tony Baxter was advocating, go in there and really do it up.
That's kind of the feel.
You end up like, I'm looking at something from 2019.
Why did I say 2019?
I don't know.
Last time I was there, probably.
People are going to think we recorded this in 2019 though.
Or really back loading.
Yeah, you're seeing more modern stuff in there and I don't know.
Well, be careful with that though because some of the 2000s added in stuff is not aging well.
Like the Pride Projection.
That's the test.
That's not in well.
But I feel like we are in more of a time where the projection has gotten a lot better
and the people are favoring practical effects.
Do you like Hatbox Ghost still?
I love Hatbox Ghost.
There you go.
That's a good way to judge it.
He's lasted five years and there's no sign of him looking dated.
2010s.
Oh, sure, yeah.
But we'll get to his room probably in 2022.
On our yes or anywhere Haunted Halloween.
You think that's a little too early.
Jason might be right.
Well, I liked that.
Yeah, let's get to it.
Let's get to it.
So this is what we're almost it's almost been an hour.
We haven't said all of them.
I think I think Mike, you're up.
You're up next.
Is that me?
I believe so.
Okay, we are going to be doing one very iconic one and one less.
Like equally iconic.
Equal iconic.
Okay, we're going to do Banana Breath from.
Well, two.
King Kongs.
Banana Breath.
Both Kongs and then a which we determined before we started.
Fart gun banana smell from Despicable Me Minion Mayhem.
Yes.
Universal Studio.
So let's explain this and I'll say this.
We're going to post along with this concurrently over on the second gate behind the paywall.
Patreon.com podcast, the ride we were we were discussing some of these issues of what was
going to be in the final 16 and we broke off a little fragment and recorded it because there
was an issue I really wanted discussed on Mike and I'm glad we did it.
Yeah, the issue is that we originally had a category that was fart versus fart and I
don't want to repeat things that we said over there.
Please listen to our important fart versus fart conversation.
That's a little bonus for the Patreon subscribers.
But what that was was fart in Shrek 4D and fart in Despicable Me Minion Mayhem.
And then I started thinking, wait a minute, I don't I'm not confident that there was a
fart smell in Shrek 4D.
No, we just talked about farts so much with Griffin Newman.
It felt very possible that there could have been.
I didn't blink when that was put on the list.
Like, of course, and fart versus fart.
We got to do that.
Then I was like, but is there a fart?
I'm not totally sure.
And then in this case, Fart and Despicable Me, I was like, let me remind myself.
What that part is, and it's in the line.
It's in the pre show and Gru is threatening to blast you, his guests with a fart gun.
Yeah, but then once blasted, I noticed the audience did not scream and recoil that.
And that is because the minions got in there and they rewired everything.
And it's instead of banana smell.
Yeah, gives an excuse for the minions to yell banana a whole bunch.
One of their favorite things.
Several excuses to do this.
So the fart gun in Despicable Me Minion Man is technically a banana smell.
And we thought, well, then doesn't it have to go up against the banana breath?
Right.
We've had orange versus orange and now banana versus banana.
And as with the oranges, probably the same smell.
I think so.
Probably the same.
Actual the same chemical makeup of these smells.
But one was a trailblazer, you know?
I mean, this, I think I don't think we got to labor around this.
I like minion mayhem.
I think it's fun.
And I think it's good.
If I was a kid, I love it.
I would love it.
Absolutely.
But we don't need to labor over this.
This is what have convoluted.
What do you mean?
It's a fart gun and then it's banana.
So confusing.
The clear less confusing thing is your tram is getting attacked by King Kong,
who ate approximately 2000 bananas enough to make his old breath smell like bananas.
And you have to also credit it because it may be an argument, whatever it goes up against,
the fact that it's like referred to and that I can attest as a tour guide that it gets a laugh when
you refer to it because people might kind of notice it, but then saying like, hey, get a load of that
banana breath.
And you watch everybody go, oh, that's right.
It just gives people so much joy that that is there.
So yeah, it has to be.
Fuck you, fart gun.
Get out of here.
And for confusing us, making us have a sidebar conversation that's very essential that you can
listen to at pitia.com slash pockets ride.
Get out of here.
You're out.
Banana breath it is.
Has to be.
And Jason, does that make you read the final?
The final round.
This is the toughest one for me.
I will say this is strange.
You're going to see here that we sort of we try to make these
understandable pairings and then we kind of ran out of ways to justify.
Again, they all couldn't be perfect and they all couldn't be a hundred percent pleasant.
And I think it's good.
There are some oddballs.
This is the might be the oddest one of all.
Roam burning from spaceship Earth versus Maggie's mouth from the Simpsons ride.
Maggie's mouth smells like baby powder, which is odd because mouse.
That's not where baby powder goes.
That's not what mouse smell like.
Not really.
No.
And even though her mouth and her big what's the thing that dangles in your mouth?
Pacify.
Oh, no.
Uvula.
The body part.
The uvula.
It looks big and plastic.
You punch a plastic one on the way into the ride on crusty.
Yes.
But it's not plastic.
It's yeah, that's that's human.
It's the human body.
Yeah, I guess it I don't know.
Maybe something would smell kind of.
She's probably like sucking a lot.
She's the pacifier.
Toys and such.
But yeah, that's fun.
This is a late cut.
Weird.
This is a last minute addition, I think, to our list because that is fun.
That's it is fun.
And you could say, OK, we could we could.
There's a little bit of a leap in logic of like, well, she's a baby.
She smells like baby powder a little bit.
She just was freshly powdered before she grows giant at the end of the Simpson ride.
Yeah.
Thus, each powder molecule also grew.
Exactly.
You could like those are all the sizes of boulders.
Right.
Because that makes that actually makes a lot of sense because the whole town then
would eventually smell like it.
All those molecules burped correctly.
Yeah, they would all tumble down the Springfield Hill.
Crush everyone down below.
Yes.
And then you get to Rome burning, which I would say
Rome burning is in the same category of smells as ginger is.
It's a little stronger than ginger for sure.
It could have been against each other.
But ginger gingerbread was too good.
Too good.
The name is the same.
Yeah, it's the same letters in the same order.
So yeah, and this one's again, a stronger smell, but another sort of subtle smell
that's just supposed to like ease you into the era and what's happening.
And Rome is burning and you're smelling like, I don't know, how would you describe it?
It's like burning wood parchment kind of crack.
It feels really like books.
Isn't that what it actually is portraying is like information is the library of Alexandria.
Yeah, yeah, it's going knowledge is being destroyed.
Luckily, the scribes, there were scribes who kept the records.
There was an Arabic scholars.
Yes, sacred Jedi texts.
Sacred Jedi texts.
It's like really wonderful atmosphere.
It is.
Yeah, this ride, it leaps out at you.
And it's going to be great when a little Olaf is there too.
They redo this ride and like.
Getting a note.
I'm writing the words down too with the scribes.
My arms are burning.
I Lord Rick Moran is out of retirement.
Titans.
Follow me.
Yeah, I mean, it's such a neat.
It's a neat moment when you, you know, in trying to think of candidates for this,
when you Google favorite Disney smells, this is always on there.
Yeah.
People love it.
And it does maybe feel more to me like in a like a strong,
like a thing you leave the ride talking about, maybe then Maggie,
which is a more subtle detail like the ginger.
Maybe that should have been paired.
I mean, I'm thinking that now.
Yes, that would have been a good.
Which ones?
Ginger paired with this one because they're both Maggie's mouth subtle.
They're more subtle smells that like really make it like fill out the mood and the vibe
as opposed to being like, oh, wow, you got a blast of some sort of smell that that sort of takes over.
So yeah, we could have done that.
Look, is this going to be perfect?
No, look, it's not going to be perfect.
It's not how the game played out this year.
Yeah, maybe next year.
I feel like this one's unanimous.
Probably probably room burning room burning.
Ah, not Michael.
What?
Maggie's mouth.
Whoa.
Would you like to try to convince anybody over to you?
I think that I can't divorce myself from that moment when Maggie uses your vehicle like a pacifier.
It's so fun to me.
If you don't know what I'm talking about, she puts the vehicle in her mouth.
She sucks on the vehicle like a pacifier and it's a big blast of baby powder.
And I don't know, that just sticks out to me as one of that.
Right.
Is a lot of crap going on.
Some might argue too much crap, but that's maybe my favorite part of that ride.
And it's such a big part of it is you're waiting for that smell.
And yeah, I have to go with it, unfortunately, over room burning, which I like as well.
I don't think anything.
I don't think I appreciate the passion.
Yeah, passion defense.
And there's no, I don't think there's anything you can pull away from room burning, which is,
I don't think there's any counter argument.
No, I mean, look, the problem is I can't, I could never speak bad of Spaceship Earth's room burning scene.
I would never, I all it's a, yes, it's a subtle thing and it's like the vibe of going up that slow,
in the best way, boring ride.
I can't, I can't even think of a thing to say bad about it.
Yeah, yeah.
It's just a personal choice.
Well, we now have our choice and I'm sticking with it.
So the next round will be Evergreen Forest from ET Adventure versus Vanilla and Waffles on Main Street.
The Orange Grove in Soarin' versus the Chili Dog in Stitch's Great Escape.
Pandorin Forest versus Gingerbread from Haunted Mansion Holiday.
And King Kong's Banana Breath versus Roam Burning from Spaceship Earth.
Some tough choices coming out, fellas.
It's going to be tough.
Let's, let's step away from it.
Maybe not for too long.
Yeah.
Going a while.
But do you want to talk about what didn't make the cut or what barely got pulled out?
There were a couple things.
I mean, we also talked about like, I love the smell of, we talked about hotel lobbies, the Polynesian lobby.
Oh, of course.
It's a fantastic smell.
But we really tried to say like we wanted the smell, the fake smell to be something very specific versus maybe just a general pleasant scent.
Yeah.
Hotel lobby fragrances, I feel like are their own category.
I think so.
Yeah.
But no knock on that.
I'd almost rather that be in there than Stitch.
But we are where we are.
I threw out the idea of fried chicken, which you can smell at various places in Disneyland.
Also, was there a fried chicken smell at Doc Brown's outside?
Possibly.
I believe so.
So that's the vague.
This is the argument.
You convinced me on the gingerbread.
I think the fried chicken that you can smell on Main Street, I think they are ventilating the kitchen.
Like I think they are.
I think you are being naive.
I think you're being naive.
Then call me naive, if you will.
I think they're frying chicken there like a million hours a day.
The argument.
It's got to go somewhere.
The argument that we had is that we smelled fried chicken over by Tomorrowland.
The kit, it butts up.
The kitchen.
It doesn't.
We looked up.
I looked at an overhead view of the kitchen and there's like a couple buildings apart.
It wasn't butting up to like PizzaPlanet or PizzaPorter or whatever the hell it's called now.
I think it was like there were two buildings across.
But was it just once you smelled this or can you always smell this?
I've never noticed this before.
I smelled it once.
Maybe I've smelled it.
I feel like I've smelled it since.
So I don't know.
It's possible.
I don't know for sure.
Let us know.
Let us know if you have the answer.
I will say when you brought up, I was like, oh, I guess you can smell fried chicken on Main Street.
To me, it wasn't nearly the same as the candy, the ice cream.
Yeah.
For sure.
It was more of, oh, I guess if I think about it, it didn't seem like so iconic.
Lindsay is now confirming the smell.
But it was the argument we were having is just, is it real or fake?
In my argument, there was fake because there weren't.
Yes.
Lindsay is saying we were by the Tomorrowland.
We were by like Star Traders.
But there's no chicken.
They aren't selling any chicken around there.
Why are we smelling chicken?
That's my argument.
To make you want it elsewhere?
Yes.
It's just using just good smells will make you hungry.
Just smells in general.
Just smells like that will make you hungry in general.
But there's a place that does barbecue on Saturdays in Burbank, like in the parking lot of a grocery
store, they have a big smoker and you can smell that a block away.
That's true.
Yeah.
But that's, I think it's positive.
It could be a waft.
I don't think Jason's insane here.
I don't know.
I looked at an overhead map of where it would have to have been coming from.
I think that's a city block.
I don't think that's more than a city block.
I think that's equidistant.
Yeah.
But that's outside.
They were doing it in a parking lot or they were doing it?
See, the parking lot's open air.
That's true.
It's like-
Again, if you have industrial fryers cooking chicken for 12 hours plus a day.
I think though the fact that I don't always smell it is an argument in my favor.
Not enough people ordering chicken.
I think it's an argument not in the favor of being on the list because if this is a
thing that only you sometimes smell and it wasn't familiar to me.
Well, that's fair.
Or Jason.
Jason, does that sound familiar to you?
Well, I've smelled it around there, but I've eaten that fried chicken a lot.
So I don't know.
Maybe I've been fooled.
That's fine.
It's always on your brain.
It's always on the brain for you.
I don't want to ignore that I just said I smelled it.
I know.
We're not talking about you.
It's not the-
Email, air-free.
We're not arguing that the smell wasn't smelled.
We're arguing if the smell was real or fake.
Here we go.
That's what we're arguing about.
I just don't think it's a top 16 contender is what I-
Did it make it this year?
I agree with that.
Not this year.
Phil Our Magic got dissed.
There's pie and there's champagne.
I know.
And we just didn't- we were Heming and Han on those.
I don't think we got the full extent of the attraction here in California.
Yeah, that might be California advice.
I caught the pie a little.
Florida Erasure.
I can't catch the champagne.
We also dissed Stink Bug in It's Tough to Be a Bug.
Right.
Could have gone alongside either- maybe could have beaten Stitch or the Skunk.
But I don't know.
I don't do not like It's Tough to Be a Bug.
Yeah, I'm not a big fan.
I don't like being poked in the back.
I don't hate it.
Yeah, to me it's a torture read.
What else do we- I think that's mainly what we- I feel like something else came off.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Listener, let us know if there was anything you really liked that you thought should be on here.
Probably one staring us smack in the face and we can't see it.
There might be.
Can't smell it.
Or we're wrong about wafting us right in the face.
All right then.
Well, round two we head into.
And match of number one, the E.T. Evergreen Forest versus Vanilla and Waffles on Main Street.
God damn it.
Ooh, both atmospheric, both very pleasant, fond memories associated with both.
Oh man.
Man, this is- God, I don't know how it could be harder than this one.
Honestly.
Here's that himming and hawing.
Yeah.
Really mentally constipated.
Mm-hmm.
I want to start thinking about this.
Dip a toe in the water of an argument.
Here's the thing.
Okay.
E.T. Forest smell.
I will say this about it.
One of the best things about it is I think that it simulates the things we were talking about,
whether on purpose or accidentally, when we talk about pirates or haunted mansion, natural smell.
There's some element of that forest smell that to me feels like accidental.
It smells like pirates water to me.
I don't know what it is.
I don't know if it's the nostalgia that's really infecting in my brain,
or it's some weird off chemical because it's old.
I don't know what it is.
Do you know what I'm saying?
There was a time where I thought it was a little accidental.
And it seems like a cousin of theme park water.
Yes.
But I guess how could it be?
There's no water in there.
There's no real nature in there.
There's fog.
Right.
Maybe the fog.
A little bit.
But the fog is a fake thing too.
But I don't think enough that they need to
jack it up with bromine, which is a lot of what you're smelling in the pirates
combination of water and bromine.
Right.
So you have to give it some points for that because out of all these smells,
it's giving me that same vibe as the pirates water, which is hard to beat.
So I do have to put one extra point on its board, so to speak.
You feel like you're representing theme park water by choosing a fake smell.
And it gives me it's an extra.
I don't know what it is about it.
It gives it an extra little edge when I'm just thinking out loud about it.
It's hard, though, because again, that Main Street smell.
I don't know if Main Street's the same without it.
I don't know.
Oh, that's a heavy thought.
Main Street works as well without that fun smell of candy and waffles and ice cream.
And we are talking about a smell that is being smelled somewhere in the world every day,
constantly by everyone, as opposed to the ET Adventure, which sadly is closed in a lot of
places, that if you are a theme park fan, ET Adventure is one of your top three things.
If you're a regular person, you might not care about this ride or the smell.
Right.
But obviously we're theme park fans.
Our listeners are theme park fans.
And I mean, we look, I put over the whole experience with ET and everything from the forest,
but it is also like without botanicus, does this hold up as well?
We're talking about holding up.
Sometimes he's not there.
The smell is broken and the smells there and it smells still fantastic.
Consistency, though.
And atmosphere.
Reliable.
I don't know what I'm going to do here.
I think the uniqueness.
This is a tight one.
I think the uniqueness will give it to ET for me because sometimes I do not want to
necessarily smell ice cream, contrary to popular belief.
Sometimes if I had a big meal or like I'm feeling like groggy and they're at Disneyland,
the last thing I want to be blasted with like super sweet smells.
Interesting.
I've never really thought about that in like, oh, stop this stupid smell.
It's sort of like maybe is it like a sickeningly sweet.
Hey, should we have included?
I know what I remember what we didn't do with the fucking the bathroom with all the giggling
in Harry Potter.
Oh yeah.
What is the smell in there?
Bubble gum, isn't it?
Oh, is that supposed to be?
I just assumed that was what it was.
I didn't realize that.
Am I wrong?
You might be right.
When I was Googling it, I was like, nobody seems strongly.
I don't know.
Fuck it.
It's not on.
No reason to go back there.
Island of Adventure has started doing more thematic bathroom scents in the bathrooms.
I remember that as a news story.
So maybe you are right, but that's just a whole different final four.
Yeah, bathroom scents.
We could do it in general.
We also didn't get, you know, I want to say we didn't put on any Galaxy's Edge and I
think there are some great smells in Galaxy's Edge, but I don't think any of them have the edge.
There isn't the one that's like that.
But I think they did a great job.
Similar Disney Sea.
I think you can attest.
Good smells all over Disney Sea, but there isn't the one maybe.
I would just say they did a great job throughout.
Journey to the center of the earth.
There's a really good smell in that elevator.
And the way that smells might be going in theme parks is what I'm saying with the subtlety.
So perhaps there again, there are subtlety, subtle smells that somebody will point out for us and go,
oh, wow, I didn't even notice that it perfectly makes the mood.
I didn't even realize because it wasn't hitting it hitting you in the face so hard.
Yeah.
But with this, with what made it Mike, do you want to lock it in?
Did you lock yours in?
I haven't locked in.
Should I?
I'm locking in ET.
You're locking in ET.
Okay.
More you need too.
The burden.
You can go to ice cream parlors and get a hit and get a little hit.
And sometimes the real deal.
That's true.
It is a lot less unique.
I agree.
All right.
Fine.
ET.
It was ET for me.
I just wanted to build the drama.
It's ET.
It's the evergreen forest.
I'm not happy about it, honestly.
Mike, I believe you read the next one.
Okay.
We are down.
We are here.
This is Soren over California.
Orange smell versus chili dog from Stitch's Great Escape.
And orange moves on, right?
It moves on.
Yeah.
No question there.
In a long episode, we could save a little time.
Number three of round two.
Jason.
We've got the Pandoran Forest tropical smell
from Flight of Passage versus the gingerbread smell
from Haunted Mansion Holiday.
It's tough, too.
Again, I don't think Haunted Mansion Holiday,
even though I do like it, is going to top a favorite smell of mine.
So I'm giving mine to Pandora.
Okay.
This one is interesting.
This one's a little tougher for me.
This is interesting.
Okay.
Because obviously we've gone over this.
Whatever the actual physical smell is,
it's on two things that we really like for the Pandoran Forest smell, we'll call it.
Yeah.
And then gingerbread.
Obviously, Jason's mad that it has a real gingerbread house.
He's docking at points, I assume.
No, I just like the you have sold me a little more that,
yeah, obviously they have to shoot gingerbread at you to really sell the picture.
They're shooting it at you.
I just like the first one.
I find the first one so relaxing and so pleasant.
And it is.
I'm giving it the edge.
It's fantastic.
Look, they wouldn't be here if they weren't fantastic.
Of course.
We wanted to say that these are all good fake smells.
We don't want to knock any fake smell that's on this list.
They all belong here.
I do.
It's such a pleasant smell that Fiji thing is so pleasant.
It's tranquility.
It's truly like the smell of tranquility, which God knows we all need a little tranquility.
You're going full Don Draper with this one.
Yeah.
I'm just trying to I'm working it out in my head now.
We didn't plan this out.
Paracel.
It's you know, I haven't been to Fiji and I certainly haven't been to Pandora.
Right.
And it gives you a little taste of gives you really nice.
It's really lovely.
But I fucking love that gingerbread room.
And I think I'm going to have to give it to the gingerbread room.
Oh, boy.
Oh, it's on me now.
There's something about it.
I look forward again.
All of it's I mean, you know what?
I talked a big game about subtlety, but all this stuff which hits me in the face with
a big broad smell, that's the stuff I seem to like.
So when I'm running the corner and I go, we're getting the gingerbread,
I get real excited about it and I got to go gingerbread here.
I really like that the gingerbread smell.
I definitely do.
I think, though, that that is that is in one attraction as opposed to what
maybe unfairly is unfair.
There's been a gerrymandering here of two attractions.
But if we're taking into account guest enjoyment and Soren over the world and Pandora,
that's three different.
Oh, sorens in Japan, too.
It's let me just let me just go there in my imagination.
I mean, that shimmer and why I'm almost thinking of it more for Soren
than Pandora, which is again, because I've been on that more and just that shimmering water,
that music is the sound of the water, too.
You can hear gentle waves lapping.
Think of when you go on a mansion holiday and it's around Christmas and there's a festive
vibe in the air and you get that gingerbread, which honestly still is one of the most festive
smells.
It really suggests to you the holiday.
Gingerbread's not on the list for me for cookies.
Really?
Because that makes sense to me.
Chocolate chip, sugar, oatmeal, peanut butter.
I might be five.
I might be more aesthetically into gingerbread than.
Well, that's what I'd argue.
I would argue that it's not maybe my in my top five cookies.
Well, then we're talking building material.
But the smell gingerbread is such a festive holiday smell.
I think I like gingerbread more than gingerbread cookies.
Like actual bread?
A slice of gingerbread.
Yeah, I don't know that I've ever had a slice of gingerbread.
Maybe I haven't either.
I don't even know what that is.
I am going to go with Pandoran Forest.
I keep playing a tiebreaker and I keep messing with you, Mike.
That's all right.
Yeah.
Ken, these are all great smells.
We don't want to knock any of the smells.
I remember being very excited going on a flight of passage and realizing,
oh, it's that smell or a smell similar to that.
So I get to not knowing what was coming, going like, oh, it's going to smell like this for a little while.
Hell, yeah.
It's a great smell.
The unobtainium of smells.
I can't smell.
I'm already very fond of.
Sure.
This one's brutal.
Yeah, but this one is easy, isn't it?
I don't know.
It is.
To me, it is.
We're talking King Kong's Banana Breath versus Rome Burning and Spish of Earth.
Two innovators.
Two early 80s.
This is the 80s representing.
Yeah.
Go, go 80s here.
I like that.
This feels just a very analog time.
Disney versus Universal.
For the ages.
Fought for in our nasal cavities.
I have to take personal bias out of it.
What a victorious summer it was for me when I was facing having to work at one of several movie
theaters and clean bathrooms essentially.
And instead I got the dream job, the dream job of a lifetime.
I was very happy early 20 something.
King Kong's Banana Breath smelling that every day is when I felt the most alive.
I don't want to be going all fast times at Ridgemont High here.
I'm fondly recalling that King Kong's Banana Breath is my dazed and confused.
For me, it's not the smell of weed.
It's the smell of banana breath.
Putting your earbuds in on your break.
Just hearing those.
I'm not a console, but I'm not a soldier.
I've got soul.
Is there any saying that because that was a hit of the time?
Is that right?
I think that's around then.
Am I wrong?
Hot fuss?
No, that was on Sam's.
I mean, that takes me back to the glory days of Southland Tales.
Isn't that hot?
It was quite a time.
Southland Tales was number one at the box office.
2004.
King Kong was number one on the theme park charts.
And Scott Gardner was cruising to adult happiness.
2004.
So kind of a clap going back, oh, something from a few years ago.
Yeah, it sounds good.
OK.
Rumburg spaceship art.
This is an important smell.
This is an important smell to people.
This feels like one that could go all the way.
This, I think, heightens a theatrical presentation.
I'll say this against Kong's banana breath.
That's that's a gag, right?
That's a gag.
Like King Kong eats anything.
And yeah, you're making.
Yeah, he's eaten that many bananas that his breath smells like banana.
But we're making fun of the car.
It's true.
Right.
But room burning.
It's a bit of drama of high drama.
The burning of the library at Alexandria.
You know, the fall of Rome.
This is humanity.
This is history.
We're carrying the record.
It's that we're talking about the written record being destroyed
and the smell record preserving the record of records being destroyed.
This doesn't go anywhere in the change.
Like in the in the in the plus in the redo of spatial
worth that they're talking about doing.
No way this is taken out.
It doesn't feel possible.
Yeah.
And it's atmospheric and it's a type of smell.
They're good.
Like chaos smell like smoky.
That's what I'm talking about that I like in Galaxy's Edge
and I like in journey to the center of the earth.
These these kind of musty smoky things are bad.
You know, it's another real smell we can include is like
pyro and the smell of the Indiana Jones stunt show.
And maybe this is the way to represent the smoky sector.
Right.
This yes, this is yes, there's a whole genre of smoky smells.
Some on purpose, some not.
I mean, yeah, it's done shows in like phantasmic.
There's fire pyro water stuff.
Gunpowder.
Yeah, gunpowder.
I wonder.
Yeah, I wonder.
There's probably places we haven't even considered.
And this is a good representation of it.
But that big monkey is so fun.
And unfortunately, I've learned something about myself in this
whole thing is that I'm not a subtle guy.
I'm not a guy who likes subtlety as much as I wish I did.
And this Kong, it's a big fun.
I don't know if you call it body, but it's a gag.
And I have to go with Kong.
Well, I certainly wouldn't call it body.
He does not have breasts.
He's not wearing his underwear.
Yeah, you're right.
Is body always sexual?
I think so.
Let me look at the definition of body.
It's always sexual.
Your use of body.
It's a whole.
We don't have time to get into it.
I would do an entire episode.
Yeah, it is.
So long just because this is it's.
I meant I should just say crude.
I should have said crude.
Yeah, you think this is crude?
Well, he's he's burping.
He's burping.
He's letting you smell his impolite.
Yeah, it's impolite.
It's the most prudish opinion.
Yeah, it's reminding us of when we used to be wild animals.
The forest.
King Kong is crude.
King Kong is crude because he's letting us smell his breath.
King K rule.
That guy's really rude.
You're locked in.
I'm locked in with Kong.
Yes, I'm going to lock in with room burning.
Oh, man.
On me again.
Yeah, and of course, I'm turned off by the crudeness.
Yeah, my bow tie has been spinning the whole time.
We've been talking about.
Yeah, the only crude I would hear about is that family of prehistoric guys who get out to mischief.
The crude, the crude.
Oh, oh, I really liked Rome burning on Spaceship Earth.
I kind of forgot that detail.
Spaceship Earth is maybe the ride I went on the most on our trip recently.
I think I did it three times.
It's really great.
That is a really wonderful moment.
It is.
Yeah, Scott scratching his head.
He's making he's grimacing at the moment.
I think this is the toughest choice I've had to make.
Interesting.
Understand.
The rest have all been.
Say what's in your heart or your gut.
Either one.
Those might be different things.
They might be different things.
This is an easy.
Banana breath.
It's banana breath.
It has to be.
I got to go with I've been going against you.
My I don't want to for the third time.
You don't have to go.
That has to be that has to be a consideration.
It's not just that.
It's not even just the personal.
I just love that.
It's like it's I think it's iconic because I agree it's referred to.
And we had we just talked about confrontation.
It factors into that.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Rome Burnham.
Sorry, Spaceship Earth.
I'm a big fan of Spaceship Earth.
Well, we've got a final four.
We've got a final four.
You know, I might have my my brackets wrong.
How are you seeing the versus what I'm seeing?
E.T.
Forest versus Orange from Soren.
Oh, yeah, that's what I have.
Tay and then Pandora Forest versus banana breath.
I really like the last four.
I really like it.
These are good.
Is that too?
Yeah, it is.
It's two Disney's and two universals.
Yeah, yeah, pretty good.
Two forests.
Yeah, forests and two fruits.
Yeah, unfortunately, it's too bad.
It's not forest versus forest and orange versus banana.
That would be perfect.
Us being like really just sweaty like, God, I can't.
I don't know.
Orange versus banana.
We will have to get there.
I like it.
I think we should just be proud of where we are.
Yeah, we should.
We've done a lot of hard stuff today.
We've had to make a lot of hard decisions.
Yeah.
So evergreen forest versus oof.
This is this is tough.
Soren Orange is yes is really, really fantastic.
These are and it's such a I'll say this.
OK, so I guess we're in in it already.
Forrest E.T.
Forrest Evergreen Forest versus oranges from Soren.
Soren Orange is smell so much like a perfect version of an orange.
I know it's fake, but it really like they nail it in a way that almost none of these
smells do or it smells like the perfect version of like they've just ripped open a hundred
oranges and you're smelling the perfect version of them.
Yeah, like it's such a good fake smell.
This is such a good.
This is not air freshener.
This is like this isn't just a well deployed smell you smelled before.
I think this is top tier.
Yes, like juicy, dewy oranges.
Yes, whatever they're doing, whatever they're pumping into our nasal cavities,
it's really triggering the right things in our brain.
You can also just go to Camarillo.
Well, sure, you can go to Camarillo.
I think it's easy.
I mean, you can get a really good orange if you pick the right time of year to go to Trader Joe's.
I agree with what you're saying, but I'm saying this is almost a supercharged heightened version.
It's an ideal.
Yes, an idealized smell.
And I'm saying they do that better than almost any of the other smells,
idealized smell, maybe other than gingerbread.
I might almost say pure quality.
If we're talking smell only between these four, this might be the best.
Context free smell.
Yes, I would agree with that, I think, because the forest one is good, but it's.
But where else can you get that?
I hear what you're saying.
Where else can you get that ET smell?
But it's not.
The forest?
Anywhere, but that.
That crisp.
That kind of, kind of inside, kind of musty.
But you can't quite describe it, which is both good and bad.
I'm saying when you're talking about pure smell, just the smell on its nose,
whatever you would say, this one, you describe it.
You could truly, you could explain it to someone else and you could convey what it is,
which I think is a strength of it.
I think that there it would be hard to convey forest and ET and botanicals to someone who has
not been there and you could explain to somebody the orange and they would go,
oh, I know exactly what that is and I know exactly why you like it.
Does that make it less special?
I'm not saying it doesn't make it less special, but I'm saying that
that the forest one is nostalgia plays into it, the mood plays into it.
And right now we're talking just smell alone.
We're talking, we're just trying to piece together here.
We're trying to deconstruct here.
So we're just talking about smell alone.
It's possible that context or that nostalgia is nostalgia and context.
They're too tied together.
As Scott was saying, if we have to analyze just smell alone,
this orange is such a pure awesome version.
Wait, do we have to just analyze smell alone?
We don't.
I'm just saying we're deconstructing here.
We're deconstructing here.
I don't know that I like the smell of citrus that much.
Really?
So the citrus is fantastic.
Yeah, no, I do like it.
But you don't like it that much.
It can be a little much.
You don't like gingerbread.
You don't like citrus.
What would you say your top smells are?
What do you like the smell of?
Bread?
Baking bread?
I do like baking bread.
OK, you like that better than citrus and gingerbread?
Baking.
Rising chocolate chip cookies and brownies.
Chocolate chip cookies have a very good smell when they're cooking or baking.
I think fresh citrus.
I love the smell of citrus.
So do I like the smell of a damn forest?
Yeah, of course I do.
You know what?
Locking it in.
ET forest.
Yeah, I'm locking it in too.
I don't even have to vote.
It's got to move on.
It doesn't even matter what I would say.
The length of the argument started me going, you know what?
ET forest.
Where else are you going to get that?
Hit.
What are you voting for?
I hadn't decided.
Do we know?
Make it official for the record?
ET forest.
All right.
I'm just trying to be honest.
I'm trying to give a, you know.
I think it's the guilt that we feel about eliminating.
But this is what this whole thing is about.
It's all about this and it's all about trying to analyze.
We said at the top, ET forest.
We're all banging our pens.
ET forest is going to go far.
I'm just trying to analyze and make sure that I'm doing this in the right way.
I don't want to jump the gun and say because one of my favorite characters in fiction
maybe my favorite botanicus is connected to this smell.
You know what?
That it doesn't deserve this.
I don't think I'm even putting botanicus in there.
I don't think that's even part of it because the moment for me
is when those stage doors open, you've made it past the operators.
You've given your name.
Why?
What could this be for?
I'm holding a passport for to what end?
And then you are out of this industry, this lobby.
This is a place I feel like I'm at the bank.
And then the doors open and now you're in a magical forest
and the coolness hits you and the smell hits you.
It's a magical moment.
It's almost more special because it's only in one place now.
Look, I don't disagree.
I don't.
I'm just trying to be honest.
I'm just trying to be good.
This takes us now to Pandoran forest versus banana breath.
Oh, versus new strap like blood pressure.
So high.
There's some like new versus these also are both like soren versus retro classic.
Yeah.
Let me start by saying the Pandoran forest versus the E.T. forest.
Well, that'll have a match up.
You almost can't.
We can't do that because if it wins.
Yeah, we can't.
Let me just say that the Pandoran forest is such a wonderful smell, but it does.
If you get if you separate the smell from the experience,
to me feels like a really great hotel lobby smell.
And then you took the hotel lobbies when we were even discussing this.
And I just talked about Polynesian.
We took it out.
It's not as specific.
I will say Kong's banana breath.
When you put it up again, now we can do this comparison.
Orange.
It I don't think is quite as good as the orange smell.
It smells worse than the orange is.
Yes, it does smell worse than the orange.
And it's sometimes fainter.
Yes.
And I was all in the past, obviously, but it didn't always work.
Yeah.
Right.
And again, I have to tie my experience in.
I did not smell that banana breath every day when I worked there.
So the inconsistency, I think you have to dock at points for it.
You know there's no inconsistency on on plight of passage.
They're they're keeping tabs on that.
James Cameron calls and checks every day.
I think the combination of the smell and the movement and the 3D visuals,
you know, it's just great.
I played a passage around the world.
I will say the Kong reminds me and this is a good thing.
Kong reminds me of banana runs.
And I love banana runs.
They are a bit divisive, I hear, which is crazy to me because I don't know.
I don't I don't like them.
Yeah, divisive.
I don't know why.
I don't a lot of people.
I think it's put it as my favorite kind of runt.
See, it goes maybe strawberry.
I would.
They had cherry runs and they've got rid of them, which is crazy.
But that's another podcast of fakie flavoring.
I tend to prefer strawberry over cherry.
Yes.
But the fakie cherry, when you go like maraschino cherries,
style fake cherries delicious.
No, that's a plus.
You do.
I love a maraschino cherry.
Like a Shirley Temple situation.
Yeah.
Which I've seen a lot of chatter.
There's a little boy that really temple boy is the name the Shirley Temple King.
I think so.
It's too late to be getting in this episode with this.
But there's a little boy who reviews Shirley Temples called the Shirley Temple King, I believe.
And he'll be a future guest on the show.
See you soon, King.
Maraschino cherries are a little ruined for me by the Luxardo cherries in the Carthay man.
Oh, well, sure.
I mean, those are fantastic sweet cherries as well.
It's just now I can't go back.
That's like you're right in first class.
I can't go to.
See, I don't really like the brandy.
I like them OK.
But give me the fucking Kroger brand fakie maraschino cherries.
That's all day.
All day.
So I the forest is just such a pleasant, great smell.
It doesn't feel that specific to me.
It doesn't.
Of all the four of these that are left, it doesn't feel as specific as those other three.
It doesn't have as much character.
I feel like it's wonderful and it's very pleasant.
And it's again, combined with two experiences that are fantastic.
It's not as specific to me.
And I got to give it to Kong.
So I have voted.
Let's do.
I don't know.
Do you know?
You go.
You can.
I'll break the.
I'll be the last this time.
As much as.
I really wish that we were ending on E.T.
Forest and.
Oh, wait, no, E.T.
Forest.
I kind of was the last two E.T.
Forest in orange in a way, but we already made it through that one.
Right.
Because I actually think maybe Pandora is lesser than I would maybe go below orange on that.
I know we are where we are.
Disagree.
And I I'm delighted by I want to look at this paper and see E.T.
Forest versus King Kong's banana breath that I really like that.
But if I'm being honest, I know where I think I have to say Pandora and Forest.
I think the inconsistency and the sometimes faintness of it.
I know where this is.
I have to Jason.
I know.
And I'm giving it to Pandora Forest.
Of course, this has been tough for you, Mike.
I think the audience is going to side with me on a lot of these.
I'm going to be very upset.
We have E.T.
Forest versus Pandora Forest.
Which.
And this is where my journey with Pandora Forest ends because.
I'd like look, I'd like to belabor this.
I'd like to do my whole analysis with it.
But what are we who are we kidding here?
Yeah.
All right.
I mean, come on.
It's got to go E.T. all the way.
I mean, I don't think that one.
Goodbye.
It has to be.
Pandora and Forest.
It has to be the picture that I have here.
SWC 1040 9 5 6 Evergreen Forest.
Sent Air.
It says, please recycle on it.
Here's the photo.
We'll post it for you on Twitter catalogs out.
This is the one.
The winner is this industrial.
This weird little black machine.
This is the winner.
Yeah.
For the 2020.
Asbestos.
Fake smell final for.
Goodbye.
E.T.
Fuck you.
Banana breath.
Eat shit.
Ginger.
And ginger bread.
It's so great.
Yeah.
I don't even.
And I.
Yeah, I think you're right.
Is it pure smell?
But you can't.
You can't fault things for getting nostalgia tied up into them.
I try.
There I tried.
Is there a single smell like of any of these smell?
Do you think anyone would be mad about this result?
No.
I don't think this ultimate victor.
And he would be mad about.
I think there will be people who would think that it number two should have been Rome
burning.
I think there will be a lot of controversy when it comes to brackets, but I don't.
I think the majority of the audience will agree with us.
And I do think it's what I said.
I forget which round it was.
I think that the forest combines almost everything.
It is got all of the elements of what we like.
It's in a perfectly placed themed area that makes you feel a certain way that even accentuates
the smell and your magical association with the smell.
It also is.
I was hitting it for not being you couldn't describe it, but probably that is actually
a positive because it's so specific to this area.
And again, it does to me at least remind me of the natural manmade weird smells from theme parks.
Again, we don't know exactly if that's on purpose or not, or if there's like some
decaying part of the ride somewhere that's helping it.
But it does add to that feeling of like this is old or something like it's been here for a while.
Musty and mildewy.
And I think there was a point in time where I thought it was more accidental.
I feel like we can see pirates in this choice.
And universe a park that not terribly good at preserving its own history,
usually bulldozes its own history.
Two mixed results, sometimes two great success.
We still still hanging on.
And it's almost the fact that it's almost like if you name three things about this ride and what
you like about it, I almost guarantee the three things are include the smell and botanicals.
And then like he says your name.
Yeah.
Yes.
Now, let me ask this.
Do if we find a way to get this scent air, if we actually buy it, we smell it and it smells
way different.
And we realize that part of the smell of the right is the right itself, much like pirates.
Can we disqualify this from much like, you know, with baseball, if somebody took steroids,
they come out of the Hall of Fame.
If we have somebody make a case that it's half this smell and half the actual old ride,
does this disqualify the forest smell?
And can't change the results.
They've been written down and signed.
As we've learned in recent history.
Okay.
Locked in.
I also think that like the smell being released, the place does matter.
The place.
Yeah.
I think the place.
Yes.
Smell that you're okay.
So this will stay and these smells might be different just in your apartment versus the.
Yeah, I have to say, yeah, it came down to ET forest versus Rome burning.
That would have been a much harder final round.
Yeah.
It's almost weird that against other competitors, I feel bad as the one who
eliminated Roam.
I guess we did together, Mike.
If you had to, what's your number two?
Take the brackets out of it.
If you just had to rank these 16, what's number two?
Because mine is orange.
I think it, I actually think the final two should have been ET in orange,
but that's just, we got that one done early.
I think it's Roam burning.
Mine is.
Mine is between orange or gingerbread.
Wow.
Gingerbread.
I love that gingerbread.
I guess I just have such an association with the smell.
I just, I can see the argument being made for orange for sure.
Yeah.
You included in there.
Listeners, tell us what you think.
Do you strongly disagree with this?
Have we massively overrated the evergreen forest?
You know what?
If I was ever on the fence and I didn't like that it was, we were calling it damp forest before
evergreen forest just gave me such a good feeling when you clarified the actual name.
Right.
Again, as long as this is accurate, but it does make it sound better and it seems right.
There's no, none of these smells I would rather have in front of it.
I would, I'd rather walk into a room full of it than the evergreen forest smell.
Right.
I wish I could, it's only Florida.
And yeah, if you work on the ride and you can steal one of these forests, don't get fired.
Steal from your job for us.
Don't get fired.
I'm just joking.
I'm just making some fun, but seriously, if you want to, you know.
Oh boy.
Well, congratulations evergreen forest.
I think we sorta, the smart money was always on this, but it's still fun to acknowledge
all these other great smells.
Is evergreen forest now a PTR legend or does that have to be a separate ceremony?
Oh.
Automatically put the winner of our final fours into the legends category.
I would argue yes.
I think so.
Yeah.
So imagine we're raising to the ceiling a basketball jersey that smells like the evergreen forest.
Right.
And then also a basketball jersey.
The radiator springs rocks are cut into a basketball jersey.
That's good.
Yeah.
Those are rising up into the rafters of Mike's apartment.
Okay.
Yeah.
So welcome to your legend status evergreen forest.
You made it.
So, okay.
I'm exhausted.
Yeah, I know.
Me too.
Yeah.
I don't know what else to say.
How long did that take?
I think honestly it was under, last time I think we went like two and a half.
This is under two hours, I think.
Yeah.
It was a little easier.
There was a clear, the final two was a lot tougher.
It was.
I agree.
Fake rocks.
What do we do next?
Next year.
Yeah, there's a lot of different things.
I don't know who to suggest away, listeners.
We've talked about some, you know, maybe less interesting things like best theme park song.
Best maybe ride vehicle divorced from the actual ride itself.
That's interesting.
If you could like drive around, what would you want?
Omnimover, you know, Wi-Fi controlled vehicle like Luigi or Rise of the Resistance.
But is it like almost, can we not even do like a good one?
Do they have to be sort of?
Do they have to be weird?
These are all good.
I mean.
Bathrooms.
Yeah.
Well, we've set a, yes, we've set a precedent for maybe not picking the most obvious thing.
Do they always have to be fake something?
Is there anything left?
I think, yeah, fake is a great component.
Fake sounds.
Sounds?
Yeah, but most sounds are fake.
Best like real animal.
Best real animal.
And then who goes up against like goats and main street horses.
Okay.
We could do one where we rank the main street horses throughout time.
So ranking dead horses, you're saying.
Yeah.
And if you alive ones.
Is there one named Duke or something?
Didn't Duke retire?
Am I thinking of a different horse?
100% there was one named Duke at some point.
I think, but not long ago, you and I both tweeted congratulations to Duke for being
a new main street horse.
Am I wrong?
It's Duke.
Oh, they believed like they did a thing.
Because they'll post on like Twitter and stuff about the new horses or new positions.
So what about best firework?
It's Red Burst versus.
White Stardust.
That's good.
Those all have names.
There's a firework called Chrysanthemum, which is like, you know, it looks like the flower.
I guess Mickey years.
If it makes a shape, that's something.
Yeah.
Best fake.
I want to say like fake sky on a ride.
I don't know.
Or sky is pretty good.
Indoor sky is not bad reason to talk about the Caesar's Palace.
Yeah.
Shops of I forget the official.
The forum shops, I believe you can throw like Small World in there, which we've talked about before.
Would you call that fake sky?
Oh, I see.
We could just.
Yeah, you would truly be.
Sky fake Final Four's.
I see what you're saying.
Fake sky.
And then maybe it's also the, you know, like the end of the Hollywood area.
Of California adventure.
Yes.
On the universal tour is a big like backdrop.
That's right.
Like where the TLC waterfalls video is filmed.
Fake cities.
London and Peter Pan.
Mexico City and the boat ride.
Like depictions of real fake real place.
Fake real places.
It's funny.
Yeah.
Well, we'll think of more.
There's got to be something else too.
Well, and how would we determine what one to do next?
Possibly by getting a list of 16 and having them compete.
Oh, that's great.
Okay, that's good.
The fake Final Four Final Four.
Maybe next year is the fake Four Final Four.
And the year after we do it.
But it's just a year wasted on.
It's a year wasted on deciding what fake thing we do.
Yeah.
All right.
Oh boy, that's funny.
This is just as much as we can stretch.
That's the whole podcast that we do.
We're stalling for something.
For what?
I don't know.
I'm not sure either, but.
Trying to put it off.
We're just trying to make it to the end of the Trump administration with smiles on our faces.
Yeah, 20 years away.
We've got four more.
Oh yeah, right.
Yeah, four.
What am I talking about?
Well, gang, on that less than positive note,
you survived, I guess, the ride.
The fake smell Final Four.
Congratulations, Evergreen Forest.
Congratulations.
Well deserved.
Well fought.
Yeah.
I don't want to be crass, but Edwin is making a smell right now.
He has farted really bad.
To really send us off with a smell.
You're kidding.
Really?
I swear to God.
Wow.
It's crazy.
It's not fake though.
It's not fake.
There's nothing fake about it.
This makes me want to keep going to force you to stay over there where he is.
He just did it once.
But you have the button so you could stop it whenever you want.
That's true.
And get far away from this fart.
Yeah.
Edwin, by the way, the dog.
Edwin is Mike's dog.
In case you don't know.
Well, see you next year for something even stupider.
Bye.
This has been a Forever Dog Production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Bohm, Joe
Sileo, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com and subscribe to our
shows on Apple Podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram,
at Forever Dog Team, and liking our page on Facebook.