Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast features a stumbling man on fire, horsey clip-clop foley
sounds, and a rowdy foul-mouthed bear we lovingly refer to simply as Ted.
Carl Tart joins us to talk the Universal Studios special effects show today on Podcast The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the podcast about theme parks that's more fun than a live broadcast
of Harry and the Hendersons.
I'm Scott Gairdner joined by Mike Carlson.
Yeah, that's true.
It's way better.
I often think about like going back in time and like going to these old like tapings,
these TV tapings and they seem like super fun but I think it's just because it's like
nostalgia brain.
Because like I imagine like Alf, going back and seeing a live Alf would be like going
to see the Rolling Stones in their prime.
Potentially except like Alf, I don't know that Alf did have an audience because there
were so many like difficulties with the puppet.
Everyone hated the puppet is my recollection of reading about it.
I think so, yeah.
The dad like stormed off on day one.
But I think it was so many like special effects, like Small Wonder didn't have an audience
because there are too many special effects even though there's a laugh track.
Right.
But that being said, the idea of seeing Alf, yes absolutely.
Jason Sheridan, any show you would like to see taped live?
I feel like three camera sitcom tapings are a nightmare regardless.
Like it's just a play that you just keep seeing the same thing again and again with minor
changes.
But what if Alf was there?
I mean if Alf was there that'd be cool if he was like talking to everyone and hamming
it up and like cursing when he messed up.
But I don't know that that's how it played out.
If they could keep it to an hour then yeah it would probably be fun.
Yeah.
Hey and joining us today, a TV veteran himself from Comedy Bang Bang and The Good Place, Carl
Tartis here.
A TV veteran.
One of the Hollywood elite.
Completely comfortable saying that, yes absolutely.
Man thanks for being here.
Thanks for having me guys.
Yeah yeah.
This is fun.
When I got the email from Jason I had to break some important news to him that is very important
to this.
Oh.
Wait what's that?
What news?
That I'm very afraid of rides.
Oh.
Right right.
Really?
Yeah.
Interesting.
Definitely afraid.
You said specifically rollercoasters.
Rollercoasters yes.
Yes.
Okay.
We're sort of in a similar zone.
And anything that moves that I can't control it.
Aligns, airplanes.
Oh really?
No no no.
I like those things.
I really like commercial flight.
But I don't.
Subways?
Yeah I'm fine with that.
Okay.
Except when they go through long tunnels.
Yeah.
Uh huh.
I hear that.
Escalators.
It gets dark.
I'm fine with that.
Sure sure sure.
Nothing goes fast.
Adrenaline drops.
I don't like drops.
Okay.
Yeah.
I'm a little, I'm definitely similar.
I've gotten better as I felt like I've had to to even get to go on rides to talk about
them on this podcast.
So it's possible to have growth in this area I can attest.
But it's hard.
It's a journey.
Yeah.
I understand.
What is the scariest ride you've been on?
Uh.
Like have you been on one and it was like that's it, no more?
Space Mountain.
Okay.
Yeah.
Is that kind of a cap?
That's like as scary as you would imagine.
Yeah that's because I couldn't see anything.
And I just didn't know when the drop was coming.
I didn't know what was happening.
Yeah.
And there's also one in, there's this park in the Netherlands called.
Efteling?
Efteling.
The Efteling.
Yeah.
And there's a ride there called Fanta Morgana.
And it's like, it's like Space Mountain but it's like outside it's just a big ass bird.
Whoa.
And like so you don't know what it's about.
It's just like this park is like, it's like what Disneyland was based off of or something
like that.
Like Walt Disney went there and so like and so that ride, some of my coworkers who we
went with forced me to get on it.
Like it's fine.
You're not going to be scared of it.
Jim Woods actually forced me to get on it.
Oh yeah.
That's not a good idea to listen to anything he says.
And I was like I don't want to get on it.
I don't want to get on it.
And I was so mad after.
I told you.
I told you I didn't want to get on it.
Like he made me.
And they were like it's not that scary.
I'm like don't tell me.
Don't give me.
Don't tell me what I'm afraid of and what I'm not afraid of.
Right.
Yeah.
I don't.
I have never appreciated like the pranking or the leaving out information about how scary
it is or get like getting laughed at.
That's what I don't want.
I want like support if I'm going to get on a roller coaster from an overcome fear.
You want everyone like cheering your name beforehand as opposed to be like you loser
get on the ride.
Yeah.
Laughing at my picture.
That's the worst.
After what's the Pirates of the Caribbean.
Because at the end it goes up.
And then you're like don't you.
Oh my God.
Don't you drop.
Please don't drop.
And it just goes straight.
There's nothing.
There's nothing at the end of that.
And I'm sure when they like took the picture I'm like and everybody else is like having
a great time.
I'm so relieved to hear this.
I was like a little afraid just of the drop on pirates until not that long ago.
That is like nothing now I realize.
But that's on like a 20 footer.
That's barely anything.
Yeah.
And you can see the whole thing.
And thank God.
I'm glad I'm not the only one.
Jurassic Park is probably the next scariest because of that only because of the drop.
Everything else is wack about that ride.
But that drop is so like heavy.
It's so forceful.
Yeah.
It's just like this big.
It's the worst.
It was very industrial.
You're in this like that building is just this cavernous.
You're just looking at pipes and everything.
It's like you're reliving like a traumatic memory.
It is how I feel.
It's steep though.
Jurassic Park is very steep.
Like that's a really steep drop.
Built into a mountain.
Yeah.
The drop I've gotten a little more used to now that I've gone on it more.
But the dinosaur still does scare me.
If I'm in the front row and the dinosaur comes at me it's too real.
It's pretty close.
Yeah.
It's big.
It's large.
Which is what we're talking about.
It's kind of a surprise when this thing's out.
I usually look at that dinosaur and go, shut up!
We about to drop!
Let me focus.
I don't care about you.
I'll get to you later.
You're going to be away from him in three seconds.
There's no problem there.
So do you go to these places and enjoy yourself at all?
Yeah.
Because they have great food.
Sure.
I really enjoy a good theme park funnel cake.
Yeah.
Sure.
When I was growing up and would go to Universal and stuff like that I would like to do Doc
Brown's Chicken.
Oh yeah.
Yes.
At one point in time that was pretty great.
I think that quality lapsed as time went on.
I feel like I did it in 2006 and it was garbage.
It was bad.
I think so.
But in the 90s I think it was a quality project.
Yeah.
It was good.
I enjoyed it.
They use the same fried chicken recipe apparently now in the Cletus' Chicken Shack in the Simpson's
Chicken restaurant.
Yeah.
So apparently it's like the same chicken or at least the 2006 chicken has been moved over
to Cletus.
2006.
They probably changed it like to just I think they just changed it like tenders at a certain
point as opposed to when I first started going there like in the 90s it was like you get
like a leg and a thigh.
Sure.
Yes.
I'm a little bothered or distracted by the question of why is Doc Brown operating a fried
chicken stand.
Oh I did not care at all.
I thought it was great.
The marketing on that got me as a kid.
The first time we ever went I was like oh I got to eat some Doc Brown's Chicken.
I never seen him make no chicken in those movies.
I don't think he cooked anything in the movies.
I don't think he eats.
I don't think you ever see him eat.
Yeah.
He never eats in the movies.
He has a breakfast machine but.
That's true.
One is for the dog and you don't see him eat the other one.
The other one is for iced tea.
Right.
Yeah.
And then it's clearly not him in the pictures at the restaurant.
It's obviously not Christopher Lloyd.
Yeah.
It's like an actor.
Oh it's the walk around.
Yeah it's the walk around Christopher Lloyd in like different places eating chicken.
He's time traveling but also making and eating chicken.
That's pretty tight.
You can't be mad at it.
He's a scientist so he'd probably be able to concoct a good recipe.
Right.
Yeah.
I would assume all scientists are good cooks.
Every single one.
Every scientist.
Like a chemist specifically.
Yeah.
I had a chemistry teacher in high school who was like trying to make a point that cooking
and chemistry were very similar and like gave us the chemical, gave us ingredients and gave
us the chemical component.
He was like, wouldn't tell us what we were making but there was like a bag of sugar and
a pile of peanuts and it's like you clearly have us making peanut brittle.
Yeah.
We are all not good enough to know the like chemical name for like sugar and baking soda.
So we all just made mismatched peanut, like bad peanut brittle.
Because he was trying to prove a point.
But he didn't say what it was until it was done.
Well he said like the amounts of each like ingredient but it would be like sodium bosphorate.
Like you know the quarter cup of this.
And it's like I don't, this is going to be like either the saltiest or sweetest peanut brittle.
Have you made peanut brittle since?
No.
Okay.
I barely made it that day.
Peanut brittle.
What an old person's candy.
Yeah.
Like is that even going to like be around at the end of the century?
Will it last?
When I was at, when I was home for Christmas some like old family member made like pecan
brittle almost.
Like pecan candy was just, pecans in melted sugar and butter like in hardened and it was
just like even, just like the texture of it was like I can't get through this.
It's too sweet.
Yeah.
You're not supposed to be eating a lot of this at all.
Like it's the worst ingredients.
Yeah.
Like I have a huge sweet tooth and I was like I can't even do it.
Right, right.
Like a butterscotch or a toffee it's like such like hardcore concentrated sweetness.
Almost too much.
Yeah.
There was, this is only tangentially related.
You would see like on TV like I'm trying to think, I think it was Honey Boo Boo or something.
They would just be like making lemonade and the lemonade had so much sugar in it and it's
like I think it's like you could just get used to your taste buds, get used to sugar
and get desensitized to it at that point to like where you have like you have butterscotch.
Like it's too much unless you're like used to eating like an insane amount of sugar.
I feel like I can't, I can't even do it.
And again, I like treats.
I like sweets.
Love a good treat.
Yeah.
Or treats and sweets, different things.
Let me think.
Yes, because I think a treat doesn't have to be food.
Uh huh.
A sweet is.
It's a little gift you give to yourself.
Yeah.
Or you receive from someone else, I suppose.
A treat could be like a 15 minute nap.
Yeah.
Oh, treats can be non-food.
That's right.
That's like a dollop of porn.
Watch a little bit of titty swinging.
I've done my work for the day.
Just a little treat.
Just a morsel.
I deserve it.
Just a little.
It sounds so wholesome honestly when you say it's just a little treat.
It's not dirty.
It's not bad.
It's a little bit of pornography.
That's delightful.
Yes.
Okay, so you were like a Universal kid.
You grew up sort of in the area.
Yeah.
I don't know if that was like the home base park.
Well, here's why I became the home base park, because my mom was a studio tour guide.
What?
Wow.
Really?
I did this job.
I was a tour guide.
You did that job?
Yes.
You got the big binder?
I still have the big binder.
In the Universal story?
Wait, the Universal story.
Is that like a tape or a video?
It was a video tape with my mom.
She started in 2002 when I was in seventh grade.
Maybe even earlier than that.
Maybe like 2000 she started.
I was like fifth grade maybe.
Me and my friends would go.
She's single mom.
So on the weekends, to keep me from not being in the house all day while she was at work,
she would just bring us with her.
She'd be like, all right, grab a friend.
I'd take my best friend Russell or my best friend Jovon and we would just go to Universal.
She'd have to sneak us in because you're not allowed to do that.
Sure.
Just bring kids all the time.
It was really easy to go through her employment entrance.
There was a gate.
I think it's definitely closed off now.
But back then it was just like, oh, you just come through this gate and just go, all right.
We would get there and she would go, okay, go in.
We just run off to where she didn't look like she saw us in case there was a camera looking
or something like that.
And we just hang out at Universal all day.
Like constantly?
Like once a week?
Yeah, like on Saturdays.
Geez.
That's awesome.
Yeah.
And in the summertime probably a couple more times.
Sure.
Wow.
And you love that every time?
You didn't get sick?
You didn't run out of stuff?
I got tired of it.
I got tired.
I got to be like, mom, can I please just stay home?
I don't want to go to this theme park every week.
No way.
Because I don't like, I wouldn't get on anything.
Yeah.
So you're left with like, you know, you could play Flintstones carnival games or.
I would do all of the other attractions.
I really enjoyed the studio tour, no matter who was giving it.
It didn't have to be my mom.
I was embarrassed when my mom did it.
I used to try to avoid her tour.
But she probably wanted you to do it, right?
She wanted me to see it.
Did she involve you ever?
She would.
And then we'd be like, oh, God.
Oh, yeah, that's mortifying.
It's like when my mom's substitute taught one of my music classes in elementary school.
Like, your mom's the teacher now.
Oh, yeah.
It feels like it would be the same sort of dynamic.
Are you from a small town?
Not that small.
Yeah.
I mean, no, it's just like it happened once.
She would purposely not take classes that I was, like, she would not sub for a class
in general, but she was a music teacher at our school once.
So it was inevitable when we had the hour of music.
Sure, sure, sure.
That I had it.
That's dope.
That's dope your mom would avoid your class.
My mom would be so stoked to teach a class of mine just to embarrass me.
Right.
And I wasn't like a bad kid.
I had behavioral issues, but I talked way too much.
Sure.
I was a rabble rouser.
Right, right.
Yeah.
Would she like, what is embarrassing you?
Would she like say like, that's my Will Carl or something or pinch the cheeks?
No, like, are you talking about on the ride?
Or anywhere or any?
What's your nature of embarrassment?
No, she would try to like, kind of like flex nuts, like be like, get me, like be mad at
me.
Oh, yeah.
Like, I'm the parent.
Right.
It's like, you don't even act like that.
Like, we don't have this relationship.
This is false.
I don't have that.
I don't have behavioral issues like that, like where you need to like discipline me so
hard and let everybody know like, I'm in charge.
Yeah.
It was like performative.
It was very performative.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, she's an actor.
Sure.
So it's performing like, and one time I skipped out on piano.
I took piano classes at recreation center, like at a park, and all my friends were at
the park too, and they were all playing basketball.
And I'm a big basketball player and I was like, I'm going to keep playing basketball.
I'm not going to piano today.
I was like 13, 14.
I'm not going.
I'm going late.
I used to try to like, because the classes would kind of run late.
They were like beginning at beginners three to four, intermediate four to five, and advanced
like five to seven.
We had the longer class.
And so I, and, but the classes would run kind of late and I would always be like, all right,
it's five o'clock.
I'm in the middle of a game.
They're not going to stop me in the middle of a game.
Like the gym's literally right next door to the multipurpose room.
And then my piano teacher would like come out and like kind of like hold his hands like
this, like, you know, like cross his arms and go.
And I go, ah, fuck off.
Fuck off.
I wouldn't say that to him.
But like, and then one day my mom just walked in and just like snatched me off the court
mid game and like tossed me up against the wall just to like make all my friends go,
ooh, I'm like, you don't even, what are you doing?
You don't do this.
You don't act like this.
The movie's bullshit.
Yeah.
She just wanted to, she was a big fan of like, she, I think she like thinks that that's what
parents should do is like embarrass their kids in front of everybody so they don't get
too out of line.
Right.
Full of themselves.
Make an example.
Yeah.
My mom would not do it.
She would just show up everywhere else for like, she would volunteer for every field
trip.
Yeah.
And she would just be like, I'm around.
And she wasn't trying to do that, but she was doing that, which is what my dad would
do when you'd watch me play sports.
He would just like hover arms cross and hover.
And I'd just be like, God, go away.
Too much pressure.
So were you then not good at sports for that reason?
Yeah, for that reason.
For that, only that reason.
And really what I'm talking about is playing tennis in high school.
That's what I'm saying.
Sports.
His arm crossing.
Really nuts up your back swing.
Yeah.
My sister, I drove my sister nuts too.
Sure, sure.
It's really in my head now.
Did I, was she still doing that in 2006 when I, when I started?
No.
Okay.
So I didn't cross that already.
She stopped in like 04.
Okay, okay.
I think that's when I asked.
Uh huh, uh huh.
How was her tour?
It was great.
She's very, she's good at that.
She was good at that.
Right, right.
Honestly, like she's good at it.
We used to watch that.
I used to help her study the lines from the binder.
It was such a huge binder.
Y'all had to memorize so much.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah.
And then all these clips, you have to, you have to memorize the numbers to know what
to pull up.
Oh yeah, y'all have to do all that manually.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
It is so, it's like, it takes up a ton of space in my place still.
I don't know why I don't get rid of it, except there's probably some podcast, The Ride Function,
Yeah, yeah.
At some point.
But then there's all this trivia you got to learn, like just in case you get stuck for
a long time.
Yeah.
Yeah, like you can just like read a list of who won Oscars for Universal Movies, which
I'm sure the audience would love just going through in, in 1952, uh, on the waterfront.
Everyone's, yeah.
It was super interesting, honestly.
It was just the history of the film stuff, like from Carl Lamley, like all that stuff
on how he started the place and how, how it's operated and haunted stage 13 or stage 27
or what?
Yeah, I think it's 27.
The Phantom of the Opera?
The Phantom of the Opera stage.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's haunted.
You know what I always say?
Like I almost memorized the damn thing myself.
And the Universal story is super interesting, like movie.
I would try, I sleep with the TV on, but I need something like consistent.
Every night I watch like Family Guy.
Sure.
Because I know it's going to be funny.
I'm going to go to sleep with good energy and just turn that on, like my DVR so it plays
all the episodes and then the TV will turn off after a certain point.
But, uh, I used to watch that, that Universal story every night.
Wait, so you got a tape that like, that, that like helped her learn the history and study
and everything.
She had to know this whole.
Yeah.
It's like Ron Howard and it's just clips from all those movies.
Is that the one they used to sell as a souvenir?
Maybe.
The Robert Forsythe?
Is that his name?
Maybe not.
If it's Ron Howard, this could be a different one.
Oh, okay.
This is maybe an internal tape.
Yeah.
Ron Howard, yeah, Ron Howard will maybe be internal, yeah.
Yeah, it's an internal, yeah.
It's like the Chuck E. Cheese, like how to play the character videos that are online now
that were internal videos that you're not supposed, like the public's not supposed to
see.
Yeah.
They want you to know.
Ron Howard's telling you the secrets.
Oh, sure.
Yeah.
There's one that I found a couple years ago.
Well, no, when we were in like high school that somebody posted it.
It was Hot Drinks, the Hot Drinks tutorial for Wendy's.
I'm a huge Hot Drinks fan.
I did a bit.
I did a song like for Atlantic City once.
Oh, really?
It's such a funny video.
Yeah.
And like, where coffee reaches the line.
It's an instruction.
It's a Wendy's instructional video about making coffee and hot chocolate and other hot drinks.
And the song is so much better than it has any right to be.
The song is good.
Cha cha.
Ow!
It's like Michael Jackson.
It's really Michael Jackson-y.
Coffee decaf for tea and hot chocolate.
Coffee, let it sit.
The stretching of the words to make it rhyme with other words.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And hot chocolate.
Chocolate.
What's the part I like a lot?
The lemon on the top.
Very nice, give your guests a juicy slice.
Hot drinks really get you going.
Blow.
He like blows the top.
Rhythmically blows the top of the hydrant.
There's so much attitude in it when he blows and then turns back to you.
He's like really working that camera.
Played at your wedding.
Played at my wedding.
Yeah.
Because it was a big thing at Funny or Die, and it was my dream to have a party where
that came on.
We said to the Funny or Die people, why won't you play this at your parties?
We'd all love it, and they wouldn't listen.
So the wedding, this is my chance, and the DJ fought it.
He's like, well, you might not understand at weddings.
It's got to be something grandma can dance to.
And I'm like, trust me, Hot Drinks is going to blow up this dance floor.
And it did, and he segued it into Erotic City.
That's pretty good.
And that was the best moment of the wedding by far.
The Hot Drinks, Erotic City mega mix.
That's pretty tight.
It was really good.
There are other videos in that series, right?
Is there a chili video or a cold drink?
There's a cold drink that I don't think is as good.
Well, there's like the blonde girl, and she's like rapping to one.
Her song is like based off of like Paula Abdul's Straight Up.
That's kind of like the beat is more...
She's like rapping about something.
That might be the chili one, honestly.
There's fingers in the chili, isn't it?
No.
I think they do talk about like any crusty bits on the grill, like put it in the chili.
Oh, no.
That is like a Wendy's thing.
Little bits of cheese.
They take things off the grill and throw it in.
They used to at least.
I have never ordered a Hot Drink at a Wendy's.
I got to be honest.
Me neither.
I love my fast food, but if I go, I'm not like...
Or McDonald's.
I'll get McDonald's coffee.
When they changed their coffee, it was like, yeah, that's all right.
They changed it?
Or after they burned that lady?
When they rolled out like the full McCafe.
You know why they rolled out the...
When they were like losing so much money to Starbucks.
They were like, okay, we need to make something.
I mean, how can you not get McDonald's coffee?
I don't.
I know how you can't because I don't do it.
But when you walk into a McDonald's at breakfast time, it smells so good.
Oh, it smells great.
Yeah.
I guess Hot Drinks then didn't work on me if I've never done it.
Do you think...
Is it still the juicy slice policy?
How have I never tested this?
I feel like they have their own limit.
You get your own now.
Oh, maybe.
It's like a nasty bucket on the side by the drinks.
You got to get a...
That's a weird area, those side lemons.
I don't trust...
When someone pointed out that...
How do we know that they're washed?
Why would you just dip outside peel into your drink?
You don't know where that's been.
Yeah, that is weird.
They do that at Portillo's where it's like they'll give you a lemon, but they just dump a lemon in.
But they bare handed...
You know they bare handed it.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Did you guys have any friends or did y'all work at fast food places?
Or any friends that would say, like, dude, do not eat there.
They do such gross things.
There's gum in the cheese.
It's just like stupid shit like that.
But it's like this has to be a rumor.
How's everybody coming in this stuff?
Yeah, right, right.
Did I have any friends with inside info?
My friend worked at Fuddruckers on Gulf Road, but we just got free food.
She didn't talk about cum in the food.
My friend worked at In-N-Out and he was like, do not get the pink lemonade.
People wash their hands in the pink lemonade.
And I was like, but that seems like a word that seems so sticky.
Yeah.
That doesn't seem smart.
Opposite of the desired effects.
Exactly.
Jokes on them, really.
I've talked about like kid rumors before, I think, on the show where like a kid was like,
yeah, there's a naked Marvel comic that Stan Lee drew and he signed his name on the boobs.
And I was like, what?
And I was like, does he draw?
I think he doesn't draw.
They're like, no, he does draw.
And he drew them naked.
I was like, that doesn't make sense.
Never found it?
No.
Never tried to find it?
I tried, yeah.
Sure.
At the time I asked around, you heard about this naked Marvel comic that Stan Lee drew?
He doesn't draw.
That's your next podcast.
Trying to figure out where that is.
The naked Marvel comic.
The answer had to be out there.
And then lots of, doon, doon, doon, doon, podcast music breaks.
Yeah, it's like a serial or Finding Richard Simmons or whatever.
Well, this was the third comic book story that I was forcibly thrown out of.
Stan drew it.
He signed the boobs.
Yow!
I swear.
I have to move to another state now to finish this podcast series.
Okay, well, so with your, so with that timeline, if you were going all the time in 2002 or so,
now I'm suspecting that your version of this topic of the special effects stages are probably different,
it's probably different than the one I saw the most.
If you had to, or your memory of what this show was as you saw it, what was your version of it?
It was the Foley, like doing the Foley, which was always great.
Yeah.
Harry and the Hendersons, I believe.
So it was still Harry and the Hendersons.
Yeah.
Okay.
And but then later the motion capture with the big wolf man.
Yeah.
Fluffy.
Fluffy, yeah, yeah, yeah, that would go off the rails.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah.
And that used to scare me.
Right.
Please don't come to me in the audience.
And it would always, always come to me.
We, well, with, oh, like the, that creature ran right up to you.
Yeah.
When it would get off the, yeah.
Yeah, when it would get off the thing.
Oh, sure.
I believe, I want to say later, towards later, the mummy stacking and then the dude gets
electrocuted.
Yeah.
Okay, okay.
The person gets electrocuted and they like disappear into the wall or whatever.
Yeah, right, right.
Okay, so that, yeah, because there were a couple versions of this.
My childhood ones were different.
But so this was this show where it's three sound stages and you like move down one at
a time.
Right.
And then in the next 15 minutes you have to like get up and like maintain where your seat
was and walk to the next thing.
And this is on the lower lot, the universal where the Transformers riot is now.
But generally, yeah, that was the format that it's like a couple of special effects kind
of things and then ending with a sound show.
And now there's still a thing like this, but it's up in the castle theater.
Yeah.
It's on the upper lot now.
It's a lot more polished now.
We were talking a little before we started and like in the 2000s one, it was a lot more
sticky.
Yeah.
Like it was a lot goofier.
There was a lot more topical jabs at like Lindsay Lohan and Paris Hilton.
Yeah.
And now it's in this giant theater on the upper lot and it's much more grand and elaborate
about the power of movies.
But we don't want to talk about that.
We want to talk about the trash on the lower lot.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let's go through it in order.
So you're saying like I love this thing, by the way.
This is like the heart of Universal when it was still exciting to learn how movies were
made.
Absolutely.
Now it's a little more like I think they don't know what to do anymore because it's all the
answer is always computers.
Computers is how we do it.
And there's no way to like demonstrate computers in an exciting way.
But these things were awesome.
So you're probably standing outside and they get some volunteers from the audience, kind
of a mixed group of there's some kids and some dads to embarrass.
We always talk about those like the great theme park tradition of embarrassing dad,
making him wear a costume that we can laugh at him in.
And the first one, yeah, for a while was The Mummy.
My version of it was Back to the Future when I was doing it as a kid.
But that had the same thing where it ends in this big electrocution gag where they're
filming the scene.
In that case, it's Doc Brown trying to connect the wires.
I remember that one too.
Right.
Yeah.
And then this but the same format as The Mummy one, which is The Mummy one like somebody's
trapped essentially.
I mean, they're slaves.
They are slaves.
Wonderful.
Cool.
And then like what is there?
Is there a curse?
Yeah, it's it's there's there's slaves and one person is stacking bricks, right?
Stacking big bricks to build the pyramids.
And the other person is chained up to this to say pyramid and then gets struck by lightning
and disintegrates.
Yes.
OK.
And just turns it and then into a skeleton.
Yes.
Yeah.
Which is this is I loved this kind of thing as a kid.
The cleverness of all the lights go out comes back on and a turntables clearly happened.
And now it's this charred not unlike the great movie.
Yes.
It's like similar gag in that.
I'm trying to OK.
Did you guys see the show or were you like was this before you were out here?
I was at Universal.
I don't even know that I knew this existed.
I did backdraft down there, but I don't even think I did because it moved it moved in 2010.
Mm hmm.
So I probably went for the first time in like 2009.
So the later version.
Oh, you might have seen the original.
So I don't think I'm just saying I don't think I saw it down when it was in the lower left.
I saw it a bunch on the lower level.
When I was first out here for a semester in college, like the very first time I went to Universal was like Labor Day weekend of 2006.
It was packed.
And like this was thankful.
I mean, we got everything done, but it was like it was so hot and it was so crowded.
I worked then.
If everyone was passing it was like there were like medical emergencies.
A lot of them.
I remember that.
They had the misters around.
Oh, yeah, they got it.
And that Curious George that like Splash Zone.
Did you do that?
Was that around for your childhood entertainment?
The Splash Zone at the bottom of at the bottom of Jurassic Park.
We staying over there by that.
Oh, that's a good way to kill a bunch of tight.
Yeah.
We have that ride to Splash.
Yeah, for sure.
Or did you ever or the play area where like the bucket dumps?
Oh, yeah, I remember that.
But I was too big for that stuff.
Oh, sure.
Yeah.
That's for little kids.
That's fair.
I was too, but I did it on the clock one of that weekend.
Actually, that I remember on Labor Day.
You got dumped with the bucket.
I like yeah, I went and like ran around the Curious George area in my uniform, which probably
was not a good thing to do and probably weirded out kids.
Were you alone?
Yes.
Really?
I was on the clock and I had nothing to do and no one was watching me.
Like all the tours had gone out.
So you frolicked?
Yeah, I went for a frolick.
Oh, thanks for framing it that way.
Are you from here, Scott?
Yeah, yeah.
Where did you go to high school?
Chaminade in the Valley.
Oh, yeah.
Nice.
I went to Hamilton.
Okay.
Cool.
LA.
Yeah.
Valley bros.
Chaminade's a real snobby.
It was private school, right?
Yeah.
They called it snobinade, in fact.
Snobinade.
I had very little arguments against that.
It's fairly true.
Did you call it that when you were there?
I might have welcomed.
I don't think I specifically did, but I wouldn't be hurt if you called it that.
As I've maybe said before, also Chaminade alumni, imagine you're Joe Rody.
Oh, yeah.
From my high school.
We're saying no.
Oh, yeah.
So the first time I went, yeah, it was a heat wave.
This was a welcome reprieve because you're just in air conditioning for like half an
hour.
We also went with a big group, so everyone had to do the photo op in front of the studio
tour sign and then do the studio tour.
The very first thing, which I advise people like if you're going to Universal Hollywood,
go straight to the lower lot as soon as you get there because if it's early enough, you
can just do all of that in 30 minutes.
Like you can do all that and then go back up.
Sure.
But we did that the wrong way.
So we were like the only thing down there that was open was Panda Express.
So we're like eating Panda Express in the heat.
And then we're like, oh, there's a special effects show.
Thank God.
This is inside.
It's cold.
So your memory is mostly that you were full of Panda Express.
And then we all were like, everyone was sunburned that night just watching the Emmys.
Conan hosted.
It was a very funny year when Conan hosted the Emmys.
Not the one where all the reality show hosts came out and the plan was that there was no
plan.
You ever watch that?
No, I do remember that.
It's one of the worst things ever to occur.
Like all five, it was like Tom Bergeron and you know, Cropes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, OK.
And they just like stood around and we're like, we didn't prepare anything.
And that genuinely is what happened.
That was the bit.
Yeah.
But then they did it.
It was horrible.
That sounds like the most boring thing that ever happened.
But the mid aughts were the aughts were very interesting time for this attraction from
what I could tell.
Because there's always been some sort of special effects presentation at Universal.
You speak called Cinemagic, which was like for the 90s to 2002 in this space.
It was called Cinemagic and that they turned into special effects stages and kind of like
grouped it in with backdraft.
What was in Cinemagic?
That was Back to the Future first.
Then the middle was an Alfred Hitchcock thing.
Yes.
And that was the one where you got to fall from the OK.
So I remember Cinemagic.
OK.
You do this one too.
Yeah, that was the first one.
Yeah.
With the big Statue of Liberty.
You're like, yes, I love this.
Body motions on this podcast.
And then you're like, silence.
You did very good falling.
You did a very realistic Panama falling, we should say.
You're on the you're on the hand of the Statue of Liberty.
Trying to hang on to the hand of the Statue of Liberty.
And then you fall backwards.
Yeah.
And there's a big practical one.
But then the guy then there's it's intercutting with a guy who's just on green screen like
sitting in a chair.
Yes.
And they like cycle through everything that can be behind you on a green screen and like,
OK, now you're Superman and you're flying through space.
And it gets a huge laugh every time.
Green screen was such a novelty.
It was so interesting to learn about.
And now anybody can just do green screen anywhere all the time.
On their phones.
Yeah.
Apps that you hate that make you mad as soon as it looks like you've got to watch an ad
for five seconds.
Right.
That thing also had like a psycho recreation, essentially.
Yes.
Yeah.
And where the guy hosting it comes out as the mother and then kind of takes his wig
off and like, just kidding.
Yeah.
And that had the info that I also found really fascinating that it's a that it's chocolate
syrup instead of blood.
You couldn't tell because it was black.
I live for those little morsels of now fairly obvious movie trivia.
But man, that stuff.
I'd go home.
I'd go back to elementary school and tell everybody all that stuff as if they couldn't
just go learn it at the theme park.
And I probably bored a lot of people.
I was going to say, do they go nether around?
Nether around.
Give a telly a tale.
I have been to a place where the secrets of movies have been unveiled.
Do you know the movies of the 1940s?
You do.
Well, the blood was chocolate.
Well, you all know Alfred Hitchcock, of course.
The master of suspense.
Everyone here a saboteur fan?
Topaz is very underrated.
Saboteur is that's the saboteur is the Statue of Liberty movie, which is weird because I
think the guy who's dangling at the end is a Nazi.
I think that's what's happening.
Like, I've never seen Saboteur.
I haven't either.
I always like when I've watched a bunch of the Hitchcock movies, I was always like wondering,
where is the universal?
Where is the Statue of Liberty thing?
And it's in Saboteur because they would use chunks of that show in in Florida for the
Alfred Hitchcock show.
Yes, like they would reuse.
They used a lot of this stuff.
And then later on, the fluffy, the guy, the werewolf who comes to life with emotion is
used in the horror.
There's a horror makeup show at the Florida Park.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's kind of the big ending of that show.
So let's talk fluffy.
That's that's like a later thing that happened where that's supposed to be like a kid is
led to believe that he's doing motion capture and this big werewolf creature is doing exactly
what he does.
But then there's like a lightning strike as if, you know, the now the now fluffy is alive
and cursed and he runs around and scares kids like Carl.
Yeah, it scared me every time I saw it.
And I saw it a lot.
And it scared me every time.
Because this is a huge suit.
This is like an eight footer.
With the red eyes and it gets scarier every even when you walk by it, like when I'm going
in and this is the, you know, sixth week in a row that I'm at Universal Studios and I'm
going in and you walk past fluffy and he's just like, you know, down and you're just
like, this thing's about to do some crazy.
Yeah, they power him up.
They power him up.
Yeah, turns on.
Was the person in the suit the whole time?
Yes.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
There's no way to get in there.
Just has to watch everybody come by.
Probably looking at people being like, I'm about to scare that person.
I'm about to scare the shit out of that lady.
Yeah.
Because they're eyeing, they're knowing they're like, they're like figuring out who looks
like the best.
Yeah.
Like scare, I guess.
They always pick the smallest kid, like who volunteers for like motion capture.
Eight year old kid, kid eight or under come to the motion capture or whatever.
Yeah.
So you didn't, you never wanted to do that.
You never wanted to control Fluffy.
I did it once.
Oh really?
Because I think they kept seeing me every week and they were just like, you can do it.
Even though you're 12 and also 6'1".
You were already taller than Fluffy.
Taller than Fluffy.
Dunked on Fluffy.
Ran away from him faster than any of the kids did.
Yeah.
You childlike man.
Man like child.
Did you ever do, did you ever do the others?
Did you do like the sound?
The flowy.
I was mixing Fluffy and Foley.
The Foley was always very fun.
Yeah.
I mean learning about Foley, like that's a fun fact to know.
Like I was called Foley.
Yeah.
After a guy.
His name is James Foley.
James Foley.
Yeah.
Feels like one of those very tour guidey like, a gentleman named James Foley.
Now he's very well known for realizing that you could do the sound after the fact.
This show is a perfect mechanism for tour guide voice.
For the like saying information so quickly that you're not even meditating on what any
of the words mean.
And you're a super robot and you have everything memorized.
And the David Copperfield-esque.
Right.
It's just all, I don't even know what I'm saying anymore.
The words mean nothing to me.
Yes.
Yeah.
It's all rhythm.
It's just this music.
Like radio DJ voice.
Yeah.
Where it's just like it doesn't matter what they're saying.
As long as the rhythm is this way.
And saying it at lightning speed.
Just occasionally punching a word like that.
There were old, I was watching old videos of this though.
And there were some old like hosts that didn't do it as much.
They were much more like, I'm trying to think of the word.
They would just like throw stuff away.
They're much more lazy about it.
And then it seems, especially now it's turned into what you're saying.
The very slick host voice and there's no personality really.
You know I auditioned in 2013.
This is like 2012.
Like two years, two, three years into improv.
So I'm kind of feeling myself being like, oh man, I'm about to go.
I'm about to get this job.
Y'all bullshitting.
I got cut after the first round.
What?
Yeah.
I made it to the hotel.
I made it to the Beverly Garland.
Beverly Garland?
Yes.
It was still that?
Yeah.
I made it to the Beverly Garland.
Which that's the improv step.
That's where you get up on stage and they give you some topic and you have to go off.
Yeah.
And I made the people laugh.
But then they, at the end, they did not call my number.
Jeez.
What?
And one guy that did get to stay, I was like, how did this guy get to stay?
Like it was this older black dude who did not have, he had a interesting stage presence.
But it was not one that I would want to see.
He ended up getting cut like the next round.
But it was like, how did he beat me in a round?
I should at least made it to the third round.
Sure.
Is this for tour guide or for special effects?
Yeah, for tour guide.
For tour guide.
Okay.
That's madness to me.
And then you're, yeah, you're like great at UCB, immediately F'd, but not good enough
for the tour.
Yeah, I can't do the tour.
He definitely can't do the tour.
It seemed like the perfect job because you get off for auditions and stuff like that.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
And it's extremely flexible, especially because you get the job and then the first summer,
they don't use you almost ever.
Really?
Yeah, it's forcibly flexible.
Do they still pay you?
Yeah, you get paid minimum wage to do the training.
Oh yeah.
And then you still might not make it past the training.
So if you made it all the way through, you might have just done like three weeks of classes
for which you're paid almost nothing.
Yeah.
And then still you might have gotten cut.
It's like, it's cutthroat.
It's cutthroat.
It's tough.
Did you do it once or were you, like is it, because you know, UCB Herald team, it took
me four auditions to get on the Herald team and I was like, next year, next year.
And were you like this, you didn't do it more than once to try to?
No.
Yeah, you were just.
No, because that process was ridiculous.
We had to wait outside the city walk for like four hours.
Geez.
Yeah.
And then finally you get in there and you talk to the person for 20 seconds.
And they just like mark on your resume or not.
And then they'll go, okay, here's a slip.
Come back to the Beverly Garner this time.
I tried it in 2008 and that like literally the month that George Bush was like, we are
in a recession and the news, news crews were there because it was like record people showing
up for the first round of interviews, which they timed with a bell.
Like you have one minute to sell yourself.
Yeah.
And like most people didn't even get to the hotel.
Like because it was so gnarly.
Like there.
Did you get to the hotel?
No, I didn't get to the hotel.
Geez.
I mean, I just like started, but like I.
We're making Scott look real good though here.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
You guys just didn't have what it took.
Yeah, clearly.
Again, it's all about saying things as fast as you possibly can.
Universal Studios, entertainment capital.
You just, you needed to talk at double speed is what you had to do.
I do wonder the origin of that, that speaking.
Yeah, me too, because everything like this.
And if you go see a tour type attraction in Florida, it's this too.
It's not like it's just like an LA thing.
Theme park headset mic based attractions.
Yeah.
Mac Orley was talking about he's fascinated with like where it's like where certain voices start.
Like that's just sort of a voice you assume.
And it's same with like radio announcer.
There's just a voice that everybody does.
Where does who starts that voice?
Yeah.
Why?
Who says to me, my favorite is like the black radio show, like advertisement for like the club that weekend.
It's going down this weekend.
Club wet wet.
We got thirsty Thursdays on Obama night.
We celebrate no bomb of y'all.
I love what's the first one.
You want to know like who started it?
Yeah.
The pioneer of.
I dreamed of a different way of speaking.
Monster truck shows like monster truck announcer.
Oh yeah.
Like Grave Friday.
Friday.
It's the same since the 80s or whatever those started.
But at some point that someone had to invent repeating it.
Hey, I have an idea.
Call me crazy.
What if people, I just want people to remember that it's going to be Saturday.
What is it?
Would it be weird if I said Saturday, Saturday, Saturday?
This sucks.
Get him out of here.
Wait, wait, wait.
Listen to me.
This guy might be on.
Let him talk.
Threat three times.
The man who invented saying the day of the week three times.
This is a statue we built to him.
A pioneer.
In front of a monster truck rally.
And he made no money for doing that.
He's an unsung hero.
Where were we though?
We were talking.
We were going to talk.
Foley.
Learning about Foley.
I think Foley is interesting.
It was like fun and cool and tactile to watch as a kid because you're seeing like here's
a box of leaves and you're like, you know, putting shoes in them.
Yeah.
Or coconuts or whatever for a horse clop.
Oh, Fluffy comes back at Foley.
Usually.
Oh, you're right.
At least in a version.
Like someone goes in a sound booth.
Oh yes.
Because like that's the big conclusion of the show.
I was trying to remember what's the climax of the show and it's someone messes up their
Foley and then they send them into a sound booth where you just see a silhouette.
Like it's very clearly a video monitor because I saw one online where it glitches for a second.
Like then it's the silhouette again.
But then the silhouette gets ravaged by Fluffy.
Fluffy comes back in silhouette form.
Fluffy kills.
Fluffy kills this volunteer.
Fluffy also it was implied Fluffy killed the first host in the second scene.
Right.
Because then the sticky guy like takes over the show.
The guy who would like every time there'd be an effect he would scream and run away.
Oh he's a co-host who does like almost nothing and then he nervously has to take over because
the other guy died.
Yeah.
But then I think some shows would end with like then the door would swing open of the
sound booth and the first host would come out with their clothes all torn and like thank
you for coming.
Thank you for.
But then I saw one video where it was just like the first host just kind of wanders out
in their normal clothes and waves goodbye to everyone.
Well you gotta do that all day.
They have more jobs there now.
Like other stuff.
Like dinosaur handlers.
Oh yeah.
Oh yeah right.
There's a lot of stuff.
And then like inside there's the giant Triceratops that walks and I think there's multiple people
in that.
At least two.
There's like an old it's like an old horse costume.
Like someone's the Triceratops' ass.
That's gotta be terrible during the summer.
Yeah.
Oh yeah Jesus.
But they gotta there's like people that have to like walk it out and then there's people
inside it I believe.
My summer job is I'm a Triceratops' ass.
Person at the top just so you know I had limpy for lunch at City Walk.
So have fun.
Zzzz.
Oh god.
Why's that ass coughing so much?
In some of my first improv class I met a couple guys who would do the special effects show
as like their day job.
Like they're like yeah it's like doing four or five improv shows a day essentially and
you get 150 bucks and yeah it's all right you know a few hours of work.
It's fine.
Yeah you just scream and say some facts.
Not much of a recommendation then.
That's fine.
That's about what it's like.
I'm still jealous of those people who do the tour guy.
Like I'll be on the tour more successful than you.
I'm on a good place.
Yeah you may have gotten this but I'm on a good place.
I mean yes.
I think any other job you can get immediately makes you more successful than the tour.
Just because I didn't get that job.
I'm just bitter.
But it does.
I've always said it ruled for like my first summer doing it was such a dream.
It was so awesome.
And then immediately summer two was like oh god this again.
How many years did you do it?
Like I did it a lot for two summers and then really sporadically after that.
And often just so I could get free parking at CityWalk.
I stayed on the schedule for a little while.
Didn't work for like I had like other full time jobs and was still on the schedule just for the free parking.
So if I got a shift I was like oh god damn it.
What do I do now?
I have to go tell my full time job.
Do you mind if I go work another job today?
You said before you would not mind doing this a little bit.
Of course.
Still.
If I could do it once a month I'd be psyched.
If you were offer only Carl on the tram tour would you?
They're like yeah you don't have to audition anymore but you can come in a couple times a month.
At this point I am intimidated by the training.
I mean like I don't feel like it.
But what if they said no training we'll give you the notes.
And I get to make it oh yeah I do that shit.
That'd be fun.
You don't have to learn any clip numbers.
Somebody will like sit behind you and do it all for you.
There will be another person there that can be like yeah this is the part where they talk about the shark not working.
Oh yeah I've watched Universal Story enough times.
It feels like it's all in there.
Day 27 is haunted.
The whole lot feels out of Africa.
1985.
You know what that big lake is?
Like where the big green screen was.
Things like that.
They use this lake in cocoon.
Statistically you could say that about most things on that property.
You might be right.
Like cocoon, Van Helsing.
Coach is the one.
I love seeing the Coach House.
That was one of my favorite things because I liked Coach.
Then the theme song would play.
Hell yeah.
Yeah everybody likes it.
Southwestern Minnesota State baby.
How's the theme song go?
You know what I'm getting mixed up.
I can't think of it exactly in my head.
I'm getting mixed up with the theme song to Recess right now.
But it's kind of similar to that.
I think what's playing in my head is Major Dad.
Is Coach kind of like a football fight song?
Yeah it is.
Yeah yeah yeah.
Okay okay.
Got it.
I remember a big coach poster by the special.
Like if I'm in line for the special effects stage.
There's a huge coach.
And they sold coach merch also.
Around this area.
Coach bags.
People are going to go is this a coach bag?
And they put it in the front.
Yeah.
Technically yes.
Craig T. Nelson on the side of a bag.
Jerry Van Dyke was funny as hell on that show.
Yeah.
He's an unsung.
He was always like a side character.
But he doesn't get enough credit.
I was going to say they were trying to bring Coach back a few years ago.
Yeah I remember that.
But for some reason.
I guess people's appetite for Coach wasn't as strong as they wanted.
I signed the petition.
Coach.
Bring it back.
They were all alive maybe at that point too.
Probably.
Are they now?
Yeah he's dead.
Really?
He was the older brother right?
I think he's younger.
I gotta look this up.
I'm worried that he's not dead.
He's dead.
A million dollars that Jerry Van Dyke is dead.
Put the pennies on the eyes.
We're going to the graveyard.
We're going to Hollywood forever right now.
I'm going to prove this.
Read it and weep Gardner.
There it is. Read it.
Put it on the podcast.
He died in 2018.
January 5th.
It was my birthday.
Really?
He is younger than Dick.
That sucks.
Dick must have took that hard.
Probably.
I believe the trivia is that Jerry Van Dyke had two options for shows at one point to star.
It was Gilligan's Island or My Mother the Car.
He went with the show My Mother the Car.
Who would he have been in Gilligan's Island?
Gilligan I believe.
I believe he would have been Gilligan on Gilligan's Island.
He went with the show that was about the
wife's ghost living inside a car.
I mean to be fair, at that time, like 1966 probably.
Yeah.
65, 66 somewhere in there.
That probably was revolutionary.
Cars were around for like 30 years at that point but still kind of like just getting popping.
Sure.
And the idea that a wife's ghost or a mother's ghost was in the car was probably like this is going to be hilarious.
The main character is going to be a car.
Yeah.
Also endless stories with that trapped on an island.
How many stories can you possibly do?
Right.
That's what he was thinking.
But that might have been a thing that may have haunted him.
Like a ghost.
Until my 29th birthday.
Until one faithful girl's birthday.
You'll always know now.
You absorbed his life force.
For another year.
Coach.
Every birthday now you will know.
Yeah.
That this was the day Jerry Maddyke passed.
Let's talk about another weird old show.
Harry and the Hendersons.
Oh yeah.
Because the finale of this show for a long time, a long time, was you have to do the sound effects for Harry and the Hendersons.
Yeah.
This was a syndicated show that ran from like 91 to 93.
And in 1999,
I think it was like the first time in the history of the show.
Yeah.
And it was like the first time in the history of the show.
And in 1999,
you could still go on an attraction
where the idea is
this is a new episode
that we're making.
And at some point in time,
there's a mistake and all of the sound effects
get erased.
And the voice in the back of the booth
says, the network called,
we're going on the air live
in one minute.
So we have to live broadcast the sounds.
For a syndicate.
There is no network.
Yeah.
There is not a network in this scenario.
I forgot that was syndicated.
It came on every day?
No, not like that. I recall seeing it like Saturday afternoons.
Yeah.
Something like that.
Like after Gulliver's Travels or something.
Yeah.
In the Zenub zone.
VIP.
Oh yeah.
She spies.
Relic Hunter.
Right before JAG.
What a boring time.
Like a boring day of television.
If all those shows
were coming out, I knew that I was like,
man, I don't have anything to do today.
I gotta go outside.
You gotta get to Universal.
Yeah, you like failed
in your day.
All you have to do is watch.
There's a weird Gene
Roddenberry related show
called Andromeda or something.
Andromeda, yeah.
I would be like, what is this?
Star Trek ripoff.
There was a martial arts themed
kind of like WWE thing.
Oh, but that was cool.
What was that called? Kung Fu Masters or something?
Something like that.
It was like Power Rangers.
Very of the time of
Power Rangers.
VR Troopers?
No, it was more of presenting it as a reality like WWE.
It was like ninjas fighting
WWE style.
You tracked it week to week?
Who's winning in the middle?
Yeah, there were story lines.
So that was the idea.
It was like live mortal combat.
The time period where every kid was taking karate after school.
And the Power Rangers are all doing karate.
Very weird.
Very short lived.
So anyway, back to
the syndicated.
My favorite Saturday syndicated show
was a show called Your Big Break
that was hosted by Alfonso
Riviero. And did you ever see
the show? Oh, man.
I was like, who knows this?
It's sort of an American
Idol type scenario
except the prize is you get
to pretend to be
a star of your choosing
in a big production number.
I don't think I've ever seen that.
You go into
a magic door and then
there's a bunch of fog and then you walk
back out dressed as
Elvis or
Michael Jackson or
Whitney Houston or whatever it is.
It's so great. And my
my very favorite one was
that a guy wanted to be Neil
Diamond. And it's
regular people. It's like accountants
or people who work at call centers or whatever.
He goes in the door and then comes
back out Neil Diamond. And then he
this guy sang
Coming to America.
Wow. A little like
stage set of an Ellis
Island staircase.
Coming off of a ship was rolled out
and a bunch of like early 1900s
immigrants walked down the stairs
like from Ireland to France
and waved.
They're coming
to America.
This is before like this is
kind of like the early
version of like lip sync battle almost.
It's like a cousin to lip sync battle.
But with regular people
not celebrities. You guys remember Great Pretenders?
Where kids it was on it was
hosted by Fergie and her
singing room like Wild Orchid.
Fergie's original.
It came on
ABC Family or Fox Family.
It was called back then. It's called Freeform now.
But like it was called Great Pretenders.
Fergie with like a lot
Fergie and like you know
midriff leather pants and like too much
lip liner. Fergie looks bizarre.
Welcome back to Great Pretenders.
And they would always like sing
that part.
We're not pretending.
We really sing. We're Wild Orchid.
Yeah.
But these kids are pretending to sing.
I used to love that show.
Would kids would they lip sync?
Yeah. Okay. So that's also
interesting.
So they would dress up. They would
lip sync and then give them like a stage
set up. And do like do like a routine.
Like I remember one I remember a group of kids
doing the Friends theme song.
But they weren't lip syncing to it.
They just danced around like a fake
fountain with white turtleneck songs.
Yeah. Whoa.
Wow. But they did the wait.
They didn't lip sync? No.
Because the friends don't sing
the song.
I kind of wish they did though. Yeah.
Kids seeing kids anytime when I
was a kid seeing kids do anything
was just I was obsessed with it. I don't think
there was a bad show where kids like Wild
and Crazy Kids like that
was I was obsessed with. But anytime they had kids
doing anything I was so jealous
of those kids. Yeah. I didn't watch
that show as a kid but I would have been so
jealous of the kids running around the Friends
fountain. Oh I was way too shy
to do anything like that. Yeah.
And yet I was so jealous of those kids.
That's gotta be fun. Yeah.
And you're like it's their sheer confidence
that got them this.
That I don't have and I'll never have. Yeah.
I can't believe I do what I do now.
Because I was the shyest kid. Oh really?
Like for a long time like through high school
and whatever you were
inward and. Yeah.
Well not inward like I was
what is it called?
An extroverted introvert?
Yeah. Okay. Yeah. Yeah.
Get the energy up. Yeah.
And be very shy. Yes. Yes. Absolutely.
Sure. Sure. Sure. I feel like I was like that
and still am like that. Sure. I think I am too.
I feel like a lot of comedy. Yeah. People in comedy are.
It felt like a fight to get me out.
It felt like I was fighting myself a lot.
To like express myself.
Sure. Sure. Okay.
And I used to because I used to do like we would
make videos with my sister and she would
be the host and I would always just have a puppet.
Yeah. And it's like it's clear
that like I was a little too scared
to be on camera. So the puppet
was brave. The puppet was
very brave. Yeah.
I would make like Barney talk or something.
Her Barney doll. But I was too
scared to be on camera.
What weirdos we are.
Yeah. Yeah. It's true.
We have the confidence now.
Sort of. Yeah. Yeah. Mildly.
All right. So Harry
and the Hendersons. I don't know.
I just love that bizarre.
And then sometimes in this show
Harry himself
because he would usually culminate
in like a very nervous
woman. And
often they would give this job to somebody who could not
speak English so that they could kind of make
fun of the person for their lack of ability
to speak English. Sure. She doesn't
understand the instructions. Something that Copperfield
still does to this day. That's right.
Yes. If you go see the Copper. David
Copperfield show. It's so many jokes
about like probably
a plant. But a woman in the audience
is a plant that can't speak English well. And
he like haha I can't understand anything you
said.
He was dead. Copperfield. David Copperfield?
Which magician died?
I say it like that. Which magician died?
Houdini died.
Which magician in history
died? Lance Burton is still alive.
A new guy. Like a younger guy that
was doing Vegas who passed away a couple years ago.
Oh Danny Gans. Danny Gans.
He wasn't really a magician. That's what I'm
mixing. Oh Ricky Jay died?
I don't know who that is. I was thinking Danny Gans.
Okay. How many
magicians have died? And have any
of them really? Since Houdini.
Speaking of syndicated TV.
You remember Magic Secrets Revealed?
I felt so guilty
watching that.
Like I am not supposed to know
like I knew about the secrets
magicians don't reveal their
secrets. And I would be like
do I want to know these secrets?
Will I still enjoy the TV specials
if I know the secrets? And then
he unmasked and it was just a guy.
Like they built it up.
You were hoping like it was
Lance Burton or Copperfield.
And they were all mad at him.
I don't think those were the real ways
that they do those tricks though.
Sometimes it's like come on we're not that dumb.
I can't remember
specifically but
I feel like people were supposedly
mad. I feel like your David Copperfields
were upset about it. And I could
be wrong about that. Yeah and then the guy
had to give a speech kind of like calming everyone
down. But this
we're celebrating magic and that's wonderful.
And he was like a creep in a ponytail
who was in my head was named like
Touche or something.
I
really hope that
Touche was the man who
took his mask off. It is I
Touche.
Those were kind of the death rattle
of magic specials I feel like.
Like that was kind of the end of the run.
Besides like David Blaine.
David Blaine ones were built up so
much of like he's going to do a stunt.
It did feel like sleazy I think about it.
Like in my little kid brain I was like
oh we shouldn't be watching this at all.
They all looked like they were filmed in the
total eclipse of the heart video
with the doves and the fog.
The warehouses with the lights shooting through the
windows. It's also around the time of
the Jonathan Frakes hosted Beyond
Belief Fact or Fiction. Similar to Step Out.
It would come on after that. Which would come on after.
They looked like they were in the same studio a little
bit like the camera looked the quality
of the video looked the same.
They just moved everything out.
Jonathan Frakes walks up. Have you ever dropped an ice cream cone?
And then they just
shipped the other show in there.
I've said it
for years. He should have had like an Adam
West something.
He's so funny on that.
He wasn't trying to be funny on that.
But when you see the super cuts of it you've seen those
right? Yeah yeah yeah. The many questions
in a row. Have you ever turned on a lamp and the
light bulb didn't work?
Have you ever tripped down the stairs and
hit your head really hard?
Nervous like so
sincerely.
It's not like he's not trying
to be like a deliver like he's an airplane
or anything. It's so fucking
funny. Have you ever adopted a big foot
and had him live with you for a long time?
Like carrying him.
Have you ever wake up screaming?
Have you ever picked up an ice cream cone you found
on the floor?
And then he has like someone else do it.
And then he'll like do it or he'll get off like if it's like
have you ever ridden a bike angrily?
And then he'll like have a helmet on
and he'll take it off.
Like he always has a prop with him.
They did one for
a football game a couple weeks ago.
He recreated one.
As a goof.
I forget what football game it was.
He's back at it? He's back at it.
He's like owning the meme like Rick Astley.
Jonathan Frakes back in the game.
I had a lunch box with
Captain Picard, Jonathan Frakes, and
Data on it. Sure.
Not a big fan of Star Trek Next Generation.
Scared of it. Another fear of mine.
Whoopi Goldberg. Whoopi Goldberg terrified me.
Because of just the way she
was dressed? Yeah.
I was very young. She's like a sorceress
or something.
She's a guy and she's lived for a long time.
She's lived for hundreds of years.
Her eyes like rolled back into her head one time
that I was like I was very afraid of Whoopi Goldberg as a
child. Interesting. No matter what?
Yeah.
In other like in Ghost,
in Theodore Rex.
I'll give you a couple reasons.
In 1990,
I won.
But my mother
is in college at the time.
And she,
her college gets to open up, college
marching band gets to open up for
Motown 30.
The celebration of Motown. Wow.
At the Pantages Theater here in Los Angeles. We're still in Mississippi
at the time. This was like her trip to LA
and she was like I'm coming back.
And we eventually did. Wow. And I ended up
growing up here. But like this is when we're still in Mississippi
and we would play this tape
over and over again to see my mom like marching down
Hollywood Boulevard going into
the Pantages because she was like the flag
girl for the college. And
Whoopi Goldberg
hosted.
And in the beginning she did this like Diana Ross
bit where she had this long wig on.
And then she like turns around, snatches the wig off
and puts it under her armpit.
Like as a joke. It was a joke like
if you need me call me. Which is something that
Diana Ross would say. But honey don't call me before
nine because I don't get up.
And then she snatched the wig off and everybody goes
Ah it's Whoopi. She's ugly.
Like people used to diss. Oh dude
people used to diss Whoopi Goldberg so much.
It was like a joke.
Oh yeah this is a really Ian Simpson's joke I think
about naked pictures of her or something.
Yeah it's bad.
But that was scary.
The cover to the movie
Telephone that I would always pass by
in the video store.
I gotta look this up. You gotta look the cover up.
It looks like she doesn't have eyes.
But she's just like looking to the side.
It's also her worst
movie ever. It's a really dumb
movie. Did you
better than Theodore Rex or worse?
Worse probably. Oh boy.
Wait you were afraid of the wig thing. I was afraid of
the wig thing. I was afraid of the cover.
And then her on
Star Trek The Next Generation which was in
syndication by the time I was conscious enough
to recognize it. No it wasn't
that one. It was like that one.
Oh I was terrified of that.
Oh wait does she have kind of like
cat eyes? What's going on
with the pupils? I think her
locks are blocking her eye
in a way that makes it weird. She looks a little
like demonic or something. I could see how yeah if you
were like this is a different
is this the same one? The trippy background.
Yeah it is.
Everything about this picture I'm just like
whoopee. Wow. I have never heard
of The Telephone.
It's news to me. It's the rest
of your day now.
Y'all have to watch The Telephone.
After you watch Harry and the Hitties go watch The Telephone.
Yikes. I was scared of Star Trek The Next Generation
but I was scared because there was one episode
where Data got possessed. I mean it wasn't his evil
brother Lore.
It was like there was some weird symbol
all of a sudden appeared on his head and he was scary.
I watched it in the hospital once. My sister
was in the hospital and I watched it on a
TV and it was like in my
memory it's like the Poltergeist TV
of like I'm just staring at this creepy show.
Oh yeah. And then like I think months
later I like worked up the courage to start
watching it and liked it.
You associate it with
medical issues and
I had to introduce the summer I started
as a tour guide was when Whoopi started
hosting it and I
just presented these clips.
You had to play them and they said we might
secret shop you.
So like don't there's this list of things
you have to do and those include the new
Whoopi clips because we don't want her getting
on and then you didn't play them all.
She worked hard filming all the
things. They were threatening
the Whoopi would do like just a random
tram tour.
Undercover boss. No yeah yeah
she might.
She is scared of the
plane flight. Is that right?
I don't know when she's the yeah she like I think she
like now famously
doesn't go on an airplane.
She travels by bus. There was
a rumor when I was in school in
Ithaca that Whoopi had a house
somewhere on the lake like somewhere
in the town. Rumor. Because there was
like people would be like I saw her.
I saw her and the grocery store had a
video store like built
in. Had a big video section.
Video and DVDs and stuff. And there
was like a mural of stars
and Whoopi was the biggest.
And they're like that's a little nod to our
our local residents. Our neighbors. And I never
quite got an answer of like
is this real? Is this just
like college kids fucking with each other
or is like Whoopi actually? But I was like well
if she needs a vacation place and she doesn't
fly she could train up
from New York or take a car service.
Like I was trying to justify
Whoopi lore. How does this balance
with what you know?
Yeah. Wow. You went to Ithaca too?
Yeah. Were you there with the birthday boys?
I was a couple years behind them.
What is all these people going to Ithaca for?
That's a college I never even heard of
until I met those guys. I think I hadn't either.
Yeah.
The birthday boys were a few
years older than me and Joe Para was like
three years younger than me. I didn't know that one.
And Bob Iger went
there. Iger went there years
before. Andy Seconda and Andy
Daley. They were long before.
Yeah. John Bally.
Two colleges I had never heard
of until I started doing improv was Ithaca
and Emerson. Neither one of those.
Because out here everybody goes to Cal State
Northridge. And if you got better grades
you go to UCLA.
Were you one of those? No. Neither. I didn't have
I went to a small school in Ohio
to play basketball. Oh really? Okay.
Oh you left and came back. Yeah.
Were there any theme parks out in Ohio?
Cedar Rapids. I went to Cedar
Rapids. No Cedar Point.
That's all coasters though. I went to Iowa.
I went to Cedar Point.
Didn't I get on anything?
They have a full half court
basket that you can do three point
shooting contest on. And I literally
sat on that all day and just won people
gifts. Wow.
That's a good story. Yeah.
I'm not getting on anything else.
Who you came with or random people?
Yeah people who I came with or random
kids if they like if I
I didn't make enough shots and only got like a little
bear. But I went home with like three novelty
like basketballs like
University of Florida, University of Michigan
like and I like
I was just on that all day like you gotta stop
like you spent so much money on this.
I spent like a hundred bucks on that that day
but I was like I'm not getting on anything else
here at this whole place. Yeah.
You were that consistent also with your
three point shots? Oh yeah. Wow.
Was it like one of those rigged?
No no no it was just the court. It was just a regular
Yeah yeah. Because they have obviously I'm talking about
yeah they're like you know like
the three point but the basket
you have to literally like get it perfectly in
and it can't touch anything or else it will fall out.
Yeah no this is just a regular basket.
Yeah Cedar Point is a terrifying one.
There's like you can't like
everything's fine.
That's only coasters. That's only like
and the scariest one. And the lake
right? There's a big lake.
Lake Erie. Yeah.
Okay.
I'm glad we're tangenting so much because whatever
it's fine. What do we need
to say about the uh
what have we missed? Well
I just loved like Universal
didn't have the best run of movies
in the aughts. Like
it is very funny how
like how much
Van Helsing stuff stuck around
in some of the special effects.
Van Helsing and then
the
special effect one special effect thing
I watched where they're doing the Foley.
They had switched it to like alright
we're gonna do Foley for the scene from
Evan Almighty.
And it's like oh okay
we're still doing the Evan Almighty
Foley. There was a
I'm interested in that because they did
I didn't see that one but then I saw one with The Clumps
with Nutty Professor 2. Yeah.
Clumps was in there for a while. They did that for a while.
And the video I saw had
a part where they got the volunteer from the audience
and the host says alright so everybody
get ready because Patricia is about to have
dinner with The Clumps.
Very exciting one.
And you get to be put in
like it's like another green screen one right?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah that I remember that one.
I think that was like around the last time
that I was going. Yeah. Okay. Okay. Yeah.
There's not a
good no one has kept a good
record of the changes to
the show. I was trying to find
no one gives a shit.
Scorpion King Shrek
Did you go through the YouTube or did you find a
No I just found a couple
of lists on the Studio
Tour dot com which catalogues
Universal Hollywood stuff. A couple of months ago I watched
a studio tour from like 1986
just to see what it was
see what was different from when I was doing in the early
2000s. Yeah. And
there was like a laser. King Kong
was still there. Yeah. Which I believe it
is still there. Burned down.
Oh it burned down. Yeah. So now they have like a
3D Kong. Oh okay.
Yeah. That old King Kong was there
from like 1976 like from when the movie
came out. For a long time. Yeah.
Made a long time. Yeah. Big awesome robot.
That was one of the best parts of that job. Yeah.
I see that all the time. You would yell at
right? You would yell at Kong? Yeah.
That was your favorite part? Yes. Cause I'd stand up
and really give it a lot of gusto and like make
it about make it personal about the people
in the tram like
like if anyone take
me I've lived my life but these
children they are young
they've done nothing to upset you
don't take a rag around on them.
Did you feel the audience
liked it? Or were you just sort of
like what I was doing? Yeah.
They weren't paying attention. Okay.
It was for me more than anything. That's my question.
I think they liked that I stood up and like shook
my fist and leaned out of the
I like really gave it cause
it's the worst to have the people just like
alright now we're about to see King Kong
uh if you feel his man of breath
and the heat of the flames
that doesn't make any narrative sense. Why would the
person be bored by King Kong?
You have man breath. I like that
banana breath. That was always funny.
Now the Peter Jackson King Kong feels
like it got put in everywhere
in that park so quickly. Yes.
So much. Well that's what
When it was coming out
while it was out while the DVD was
at like this special effects show they just like
you know the 2004 Kong
starring Adrian Brody and
Naomi Watts. You love it. You all love it.
That movie was just sold to us.
It's like this is
it's the Lord of the Rings guy and you love this.
To tie it back to
Whoopi, the my most
hated video on the tram
was where she is outside actually
of Halford Hitchcock's bungalow.
The bungalows were producers of offices
on the lot and she
gets a megaphone out and she has a message
for the various producers who were around there
and she says people
of Hollywood producers
I've got a pitch for you
less movies with giant
monkeys more movies
with me.
It plays out at about that speed.
No one laughs. Never
in several summers not one person
ever laughed at this. Then
she repeats it.
Less movies with the giant
monkey. It's slower this
time and I have to play this.
I have no idea. It dies a horrible
death every single time.
I don't blame her as much as whoever
wrote it. This was a garbage video.
If you ever had to sit through this on the tram
any listeners I apologize
and trust me the tour guides
did not want to play it. I am sure I saw this.
I have no memory of this. I mean I really all I do
remember is just her getting eaten by scarabs.
Yes. Yeah. I remember that.
I think that might have been like around the last time.
I'm trying to figure out when's the last time I went
to Universal.
I graduated high school 2007. It had to be
around 06.
Probably when you were doing like
had to be around that time. Yeah.
Like the last time.
Absolutely still would have been Whoopi.
But Whoopi's still on it now as I said before.
She gets eaten still right?
Yes. The rest of it is Jimmy Fallon but they
couldn't figure out how to get her out of the mummy part.
So now if you go on the tram what happens is
Whoopi Goldberg suddenly appears
and is eaten by bugs immediately and that's
it. You don't know why she showed up.
It's totally out of context.
She hasn't appeared before. All of a sudden
they cut to her. Which I kind of like
that you have to say. It's bizarre.
Whoopi Goldberg.
And she is and then the bugs come.
But so much, yeah so much King Kong.
And so much mummy.
Because at one point in time
I was trying to add this up that
okay so there's that. There's that part of the
tour where the room spins around and that's based on the mummy.
That's not there anymore. You could go there at one point
you could go to Universal and go to that. It's part of the
tram. Then there's a maze
of the mummy. Then there's the mummy
coaster, the ride of course.
And then also the
part of this tour where the guy gets
electrocuted. There were four
mummy attractions in a
very limited park at one point in time.
The Scorpion King movie
and the Brendan Fraser mummies were
like huge hits.
But big enough to justify four
attractions? And getting rid of them.
It's them tying together.
I'm a big mummy fan. I do love that Brendan Fraser mummy.
Bring it back. Reboot it.
I think it's them also
high on their own supply.
The mummy, we made the classic
mummy and now the mummy's
back. It seems odd though that
they would have gotten rid of the back to the future thing to
put the mummy in. Because everyone loves back to
the future and still loves back to the future.
And the mummy hasn't I would argue maybe not
lasted like back to the future.
Well it's like when they say like so
the universe has made some of the most memorable
moments in movie history.
And it's like yeah it's Hitchcock stuff
and like classic movie
monsters and then the minions and
like it's the characters from Sing.
And it's like I don't know
as a society agreed these
things are equal yet.
Also
I saw a video that had a lot of
heroes. They had to push
heroes everywhere.
Claire Bennett the cheerleader.
Save the cheerleader.
As they constantly say Claire Bennett the cheerleader.
I think
this show I think this used to be a great show
and then it just became like a dumping ground for
what do we have to promote that's from recent.
One of the newer ones on
the upper lot it's like and now we're going to Foley
the film Identity Thief
starring Jason Bateman and Melissa
McCarthy. Yeah. And you're like what?
Yeah that's a trip. And then they love the guy on
fire.
And then I watched the family do it
and the bit kills still. Oh yeah.
It's still funny. Like she throws something
in Bateman's head and like it hits in one
of the family like hits like a pan.
Cowbell I think it is. Yeah.
That's the thing about this show. It all
kills. It was all great. Yeah. I
think legitimately they always did a good
job with it. And you
if you have fun memories of it and you
went like constantly. Yeah.
That's a testament to it. It was always
very fun. I really enjoyed
going. I remember I would go in the back
draft and I remember
saying it's like such a loser ass kid
because I would go every week.
And so I knew that the pipes were going to fall
and I remember like looking at a person
being like you might not want to stand
there. I'm not going
to tell you why.
Like a little dickhead kid.
So like ruining surprise
for me. I've outsmarted this
thing. Yeah. I know what you mean.
And then still being scared when the pipes fell
because you don't know exactly when they're going to fall.
Yeah.
I was just going to say, did
you watch the upper lot version
of the show? Yes.
We didn't talk about who
the new mocap thing is.
Oh, yeah. What is it?
It's a little bear named Ted.
Oh, yeah.
Ted is now in the show.
And instead of fluffy, it's Ted.
And Ted doesn't kill anybody or anything.
But he's he says
I think he says friggin sweet at a certain
point. And then like he hits his butt
and he goes like this is for the ladies.
Yeah. He shakes his butt out.
Shaking his butt and like slapping his own butt.
Yeah. That probably works
pretty well. Yeah, it works great. Getting Ted
in the park is not the worst idea.
It'd be a little outdated if there was a Ted ride now.
But maybe they should have had a walker.
Ted is on the tour by the bungalows.
There's that big Ted. There's a statue
with Ted. Yeah. He has a martini.
He has a martini, yes.
That's that crazy son of a bitch.
He's doing it. Ted III eventually.
Or MacFarlane too busy
with the Orville.
With his Star Trek.
Yes. I read a rumor that he was going to
buy Star Trek the other day.
What? Buy it?
I'm not saying that's going to happen. Yes, he was going to buy
it from Viacom.
How do you guys think money
works at that point?
Money is not real.
When you're having that discussion, it's like oh, money isn't
real. Ratings, numbers
are not real.
But he's one of those people where if you ever stop
and add up, you know,
all right, so he gets money just from like
one episode of being a voice actor.
Let alone that he's on every episode
of many shows
that air all the time. Let alone that
he also wrote the shows. Let alone that he's also in Ted.
Let alone that like, does he have like
seven billion dollars? How much money
does this guy? Yeah. He's got a lot of money.
He's got a lot of money. Probably. So he could
buy Star Trek, honestly. But
does he like write a check?
For Star Trek? He pays you the order of Star Trek.
Yeah.
To Captain Picard.
Yeah, he buys it from Captain Picard.
Money's like wired at that point, right?
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, he is a guy.
And then that guy does
it. Yeah. Through something
that we don't even understand. Yeah. It's like
a computer, but it's not. Like we...
It's through a holding corp. It's called like
Giggity Giggity Inc.
Yes.
But it's in like a different country and
you have to go there to
buy Star Trek.
Congrats. Congrats on the purchase.
So I guess, yeah, let's confirm the rumor. Seth McFarlane
is buying Star Trek. He's buying Star Trek.
He's done. He just got on a flight to Switzerland.
Um, because
Orville was suddenly in the Star Trek universe,
that'd be pretty crazy. Oh, he just
combines them? Yeah, maybe. Why not?
He is just making Star Trek.
So why not?
Get... Jonathan Frakes directs Orville episodes.
Oh, really? Yes, Jonathan Frakes is a
successful television director.
Yeah. In the second half of his career.
Wow. Alright. So the ultimate
spaceman. And then eventually it'll all buy
Star Wars back from Disney.
Yeah. Star Trek and Star Wars will combine
at a certain point. Star Wars versus
Star Trek can finally happen. What a dream.
There was an X-Men versus Star Trek
comic I had and I was obsessed with it.
Cool. And the only thing I can remember
is that Kirk hits on Jean Grey.
That's pretty exciting, huh?
Did Stan Lee
draw her naked?
He drew her naked and
signed the boob and then he drew Kirk naked and
signed his penis.
I'm drawing Captain Kirk
nude for the first time.
Look close. That's not a
pub.
It's my signature. It's my signature.
I'm drawing now.
What? Any other memories of this
thing we missed? There's a guy on
fire. A guy gets lit on fire. Oh yeah.
Yeah. That's cool. And the audience
just seems horrified by it more than
anything. They all kind of feel like, oh.
The image is haunting of a
man on fire. Guy's really
upset. It's kind of
upsetting.
There's a weird preamble to it where they're
like dousing them with chemicals
to show you how they prevent it.
He's got a face mask on.
They all just seem
miserable. Like, I gotta get lit on fire again
today. God damn it.
He's like counting
down like, all right, I've been lit on fire three times.
Just three more to go.
Might be lunch soon.
Yeah. He's only that dog Brown's chicken.
Yeah.
I can't imagine that job.
No. Probably not.
Because on a movie set, maybe you do it
like once per shoot. Like a day.
There's a day of being lit on fire.
All day. But all day, every
day, five days a week.
Being lit on fire at Universal
Studios.
If you're a fire person, let us know how it is.
We'll come talk to us.
More exciting for an audience than learning about how
they created all the fairies in Hellboy
2, The Golden Army. Another
segment that stuck around for a while.
That's not, yeah.
But they still do the fire,
right? Somebody gets lit on fire still?
I believe so. In the new show.
In the new show, for sure.
We don't like as much what they're doing these days
in these identity thieves and Hellboys.
What are they, we're
forgetting to plus it up. How do we make this show
great again? How do we take it back to its glory
days? Make this special effects show
great again.
I like that phrase.
Do we bring back maybe Harry
and Fluffy fight?
Harry and Fluffy fight.
Ted though. Yeah, him too.
Ted falls off the Statue of Liberty.
Sure. Like in Saboteur.
Well what's popular now? What is popular
in 2020? Minions. Minions are still
popular. I don't know what
Universal makes right now. Jurassic
World. Well they made
Cats and
what's the other big one? Doolittle.
Cats and Doolittle are their
properties. I wish those were hits
though. Cause a Cats thing,
a special effects Cats show.
Where you mocap, move the
cats around. Yeah, where you rum tum tugger.
Yeah.
That'd be tight. Yeah.
Maybe this is a separate attraction
but like Universal doing a show
that is the Jellicle Ball.
You get to go to the Jellicle Ball.
You couldn't be mad at that. Sure.
That would be good. Cat themed drinks.
Doolittle.
I don't know if you've read about Doolittle
at all. Doolittle
is not the greatest
movie in the world. It ends with Robert Dunning Jr
as Doolittle pulling bagpipes out of a
dragon's asshole.
Okay, I'm in.
So maybe I've sold it now.
That's the climax of the movie. That's like
the last thing he has to do when the movie is over.
So
something like with a dragon.
Well then, okay, so clearly what it is
and any of you guys feel free to be
the volunteer but let me just, I'll be
the host and then it's very
important that when the red button goes
then you need to make the sound
effect of bagpipes coming
out of a dragon's asshole. Okay,
so here we go. Look up at the screen and
Doolittle is pulling them out and
vroom, brrrr.
Vroom, brrrr.
Oh, dear.
And now we just need one more
thing. We're about to go live. We're going to go live
to theaters with Doolittle
It's broadcasting in one minute
and we need what is the sound
that the dragon, the pain sound that
the dragon makes and here we go
in three, two, one
Arrrrr Instagram
Alright, now we need you all to help
ADR Doolittle's lines because when
Robert did the first pass he couldn't understand
his Welsh accent so we need you all to say
It's okay to be scared
all at once. Alright?
Alright, on three. One, two, three
It's okay to be scared
We all make the same thing
Oh, hey
And very good
We saved Doolittle
Enjoy the rest of your day
The box office numbers are shooting up
It's 300 million in a weekend
It's bigger than Iron Man
It's profitable. You did it
Alright, thanks Carl, Mike, Scott
and Jason
And Carl, you survived podcast
The Ride. Thanks for being here
Thanks for having me. You can cut out some of those tangents
Never, never
What do you mean?
We'll cut out the regular stuff
We'll cut out the stuff about the topic instead
Hey, let's exit through the gift shop
Is there anything Carl that you would like to plug?
Listen to the flagrant ones
It's a Patreon, so you gotta dig
into your Seth MacFarlane pants
and take out your five dollars
Splash money around
like you said
If you like basketball, or if you don't
It's a basketball podcast hosted by me
Sean Clements and Hayes Davenport
of Hollywood Handbook, if you like that
Sure
And join us
Will you be going?
Do you have any like
I'd like to get better at rides
Or is it just
Oh no, I've settled into
Yeah, I'm not gonna be done
What about a Horror Nights situation?
I don't do that type of stuff either
I'll punch somebody
Alright, you're speaking my language
Hey, we also have a Patreon
Go to Patreon
Let's do both at once
Double drive to
Flagrant ones and to ours
Podcasts ride, the second gate at
Patreon.com slash podcast the ride
And we're on Twitter and Instagram
And Facebook
And we're
Almost done with the lower lot
We've covered almost all the attractions
Down here, not Transformers yet
And not Lucy Attribute
I feel like we gotta be heading to Lucy Attribute
I'm still building to that opus
Lucy Attribute is gonna be
Two plus, I think
That's gonna be a big one
We're recording second episode after this Scott
That I think will be one of your like dissertation
Like opuses
Lucy Attribute
Yeah, I pushed it cause I was sick
And I didn't feel up to it but now I think I'm ready
I think, but we'll see
I might collapse during it
But if you wanna know what that's all about go to the second gate
But hey
Thanks for listening and
Thanks for celebrating the magic of the movies
And it's okay to be scared
Bye everybody
For ever dog news by following us
On Twitter and Instagram
At forever dog team
And liking our page on Facebook