Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast contains a thorough dissection of three theme park stunt
shows.
One will make you say, what a feeling.
One is possibly too old for this shit.
And one stands in the darkness, afraid to step into the light.
Hey, those are great hints.
It's podcast the ride.
Welcome to podcast the ride, the theme park podcast whose famous stunts aren't physical,
but actually weeks long themed shows about outdoor shopping malls.
My name is Mike Carlson.
Joining me as always, Jason Sheridan.
Yeah, that's accurate.
That's a good assessment.
I would say so.
I would like to do more physical stunts, but there really doesn't seem to be an opportunity
unless we're doing some sort of live show.
So I guess if we do more live shows, I would not mind being set on fire.
Let me bring Scott Garner in here as always as well to weigh in on being set on fire.
I suppose.
Well, the demonstrations make it seem pretty simple as long as you got a good team on your
side.
Yeah, the team is very important from what I understand about stunt shows.
I'm not saying I need to do the full like man on fire thing where he like lurches forward
and then falls into the water.
Maybe just sort of like my arms set on fire where they put something thick around your
arm, maybe like a wrap.
And then they set that on fire.
And then a person comes with a fire extinguisher and puts it out real quick.
That's more what I'm saying.
No max some no max involved.
I believe that's the you know, stuff that doesn't catch on fire that protects you.
Oh, I didn't.
I guess.
Yeah, please.
No max, please.
I know there's a gel as well.
Which we can just do on our own, right?
We can just if we just buy some no max and like watch a YouTube tutorial or two and then
we don't need like a fire marshal around.
Yeah, I think that's probably OK.
I think we try it at home.
I would like to pledge next time we do a live show, whenever this social distancing is over,
there will at least be one stunt in the show.
I don't know what it is.
I'm not going to say it's fire.
I'm just going to say I want to stunt some kind of stunt in the show.
So that's my place.
Well, so I mean, most of the stuff, most of the shows that we're going to talk about
today have a warning about only trained professionals should do this.
Do we consider ourselves trained professionals because we've watched so many stunt shows?
Like, does that count?
Yes, I think that actually does count.
I think sometimes people discount people that aren't trained formally and they think that
they can't do something well.
But I know there's many many professional wrestlers I've read about who just started out
doing their backyard wrestling and they self-trained and they're real good.
So I think there's a lot of examples, also like piano and guitar.
People don't necessarily take lessons and they can become sort of virtuosos.
So I think we have watched enough YouTube clips of people doing stunts for us to
comfortably be able to pull off a stunt in a live show.
Yeah, so our next live show is going to be playing piano and guitar on wires.
We got to connect a piano to wires also, and it has to fly around concurrently.
Synced up with us like Tommy Lee or what was the other Astroworld, the tour,
Astroworld tour.
And I think Kiss is flying around typically also.
I saw a recent Kiss live video and they were there on wires.
OK, they're in real slow, real slow freights at their age.
They're on wires.
Yeah, but it's not quite zipping around like, you know, it's not Peter Pan style.
No, no, no. Yes.
And there's no there's no flips or anything.
Right. It's it's it's kind of moving at the speed of like the
the handicapped seat on the stairwell moving up real slow.
So they're essentially taking an elevator on its last legs up.
Like, well, it works, but the inspection date is in two weeks.
So it might not be working after that.
You know, is it just a practical reason they're using it?
Maybe like they're having a hard time getting from backstage to the front of the stage.
And it's just easier on their hips if wires lift them and bring them
to the front of the stage like they need ramps.
But instead, they're using wires in their concerts.
Yeah, maybe some old folks, too, in their homes.
Maybe if there were wire space systems, they could get up
and down the stairs easier than with that slow moving chair.
Oh, yeah. I is this a is this potentially an episode?
I do this count as themed entertainment, just doing a history of musicians
performing on wires in their shows.
Sounds good to me.
I that that seems like a lot of fun because we just named a couple of kids.
I know Garth Brooks, a big wire guy.
Oh, yeah.
What? Yep. Yep.
Yeah, I think you may be the first country wire guy.
He might have brought wires to the country fold for the first time.
I've seen a really good performance from I forget which award show
maybe the American Music Awards.
That is a performance of Yart Rock Classic Sailing
with Nsync and Real Christopher Cross.
And when the chorus strikes and they sing about sailing,
they go flying.
All of Nsync leaves the ground and Christopher Cross does not.
He stays grounded because he's not doing wires at his age.
So I just if we just all looked up who's done wire flying,
I think that'd be a lot of fun.
I think we haven't really.
I mean, we've talked a little bit about this on the show, but I do think
I don't know, Jason, you chime in.
I think we all have an affection for wire flying.
Absolutely. I know Pink had some very elaborate
wire work in her shows for a while, and then she got fucked up doing.
Oh, my. A few years ago. Yeah.
Because like wires in general, I mean, there's a great
Little Mermaid show in Tokyo, Disney Sea, where you're basically.
Scott, you didn't see this, right?
I did see it. Oh, yeah. OK.
Yeah, it's fantastic. Shockingly great.
It's so basically, yeah, you're the idea is like you're on the sea floor
and you're looking above and watching Ariel and her sisters.
And I guess I forget is King Triton involved.
He's a is he a puppet?
How do they represent him?
Yeah, I think I think it's an animatronic.
But yeah, you're you're watching like the whole Little Mermaid show
above you on wires in a very like kind of intimate theater.
With some cool effects.
So I think there's a lot of like different pivot and spin points on those wire.
That's like, you know,
there's like 16 wires involved in that.
That's just not like the two picking you up. Right. Yes.
And there's I mean, there's a great history of wire work,
obviously Tinkerbell at Disney.
So just the episode wires exclamation point.
I think that's kind of what we've hit on here is that there's just going to be
an episode called Wires in the future of podcast the ride.
Sounds good to me. Yeah, it sounds great.
Yeah, yeah.
Hopefully we don't land upon too many like grisly accidents
as we look up wires.
I should say Pink was OK.
Pink was OK.
And it looked very cool what she was doing.
Hmm. Well, yeah, she did wires on some award show I saw.
Yeah, she's yeah, she's good.
Well, she's in wires, a lot of fun folks in wires
for right now.
We are here at Stunt Show Showdown
to a sequel to an episode from our first month.
Yeah, it was forever ago.
Yeah, it's like Son of the Mask coming out all those years later.
It's a real Viva Rock Vegas.
It took a lot.
Just a lot of issues pulling it together.
We were able to reassemble the original cast, unlike Viva
Rock Vegas and Son of the Mask back to back draft to back draft.
You got some of the cast.
Yes, yeah.
And so they're to be commended for that.
But we this is more than just quick little cameos.
This is the full original cast of Stunt Show Showdown
from 2017 reunited here in 2020.
I don't know what took us so long.
I I liked the first one.
And I'm excited to see what you guys have in store.
There were just so many good, you know, there were so many good other episodes.
We forgot.
Yeah, it showed how naive we were because I mean,
Sindbad and the Spider-Man musical, not the Broadway musical,
but the Universal Hollywood musical.
We could easily get full episodes out of both of those now.
What was the third was the third of Batman show?
Yeah. Yeah.
From Six Flags. Yeah.
Yeah. Oh, those would all be their own thing easily at this point.
We even I don't know the timeline that this is coming out,
but either soon or it's already come out.
We did a second gate about a quote unquote stunt show that
like I think barely even qualifies to be in this episode.
And yet it's its own episode on the second gate.
Yes, that's true.
I I will say what the one I'm going to present today.
You'll probably say that I should be taken out of this showdown,
that I that mine doesn't really qualify as a stunt show.
But I'm not even sure where we would put it.
I guess it's sort of in the same vein as what you're talking about,
like a street type show.
But anyway, we'll get there.
We'll figure it out. Yeah.
Well, that might be a good cause to discuss.
What is a stunt show? What makes something a stunt show?
And if it does not qualify,
then perhaps we'll have to give it the the negative rating.
Do you guys have I had to go back into the episode and remember that we did?
First of all, I had to remember, did we in the first one all
where the stunt shows all competing against each other?
And apparently the answer was no.
So there is no winner in this.
OK, the winner is all of us for gleaning and sharing information.
It was that we judged each one that we all presented on a scale
of that it's either a perfect aerial flip or a miss aimed kick in the dick.
That is right. Right.
That is what we did.
I had to go back and brave an old episode.
I listened to as little of it as possible.
I listen to episodes now.
I didn't used to, but I don't.
I haven't heard anything we did in the for the first 10 or so.
And I don't have any interest in it.
I hear I agree.
I listen to the some of the I listen to these if I added to the episode.
But I forgot that you have to.
Yeah, yeah.
It's a long time ago.
It was the it was the the the feral era.
In fact, I don't even that name doesn't even sound familiar.
It's like the gene domain in era of SNL.
It's rarely discussed.
I don't even remember. That's a different that feels like a different lifetime.
Kind of does. Well, for one, it's when we used to be able to go outside.
Oh, that must be true.
Remember, you're I forget when that was.
That feels yes.
It feels like a dream.
It feels like we've been inside for a year, I think.
But it's been so days.
It's been days.
We might have heard.
What if we already did this entire episode word for word and don't even remember it?
That's how hazed we are.
That's that. Yeah, I could believe that I could.
There's been times recently when we're doing the show and I go,
have I said this a million times before or never?
Or is it all happening at once?
Is it sort of now has this all driven us mad?
And we're all realizing now that like time doesn't isn't really linear.
And we've all like it's just an infinite loop.
And we're all repeating the same thing over and over again.
I know for sure I have texted, did we talk about this in conversation?
Did I talk about this in conversation with someone else?
Or did we talk about this on air while recording?
Yes. And a lot of the times, we're not quite sure.
I was going to say the answer is I don't know.
The answer to all three is usually maybe.
Mm hmm. I just listened to something from one of our
quarantined episodes where I like repeated information
that I had said in the previous sentence.
And I and I'm and I'm worried about listening to episodes from the first month.
I think there I think the biggest problems are happening right now.
Yeah, that's probably right.
Yeah. So.
Anyway, we're losing our minds is what we're saying.
Yeah, we are. We are.
But, you know, I'm happy to be revisiting this old format
and to talk about three different stunt shows.
I think you guys know what mine is because I threw it out there,
but I don't know what your guys are.
So I'm really excited to learn.
How do we begin? How do we get into this?
Well, I can start because one of my discoveries about mine
is that you'd think this stunt show had entered the witness protection program.
There's so little paper trail on mine.
But I this is why like now, yeah, to qualify for being in this
three topic episode, it has to there has to only be like
five available sentences about it.
That's the only way we can make it fit.
Of course. Well, should should I kick it off?
Because I might.
Mike has me so intrigued.
I don't I feel like I feel like we need to build to Mike's mystery topic.
I'm fine with that. Yeah. Kick it off.
Yeah. I think I think Scott's honestly I think Scott should be the main event.
Mine's a little shorter.
Oh, OK. Yeah, I do a little bit anyway.
Well, yeah. Kick it off.
Slam it off, Jason.
OK, well, that's an appropriate attitude to go into,
because I want to take you back to the go go mid 90s.
Six Flags Great Adventure, a park that sits on a lake.
And when you have a lake, what are you doing?
You're doing a water stunt spectacular, specifically
the movie we were all thinking about in 1996,
the lethal weapon water stunt spectacular.
Oh, I don't know about this. Have I?
OK, so this, I think, has been mentioned very briefly on the show,
because for me, well, one, I had to research this topic
just to make sure I didn't imagine this happening.
But two, the reason I know I didn't imagine it
is because like Inception, I have did they call them totems in that movie?
What do they call the top and stuff?
The top? Yeah, I think I think so.
I saw the lethal weapon water stunt spectacular at some point in the mid 90s.
It ran at the park from 1996 until September 2001.
Make of it adventure is the one in New Jersey with Kingda Ka that we talked about.
Yeah, yeah, it's kind of been in the air recently on the show.
Yeah, great adventure. Six Flags Great Adventure in New Jersey.
It's kind of equidistant between New York City and Philadelphia.
So kind of a big regional park for the area I grew up in.
And we would go a lot for I mean, it's it's a day park.
You know, people just go for the day.
I think there's one or two hotels close by, but
it has the drive through safari or used to.
Now they've kind of modified that a little. But
we would go, especially like the years we didn't go to Disney.
We had a tendency to go to like Six Flags Great Adventure or Dorney Park,
which Cedar Fair owns now.
That's in Pennsylvania and Allentown.
But anyway, the the Lethal Weapons Show, I remember seeing.
And so 1996 is right smack dab in between Lethal Weapon
three and Lethal Weapon four, which I remember the promotion.
They really promoted Lethal Weapon four, which also added
in addition to Riggs and Myrtle and then
Joe Pesci, Lethal Weapon four added Renee Russo and Chris Rock to the cast.
And this the Lethal Weapons
show features lookalikes for Mel Gibson and.
Oh, God, I'm blanking on his name.
Who was Murtagh and Danny Glover? Danny Glover. Right.
And then and it features a lookalike for a bleach blonde Joe Pesci,
because if you recall those movies, which I really do not recall much of them,
Joe Pesci is in them with bleach blonde hair.
I'm going to send you guys one of the few Leo gets Leo gets.
Yes, that was his character.
You can see this is the YouTube preview image
for what little video is of this show.
And you can find video.
I can send you this link to there's video on YouTube.
And what it is is not B roll.
It says it's the A roll camera for a commercial shoot
for this stunt show.
So it's like a lot of slow motion footage of jet skis and speed boats.
There's a moment where Murtagh does a somersault in front of a tank
firing a gun that the tank explodes.
Hell, yeah. It's kind of awesome.
But yeah, this ran for like five years or so
at six, great adventure on the water.
It had a big sequence where a speedboat jumps through a houseboat set.
And it I remember thinking it was awesome.
And famously, the why I remember it is because after the show,
we got to go up and meet the cast and they gave out spent bullet casings.
Oh, you mentioned this before.
That sounds familiar.
So next time I go back to my mom's house,
I have to try and find this bullet casing.
I'm sure they love it when you bring spent bullet casings on airplanes.
But yeah, they were just giving out bullet casings to children.
Did you I mean, do you like, oh, this was awesome when you got the casing?
Oh, I was psyched.
I was so excited to go up and get like a blank.
The bullet casing for a blank.
So this this takes place on this took place on the lake.
There was a lot of barges.
And it was you would sit in these bleachers for the Great Lake Grandstand,
which was built with the park opening
and eventually demolished and replaced by a rollercoaster,
briefly named Total Mayhem and then renamed to the Joker.
Oh, it got jokerfied.
It got jokerfied. That's right.
Now, if you're talking total mayhem,
the Joker, you know, he is total mayhem.
He is total mayhem.
Which which joker do you know was it like model after just the comic book Joker?
Or was there a specific?
Yeah, I believe it's modeled after the comic book Joker, like the 80s, 90s one.
So there there is like I said, there's very little record of this stunt
show online. What I a lot of what I found, I found on the website.
Great Adventure History dot com.
And they place this in context on their website.
They they talk about season 23, the 1996 year
on the heels of Six Flags Great Adventures record breaking season in 1995
when attendance surpassed four million guests for the first time.
The park was at an all time high heading into 1996.
And this was a new attraction for 1996.
The other thing that opened up that was really big was an indoor
roller coaster called Skull Mountain and then a Birds of Prey
wildlife show or not pretty based on the movie.
No, no, not not based on the not not based on birds of prey.
Yeah, not birds of prey.
Imaginarium of Dr. Parnassus. Right.
And I, Jason, I don't want to get too into the weeds here,
but I assume it was Birds of Prey based on the hero group, Birds of Prey.
Because Harley, because they took the turn, the name Birds of Prey,
and they've they've made it with different characters.
But it used to be like with Oracle, a.k.a. Barbara Gordon. Am I correct?
Well, that is the original birds.
I meant like hawks and eagles.
I meant the literal birds of prey.
You did not mean the DC comic heroine characters.
No, I did not. I did not mean that.
Well, I got excited. Sorry.
So here you can get excited by some poor theme park journalism,
because that is another piece of this show.
I found found an article in the New York Daily News
that is 20 facts about the three new experiences
coming to Six Flags Great Adventure.
And this article is insane because it is a numbered list of one through 20.
But they alternate which ride they're talking about.
So they'll talk about explosions for a couple of facts
and then just talk about, you know, a Griffin vulture has a wingspan of seven feet.
They don't tell you if you're talking about a coast, a stunt show or birds.
And yeah, that's right.
Like, here's number two.
The dock explosion in the lethal weapon show is ignited by a propane line.
And the billowing flames reach a scorching 2000 F.
So they didn't spell check 2000 F, 2000 F.
There's no degrees. They missed the word degrees.
Over 2000 F's.
Also, I joined you on New York Daily News dot com.
I looked up this article.
It is a disaster. It's crazy.
This is the this is my my side of the episode might stop recording
because of a virus by the end of this.
There's so much shit popping up.
And I just to make sure when you mentioned inception a little bit ago,
I Googled inception totems and it was totems.
That's right. And now I have a pop up ad for a fucking totem
on daily news dot com. Whoa.
This sucks. That is too much listening to me.
Too much spyware.
I'm so mad at this website. Anyway, continue.
You mean to tell me the New York Daily News, Jared Kushner joint?
Oh, wait. No, is that the New York Observer?
That'd be too perfect.
I don't know. I'm sure it's owned by someone terrible.
Yeah. OK. My favorite fact in this is a number five.
Once Riggs's trailer home blows up, look for a toilet
and a box of milk bone dog biscuits in the rumble.
Lethal weapon fans will remember the tense moment
when a ready to detonate bomb trapped Murtaugh on the toilet and lethal weapon, too.
And dog biscuits are the favorite snack of the ever self destructive rigs.
Which I forgot in the movie that Mel Gibson stomps around eating dog biscuits.
Yeah, I'll be honest, I did, too. That's.
That honestly, I would be surprised if real Mel Gibson did that, too.
I wouldn't either.
Richard Donner, the director, also, I believe, came back for all four of these movies.
He did. Yes. And he's coming back for lethal weapon five.
I read he's 90 years old. Is that happening?
Yes, it's happening. Original cast.
They didn't say he Richard Donner would be directing,
but they did say and Richard Donner will be back.
And he I believe he just turned 90 years turning 90.
So wow, wow.
Once they're making movies again, buckle up.
He the last thing he did was the movie 16 blocks starring Bruce Willis.
And before that, it was lethal weapon four.
Yeah, he's he's had an interesting career.
I mean, he he's been around forever.
I mean, he made Superman when he was like 50, I think.
Yeah, I think I believe that's right.
So what else can I say about this show?
I mean, there's some other facts.
There's a big motorboat in a daredevil stone.
A motorboat crashes through a yacht flying 10 feet in the air.
That is in the you can find that in the a roll, b roll footage.
I sent you guys, which has no sound.
It's just very it's like cool slow motion explosions and boat jumps.
Yeah, I mean, the show looks cool.
And you can also see in the comments on the video,
people who were in the show go like, man, this was a hell of a time.
I always liked pink team, but I didn't trust white team.
Like people just talking about their their co-worker memories from working on it.
Wow. I mean, I assume.
Yeah, it was like it's it's we've said many times before.
It's like a theater company.
Yeah. Where you get very bonded, you know, jumping on the back of a water
ski and pretending to punch someone in the back,
which is a clip I'm watching right now of this stunt show, which I really,
I really enjoy that like fake punches to like the person's shoulder
while they've like they're behind them on a jet ski.
Yes, there's some good stuff.
The Murtaugh actor crawling out of the lake.
The other thing about this lake is from the pictures from the 90s,
it looks like you could pretty much just walk into the lake.
Like there was a tiny fence that I think even I could have stepped over
and just walked into the lake.
Well, that's something you often have said that you're looking to walk into a lake.
Oh, sure. The ocean lake.
Yeah.
Yeah. Well, yeah, I guess you're right.
You say I'm going to walk into the ocean.
That's something you say often.
So this would be perfect for that.
There's a couple different and I'm not sure.
Is this I'm sure there was a Batman show
here, too, because I've seen a different Batman water show.
And it's interesting because it looks like it just opens up into a swamp.
It looks like a
there's swamps and marshes.
Yeah. And some nature trails back there.
I had the 1996 the front of the map.
I think I sent you guys the back of the map that features the lethal weapon,
which, of course, features a boat jumping in front of an explosion.
And the the Batman Forever show was running in 96.
And that had its own like amphitheater.
So they had two stunt shows going at one time.
Wow.
So maybe it wasn't this one.
I will. We'll get into that eventually, I'm sure.
But yeah, that's I see the picture now.
And they have the classic Batman Forever
Batmobile with like the weird, I don't know what you would call it, slats
in the Batmobile. Yes.
Very, very distinctive to Batman Forever.
Yeah. All the Batmobiles are good.
That's sort of a stance I have.
All that mobiles are good.
I don't think there's been a bad Batmobile.
That's right. You can have people have qualms about specific bat Batman.
But the cars are always good.
Yeah, the cars always.
You know, just a quick side note.
What's everyone's favorite Batmobile?
Batman animated series, maybe.
That's a good one. I have a toy of that sitting right here.
Scott,
maybe predictable, but it's hard to say no to the original Batman.
Yeah, yeah.
And I live pretty close to the Chuck Baris facility, which is a big mural of it
in the valley and so makes me happy when I pass by that.
Sometimes there is a Batmobile, the adult Batmobile in the original.
And one time, and I still don't know why,
I was at my high school and the old Batmobile was there.
Oh, someone had it and I still don't know why.
And it shot flames in my high school parking lot.
Whoa. The real day.
It was wonderful.
So I might have to go there.
Although even this you only said mobiles, but I'm also I love the 60s helicopter.
Oh, yeah.
That bubble helicopter that
he flies over the city and everyone waves at him.
That's my favorite part of that movie.
And just like everyone waves at Batman for five minutes.
Well, that's and that's the one he hangs off and he gets the shark on his leg.
That's the shark repellent sequence.
Yeah, yeah, that's great.
I think I am I have a toy of that as well.
I do I have some affection for the Batman and Robin Batmobile, though.
I think that was kind of cool.
Yeah.
So I like the one that you're currently
showing me here because it reminds me of the music video for Kiss from a Rose.
Yeah, I see this taking off real fast.
Set to
makes me makes me happy to look at.
Sure.
Well, we'll get we'll get to the full dissection of all the Batmobiles eventually.
Well, that meant stuff coming.
Yeah. You know, you know, it doesn't make me happy to look at.
Sorry to go back to this after the ad for the inception totem went away.
I got a new ad for a face mask, perhaps
because of the virus, a face mask with the V for Vendetta face on it.
That's awesome.
The guy walks mask.
Um, I don't care.
I don't know whatever.
This is some dystopian shit looking at a V for Vendetta face mask so I can go
outside and virus times on New York Daily News dot com.
This is garbage.
I'm not going back to this website ever again.
Yeah, you may need to completely erase your hard drive and reinstall your operating system.
I'm throwing the whole computer away as soon as soon as we're done.
Yeah, I don't know when the new one's going to come.
We're not going to be able to record for like six months, but it's why you got to do
what I got to do is record it into your phone and send it or text it over and I'll
piece it together.
This be memo quality.
Sure.
I found so I think the last artifact I found, I mean, I think you guys some screen grabs,
the screen grab of the YouTube window is the rotting barges that were just left
from this show left in the lake.
I don't know the current state of them,
but they demolish this grandstand, I said a few years ago.
But the other artifact I found of lethal
weapon is a again poorly formatted because it's so old.
It is from Backstage magazine.
It's a casting notice for theme park roles from February 2001.
And at Great Adventure, they were staffing up for walk around Looney Tunes
characters, dancers who can sing, technicians and stunt performers for
the Batman Forever show and the lethal weapon stunt show.
They didn't list a rate, but the Six Flags Fiesta Texas casting
notice list, stunt performers make more than five hundred dollars per week.
So pretty good, I guess, in 2001 numbers.
You know, I think at a certain point,
this all just becomes the same routines you kind of step through.
A lot of these parks, of course, are seasonal because of the weather.
So the season usually runs like
May to October, depending on Halloween stuff and when they open up in the spring.
Right. So when it's summer in the late 90s in New Jersey,
it's a hell of a time to be a stunt performer.
It. Oh, man, I can't even imagine like the the Riggs and Myrtle actors are probably
partying, partying so hard in central New Jersey.
Yep. Different girl every time they wake up, perhaps more than one.
And I bet I mean, the Leo gets the Joe Pesci act like stand in.
I mean, he had he probably had to be a funny guy.
So he's probably doing all right with the ladies, too.
So the photo you sent of him, he looks a lot like John Daly, not our friend,
the comedian, but golfer John Daly. Yes.
Leech blonde hair,
goofy shirts, goofy attitude.
Oh, the other thing you can notice,
the bad guys in this are very clearly the nondescript 80s, 90s,
bad guys of like green and black fatigues and red berets.
This is before this is before every movie made the bad guy of Middle Eastern descent.
This was like generic baddies.
And that's how you just filled out Steven Seagal and John Claude Van Damme movies.
Yeah. Air Force One is kind of the Air Force One.
Con Air, I think.
A little the rock, certainly.
I yeah, I miss generic terrorists,
generic genererists.
I think I grew up thinking that was the worst thing that I would have to face as
an adult is like, you know, maybe if you're unlucky, there's some
beret guys on a plane that you're on or someone you know.
Beret guy. I like beret guys.
Yeah, right.
Oh, no, this guy on the plane.
Oh, no. A second and a third and one beret girl.
Yes, there was one one beret girl.
Well, if it was a black beret,
it was probably a Frenchman that was going to walk into an open manhole.
But if it's a red beret, watch out.
Now I know why you didn't have such a great time at Disneyland Paris,
because there must have been so many berets there.
You were in France.
I was suspicious you were nervous every single one of them.
Yeah, I was I was raised to fear beret wearers.
Yeah, that's all it makes so much sense.
I really I've never been able to handle watching that movie about the I've never
seen it, but I that movie about the terrorist Rushmore.
Right. I have the right on that.
Yes, I think yes.
The cover has always scared me with you.
It's Hellraiser with me.
It's Rushmore.
I mean, you're not Max Fisher is kind of a terror.
He's definitely a terror.
He does. Yeah, he blows a lot of shit up.
Yeah, true.
Well, I guess it makes a lot of sense.
Yeah, but then the Street Fighter live action movie paved new way because I
believe Jean Claude Van Damme as the good guy in that wears a blue beret as Guile.
Oh, right. Yeah.
Jean Claude Van Damme is Guile.
Oh, so it depends on the beret color.
Yeah, red and burgundy.
Always a problem.
Right.
Yes. Darker.
Yeah, I guess red is the more sinister color than blue.
Mm hmm. Yeah.
So so just check that color.
Don't be blindly afraid of all beret wearers.
Right. That's a good PSE.
Nice lesson. It's a lesson that with the lethal weapons,
the stuntship teaches you.
Well, that's a lot of fun.
I wish there was there was more on this.
That footage you sent is wonderful looking
like the sunlight beaming 35 millimeter film.
It looks like great.
It looks like you could.
I was going to say it looks like footage from like a better Thunder in Paradise or
something. Yeah, like it looks like you could put it into a syndicated action
adventure show.
Yeah, it feels very syndicated opening.
Yeah, absolutely. I don't know why somebody didn't buy this footage and cut it
into footage of a much more boring show that rarely has jet skiing in it.
Well, I'm sure at this point, no TV shows are in production.
So I think we should throw it out to the universe that this footage is still
available to be used as a TV show.
Yeah.
I also sent along one of the rare one of the 90s, that classic 80s, 90s
illustrations, park map illustration style.
And that does list the lethal weapon show on the grandstand.
As you can see, they built their log flume on the water, too.
So that looks very cool.
I did not remember that.
Right. Yeah.
That's that kinetic energy we're talking about.
Yeah, kinetic energy.
And then they have rapids and that's all the way on the other side of the park.
So great adventure.
Yeah, great adventure, much more like
nature wise, aesthetically pleasing than than Magic Mountain, I'll say.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Most things are
Magic Mountain
the aesthetic of no many no aesthetics or too many aesthetics.
I cannot wait to go back to Magic Mountain.
And this is all that's the first thing you're going to do.
That's the first thing I'm going to go.
And I'm going to say, oh, they must not have painted things in a while because of
the virus.
It's got a lot of slick.
Wow. Yeah.
A lot of stuff that seemed like it's decayed here because of the virus.
Everything's look, things are back to normal.
Every every building is being hosed down for some reason.
First thing in the morning, get the hose on, spray the building, spray the walkways.
Yeah, it'll happen.
It'll happen, at least hopefully.
Hopefully in the next decade.
Yeah, that's the dream.
That's wonderful.
What do we what do we call this?
Is this a perfect aerial flip or a miss aimed kick in the dick?
I'll say it seems like perfect aerial flip to me.
Seems like perfect aerial flip.
But what we can tell. Great.
I love it. Good show.
Good show.
Yeah. Mike, what do we got?
All right. So here's the thing.
Like when we say stunt show, when we break down what it means to be
a stunt show, like we think stunt show means guns and fire
and either like ATVs or jet skis, like that seems to be the thing
when you consider something a stunt show.
But is what is what would you like a stunt?
Does that mean like it's dangerous or does
that mean somebody's just showing off a skill that would be considered a stunt
to a normal person? I'm getting nervous here.
You know, is dance is dancing in an area on high like construction equipment?
Is that a stunt show?
Because I would argue it's more dangerous than a normal dance performance.
Well, it's definitely intriguing.
I'll say that.
All right. Let me see if I can actually just screen share and show you what I'm
talking about here, I believe I can.
Hopefully it'll work and I won't have to edit this out.
All right. How are you doing here?
I'm seeing. Yep.
All right.
This is flash dance in a tell.
This is in an Italian movieland theme park.
And it is a show,
as you can see,
where
on a little tiny set that's a construction area, a man in a nice suit comes out and
explains from what I assume because I don't speak Italian.
He explains that we're about to see essentially the main character from
flash dance, dance and do a routine on all this scaffolding and construction
equipment. So I from Flashdance, who is the main character in Flashdance?
I have all this written down because I have not seen the film Flashdance.
Hold on. Let me grab this
flash dance. I know she's an 18 year old welder.
It's Jennifer Beals.
And she's Alex Owens.
That's the character.
And this is a very short show, but it's on a tiny stage.
So here, let me just fast forward a little bit.
So two of the songs appear.
What a feeling happens later.
And then this is, hold on, let me find it.
It says it on the bottom here.
It's He's a Dream from Flashdance.
That's one of the famous scenes of Flashdance.
It's probably the one you've seen where she dumps the water on herself on the stage.
So that should be to maniac, shouldn't it?
At least that's in the video.
That is the video with the clip I watched from the movie.
It's this song.
So as you can see, there is just one single performer
scaling a construction site in a big curly wig.
Like it's a Halloween costume of real Pearlman on Cheers.
Yes. And she's got like construction clothes on and she's slowly taking them off
in a seductive way.
I see the bucket.
I see Chekhov's bucket.
There is a bucket on this construction site.
So she is like holding onto poles.
She is like doing what I would call like
she's doing like mild acrobatics.
She's hanging.
She's got good upper arm strength.
He's hanging.
I see the chair.
I see the rope.
Something's coming.
I see the bucket.
There's the bucket.
The moment's happening.
Is it going to take her wig off?
She's good. She took her pants off.
So now she's wearing a leotard.
Oh, this is European.
She is spinning around and she's like doing that kind of like dancer
pounding on the ground with her like she stepped on a bucket that might have like
concrete in it.
It could have any sort of material for building or renovating.
It seems very sturdy.
Yeah, that bucket definitely wobbled.
So now here's here's another
another song, another music.
Now she's trying to get the audience, which is just a little group of people.
It reminds me of the Muppets.
Great moments in history where there'd be like a small group gathered around.
And I find maybe I'm wrong, but I find this bizarre.
I find this whole thing bizarre.
It's pretty weird.
Yeah, I'm definitely not something I've heard of.
You really went dumpster diving here.
Yeah, this is the one.
Here we go.
Now we're getting to the
what you want.
It feels like it feels like and this is no offense to the performer.
It feels like she watched a couple of clips of the movie was like, all right,
got it, I'll just improvise my way around this.
I kicks high kicks.
Well, I saw post a video of this.
I can probably it's almost over.
This is one of the weirdest things I think we've ever run into.
Good job building to the bucket.
Yeah, so.
So here we go.
And then the bucket drop.
Yeah.
Wow. Live bucket drops.
So she drops water on herself, like in the movie, but it's not on a stage like
in the movie, it is on a construction site.
And then this very like
well-dressed Italian announcer, I think, assumes like tells you to go on your way.
Did we see the audience?
Let me zoom back here.
You can see this is where the audience, this is like there's no like it's not an
arena or anything, it's just like kind of you gather on the street.
It's like, you know, a not sort of like cowboy show.
You want to children sitting on the floor.
Yeah.
So Flashdance, this is this clip is from 2014.
I believe I found a clip from twenty eighteen.
So but I don't believe the show is still happening.
That being said, it's still strange to me
that they went with Flashdance in 2014.
This feels like when someone does like a cartoony European like, yeah, we got the
Hollywood, you know, kiss, kiss, bang, bang, sexy, late, oh, Flashdance,
sexy lady bucket drop. Oh, yeah.
You know.
Yeah, baby.
I mean, I guess maybe it's got sort of like, you know,
Europe, from what I understand, is a little more comfortable with a little
sexuality and they were like, oh, Flashdance.
Yes, this is the perfect street Miss fear type show to give families when they come
to movieland park, it does feel a little sexier than what would be in an American
park. Yeah.
So I don't know if we consider this technically a stunt show.
If you want to disqualify me, I'm comfortable with it.
But she is on elevation.
She's not just dancing.
Yeah. Yeah, there's heights at play.
Yeah.
Ah, I, hmm, I don't I'm not in the mood to disqualify it.
That's fine. I really enjoyed it.
And the answer, by the way, is that she aimed the the bucket kind of at her torso
and not at the wig, because I do think the wig would have come off great.
Her hair is not.
And she's got to do this a lot of different times a day, I imagine.
So, yeah, you can't soak a wig because they probably only have one wig.
I think so. Or maybe.
A lot of big lice risk at this park.
Two wigs, perhaps.
So, Mac, you take the wig.
You're doing two o'clock.
I'm going to lunch and have a smoke.
I was so I looked and I was looking and it first of all, I got it was very
confusing because there's a movie park in Germany and it's not this.
This is movie land.
And it is I don't know if either of you looked into any of this.
It's like there's a place called Gardaland and that has many different things.
It has a water park.
It has movie land and it has a medieval times, apparently.
Whoa.
So it's this big sort of a piece of property in Italy.
Gardaland, Gardaland, it's G-A-R-D-A-L-A-N-D.
Next to Lake Garda, that's why.
Right, right, right.
So I was looking through movie land and I
believe the Flashdance show is gone.
So I was, yes, I was looking through and this might open up a whole other can of
worms that we will end up getting into in another episode because they have a lot
of different shows, they have Medusa and it says Medusa epic show.
They have something called Choice of New
Generation, which is new 80s films and spot symbols of pop culture.
And it's pretty clear in there that Doc Brown is in the show.
There's a young man.
There's a young man in a Doc Brown outfit at the front of the show.
And I think if you look around, there's like a guy dressed as Terminator.
This seems to be more of a dance show, so I didn't want to put it in the stunt show,
although to be fair, I also didn't watch it.
I just think that this is we're going to have to get into Choice of New Generation.
There is also an actual stunt show at
movie land called US Army Stunt Show.
That's very good.
Cool.
Which I think we can for sure pencil that in for Stunt Show Showdown three.
There's man. Yeah, absolutely.
They have there's somewhere they have something called Time Voyagers.
Yes, I saw.
Oh, my God.
It's like a really chintzy Mount Rushmore with a like a pirate and a conquistador
and a Native American in a headdress and an astronaut.
Yes, there is something called Sweet Nightmare Opera Rock.
All right.
Let's be real here.
Forty percent of European theme parks are just the fronts for laundering plundered
World War Two riches that they still haven't.
They laundered it long ago and then they
just kept running the park as everyone forgot why they first opened like US Army Stunt Show.
Well,
movie land, I will say, movie land is doing a hell of a job doing it.
They have something called Bandito Live
that says help the sheriff to capture the infamous Bandito.
Will you make it?
There is something called Voices Magic.
The Thousand Voice Man arrives in movie land.
Oh, yes, and voice man, the thousand voice man.
And what I believe has replaced Flashdance is something called Full Candy Jacket.
What a phrase.
And let me show you a picture from Full Candy Jacket.
I'm texting it to you right now.
It is a like Marilyn Monroe,
USO style show on the same stage that Flashdance happened.
Peanut butter filled chocolate covered full candy jacket.
It's a yes.
Marilyn is kind of swooning, surrounded by USO guys.
And Marilyn has a very visible tattoo that says never stop dreaming.
Yes.
And I'll let you I'll send you I have the link to the show here.
We don't have to watch it like this, but I'll you'll get to see that it's very
much the same set, but it says Full Candy Jacket and it's painted on the bricks
behind the performers and they've reconfigured it to, I guess, look a little
bit, I don't know, more like the turn of the century, not turn of the century,
but like around, I guess this is World War Two.
Century. Yeah.
Mid-century is really what I meant.
They painted the cans to say gasoline.
Right.
So anyway, I guess really this is sort of
a backdoor pilot for a movie land episode.
I think it's coming to me.
And if you'll let me just pitch you here on the show, because we have done very
little in the way of strange European theme parks.
Yes. And I think it's time this really gets me in the mood.
And I'm going to propose a month or a series, however long we want to make it,
a series called Podcast the Rides European Vacation.
Oh, that's great.
Where we just do it.
We try to hop all like maybe don't try to not repeat a country.
Try to do like a rail trip.
This is our studying abroad month.
And we do it.
You know, it's a we're cooped up right now.
We can't travel. We're not going to be in Europe for a while.
Let's yeah, let's take a little European adventure with the podcast.
That's fun. Yeah, I love that.
Before the summer's through, I think that could be really fun.
Doing virtual a lot of blogs are doing virtual tours or virtual vacations like,
yeah, let's get on that bandwagon, you know.
Yeah, I would.
I want to talk about Diablo Leak in Vertigo.
Which is a thrill ride at Movieland, and they also I said Bandido had a live show.
He also has a CGI 3D adventure.
The character appears in two.
The character appears in two different rides or performances.
Cool.
So Movieland is on on the docket.
That's definitely maybe we kick it off there.
We'll figure out the best itinerary to cover the most ground.
But I yeah, let's have it.
Let's have a European adventure.
Ciao Bella.
So
so we will post links to all of this, obviously, but then Flashdance.
So you can enjoy what Italian children have been enjoying for years.
I don't know if this is a good idea, but I was when I when I studied abroad,
I went to Interlaken, Switzerland, and there was a theme park that I walked
up to and was too cheap to go into, and I'm looking it up now.
And it was called Young Frow Park.
It was only open for like three years.
And that apparently was the time that I walked outside of it.
And it is all about, like, extraterrestrial theories.
Like, it's like it's a theme park.
As I'm going through it, it's about like
the Mayan calendar and cargo cults.
And much like you're a Disneyland,
some article called this place a cultural Chernobyl.
Well, I think we found our first port of call.
Young Frow Park, we're coming.
Frow Park.
Here, it's like about crop circles and it's a theme park about
alien conspiracy theories.
Jesus, I mean, why didn't I go in there?
Yeah, I mean, that's I'm upset.
I'm upset at you.
I was right there.
Oh, well, and I was there literally several
months after they opened the crop circle area.
Oh, my God. Oh, Jesus.
I was an idiot. Oh, I'm so mad at you.
All right. Well, I'll figure this out.
Yeah, we'll figure out our Europe itinerary.
But oh, my God, this is a great idea.
So if we have to judge my pick for a show, the Flashdance.
Stunt show, I'll call it.
I can't see not calling this a perfect aerial flip.
OK, Jason, what do you think?
I'll give it the same.
You know, she had to sign some waivers, had the train of like, OK,
make sure to climb this this way.
You know, there's some risk there.
Yeah. OK, great.
Well, last it'll for a long time.
We'll see if your candy jacket has the staying power.
Well, and you can't you know,
you can't grade down something that led to our upcoming vacation together.
That's true. Yeah, that's true.
Really excited.
OK, well, that brings us to my stunt show, the third and final stunt show.
And you know what?
Why introduce it myself when I could let
one of my favorite actors tell a tale?
I am David Hasselhoff.
You know, if they watch, we make it all look so easy.
Now, come watch the Sea World pros
and see for yourself how wild it really is.
The new live Baywatch Sea World Adventure show, all the life saving,
wave breaking, pulse pounding drama of Baywatch in the third shattering,
sun splashing, high soaring splendor of Sea World.
New Baywatch Sea World.
It's making quite a splash.
Yeah, we're talking Baywatch.
If you listen to the show a lot, you know that I become a big Baywatch fan thanks
to Baywatch Remastered, which recently went up on Amazon and Hulu.
Beautiful film transfers mixed with very
awful new music created to replace the Unclearable 90s pop songs
originally in the show.
Does that add gives me a lot of feels here in words like wave breaking and
sort of shattering, which I don't know what that means, but it all sounds cool.
Yeah, this was at Sea World and it was at.
I don't know if this is all the Sea World's, but it was at four Sea World's,
those being San Antonio, San Diego, Orlando and Cleveland.
I know why it's like all Orlando makes sense.
San Diego makes sense.
And Cleveland, I don't know, I guess,
I think maybe also on a lake, probably much like the
New Jersey one you mentioned, Jason.
Yeah, so it's we're in some similar territory.
You and I, Jason, it's a beloved 90s action property.
It is a show involving jet skis.
I'm sure you can imagine,
you know,
my my recent love of Baywatch, it's been so much fun diving into Baywatch.
And I was trying to meditate on why and try to make the sell on Baywatch a little
more. And I realized it shares so much in common with the full house.
It's kind of like all the same stuff I like about full house where it's it's
it's a lot of big swings and really ludicrous stories and extremely incorrect
takes on pop culture, like they're making stabs like this is what the kids like.
Right. And they are completely wrong at every turn.
A lot of magic and amnesia and flashbacks and things that it shouldn't have.
Beach Boys and Little Richard, both on on Baywatch and Full House.
And
I think the the stunt show carries some of the Baywatch spirit with it.
You know, it's not always super affiliated and there's no characters.
That's the thing that I will say.
I think you're watching essentially a separate branch of Baywatch at each
SeaWorld Park that you're attending the show,
all united by an opening message from Mitch Buchanan is played by David Hasselhoff.
But it you know, I think it has the Baywatch spirit in that the plot is is
pretty bizarre and could drive them insane.
So let me share the screen one more time.
And once again, let's Mr.
Hasselhoff do the talking.
So if you're ready, let me say.
The Beach and the Boardwalk before you has been closed since 1942.
It was voluntarily donated by the owners to help in the war effort.
No one knows exactly what went on here, but we do know that before it can be reopened,
Baywatch needs to complete a thorough safety inspection.
So unless you know exactly what you're doing, these waters are off the loose.
And now,
so it's strange that just a few moments ago, Jason, you mentioned that
this European park was a front for World War Two.
Yeah, because that's kind of the plot of the show.
This beach has been closed since the war was used in the war effort.
So like used to fire bombs from I don't know.
Is it just like loaded front to back with weaponry?
I don't know what happened here.
Like Mitch didn't go into detail.
Keep up morale on the home front.
Like, well, people need a little little bit of entertainment.
You know, oh, maybe there was a lot of USO type shows at this play, a lot of full
candy jacket. Yeah.
So it all ties together.
As it goes on, there's kind of the implication that this
Mitch kind of says that it's it's unsafe and, you know, there there might be some
World War Two remnants on this beach. Now, I don't know why we're there.
They shouldn't have allowed us to be in the stands at this beach.
But nonetheless, we're there.
But they can't really do anything on the beach until Baywatch has done a proper
inspection. And that is kind of the central conflict of the show because Baywatch says
nobody can be here, but somebody else has a different idea.
And that's DJ Johnny Jam.
DJ DJ Johnny Jam is determined that this exact beach, World War Two artillery beach,
is the perfect place to have Beach Fest 96.
I don't have the clip queued up, but it is described as the biggest, the baddest,
the coolest event of the year.
And then, oh, yeah, by Yellow Plays, as well as an original song, which goes
something like Beach First, Beach First, Kick Some Spray, Beach First.
Come on, let's jam.
Kick Some Spray.
Once something has been sprayed, it's kind of dissipated and it's not really able to kick it.
Kick Some Spray seems like it traded back and forth between languages a couple of times before.
Yeah, that started as Let's Rock.
And then it got translated and translated back four times.
And now it's Kick Some Spray.
Kick Some Spray seems like it would be like Ocean Spray's tagline, like the juice.
Ocean Spray.
Kick Some Spray.
Drink Grapefruit Juice.
And then it's just like, yeah, really,
really fake, flat prune juice.
You don't understand why you're kicking spray by drinking this.
But they saw like the Sunny D commercial
and they're like, we need attitude in the 90s like this.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. It was mostly Sunny D influenced.
We got to get the Sunny D crowd in.
Kick Some Spray.
The Pog crowd in.
Yeah.
This was a regular occurrence in Baywatch episodes, right?
Like the antagonist would be some suburban
nightmare fan, death wish style.
Like these teens, they've got a new they've got a new drug called like the itchy.
Like, and it's like you do the drug by scratching.
That's how it gets into your bloodstream.
I have found the tagline for Ocean Spray products from the 90s.
Oh, yes. Crave the wave.
Oh, yeah, I remember that.
And wait, there's another one, too.
It's your zing.
Crave the way, crave the wave, and it's your zing.
Slay the Bay.
The beaches have been overrun by teens ODing on zing.
We've got to do something about it.
It's a powerful new drug that's also a juice.
There is a pretty crazy overlap, honestly,
between this and an earlier episode of Baywatch in that it's about the tension
between the Baywatch lifeguards and a very callous, cocky DJ who thinks he can do
whatever he wants on the beach.
And in the episode of the show that I'm talking about, that DJ is not DJ
Johnny Jam, but DJ Larry Lumen Large as played by Jeff Garland.
That's right. Oh, yeah.
Yeah. So he might not be aware that his story may have been sort of the inspiration
for a stunt show that ran for several years.
I would bet he is not aware of that.
And if we made him aware,
he would say, oh, OK, wow.
Living the dream.
Yeah.
So I will tell I will tell him.
Yeah, yeah, let him know they didn't carry on the Larry Lumen Large moniker.
I got curious about that episode, and
he's on record in some interviews saying that it happened because he was at a
wedding and met a guy who was a producer of Baywatch.
He was like, I love Baywatch.
And he said, the guy said, all right, you're going in the show.
And then he was, wow.
It's just a little casual.
But they wrote it for him.
Wow, that's great.
And the luxury of being that was pre-curved to hear he had enough cloud even then to
get a whole Baywatch devoted to him.
Damn Lumen Large, Larry Lumen Large.
But this is DJ Johnny Jam.
He shows up, starts leading Beachfest 96.
And that consists of that's kind of the excuse to just do like a bunch of water
tricks that might be in any show.
There's just like a lot of good, you know, just just really good
basic, you know, like barefoot water skiing and ramp jumps.
There's you know, there's danger along the way.
At some point, there's a there's a runaway boat, just a boat without a driver.
I don't know how they're doing that, if that's remote controlled or if, you know,
there there's somebody that just like ducking low.
But somebody has to do a jump from a piloted boat onto the runaway boat to take
control of it. So that's pretty cool.
It's not all water stunts.
There's also a at least the Orlando one had a huge inflatable pink boombox.
That's pretty great.
Once the end is T-shirt cannons, you can't have a beach fest for that T-shirt cannons.
Sure.
You know, in fact, the lyric of the song
states a pretty logical sense.
If you're going to if you're going to have a beach fest, then you got to have fun.
I wouldn't I can't dispute that.
No, that's true.
So then there's a there's a race of souped up bathtubs like a bunch of bunch of beach
kook locals all drive around like here's a here's a bathtub that looks like a big
rubber duck or something. Well, kind of predicted the Red Bull
Fluke dog, if you know, yes, yes.
You have to remember this is a pre fluke dog time.
Each has 96 is the original fluke dog
in the before times P.F. pre fluke dog.
I'm Mike, you say you're making a beeline to to Magic Mountain.
I'm going I'm hitting the next fluke dog.
It's like dance over.
We've all got our spots.
Not that I did it before, but now, you know, I'm doing that.
And like the Coney Island hot dog contest.
Oh, Jason will see you there.
Yeah, we should.
That would be a pretty good because that's at Coney Island, right?
Yeah.
By going to the hot dog contest.
America, you know, go, Jason.
America is open.
No, I've never been to the hot dog eating contest.
I have to say, I mean, every every
East Coast beach is just a shit show on Fourth of July.
I have to imagine Coney Island is disgusting
at the hot dog.
Yeah. When you when you add the crowds
in the insane heat to a bunch of water soaked hot dog buns.
Yes. Yeah.
Competitive Eaters, very normal, normal lifestyle culture.
You know,
the documentary, the 30 for 30 about it is genuinely wonderful.
Oh, yeah.
Extremely, extremely moving.
If you can imagine that.
But so anyway, all this nonsense is going on.
They think they're just having fun, souped up, bathed as they kind of announced
they implied they're going to light off some fireworks.
And that's when they've crossed the line and the Baywatch team shows up and they say,
shut it down, they're they're shutting down the beach.
They're the Jaws mayor, not the mayor, the Jaws, everyone but the mayor.
And so in this, like, it's kind of weird because Baywatch are the heroes.
But by telling everybody, just showing up
and shutting down the fun and telling everyone to play it safe,
they're sort of the villains in a way because we're having fun with bathtubs
and then they end all the fun.
Hmm. Hmm. Interesting.
So I don't end up really on their side.
And then obviously also they're missing the you know, they can't be as sexy as that
flash dance show.
So you're missing the, you know, the horrible 90s term, the jiggle
appeal of Baywatch.
It's definitely not as sexy as the show.
You don't have the, you know, you don't have big curves on the one pieces.
I think everybody might be in shorts, even you might.
It might not even be full swimsuit attire.
So it's not giving you the full Baywatch experience.
Is it more suggestive than the flash dance?
I would say it is not.
I think she is.
I think that flash dance woman is just skimpier than the family.
So it's a family, family friendly Baywatch.
Yeah, yeah.
That's it really ups the safety component above the sexy component.
Right. Sure.
Which puts it sort of at a at a detriment.
That's not to say that the Baywatch team doesn't have fun as well.
I think they even say, well, they say unsafe is uncool.
And then that gets an applause from the audience.
Yeah.
Hell, yeah.
And then they say, we'll show you how to have fun without hurting anybody.
Oh, my God.
Oh, cool.
Let's sort of alarm things.
Yeah, I mean, that is good.
Yeah, I don't believe it.
Someone has to be hurt somewhere for fun to be.
Scott, can you clarify something about Baywatch for me?
Baywatch operated on MacGyver and Batman rules and that they were good guys,
but they didn't use a gun like they could get in fights,
but they would have to hit people with like oars and buoys.
Is that correct?
Yeah, I think you can you can knock people into the water.
But yeah, it always ends up at that very Batman point where somebody is, you know,
about to drown or fell off the boat or is dangling for their life off a cliff.
And then they will save them.
Yeah. But they watch nights.
They watch nights had gone.
I got David Hasselhoff had a gun.
Most likely.
I mean, what's more distracting is that it had, you know, like ghosts and possessions.
I mean, it has the coolest weapon in the
entire Baywatch reverse, which is that when a Viking comes back to life
and then perishes, that Mitch is insistent on giving him a Viking funeral and perfectly
fires a flaming arrow out of a bow into a lake and yells Valhalla as he does so.
Which is like, why is Mitch is a perfect flaming bow and arrow
fire on top of being a detective and a lifeguard?
Was he shooting those at the same time, those shows?
He was. And not only that,
there's the first couple of seasons Baywatch are a little dull.
It was originally on NBC and it was just more of kind of a state drama.
And there was a pretty boring character
played by Parker Stevenson, who is a lawyer and a lifeguard both.
And you just lose him.
He's no good. You got to wait for, you know,
Sam Anderson and Yasmine Bleefe, I feel like, is the the sleeper, like best character
in the show. So when they show up, it's really operating,
you know, on all cylinders.
And I was I got curious, like, you know, there's this sweet spot like The Simpsons.
It has like here's the seasons where it was absolutely the best.
And I was like, is it the same seasons they were also making Baywatch nights?
And absolutely, it lines up.
I forget it's like 95 to 97 or something.
Like they were so exhausted that logic went out the window.
It's like these are full.
These are not only like, you know, it's not like Netflix size 10 episode.
These are like 24 episode seasons for both series.
So Hasselhoff is like making 100 episodes a year.
They're all really involved, like stunts and water work.
It's such complicated shows.
And he's in every like he's in he's in so many scenes, right?
He's certainly not in every scene, but he's in every episode.
Right. Yeah.
And doing a lot punching and diving and kicking and arrow throwing.
And were they prime time or syndicated?
All syndicated. OK, it was only prime time in season one for NBC.
They canceled it and then they were able to parlay
Hasselhoff's European popularity into getting it on syndication.
And it became just the biggest cash cow ever.
Wow. Wow.
Yeah, yeah.
They live the dream.
Much respects to Team Baywatch.
So anyway, they show they have fun without hurting anybody.
They they all dance a lot like all the lifeguards to a dance somehow imparts safety.
I think at some point they danced to the song Come on, Baby and Rescue Me.
So that's fun. Songs tie in.
I'm trying to think what I'm what I'm missing here.
Well, so that tension that I was describing,
you know, the beach fest people are all dancing.
Then the lifeguards are all dancing.
But then it comes to Ed because they discover a World War Two torpedo in the sand.
And I might have gotten a little fuzzy if you can imagine that watching the single
camcorder feed that went for 50 minutes that I went in and out of paying attention.
But the torpedo gets fired.
And I'm not sure what like did the DJ somehow commandeer the torpedo and say launch it?
I think they want to like launch the fire, like start the fireworks with a torpedo.
Hmm.
And you're thinking DJ what would Jimmy Jams?
What is his name?
So not Jimmy Jam, but Johnny Jam.
Johnny Jam. I'm sorry.
That's his brother, Jimmy.
Yeah, related to the Janet Jackson producer.
Yes.
So you're thinking maybe the DJ set off the bomb, but it's not clear.
I think it might be like as part of the show or that or Baywatch did it.
But like, how are they qualified?
They aren't explosives experts.
No, I'm not sure.
I don't know how this plays out, but a torpedo is fired.
And then the DJ says,
like, OK, well, we had nothing to worry about.
That was a dud.
And then a bunch of explosives and pyro go off.
So it was not a dud.
This whole thing happened on top of an active World War Two torpedo.
There's so much crossover, honestly, between our three stunt shows.
Yeah.
The war looms large.
Yes.
Yeah.
Lethal weapons such as torpedoes.
Mm hmm.
What would you say?
So if you were assessed, like if you were to take the stunt show and put it in TV
show form, do you think this would be one of your...
How would you assess it as maybe just a show?
If you were to adapt to this, I know it's been adapted before,
but do you think like that's...
Has there been something like that?
Has a DJ set off a World War Two bomb?
I mean, it seems like something they would do.
And with the nods to the past, it feels like very, very Baywatch nights.
The only way I think it could be better is if like a ghost of an old soldier came
back, who's like a World War Two general, who's like one of the major...
MacArthur?
Yeah, OK, ghost of MacArthur comes back.
Rommel, the Desert Fox.
Oh, sure.
That was that was Conan's nickname for me at the show.
I'm not sure why.
The Desert Fox.
I think he thought my name sounded Germanic.
I don't know. OK, that's not as Germanic as Hasselhoff.
But yeah, yeah.
Anyway, oh wait, no, is the Desert Rat?
I had that wrong.
It was Rommel's something...
I was related to Rommel.
I didn't understand because he knows about history and I don't.
Anyway, yeah,
I even got the name wrong just now.
Yeah, as far as it being a show, I mean,
I think it could easily be an episode of Baywatch because so much time is killed
with dancing definitely seems like something they would do.
Also similar to Full House in that, like,
if they can think of a reason to have a band come by,
that's half an hour of the show right there.
Right, right, right. That would kill so much time.
Yeah, they have a ton of things where like
like a magazine is begging Hasselhoff to put him on the cover.
Like we're profiling local heroes and you're one of the biggest local heroes of all.
No, no, no, I'm just in it for the work.
I'm in it to save lives.
And then he relents and they do do a sexy
photo shoot with him and that montage takes like seven minutes.
If it's all slow motion,
perfect excuse to kill a bunch of time.
So anyway, but
you know, funny, you mentioned that
there there was a crossover between the show and this stunt show.
And it's why I became aware of this, because in the episode Baywatch at SeaWorld,
they killed a bunch of time by just showing the show for a while.
Oh, my God.
So just all of the beats of it, all of the Beachfest 96 shit.
DJ Johnny Jam is there.
It's they work it into the plot.
And I should say, by the way, this is the second SeaWorld episode of Baywatch.
They've already been to SeaWorld.
They're doing it again.
They did Universal Studios, too.
So I also love it for that reason.
It's a show that'll kill tons of time at a theme park.
And the idea is that there's a stunt show at SeaWorld that's struggling and they're
looking for a sponsor, and meanwhile, Baywatch is looking for a way
to get the word out about the work that they do.
So they decide to sponsor the stunt show.
So in this world, a local lifeguard team
in from L.A. has decided to sponsor a San Diego SeaWorld stunt show.
Hmm. Huh?
I don't understand.
I don't know why in this universe, why would you go to this?
Like you would have no way we'd be so confused as theme park fans.
Like this is a stunt show based on like a
a team of like seven lifeguards in Santa Monica that have the discretionary funds
to fund a stunt show two and a half hours away.
By all means, let's not let's not give raises to the people who work here,
to the seasonal employees who have nothing to do from September till
till April.
No, no, no. Let's sponsor a SeaWorld show.
Also, they play the Baywatch theme song within the show.
And you got to ask what what is that to them?
Just like if the Simpsons song plays
in the Simpsons, what if they they don't know what that song is?
Right.
That's they would become like self-aware
at that point and their brain might be destroyed.
Yeah, that might be that might be my note for the episode.
Like they they all the lifeguards should have started asking these questions.
CJ should have asked all these questions and then all their brains should have
blown up.
Anyway, they bring this up like what if we sponsored a stunt show collectively
and then it's like, all right, well, we'll go pitch it.
And then another scene happens.
And then when you come back, there's you're just looking at the outside
of Baywatch Lagoon Stadium and and there's a giant merchandise cart
with the Baywatch logo all over it.
They're like, well, I guess the pitch went fine then.
And a Baywatch lifeguard is directing the show.
So they've not only allowed Baywatch to brand their show,
but they're letting a lifeguard do the theme park directing work.
Wow.
I think it's so funny, the idea of like just the like Baywatch writers just being
like, all right, I don't know.
And then one of them says, like, you know, we can just use that stunt show to kill
30 minutes and they get so excited or like, yeah, like what?
Like maybe they're like, oh, I got to have 20 pages in the script.
And they're like, oh, just maybe a stunt show.
Maybe just put a stunt show in.
Like they must it must have been it would be like me trying to fill a paper in high
school. It's like, well, it's supposed to be five pages long.
And I'm like, I only wrote two and now I'm bored.
It is the writing equivalent of triple spacing.
Yeah, exactly.
Get some more quotes in there, maybe a chart, maybe photocopy a chart and paste it in.
Footnotes are good if you can make the footnotes really long and that really,
yeah, that gives you a lot of the but footnotes also make you seem really smart, too.
Yeah, yeah, you know, well, that's this.
Yeah, they're they're they're pulling out all the stops, but they do add a twist,
which is that once the show is open, yeah, as I said, they just show it all.
And like the characters from the show,
like Mitch and CJ just sit and watch it for a while.
You just watch them clap and then
but then something happens off on the outskirts because like the Lethal Weapon
show, this is on a real lake and a boat of drunkards rides up and watches the show
from as close as they can get to the show.
And because they are drunkards, they knock a beer into some kerosene
that's there for the onboard barbecue and the boat is lit on fire.
So the Baywatch crew that thought that they were just going to enjoy watching a
stunt show based on them, asked to dive into the water and go do
what they do in front of an entire stadium at Sea World.
Wow. Very self-aware.
Yeah, pretty huge.
Somebody else that's not part of the show.
And then they they do it.
They save the people despite being drunkards.
They decide that they deserve to live and and they get a standing ovation
from the entire SeaWorld audience, so it's it's it's wonderful.
It's very beautiful.
I don't know that beer or kerosene are that unstable that they would immediately
ignite, you know, at a mild.
It's not even like a visible puddle.
It's like a couple of drips and then the entire boat is on fire.
You don't you don't really see a lot of like action movies where it's like,
I need to make a Molotov cocktail.
Someone hand me that beer.
Might be too much.
It's not the best starter.
No, I wouldn't think so.
This sounds like the perfect plot of like the 60s Batman show
where like they went to see a stunt show based on Batman and like Batman's just
going to watch and then he has to get involved.
Oh, yes.
And then it's like kind of unclear who's the real Batman and who's the stunt Batman.
Right. But like, yeah, Batman and Robin are
just going to like support the effort, the creative effort of the stunt show.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And then they're they're come in, they get a prize at the end and like, well,
we're not here for the spotlight.
That's what the hardworking theme park performers.
Right.
Struggle valiantly every day.
That's what they deserve.
The spotlight. They're the heroes.
It's quiet, humble crime fighters.
That's all. But anyway, thanks for the metal.
So, you know, it's a lot of fun.
It's all made.
It's all elevated for me by the fact that it was part of the
part of the real show.
Now, if there was ever anything that would
knock one of these three that we're profiling from Perfect Aerial Flip to
Miss Same Kick in the Dick, it may be that there was a horrible accident
in the Cleveland version of the show and this footage of it on YouTube that I
don't recommend watching where a boat just like is plowing towards the audience
and then does plow into the audience.
It's horrible. It's really, really bad.
Nobody died, which makes it a little more
acceptable to laugh about slightly.
But it's bad. The video is bad.
They warn you in the video.
It's bad.
Yeah, yeah.
And let me add crashed after a mechanical failure.
So I,
you know, fun that everybody dances to come on Baby in Rescue Beat.
Not so fun that it grisly accident happened.
SeaWorld Cleveland was not long for this world.
And it actually became a six flags in 2001.
And now I think is nothing.
I think it may not be there at all, perhaps.
And Ohayan listening can let us know.
But I wonder if that kind of portended the end of
the Baywatch stunt show and SeaWorld Cleveland in general.
I guess you could say the minds behind the Baywatch show at SeaWorld Cleveland
were not always ready, and they did indeed let that boat out of their sight.
I'm looking, Scott, I'm looking at a clip here from the show that says
Baywatch at SeaWorld and it says Baywatch at SeaWorld.
This is the description in Cleveland, Ohio, with Rose.
Some I'm not sure this woman's name in the beginning.
And then it says Typhoon Tommy is at the fifty five second mark.
Typhoon Tommy, Typhoon Tommy.
I don't recall what Typhoon Tommy is all bad.
Could that been a I don't have any other information.
Could that just be maybe a performer that went by that moniker?
Yeah, possibly.
Maybe that was a specific person doing a trick or a flip because at fifty five it
looks like he's just hanging off of a boat.
Oh, maybe so.
Tommy was hanging off of a boat.
It all culminates in a jump off of a ramp where there's four guys all on skis doing
a jump at the same time.
That's kind of what the thing builds to.
And it's pretty impressive.
There's also a part where all the Baywatch
lifeguards all do a pyramid together, which I don't know why they would.
I don't know why a bunch of lifeguards are doing a pyramid, but it's cool.
I should also say something I like, which is that
Pamela Anderson, her character CJ, spends the episode caring for animals at SeaWorlds,
including an injured sea lion.
That's what a lot of the episode is about.
In real life, Pamela Anderson is a huge anti SeaWorld activist.
Right.
She may like, yeah, major animal rights
person and campaign against them.
So it's very it's weird to watch her in this now,
you know, like reciting gunpoint lines about this place is really good to the
animals. And if this wasn't here, a lot of animals could get a lot more hurt.
It's I want I assume I wonder if.
I mean, does she she denounce this episode?
I don't know if she's had to publicly address it.
Maybe after we bring it up, she will.
I'm not asking her to.
I think it's pretty cool that she was, you know, she was being fed the party line
in the 90s and today is like, fuck that noise.
Yeah, I also think she's cool because she married producer John Peters to pay off
her debts and then divorced him 12 days later.
Oh, that's the greatest story I've ever heard.
Isn't that insane? Yeah.
And what a delight.
I would like to talk about that for an hour, but we're almost at the end of this
episode. Yeah, yeah, we're pretty close.
This year, married and divorced as he divorced.
He was about to marry a woman and broke up with her.
Oh, to do so that he could achieve the dream of marrying Pam Anderson.
Yes. And then they were married for a couple of weeks.
He had paid off her bills and then she divorced him.
Wow. Wow.
Cool. John Peters is the guy who Kevin Smith has that story about producing Superman
that never happened with the spider, with the spider.
Yeah. Mechanical spider in there that ended up in Wild Wild West because John Peters
was obsessed with the idea of a giant spider in a movie.
And a former hairdresser, Barbara Streisand.
Barbara married to Barbara Streisand.
Yeah, yes.
Extensively, yes.
Until I do a quick Google search here.
No, no, dated.
Maybe just dated. Sorry.
He was made to Leslie and Warren, though.
Geez. Oh, wow.
Oh, so good and clue, which I just watched.
Wow. Yeah.
What a dating lineup.
Scott, that SeaWorld in Cleveland, I realized it sounded familiar to me.
And it got roped into the
G Geauga, Gigauga Lake
story.
It's the whole thing where like
a theme park kept changing hands and then it got roped into the Six Flags World of
Adventure, which the SeaWorld got molded into.
And then it became a wild water kingdom,
which is also the name of a Cedar Fair Water Park at Doherty Park in Pennsylvania.
It's a whole thing.
I believe a listener who is working for a Cleveland media outlet had made a video
about the history of Geauga Lake, Geauga Lake.
I do not know how to pronounce it.
But yeah, there's a whole massive larger story about this area,
this entertainment complex.
Oh, weird.
Oh, so just like traded hands at times and pretty much owned by anyone who can own
a theme park of this size.
She's now now been demolished, it seems like.
I think Wildwater Kingdom, it looks like it closed in 2016.
She's
well, happier times when Mitch and the gang were imparting the important lesson
of keeping it safe on World War Two artillery strewn beaches.
What do we think?
What's what's our what's our another winner?
Wow. Wow.
Despite the despite the accidents, despite the accidents.
Yes, this is another winner.
It's a great IP.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, and I think, boy, and it's a winner without even me
me forgetting the detail that it's full of something called an air chair.
Oh, my God.
Like a guy's like on a chair that's also a water ski.
And in the boy in the episode so many times, DJ Johnny Jan says, and there he is
on the air chair like the fan man.
I yeah, that's kind of a kind of a new generation fan man,
tired fan man, wired air chair.
Yeah.
Well, congrats to Baywatch and to all three of these for being perfect aerial flips.
You all did it.
Yeah. The trifecta.
Wow. Wow.
And and a little vacation has been inspired.
This was very fun, very positive, very productive.
Yeah.
We really did it.
Congrats, guys.
I don't know.
I need a stunt to your way to.
Yeah.
I ran out of energy five minutes ago.
Enjoy.
We don't have energy.
Enjoy the rest of your day in your podcast.
Yeah.
Crave, crave the wave, crave the wave.
What was the other one?
Kick the spray, kick the kick, the spray.
Yeah, the spray.
Kick some spray, kick some spray.
Yeah. OK.
Well, that's the way to do it then with a little DJ Johnny Jam attitude.
And since we've temporarily retired, our typical episode ender, let's say thanks
for kicking some spray with us here at Podcast the Ride for more podcast.
The ride. Oh, yeah.
Yeah. Thanks for the guitar.
Yeah. Here.
Throw it in.
Hell, yeah.
For more podcast, the ride surf shattering energy.
Check out our Twitter, our Instagram and our Facebook.
Well, we're great.
Perfect.
Excellent shredding.
And if you want to break even more waves,
head to podcast, the ride, the second gate at podcast, the ride at patreon.com
slash podcast, the ride, make it well,
make sure to get your spent bullet casing on the way out.
Well, well.
And now, gentlemen, as we end every episode, let's all reach up, grab the rope
above us and douse ourselves with water.
We were.
Oh, great cats were sounding like cats now.
There's a thin line between shredding and mewing and mewing.
All right.
Well, great.
Let's let's go out on that here.
Maybe one more in mass and goodbye.
Well, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Bye bye.
Forever.
This has been a forever dog production,
executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm,
Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify or wherever you get your
podcasts, keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and
Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.