Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast contains some big news
from me and some big questions from you.
Papa Scott welcomes you to Podcast The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, a podcast about theme parks hosted by three childless men in
their 30s.
No longer.
I am Childed Man in his 30s, Scott Gardner, joined by Uncle Mike and Uncle Jason.
How are you?
What if that was the way you told us to?
That would have been something.
Yeah, wait.
Oh, I mean, I was trying to surprise the listener, but this whole time I could have
surprised the host too.
No, I actually don't know what the fuck you're talking about.
So what's up?
Oh crap.
I thought I saw you on there.
OK, well, I got a lot to tell you.
You know I got a new phone.
You know I switched to Android.
I got a new phone number and really messed up my entire life.
I also I thought you were just like trying to be polite to Erin and not bring it up.
I guess clearly you haven't been paying you were paying a lot of visual attention for
a little while there.
Well, she kept standing behind pillars holding boxes, you know.
Like like a Veronica's closet actor, you know.
Conveniently passing donkeys and camels a lot of the time.
Yeah. So, yes, it's true.
The news is true.
Yeah, I'm I'm a dad, everybody.
I'm I'm Papa Scott now.
Let's make that permanent.
I'm going by Papa Scott, which which sounds I mean, it is good, but it sounds a little
it does sound a little similar to pop a squad.
So I'm not I'm not thrilled about it in that regard.
But I am thrilled because I just I just had a baby.
My wife and I just had a baby.
And just to be very clear, this is not some extended bits.
And we're talking about Rex or something, though we do respect him as number one.
We have had a second child.
And and let's do the gender reveal as well.
It's a good boy. Whoa.
Wow. He's a very good boy, everybody.
He really is, too.
I mean, I was going to say that regardless, but I certainly would characterize him
having met him now as a good boy.
Yes. Do you I mean, are you already like are you already gauging like
how good he's going to be with certain drop rides or
launches?
I yeah, I'm doing like a conversion
scale kind of on my body.
Like if I lift him up this high at his size, how many feet is that
equivalent to a Tower of Terror or to a lesser one, just like a camp Snoopy
kind of thing?
I I think, you know, a Tower of Terror.
Well, I guess if I if I got up like on a high flight of stairs and I jumped down
and he was in my arms, then that that that might be like a Tower of Terror height.
But I probably couldn't like jump way back up to that.
It's hard. It's hard to do a launch.
Right. Yes, I see what you're saying.
Well, yeah, you say that because I now that reminds me of when Joe Rody
was describing what his philosophy was when he when he
reskinned the Tower of Terror into Guardians of the Galaxy Mission Breakout,
is that he wanted the car to simulate the fun of getting tossed in the air
like you're a baby.
Oh, you better believe I've thought about that when I've held him
like any like just kind of sudden.
I'm not actually jumping around with him just to be clear.
There's no Michael Jackson hijinks.
Yes. Yeah. Yeah.
I think even if you did even just like a slight elevation, he doesn't even
respond to yet. He's very he's very new, by the way.
We're recording this.
He's not even two weeks old as we record this.
So but yeah, when he
I'm certainly not giving him a throw any time, but I with that Rody explanation,
I'm excited to do that.
I'm excited to give him him little rides.
You know, I'm thinking about the theme park angle of all this.
I was trying to theme the room,
creating a imagineering a themed environment for my son.
It's wonderful.
Yeah. Would you like to tell the listeners how
and where you told us?
Because it's very clear in my mind.
Do you? Yeah, I love that I can say that.
That for you, for the for the long time listeners of the show, that
Aaron and I told Mike and Lindsay and Jason in Epcot Center.
We were in World Showcase.
I think we had just left the Mexico Pavilion and
I and knowing that, yes.
So we knew right before we did our Orlando trip back in October.
And I definitely was in the effort to, you know, imagine
here a fun little breaking the news moment.
It was crazy knowing like, oh, I think I think we get to tell
the guys in Disney World. That's going to be nuts.
Yeah. What a what a perfect on a Disney World trip.
So crazy. What a what a way to heighten it.
It was so boggles.
And we were like we were trying to find the right moment, too,
because I knew it was going to be
it was going to end up being a problem because there were going to be rides
that Aaron could not go on.
Yeah. And and we ended up there just wasn't the right moment to say it
on the first day when we were in Disney Hollywood Studios.
So I'm just going on Tower of Terror and rock and roller coaster without her.
It was all it was all such a bummer.
I know she like specifically was really dreaming
and hankering to go on the original Tower of Terror.
So that was a bummer.
And we all got to go on the new Hagrid's coaster.
We had to like, you know, with our crazy connections, jump on that thing.
And she just had to sit back and hold our back.
Which we we made a point not to pull the Can You Hold My Bag?
Yes, very often.
But the Hagrid's thing was kind of last minute.
So we didn't know where to put anything.
Kind of quickly. Yeah.
So it's chaos around there.
And it really to use a Simpsons analogy,
it was a lot like Lisa coming back from the itchy and scratchy movie.
And like, so how was it as OK?
And I'll be honest, it's the greatest thing I've ever seen.
Exactly. I mean, it was hard to suppress the excitement
over that ride and several other rides.
So, Aaron, I just want to say,
I'm sorry we'll get you on all of those things.
I owe you a lot of bags held.
And I guess so does so do you guys, too.
Yeah, yeah, that's true. Yeah, that's true.
We didn't like, you know, she was sitting.
We didn't like, you know, just keep comically
handing her bags that weighed her down slowly and then,
you know, blocked her face in the end.
Like it was right. She was comfortable.
Well, well, look, if these parks open within the next year or two,
we'll go I'll hold the bags. Jason will hold the baby.
Hey, all right.
Give them all give them all a drop right.
Yeah, I'm the yeah, I'm the au pair.
You guys can bond over having extremely persnickety stomachs.
Yeah, Scott, I I do have to tell you,
I don't think I've ever told you this story.
But the night before you told us, Mike and I were at a bar
and I actively said the phrase, hey, did you notice we've been out of town
for three days and Aaron hasn't had a drink once?
You did notice.
Yeah, we were definitely because, yes,
it's a tell. It's definitely a tell.
I think I said, yes, I did notice that.
We were wondering and we thought about telling you guys at the
what's the place, Bahama Breeze?
You're thinking of the Schaumburg, Illinois, Bahama Breeze on Golf Road.
There's a restaurant.
It's a chain called Bahama Breeze that we went to after Woodfield Mall
to, you know, just get a nightcap as you do in Schaumburg.
What did we order? We ordered that was like a flight, right?
Or you had a flight.
You had a rum flight. Yeah. Yeah.
So in comparison, you must have.
Yeah, you must have been a little fishy that I had a flight,
which I didn't finish, and that Aaron next to me did not touch the flight.
Yeah, that's that's all a little insane.
Yeah. Oh, man.
That's that's so funny. You guys noticed it didn't.
We were wondering, especially because we kept.
There were other people who we told just because we had this twice
where we went to a restaurant, a drink order was placed.
And Aaron said, just a just a sparkling water for me.
And especially this was her dad was one of these scenarios.
Her dad gave her the biggest raised eyebrow glare I've ever seen.
And she just like, fine, I'm pregnant.
They could not hold it on. Hold it in.
I'm just saying you guys have a reputation you uphold.
Hell, yes. Yeah, it's it's pretty crazy.
And that's that's the main thing.
Look, if if if Aaron's if Aaron's listening back to this,
obviously, I am so impressed by your
you know, by your strength getting through the pregnancy and through the,
you know, through the delivery and everything.
But the drinking thing primarily and especially because we were in Epcot
Center during the Food and Wine Festival and you did not have a single drop.
And oh, my God, the fortitude, if that doesn't show that she could be
an incredible mom, then I don't know what does.
Yes. Kudos to Aaron.
That's it's that's a very hard scenario all around.
We could do an abracadabra.
There's so much we couldn't get done.
Couldn't do an alcoholic Star Wars milk. Right.
Yeah. Yeah.
All that combined with the, you know, incredible heat and, you know,
it was it wasn't as fun of a trip for for Aaron.
We ended up we ended up having a good time. Sure.
Oh, my God.
We it was such a bummer to like to to get that to realize what was happening
and go, oh, my God, Disney World. Oh, yeah.
I realize also it's possible that at some point in time,
because this is kind of a little verbal record of the birth of my son,
it's possible he could be hearing this someday.
So maybe I should cool it on the swears for a little bit. Hmm.
Yeah. What age would you anticipate he starts going into the back
catalog of your paywalled podcast?
Wait, is this a paywall?
Is it a wall? I thought it was a main feed.
I think it's OK.
I think my this is the second time during quarantine that I've been incorrect
about where the episode we're currently recording is going.
Well, who know? We don't know what date is.
Yeah, I know.
Literally, the main thing I have had besides a couple like Zoom
things is is recording.
That's the only thing on my calendar is recording and like,
oh, I'm sorry.
I took it off your calendar for a little bit.
Our boy took it off your calendar.
Oh, that's OK. I mean, that's the other thing we have.
We've been going.
We've been working hard for a while now to get a backlog,
to get like a buffer.
Yes. And which thank you, guys.
Thank Mike and Jason.
Thanks so much for that, for building up the
the catalog that could exist if I need to do a paternity leave.
I don't know that I super will because he is pretty mellow at the moment.
But you just, you know, just in case some crazy thing was going wrong.
It's nice to have the cushion.
But so, yeah, for our listeners, with that, I don't think you'll hear.
You won't get a break from me if you wanted a break from me.
Sorry, I don't think you're going to get it even with the birth of my son,
because we've been. Yeah, we've recorded.
I think we have like 13 in the bank right now.
It's like a crazy number.
Yeah. And none of those reference that you have a child.
None of them reference that I have a child and none of them reference
the coronavirus.
I mean, I guess they start to at a point.
But we like, yeah, that became the issue.
Like that's part we were doing the backlog and then, oh, God, this breaks out.
And yeah, so it's like a lot is going to be missing.
And I guess, well, that leads me to another point,
which is that we had to do this during the virus.
And I say I don't have like a real any like jokey material here.
It was just, you know, we were we were very nervous.
It was very crazy.
And it sort of impacted the way we rolled out this news.
Actually, if I could go way back, the plan for a while was
we were going to do an episode with Aaron.
Aaron was on the show back in the city.
Well, it hasn't been on in a while.
We're going to have her come on and introduce the news, like,
you know, say she was pregnant and that that could be fun.
Right. Then
the day before we were going to record her episode,
it became clear that Fry's Electronics was installing my video and closing.
So bump, Aaron, that's not happening.
Sorry, we got to go down to fries.
All right. So we'll reschedule it for a couple of weeks from now and should be good.
Then the virus defining event of our lifetimes happened.
And I'm like, I don't want to tell the audience we're having a baby now.
They're going to be so worried.
Yes.
I think it's like it's not a fun way to break that news.
So what I'm happy to say is that you don't have to worry.
You didn't have to worry. We didn't have to worry.
You know, he's fine. Everybody's fine.
The delivery was kept so separate as a separate wing of the hospital.
If you are pregnant right now or if you have someone in your life,
you care about who's pregnant.
I can't guarantee anything about the scenario in which the baby will be born.
But we at least are a case of, you know, you can
you can have a baby in coronavirus times and it can be safe and not insane
and still just as wonderful and magical as it's supposed to be.
Yes, that's I mean, that's yes.
Having baby is stressful enough, I would imagine.
So it's good. It's good because I think you guys had a nice timing where
and not the nicest timing, but like nice timing where it was like
they had a few weeks to figure out exactly what was good.
It wasn't like the day after it hit.
Yes. Yeah, because there was so much I didn't know.
I went like when the state went on lockdown, I didn't know what that meant.
And then you hear
I think some news story was going around about like in France,
they aren't allowing the partners in the delivery.
And I was there. Let me be clear.
If I'd use the virus is like, yeah, I'd just rather not.
I just I don't feel safe.
I mean, I know it's not a law or anything, but you made them.
You made them quarantine in a hotel for two weeks to before they came back.
Sorry, guys. Enjoy the enjoy the Radisson.
I know, but I think like in
I think it's having a little in New York and may still be.
I don't know. I don't want to say all this and then have somebody
not be able to be with their partner.
I think delivery, but I places. Yeah, I just don't remember where.
I don't think it was widespread, but I think the news story was going around
enough that I started getting a certain kind of text that was like,
hey, just thinking about you and just really want to make sure.
I don't doubt that's people who who care.
But I just started feeling a lot of dread from people.
And I was like, I don't hospitals never said anything.
I think it's going to be OK. And it was OK.
We just had to have masks on for a lot of it.
And, you know, grandparents couldn't be there.
But I don't know. Besides that.
But you're also so tired.
I'm like, as much as it would have been nice to see everybody
and have that moment, but you're like, I don't know.
I'm not in a state to socialize.
I haven't slept in days.
So it all it's it's it's working.
It's it all worked out. I'm happy to say. Great. Great.
Yeah. Yeah. What was what else was on my?
Oh, sorry. Go ahead, Jason.
Oh, well, I was just going to say, now that you are, you know,
essentially spending a lot of time with a small cantankerous creature
who loves to sleep 18 hours a day, I just wanted to say, you're welcome.
You're welcome for the prep work.
You're welcome.
Dealing with me for three years has prepared you.
What's this voice?
What's this voice coming out of you?
Yeah, well, you're welcome.
A little more grandmother.
Harvey Fierstein over here.
It is Harvey Fierstein.
I did was Harvey Fierstein was not.
Oh, I just watched the the Steven Sondheim 90th birthday
celebration last night.
Harvey Fierstein, not on, but
the the version of Lady Sue Lunch was done by Christine Beranski,
Meryl Streep and Audra McDonald.
So still star studded, but I beat them by a week.
Oh, because you did.
Yeah. And this is archived on Twitch.
You did a stirring rendition of Lady's Lunch.
We did a little there was in case you didn't see it.
There was a Disney sing along telethon, not a telethon.
Well, yeah, I said it was money.
Kind of.
Yeah. But yeah, a lot of people sang Disney songs from home.
And we decided to do a little one ourselves right after it was over.
Yeah, Jason, I loved your Sondheim.
Mike played keyboards and did a little medley of goofy movie
eye to eye and the and the city walk saga theme.
I kicked it off with I'll Make a Man Out of You with the Johnny
Husband's super pronounced song from Mulan.
Yeah, that was a blast.
I let me say this.
Oh, that also leads me into sort of the next little step of the delivery story,
because that was a that was like it was right before.
Like it was really close to when we
went into labor, like not the night, but it came soon after.
And we've been having fun with these little things on Twitch.
And I did a thing where I made a car thing, Manhattan at home,
and I did a little DJ set with with Rex, my first son.
And I won't I won't neglect him.
Rex, if you're listening, I love you just as much as before a couple of weeks ago.
So anyway, that was a little fun thing we did.
So just with that in mind, let me paint the picture of the the delivery night.
I don't think you guys have heard this full thing necessarily either.
Basically, I think the day that we did that little
our little sing along thing, we had an ultrasound that from the
the doctor's point of view was very like, all right, so he's doing good.
And, you know, I think you still got some time and, you know, he's not too
not not getting too deep there and you should be good.
So we felt like, OK, so we have a little more time to prep and everything's fine.
I had a glass of wine that night.
And then like, you know, a little bit later,
a couple of nights later, we're
thinking about that ultrasound and like, all right,
he's not due for a couple more weeks.
I think we're fine, you know, chilling out with a little drink or something.
Sounds nice.
So I we decided to go treat ourselves to take out
and go to a place that we miss very much in quarantine.
The Tam O' Shanter, Walt Disney's favorite restaurant
and perhaps my favorite restaurant as well.
So we already take out from there.
And on the phone, they kind of upsold me.
They said, you know, we have cocktails to go.
And I haven't done that in these quarantine times.
And I was like, well, hey, we're chilling out.
This might be one of our last nights to chill out.
I will do that. I will get a maple old fashioned.
And my
how do I want to illustrate? OK, so
we get a maple of fashion.
We drive out there.
We're chilling out, playing a game of trivial pursuits.
And in fact, I went and found the card.
I found the question that was right before things started happening.
And I'll actually I'll ask you guys the question.
I'm curious if you guys know.
OK, what reveals the pirates skeletal shapes in Pirates of the Caribbean?
The Curse of the Black Pearl.
Oh, that's a good.
So what? So, yeah, because they're dead.
I remember this. They're dead in the movie and something
reveals that they're dead by showing you their skeleton.
Now I understand the question correctly.
I think so. I mean, I haven't I haven't seen that scene.
So I don't I don't know this moment very well.
Is it some sort of Jason? Go ahead.
I think I know it.
Is it the moon? Is it the light of the moon?
It is moonlight. Correct.
Wow. Great. You nailed it.
And that's the that's the toughest one.
That's if you're a little six, that'd be your question.
Much easier than who was Johnny Depp's inspiration for Jack Sparrow.
Right. Of course.
Which is
Joe Perry from Aerosmith.
Yes, as we as we all know.
Absolutely famously.
So anyway, you got the right answer, Aaron.
I asked that question and her water broke.
Whoa.
The moon controls the tides, boy.
I feel it was a question about moonlight.
Davy Jones's locker.
Um, yeah, it would now let me let me say this about that.
We took a delivery class that sort of
underlined something for me that I didn't realize.
They said, you know what?
It's not like it is in the movies.
It's not, you know, that you're doing something.
And then all of a sudden, oh, my God, my water broke.
It can be a really tedious process and it's preceded by contractions.
And maybe you don't even feel them and you don't know what they are.
And then, you know, your water breaking
might not be so deep, deep into the process.
Cut to us exactly like it is in the movies, like completely unexpected.
No question that's what it is.
And as I said, weeks to go from when it was supposed to be.
Don't worry about the you know, he's super healthy and it's all fine.
Just to say that. But it totally blindsided us.
We put the trivial pursuit down and I am at this point about halfway through
my maple old fashioned from the TAMO shanter.
A thought occurs to me.
I had been seriously thinking about had they not suggested a maple old fashioned
to me, I had been thinking about bringing the food home and making a Carthay,
Manhattan, and these are strong drinks.
I even thought about doing one of those little twitch things.
I was like, oh, that'd be fun to do.
Maybe I'll do one more of these little DJ sets and I'll like entertain the
power of some of our audience over this wonderful, very strong drink.
This maple old fashioned, I think saved my life, saved my baby's life, or at least
the experience, like thank God for this TAMO shanter, less strong drink because it
was totally fine. I was not driving intoxicated.
I oddly was going slow for me.
I didn't I didn't guzzle the thing.
But thank that would have been just a cursed Carthay, Manhattan.
The Pirates of the Caribbean, the curse of the Carthay, Manhattan.
What do you mean?
You guys aren't taking a lot of lifts right now.
I guess, yeah, worst case scenario.
There's like one stray one 50 minutes away.
He's in Sylmar.
Hurry up, hurry up.
That preserves the Carthay, Manhattan, luckily.
Yeah, preserves it in your brain and like you'll be free to sip.
I mean, maybe tonight you could have one like there's no association with it.
I would love to drink that.
I also, again, uncharacteristically,
this every step of the pregnancy has pushed the drinking because I can't imagine
like the energy we're doing shifts and I got to stay up pretty late.
And I can't admit you combine that with drinking.
Oh, my God.
So, yeah, who God, who am I?
That's what's happened. Like what an identity crisis.
I'm not drinking.
Erin and I went to Disney World and we cheated and drank for days, months, really.
And on top of all this, I think we have to talk about this,
the original tagline of the show, no, yeah, applies.
It's just not factual anymore.
I know. I've been thinking about this since you said it.
I was the first thing I thought.
That's the first thing I thought of before anything like, oh, that's great.
They're having a child.
I thought, oh, no, this ruins the tagline of our podcast.
Yeah.
I think that's the first thing my parents said.
Is it really?
I think I always got an air and I have to maybe and they're like,
you got to change the tagline of your podcast.
Multiple friends and the guests of the show have brought this up.
Yeah, this was this was kind of the branding.
And not only that, I mean, like it's been a whole thing, too, because I think
the idea was that that's something that we say at the top of every episode,
because I really like that joke.
It was an undeniably funny joke.
Jason, maybe you thought of that.
I don't recall.
But the
the reason we changed the jokes at the beginning is kind of because as much as I
like that joke, I did not necessarily want to my personal brand to be childless man
in his 30s because I didn't know I really didn't know.
And I'd be lying if I said that the tagline
and the joke wasn't in my head a little bit in making this decision.
Like I like it's I think maybe there's a way you could view this,
where this baby that's in the other room is here because of the joke.
Why was like you were proving to the joke
that you were going to have a child and not be a show you
a 30 something theme park guy?
I will invalidate this joke.
I will have a child and hopefully there will be a world with no theme parks.
I know that's funny.
You say that I feel like maybe I only said this into my own head, into my own head.
I remember thinking, you know, if kids come
into play anywhere at this at during the course of this podcast,
I'm also seeing this podcast as a little bit of an insurance policy for us to still
have to go to them with some frequency.
Yes, that is a very good point.
I don't know who I said it to.
It would kind of be justified for me to leave and go to a theme park.
It is work at this point, which it looks like.
Boy, let's flash to when you thought of that joke before all this.
And we were just getting all this together.
But now, like this is this is a was where is like a technically a job that I have
that helps my son and that that factors in and that if I go to Disneyland
without him, it's still in his best interests.
Yes, it is.
He yes, it's not something some weird
thing that his adult father does that's just bizarre.
It is just pure work.
It's just purely for his benefit.
Yeah, you know, you guys can all go in on that at this at this point in time.
You're you're doing you're doing it for him.
Yes, we're all doing it for him.
You can all print print out that that that Simpsons moment, all the pictures of Maggie
do it for pictures of my son and mixed with pictures of the theme parks
that obviously we don't really like to go to that much.
Right. We got it.
Yeah.
So, you know, you're we're talking about the joke.
And when we were I like the joke is funny, but I did that.
I was always built in in my mind and I didn't know who was getting to it first,
who was getting to baby first.
But I was always in my mind.
And that joke probably will have to change.
But this will be a perfect this podcast will be a perfect reason for us to not
change our behavior at all.
Absolutely.
And and yeah, I mean, I should amend what I said earlier that if I go to Disneyland,
it's in his best interest.
That is a statement that will apply in twenty twenty two.
Yeah.
Even if the park opens before the end of the year, not for me, I'm not passing.
I'm not passing anything to that kid.
Yeah, no, you're like one of these drugs has to be like a mirror, like one of these
clinical trials has to just be an incredible success for, I think, even me to go
that, you know what I call I don't want to say I literally this morning or a few
hours ago was like I made the claim like the first day the parks are open.
I if one of us has to be there, it's going to be me.
Yes, I like, oh, there's no way the other two would go.
But I have like I want to see this.
I want to.
But what's this, Jason?
What is the scenario?
And I don't want to get too off off off baby talk.
But what is the scenario?
It all depends on the scenario.
If we've had widespread antibody testing
and we know some sort of percentage of people who've had it and like like there's
a there's a there's a variety of ways maybe I do think about going.
But if it's like they open next week and you just got to stay away from everybody.
Are you going?
I I don't think in that scenario, I think I have spent a lot of this quarantine
reading like the the speculation and the industry watchers.
And I think Disney being as cautious a company as they are,
I think I don't think they would open until like the eyes were dotted and T's
were crossed. What do you mean?
Like like stuff was not super secure, even just the way like China has only reopened.
Shanghai Disney has only reopened the shopping district and one hotel.
Right. But they're they're gearing up, supposedly.
They're gearing up. But like, I don't know.
We'll talk about this in a little more on this.
But you are. Yeah, Jason, we'll talk about it.
Jason, I guess. Yes, Jason, I guess will be the cover.
Porter chances are like.
I just also like just as someone who's always been interested and fascinated
by these places in this industry, like I'm just curious to see what it's going to feel
like, you know, personally as a fan and then just like as someone who covers it.
I want to see how people behave.
I want to see how the parks behave.
I just want to see what it is.
I look I obviously share your fascination.
I am worried about your lungs, though.
I will say that.
Well, I think I have
I think I'm in pretty good health, shockingly.
I know the portrait I portray on this show, but I really don't have a lot of ailments.
My last physical was fine.
You got a deep call.
You have a deep cough sometimes, though.
That is has not.
I think that is the Southern California air, Michael,
because I have really not have it had it very much lately.
The air is so great.
It's so clean.
It's one I really it's actually been with like having a having a son and like it's
maybe think about childhood, obviously.
And I'm like I'm like unlocking old memories and stuff.
But part of that has been I keep walking around and thinking it feels like 1994 to me.
This feels like a type because I grew up here.
This feels like a type of weather I haven't experienced in L.A.
since I was a child.
Wow, it's not weather, but air quality, air quality.
Right. Yes.
No, there you can notice it.
I think I would probably notice it more if I was living in Hollywood.
But it's it's surely different.
Yeah, yeah.
You can feel a difference.
So as long as Jason doesn't have a banana in the morning,
that is the entire system.
Not afraid of covid-19, but not afraid of an early morning banana.
Early morning,
coffee before coffee before 7 a.m. or an early banana.
I'm extremely curious.
Obviously, it is no solid foods yet and there won't be for a little bit.
But I will be very curious.
I will definitely take a picture of the first time my boy successfully consumes
an AM banana. All right.
Well,
oh, no,
now you're now you're Monday-esque rivalry with my son will
kick into gear.
We will.
Oh, we got to have a contest to see that Jason and your son
eats the same thing and see who deals with it better.
But there will be there'll be those things that are like, I love mashed peas.
I've always been big mash pea guy.
Let's let's OK, we probably I don't know if we're going to come upon a new tagline
for the show, but let's talk, let's talk.
When is when is he getting involved in the show?
When is when is because because first of all, we appreciate like this is a great
storyline in year three, you know, this is a great hey, just like I love Lucy.
We have a little Ricky. We got a little Scotty.
Exactly. So that's good.
So but when you know, that's what's going to be good is like when you get to go on
all this stuff with him. Yeah.
Yeah. I mean, also, you know, because it's
like going to be very emotional and moving, but also for content.
He is content.
This is the we're witnessing the first moment right now of him being kind.
If you're listening to this son, you are content also context.
If you're listening this way in the future, everyone in the era your dad was
growing up in where had to be just voracious makers of content at all times.
Or they would everything would fall apart and they'd starve and die.
Hopefully it's different in your time.
I don't know when he's hearing this,
but yeah, I don't know.
I mean, it's going to be nice kind.
I mean, it's going to unlock episodes that we can do.
We can review changing tables.
We can do a changing. Yes.
Final four. Maybe you can join us to that.
I know what else is on the table here.
I
you can do.
Well, you know, you know, one thing I will say just with things that our
audience knows about, we already know the the first Halloween costume,
because Halloween is a big deal. Oh, yeah.
That's a major thing we've been looking forward to.
Having a baby.
He's going to be truffles the bear.
Wow.
Good.
We can't wait for that.
Great choice.
That's that's better than Christmas, I think.
Now you will be able to and I forget what what is the like pirate or a pirate
equivalent of the Bibbidi Bobbidi boutique?
Oh, yeah.
I don't recall.
There will be some whatever that is,
whatever like the equivalent for for little boys is now you will be able to do
some you will be able to first hand review experiences that were at off limits to us
as men in our thirties. Yeah, yeah, absolutely.
Yeah, there's all these things that I'm not a creep if I go to now.
Legoland that opens that up.
Oh, perfect. Well, I'll be.
Yeah, we all can go to Legoland because there's a child with us.
Everybody can go. Yes.
It's we're going to be a lot less judged for going into a Chuck E.
Cheese now. Oh, oh, I didn't even think about that.
Yeah, yeah.
Although I say I'm more worried about going into a well times Chuck E.
Cheese than I am about anything in the covid era.
Oh, I saw I don't know if this is true.
This is a little bit of a tangent, but I saw a headline and I really I need to
read the article that in order to boost sales for Chuck E.
Cheese during covid that people they were renaming Chuck E.
Cheese on the Grubhub and stuff app on the delivery apps.
Yes.
So somebody ordered from Pasquale's Pizza
and Wings and realized it was Chuck E.
Cheese, which I love.
It was I think that was near in or near Philadelphia.
And there is a Pasquale's like there are Pasquale's pizza.
It like unrelated.
So they're like, oh, I wonder if it was like that place.
And then it was just like, nope, it was Chuck E.
Cheese in disguise.
Oh, my God.
Because there's been this syndrome of, you know, and I think the famous one in
L.A. is it's Steve Aoki as a pizza place and it operates as five different kitchens
on various food delivery apps and so for what and they they owned it.
Chuck E.
Cheese released a statement said, yeah, we're trying new things.
We're trying a new business model to kind of, you know, try to find a new
audience for our delicious pizza and wings and like you're so you're pulling the
Aoki scam. That's kind of a weird little scummy thing to be doing.
Hey, if people if it keeps people employed, whatever.
But I don't Pasquale's pizza and wings.
They should have. It should be Helen.
It should be Helen or Munch.
That's what I think.
You know, it's funny. It sounds too real.
It would have
like that's they are going for an audience
entirely of people who don't get that reference.
Like if it was us making that order, we would have had them in a second.
That's a good point.
Yes, I think I guess for whatever reason, your average American doesn't know the name
of the pizza chef that was discovered by Chuck E.
Cheese in the kitchen playing on the pie plates, his full name being Pasquale P.
Pie plate.
That's right. And again, if I could, you know,
allude to a world where my son is listening to this, hey, bud, your old man
spent a lot of time thinking about the various robots and the Chuck E.
Cheese is we know the full names.
You know, we love that it's Charles Entertainment Cheese.
I spent a lot of my life thinking about that fact.
And that's the kind of info I'm so excited to pass on to you, pal.
He's going to be such a tough guy that hates robots and loves sports.
Very, very possibly.
If things do go in an opposites manner, that could be the case.
I don't know. I hope he's not an opposite.
I've told you guys I am like keeping kind of a loose grip on the theme park thing.
I'm not going to just pounce on him and just throw info at him.
And then in 84, they added something called Horizons.
And that was a neat that was where you could sort of like a different past
of the future. And you sound like a robot butler.
And I'm not going to like I'm going to cool it.
I'm going to ease him into the waters on Disney stuff.
There's posters in his room already.
So he'll have like fond memories, hopefully buzzing around his baby brain.
As we talk about, of course, we have a baby brain scenario here.
And I'm excited about that.
I don't know. I'm not going to force it.
But of course, I would love him to be a theme park buddy.
Don't you are you playing, though,
like just at a low volume during the day, like an ambient Tomorrowland loop?
Oh, I haven't yet.
But that's really chill. That's actually very chill.
But also, you know, you're getting your planning the seed.
Like these are important times for a brain to develop.
Yeah, yeah.
And if he can have deep lodged memories
of the barely futuristic smooth jazz of Larry Carlton,
I mean, I'll be happy for many reasons.
But yeah, I mean, you know, you got to all you can do is try to be a nice guy
and raise a kid who's a nice guy, too.
And, you know, I'm not planning any weird.
I'm not going to make him hate.
I'm not going to plant some weird cult
thing in his brain where I say some keyword years later.
And now he's part of a kid army.
All I'm trying to do is implant the Tomorrowland music loop and hope it gives
him some nice. Yeah.
Also, you got to get us into that mom's panel.
You got to get us onto that.
I know that's that's where the real dirt is.
The raw intelligence.
I will blow the lid off that thing.
What I
will say this is going to be a Scott is not going to be happy that I'm going to
re bring this up, but I think Jason will be happy.
This gets us closer to an idea I had about a year and a half ago.
Hey, yeah, yeah.
Have we talked about this on the show?
The audience know this.
I don't think the audience has heard this yet.
This is an idea I had a while ago.
It was more of a bit at the time, but now it's getting closer to reality.
Yeah, yeah.
We're thirds closer because here's here's the genesis of it.
I think it was we went to Knott's Berry Farm with Doug Barnes of Season Pass.
We were talking about how a lot of what they call mommy blogs and get to go to
all the Disney events.
So I was trying to think of a way that would actually get us on Disney's radar
because doing a reverent podcast with swears is not going to work.
So I said, well, what if we had alter egos?
What if we started a podcast called the Disney Daddies
with a Z with the Disney Daddies?
And I think my my idea, my idea for at least the bit was that we were three
single dads with three sons each and they were all a handful and they were all a
handful and we love them, but they're a handful.
We love them.
And that phrase, maybe one of the hardest, the hardest laughs I've ever had.
Like Jason and I met Doug and Robert at Portillo's.
We hadn't met them before we talked.
And then I think we drove over to Knott's and I think I said that phrase to you.
And I do think you were like crying, laughing.
I guess I'm tooting my own horn.
But yes, I think that my memory was like you couldn't you couldn't catch your
breath, your lungs couldn't handle three single dads with three kids each, three
sons, three sons, that is all boys.
It gets worse.
The more sons you add, yes, gets more of a handful.
The more sons you add.
Oh, I would imagine I was wrong.
I said we were a third there were only a ninth there.
So we're not.
We're a ninth there.
We're a ninth there as far as the bid is concerned.
Now, will the Disney daddies rear their head at a certain other point before we've
completed the prophecy where we were all single?
Yes.
Sorry, Scott, in this prophecy, you're divorced.
Yeah, I know. Wait, I have to break up with Aaron for this.
Looks like a bad time.
But if it if it gets us into an extra panel, it'll get us into an extra panel.
And the joke I made a year and a half ago will come true, which is all that
matters.
But yes, we're one ninth of the way to actually be one ninth and three divorces
away.
Or I guess honestly, one, you could you could be the only divorce and then we just
never marry. We just have three kids.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, that's it.
It doesn't matter how you get there.
It's about that. It's about the destination, not the journey.
About the bit of the Disney daddies.
I approve this plan.
However, you know, like, hey, my my son cannot communicate barely anything.
He does not give his permission to be part of this.
I will only do this with still a fraudulent child.
All right. All right.
The real child is not any part of the so we still got three to go.
Statistically, like just the chances of us, say we each have three kids,
which that seems hard enough.
I love that. I love this one.
But oh, my God.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
Dying up the numbers to three just yet.
Yeah, I think I suggested Jason get a dog and he almost passed out once.
So I don't know.
We'll see.
But even the chances of just all of them being sons.
So it's going to be probably pretty
impossible to completely fulfill the prophecy of the Disney daddy.
So it did happen if we somehow actually as much as yeah, there's the there's the
fake way we could do it and just start.
We could just buy a Geo cities and start to get this website off the ground.
But also, what if we that would be bizarre if we look back and like, oh, my God,
we all had three sons, it's like the what if you like better?
It's like the better call Saul like pre it's like the origin story of the Disney
daddy's is what podcasts the ride is watching it form.
We also if we were if we could all say
that we all if we could legitimately say the phrase my three sons, that makes sense
because we're all such big fans of William Frawley.
We're all big fans of I love Lucy.
And later, my three sons are going to force William Frawley on your child.
Oh, absolutely.
Stan, you know, it's important they learn the standards early on, you know, the good
stuff rather than Santa, I'm going to do William Frawley.
That's who brings presents every year
and also like tries to shove a bottle of whiskey in his mouth.
Put some air on you.
All right.
I think that's a great Christmas tradition in general.
Yeah, so I think, yeah, the podcast will look back ten years from now.
We'll all be not funny anymore.
There'll be no comedy.
It'll just be a blog, a GeoCities blog,
and we'll go and get free things from Disney, which is more like Apple at that time
owned by Apple. We're mad there was we're just mad there wasn't enough Mountain Dew
at the Caribbean beach, silly string battle.
It just wasn't they really skimped on refreshments this year.
I'm not like, hello, you're the most successful company in the world.
Can we get some Mountain Dew?
There's no hint of irony anymore.
There's no self-awareness.
It's just like I counted the fries at the hungry.
I counted the fries that you get with the cheeseburger at the Hungry Bear.
And you used to get 35 fries and now they're only giving you 27 or lower.
And I think this is shameful coming from the Disney company.
You call this guacamole.
I call it melted avocados.
The hand soap used to be pink and now it is dark blue.
I disagree with this.
It smells bad, too.
I really don't like it.
The Disney swan is disgusting.
It's shameful that it's next to the Disney dolphin.
I'm not keeping these up equivalently.
I'm one of the three goddamn Disney daddies.
Do you know who I am?
I'm on the list to get into this opening night PR event for Legoland.
I'm one of the goddamn Disney daddies.
Well, I don't see I don't see your three sons anywhere.
Oh, no, they don't come.
They don't get what they don't come to the things you get.
They're a handful.
They hate me.
They hate Disney and they hate me.
Doesn't make me any less a Disney daddy.
I don't know why I'm in New York now, too, if I'm a Disney daddy.
Because we're persnickety.
In all these years, we got a lot more persnickety.
Partially because of the handful and partially because we are the food lately
on resort has not been up to snuff.
This is going to be a fascinating
character study over the course of 10, 20 years, this podcast.
Yeah, yeah.
Decay, the mental decay.
I mean, it's very funny.
It's lining up with the decay of all media, like the rise of this,
the rise of podcasting, who knew the rest of media is just disappearing.
It's been referenced on the show before,
but there will be an episode that will be the Walter White in the crawl space
breaking bad moment when there was no going back.
Did it just happen in terms of our sanity with the father of the pride?
Well, that was, you know, that was that was a that was a push.
That was, you know, Walt, I'm trying to think what when he did like that was
maybe when he throws the explosion in the room with Tuco.
That was an early worse than that.
Yeah, that was an early one that was slightly breaking up, breaking us,
but also, you know, it put us on the dark path, but it wasn't no return yet.
I don't think I'm kidding when I say this,
that I had a worse day doing the father of the pride marathon than I did
during childbirth.
That I believe I genuinely there was.
Yeah, there were there were there were
highlights or good things that happened.
I'm not sure Aaron would agree.
It's probably a different perspective for her.
But I would like I'm like, which day would I rather recall?
Absolutely. Yeah.
Even taking the, you know, the photo, the Polaroid moments, not into account.
It was father of the pride way, way more tedious.
We yes, in case you don't know what we're talking about.
Last week, we put out a Patreon that was us watching all 13 episodes of a Siegfried
and Roy cartoon called Father of the Pride.
And we did it in about what, 10 hours, 10 compact hours, less eight.
I don't know.
I feel like, yeah, that's about how long
labor was, actually.
It was like equivalent times.
Yeah, I believe that.
God, again, we're my son to be listening to this.
If you bailed, I understand.
And if you're asking why I do this or have done any of this, I don't know.
I couldn't tell you.
You'll be you'll be unsolving the mystery
of your dad or solving the mystery of your dad for for a long time.
It's in your hands now.
I picture him like at 17 listening to this and he's dressed like Mutt Williams
from Indiana Jones and the Kingdom of the Crystal Skull.
Like he's a cool guy.
Yeah.
Heading towards the 2050s,
greasers are going to make a big come back loop back around.
Yeah.
100 year.
It would be like, yeah, like Streets of Fire, like that, like future greaser,
like Willem Dafoe, if you know what I'm talking about.
This movie Streets of Fire, I forget who I forget who directed it.
Somebody's going to throw his iPod in the iPod or whatever device he's listening
to this on, he'll he'll throw it in the trash before he goes out and wins state.
Yeah.
He took his football team all the way to state, right?
Yes. Is that the kind of thing you do?
Dad, I play basketball, you idiot.
You don't even know what sport I play.
Oh, my dad. Yeah.
He talks about robots or something.
I don't know. I don't like to talk about him, honestly.
And I'm right there.
My dad bought my dad, my dad bought an old smart one animatronic from the auction
down the street, and he's been trying to restore it for the last six months.
You could barely get him to talk to me.
I don't want to talk to him, but I could barely get him to.
He made me learn that name.
He ran flashcards of all the robots and didn't teach me multiplication tables.
He said, if you can't learn math from a ride, it's not worth learning.
He did tell me something about thanking the Phoenicians, though.
I guess I'm thankful for that.
And he laughed.
He laughed a really quiet chuckle to himself when he said it.
I don't know. A long time.
Dude's weird.
What can I say? Let's get high.
Let's get high with some future weed.
I probably am at the point where I should peace out.
And this was all a lot of fun.
And I'm glad we did.
But I am going to part ways and I am going to do baby stuff.
And I've made it about me and about my son for a while.
Now, Mike and Jason are going to make it about you and your questions.
Thanks for sending them in.
I'm sorry I'm piecing out, but you survived,
if I guess I'm right, the story of my child's birth edition.
In all honesty, this has all been really wonderful.
I am more psyched about this at this juncture than I imagine that I could possibly be.
He's the best.
You guys are the best.
Aaron, you're the best.
You're the audience. You're the best.
Full of love and joy.
And Mike, as you were saying, the irony is dripping away.
This is where it starts.
It's all earnestness from here.
We could be earnest.
I think the listeners would share.
We would just say congratulations, Scott and Aaron.
Yeah, very excited about the new edition, you know, in a non-ironic way.
We don't have to make jokes.
Be nice. Yeah, true.
This could be a sincere moment.
Oh, maybe this is the Walter White moment when there's no going back and we're not
we're not ironic anymore. Oh, my God.
I don't know about that.
Oh, Jason.
As Scott and Aaron were dealing with giving birth, I won an auction on eBay for
an Islands of Adventure watch from 20 years ago.
No, but that's not.
There we go.
Oh, I guess. Yeah, it's got you're kind of right.
Yeah, it's not ironic.
Yeah, it is.
It's your favorite.
I love it.
That's your favorite place on the planet Earth.
Yes.
And look, you don't find Port of Entry based merchandise a lot.
So I thought it was interesting.
None of it's ironic.
This is all stuff that we that we love.
And you know what?
I think like that childless man, the childless man in your 30s, I think
I think that it's not a literal fact as much as it is a state of mind.
I still feel like a childless man in my 30s, even with a child, because I think,
well, you know, that that joke implies like a sad person, maybe he was obsessed
all these things that nobody cares about.
But how much joy have we gotten out of all of these things?
And how much joy did it bring me in the lead up to to having it before there was
this baby giving me joy? It's all it's all it's all fun and wonderful.
And maybe I won't be
talking in this particular way if I stop if the sleep gets tougher.
Well, you know, who knows what's around the corner?
But, you know, why don't we let's is it three child like men in their 30s?
You know what I mean?
Three Peter Pan, three Peter Pan, three Peter Pan.
No, no, no, no, no.
That is one I am scrubbing that.
I've said this to you guys already.
My son will not know of Pan.
If you're listening to this, don't worry about it.
I'm not talking about anything.
There I don't want to hear anything about.
I don't want to grow up. You're growing up.
You're doing it.
You're not a little boy forever.
Don't be ridiculous.
Your son's in the big top hat with the glasses.
He's best friends with.
I like those guys. They're fine.
But I you know what?
I maybe
if we decide to tweak that as time goes on.
But I think first of all, that's the least
amount of letters that we could possibly have to change.
That's only like that's only three.
Yeah.
And you could actually delete it such
that the E just goes backwards two notches and you add the S's on the end.
So I like it for clarity and brevity.
But I also I like the ring of it, too.
Yes, I mean, we could really take the word out.
Three men in their 30s, also pretty funny.
Yes, I know me having a kid doesn't excuse any of this.
Also, I will say once we're all what do you consider late 30s?
Is it 37 and on?
What do people think?
I think 37 and on.
Yeah, because I think mid would be 34.
We could say for now, we could say
three
men in their mid 30s.
Mid is funny. And then late 30s is even funnier.
So we can adapt it there as well.
Just add a little bit of an extra like
mid 30s is a funny, more specific thing.
But late 30s, I think, is really is good.
We can all try this together with a screen share.
We could all kind of workshop it and just make sure we all feel good about the words
forming as we adjust to the very important Twitter bio.
Yeah.
So we're going to do a lot a lot of work on this.
But these are just some early ideas.
Yeah. Yeah.
Well, yeah, for now, from some childlike
men in their mid 30s,
one of which has a son in his less than two weeks, who is absolutely wonderful.
I love him very much.
I for now, I'm signing off.
You guys do whatever you want to do.
Thanks for bearing with me and audience.
Amazingly, because we've been recording so much, I'll talk to you next week.
It'll be like Scott.
Scott's not doing anything.
Yeah. Yeah.
It's like none of this ever happened.
It's like it's it's like, well, time travel to late March.
Awesome. Hey, thanks, fellas.
This was nice. Nice talk to everybody.
Welcome back, Jason.
A mic are here. We're back.
We're back. Yeah, fine.
I was fine an hour ago.
I feel like, you know, how do we how do we top, you know, a baby announcement?
We really can't, honestly.
We really should have just we should have just done an hour and not
you know what? I don't even want to do the mailbag.
OK, well, this is a big turn.
Yeah, I think we should just stop.
I think we can't top it.
I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding.
We're going to do the mailbag.
We asked for questions.
You had some things you wanted to talk about.
I can chat.
All I have to do is watch Better Call Saul season finale tonight.
So I'm here. I'm ready to go.
Uh, yeah.
Well, I don't know.
I have been spending some of the quarantine reading, you know,
the theme park blogs, the theme park trades and, you know, in between people,
you know, reaching reaching for content, I feel like there there has slowly been
an uptick in like actual like, I guess, two categories.
One is like people trying to estimate when stuff's going to open back up.
Well, that's a guess.
The guessing game of if you go on any of the, you know,
mouse info Facebook page, it's not the real like if you go there,
it's just endless speculating people just throwing out months that they think is
the day that these parks reopen.
It's it's yes, it's endless.
It's endless when you're talking about people guessing.
Yeah, I mean, I was reading Blue Loop a lot and like they had, you know,
some longtime theme park industry journalists and watchers like speculating
of what's going to happen and like it the these seemingly agreed upon thing is
that like, well, they're going to, you know, kind of discourage cues for a while.
Like tight cues, probably wear masks, you know,
probably make people stand six feet apart, that sort of thing seems to be a given.
If only because Shanghai Disney has slowly started to reopen.
Well, yeah, they have not opened the park as of this.
I mean, unless they go surprisingly open it up and what we're recording this like
a week and a half before this comes out.
Yeah, I mean, it's interesting.
I don't know.
Still the problem with this is that we're so early into this
pandemic that I don't know.
Like, yeah, like Shanghai could have opened
and there could be a big resurgence in the disease and close before American parks
even go, so I don't know. The whole thing is chaos.
I don't I truly I'm sure Disney and Universal are having discussions
because we've heard for sure that there was a survey sent out asking Universal
people if they would be willing to do a covid test before going into the park
and if they would be willing to wear masks, have those restrictions.
So obviously internally, they're all gauging it.
But I at a certain point, I was thinking, you know, maybe it'll be ready for haunt
season so I can you know, I'm a guy who loves haunts.
Maybe we'll be ready for haunt season.
I don't I don't know that that's going to be I don't know that's going to happen.
I really don't. I'm doubtful.
I think, yeah, I feel like.
I feel like I saw the shift in real time,
like within a week of like, will it be ready for haunt season to early 2021?
These places. Well, because especially because California,
California is basically saying they don't think there should be any gatherings,
large gatherings, sporting events, etc.
concerts until twenty twenty one at the earliest.
So yes, and this could this couldn't be more depressing after the joy of childbirth.
The miracle of life.
True, that's true.
You know, we'll get to the questions, we'll get to the we'll get to the questions.
The other category of stuff that you and I have texted about a bit is that
universal construction still going full steam ahead.
Yes, because it is OK.
So Disney stopped doing construction and now construction everywhere has stayed
working in places, even like in California and certain certain things that you
wouldn't think are maybe essential.
There's still construction going on.
They're going to blow up the bridge over here by my apartment.
Yeah, they have already.
That's a whole thing.
And I think that is not slowed down at all.
But yes, Disney, Disney just today laid off a lot of their construction workers
that they have on the payroll I read.
Yeah. And I think mice chat just posted a big
rundown of aerial photography of Jason.
I saw all the mice chat photos today.
Do you think I didn't wake up and first thing?
Check mice chat dot com. Of course I did.
They had an aerial photo of a Quinjet in the Marvel land.
Yeah, it was like covered with like a blanket.
I guess not a blanket, I guess like a tarp.
I don't know. It's unclear if maybe there
are a few people still doing stuff at Disney.
But as far as like massive construction,
it appears that all the parks have ceased to cease working.
Not the case with Universal.
I heard this.
I think I was in a Twitch stream.
A lot of my anecdotes now are about, well, I was in a Twitch stream and a nice,
a nice viewer of the stream.
Let me know that Universal was still building.
And then we have a friend who lives right off of Lancashire, right by Hollywood
Universal. And he was like, oh, yeah, Universal is working around the clock
because you can see Nintendo land.
You can see Mario Kart from Lancashire, this giant building and apparently he
goes, yeah, I stand out when I take the dog out every night and watch the
construction. So it is very interesting.
My speculation is that Universal is owned by a telecom.
It's Comcast Universal.
They have a lot more money coming in than Disney does.
So I kind of feel like Universal is like, you know, now is the time to strike.
Now is the time we're going to get one up on Disney because they don't want to just
keep building and we can just keep construction going.
So I guess, I guess we can expect Nintendo land on the same timetable from whatever
it was going to be. Yeah, they're going to open up with brand new stuff.
It'll be two years out of a pandemic.
And it's like Universal has new rides in every park.
Yeah, because I don't I mean, I think that's the only way that will certainly help
boost attendance because that survey they were sending out were like, how would you
feel if half the park was closed?
And I was just as a laugh reading that.
It's like, are you still going to charge
100 percent of admission with half the park closed?
Because these places not really famous with doing like discount sales or
slashing prices, you know, how would you feel if you had a bad time at the park?
Yeah, my family, if we let you down,
my family was looking towards like a trip to Florida when it was decorated for
Christmas this year. And then I think we just kind of called it because like, well,
at best it would be weird, like it would be a little too weird for a little while
or a little too many hoops to jump through.
There's just no way.
There's just no true way to prevent the
spread of an infectious disease when you're talking about a bunch of people
cycling through buildings all day, there's just no way unless it was like
unless like Space Mountain was like one person goes down the aisle and then a team
member comes in and sprays disinfectant down the hall.
Then the next person comes in like there's no real way to do it.
I don't know. Who knows?
The answer is I don't know. Haunt season.
There's a look if I think I've been saying
that they could just turn Mickey and Friends into a covid-19 testing site.
They just throw up booths in front of the
ticket booth in the Mickey and Friends parking garage.
And they literally just do the crazy swab.
That might be the only way I like feel kind of secure about that.
And even then it's like, who knows that that's even that good
of a way to gauge? Who knows?
Sure. So we don't have any answers.
You turn us not for answers, I hope.
We're just we're just a couple of idiots.
We're just a couple of idiots.
But like, you know, if you're looking for a deep dive,
start searching Universal Patents because they're out there.
Oh, yeah, there's Universal Patents.
Yes, there's a crazy ride that looks like it goes in water and then it flies.
That's very exciting. All that stuff.
Yeah. You know, like, look, you come to us for message board speculation
and reviews of aerial photos of Disneyland posted on micechat.com.
Yeah, that is what we're here for.
And believe me, there was an helicopter
video of somebody flying over Disneyland the other day.
I watched the shit out of that. Sure.
And I was I was I was like, oh, yeah, that's what the guy was very
amused by the Splash Mountain show building and how it looks so different from from above.
And you know what?
He's 100 percent right.
I zoomed back on that three times and went, wow, he whoa, it looks so different from above.
So that's what I've been doing with my time while Scott's off having a baby.
Scott's off. Yeah.
Do you think he's still like, you know, while he's rocking the baby back to sleep,
is he checking those mice chat aerial photos?
Well, he yeah, I I haven't been texting him
mice chat aerial photos.
I don't know, because I feel like sometimes on the show we'll be like, hey,
did you see this? And he'll be like, oh, what is it?
What did I have to see?
But then like then he's listening and watching all the same stuff we are.
So that's true.
I think there's a good chance he's he's seen that Quinjet with a blanket over it.
I sent a very odd special of like circus acts in World Showcase.
And I was like, you guys seen this one?
He was like, yeah, we watched it last week.
And I'm like, OK, we're all doing we're all doing this.
I'd also like to say that I found the
Disney Daddy's logo I made a year and a half ago.
Yeah, it's great.
We'll be posting that.
And all I can say is a rainbow Comic Sans.
It's yeah, it's rain rainbow Comic Sans as if I'm Karnak.
And I was about to do a joke.
So, yeah, Disney Daddy's, you will see
that on the Twitter and eventually whatever we use the IP Disney Daddy's.
I really should copyright it as well.
Yeah, because I don't want I don't want that falling into the wrong hands.
Print it out, put it in an envelope, mail it to yourself.
Poor poor man's poor man's copyright copyright.
Yeah, is that right?
Yeah. So that just means you don't have to pay a fee.
It's just like does that really work, though?
I don't I feel like it worked back in the day where everything was mail based,
you know, where you just everyone had a ton of catalogs for anything specific.
I feel like I feel like poor man's copyright should be called lazy man's copyright.
Yeah, I think that's right.
Lazy dude's copyright.
That's let's from now on, we're calling poor man's copyright lazy dude's copyright.
Let's do it.
OK, so what are we doing? Mailbag?
What are you unless you mailbag? Yeah.
Other stuff. Do you have any announcements?
Do you are you having a baby or anything?
No, I have lost I lost my eBay bid for the
Incredible Hulk coaster in cast member uniforms.
OK, which, yeah, I don't know that they I do wonder how they got a hold of it to resell.
I got a notification from eBay today
that the seller of one of the Michael Eisner signed eight by tens will give me
a 15% off discount, bringing the total to, I believe, thirty eight ninety nine.
I believe
they could do better.
I could make another offer.
I could see if we get 30% off.
But, you know, let's see.
Maybe we will get to talk to the man himself.
Maybe he has, you know, a picture of himself on an eight by ten wearing a Winnie
the Pooh sweatshirt. Yeah.
Michael, that would be the that would be the last thing we'll ask him on the
interview. Do you have any eight by tens of you, preferably in the age range of
thirty eight to fifty one, wearing sweatshirts with characters we like?
Yeah, that is a thing I find endearing about him, that he looked like, you know,
he would dress like a person going to the park.
Yes, Eisner needs to look more like a dad, like a dad look like he needs more
sweatshirts. He needs more like back like backward baseball caps.
Liger. Yeah, Iger.
Iger busy. He's busy right now.
But I want to see like I want to see like War Room Iger, you know?
Yeah. Get him in a spirit jersey.
Spirit jersey. Yes.
You know what would be good?
Yes. Anything that didn't sell at the theme parks he should be wearing.
Like, really, we're cutting the budgets here.
Let's show in the company that he is
participating as well swing by the Disney character outlet and.
Like if the I'm so fly, Peter Pan shirts weren't selling, he should be in like an
XXL I'm so fly shirt in a picture of him in like a war room meeting with Chaypeck
in the board. That's great, because then all the business,
like all the like wannabe CEOs out there will be like, oh, wow,
I got to get one of I got to get
like that Timon in that XXL Timonin Pumba sweatshirt that said grub time on it.
Yes, he should he should have he should be
wearing athletic pants that say Nutcracker in the Four Realms on the butt.
He should be any sort of merch that clothing that is left over.
He should be showing us what he's doing and proving it by wearing that.
And then also fulfilling
Michael Eisner's legacy of dressing more like a dad, more like a regular Joe.
Yeah, because they're not going to move those pallets of Artemis Fowl baseball caps.
I don't think those are going to go fast.
So I started.
Yeah, I was just going to say Eisner, now that I think about it, you know,
he owns this company that makes like Bojack Horseman and made to convert.
He has a there's a picture of him wearing
a Bojack Horseman hat and wearing a John Cena shirt.
And this is from the last few years.
So he is still doing it.
And every man he's in the every man.
Iger is trying to be too cool for school.
He's trying to be James Bond.
We don't want that, especially right now during a crisis.
We want we want Artemis Fowl, Nutcracker in the Four Realms, Lone Ranger.
If he could wear Lone Ranger shoes, Lone Ranger boots, Toms.
Oh, OK.
Toms that look like promotional Toms that look like boots.
Toms that have spurs on the bottom.
If there's spur Toms that Iger could be
wearing, I think that would if the whole board, honestly,
chapec kind of dresses like an office guy, I think chapec could be helping out to
and yeah, any of these movies and dig back, dig back into the archives.
Mr. Boogity shirt for Bob Chapec.
Herbie goes to Monte Carlo sunglasses.
Anything, any of that stuff works pretty well, I think.
Absolutely. OK, we're way over now on this episode.
Let's just get to some questions.
Let's get to some questions.
All right, you got one queued up.
Uh, hold on.
Do you have one? I mean, I sure.
Yeah. OK, go ahead.
Jen DeMare, Jen DeMare, Maria.
I'm sorry, I've butchered your name already.
Mranardy, she asked if I'm allergic to bananas.
And I don't think I am, but I will say this.
I was told by someone via DMs that what I think is a banana allergy might actually
be something in disguise, it might be an oral allergy that I have to ragweed.
Oh, yeah, I don't know if that's true or not, but apparently that is
sometimes if you eat a banana, I can just read what she said.
She said the proteins of the banana are similar enough to those of ragweed
pollen that it causes your oral mucosa to have a minor allergic reaction.
It will likely happen with cantaloupe
and honeydew and maybe chamomile tea.
So I should try that and see if it's the same thing.
So that actually sheds more light on what happened in the recent episode
from Confrontation. I was discussing how I like cough a little bit eating a banana.
And we tried to see if I was allergic by rubbing a banana on my hand,
which is probably not the best way to do it.
But nothing happened.
I did not have any sort of skin reaction. Anyway, you were saying something.
I was going to say, how do you fare come pollen season?
Because I feel like like
Jason and I are calling out like, oh, this is a bad year.
I thrive during pollen season.
You thrive.
OK, I thrive.
So I'm fine during then.
What do you got?
OK, I actually just came in through our email.
This is from AJ Curry.
Assuming no park hoppers, what's the ideal order to do the four parks on a Disney
world trip?
They say they're partial to Magic Kingdom, then Animal Kingdom,
then Hollywood Studios ending in Epcot.
I think that's a pretty good order.
I think it kind of depends on where you're staying.
Yeah, I mean, there's a lot of variables to this question.
Yeah, I mean, as a kid,
you know, you go the family, you know, you usually hit up Magic Kingdom first.
Although when we got a little earlier, a little older,
we would usually get down into Orlando around lunchtime.
So then by the time we dropped our bags at the hotel, had some lunch,
I think we would usually do like a half day at Epcot because that's an easy park
to like kind of just ease into, you know?
Yes. I mean, Epcot is like I kind of consider Epcot the your safe house,
your chill out house for the parks.
So it's like maybe you did have an intense day at Magic Kingdom trying to do a lot
of rides. You go to Epcot and you chill out.
There's the most chill out zones at Epcot.
That's what I like.
So my real I mean, I would say like, you know, do Magic Kingdom, go to Epcot,
do Hollywood Studios, go to Epcot, do Animal Kingdom.
And then you guessed it. Go back to Epcot.
Sure. It's like I like that.
Now, I guess if the question is you have one day per park, if you if you don't do
the hopper, if that's what the exercise, the mental exercise we're doing here,
I think honestly, for me personally, what I would do is I would do Magic Kingdom
first because it's similar to Disneyland, but I like Disneyland better.
So it's sort of not as much of a priority.
Then next, I'm probably going Hollywood Studios,
even though Hollywood Studios has gotten more stuff over the years,
then I'm doing Animal Kingdom and then I am probably ending on Epcot to just send
the trip off on a nice, relaxed note.
Yeah, I think that's right. Sure.
Well, I think their order makes sense, too, of like Magic Kingdom and Animal
Kingdom, like knock out that part of the property and then shift over to the other
part of the property. Right.
But I mean, I understand cost is always an issue.
I think park hopping in Florida is such a joy.
Yeah, that's sort of one of my favorite things is to have the flexibility there to
do that is to be like, oh, wow, we realize Epcot is open two hours later.
We should do the yeah, let's do it like that.
There's a fun discovery there.
So anyway, that's that's my feeling on that topic.
I have a question here from Thomas Lipscomb.
What other animatronics would you like to see turn into DJs?
Now, we've talked a little bit, I think was on the anniversary show from Dynasty
Typewriter about, you know, like an Eisner DJ, but he doesn't have an animatronic.
So we really haven't fully gotten into animatronic DJ talk.
Now, my answer is.
The problem with my answer is it's mostly like all of them.
Yeah, I can't think of a single animatronic.
I wouldn't want to be a DJ, but let's maybe that's actually better.
Unless you have a good answer.
Let's figure out animatronics.
We do not want to be DJs.
I think easily Trump.
I don't want the animatronic of Trump to be a DJ.
Yeah, I think anything.
Anything too scary, maybe?
Like, I don't know if I want to be constantly looking at the alien encounter.
Alien.
Oh, wait a minute. Now, that's interesting.
You're saying the terrifying, not the what's his name?
And I can't think of the alien before the cute alien that they fry.
Skippy. Not Skippy.
You're saying it's truly like xenomorph.
Ask. Yeah.
Alien DJing.
Yeah. No, I think I would want like Skippy and a hat and like a lot of wristbands.
OK, let me let me throw this scenario out at you.
It's alien encounter.
It's the same room, but you can have a drink with you.
And that alien is in the tube, but he's DJing.
Oh, OK.
And he's doing all the hottest hits of the day.
If he's being cool, OK, maybe, maybe if he's being cool.
I think he's being cool.
I think he's playing the newest hits from Travis Scott.
I'm trying to think of other hip artists that I could reference here.
Hmm.
Dua Lipa.
Yes.
Charlie X.I. Is that right?
Charlie XCX. XCX.
Sorry. XI.
XCX.
Yeah, Charlie.
Sia.
I know she's been around for a long time.
Still hanging around. Yeah, she's great.
She covers her face. I know her.
So he's DJing.
You have a fun cocktail because it's Magic Kingdom in Florida and you can drink there.
So that's good.
And then you're sort of it's sort of like an enjoyable show.
But I will say probably once every few hours, the alien does break out and try
to kill everyone in the middle of the DJ set.
So you're listening to a Travis Scott song and then the lights go out.
And then the alien attacks you while that song is playing.
I actually think it sounds less scary.
Yeah, yeah.
Wait, no. So you're saying he does attack you.
OK, I'm saying he has to occasionally attack, maybe not every show.
I think it should go through.
OK, maybe if it goes through the motions like he's going to attack and then he just
his like little arm claw thing just stretches out and it's got an air horn.
Or like a T-shirt gun or something like it's
like, yeah, like he fools you.
Yeah, it's actually a reggaeton horn.
That's good.
So, yeah. And then like when you hear him, like that's when the beat drops,
it seems like he's going to attack and then the beat drops.
Oh, yeah, that's good.
And then like you hear him like scratching next to you.
You hear him scratching a record for the DJ set?
Yeah. Yeah, that's good.
I'm trying to think that.
I think that I was going to say the Yeti, the Yeti should be a DJ.
But he doesn't have much movement, so I guess he's out.
I will say I don't want the Yeti to be a DJ on Expedition Everest.
Right. Just because he doesn't have the range of movement.
But I do want the Abominable Snowman on the Matterhorn to be a DJ.
OK, yeah, he moves around a lot, moves around a lot.
He keeps the energy up.
He can keep the energy up.
And again, I'd love I would love to go on the Matterhorn while they're blasting one
of my favorite modern artists like Travis Scott.
Yeah, let's see.
I'm trying to think of any other animatronics I don't want to be DJs.
It's tough. All the other presidents.
Yes, they should all be DJs.
Maybe not George W. Bush.
I'm still hung up on scary.
So like any of the Harry Potter, like the Death Eaters or the Big Spider.
Oh, I think a Death Eater DJ would be awesome.
Yeah, you just don't like scary.
You don't like scary DJs is what we're getting.
I think he's got if he has a flat brim hat on, I think it humanizes him.
Are you make some cute?
Are you scared of dead mouse?
Oh, dead mouse is a little because he's just the head.
He has it, but it's not.
Yeah.
But I'm saying you can't see his face, so you do find him scary.
Do you find Daft Punk scary?
I don't think I find Daft Punk scary.
Dead Mouse has the X's over the eyes usually.
Right. Yeah.
So he's dead because he's dead.
Yeah, because he's dead.
Yeah. Yeah.
What if you put dead mouse on Harry
Potter and the Forbidden Journey or whatever the ride is called?
That would certainly make it more foreboding for my taste.
I think that that theater part of the ride, though, would be cool if that was a big
DJ room and there was a strobe going because that part of the ride freaks me out.
OK, yeah, yeah, it freaks me out, too.
That could be a cool Horror Nights flip if she would loosen up a little.
Yeah, come on, J.K.
And make it a party.
J.K. won't have any fun and let us have a party in Harry Potter land, which is what
we're all dying for. Harry Potter and the Forbidden Party.
It's like we it's like they have to have it's like she's mom and like we have to
have it secretly there while she's not like she's not home.
And then we can have we can have all the fun you can project, you know, you can
play modern songs in Hogsworth.
I was about to call it Hogsworth.
Hogsmeade, I know what it's called.
Sure. Is Hogsworth a character or did I just create a character?
I think you just created some sort of pig based character.
I just created a character called Hogsworth and he's got a monocle.
He's got a top hat.
He he's a ruthless businessman.
Oh, he's a tyrant. He's a tyrant dictator.
He's a dictator. Yeah.
And he is on, let's say he's a mascot of a candy bar that I just created called
Hogsworth Hogsworth's.
It's a little smoky.
It's it's almost like he tricks you into thinking there's pig in that chocolate bar,
which is something you've been saying for a long time that you wanted a chocolate
bar that made you fooled you into thinking you were eating pig,
fooled me into thinking I was eating pork product in my chocolate bar.
The commercial is like, you'll think you're eating pig.
I am very, you know, I am sure, you know, people say, oh, he's a treat guy and he
likes pork. I'm very conflicted about a lot of that, like chocolate covered bacon or
maple bacon donuts. I feel like I've had good executions of it, but
I feel like it's a thing that you can't skimp on.
Like it can't be a thing.
I'll be honest, I don't go wild for it.
It's not my go to it.
I'm not that into it.
I'm kind of a sucker for like birthday cake flavored stuff.
Well, now you're you know who you're talking to here.
Well, yeah, I know you.
I know you would agree on that.
But like, I think we are a comic con and they were passing around like trays of
like maple bacon donuts, and those were pretty good.
Sure. I'll eat.
Look, if we're at a party, a comic con and there's a tray of bacon based
something, I will have it, I will try it.
But it's never my top order because getting it wrong is it's it's bad.
It's extra bad.
Yeah, a bad birthday cake, a bad birthday cake thing is like whatever.
You can stomach it, but it doesn't matter.
All right. Do you have a question?
I do. There's another email.
This is from Justin.
Justin says he he lives in New Jersey and recently moved for work next to the
Atlantic City Airport.
He bought an annual pass to Disney World right before everything got nuts.
And his plan was to fly down for weekly Saturday day trips.
And Justin was wondering if
do we know anyone in the PTR community that is as crazy as he is?
I don't think that's that great.
Like the flight from Atlantic City is very quick to Orlando.
I think it's very ambitious.
And Justin, I think you might have the worst timing
imaginable on that purchase.
I think I think most of the podcast,
the right listeners are just the resources away from being just as crazy.
I don't think I don't know what your situation is,
the flexibility in your life to be able to do that.
I think with the right amount of money and the right flexibility,
I think all of us would be like, we fly down to Florida once a month.
The only thing to me that might be slightly crazy on that angle is that the only,
I believe, the current domestic airline that only serves the only one that serves
the Atlantic City Airport is Spirit.
So I think the craziness might more come from like,
do you really want to fly Spirit Airlines that much that often?
The other things that fly in there are like
New Jersey's Air National Guard and like charter flights from Caesars.
Also, Justin is asking us this question.
You got to know who you're talking to here.
He has to bring something a lot crazier to the party than that.
If he's thinking he's going to like out crazy us,
like, have I like multiple times driven an hour and a half down to Anaheim and gone
to like work on my laptop for no reason?
Yes, I understand that's not a big of a commitment, but he's got to bring up
something like, you know, I put out a put a third mortgage on my house
in order to fund an annual pass.
He's got to say like, you know, I I'm driving to Florida every time.
I'm staying up 48 hours, going to the park for 12 and driving back with no sleep.
That's crazy. That I would say is crazy.
But once a month, taking a nice little flight and going to a theme park,
you're a very normal person, sir, when it when he compares to people to listen
to this show and the people who perform this show.
Yeah.
So I'm saying I'm saying, Justin, you're going to have to bring it, brother.
You're going to have to really bring it
if you want to be the crazy one in this henhouse, if you want to be the fox
in this henhouse.
Yeah, I mean, we sometimes we have gone down.
We've made the mistake or had to go down Friday late afternoon, early evening.
And that drive, I will tell you, the drive from the the drive to Anaheim from Los
Angeles can be twice as long as that flight from the Philadelphia, New Jersey area.
Yeah.
Um, yes, I agree with what you're saying.
So, yeah, Justin, try harder next time.
That's what I'm saying. That's summing up.
Let's see here.
I have a question from Dave Lindquist.
If you had a time machine and could use it
only once to visit a theme park at any point in the past, what park and year
would you pick?
I mean, you got to go opening day Disneyland, right?
You got it. You got to do that.
I know that's a that's a trite.
That's an easy answer.
But you got to see the heels in the cement.
You got to see the people being like
paying a nickel to use a ladder to climb the wall.
You got to see Walt walking around with Art Link letter.
You know, you but don't you think there is like like there's got to be a day back
in the 90s back when everything we like that's now closed is like open
simultaneously? Well, look, of course, there are a million answers to this question.
Yeah, I would also say there's there's
opening day of Indiana Jones to hopefully get hit with the ice effect.
That's true. Yeah.
And in case no one knows what I'm talking about, the supposedly, according to the man
who made the ride, Tony Baxter, for the first month or two,
there was an effect on the Indiana Jones ride where they would drop ice on you
just as you were entering the temple and seeing Mara or maybe after it.
I'm not sure. I think it might be right after it.
But it's around there.
But the effect was essentially there was a
like a I guess an industrial freezer in the ceiling that would create ice and then
drop it on the front of your car to make it feel like the whole place was coming
down. Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
Wasn't it where you see the large boulder?
Wasn't it that at that point and Indy's hanging from the rope?
I believe it's earlier. I could totally be wrong.
You can Google it while I'm talking if you want.
But I believe it was at least before or after Mara.
I think I think.
But what happened was it's an incredible strain to put on that freezer and they
just couldn't get it working consistently.
So it's in there, apparently.
It's still in the ceiling.
It's just the effect doesn't work anymore.
But, man, I am obsessed with this effect.
I'm obsessed with the idea that there would
actual physical stuff would drop onto the car at a certain point.
So I like that.
That is definitely on my top
hundred theme park history days that I would want to visit.
I feel like they wouldn't even get anywhere near that level of liability now.
Yeah, you would think I wonder what I wonder what like fail safes they had in
practice then to make sure like no piece of ice hit a kid in the front row of the
car, because you would think that would be very possible.
Yeah, I would want I would want to go to
Disney land to see the opening of Star Tours where George Lucas was there with C
3PO and R2D2.
That like stuff like that, for sure.
Yeah. And and the face character.
Luke and Leia and Han, right?
Oh, was that the same?
I think that's the same day. Yeah, I think so.
Yeah.
So stuff like that is a big deal.
I would love to see.
Like, I would love to go visit knots before it was nots Berry Farm,
like when it was a berry farm, when it was just a roadside.
Like chicken pie restaurant.
Yeah, I think we could both agree that we would both visit the roadside chicken pie
stand.
You guess she always made fried chicken.
I guess she wasn't really a chicken pie place.
Every time we go place, every time we go to knots, you put a comment card in the
box that says, could you shut down the theme park and just focus on chicken pies?
Please.
Could you just?
Yeah. Can you just make it a point to be a dirty roadside
car hop focus on chicken pies and jam, please.
So focus on chicken pie.
This is distracting from your core mission to feed weary travelers going
between L.A. and the and San Diego.
Your your first bluegrass album is called Chicken Pies and Jam.
As far as I'm concerned, when I finally
force you to put out an album, that's after you sing.
That's after you sing the old ones.
Yeah. Like Bill Frawley, which will.
I guess that episode hasn't come out yet.
There'll be some fun singing of the old ones in a few weeks.
That's all I will say as a tease.
You know, we got to wait for the recording booth to open back up.
We got to wait for Barry Gordy to have some availability.
You will only work with Barry Gordy.
Well, he's still kicking, right?
I believe he is.
I believe. Oh, is he?
Yeah, I believe he's alive.
Oh, I was trying to make it.
I thought he died years ago.
I'll look it up, but I believe he's alive.
And I'll cut this out if he's not.
He is 90 years old, my friend.
Wow.
Barry Gordy, and maybe he's not working, but we'll we'll pull him out of retirement.
Yeah, we'll pull him out when he hears
when he hears that Jason Sheridan from podcast, The Ride wants to start a
recording career.
He will he will he will get into action.
He'll spring into action.
I thought this day would never come.
It's like I
I love the ironic theme park podcast.
I was going to say the last one I have is, of course, opening day of Hard Rock Park.
Oh, that's a good one.
Yeah, that can you imagine?
Can you imagine walking around and seeing
Winston, the punk rock dog?
And can you think you'd have to tear me away from Knights and White Saturn?
What is also great is that if we were
there opening day, we would be one of about 200 people that visited and we would
be able to get on all the rides a lot. Oh, yeah.
So we would not be fighting crowds opening day of Hard Rock Park.
Yeah. So I don't know those.
Honest to God, if the time machine was
giving me one day, that's probably opening Disneyland.
But look, if I have the time machine
for a couple of weeks, you know, I'm going all these places.
Sure.
All right. I got two quick ones to wrap it up.
First one, Alice Carpenter, as all of these older Universal episodes have me
searching eBay for some old Universal merchandise.
What are some of the crazy merchandise for Universal that you stumbled upon?
Well, I teased this earlier.
I bought I paid twenty dollars for a watch, a rectangular watch, an odd,
odd shaped watch that has the Islands of Adventure lighthouse on it.
And so I'm waiting for that to arrive.
I lost out on an auction for a red
baseball cap that had Nancy and Sligo on it on the front.
Yes. And on the back, it said Islands of Adventure.
It must have been an opening around opening piece of merchandise.
Oh, my God. I really tried.
Was it it ended up going for I think maybe I just waited too long.
It didn't go for a lot like 15 or 20 bucks.
You lost it. I know.
I know this is great.
There is no I mean, we look we have a lot of fun on this show.
I made a lot of offers.
I made a lot of offers on that one.
And then I think I just made too many.
We talk about, you know,
we've compared you to different cartoon characters.
But I I think my favorite one to compare you to is Sligo.
Is I mean, look back in the spotlight, the modern the current Nancy comic.
I am I am wonderful.
I am desperately searching for this right now.
It's Islands of Adventure, Nancy and Sligo baseball hat.
Yeah, it's gone.
This was ages ago.
This is a while ago.
Oh, my God.
I am this is I've never been more panicked to try to find something.
I know. I know. Right.
There's it's not on.
There's not a new one on eBay.
Oh, my God, we have to find this.
We have to all have one, too.
Oh, that'd be great.
Yeah, that'd be really good.
Oh, my God.
OK, I guess I'm going to have to get back to this.
I guess we'll start.
Yeah, we'll start the hunt.
You win because I don't have anything nearly as good.
Universal we've talked about before doesn't is a little bit lacking in the
crazy merch arena.
Yeah, we just pay.
I mean, we were there for the 20th anniversary of Islands of Adventure.
And there was no anniversary stuff.
I was shocked.
Yeah, they didn't at least have a T-shirt.
There's
I see a Dudley Do-Right baseball hat with like Ranger character.
Oh, no, no, no, it is Dudley himself.
Sorry, it's Dudley. Yeah.
He looks weird on the hat, though.
I would know Dudley Do-Right is weird printing on this hat.
These weren't the best Nance and Sluggos,
which might have made it only the more valuable.
I was going to say that makes it better.
I don't think it had a buy it now option or else, obviously, I would have just done that.
But because like even just going through the hats for Universal,
I'm not seeing anything that like blows me away with its like kitschiness or its
weirdness. Yeah, it's a little I mean, I kind of I like a lot of the merch that you
find on eBay because it's so like square like it is.
There's a lot of like they really tried the year T-shirts for a while.
But yeah, I found an Annie hat, though.
That's pretty good.
Islands of Adventure orphan Annie white youth hat, which sounds like it's a racist
thing, but no, it's just the color of the hat is white and it's for a child.
It sounds us some way.
It definitely sounds odd.
White youth, white youth, saying white youth is really.
You can't say white youth.
You can't say what youth these days, folks.
Folks, we're bringing it back.
We're bringing back the phrase, we're bringing it back.
The hat measurement and the color white youth.
And we're going to make it happen.
So this is a this hat looks like pretty pristine.
I wonder if this is actually a newer item.
There's like the yeah, there's some kind of hat stuff.
But Universal really feels like
whereas Disney will carve out 10 percent or 20 percent for retro and to cater to
nerds like us, it feels like Universal is shooting for mainstream purchasing,
you know, 99 percent of the time they're shooting for like grandma who likes cat
in the hat, but she's not looking for some sort of vintage shirt to represent like
the Blues Brothers show that happened 20 years ago in the streets.
I know it's also happening now, but.
Yeah, and maybe that's part of it.
It's like licensing on some of those movies gets very weird.
But like you would think it would be a given to have like a faded like the neon
Universal Studios Florida sign, like the neon like just Universal Studios logo
that you can see the statue of at Hollywood.
You would think that would be a given.
Like Disney has like very a long time ago figured out like, oh, let's let's
sell some Heather Gray beat up Mickey shirts like that's like an easy go to purchase.
Yes, it fools my idiot brain.
I go, oh, that that's cool and it looks cool and it makes me seem cool.
Yeah, I I I went down a rabbit hole trying to find like they're they did have a little
bit of older merch that you can find on eBay with the Universal Escape
Universal short lived marketing
logo, which I I don't want to give.
I
wait for her to be back back from maternity leave before I start giving
Eric Gerdner T-shirt design suggestions, but a T-shirt with the in the Universal
Escape style, maybe we just sell one of those and it's just to me.
But I think it's my fancy.
Yeah, is she two weeks out from out of childbirth?
Yes, I think texture after we're done, though, with a couple exclamation points.
Hey, I've got some ideas for new T-shirts to get on this now.
I think you really should start now.
Well, it's like Scott said for this for their son, for their son.
Yes, that's what it's for.
That's what we're doing that for now.
I just found Rare Universal Studios,
Islands of Adventure, Toon Lagoon, Popeye, Coin Medallion.
This is interesting.
Sixty three seventy five was purchased for.
So that's pretty weird.
Is that in like a little booklet?
Yes. A little box.
Yeah, I've come across stuff like that.
Yeah, they did have collectible coins for like odd collectors going after like
the Franklin Mint enthusiasts, right?
The souvenir spoon
enthusiast. Hey, bring that.
Let's bring back tiny souvenir spoons.
Maybe that's something we need.
The spoon collecting market.
Spoon collecting.
Because, yeah, pins, I don't know, are pins as popular?
They tried. I mean, they have a lot of pins.
They tried doing a little pin thing for a while.
Right. But I think spoons, spoons is the way forward.
I mean, there's fan blogs, there's blogs and podcasts just about Universal.
Like the I think the market is there for a little bit of weird stuff.
Yes.
I mean, we've met some of the merchandise people from Knots.
And they're all in on the company's history on like obscure stuff.
And I am very impressed with what they do with the smaller.
Yeah. You know, staff and stuff they have.
They can't go hardcore, though, because like we want like circle Cloud nine and
Circle K shirts, which I think they may have done a little bit a while ago.
But those aren't always in circulation.
And also we want the music of Knots,
which doesn't seem to be anything that they'll do soon.
No, because like Knots has like there's an original song.
There's a lot of original music,
but there's an original song on the Halloween overlay of the log flume ride
of the I'm blanking on the name of it because I'm in a hot room and I can't
remember anything. Timber Mountain Log.
Thank you. Timber Mountain Log ride.
There's an original song that that animal band is playing and I want it.
I want to listen to I want to listen to I want to make a playlist of that.
A Travis Scott song.
All my favorites.
It's just those two and they loop.
Yes, the Travis Scott song I like and the Timber Mountain Log Halloween overlay
music, Halloween overlay. All right.
What else was your last?
OK, we have last one.
It feels fitting because I know you said you want to go watch better call.
So this from user Draking Bad Draking Band.
Nice.
What's your favorite Disney resort hotel that you've never stayed in?
This is a funny you.
This is the you just picked like a very dry clinical question to end here.
I figured it would inspire some conversation.
It'd be a nice note to end on.
It sure sure it would.
But it wasn't like, you know, which which character would be.
Oh, no. If you have one of those, we can end on one of those.
No, I don't think I have one.
I'll give you my answer, I think.
And it was Disney specific. Is that right?
They said Disney. Yeah.
Yeah, I think I have stayed.
I am very lucky I have stayed at all the big three.
I've stayed at the three contemporary Grand Floridian and Polynesian.
So I think that Animal Kingdom Lodge looks cool and I have I would like to stay
there because it reminds me of Grand Californian.
Very lucky I've stayed there as well.
But I like I'm very fascinated by it.
I haven't even actually been over there
to that hotel.
Oh, I ate a Boma once.
Yeah, it's really neat.
So, yeah, I think it's that I think that's my answer.
But, you know, there's new ones opening up if if things open up.
What's the new one called that's opening or opened Reflections Reflections?
Disney Resort.
I mean, that looks interesting.
Yeah.
But yeah, I don't know.
I would you have a big one?
Well, I
yeah, for practical reason, I
and we my family have talked about doing this next time we go down.
I've never stayed at the yacht or beach club.
And that is the only way to get to the crazy pool nowadays.
Like you used to just be able to.
We would I mean, we would stay on site and we would like pool hop all the time.
And if you stayed at a Disney hotel, that was kosher.
And if you were cool about it, it was always kosher.
And then it was just vacation clubs.
Members could pool hop.
So we got that perk for a few years.
And then
now I think they've even limited that pool specifically to like, yeah,
vacation club members can still do some pool hopping.
They cannot go to
God, I'm blanking on the name.
It's like it's a big selling point for the resort.
Hmm.
I don't know.
I what's funny about it is I didn't even think about Yacht and Beach Club or
Boardwalk because I hang out over there so much in my brain.
I felt like I have been there, but I have not stayed.
Yeah, I have not stayed at either place.
And I would love to do that, too, because that's what the boardwalk a couple of
times and yeah, it's great that combined with Epcot Center like that combined with
World Showcase, I don't should I?
Is that the best plot of land on the Disney World Resort?
Is that the best, coolest section, especially as our adult year as adults?
As adults, I think, yeah,
being able to walk to Epcot and Hollywood Studios and having that many bars
and restaurants and nice hotels, it is pretty.
It is pretty hard to beat
that as far as ambiance at night is hanging out on the boardwalk or hanging
out at Yacht and Beach Club, walking into World Showcase, leaving.
I think I said this on the episode when we on our recap of when we took our trip
is that I was really wound up the day first day we got there just because I
hadn't slept a lot trying to coordinate everybody getting into the park at the
same time, blah, blah, blah. And I went over.
I sat at World Showcase.
I had a drink while I watched the Bahamian.
I and I remember going like having a sigh and I went, ah, yes.
And then I walked World Showcase.
So I met up with you, gave you a piece of bread that I had bought.
And then we walked over Yacht and Beach Club boardwalk area.
And I was like, this is the greatest.
Yeah, the greatest place.
So I guess Yacht Beach Club actually might be my answer to Storm Along Bay is the
with the place I was trying to think of.
That's the big like themed pool area.
And you got the Cape May Seafood Buffet.
You got beaches and cream.
You got all those restaurants.
I've also never stayed like right in the middle of like the main building
and contemporary like I stayed at Bay Lake Tower once.
You know what? That's a good quote.
You know, you're making a good point.
I have maybe not stayed in that main building ever, even when I was.
I got to ask my mom.
There used to be two wings and they demolished the one to build Bay Lake
Tower and the other is still there.
That's you know what?
You're bringing up a very good point that I maybe when I was a kid, we didn't stay
in that main building and that still needs to be done at a certain point in my
vacationing. Yeah, I mean, you're right.
I like those main those main lodge design, the wilderness lodge in Grand
California, that means sort of like you come out into I don't know how much sound
travels into those rooms overlooking a giant concourse like that.
But right.
All right. So that's
those are the answers.
There's a few of them.
And now the real final question, which animatronic would you not want as your
surgeon?
Oh, as my is that real?
Are you serious? No, I just made that up.
OK, you can answer, though.
Uncle Orville, it seems like he has doesn't have the right temperament for a surgeon
to cantankerous, so right.
I'd probably get along with him personally, but I don't know if I want him slicing me
open. Yeah, I would like you know what?
My answer for this is who I do want is the probe droid on Rise to the Resistance.
Oh, yeah, he's ready to go.
He's ready to go.
He knows how to probe easily.
You can easily program him to do open heart surgery or something.
I assume that's my understanding.
Anyway,
we are over two hours here.
How about that? Oh, how about that?
Great. So I guess I guess I guess we'll call it here.
Send us more questions next when we ask for these next time.
I don't know why I'm asking.
You could send us questions whenever you want.
Yeah.
And we'll get to more mailbags.
And also, we like answer stuff on Twitter or Twitter.
So, you know,
just just hit us up at all the different social medias.
You have again survived the Jason and Mike portion of podcast, the ride.
No big announcements as far as any children we're having, but hopefully a lot
of fun and a lot of laughs follow us on all the social media, Instagram, Twitter,
Twitch, it's all podcasts, the podcast, the ride.
You know how to do it.
You're probably following already.
You know what you should do, too?
While I'm doing this is rate and review us on iTunes.
Yeah, we always forget to say that now.
We always forget.
Help us. It does help us.
I still a little bit unclear how it helps us, but supposedly it does.
So rate and review us on iTunes.
And yes, we will see you next week or next Wednesday.
If you're a Patreon subscriber.
Also, a quick plug.
We have a paywall Patreon, a lot more fun stuff we're doing over there.
You know, very special topics like the
film that plays in the Eminem store in Las Vegas, specifically in Las Vegas,
as it is Las Vegas themed.
Yes, it's specifically Las Vegas themed the video, the film.
So all fun stuff over there.
And yeah, you got anything else you want anything to plug, Jason?
No.
Any eBay auctions you'd like to plug that you're trying to win?
No, no.
OK, well, then I think we can say goodbye.
Yeah. Have a good night, everyone.
Or day or day.
Either one.
It's dark here now.
It is dark here.
This has been a ForeverDog Production, executive produced by Mike Carlson,
Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Bohm, Joe Silio and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit ForeverDogPodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple
podcasts, Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest ForeverDog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at ForeverDogTeam and liking our page on Facebook.