Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast contains possibly outdated information about public health, condiment
pipes, two of the most popular characters in fiction, Aladar and Kron, and a robust discussion
about the animal kingdom ride, Dinosaur.
Get to your time rover.
It's podcast, The Ride.
Welcome to podcast, The Ride, a theme park podcast that specialty is not time traveling,
but time wasting.
My name is Mike Carlson.
Joining me as always, Jason Sheridan.
Yeah, I'd say that's accurate.
Scott Gerdner also joining us as always.
Yeah, sometimes I feel like we've traveled several years in time and it's just been several
hours.
Exactly.
That's the magic of this podcast.
You don't know where the time went.
I also think, you know, also not knowing what time it is.
I don't know if people are hearing this still in COVID lockdown times, but ever without
I feel like some of these episodes are taking, you know, several months to get through.
Yeah, you're saying.
Depending on the listener, if you used to like have a 45 minute commute somewhere and
that's how you observed the episodes and you don't have that anymore, then yeah, you could
still you might be back on like a February episode, many, you know, in June.
Right.
It's like five minutes a day now is really all the time you have to yourself to listen
to podcasts.
Whereas before, yes, you could like rip through three podcasts in a day.
Yeah, yeah, pretty much.
So I don't.
Yeah. And if, you know, if people are too nervous to go on walks or whatever, then you
really aren't absorbing it.
So if you're if the only way you have to listen to it is like moving from the kitchen to
the bathroom, then, you know, just start doing it way more often because we need you to
get through these.
Should we get I mean, but should we maybe just make the episodes all 15 minutes long,
like rip right through it, be like, OK, this is about dinosaur.
It's a rocky ride vehicle.
I like it, but it's scary.
Jason, what do you think?
Wrapping up.
Great. Great to see Dr.
Seeker and Dr.
The other one.
OK, Scott, final thoughts.
Yeah, you know, Gwana Don's, you know, it's nice to rescue him, but that that
sort of super scary.
But at the end of the day, it's a lot of fun.
OK, well, you've survived the podcast, right?
And that's like that's about all the people have time for, honestly.
That's what we it's what we have to do.
But hey, come on, man.
You are we are you saying we're not going to take time to talk about Dr.
Seeker? Oh, man, maybe if I really think about it, I guess we have to talk about Dr.
Seeker for over 90 minutes.
We got to talk to Dr.
Seeker. Some people are still taking walks, doing that wonderful activity of jumping
into the street when some lunatic is not leaving your room on the sidewalk.
Well, especially if it's a jogger, the jogger, they've I've seen, you know, we've
all seen the articles about where the jogger leaves like a trail of germs in their
wake. Yeah, I saw someone posting from France where the mayor of Paris was like,
please stop jogging.
That has not really happened in Los Angeles, although been kind of gloomy here anyway,
so kind of scaring people inside, even besides the quarantine.
Is the way you leave it, you leave a trail of like ribbons of germs behind.
You're exhaling more.
Yeah, yeah.
You're going so fast. It's like kind of like you're almost like crop dusting with germs
because you're going so fast.
Like if you were just like walking at a normal pace and you like exhaled, it would sort
of like linger in the air a little bit and it would fall.
But since you're jogging, it's like you're it's like a water, an air and water show
with like X, like the fumes from a plane as you're like streaming down a sidewalk.
It's like going everywhere.
Again, supposedly. Jesus.
Every day is a new thing to make us paranoid.
I don't want this to be too much focused on what's going on right now.
We need to talk about dinosaur.
But I did finally see an article just now that said we don't have to, you know, pour
bleach all over our groceries and not like another definitive article, because that was
another concern we've all had is like how much we need to disinfect our groceries when
they come inside. So.
Well, yeah, that was my favorite era of it when people saw one video with one doctor
who told us that we need to like scrub each carrot.
We have to do like an hour long massage.
We have to do a bath bomb for every carrot.
And then everyone took that as as the Bible because he is a doctor after all.
So that was that was a fun couple of days living in carrot bath paranoia.
But like people need to remember, like Dr.
Drew is technically a doctor and he was saying this was no big deal for about three
months prior. So just just take everything with a grain of salt is what I'm saying.
Yeah, trust Dr. Oz, not Dr.
Drew. No, no, Dr.
Oz was saying it wasn't a big deal either.
Dr. Phil, Dr. Oz, Dr.
Feelgood. Those are the doctors to trust.
Well, we all like Dr. Feelgood.
We all like Dr. Feelgood.
Did they never steered us wrong?
Did they fully did they debunk the ibuprofen thing, too?
Wasn't that like one? Yes.
Yes. One French one French dipshit.
Like God, everyone was scared of ibuprofen.
I believe I believe the headline was French dipshit gets it wrong.
I think that's what I read.
But I repeat myself, right?
Was that a French accent?
I can't hear it very well over the zoom.
So no, no, that was just like a kind of accent.
OK, yeah, you were like like an upper crust voice you were doing.
Yeah, or like an exhausted kind of voice.
I see. Yeah.
OK, so anyway, you know, Dr.
Dr. Dre says just chill till the next episode.
And maybe that's the best doctor advice that you can take.
Yeah, I'm into that.
Yeah, it's just all chill to the next episode of life.
Yeah, I think he's right on about this.
Yeah. And obviously, I'm getting high as fuck every day of this thing.
Yeah, me too.
And what I mean by that is I have a white claw and a kombucha.
That's what I that's my that's my drug of choice.
Yeah. Two sugar drinks.
So much is different for me since the quarantine.
I don't know who you are anymore.
Yeah, I'm way different now.
I'll be changed.
Everyone will notice a change when they actually see me in person.
So anyway, I guess we should talk about dinosaur.
I guess we should.
There. Yeah, it's the ride that answers the question.
What if the Indiana Jones ride was unpleasant?
Yes, that is what it that's that is basically the mission statement for this ride.
It's interesting with dinosaur because let me let me back up.
Scott, did you go on dinosaur this when we were there?
I forget. Do we go on together or no?
No, I didn't end up doing it.
It was like I think I'm going to be facing the choice between
a fast pass for dinosaur and a nap.
And I think I chose a nap. OK.
That was our most exhausted day, if you'll recall.
And it was pretty good to me.
We got up. We went to Pandora early.
And then we did Everest.
I got you fast passes for the Kilimanjaro Safari.
You ran. Yes, you ran.
You ran a little scheme there. Appreciate it.
Tiffins. We were at Lindsay and I ate at Tiffins.
So, yeah, dinosaur dinosaur.
I have a like a complicated relationship with because like a lot of
and I'll say kids, but I really mean like, you know, 14 year olds.
I got really scared on it when I went on it the first time.
And I haven't completely gotten over it.
The trauma is still kind of there.
There's other rides that obviously I was scared on the dark rides.
I've kind of gotten over all that stuff.
But there is something about dinosaur that I'm still a little skittish about.
And I can't tell if it's just deep seeded childhood trauma.
And when I say childhood, I mean tween or teen trauma.
Or it is, as you describe it, deeply unpleasant.
Well, Mike, isn't there a photo of you from a trip in the last five years
where you look upset on this ride?
Am I remembering that correctly?
Well, I think I told the story on the show.
I had gone with a couple of friends to Orlando a year prior,
the prior year that we went.
And I went on dinosaur then.
And I was like, look, it's a ride.
You're an adult man.
You have a theme park podcast.
You're a theme park journalist.
You need to keep your eye.
Don't be scared of this.
You're an idiot if you think you're scared of this.
It's not it's it. First of all, it's a Disney ride.
Nothing's going to happen. You like haunts now.
You're a different man. You're a new man.
Everything's going to be fine.
So you went in dinosaur.
I kept my eyes open the whole time.
I was like, you know what? This is fine.
This is a ride.
I can enjoy it like any other ride.
And then when the picture opportunity happened, when the photo spot happened,
I think it's when the carna tour.
Is that what is it? Carnotaurus?
Carnotaurus. Carnotaurus.
Yes, I wrote that down phonetically.
I'm going to apologize because I will probably mispronounce some dinosaur names.
Yeah. Oh, yeah, I will.
I will for sure as well.
Tyrannosaurus. That's how you say it. Right. Yeah.
Nailed it.
And when the picture opportunity happened, apparently,
and I didn't even realize it, I turned away.
I turned away like I was scared.
So I thought I was being brave, but the picture said otherwise.
Well, but it is a scare at the end, right?
It's the it's the picture happens when the carnitourist is like right above you.
I believe it's right before that. OK.
I believe it's right before that.
But still, I humiliating myself again on this ride in my 30s.
I felt I had done a good, very good job of being comfortable on it.
But there there the proof was that there's still something
that's bothering me about the ride.
So I don't know.
You might just have like you might just have resting frightened face
because when we all went on the Knott's rapid ride together,
I was taking video of it in every frame that I saw.
You did you? I guess you didn't look terrified.
You just looked like actually you looked like you smelled something horrible.
It's right. Like every single frame where you were on camera.
So that just might.
And I know you weren't scared of the rapids ride.
I do know that's the rapids ride.
No. Yes. Yeah.
I that communicated to me.
But that just might be how you look on rides.
I don't know. You're you're a little squinty or a little like, you know.
Look, thank you for saying that because you're trying to get me off the hook here,
because I do grimace a lot.
I think I have like resting grimace face.
That's a good word. Rest in grimace.
Not not McDonald Land grimace, just a normal grimace.
But I have resting McDonald Land grimace.
I have resting like I got to get a shake.
Thank you, Jason. Thank you for making that joke.
So no one else had to, you know.
I feel better if I make it.
Yeah, yeah. Get ahead of it.
Yeah. Shows you have a sense of humor.
Sure. We can all laugh together.
We can all we're having a lot of fun.
Uh, so, yes, I was going to say thank you, Scott, for saying that.
But if you look at this picture, the picture,
I don't even have like a grimace on my face.
I have my head is turned away.
I am physically like recoiling from whatever robot is like coming out at me.
Do you have the can you remind us of what this photo looks like?
I don't have I have it.
Let me OK, I'll find it while we're talking here.
I think that'll take a minute.
I apologize. Posted it to the Twitter.
If somebody else wants to give their feeling about when they first went on
dinosaur countdown to extinction.
Yeah. Well, maybe maybe we should do the little
the the cliff notes of what it is for anybody who doesn't know off hand.
We haven't been animal king.
So it's it's it's in Disney's animal kingdom in Florida.
It is an opening day attraction.
It uses the same very similar ride vehicle and mechanism to the Indiana Jones
adventure, that being sort of the the simulator on a moving track, essentially.
Like it's you're you're on wheels, but it's simulating a little bit more
movement, and I think it may even be the same literal track layout.
It is of the Indiana Jones adventure. Yeah.
OK, yeah, it's the same.
The term is enhanced motion vehicles, which Imagineering developed
and was used for Indiana Jones in Anaheim, Indiana Jones at Disney, see dinosaur.
And. That's it.
It weird.
Well, it must be expensive as hell, but or else they would have done it more.
It's like such a like revelatory, amazing type of ride vehicle,
but it's got to be super cost prohibitive.
Yeah, I believe the estimated cost for this ride is
is it between 40 and 60 million?
I had it somewhere in my notes.
Yeah, I think I saw that number that was similar to that.
Yeah, I mean, it is very expensive,
but it was put in this it was done here for cost reasons to save money.
Yeah. By repeating the same track, basic track layout and ride vehicle.
It seems like.
I guess to use the same blueprints.
Yeah, has got to save him something.
The the apocryphal story is that as they were building Animal Kingdom,
they discovered that taking care of this many wild animals is expensive.
So they needed to cut costs.
And at some point, it came down between Dino Land USA
and Beasley Kingdom and Dino Land USA.
Those those imagineering those imagineers more willing to
cut costs and merge to attractions and and kind of skimp and save a little.
And a lot of the Beasley Kingdom imagineers
went on to move, shift over to Universal
and put a lot of their mythical ideas into the lost continent.
Yeah, there's a good there's a YouTube video.
I think it's theme park history that I watched.
Did you watch that too, Jason?
I watched that. Yeah, that video is great.
They had a really thorough examination of the ride and the many changes of the ride.
He yes, he posits that the Dino Land USA people were more willing to compromise
than the Beasley Kingdom people.
There was going to be two rides.
There were going to be two dinosaur rides,
and they were willing to combine them into one ride.
And basically just use the same Indiana Jones track layout and vehicle.
So they got their stuff built.
They won. And Jurassic Park also was a big part of why Dino Land won,
because, you know, dinosaurs were all the rage.
Jurassic Park and also at the time,
Disney had entered into a 10 year partnership with McDonald's.
And when Dino Land USA first opened, the McDonald's logo
and references were just fucking everywhere in this part of the park.
Yeah. So yeah, even in the line for this ride, there are red,
yellow and white pipes that are supposedly meant to remind you of ketchup,
mustard and mayonnaise.
They have a chemical formula for each item on it.
Whoa. Yeah.
Even even further than I thought. Wow. Yeah.
Yes. I don't I don't know the logic behind that.
I don't know why in like a museum or like whatever.
I guess we're in a museum sort of in an institute.
There would be a need for pipes that shot ketchup, mustard and mayonnaise.
But there are.
I think museum workers are loving it.
Ba ba ba ba ba. You know, they got to eat.
They need a quick lunch.
They need a quick, reliable lunch like anyone.
Yeah. I have you look, Jason, have you looked into installing these type of pipes?
Like what would the with the city of Los Angeles be willing to?
You know, three different colored pipes in, you know, I would love it.
But yeah, the contractors, it's such a pain in the ass.
Find it a good contractor in Los Angeles.
You don't want to skimp on a task rabbit sort of thing for ketchup,
mustard, mayo pipes. Yeah.
You want a real pro.
If any of the listeners have recommendations for a plumber
that can install ketchup, mustard and mayonnaise pipes, let us know.
Yeah, because, you know, we I would be honestly, I'd be interested in it, too,
because who doesn't like those three condiments?
I know some people don't like mayonnaise, but I think that's crazy.
Many times, I think the question is, do you have that installed
just next to a water faucet?
Is it is it a kitchen thing or do you
is it is it a shower thing?
Do you want to get bathed in these items? Huh?
Well, I mean, at least if you put it in the shower,
that gives you the option to be bathed in ketchup, mustard and mayonnaise.
So it's always nice to have the option.
Obviously, you can take a hot dog into the shower with you.
But yeah, you can't you can't have a bath in the sink if you do it there.
So I would I would advocate you put it by the shower, at least in or in the shower.
Yeah.
It running through pipes also implies that you have the option
of hot and cold running mayonnaise.
Oh, that's interesting.
You can you can really warm it up if you want.
You can get blasted every morning with gallons of hot mayonnaise.
Jason, Jason, the mayonnaise bill is through the roof this month.
Oh, come on.
You've got to cut down on it.
It was cold this month.
The you're running through hot mayonnaise heaters.
You're the there.
The repairman has been out to fix the hot mayonnaise heater three times this month.
Well, he should have done a better job fixing it the first time.
I'm like I'm like a like a rolling pin wielding wife in this scenario.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
What are you doing, Jason?
The economy's hard right now, and we're going to hand all our money
over to the DWKM.
M.P.
Jason, real quick, what is your mayonnaise brand?
It's back east.
It's called Hellman's and on the West Coast, it's called Best Foods.
It's one of those Mississippi, the Mississippi dividing lines once.
You mean you mean basic, basic is what you're saying.
Basic mayonnaise. Yeah.
OK, I don't I don't actually don't have any mayonnaise in the apartment,
but I do like mayonnaise. Yeah.
I have OK, so I have sent the photo to you of me cowering next to a child,
by the way, who is looking at the dinosaur.
I am not I am my head is down to the left.
And I am like cringing.
It's one of the most humiliating photos of my adult life.
You're trying to like turtle into yourself.
You're trying to shrink down.
I don't I also don't have a memory of doing this.
I I have a memory of of being on the ride and everything going well.
And I enjoying the ride for the most part.
And then I see this photo.
And apparently that was all just a fantasy I made up in my head.
I must have like blacked out during the ride and had a dream
that I comfortably went on dinosaur and enjoyed it.
But I really look like this most of the time.
You were smiling with a pipe in hand.
You were like a little golf clap.
Good show, Carnotaurus.
Yes. Like just like chuckling.
Ah, look at that. A pterodactyl.
Ah, very enjoyable.
Perhaps the children on board might be frightened,
but I, an adult, educated man, am perfectly fine.
The children. Yeah.
The children on board all seem a little surprised, but also delighted.
Your friend, Luke, sitting next to you is overjoyed at this.
Of course, everyone is.
I would like to point your attention to to the family right behind you
appears to have custom Mickey avatar shirts on.
Oh, that's a mom and dad.
A mom and dad look like Navi, but also has some Mickey ears in there.
Very fun.
And then like there's a kid in the front row, a little kid in the front row,
and his mom is pointing out like, look at that.
And he's like looking at it. He doesn't seem scared.
She's just trying to be like, look at that. Isn't that cool?
Meanwhile, there's only one asshole in the car who's looking away in terror.
Yeah. And if any of them bought this photo, they've made fun of you ever since.
This is if OK, if they all have like photo pass
and have the photo, this is a photo they will make jokes about me for generations.
This will get passed down in the family.
And let's be like, remember that wonderful trip we took to Walt Disney World?
And remember that adult man who couldn't handle a robot dinosaur that was 20 feet away?
Like this is someday the little boy in the front will be telling his little boy,
I want you to be strong and brave and nothing like this pink hoodie guy
from our 2018 trip to Disney World.
Look at him. He's in his mid 30s.
We can tell how old he is just because he dresses like a child doesn't mean he's a child.
He's an adult man.
You know, I'll say I I rode this ride.
I think I would have ridden it opening summer in 1998
back when it was called Countdown to Extinction.
And I liked it.
I mean, we didn't have Indiana Jones on the East Coast.
So this is my first experience with this type of ride vehicle.
And I remember being delighted by this ride, especially because I think it's
the most traditional kind of thrill ride attraction
in the original Animal Kingdom, Opening Day Animal Kingdom Park.
I think I bought a little time rover and had a nice time.
But as the years have gone on, it's kind of sticking out that they need to do
some work on these dinosaurs and that this ride is very dark inside.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Visibility is kind of the issue more than anything.
And yeah, I think they've let you know, we're all everybody's mad about the
the Yeti and Expedition Everest.
But I think there's a lot of smaller animatronics in this attraction
that are not working on the regular.
Yeah. Look, I guess I I'm not the one to tell you I saw this stuff firsthand,
because obviously, who knows what my eyes were doing.
But from the videos I was watching today,
yes, I think there's a couple of them that could be refurbished.
But the darkness does hide, you know, some of the flaws,
unlike that opening scene from the Jurassic Park ride,
where, like, you know, you would see the dinosaur skin just hanging off of its neck.
Yeah. And like the sun damage was was too great to not notice.
They might be real fucked up if you put a light on them.
So maybe light isn't the answer. Yeah.
Scott, what did you have you been on this ride?
Yeah, I did this.
I've done it a couple of times.
Yeah, I must have done it around ninety nine.
And it might have still been countdown to extinction.
I don't I don't recall.
I think my reaction was I thought this was going to be the major breathtaking.
Like, that's that's the killer ride in Animal Kingdom.
And that was kind of my reaction even then, because I I was lucky enough
to have been on the Indiana Jones adventure by then.
So I was like, I was so excited about realizing, oh, it's kind of a similar thing.
And yeah, I felt kind of let down just because it is more
a it's what I said at the top.
It's it's just more unpleasant to me.
It's it's it's a lot of loud noises.
Is there not a score?
There not a music score running through it?
I don't believe so.
No, just that's kind of weird to me.
Just dinosaurs and like the meteor crashing sounds, which they
and they they did turn down like we're we're listening to the team down version
since 2000.
Yeah. Oh, you're in, you know, in terms of filling in info,
that's probably the other thing to say.
So this is I mean, the basis of the attraction is that you're being
beamed back in time and kind of an all terrain vehicle.
And you were taken back to a little too close before the comets all started
landing that caused the extinction of the dinosaurs.
That's why the ride was originally called Countdown to Extinction.
But in a bizarre, not bizarre, just kind of a confusing
cross promotional move.
This ride sort of was reflective of the upcoming film
Dinosaur was released in 2000.
And then they just went all the way full tilt with it and made it
a complete tie in to the movie Dinosaur.
And it's been named Dinosaur ever since.
I, for one, kind of prefer the title Countdown to Extinction.
I find that a little cooler.
It's definitely a better title.
The development is so confusing because it seems like Michael Eisner said,
all right, imagineering and animation work together to make these dinosaurs
coherent with both your projects.
So there is an Iguanodon and there is a Carnot
Carnotaurus, which was recently discovered at the time.
They they work that real life discovery in
to the movie and the ride.
But they called it something different for two years.
And then when the movie actually came out, yeah, like you said,
they changed it to Dinosaur.
So still trying to figure out the cross
inner company, get synergy there, kind of odd.
The synergy, I think, was getting a little out of hand because
elsewhere in Animal Kingdom, you had it's tough to be a bug,
which slightly predated a bug's life.
And in both cases, they don't totally reflect the movie.
Like there's so many bugs in it's tough to be a bug who are not in a bug's life.
And this is really strange where it's a trip back into the world of the dinosaurs,
which the movie Dinosaur takes place entirely in the dinosaur world.
And there certainly is no mischievous doctor
trying to have you bring a dinosaur back for his personal gain.
There's no time travel element in dinosaur.
There's no humans in it.
So and not all of the dinosaurs.
In fact, they aren't at all like the dinosaurs for the most part in dinosaur,
because mainly the dinosaurs in dinosaur talks.
And there's some real logic flaws once they switched it to dinosaur.
So you're going back as a meteor shower is happening and you spoiler alert.
You do happen to rescue the Iguanodon in the ride.
But does the logic then follows if this takes place after the movie dinosaur?
Everyone else in that movie has died in the meteor shower,
except the protagonist, who we all know is Aladar.
Aladar. Of course, it's Aladar.
Of course it's Aladar.
Or the other option is that in the movie Dinosaur, there is a brief meteor shower
early in the movie, and that's when they have to flee the island
that they first you first meet a lot of the characters on.
So then if you're rescuing Aladar at that point,
then the events of the movie don't occur.
Hmm. I didn't think about that.
Oh, weird. So that might.
So either this is the extinction of the dinosaurs and you have removed
this character saving him, which he would have died.
But his entire family and everyone he knows and loves is dead in the process.
Or that this is what we're seeing is the
the bombing of Lemur Island.
Yep. You got it.
OK, I think I'm caught up then.
Bombing is not the right word, but I mean, sort of bombing
bombs from the from nature, nature bombs, bombs, bombs,
bombs from heaven.
That's what I call asteroids.
Yes. From heaven, Jason is called.
They were sent by God.
Yes. The lemurs had sinned and only only God bombs could make it right.
This seems like I was this sort of reminded me of the story about Michael Eisner
wanting to have the Darrell Hannah splash, have something to do.
Movie Splash have something to do with Splash Mountain.
Like that was sort of he's always tried to do sort of like a synergistic thing
with rides. And here he kind of got his wish.
And he did not with Splash and Splash Mountain.
Because people like maybe in the 80s, there were people there
like Tony Baxter, who predated him and they weren't scared of him.
And they would tell him an idea was stupid.
But by this point, maybe it's all people who've only lived in Eisner world.
So they feel like they can't say no to him.
Yeah, maybe he yes, he maybe it was like it was obviously it felt like a different
time from what we've heard from, you know, imagineering interviews and stuff.
People like the 80s felt like in the early 90s felt like very collaborative.
And there was a whole everyone.
It was a team of rivals, but everybody was getting things done.
And then by the end of Eisner's tenure, it just seemed like everyone had had the wind
knocked out of them. The bubble had been deflated.
And maybe it was just like, all right, well, we'll figure out how to make this ride
tie in with Aladar, the dinosaur from the movie Dinosaurs.
It's not a random Magwana Dawn anymore.
It's Aladar. It's very clearly Aladar.
I guess you have to rescue Aladar now.
But like you're bringing him, you're bringing him into the future for like tests.
It's not even like he's I guess he's being rescued, but like at what cost?
Why does he want to live here in this time?
The mad scientist who is trying to get a hold of this iguana
dawn is putting countless people's lives at risk for scientific notoriety
for for the sake of getting a hold of Aladar.
Yes, I wish he was.
I wish he was Aladar.
I wish you had the name.
Yeah, that would clear it up.
But I think they only filmed the actor
before the movie before they had made this decision.
So, yeah, it's a it's a tie into a movie, but no characters are named.
Right. You see a little CGI clip of Aladar in the pre show.
But yeah, he doesn't see Dr.
Seeker does not say Aladar, so it's very confusing in the pre show.
He so so this day, yeah, this doctor, Dr.
Seeker lets you know that he wants you to go back in time
and bring back this particular iguanodon.
It's this one here. I'll show you.
And he brings up like security cam footage.
But the security cam footage is clearly finished shots from the movie
dinosaur. So it's you.
You're thinking you're going to go get like, you know, anatomically correct
dinosaur, but instead you're showing a dinosaur who's like doe eyed.
You know, he's like conveying emotion, which is very jarring,
especially then when you go to the dinosaur world and it's just a lot of like,
it's just a lot of like roaring, you know, no brain cells
dinosaurs who can't show you that they're like pensive.
Right. They can't like they can't win you over with their cuteness
like Aladar can a dinosaur who I would assume most
younger people would know now from there is I don't even it's
it might be too old even for people to know it as a meme.
But there's a screen, a grainy screen grab of Aladar looking like he's going,
uh, that I see every now and then it's like a reaction photo.
Oh, like a gym.
Like, yeah, like a GIF or even just a J.
But let me see if I can find out, see if I can find it and send it to you guys.
Saying, uh, like, like his mouth is just kind of open and he looks a little.
Yeah, his mouth is just kind of gape.
He just looks a little slack jawed.
Hmm. I'm looking at a get a GIF here of a baby.
I don't know if it's baby Aladar, just a different baby dinosaur
sneezing and, uh, I don't know.
I don't even want to send it to you guys because I think you're going to.
I think you'll love it in some perverse baby Grinch way.
Oh, that's how awful I find it that I feel like it's guaranteed.
Oh, yeah. Give me that.
My mouth is watering for this.
Well, just look for dinosaur Aladar GIF.
Dinosaur Aladar GIF Aladar GIF.
Don't look at the one of Playa.
It's not Playa. It's Alad.
It's I think it's baby Aladar.
Oh, OK. He oh, I see this.
Oh, yeah. Oh, he sneezed. Oh, yeah. I love this.
No, you don't. Yes, I do.
You're being contrarian. I'm not. No one would like this.
I often. I don't you like this.
I don't know when this episode is coming out versus Patreon's,
but there's a couple of characters I've said I hated recently,
and I think that makes it clear that I am not biased.
I like. Yeah.
But if I bring it up and say I don't like it,
then you immediately say you like it.
Well, next. OK. Look, the next time this type of thing happens,
you have to go in neutral to prove so I can prove that I'm being unbiased here,
that I do like baby Aladar sneezing.
Let's see. Audience will also decide.
Let's post this.
The baby grinch, very decisive divisive baby Aladar,
I think going to be less divisive.
I don't know why I can't talk right now.
No, this isn't good.
Mike, can you say we might be worse?
Can you send me Aladar?
I will send you avatar avatar.
Baby avatar.
You know, it's funny you say that because obviously we all know
the voice of Aladar is one of our favorite actors.
Let's all say it together.
D.B. Sweeney, Sweeney, yes.
And D.B. Sweeney is Aladar.
And he's also Avatar Ang in The Legend of Korra,
the sequel to Avatar, The Last Airbender, which is not James Cameron's Avatar,
which has Dr. Augustine, who is not Dr. Ogden.
Right. Keep that straight, everyone.
So but D.B. Sweeney is Aladar and Avatar Ang.
D.B. Sweeney is Al.
What is he?
He's not Avatar Ang.
He's Aladar and Avatar Ang.
It's just Ang. It's just Ang.
Avatar is the name of the show.
No, no, no. I'm looking at it.
I clicked on a Wikipedia where he's still I think it's acceptable to call him Avatar Ang.
Wow. I think.
I mean, you know, we were both right.
I watched I watched some of the first I even watched any of the sequel
that the Legend of Korra where they're older.
But yeah, I remember a little of the show.
Jason on the Wikipedia, he's he goes back and forth.
Yeah. Sometimes he is Avatar Ang's every Avatar Ang and sometimes he's just saying,
I've sent you the GIF, Jason. I love it.
I love it. Yes, of course.
No, you don't. Why?
This is not cute. No, it's not.
He is cute. Why?
I think this is so he's a little cutie.
Jason's right. This is this is horrifying.
Late 90s CGI.
No one would if you saw this on your own, you would think this was bad.
I don't. But everyone's taking a stance.
You're all against me. That's what's happening.
Nothing to do with it.
Has nothing to do with it.
I think the next is going to overwhelmingly like baby Aladar. Jesus.
I bet over 75% will vote yes on baby Aladar.
I can't say that I don't like anything
because everyone will get in lockstep.
I didn't like Fuzzbucket.
Oh, well, all right, that's true.
But I think if I said I did, if I came out first and said I didn't like Fuzzbucket,
where would we be then?
I think I would have completely agreed.
Fuzzbucket is so unpleasant.
He's such a little turd.
I do not like him.
Go to our Patreon if you want to listen to us talk about the
Disney Channel movie.
No. Or was it ABC?
I think it was on ABC.
Yeah. OK.
It's about an unpleasant little character who kind of grifts a little boy.
That's the best way.
Yeah. And I don't remember the lines anymore is I've tried to force them out of my brain.
But it's like, you know, he says things like, hey, fun boy.
Kissy. Right.
Doesn't he demand kissy?
Right. Doesn't he demand kisses at one point?
Give me give me kissy right, fun boy.
Kissy. What's he says?
Something like, what's going on, party boy?
Oh, it's even worse.
And then he's like, then the little boy's like, because Fuzzbucket, like, is just using
the little boy and he's like, don't you like me?
And he's like, oh, yeah, I do.
I swear. Yeah, yeah, sure.
I do. That's right.
And he's so like, he's not cute.
He's unpleasant.
Is all of his friends.
Doesn't he have a friend named Stinky or something?
Yeah, he sure does.
Jason. I think Jason is the one on record that said he like Jason like Stinky.
I like Stinky. Yeah.
Yeah. But I don't even like Stinky.
I won't go on record as saying I enjoy Stinky from Fuzzbucket.
I think I'm looking at a different
different gif now that is baby Aladar either peeing or pooping.
Oh, my God. Send that over here.
Send that our way. Yeah.
I have to I'm going to send this of him sneezing just to make sure,
because I are you talking about the same gif?
No, no, no. This one is no.
This one is Tim Gagling or something.
I'm sending it over right now to you.
And I'm going to see if we're talking about the same thing,
because again, Jason and I are looking at this and we we say this is cute.
And I am sending to you with the email subject line piss.
OK, I will be very honest if I like baby Aladar going to the bathroom.
I'll be very honest.
There's there's a lot of fun dinosaur content.
Oh, yeah. This came up even bigger this time, Mike.
I can see this is a sneeze. This is different.
I'm sending you what I think is pooping or peeing.
All right. This is I don't OK. I don't like them.
Well, while you guys are OK.
Oh, hold on. While you're starting this out.
Let's see.
I think Scott is right.
This this baby Aladar is pissing or shitting right now.
I'm looking at him.
I think this is I think this is cute, honestly.
This is also cute. This might be cuter.
Why is it? Tell me why it is not because it's making a funny little face.
It's a little baby dinosaur guy.
He's just a little guy.
He's a little guy who's way too shiny and doesn't match his own background.
And a dinosaur would not be this expressive.
And yet he's also a dead eyed Zemeckis type creature.
Nothing about this is good.
This looks better than adult Aladar in the movie.
I might agree with that. Yes.
Should we should I like text Lindsey? She's downstairs.
Should I text her and say, do you think this is cute? Yeah.
Yeah, sure. Yes. OK. Send her both because I really both.
I'm I I don't think I'm trolling here.
I really don't.
I think this is cute.
This might just convey different taste or something.
Maybe I'll do the same to Aaron.
Sorry, listeners, that this has just become us sending files around.
No, no, I think they're I think they're gripped by this drama of who likes
the baby Aladar shitting or sneezing.
I have some I wanted to get your guys's feedback.
So did you guys come across, you know, we talked about the McDonald's
sponsorship.
Did you come across the posters of hand drawn
dinosaurs that say like food fangs and fun?
And did someone say styrakosaurus?
And have you had a crocodilian today
and it's one dinosaur eating another dinosaur?
No, I've seen none of this.
I saw. Yes, I have that right here.
And that is really terrifying.
It is a pretty detailed drawing of a dinosaur eating a crocodile.
Head first. Yeah.
Here, I'll send this to Scott. I have this.
Yeah, I am very shocked that this would even be in a Disney park.
I mean, it feels like something that would be like leftover from like the 60s
or something where you're like, well, it's been grandfathered in
because of how terrifying it is.
But yeah, yeah, it's it's a cool drawing, by the way.
Food fangs and fun.
The dinosaur McDonald's tie together in general is very bizarre.
I don't know why these properties are matched.
They are not is the answer.
They just McDonald's was looking to give them money and they gave them dinosaur.
Yeah, I think they had to fit it in where they could
because like it was you could get
like McDonald's food at the restaurant, a source.
Yeah, which is still there.
It just does not serve McDonald's food.
I when we when Lindsay and I were there a couple of years ago,
there was a very nice, quirky, older fellow who had a dinosaur puppet
who wouldn't leave people alone with it, who worked there.
They did work there. You're sure he worked there.
He at least had an outfit that resembled a Disney employees outfit.
I assume I think he took a tray or two, too, although none of that
really confirms that he worked there. Yeah, exactly.
Guys, the weird speckles on these posters make it seem like
the dinosaurs are surrounded by locusts or germs, honestly.
I mean, that's what's in my head at this point. Yes.
I mean, that should have been the warning that God was going to unleash upon them.
His his un un-mighty is almighty wrath.
You know, they were war. I do know.
I think we might all be screwed in this current scenario,
unless some other doctor and some other species
right before our extinction wants one of us in particular.
Like if some other species Dr.
Seeker in a thousand years wants Jason
and then some truck shows up and grabs him before the virus gets us all. Mm hmm.
That's the only hope any of us have.
I have a question.
Will future Dr.
Seeker be explaining his plan in glorious four by three aspect ratio?
Because this is no this ride pre show is notable for still having
standard depth footage.
Never a film cut of this film cut.
So it's time travel in that regard.
You're first you time travel to 1998, then you travel to the Cretaceous.
By the way, to follow up on the on earlier and might keep me updated.
But I texted Aaron, she walked in the room and said a very definitive no.
So we might just be getting different.
This is the different tastes of the unified Gardner's.
Aaron, who had no idea what we were talking about.
And I guess everyone else, I guess it's us against the world.
Hey, I'm waiting for Lindsey to respond.
She is downstairs playing Animal Crossing, which is become her addiction.
In quarantine time.
Yeah, you tweeted about this.
Oh, no, it is.
The hours are staggering, I'll be honest.
Like, I feel like I'm like my parents from like when I was like,
you really have to you're going to keep playing, huh?
OK. Huh.
It's made Twitter extremely confounding to me, not playing Animal Crossing.
I don't know what 85 percent of it is anymore.
All right. OK. Lindsey has weighed in.
She I said, I said the two GIFs, I said, do you think baby
Aladar is cute? And she wrote, yes, exclamation point. Boy. Wow.
Well, we hey, we find who we're meant to be with, I guess. Yeah.
Guys, I'm going to break the tie.
I texted them to my girlfriend and she also says very cute.
So very, very Lindsey.
Lindsey added a very cute to the text right before Jason said that.
And she came here. You're talking about.
Yes. Very cute.
Yes. I think we're getting I think over 75 percent of the listeners will agree.
I don't understand.
Why is that very cute?
He is that the mouth. It's a horrifying mouth.
It is like weird CGI rubber.
This is not good.
I don't know. Again, I don't think we're trolling here.
I don't think there's a well.
I mean, yes, this this test, the wife and girlfriend test is a
is a good litmus, but I don't understand.
I don't understand where anyone's coming from.
Lindsey is also now texted who the F is Aladar.
A very good follow up question.
Hey, maybe we should explain a little bit and we should talk about the 2000 film
don't say Aladar
that the 2000 film dinosaur.
This is a movie that everyone can revisit now if they have Disney Plus.
And I'm sure that very few people have.
I've never been able to stand this entire film.
And it is a movie that perhaps notably combined
real backgrounds, real nature backgrounds with CGI
dinosaur characters, which I'm sure made it the dullest film ever to shoot in history.
That sounds so boring.
They just had to go film plates for a long time.
And it's all very disappointing because the weird history of this movie,
where this was in its original development, was supposed to be a vehicle for Paul
Verhoeven with that, which is so great.
I lost my mind when I saw that fact.
I could just imagine Paul Verhoeven, 90s
Paul Verhoeven making a CGI brutalist dinosaur film.
That would have been awesome.
Yes. This is what he has explained in every interview
that it was going to be just really gory and fucked up
and just about like the the the pointlessness of of life.
I get not the point of this, but like, you know, the why flail against a death
that is coming no matter what it's going to be really severe.
And it just like end with extinction.
And that's that's it.
That's the end of them, which is kind of the end of the ride.
I guess that's that stayed unified.
Yeah. I you know, this ride kind of like is
is an interesting little special feature for the movie dinosaur,
because it regardless of the events of the movie, it reminds you, yes, that death.
Death comes for all of us.
I guess that's kind of a little special feature on all Disney movies.
Eventually, these characters will die.
And yeah, whether we keep in mind, yeah,
but only dinosaur had the guts to say only the dinosaur had the guts to say it.
By the way, guys, I pulled it up on Disney Plus on the app and under extras.
Look what I just said.
You look. Look what the only extra is.
There's a little clip.
There's a little.
It's maybe it's maybe.
Oh, no, no, no.
It's our friend.
What's that tired, tired, baby Grinch wired baby Aladar?
What's that? What's that?
I smell wafting through the air.
Why, I think I smell a little content coming our way.
No, please, no.
Ever since everyone spend this time connecting with your family,
zoom with your family and don't send us shit.
Just doesn't you think there's there's enough stuff in the like lore of podcasts
to ride to annoy Scott with?
We stumble upon baby Aladar.
How have I amassed a fan base that loves
only things that I find extremely abhorrent and unpleasant?
I mean, do I want like should there be a Photoshop of Randy Gerber
holding baby Aladar?
You know the answer.
Yes. Wow.
Now I can.
Now I hear a rumbling in the distance, a voice,
a cacophony of voices all at once yelling plus us up, plus us up.
No, no, no, no.
I'm not watching.
Hell, no, no dinosaur.
This is bad enough as it is.
Didn't we learn anything from our last plus us up?
Patreon exclusive dinosaur watch alone.
Please know, Aladar, Aladar.
I have hated the idea of this film.
I can't even stand watching short clips.
This is such an unpleasant movie.
Let me look up Aladar.
I'm going to look up Aladar plush.
When I was 15, I'd see trailers for this on TV with him saying, stand together.
I'm like, what is this move?
I don't ever want to see what this is.
Why would anyone like that?
This ugly gray dinosaur yelling stand together.
I see any other movie.
I'll go see what's that bad like,
you know, Jack Black, Steve Zahn movie from around that time.
Much rather see that narrows it down.
That man, early animal kingdom had tie ins for Bugslife, Tarzan and the dinosaur.
What a time.
Jesus. Oh, terrible time.
I'm looking I cannot find any baby Aladar merch.
I think it's all regular Aladar adult Aladar, who I don't find near.
I'm not as attached to him now like I am to his baby self.
I see only baby.
Well, yeah, it was all downhill from then, I guess.
Yeah.
I see some other things about the movie dinosaur,
not the not the boring movie that I assume that they like.
At every turn, they denied things that could have made it cooler.
I should say specifically that not only was it going to be Verhoeven,
it was going to be a collaboration between Paul Verhoeven and Phil Tippett,
who did the Ed 209 sequence and Robocop.
So like that crazy, gory sequence as an entire dinosaur film.
So cool. And it didn't happen, doesn't even like any of that.
And then it sat on a shelf for a long time.
The only thing that stayed consistent is that there's a character named Suri.
Like in the in the Verhoeven version, there was going to be a Suri
that was ultimately played by Hayden Panetti.
So there is. Oh, that's oh, and that's a lemur.
But also there were going to be real lemurs in the movie
because there were lemurs in the time of dinosaurs and there's lemurs now.
So they were going to round up real lemurs to interact with puppets.
Whoa. Cool. Yeah, that sounds really cool.
And then but obviously none of that happened.
And instead, they made this boring thing with this not good baby.
And not only that, they said there was a full song
written and performed by Kate Bush called Out of the Storm.
And preview audiences didn't like it.
And the producers asked Bush to do rewrites and she refused.
So there was they they also denied Kate Bush.
Although I will say that then she reworked the song.
And it is a song called Lyra in the movie The Golden Compass.
And I checked it out and I'm not so much a fan of the song Lyra
from The Golden Compass, but nonetheless,
it feels like Kate Bush contribution would have made this movie
a little more interesting.
I agree with that.
I just started listening to some of the classic Kate Bush albums.
I was I never really got I just never came across my desk,
but I have been listening to Hounds of Love and it is good.
So, yeah, I'm sort of I'm kind of a latecomer with her a little bit.
Yeah, a little bit. I know it's almost
too heavy to listen to.
Like it's all like dove in a little and then I'm like, I can't
and handle this more.
I'm so way too many feelings. Yeah.
She's good, you know, much like staring at a photo of baby Aladar.
But I have I just have a limit.
Now, hold on. What if I were to tell you that the Iguanodon
with the one we are to assume is Aladar in the ride?
The main time you see him in the ride, he is holding up a tree
to help you escape.
And he's also screaming.
Pretty cool.
And it is but in TV Sweeney's voice or just like a roar,
just a just a painful scream, like a high pitch
as if he's watching everything he knows.
Burn up from God bombs.
What a strange ride.
Watch characters suffer.
Yeah. Wallace Langham has a ticket for you to see your friends
go through hell like if Midway Mania ended with the scene from Toy Story 3
where they're all in the incinerator.
Like and then and then only one of the toys made it out.
Only Ham makes it out. Yeah.
Only Ham survives the incinerator at the end of Midway Mania.
Bad news, troops.
Your poor slingshotting is doomed all the characters to die.
Oh, man.
Yeah, this is the most bizarre, honestly perverse, perverse ride.
You know, we talked about when the ride,
the first two years of the ride when it was countdown to extinction
were a little different when they switched it over to dinosaur in 2000.
They did make some changes.
One, they dropped the height, the height requirement.
Got a little shorter.
The vehicles got a little less jerky and the sounds a little less sinister.
It was more so.
Oh, my God. It was jerky and louder.
And I guess they were playing the sound of like stomping
as if like the dinosaur was right behind you.
And the ending was a big change, like the ending.
It looked like you were about to be hit by an asteroid.
And then you threw a quote laser net over
the Iguana Don, and that's how he gets back.
Now talking about a laser laser that specifically laser that it was a laser
net, and now there's a big, big carna car.
I can't remember how to say this.
Carnotaurus, a big carnotaurus pops out at the end,
and you just kind of like happen to get the Iguana Don in your field.
Yeah, they tell you, you got it.
You got it. And of course, unlike Indiana Jones, where you actually see
an Indiana Jones animatronic at the end, you do not see one last
Iguana Don animatronic.
You see video footage of CGI Iguana Don wandering around like
facility hallways, empty hallways.
On standard.
He's stuck in a he's stuck in a laboratory.
For once he was screaming because his friends are dying.
And now he's stuck.
Now he's in a time that he doesn't understand.
He doesn't know what a wall is, much less a computer.
Similar to like Biff running around the Institute of Future Technology.
On the Back to the Future ride.
Except it's a dinosaur.
Much scarier for him.
He's he's like, you know, he's like what?
He's like 17 tops, right?
He's still pretty young.
Yes, yes, very young.
The theme park history video said that there was going to be
maybe a Pepper's ghost effect to actually make it look like
the dinosaur was like with you or coming back through time,
which would have given a little bit more of a suggestion of what happened
as opposed to just like, oh, yeah, and we got the dinosaur.
It worked.
Now he gets to live in a laboratory.
Yeah, yes.
Or he escaped and like it was a lost world scenario
where he like ravages a town.
That's probably what's coming.
Yeah, he's going to like he's going to run through everything in Dino land USA.
I would love Dr.
Marsh and Dr. Seeker to chase the Iguana Don in a Cadillac.
In a top down Cadillac.
They also swapped out the statue in the fountain out front.
Used to be a Styracosaurus.
And then when they switched it to dinosaur, they put
an Iguana Don that in theory is Aladar in the fountain.
And they put a bunch of landscaping around it because some blogs,
some blogs were saying that the original fountain with no barriers,
people would just climb into the fountain to stand next to the dinosaur
or like splash around.
So, yes, I said I saw that.
Animal Kingdom, famously a very hot park, very extra warm.
The day we were there was the hottest day we were we were there.
Used to be a lot less inside attractions there,
but even still with with the foliage grown in after 20 plus years,
still a very warm park.
Yes, it's just a giant sauna.
It's the world's biggest sauna.
Yeah, that's why I napped instead of going to see Aladar.
Yeah, I mean, it is a cool.
This is one of the places, you know, you can get out of the sun
because it's all indoors.
So that's a good thing about it.
Right, a more traditional thrill ride.
Did you guys you can get some AC and why and hear characters scream,
bombs dropping, lightning strikes
and a very screechy radio with the voice of Wallace Langham.
Yeah. What could you not love about that?
And and the robot voice identifying dinosaurs.
I think if I was a dinosaur, a big dinosaur kid and hearing all the voice,
I think I would be very excited, even though dinosaur
what we know about dinosaurs seems to change every year.
And this ride is probably already been, you know,
retroactively incorrect in many ways.
Yeah, like certain dinosaurs, they'll be like, oh, yeah, you know,
that dinosaur you've known about since you were a kid.
That dinosaur never existed.
That was that was fake.
Somebody thought that's what one was, but it didn't exist.
You know, like, oh, OK. Yeah.
And then like Jurassic Park did the whole like they're birds.
And then like some people are like, they're not really birds. Yeah.
So, yeah, you know, hopefully, hopefully in a few century,
we'll figure out what dinosaurs were.
I mean, we know for a fact it's the past.
It's a blast or it's fast.
It's a blast. And it's in the past.
Mm hmm. That's the motto of this ride.
Of course. It's cool and good.
And we all know it.
Um, we should we talk about the about the video before?
We talked about the four by three nature.
But yeah, you meet you have both.
Initially, Felicia Rashad,
who's the director of the Dino Institute,
which is a real highfalutin name, the Dino Institute, Dr. Marsh.
We just did a fake doctor final four on Twitch.
And I didn't want to have too much dinosaur in it.
So Dr. Seeker was in, but Dr. Marsh was not in.
Like, we don't know as much about her.
But she is, you know, more professional
and just giving you kind of the museum tour you think you're going to get.
And then Dr. Seeker announces that he is not your daddy's doctor
because he comes on screen with a puppet and makes a weird voice.
And so you immediately are shown that he is a little more oddball and casual.
Dr. Marsh, kind of dismissive of the old museum,
kind of like this looks like shit now that we got the time for.
And then and then then so you got Dr. Seeker, who's you know, I did.
I always liked this video.
This this video is a successful component to me.
And I like Wallace Langham.
He's good. He's good. And Larry Sanders,
a very good part of that show, Veronica's Closet.
I don't know how he is on that.
I've never seen Veronica's Closet.
I have not seen it either.
No, let's keep it that way.
Let's not start thinking that's a second gate.
Depends on how long this whole thing quarantine lasts.
Oh, God, speed it up, speed it up.
But yeah, it's all very this is a very back of the future ride vibe here.
Maybe too much. So maybe it kind of paved the way too much.
Yes, that might be when I'm analyzing about it,
like like why maybe it doesn't stick out to me as one of my favorites.
I feel like it does kind of feel like not as good as the back to the future.
It's like very similar setup.
It's a time. It's an institute.
This obviously is a dinosaur specific time traveling institute.
But it all feels less fun.
Oh, to me, let's not forget the first pre show in the queue
where the exhibits kind of get highlighted.
Bill Nye is the narrator in that section.
Very nice choice.
Bill Nye from Universe of Energy is so much.
Bill Nye, he was in other stuff and interventions.
There was so much Disney just owned Bill Nye.
They shoved them everywhere.
I believe they touch the television division, partially funded Bill Nye,
the science guy, and I think he's still caught up in legal,
like trying to untangle the legal of that
to then put those because those are on Amazon or Netflix.
The Bill Nye, the science show where they know is a new show.
That new show. Not sure. Rough.
Yeah, I haven't seen it.
I mainly know him from like, you know, I haven't seen a couple of months
as a new viral thing where he says like, and I should know.
I'm Bill fucking Nye, bitch or something like that.
Yeah, that's he'll do a video where he swears.
It's got all the novelty of like Bob Saget swearing.
It's or standups really dirty.
I don't know if you know that.
I look, you know what?
I just recently did that come across my desk that Bob Saget says words
that I wouldn't expect him to. Yes.
And I was. Yeah, it's crazy.
He's all about farts and stuff.
I haven't gotten over it.
I feel like no way Bill Nye shows up every now and then to if like
some Republican senator named like Turd Trudgley says, like,
if the Earth's getting hotter, God wants that way.
And Bill Nye shows up to tut tut them.
Yes, I think I said this on the universe of energy episode
a few years ago, where it's like Bill Nye smacks down Tucker Carlson on Fox News.
And then you watch it and he's like, no, the Earth is getting hotter.
And then it's like that was the clip.
Oh, snap.
And then you're like, well, did he really smack him down?
I don't even he wasn't even didn't even give any good evidence.
It's according to the Internet.
There's no interaction on TV that isn't a smackdown or an evisceration.
Yeah. No, this Bill Nye is smacking down left and right, according to the Internet.
I don't know what he I don't know what he said about the virus pre
it coming out.
So I can't well, I don't know.
I'll look into that.
Well, he is anti vaccine.
That's the one weird thing is that.
No, no.
That would be so funny if Bill Nye swears by all science.
But he's like, I don't know about these vaccines, though, you know.
Yeah, he's a big flat earther.
But besides that,
everybody just got that one wrong.
What can I say? I'm Bill Nye, bitch.
I came across I was wondering, did you guys come across the article?
Do you remember Disney magazine?
Disney's official magazine that covered Disney?
Of course. So, you know,
did you guys come across the scans of the article where an editor from that
was like a cast member at Dinosaur for the day on the attraction,
like worked all the different roles on it?
Oh, she got a tour before the park opened
and says this guy, Chuck.
Chuck is the cast member showing her like shadowing her.
She's shadowing and he's showing around.
The writer of this article says the dinosaurs are especially eerie.
Quote, they run all night.
It's easier on them due to the hydraulic system, explains Chuck.
They're set on night mode and don't go through the full range of motion.
So they nod and sway gently back and forth.
They're worrying mechanisms audible in the pre-opening silence.
Yeah. So creepy.
They never stop.
I per this like 20 plus year old article,
the dinosaurs just keep moving all night.
Whoa. Is that could that be common with animatronics?
At least this generally.
I don't know if modern animatronics where the hydraulics are a little different
or it's electric motors instead of hydraulics.
But just imagining all these weird little dinosaurs
just kind of swaying all night long is
is a horrifying image.
Well, I obviously I don't like the sound of that.
That scares me. Yeah.
Makes me makes me turn away and wins.
I'm going to have a nightmare where I wake up locked in the never ending,
perennially moving over a dinosaur ride overnight.
And I'm horrified by that.
And then I look down and there's baby Avatar or baby Aladar.
And maybe have it.
And I have it.
I don't like baby avatars either.
And I and I have to raise him.
He's my responsibility now.
Oh, that's yes.
That would I think you would like that.
I think that I think you. Yeah, I think you would.
Are you guys at all comforted by this attraction
being in the brotherhood of the dirty yellow strap?
Well, how about most attractions are?
I guess so. Yeah.
It's either lap bars or the dirty yellow strap.
Yeah, a lot of a lot of dirty yellow straps. Yeah.
Yeah, I yeah, I think I hearing that with the robots.
What is like this?
What would be the scariest Disney ride to have to spend the night in?
Like, would it be this one?
It might be this one.
Maybe because it's loud and unpleasant.
And like Indiana Jones, I guess there's a lot of stuff going on, too.
And that would be scary.
But like when I would maybe sleep in the room of skulls on Indiana Jones,
and I feel like that would be OK.
If you had to stay in the
are you proposing that we have we can go anywhere in the rides?
You just have to stay somewhere in the ride.
I think so. Yeah.
Well, but what would be what would be the scariest?
Yeah, like there would be almost like no good spots.
And like maybe don't count pre shows because there's not a lot of chaos
in the pre show, but like on the actual ride itself from the ride vehicle on.
I was going to say if you had to stay in
the Pleasure Island area in Pinocchio's Staring Journey
and the the like the the carnival games were going,
the like Ding the Bell game was going all night.
That'd be pretty horrible.
But I could just keep moving into Gepetto's room,
which has no robots and just a bunch of clocks.
So that you'd be fine over there.
But then you have to hear like an old man sobbing all night as he sleeps.
Yeah. Are you are you suggesting set lighting or work lighting,
like work fluorescence or like colored story lighting?
What do you like? How much of the ride is running?
Oh, I would say like with with the information about dinosaur,
let's say they're all like that.
It's like they're in B mode.
All the animatronics are kind of moving.
It's dark in there because they don't the lights are not unless they're
like fixing something. So it's mostly show lighting.
The animatronics may be not moving as crazy as they usually do,
but they're moving a little bit and the sounds are all still running. OK.
Yeah, I mean, the sounds are really unnerving.
There's so much darkness in this ride, although that Disney magazine article,
the editor said that like even the dark sections are set dressed,
like have plants in them, which then begs the question,
why isn't there a little more lighting even just on some plants? Like
if there's set dressed, why aren't they lit?
Yeah, I assume it's because they don't want to like show.
I mean, it's such a big building, but it's like it's kept dark.
So it kind of makes you feel like maybe there's more out there,
but it does just kind of feel like you're in a tiny space, honestly.
It doesn't. I'm kind of I'm kind of if you'll forgive me,
I'm kind of stuck on the previous on Mike's on your scenario. Yeah, go ahead.
And I it's you know, they don't it's not there anymore.
But I think I thought of a bad one, which is if you had to be in the
Wizard of Oz in the great movie, right? Oh, yeah.
Oh, like in the in the like the where the munchkins are all.
Yeah, if it were if it were that bright and you couldn't leave for like
oh, that's a good. Yeah, that's yeah.
And then like the munchkins kept popping up in the manholes and stuff and
and follow the yellow brick road was playing over and over again.
That witch or a pretty, pretty realistic animatronic. Yeah.
Yeah. Anywhere in great movie, right?
Might be might be a little rough.
Right under the these are bad on alien. Oh, Jesus.
Like a bed underneath the xenomorph, you'd have to sleep like a cot.
Dear Lord. Yeah, I don't think that I don't know that there's a good spot in
in great movie ride.
Is there any beds in that move right?
Hmm. Jason.
Well, in the gangster scene, there's clearly like some flop house facades.
Yeah, but those are facades.
Not even a full flop house.
I bet Bugsy would Bugsy would tell you he could make you sleep with the fishes.
Yeah. And that's you don't want to do that.
Right. What about what about like,
could you think you could like sleep on the plane in the Casablanca scene?
Is there a plan allowed, though, if the motors are going on?
That's true. Maybe not scary.
Maybe that one would just be unpleasant melancholy for me.
Yeah. Huh. Footlight parade.
Jason, would you sleep in probably footlight parade is the most, you know,
that's probably the chillest.
Yeah. Yeah. Huh.
I'm trying to think.
Maybe you could go in like a saloon part of the Old West
where the chaos isn't happening yet.
Mm hmm. Maybe the exit,
the little exit area of the Tower of Terror in Florida
with like the ventriloquist dummy.
Oh, like at least because that's that's kind of a cozy spot.
I bet you could like find a spot in there.
Tower of Terror Lobby, the Hollywood Tower Hotel lobby.
That's that's nice.
Yeah, but no lobbies. I said no pre shows.
But that's a literal lobby.
That's a literal hotel lobby.
So you know, OK.
Hmm. Maybe the hallway.
The hallway of Tower of Terror before it becomes a starfield.
I guess then ghosts are just constantly appearing.
The fourth dimension room, you mean? Yeah.
Oh, you mean like one of that when it opens the door
and you see the family down the hall. Yeah.
Yeah, but there's go. That's a ghost.
There's a big guy in the fourth dimension.
Yeah, I mean, that might that's scary.
So that's I guess I forget what we're actually trying to solve here.
It's the scariest one.
So I guess that is a contender.
But if we're trying to pick a nice one to I don't know.
And none of them are ideal. Nothing is ideal.
I'm trying. Yeah.
So what is the what would be the ideal ride to spend the night in?
What would be the most pleasant?
Is it maybe, you know, it is probably sleeping under the stars
and Radiator Springs racer the inside area,
like by the gas station, just sort of sleeping on the ground there.
That's nice.
It sounds kind of nice. Yeah.
You know, vibe wise, maybe Peter Pan's flight wouldn't be too bad,
but I don't know.
I don't want to be on record saying that I would like to spend the night
in Peter Pan's flight.
I think that's an arrestable offense.
Yeah, that's probably I mean, yeah, because you'd be in Wendy's room.
Yeah. You'd be in the Dowling Children's Nursery.
I mean, God, I'm like Robert Downey Jr.
in 96. Some guy here.
I just fell asleep in this kid's bedroom.
I guess you could you could, you know, spend it on the ship,
on Captain Hook's ship.
Yeah, they're just on the ground in Alice somewhere.
OK, yeah, that's not bad.
The birthday scene would be unpleasant because there's such a such a loud party.
Keep it down.
Yeah, that's like I guess the most pleasant.
Oh, you know what? You know what the answer is?
It's the Navi River journey. Yeah. No.
What? No.
Well, not in the not not in the room with the I don't like this as much as you guys.
I hate not not in the room with the shaman.
Hell no. I'm not spending the night with the shaman.
I don't know. That's kind of a soothing song.
I think within earshot would be nice.
Not right. Not like sleeping at the shaman's feet or anything.
Not her feet.
I think I'd be a little scared of all these like sparkly snakes slithering around
or whatever the hell is happening in there.
Yeah, it would have to be in the right spot because obviously there's
different beasts flying around and running around.
But like by the by the big the frogs, when the frogs are jumping on the leaves
right there, I feel like, you know, you look up and you just enjoy the
pandoran frogs hopping from leaf to leaf.
And you have a nice night's sleep and you can hear in the distance
that beautiful song sung by one of our favorite characters in fiction.
Oh, what about in E.T., the green planet, when they're having a little party
and they're sliding up and down, there's little water.
I love I love that.
But that's going to be how you're going to sleep.
It's a party. I'll just be up all night.
Yeah. Be full of piss in there.
Well, you know what, if I want to just get a good dose in,
I should just go to living with the land, right?
That's what I do anyway.
Which part of living with the land would you sleep in?
Would it be in this lab, the science lab?
I just feel the tomatoes.
Yeah, that's yeah.
Yeah. What's really anywhere?
Any part is completely suitable to sleep.
What's the softest fruit you could make a bed out of?
Jason. Oh, gosh.
Yeah, some of those tomatoes.
Yeah, bananas.
Depends, I guess, how much they've aged.
Tomato would might burst my way through.
That'd be like sleeping on like a partially inflated air mattress.
I think it's all it's all going by the end.
And then, you know, that ends with a big splatter. Squash, right?
Maybe a big squash.
Sleep too hard. I think big squash. Maybe.
I mean, that sounds I would like to see you sleeping on a big squash.
But I don't think that's going to be comfortable for you.
Yeah, that's going to be a great photo op.
But I don't know that that's going to give you eight.
Oh, can I sleep on a raft in the in the fish, the fish farms?
Just on my back with the gators.
Not because it's not going to smell good in there.
Here's a good one on the porch right before you go down the
waterfall on pirates in Disneyland on that porch in the swamp.
That's good. Any porches or the porch in living with the land
right before the thunderstorm, you get a little white noise.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, that'd be nice because there's no like animatronics
bothering you or anything happening that might distract you from getting.
You're actually wrong. There's an animatronic dog right there. But.
But he's not doing jack shit.
So that's fine. I'll sleep soundly.
Mm hmm. Yeah.
So look, I mean, another will throw again, throw this out to the listener.
What ride would you not want to sleep on?
And what ride would you want to sleep on?
Sleep in, I should say.
Yeah, let us know.
And then we'll kill a whole episode reading each and every response. Yeah.
We thought it's a lot filled. I'm wasting.
I like that we got to have a lot of time not talking about dinosaur.
That was nice. But maybe we should get back to it
so that we can stop one day.
Any other any other thoughts about dinosaur?
Well, I was trying to figure out like I we were talking about.
We've talked about this before. We're living with the land.
I've talked about how I think Soren is better in California
because of the facade and because of outside.
And I find like I think we even underestimate sometimes how much
all of the stuff around a ride makes us want to go on.
It's like Tower of Terror even California, which I know it's missing
the the room in Florida.
But like we didn't go on it that much, even though it's a great ride
and it's a fun ride system and they change it into Guardians of the Galaxy.
And it's like my favorite ride in Disneyland now.
But I'm trying to figure out like I find so much of the queue on this ride,
like not that fun. I don't like the building.
I don't like it.
Nothing draws me to it. It's out of the way.
Like, you know, like mustard pipes.
I love mustard pipes, but I'll be honest, I didn't know about them
until, you know, five hours ago.
It's mustard pipes, the voice of Bill Nye, Aladar splashing in a fountain.
But I don't think I guess what I'm what I'm getting at is
I think the ride is actually better than I give it credit for.
I think the ride is better than
than my memory of it is.
And even though I'm apparently still terrified of it,
I think with like a different framing device or a different show building,
I think I make a, you know, point to go to it.
Every time.
Let me ask, this hasn't really come up.
Were you guys dinosaur kids?
Were you ever did you ever have a dinosaur phase?
A little bit, but nothing major.
Not not not big time, but yeah, I dug them and I yeah,
I certainly look forward to like, you know,
any museum trip that involves seeing bones or whatever.
Yeah, I remember I had like little models of them.
I, you know, I feel like it lasted for like three months.
And then I was back to Ninja Turtles, probably.
Yeah, I feel like I had a little fit.
I probably the way you guys are talking,
I probably had the biggest dinosaur phase.
I'm going to go ahead and say there is a chunk of our listeners
who had a dinosaur phase.
And I'm very curious if people who were big dinosaur kids
like this ride more, you know.
Yeah, I see what you're saying.
But also like, you know, Jurassic,
the original Jurassic Park ride is fantastic. Yeah.
And I, you know, like it a lot more.
And I don't think it's just because it's tied to the movie
because it's like you don't see any like other human actors.
There's no robot really on that ride.
So I think it's just a better ride in general.
I mean, I think that's not controversial what I'm saying.
I'm not some genius who's come to that conclusion.
Yeah, I think that's right.
I mean, I like I do like this ride.
I really liked it when I was younger,
but I wrote it when we went down
last year to when we were in Orlando, I wrote it.
And I liked it.
It did strike me how much of the ride is hidden by darkness.
But yeah, I had a nice time.
Yeah, short wait, pretty short wait when I was there.
Another thing, when you compare it to Indy, which is unfair,
but it's also fair because it's the same thing,
same track and everything.
It's like this one, it feels small.
Indy, Indy, you really like feel like, oh, my God, we're in this giant temple.
And it's like art directed well.
And your eye goes to these different scenes.
And like it's such a it's such a giant,
crazy experience going on in these still to this day. Yeah.
And this almost feels like you're on a bigger, like dark ride.
Like this feels like somehow much smaller in scale.
For like, like imagine you have never been on this ride and imagine you're like,
OK, here you have the track for Indiana Jones.
You have that size show building.
It's going to be it's going to be the exact same ride, except dinosaurs.
And you'd be like, holy shit.
You would imagine like turning the corner when you see like the giant temple
in Indiana Jones, but like a giant dinosaur in the distance or something.
You'd be like, oh, my God.
It doesn't feel like that at all.
It absolutely I hear exactly what you're saying.
Yeah, it feels like you go into like little tiny show scenes.
Where a dinosaur pokes out and you go, oh, that's not it.
And then you move on.
It's like it's weird. I don't know.
It's a room of small rooms and false guessing.
Yeah, it's not again. I don't it's not bad.
I think it's better than I'm giving it credit for.
But there's just a lot of like little things where I go.
Well, if you have all the same resources as Indiana Jones,
I don't know why the ride itself feels like this.
From Q pre show to the actual ride itself.
It's so I don't know. I don't know why.
I just should be better.
There's not enough tricks.
The dinosaur is either I guess more at you or they fly over you.
And that's kind of it.
Yeah, I guess it's I mean, the limitations from just having
animatronic dinosaurs, I'm sure is a big part of it.
But it should I don't know why the scope isn't somebody's going to be mad at me.
A lot of people will be mad at me for saying this,
because I think this is actually like a sleeper ride for people. But
I think it might be. Yeah, I know.
I don't know that people will agree with what we're landing on.
And we just kind of don't like it. But we we can't lie. I don't know.
Jurassic Park has a scope.
There's a scope to it like dinosaurs in general should be.
You should feel like the first, you know, that scene of in Jurassic Park
where they see, I forget which dinosaurs, the long necked dinosaurs,
where they're like, it's that wow moment where you go, oh, my God, it's dinosaurs.
And they have that same moment, which they, of course, have gotten rid of
on the new Jurassic Park, Jurassic World ride, where you go into the thing
and you go, welcome to Jurassic Park and the majesty and how big
the dinosaurs are. And I feel like you get even more of that
from the universe of energy than you do from here.
I totally yes. You know what?
Because the bronis are so tall.
I don't feel like any of these dinosaurs are tall.
I think it's just missing like taller ceilings, bigger.
Right. Isn't the isn't the carnivore
carnivorous kind of kind of short?
It feels like that. I mean,
and then when you think of the Indiana Jones building,
I don't know if this building is maybe doesn't have as high a ceiling,
but Indiana Jones building feels like it's 10 stories tall.
I'm sure it's not that tall, but it feels so tall
and it feels so expensive.
The scale, the scale is much bigger.
The theater tricks work better on Indiana Jones.
I mean, I'll agree for sure. I agree with that.
Well, and if we're comparing it to both the Jurassic Park ride
and the Indiana Jones, which all feels kind of fair, both are.
Unfortunately, both are tied to film franchises that we really love
and no knock on Aladar and Kron or anything.
But it's of no never want to offend Kron, never
know. And that's
praise be to Kron in Kron, we trust.
But it's not only that you in both Jurassic Park and
Indiana Jones, you're getting not just the connection to the franchise we love,
but also the stirring score of both and moments being punctuated by
this score that gives us feelings otherwise.
And then this just doesn't have music.
It's just like, is that it?
No, not our dino.
Vroom, just loud sounds.
And there's no majesty in this.
It's just it's very stressful.
I feel like it's like uncut gems.
Very much right.
It's like because I think when you're in the in the queue,
the queue is sort of setting you up for more of a Jurassic Park type experience.
Yes, it's very like, look at how big these things were.
Isn't this amazing? Like dinosaurs existed.
They were big.
And then the ride is this like very like, you know, tense, unpleasant thing.
I mean, I almost think it would be better if it was like the ride was called Dino
Hunters. And, you know, you went through like this
Transformers style base and they were like, all right, here's the deal.
We need to kill as many dinosaurs as we can.
Dinosaurs have been running amok in this part of the jungle.
Like it would get you at least in the right head space for this type of ride.
Come back with Kron's body or you don't get to come back.
Deliver the head of Kron to my desk, or you will be drummed out of the academy.
We are Dino Hunters.
And it's like, all right, dinosaurs are the enemy.
We're getting ready for like a very like tense ride, kind of a thrill experience.
Is it like the end of it's a video that starts with a guy.
The lights are off and he's just a silhouette and then a light hits him.
And he's wearing like a velociraptor hide as a big trench coat with.
Yes, that's good.
And that shows you that he's had previously successful missions.
I guess we want a Joe Exotic, I guess.
Yes. I have dinosaurs.
That's a.
I kind of think that we would all be sort of less conflicted
because because I'm trying to work through my feelings here.
I think we'd all be a little less conflicted if it was all sort of a unifying thing.
If it all felt like a unified ride.
It shouldn't be very warm at the beginning
and up through like it's a warm building.
You look at it's the wonder of seeing dinosaur bones.
You meet Felicia Rashad, who's a very warm personality.
And then it hands off to, you know, will weasel Dr.
Seeker and then it's all unpleasant after that.
It's like there's a hard divide there.
So you want an all warm ride or a ride that's all murdering.
It really ups the tension at the end.
Once it starts counting down to a catastrophic meteor strike,
which is kind of a neat trick, but also like, oh, well,
I know this ride is going to be oversuit.
They are counting down until the end of it.
Yeah, that's weird, too.
Yes, you're right.
You're like in a hurry the whole time.
Yeah. And I mean, there's obviously contradictions to what I'm saying.
There's rides that are sort of like, you know, fronts for like fake.
Like they're much more pleasant in the queue and everything.
It's just I feel like it eases you into what's happening more than this one does.
It's just Jurassic Park is very warm and then very severe,
but not until the climb and the climb is the transition.
So you get the wonder of dinosaurs and then you get the terror of dinosaurs.
And this kind of doesn't ever give you wonder.
The entire actual ride part is just very stressful.
And also, I think I don't know exactly how I've presented it,
but I kind of feel like a good ride has like three or four, five moves.
Like different little things that you go, oh, yeah.
And then that happened. It was cool. Oh, that happened.
It was cool. And it could be anything.
It could be Optimus Prime saying he's proud of you.
It could be like a little drop, whatever it is.
This doesn't know that I consider that a move, but OK,
well, I move is maybe not the best way to drop and being told you're proud
or both moves. Well, a moment.
I should say moments, different moments where you go, oh, and that was cool.
This is the same moment over and over again.
Yeah, which is like, oh, God.
Yeah. So it's yeah, I, I really don't think I'm as negative as I'm sounding like it now.
I'm just trying to figure out what it is about it.
Well, let me let me ask, will this story change your opinion?
The biggest news story about this attraction in the last 10 years.
Do you guys know about this?
I think 2013, a woman found a loaded gun in a ride vehicle.
So that person was thinking that they had the dinosaur hunter idea before I did.
And they wanted to be prepared to, I guess, yeah, to shoot the carnitourists.
Thankfully, did not open fire on the carnitourists,
turned the attraction into cast members, cast members passed it along,
turned the gun into cast members, passed it along to the authorities.
The owner of the gun said he did not know about Disney's policy against weapons
and he did have a concealed weapons permit.
So that was, you know, that could just happen before they had the metal detectors.
Yeah, that was the old days.
I'm sure there's no way anybody could sneak anything weird in now.
Sure, it's a foolproof system.
Yeah, that's a little bit scary.
You got to be protected in case, I don't know, Pluto comes at you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. You really.
How does he know all the other?
How does he know all the plush characters don't have weapons as well?
Yeah. Well, I think maybe they were also like thinking like, well, on the safari
to we should be prepared.
You know, in case a giraffe.
Attacks us notoriously aggressive animals.
Yeah. Yeah, that's the story.
I was reading and this is I forget where I was reading it, so forgive me.
There's been a lot of chatter recently in the last few years
about them doing something to this ride.
Like probably like the biggest rumor, of course, is that they're going to make it
into the Indiana Jones ride. Yeah. Right.
But there was a new thing I read and this might be new as of a year or two ago.
And who knows, of course, with the state of the economy right now,
when anything ever will happen with theme parks again, honestly,
I am wondering if the epic world,
whatever the third universal park even happens now, who knows?
Oh, no, it might not.
I wonder if Mario will just sit there at Universal Hollywood for like
unbuilt for five years after this, who knows?
And that is too sad to think about.
Sorry. Sorry to bring everyone down again.
Now, now we're sad.
Now, Jason, finally, it's hit him.
How this whole thing is a bummer.
I mean, I'm just feeling really excited and cool about like, oh, cool.
Going on a ride and finding a gun. Neat.
Yeah, sorry. And then you brought us down. Sorry.
The idea of lifeless Koopa troopers,
let alone Koopa paratroopers.
Oh, so sad. They'll never move again.
But I read and this now I was like, I was always like, oh, I guess that's OK.
If they just put the Indiana Jones right over there, it's like, obviously,
we'd all want a new ride, cooler ride.
But someone brought up the speculation or I guess the rumor that
they would keep the dinosaurs on the ride in Indiana Jones would be added to the ride.
Oh, yeah. And I was like, I was like, hell, yes.
Yeah, I was thinking like, yeah, Indiana Jones has met aliens now,
but he hasn't met dinosaurs yet.
I think I was like, oh, like Indiana Jones goes to the island of the dinosaurs.
You sign me up.
I mean, I guess you could go in the time machine, too.
But I like the idea. There's like a secret island of dinosaurs.
And then I was like, OK, yep, yep. Let's do that.
Remember, remember in the like Saturday afternoon, like syndicated
cheapie dramas, there was a lost world show for a while.
The is it Jules Verne or Robert Louis Louis Stevenson lost world,
but very conveniently done when the movie lost world was in the air.
I don't remember this at all.
Oh, because that title was up for grabs.
Yes. So you can confuse people.
Sir, Arthur Conan Doyle's The Lost World. That's who it was.
Oh, OK. So, yeah.
So if if there's ever any money freed up to do anything to dinosaur the next decade,
I fully fully rubber stamp Indiana Jones meets the dinosaurs.
So what are the moments of this?
Do we get to see him like like whip a raptor?
He probably has to at least whip toward a raptor.
I think there should be a scene where he's in one of the dinosaurs mouths.
His his feet are sticking out like wiggling,
like he's about to be eaten by a dinosaur.
And then like he does something to free himself or we help him free,
get free from the dinosaur.
You can tell that there's trouble because like a, you know,
like a baby triceratops ended up with his hat.
Oh, yeah, that's good.
I mean, that let's see what else.
He brought a Nazi with him and you get to see a T.
Rex devour and that's the yeah, perfect.
Maybe like there's a big dino and he like kind of looks at you
and he goes, at least it's not a snake.
Yeah, that's good.
There's a boulder that starts rolling or so you think,
but when it gets a little more lit, it's a it's a big brontosaurus shit.
It's Aladar shit.
It's an it's an iguanodon giant shit
rolling toward Indiana Jones in the vehicle.
Oh, cover your nose.
It's a big one.
Oh, cover your nose is everyone.
Oh, no.
And then you can use like that grass, like that dirt grass smell from Soren.
And then you then you go around the corner and then you see like the wreckage.
But it's that it all it all hit him and it's like Biff and the manure.
It's like Biff and the manure.
And there should be another ride vehicle stuck in it, like another time.
Time over vehicle.
Time Rover, thank you.
An animatronic of you wincing
stuck in a big pile of iguanodon shit.
That's great. Yeah.
This ride sounds so much better.
This is great. Indiana Jones versus the dinosaurs.
Is it? Wait, did you use you said the island of dynasty?
Would it be called Indiana Jones and the island of dinosaurs?
That was my suggestion.
I like it. My temple of dinosaurs.
Yeah. My suggestion was like it's not there's no time travel.
It's just like there's a secret.
Like he finds an island that still has dinosaurs on it somewhere.
This is what I've complained about this four or five times,
I'm sure, on the show at this point.
But this is what George Lucas's sort of idea was, not specifically dinosaurs,
but was going to be every movie was a different crazy genre.
Every. Yeah. Every genre of like pulp novel.
Right. So like like his idea was Indiana Jones and the Saucer Men from Mars.
And it would have been like, I think like Mars Attacks meets Indiana Jones,
which is awesome.
And then Temple of Doom came out and people were like,
this isn't like the first one.
And then they just have been remaking the first movie ever since.
Guys, I got to tell you, I just found the best eBay item.
Rare Disney 2000 Dinosaur movie, Baby Aladar, Pop-Up Watch.
Whoa, what do you mean pop up?
Watch pops out of an egg.
And there's a very small LCD screen.
All right. I've made it.
I've made it. I don't mind.
I don't mind this guy. He is not as horrifying to me.
I've made an offer for $10.
I like him more.
I like this plastic baby Aladar more.
Actually, actually, you know what?
Their shipping is five.
Let me make an offer for $8 or $7.
Then let me break down my feelings.
Plastic toy, Baby Aladar.
Fine. I feel like I've filmed Baby Aladar.
Hell no. I don't like Baby Aladar in this watch nearly as much as I do with CGI.
Yeah, I got to agree with Mike.
It's because I said I like it.
It's not. No, that's why it's not.
The other baby's better.
If I if I if I sent you guys a 4am text out of nowhere, out of context,
a baby Aladar, you would all say this is bad.
I'm going back. There's no way I will pass a lie detector test.
Hook me to a lie detector and ask me about the cuteness of all these characters.
I've said I like madness.
I do. I do a podcast with maniacs.
I think, look, I'm very, very sane when it comes to cuteness.
I am very within my mental faculties.
I found I found an Aladar
adult Aladar McDonnell rubber dino hand.
Oh, I just said you the hand puppet.
Now, this is that.
Oh, you did. Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I hate this.
We're back to hate for me.
Aladar hand puppet.
It's a little too expensive.
And I have too much too many toys.
But if anyone has an Aladar rubber hand puppet and we do a live show in the next decade,
feel free to gift this to me.
Um, I'll I'll say this, though, after all of this
animosity between me and baby Aladar, we could make up for all of it.
If when Indiana Jones goes to the island of dinosaurs,
if we get to see baby Aladar eating Mutt Williams,
all is forgiven, baby Aladar.
Oh, man. Baby Aladar eating Mutt Williams.
Just the leg. Yeah.
Again, just the legs.
You see him like like writhing around.
Just his cuff denim.
Oh, yes.
I.
His blue suede shoes, which played on the ground.
Well, did we do it?
Did we survive? I guess.
I think so. Well, the last this isn't anything I really need to say,
but it's the last note I had was that I think it's clear that they picked Carna.
I can always carna sort.
Now I can't say anything.
Carnasaurus, Carnotaurus, what?
Carnotaurus. Geez.
We've I've lost my mind trying to remember all these names.
I. It's gone.
It's pretty clear.
It's pretty clear to me that they were like, OK, we cannot have
the T-Rex be at the end like Jurassic Park ride.
So let's come up with a different dinosaur that's almost exactly
the same as a T-Rex in scary.
That's what I was saying.
They had recently discovered that one
and they conveniently slotted it in.
But I have to.
That's I mean, I think I'm not making some genius point here,
but don't you don't you think that's why they chose this dinosaur?
Oh, for sure. Yeah, I think early on they probably were like, well,
obviously the scariest big one is a T-Rex.
But yeah, that is complicated when it's so identifiable.
It seems like they went with a bunch of dinosaurs
that were not used in Jurassic Park, like the common ones.
There's a raptor. There is a raptor in this ride.
It's not really a super scary moment.
I don't know. It's hard to make the raptor scary in the universal one, too.
Well, supposedly that if I mean, I think this
the roller coaster is being built for islands next year.
So maybe that one will have to be finished.
Yeah. But supposedly that is a little a little section in the raptor cages.
So let's see if they can make the raptors as scary as they are in the movie. Yeah.
We'll see. We'll see what the future of dinosaur based entertainment holds.
Something to look forward to in a crazy time.
That's right. At least someday.
I think there will be robot dinosaurs again.
I'm hoping we get a live action CG at Aladar.
You know what I'm saying?
I think Aladar on Disney Plus, Baby Aladar,
sort of the better call Saul for Aladar
and dinosaur to see him as a baby.
So multiple seasons of Baby Aladar to see what happens.
Baby Aladar to see what formed him, how he got his principles,
to see what shaped him as a as an adult man dinosaur.
Sounds great. I think that's all great. Yeah.
And I think Jason Sheridan should motion cap the Aladar.
If called to serve the baby, Aladar called to serve.
Yeah, I'm a little baby.
I'm just baby Aladar.
Jason, could you do a little?
I'm yawning.
Jason, do a little of your baby Aladar for us.
Does it sound like Stitch? I don't know. It might.
I'm hungry for plant.
Oh, wow. He's a little baby. He's cute. He has a cute voice.
Oh, Jesus. Say I'm hungry for plants again for me.
I'm hungry for plant.
Adorable. Plant singular?
Plant? I'm wiggling. What am I doing?
Oh, wow. I love this.
This is great. I made a little peepee.
This is definitely cute.
Do you like baby?
Do you like baby from dinosaurs better than baby Aladar?
Do you think cute? Yes. Yes.
I may like baby from dinosaurs better, but I don't know that I think baby
from dinosaurs is baby Sinclair is not cuter,
but baby Sinclair is more like funny and endearing.
Yeah, baby. I think he is more aesthetically pleasing. Hmm.
Well, there's going to be a lot of debate raging when this comes out.
Yeah. Scott banging on a keyboard to write us a stern letter about
doesn't like baby Aladar.
Truly, this is madness.
Although, oh, God, I just looked at baby baby Sinclair toy.
I wait, where did it go?
God, it was like I imagined it in a
Shuko esque fashion. I saw like a bunch of unpainted baby Sinclair.
Oh, my God. It went away.
It was in the preview and now I'm not.
There's some horrifying babies and clear dolls.
Oh, yeah, I found one.
Maybe what I'm fine.
I don't maybe I don't want to raise a baby dinosaur.
That's what I'm going to see.
That one's that one's OK.
OK, well, we'll buy that for you.
I don't like that it says, got to try me, got to try me.
Try me.
Oh, here we go. Try me.
Here's a child's baby Sinclair costume.
You know, oh, God, oh, no.
Oh, he's got like a plush.
It's like a foam head and a big diaper and separate skin tone pants.
This is not good.
OK, look, I'm going to I'm going to hit the escape
patch from this video or from this video from this episode.
You survived, but I guess the right.
But I'll also say I'll tie this into the socials by saying go to our Twitter
and perhaps also our Instagram or Facebook to see some of these horrifying things.
But also one more thing.
Oh, God. Oh, God.
What is this weird?
I don't know. Like a knockoff ripoff.
As
well, you can see lots of horrifying baby Sinclair's and allodars
at our at our Twitter, if I guess the ride.
Oh, God, please stop. Please stop.
Let me let me, though, also send you what I think is the is the ultimate
in 2000 dinosaur aesthetics.
You guys check your text messages.
I got to check out a little of the dinosaur Gameboy Color Game.
Oh, wow.
The stills of this that I'm sending and I'll post on Twitter,
I think are like vapor wave masterpieces.
Oh, good.
These are these are unbelievable.
I hate the aesthetic of the film.
This I'd watch a whole movie of this.
No problem. Oh, yeah.
This is like you could imagine like some like city pop playing.
Yes, yes.
These are all like album covers waiting to happen.
Like Aladar is blue.
He's like he's a very royal blue.
There's a weird thing that says in really eight bit font.
These pillars indicate the exit and it looks like blood.
These stones, I don't know what I'm looking at there.
And then a close up of a very pixelated Aladar eye that says
Lemur Island is gone.
These are great.
And then and then this really like sad gathering of four dinosaurs.
You can't tell what half of them are.
And then I like step down eight bit rainbow and it says you win.
These are this is like some of the best aesthetics I've ever seen.
So credit to the makers of the game.
That song, Lemur Island is gone.
If you're a vapor wave artist,
take Lemur Island is gone for an album, please.
It's waiting. It's waiting for you.
I was doing a lot of I texted you, I was doing I'm listening to a lot of marauder.
Hey, that's good news.
That's smart. Oh, very good.
Any discoveries and you want to share?
Do you have you do you know the Giorgio Marauder and Joe Esposito album?
Solitary, you mentioned who's Joe Esposito?
I actually don't. I forget he's there's a song he has.
I got to look it back up.
But the album is fantastic.
Wow. OK. It's like I.
Yeah, he's I got to look him up here.
He's a singer. He he's an older man.
He's a
I'm stalling his older man's here while I look it up.
He's he's written songs, Donna Summer, Rita Franklin.
I'm trying to think of what his
I don't know.
But look, the point the point is,
look at the stills that we're posting of the dinosaur Game Boy Color game.
And, you know, by the way, in general, Game Boy Color,
there's some pretty fun stuff on Game Boy Color.
I was not aware of this area,
but I found a Game Boy Color game.
Maybe we just have to play this over on Twitch, which is another thing I can promote.
So we've been doing stuff on Twitch and having fun there.
But there is a Shrek game for Game Boy Color.
And the game is called Fairy Tale Freak Down.
And I've looked at part of the game in which Shrek is in a fistfight with Pinocchio.
He's just punching Pinocchio in the face.
Wow. Fairy tale freaked out rules.
I think I'm I think I'm off of dinosaur.
I think I'm a big Game Boy Color guy.
So play dinosaur for Game Boy Color and listen to Marauder.
And you'll be in a static heaven. Yeah. Wow.
And as for other bullshit, you can always find that three extra episodes
of bullshit a month on Patreon dot com slash podcast the ride.
That's the second gate. Anything else, fellas?
That's it. Just I'm pretty worn out.
That's a little too much alidar for one day for anyone.
I could do in a little more elder, but I agree.
It's almost done. It's almost if you guys want to do a talking
alidar after show, feel free. Oh, yeah, maybe.
I'm getting hungry. I'm going to have to eat more plant.
Oh, is that a baby? Yeah, he's back. He's back.
Oh, baby alidar.
Oh, love him.
He's the baby. Got to play with him. What was it?
Try me. Try me.
Oh, God, if we're there, where's the Godbombs?
When I need them, baby, baby Sinclair and baby alidar on the same show.
Wow. The real odd.
That's how they own them both.
They own them both. Yeah, they own them both.
All right. Well, I'm good.
All right. I'm more than good. Goodbye.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson,
Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter
and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.