Hi everyone. This episode was recorded a while ago. A simpler time when the only thing we had to worry about was a global pandemic.
We again want to voice our support for the protests against police brutality going on across the country and now across the world.
The other day on Twitter we linked to bail funds and mutual aid funds.
There's also links in this episode description to GoFundMe pages for the family of Breonna Taylor and Darnella Frazier, who recorded the murder of George Floyd.
As well as a group called BEAM that focuses on black mental health and the National Lawyers Guild.
Thank you for listening. Stay safe and once again, black lives matter.
Podcasting Titan Mike Mitchell joins us for the ultimate discussion of churros on Podcast The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the only theme park podcast where we have to stop halfway through every episode to swap out the six propane tanks that power the show.
I'm Jason Sheridan, joined as always by Mike Carlson.
Yes, I am Mike Carlson. Yes, we're doing something backwards I feel like as far as being able to record here.
I feel like we're using an old school way of powering. We really should just use some sort of electrical system, but we're not.
No, no, we're using clean burning propane. Was that a Johnny Carson?
No, that was Hank Hill. It was Hank Hill. Yeah, it's close though. It's close. That's Scott Gardner.
Yeah, yeah, good voice and good recording method. Yeah, I mean now that we all have our six separate tanks, we're certainly burning through a lot, but it's the only way to get it done.
Yeah, you gotta do what you gotta do.
Yeah, boy, this is a fun one. This is fun to talk about for a little while. Talk about things you miss from the days of theme parks being open.
I'm excited to have some mouth memories.
What was wrong with that? That was an acceptable phrase I feel. You hit me recently for saying gross stuff, but that one, I don't know why that one hits me real strange.
Mouth memories. It's perfectly natural when you're thinking about something you ate once, it's a mouth memory.
I'm impressed. I love it.
And today it's mouth memories of one of our favorite things to munch on, which is a big foot long rod. It's mouth memories of foot long rods.
What is this? What is this innuendo?
These are just things that I'm saying innuendo. I don't know what you're talking about. It's what a churro is.
This is not our podcast. This is not the podcast I know.
Hey, let's bring in our guest, a man who deals professionally with mouth memories. You know him from the Doughboys and the Birthday Boys. It's Mike Mitchell.
Hey guys, how are you?
Hi Mitch.
Great. Thanks for joining us.
I don't know if I want to be known as the mouth memories guy, but I guess I'll take it.
Provisional mouth memory historian, Mike Mitchell.
I do have a lot of good nice, nice mouth memories over the years.
It's like, it's like regular life where you have, you have good memories and bad memories. The bad memories usually just burn in your mouth.
I think burning your mouth is the bad memories.
Yeah, nothing like a burning, but burning sensation, burning mouth memory. No, acidic. You don't like that.
Yeah, we're getting like, I don't know, when you're younger getting dirt or fucking dog shit in your mouth or something.
What? Dog shit?
You know how kids, you know how kids always wrestle around and get a bunch of dog shit in their mouth?
I mean that wasn't my experience, but.
Ah man, that happens all the time back where I'm from.
Jason, Jason, do you have that experience as well since you're more from that part of the country?
Well, no, but I'm not the king of mouth memories, you know, I'm not.
Maybe this is, this is maybe a good point of discussion. What is everyone's worst mouth memory?
What is the worst thing that you've had in your mouth?
And I'll start just to give you guys time to think of one.
One time I was really dumb as a kid, although still too old of a kid.
I think I might have been nine or 10 and I had, I was so absent minded that I let, I think I did like chew on stuff.
I wasn't supposed to chew on like toys and even like a wire or something.
I did chew stupidly and I picked up, I was like, you know,
robotically picking up a glass of water and then just instead picked up a like a loose wire of like an AC adapter.
I remember it was for a portable TV and I just put it in my mouth against my tongue and it gave me a shock.
So probably the stupidest thing I ever did.
It wasn't that bad of a shock, but definitely a shock.
That is, that is more insane than wrestling around and getting dog shit in your mouth.
It really is because I chose it. There were plenty of things that there was, there were edible things near me.
There was water. Yeah. Why would I put just the end of a plug?
Did your hair frizz out like a mad scientist?
And I became a different person.
I started to like speak in different voices as if I was getting different frequencies from the radio.
Right. Yeah. You know, baddie coda-esque situation.
Wow. Are you, can you still, do you still feel electrified on certain nights?
If you ever see anything weird happening, you know, the like patterns in the sky or what you think might be happening in the sky,
or what you think might be a meteor shower. It's, it's me.
It's still residual from this nine year old accident.
Wow. That's crazy. You're like a Jamie Foxx electro character from The Amazing Spider-Man 2.
Jesus. What? What? What's wrong?
It's a good, a good mind memory. That movie. Yeah.
That I will say that it's the music when like Electro is like turns into Electro or whatever is so bad that it is kind of funny.
Isn't there like, isn't there a music, isn't there music that's like Electro Man?
Like there's like weird background music when he becomes Electro. Do you know what I'm talking about?
I think I do, but I don't. Yeah. Yeah, I kind of do, but I don't know. I don't remember anything about it.
I mean, I just, I remember just like the whole thing is ridiculous and I was laughing the whole time.
Let me just say this is wrong, but it's something like Electrify, like kill them all, Electrify.
It's very, very, very shitty. I remember that much.
Man, I'm trying to find it. I can't. I, ooh, if we, if we find it, we'll post it though. I want to hear this.
If not, we'll just lay in. We'll like use that little sample of you just now.
We'll make another track and we'll lay it under the actual movie.
That'll just be what people think. Like your mind, everyone's mind memory of this in 20 years will now be your soundtrack for Electro.
Any other mouth memories?
Well, the night, oh, you're asking Mitch or you're asking all of us?
Anybody.
Well, my, the, if you want a bad one and it's not, I want the worst.
As bad as you can go.
Okay. Well, I had a surgery when I was, I think in eighth, seventh or eighth grade, because I had too much gum.
Like there was too much gum in my mouth and not chewing gum, gum.
Spearmint? Oh damn.
No, no, no. I had like excess gum and they were like, well, we're going to cut it off.
Oh.
So I went and had a surgery and they put me out for it, but I remember it.
So it was like one of those surgeries where like they didn't really like completely knock you out.
I think they just gave me the gas.
So I, I have memory of being kind of half asleep and woozy, feeling like a knife on my gums.
Whoa.
Oh my God.
Dear Lord.
It was, it was kind of traumatic.
This is a, this is a joker origin story.
Yes. That's a good point.
Gas that made you crazy.
And then a knife on your face.
And I asked for the mirror and the surgeon, surgeon gave me the mirror and I said, oh wow, that looks a lot better.
Thank you.
That's great.
That, that mirror moment is great.
And the Simpsons, it was, it was Perry on Simpsons, which you know, yes.
That's one of those where I knew the parody first and not maybe had not seen the original yet.
Oh wow.
Yeah.
I have some bad mouth memories.
Let's see.
One of my, one of my first ones, and I think that it like made me hate this creature more than anything is that I had a, I was at my grandma's house and I had a Coca-Cola and it was on the porch.
I took a sip of it and then in my mouth I felt moving.
What I pulled out was a carpenter ant.
Oh man.
Pretty big.
And it was, and it, and it, and it just stuck with me forever that I could like feel all of its legs in my mouth.
Oh yeah. I'm looking those up.
Those are huge.
Oh my God.
Like, like a penny sized.
Yeah.
People, it's funny because like people on people in California are like, ants are cool.
And look, ants are cool in their own way.
Like they like are, you know, they do their little thing and they're like, they're like a little crew and they're really tiny out here.
But on the East Coast, we just have a lot of carpenter ants, which are kind of like these bigger black ants.
And they like are more to me, like they always felt more like cockroaches were like in your kitchen or something.
And if you had stuff out there would just be like, you'd move it and then there'd be like seven of those big things and they'd all scatter and it sucked.
Yeah.
But I also ate, I also was at the, I was at LAX airport and I ate a Labre bakery sandwich and I bit into it and there was a stone in it, like a little rock.
Oh, that was a bad mouth memory.
I have a lot of bad mouth memories.
Mitch, didn't you, weren't you with me somewhere where you bit into something hard?
Yeah, I was at, it was at, what's it called? The Hillstone.
Oh yeah.
I think so.
Oh, was it bone?
Yeah, it was bone. Yeah, it was from the, it was from the French dip sandwich.
Yeah, I think I've had a similar experience with that same establishment and that same sandwich.
Really?
Yeah, I think they're just, I think they're just going too fast because they do everything but from scratch there.
And I think sometimes they're just going too fast.
Not that I want to drag out all the, I have a couple of quick bad mouth memories.
Sure.
Or worse than the bone.
Okay, so both, so two, the first time, I think it was like one of the most I've ever been sick to my stomach and it felt like such a betrayal because I liked it so much, the place, and it was the Wendy's Super Bar.
That's what it's called. Can someone, anyone know if that's right?
They used to have a little buffet. I think it was called the Super Bar.
And it was salad, tacos, and spaghetti. And we loved it. Everyone in my family loved it. And I had it when I was like once in elementary or middle school, went to bed and just woke up in the middle of the night and just, it was just bad.
But in terms of unpleasantness, I got my wisdom teeth out.
Summer after my junior year in college. And I was, you know, on the mend for like three or four days. Like I was starting to feel better. So I went into this desk job internship I had, you know, the Monday after.
I think I had it done on a Thursday. And I was like, I think I'm okay to go into work. And it was starting to hurt. And so I just like took a Vicodin or whatever. And then it was like lunchtime. And I'm like, man, I'm starving.
I just like kind of started doing solid food again. And I went and I, because it's me, I got a kielbasa sandwich.
A big kielbasa because I just wanted some comfort food. And I bit in and it was one of the most painful sensations I've ever experienced.
Oh my God.
No spices and the salt or everything. And I just like threw it in the garbage and went to my boss and was like, I'm sorry. I have to go home.
I overestimated how I was feeling.
That's a tough surface. Like it can be pretty taut. The sausage casing.
Yeah, for sure. One of the most taut foods.
Pretty taut. Yeah. Soft to roll but taut surface. Yeah, you're right.
It's tauter. Yeah. Is there a tauter food? Mitch, you're the expert.
Hmm. I tauter. No, I mean my stone sandwich from La Brea Baker is more taut.
Stones are very taut. Yes.
I, Jason, I went out too early after I had my wisdom teeth removed and I went drinking.
And I remember just like blood leaking into my mouth from the wounds, like from the spots where I was stitched up in my mouth.
Yeah, mine was. I shouldn't have been drinking booze.
Yeah, mine stuck around. My recovery was long. I had sores for a while.
Bone spurs, little pieces of bone slowly peeking through my gums.
God, you couldn't serve. Yeah, I was going to say.
Yeah, yeah. I was using prescription grade mouthwash for like months after that.
Bone spurs in your mouth? Bone spurs, yeah.
That's wild. I was back to work like a day later after my wisdom teeth were gone.
I know everyone has a wildly different experience with that. My friend was in bed for like two weeks.
And I was back to work like the next day. It's weird how that is.
By the way, I was going to say a tot food taffy. Is taffy tot?
I think so because there's a pull to it. That seems right.
There is a pull to it, but it is also like, oh yeah, you're right. I guess I don't know. You're right.
It's something that's tight, right? Like a, oh, jerky, beef jerky.
Beef jerky. There we go. Jerky's good. Yeah, like diner steak, like diner skirt steak, I feel like.
Yeah, it's interesting though because the kobasa has like the skin, the outer skin is the tot thing.
It's almost like it has like a tot shell. Yeah.
It's like the whole item is not the same consistency. So like with a steak, obviously sometimes the outside is a little bit more cooked than the inside.
But it's hard. There has to be different classifications here is what I'm saying.
Sure. I picked something that literally you can keep stretching with taffy, but still in my mind that is a hard candy to eat.
It is. I don't know. I guess like rock crystal candy.
Which will factor into today's topic, by the way, a little spoiler. Yeah. Yeah.
They have interacted with with churros. I think maybe it's if you took taffy and pulled it over something else, like it would have the tautness of a casing.
So if you like, if you made a sausage out of taffy with the taffy lining.
Yes. How come? How come that hasn't happened yet? It should.
What would go well with it? What would be good inside? What filling do you want in a taffy sausage?
Hmm. Buttercream.
So like something soft, something something with give, you know, more than taffy, I think.
I agree. I say I vote egg.
Just just yolk.
Yeah, just a yellow yolk and not like Cadbury style.
You're talking about just actual egg.
You take it out of the shell and put it into a different shell.
That is my vote.
This is this is so far.
This podcast is a it's something for jigsaw to listen to because it sounds torturous.
Well, maybe what all this is served to do is make the idea of our topic that much sweeter.
We've had all of our worst mouth injuries that now I mean, all in any world, we'd be thrilled to think about churros.
But now how great does a churro sound to you after all that shit?
Yeah, very good.
No, 100 percent. I'm I would kill for one right now.
I want one very bad. It sucks.
Yeah, I know. This is this.
You know, it's a good we're still doing this in quarantine times for the we'll say for the historical record.
And of all the things that you can't get in the parks and they're remarkably there's no like, you know, mobile.
Service situation.
I'm sure there are places that sell churros, perhaps even superior to Disneyland churros in and around the city and other cities.
But yeah, I'm missing them a lot from theme parks right now.
And Mitch, this was your call. This was this is something you wanted to talk about.
Well, there was there as far as as far as things to.
Yeah, I mean, I think it's a good thing.
I think it's a good thing.
I feel like there's never a time I don't do it, which is fucked up because I've gone like, you know, twice in a week or whatever.
So I shouldn't shouldn't be doing it.
But, uh, getting a churro is is is the is the is the big one to me.
And I can remember so specifically the first time I ever like even heard of churros, which was before we went to the park.
I think it's the time we took up.
My family took a Winnebago down there with this with another family, my godparents family, and my godfather son Neil was just talking about churros and I didn't even know what they were.
And I put the I loved fried dough because I was a kid, you know, and then like, oh, it's kind of like fried dough, but it's got churros in it.
And it was kind of the most exciting thing I had ever heard of.
And then I can't really remember that for it because I can barely remember anything.
I mean, like, I remember parts of Disney World in my head, but I was probably like eight, seven or eight years old when we went down there this time.
So I don't know if I remember specifically.
I can't remember anything.
I mean, I remember parts of Disney World in my head, but I was probably like eight, seven or eight years old when we went down there this time.
So I don't know if I remember specifically.
I have like a vision of my head that we were near like the Country Bear Jamboree the first time I ever had one.
But I can't remember specifically.
I kind of associate them with frontier lands in general.
I feel like that's, you know, you can get them a bunch of places, but that that tends to be one in the parks.
My two spots.
I have two spots in Disneyland, but but I want to hear everyone's I want to hear everyone's churro thoughts.
Well, there are a lot more there's a lot more spots in Disneyland.
There's certainly spots in Disney World, but Disneyland, they're they're like kind of everywhere and started in the Disney form started at Disneyland, not at Disney World.
All right. All right.
Yeah. What's what are the perennial spots we feel like in the in the parks?
Where do you do it, Mitch?
My two spots are so when I get into the park, I usually now this is going to probably fuck people up because they probably don't do the same route.
But I I go to Tomorrowland first.
I go in and I take a right towards Tomorrowland and I usually get a fast pass for either Star Wars or Space Mountain.
And I just see what's available, obviously.
And then usually Space Mountain is like a thing that you have to wait the entire, you know, a few hours for or whatever, sometimes the whole day.
Exactly my route, exactly what I do.
Yeah. Do you really?
Yeah, yeah. And it's kind of good to do it because Star Tours has like if you check the weight on that, that's sort of your litmus test for everything else in the park.
Like if that's crazy, you go, oh, it's going to be bad.
And maybe there won't even be a Space Mountain option.
Yeah. Yeah, I know. That's that's an it.
Look, it's not that like it's not like this is like some sort of really thought out route.
It's basically going straight and taking your first right.
Yeah, make sense to me. Right.
But when I'm there, I usually do I'll get on the Buzz Lightyear ride, especially if that's just like a walk on because I think that's fun.
The Buzz Lightyear shooter master.
What is the bug Buzz Lightyear blaster astro blasters astro blaster.
OK. And then I'll do that.
I'll do that. I'll do that right.
And then I'll get off and I'll get a churro right.
It's basically against you guys will know exactly what I'm talking about.
But it's when you're walking towards Space Mountain and it's kind of like right there where the kind of split happens where you can go to the like to get food to the left or go towards Space Mountain to the right.
You know what I'm talking about? Oh, yeah.
It's like in front of Star Traders, the gift shop, the Star Tours gift shop.
Yes. Yeah. Yeah.
And I'll go there. I'll get myself a churro and a Coca-Cola.
So it's maybe like in your first hour in the park.
It's it's an early part of the day for you.
Yeah. Usually the thing is, is that like driving down there, I never want to I never really want to get food.
And if I do get food, I'll tell you what I do if I do get food.
But but driving down there, I like I'm like, oh, I want to just eat theme park food the entire day.
And so like a lot of times you go down there, you know, it's an hour ride or whatever hour plus.
And so a lot of times you'll grab something like a coffee and a bagel or whatever.
But if I if I if I don't eat anything at all and I'm just driving on this route, that will be like kind of my first snack of the day is a churro and a Coca-Cola.
The healthiest of all breakfasts.
Yeah, that's a lot of sugar, Mitch.
It's a lot of sugar. I mean, hey, in my mind, Jason, it's a theme park day.
I'm doing I'm doing the parks. I'm right there with you.
No, trust me. I mean, I a lot of times if I'm going early in the morning, I I may have already had my share.
I may have gotten coffee and donuts or coffee and Danish on the way down before I left the city.
And then then are you still doing a churro or no?
I don't I I get a churro every now and then, but they're not usually one of my go tos.
Yeah, interesting.
I agree with Jason. Not one of my go tos either.
This makes so much sense because it is mine.
And I feel like we're often on separate sides of the tree scale.
And I get churros way more than than anything else.
What are you? What are you?
What are you guys? What are the what are the for Carlson and Jason?
What is a thing when you go to the park that you get almost every time you go?
Jason, go ahead.
I usually I mean, I'm a big chocolate guy, so I'm usually one something from either one of the candy stores,
like one of the confectionaries or some sort of elevated ice cream, not just a scoop,
not just a scoop, either like a scoop with a chocolate cone or a sundae or a milkshake.
Yeah, because you're like you're saying it's a theme park day.
Some of the like little chocolate cake or treats back in Star Wars, back in Galaxy's Edge,
the little there's these little chocolate and passion fruit puff balls.
Those are very good.
I'll say what's the Ronto wraps have entered the permanent.
I get it every time for me. It's now on the list.
Yeah, Ronto wrap is like the best thing.
And then the vegetarian option is really good.
Like Ronto wrap is I that might be the thing I'm craving from the parks the most right now.
Yeah, it's so good that that that for me, you guys know that I that I love pizza port.
I'm a fan of pizza port.
And yes, we were I was trying to remember if we talked about this on the show
or is this just a sidebar conversation with you because that's like that's a topic we really want to do with you.
But I feel like we all got to go down to do.
I don't want to do some bullshit Zoom version of the pizza port episode.
Right. No, yeah, we got we got to go down and see in the pizza.
I genuinely like the pizza port and I like big theme parky slices of pizza.
And that is exactly what pizza port is.
It's a big fucking looks like a looks like it's from a movie.
It's I mean, it's perfect.
And look, it's not the best pizza in the world, but it's I think it's damn good.
And they got giant pepperoni slices on there.
It's a blast. I love pizza port.
But I like to wrap my head over that.
We all have thoughts very, very early in the podcast.
Mike and I went down one day and ate at pizza port to try the hamburger pizza.
And I remember we sent pictures to Scott and he was so horrified.
Kind of rightly so because it did look like a big pile of garbage.
I mean, that was a special event pizza.
So special limited time offering.
Yeah, they got specially shitty.
I think my thought and I don't want to ruin the episode because we will do that as its own thing.
But I think I love what you're saying, Mitch, and you have me sold on the idea of it.
The idea sounds great, but I feel like the reality is lacking.
I think that pizza over the year, I feel like I've watched it get more expensive, smaller slices and shittier quality.
Like just every year they shave off a little bit, a little bit until like a pretty well, that's a five dollar hunk of pizza.
That's all right. It's pretty good.
Now it's I feel like nine dollars and the quality is a little questionable.
I always I always just feel like I can get two of those.
I can get two slices of pizza, poor pizza and which is I mean, you're right that they have gotten smaller, but they're pretty decently big.
And I'll be good for the rest of the I mean, I'll be I'll be fine.
And I'm sure I got a churro on that. That's a theme park day to me.
I'm very happy.
I'm very happy. So kind of serviceable, like quick salads at pizza port, too.
That's like, oh, I just need some vegetables.
I've been eating garbage.
Those big pieces of garlic bread in the red bag.
Delicious garlic. So garlic like it's garlic breadsticks, breadsticks.
Yeah. See, people like pizza port. You like it.
It's good.
I know how this goes, where if I don't like it, then not only are the other hosts against me, but 85 percent of our audience.
So this is the beginning of the pizza part is good movement.
And I recognize that there's better pizza on property.
There we go. There's better pizza.
But sometimes you want like school cafeteria pizza.
And where where is this better pizza? Where is it?
The pizza, the Vietnam poli, the pizza in downtown Disney is like actually like very solid pizza.
Mm hmm. See, not on the not on the lot.
Get out of here. That's yeah.
You want it. You don't want to leave the park is what you're like.
If you're stuck in there, those gates, you know, I don't care.
I did. Look, I think you know what, Jason, I'm sorry to say this, but I think eating in downtown Disney is trash.
You say this having done our Earl of Sandwich episode.
You know what? That was bullshit, too.
I can't. My ears are flutter.
I can't handle this.
There is there's good there's good food and downtown.
But I don't know. I want to eat in the parks.
I like eating in the parks.
And it's funny because I don't eat at a ton of places in the parks.
I don't eat at a ton of places in the parks.
I pizza port is one of like one of my main spots.
And then I have eaten right there near near the like at in Tomorrowland at the like that little state, those stands there, which I like.
Basic burger place.
Yeah, the basic burgers and stuff like that, which people also kind of don't love.
I don't know what's what part of this what part of the park is best for food.
But I will say if I don't get a churro in Tomorrowland near near that the gift shop for Star Tours, I'm getting it outside the Haunted Mansion.
I think you guys I think you guys know the card I'm talking about.
Oh, yeah. That will be a little later in the day if I made my way over that way.
Interesting. You know, it's weird.
I feel like I don't typically go to either of those.
I feel I think my primary spot is one of the ones in front of the castle.
And that's like a night like I feel like I get a nice iconic Disneyland moment because often you're rushing past the castle to get to other things.
And that's the thing that makes you stop in that nice, you know, square area, the hub and then be there for a minute.
And it's nice to be holding that big churro and looking up at the castle and kind of being in the heart of the place and doing a primary Disney show.
Doing a primary Disneyland thing.
That's what that's what I call a panic churro spot, because for me, if I'm getting one from there, it's because I hadn't gotten a churro all day.
And then like my fat guy mentality kicks in and I'm like, I need a churro.
And it's like me desperately trying to get one on the way out of the park or like crossing through lands or something like that.
So I like this strategy and psychology is all interesting.
That's a yeah, that's a panic churro spot for me. I truly I think that I think churros are the things I've eaten the most at Disney.
I love them, especially if they're look, if it's a hot, fresh churro.
Come on. It's unbeatable.
You know, that's a great point.
There there's a I feel like there's a big difference between like a hot, fresh churro and one that's been like hanging out for a little while.
Yes. And that is that is a huge that is that's a huge issue.
I mean, like there you can if you get if you get a cold churro, still good, still good.
Yeah, it's it's it's not it's not it's it's it's it's it's a bummer.
It bums me out. Sometimes, you know, if I get a cold churro, that means I got to go searching for a hot churro after that.
I got to get two in a day.
That's fair.
I'll tell you what I I mean, the place I like the churros in is they've been doing like in terms of limited time stuff Sundays with like a churro cut in half and wedged into a Sunday.
And that's a place I like to see a churro.
You can kind of tell that like this the margins on this or the raw cost of the ingredients are like next to nothing because a churro Sunday with a churro wedged in it is not that much more money than a Sunday without a churro wedged in it.
But in my mind, it does elevate it. Similarly, like at some of the sit down restaurants, they'll do like bite sized churro bites with the dipping sauce.
And I love a dipping sauce. See, I agree with Jason.
Oh, yeah. I was I'm just going to like I think sometimes when I get if I get a regular churro, sometimes it does feel like, well, it's not so fresh.
And it's it's a lot. There's a lot of it to eat.
And sometimes it feels like a little bit of a chore.
I usually like to split it in general.
But if there's a sort of specialty, if there's some specialty one, which when we were doing 80s at the 80s night at Disneyland, there was a Reese's peanut butter Reese's peanut butter like pieces churro.
And we're like, well, that sounds like interesting. Let's get it.
We got it. It was not good.
But we wanted to try it.
And then but on the other side of that is like a year or two prior, my friend was out here and there was a s'mores churro with a little like marshmallow dipping sauce.
And that was excellent. See, that's interesting because I was looking up all of the like different flavor churros, which Disney has gotten into in the last few years.
And I don't know. I think there's two issues.
One, like some of the flavors like I got to say cookies and cream, a solid ice cream, a wonderful in a blizzard or a milkshake.
But cookies and cream as a flavor. Not my favorite.
Not not one of my go to when it's just like they just shove some crushed up cookies and some goo on there.
And then the other thing you run into with these kind of like variants of churros is you're creeping to six dollars or more.
Like the value. Yeah. The perceived value is starting to disappear.
Regular churros are at four seventy five at Disneyland already.
And Jason has an app to track this like a stock sap.
I looked I did look this up. I looked this up and I wrote this all down.
The dipping sauces will get you probably around like five fifty.
And yeah, I don't know. I just the perceived value in my mind sometimes.
I feel like I feel I feel like a churro shared is a really good option, although it goes pretty fast between two people.
I have I have I have a lot of thoughts on what you guys have all said.
I can probably just please I can just I can just sum it up by saying I'm angry.
Oh, boy. Oh, what happened?
Where did where where were you made angry?
No, no, not really angry.
But also we didn't stop down for my dumb joke enough, Carlson, that it's a churro when you have to eat a cold one.
Oh, that's great. Yeah, that's really good.
The connection is a little my connection is kind of going a little in and out.
So I apologize. Yeah, I think the fuzziness of our connection made the enunciation tougher.
I missed it, too. I blame Zoom.
Well, although I know it's good that now that I've brought it up multiple times and gotten churro out there, I think that people are just probably bent over slapping their knees right now.
They've paused the show probably.
They probably only show us pause.
During these trying times, Mike Mitchell has given us some relief, some solace, just some laughs.
The comedians are saving America's spirits.
All with churro.
Who would have thought it would be that easy?
I don't like I don't like a couple things you guys said.
One, I don't like churros and ice cream.
I'm sorry, Jason.
OK, first of all, it's cool.
It's cooling down the churro to my you're getting a cold churro no matter what.
And I don't like flavor churros.
I don't like dipping sauces.
If I get a churro, I want straight up churro.
I want to I want pure churro.
Pure churro.
I want pure churro.
That's what I say when I get to the front of the line.
You're going to give me a beer churro.
I genuinely just like the old classic version of it.
I now this being said, my godfather's son, who hyped up churros for me, he's he he owns
a restaurant in Quincy and he had a restaurant in in Braintree at one point.
Oh, wait, no, Weymouth Landing.
Shit.
It doesn't matter.
But he better get it right.
In Weymouth Landing.
That's where I was.
And he and he he was the only one who was in the restaurant.
And he had churros as it was like it was called Passport and he had a bunch of like different
foods from all over the world.
It was kind of what the idea of the restaurant was.
And it was a fantastic restaurant.
And there was a churro dessert and it had dipping sauces and there was like chocolate
and caramel and everything.
And I did enjoy those there.
But when I'm in when I'm in Disney, I don't need when it comes to dip and save it for
a pretzel with cheese because I don't need I don't need dipping for the day.
Mitch, America, I believe, has agreed with you or Disneyland guests have because I read
somewhere that they did try to do dipping sauces as an add on option in the carts and
that they were they were pretty roundly rejected.
I think they weren't loved by the by crowds.
But also what does this thing say?
It said they're they're difficult, difficult to sell and hard to keep warm.
So it actually might be a little bit of a surprise to me.
Difficult to sell and hard to keep warm.
So it actually might have been more logistics than the audience rejecting them.
But they did not take off at Disneyland.
Yeah, that makes sense.
I mean, like I and I and I love the Mickey pretzel with that is actually probably my
second snack as far as as Disney snacks go as a Mickey pretzel with the cheese.
Yeah.
Yeah, I do like that.
I don't get that often, but I do like that.
I like the cream cheese one, the stuffed one.
Oh, wow.
Yeah, that one's real good.
What is it stuffed with?
Like sweet cream cheese.
Really?
I think there might be a peppery.
There might be a pepper Jack stuffed one, too.
Can you get the then you get the dipping cheese as well and dip it?
No, you don't get the dipping cheese.
I think it's like one or the other.
Oh, you probably could get it.
You probably order it separate.
Sure.
Yeah.
That's an add on though.
Right. Yeah.
It doesn't add on.
Yeah.
Oh, you're paying for it.
You're going to you're going to pay.
You get whatever you want.
You're going to pay.
Mitch, I'm going to make you more angry.
How do you do you know about the Caliente churro?
No, but please do tell me is there cheese in it?
No, it's kind of it's like rolled in red red hots, red hots or spicy cheese.
Spicy Cheetos that I have tried that one as well.
It's insane.
It's one of the craziest things man has ever attempted.
And man's hubris in creation.
It does. It's like it's the sweetest, sugariest, craziest thing.
There's no way you can eat even like a quarter of it.
I feel like.
Oh, have you tried it?
I haven't.
No, I haven't tried it.
No.
Honestly, that's just it sounds like an abomination.
I would never I mean, like even when it is like I've been tempted by like, oh, the strawberry churro.
But I just I know that I just love the classic churro.
There's nothing better.
I don't know about add-ons in general.
It seems like if I had to get Mitch's hard, no, I don't know if I'm hard.
No, but I haven't had a great example to change my mind.
Mike, are you sort of like amenable to it?
But you're also you haven't had a lot of success.
Well, as I said, I seem to I from earlier when we were talking about treats, I am generally I try to do one treat.
If it's a big day at Disney, one treat a day.
And usually I save that till the end of the day.
And usually and I mentioned this before, it's usually my two scoop cone with the sugars on the outside with the sprinkles.
That's usually what I get.
And I rarely do.
I probably literally at Disney have a churro a year.
Probably like probably that we're pretty opposite.
This is crazy.
So I just it doesn't it's not in my top three, I think.
So I'm I'm I totally recognize that if it's warm and it's good, the regular churro is delicious.
And I've had a lot of now I've tried these other versions and most of them fail.
I do do think that's smores when they had that I think was limited time is I think maybe I even liked it better than a regular one and it had a dipping sauce.
So I'm not I like the experimentation with this, but I think probably in general they haven't really figured out a formula to like completely put new flavors in these things.
Like most of these things fail.
These different versions.
It's hard. I think it's hard to like, you know, it's like it's it's science here and it's you know, you work very hard trying to come up with a new equation, like a new formula.
And it just doesn't work.
Most of the time it doesn't work adapting the churro into a new form.
I feel like like I feel like it's like it's just as an American thing to get like a new mainstream snack that would fit in at a theme park.
I feel like I just remember being around when or, you know, being a kid when when Buffalo Chicken became more popular and you saw more places and yeah.
I felt even that when that was happening, it felt like is this going to work like Buffalo Chicken like and I mean, of course I loved it, but it felt it felt to have like a mainstay sort of snack or dessert at a theme park.
I mean, I'm trying to think of like for me in my eyes with Disney. What are the rundowns of snacks? You got pretzels. You got churros. You got ice cream. You got pickles.
What are some what what are some newer like within the last 10 years besides Ronto wraps or something?
They've got like a lot of different cookies. They have those big like they have a lot of things in the confectionary like they'll have like a big piece of chocolate with peanut butter inside.
They have fudge. They'll have these like I like these things called tiger tails that are like marshmallow with like sugar on the outside that looks like it's the Cheshire cat's tail.
That's pretty good or Tigger's tail at Disneyland. A lot of the carts, the outdoor carts have the chimichangas or the the corn.
The yeah, not quite a low take corn, but kind of similar.
That's a macaroon presence. There's a Matterhorn macaroon. Although I have found that out from an article. I didn't really know this macaroon before, so I don't know if that's a primary.
Oh, delicious. Yeah, it's a coconut mac macaroon that looks like a little mountain with icing on top.
But then the French macaroons have they've been making those more in the parks.
Don't you think that churros are like a what's a good way to describe it? A load bearing snack? That's not good.
Yeah, I like that. Yes, a pillar foundational. A foundation snack.
I like a found like ones that you can find all around everywhere, not specific to like certain parts of the park, but are could kind of float around.
That's a good point. Yes, because some some of these things feel like they need to be in certain areas, but there's like there's nowhere where a churro is out of place.
Yes. And also, I got to say this. We haven't talked about it yet.
Ease of the ease of snacking with a churro. You get the little piece of paper.
You got a big stick. You just you just taking a big bite out of that thing. You know, you don't have to get any of the cinnamon sugar on there.
And on yourself by on there is what I mean.
Not yet. That's great. Your body. There's no there's there's no dipping involved.
You just you just eating the thing straight up. I think it's I think it's just an easy snack for me to eat.
Yeah. Well, much like the the revelation in the now classic film, The Founder with Michael Keaton about the founding of McDonald's, the revelation that the burger does not have extra plates or containers.
It comes in its own wrapper. I think it's a similar simplicity to the churro.
Yes. Yeah. Yeah. The ice cream when you're eating an ice cream, especially with two scoops, it's a race against the clock.
Yep. It's it's good, but it is it can be a bit stressful if maybe you're not feeling like you want to like furiously lick.
Oh, yeah. Especially if you're in Florida. Man, watch out. Yeah, that thing.
It's toast, but it's sure. Oh, you can stroll and you can split to major functions.
And can I also just say this? It's not too hot that it's an issue on a really hot day.
It's not an overly hot product where, like, you're like, oh, man, I don't really want to, like, have a bowl of soup while I'm walking around.
It's not soup in a bread bowl. That's right. It's not super bread bowl.
Look, am I now trying to convince you that churros are the best snack in the Disneyland parks by the end of this?
Yes. And I think that we're getting there. I think I'm getting closer.
I feel like it's an argument. It's not an argument towards people who don't like churros.
It's about like moving it from number four to maybe number two. Yes. Yeah, I guess I am not arguing against it.
I just think I being at the park, here's here's I think that perhaps the bare bones presentation of the churro is part of maybe why it's not in my top three or five or something like an ice cream has a lot of colors.
It sprinkles have a lot of colors. If I'm getting a cookie or something, it's got I like a cookie with a lot of different frosting on it.
I do think perhaps when I'm in the park, I am looking for something that feels a little more fantastical.
So the churro itself is pretty standard. It's a brown and a sugar, but it doesn't sort of evoke even the I know it's such a theme park food, but it doesn't give me like the feeling like I'm in some sort of magical candy land.
It's a big long stick that you chew on.
It doesn't have a face on it. It doesn't have sprinkles. It doesn't have many colors. It's good.
I'm just saying if it was like a magic, like maybe it was like Merlin's wand. Oh my God churro and it had a little color or something.
Then I'm like waving it around and pretending I'm a I'm a wizard. And then I'm feeling like I'm really part of this whole magical Disney Day.
Or like in Japan, it's shaped like a Mickey, you know, it's shaped like Mickey's and it's classic.
If you look at it, if you look down the barrel, it looks like a which I don't think I realized till our treats episode recently. Yes. Yeah.
In Tokyo, specifically in Tokyo specifically. Yeah. Yeah.
That's the other thing. Like I Mitch, I'd be inclined to agree with you, but I feel like the the churro would get knocked out by the classic Mickey ice cream bar in my at least in my concern.
The Mickey ice cream bar is great. Yeah. And also I just I just want to quickly ask, did Carlson mean Merlin from the sword in the stone?
You wanted to be like his wand? Yeah, I look I'm just spitballing here. I doesn't have to be Merlin from sword in the stone's wand.
But I'm just saying he is he's one of the first one. You know, it could be a fairy godmother's wand.
Well, hold on. My question to you guys is Jason, your favorite snack of the park is what was it? A bowl of sweet cream or something?
A taxi sausage. I would probably go like a sundae like like an ice cream sundae. Some sort of a soft drink cup filled with sweet cream.
If I remember if I remember correctly, your skittles.
I like a I like a Disney like shopping bag full of skittles.
Mike brings a thermos of ice and he's like, can you just a shopping bag of skittles so I can combine it with my icy thermos?
Yeah, I dip each skittle in a different flavor, a different color part of the icy.
I just feel like look, the interesting snacks that's over in California Adventure.
If I'm going to get a bread bowl with mac and cheese in it or a cone rather a bread cone with mac and cheese, I'm going over to California Adventure.
And that there's a reason that that's not available everywhere.
Right. Like, I love that. I love the mac and cheese cone.
Yes, I do, too.
I mean, like, but Churro is just a classic. It's so great.
And I might I might bring this up, Mike.
I agree with you that there might be if there was some way to put a stamp on the Disney.
I like that in Japan, if you look down the barrel, it's a Mickey shape.
I think that's cool. But it's not like it's still it's a subtle detail, so subtle that I missed it entirely.
And so it would be nice if there was something to, you know, if it had Mickey ears on the end or something.
But the whole thing, if it was a color and if it was flavored, as we've established, I think the flavors are no good.
So I think just for taste, it has to stay just just basic and cinnamon.
And as it comes, you could do a food, you could do a food coloring, though, that wouldn't affect the taste.
I suppose. But I you know, it feels that feels weird to me.
I'll go back to my as much as it was one of the best moments of my life to have a blue wine on the table.
I was drinking it and going, but why this is just added food coloring.
I kind of, you know, as much as it looks cool, I do.
I know it's just white wine with some blue blue in it.
What is the purpose of this blue?
I want I want some flavor out of my fake color.
Right. So I have just I just Google this because I thought I remembered it and I was right.
I am texting everyone.
There was I think it might be limited time.
But they were selling lightsaber churros.
Yeah, I remember. Yeah, that's good.
So I've so I think I think they were just for an event and I've sent you a picture of them.
So that is closer to what I'm talking about.
I do think like it's a neon red and neon blue.
I don't even necessarily need to be that different in color.
But I do think that's just just just just just the food coloring that those still taste the same.
Basically, those those I have to I have to check.
I don't know that to be the case.
Do you guys recall when there was a little trend of rose gold items in the park?
Yeah, I sure do. Pink and gold.
And I did you I think I might have been with you, Mike, when you had a rose gold churro.
Am I misremembering this?
It's possible.
But did I split it with Lindsay?
I don't know.
She's usually the one that likes the churro, I think a little bit more than me.
So generally, if we had it, it was like maybe she wanted it and then we split it.
I don't remember.
I don't have the memory of having the rose gold.
I might be able to.
That churro was for millennials, so it probably tastes like freaking avocado toast.
Or ass or ass.
Carlson, I just want to say to you that I and I mean, and Jason, both of you, you're both volunteers.
I can't believe you're not I can't believe you're not really churro guys.
I mean, it truly it flips my entire worldview about you guys.
I I I I'm shook to my core.
I thought you I thought you I just clearly just assumed you were both churro guys.
Well, I'm sorry to let you down.
I hear I like I I don't want to seem like I don't like them either.
It's like I also like and these are I think these are in the same family.
I am a big fan of those cinnamon twists at Taco Bell.
I love those.
So you like so you so hold on.
So you like the worst churro?
Well, I'm saying that I like it.
The family and they don't have a lot of other options as far as dessert at Taco Bell.
I mean, they do have a lot of other options.
But I like a little of that.
So I'm just saying I'm just defending myself that I like I'm in the family here.
I just there's stuff makes me feel more part of the special special world than a churro.
I also have a sense of cinnamon.
I find kind of irritating to the gums in large quantities.
I love cinnamon toast crunch.
Cinnamon is a bad mouth memory.
What are you talking about?
But like it irritates.
It can irritate.
Cinnamon irritates you?
Yes, you have a little cut or something or like cinnamon toast crunch.
If you don't let it like soak in milk and like the specific you're eating cinnamon when you have a cut or eating kielbasa when you just had dental surgery or having a banana at 10 a.m.
I read you know you can overdo it on cinnamon.
There's a reason dentists tell you like don't buy cinnamon toothpaste.
It's it's it's not great.
It's caustic.
Wait, is that a real thing?
I have had dentists say like, yeah, don't get cinnamon.
Why would you have cinnamon?
For sure don't have cinnamon toothpaste.
It was a trend for a while.
I know what you mean.
It's like medicine.
That's cinnamon.
Can I quickly can I quickly ask have you moved on to bubblegum bubblegum toothpaste?
Well, I'm on the birthday cake toothpaste.
Cinnamon tree is a classic.
I think I feel like cinnamon toast.
Obviously, when you're when you're just cinnamon toast with butter and cinnamon on top of it.
Yeah, great tree.
I don't know if I like stuff that's cold as much that cinnamon like I don't love cinnamon cereals.
I think I enjoy cinnamon toast crunch, but it wasn't my favorite.
I like frosted flakes.
I like a like a more sugar like I mean, they're all sugar based but kind of like, oh, it's corn flakes and sugar.
I'm fine with that.
Cinnamon cinnamon toast crunch.
Not my favorite.
I still like it.
But I tried cinnamon coke and cinnamon Coca Cola is is bad.
It was it was not good at all.
Like I I I I I I think I enjoy cinnamon stuff when it's warm or hot warm to hot.
Mitch, what do you think about horchata?
The cold rice drink usually have very cinnamon forward flavor there.
Do you know what?
That is probably you got me.
That's probably the one cold cinnamon thing that I really like that I do.
I like a lot.
I don't even know if I love it, but I do really like it.
Yeah, I had cinnamon toast crunch yesterday.
I like cinnamon.
I'm this is you like like cinnamon.
You like cinnamon toast crunch.
You like Taco Bell things and not.
And I like cutting my mouth and pouring cinnamon into the wound.
I think it feels good.
Cinnamon toast crunch is in the top five cereals.
But like I can't I can't overdo it.
I can't overdo it in the way that golden grams do not irritate in the way that cinnamon toast crunch do another all timer.
The double scoop ice cream with a cone with sprinkles.
There's so much going on.
I can get a I can get a sherbet scoop.
I can get a cookie dough scoop.
I can then enjoy eating the sprinkles off the side of the cone.
There's so many different things there that stimulate my mind as well as my palate that I enjoy.
Like it's just such a ultimate theme park experience.
It feels so indulgent as a kid.
I used to like looking at a cartoon strip with like 10 different ice cream scoops on a cone and I'm not I'm not doing that obviously but I'm getting the closest.
Yeah.
What cartoons what cartoon strips are you reading.
What it was probably did Dagwood ever have a big ice cream cone in addition to a big sandwich.
You know he did.
Joghead.
Joghead was definitely.
I had a bunch of shakes bunch of scoops.
He had so many others.
I'm for sure if you look up Joghead lots of scoops there has to be a picture of him.
I will Google it right now.
So I always like that.
So that's it's just nothing is going to beat that for me.
It has to be visually busier for you like a baby's mobile.
I am a lot like a baby.
That's called eye memory Scott.
It's a cousin of mouth.
I'm a little bit of a
entertain me snack.
I'm sure.
Oh OK.
Cinnamon brown.
I have bored done straight line garbage.
Put on a show for me snack.
I know.
So on top of that I can't believe that you guys chose the Taco Bell cinnamon twists which
are like they're they're like the empty shell of sure they're like if I hate this analogy
I would be like I would just snapped churros right before they were about to break apart.
They would be cinnamon twists from Taco Bell.
Cinnamon twists shells.
They pay you to cart them away.
They're like please please we cannot get rid of.
We've had the same stock since 1989.
And they're still good.
They still taste good.
I've sent you all a photo of Joghead.
He's got one two three four five six scoops on an ice cream cone.
This is this is a guy.
This is one of my childhood heroes.
Can you will you do Joghead's line.
I'm going to do the other line and just let's just enact this little scene of the cover you sent us.
Sure.
It's very it's very 70s is what we're looking at.
It says teen disco tech light show.
Man I dig having a lot of wild colors in my fingertips.
All right.
And I have my tongue sticking out.
It's like I'm like licking my lips and I'm holding that ice cream cone and I say so do I.
Great scene.
That was that was better than Riverdale.
Great.
But hold on a second.
Hold on.
I.
What.
Hold on one moment here.
Yeah.
Joghead likes the ice cream.
First of all Carlson you kind of look like Joghead.
He's a tall man.
Yeah.
And he and he and he's attracted to the color of the ice cream.
You may be a lot like Joghead and I see a lot of similarities is what I'm saying.
Mike Mike looks like Joghead.
I behave like Joghead.
We're a dyad.
We're a dyad in the.
In the river force.
You're you're are you Kylo and I'm Ray.
I guess that's how I do it.
By the way by Jason you really should not bring up new Star Wars when Mitch is that is a dangerous.
That is really dangerous.
We don't want to get off on a bad thing here.
Well we don't want to get go down this route but Mike you you set up a transition perfectly with this Joghead cover of the teen disc teen disco tech light show goes right to the origin of Disneyland churros.
Oh right right.
I'm assuming we all saw this apocryphal perfect perfect story.
This is what yes Mitch get ready to hear the tale of how the churro came to Disneyland.
Oh wow.
It's a lovely story.
Jason go ahead.
Well OK so there was a man named Jim Loman and he was in charge of the food and beverage services at Disney's Fantasyland and they were about to open a teen nightclub that one week we talked about a lot on the show called Videopolis.
Yeah.
And it's it's so fun.
It's very 80s.
It's it's a lot of cast off L.A. Olympics televisions rigged up to show the triangle's purple and teal triangles all the big like fonts and stars of the day.
And he needed some sort of like snack to sell back there to teens and he attended a race at the Long Beach Grand Prix and saw a churro booth and that it was very popular and you only needed a very small warming oven for it.
And he found the company who made it reached out said Disneyland was interested but they knew the churros they were selling were only six inches so they knew they need a little a little more Disney oomph to it a little more Disney magic.
So they asked them to make it 12 inches and pretty much an immediate hit.
The story goes that like as they were rolling out the cart they were going to test it out in frontier land first and just the smell of cinnamon sugar like cause like 30 people to follow that cart and then they just kept adding churro carts like the Pied Piper.
Yeah.
They could they could have driven those people right into the river right into the rivers of America.
Jason when was this what year was this.
This would have been 85 around 1980.
The churro was born at Disneyland in the summer of 85 right when I was born.
And shortly before me and the who's the other big oh as we I alluded to at the top of the show.
So one of the big changes over the years of how they did this eventually as they added more and more churro carts they roped it into like the outdoor food and beverage vending along with like the popcorn and the ice cream carts and that sort of thing.
But the original churro carts were loaded up with six propane tanks each and they would run out and they'd have to reload it.
And the other thing is propane is explosive.
That's insane.
Yeah.
So this operated by teens mostly teens wheeling around a bunch of propane in a theme park propane wielding teens.
And now you're opening your opening makes even more sense.
Jason I thought you were just being funny.
Yeah.
It was not just a non sequitur.
It was a very very specific reference to the story.
Jim Lohman also kind of got my ass in terms of some of my complaints about churros getting more expensive.
He he is quoted as saying you know people wondering like well food's a little pricey at Disneyland and the price of churros it's just cinnamon sugar and dough.
It's like a kind of a doughnut basically.
And he says it's either low food prices and pay to watch shows and watch entertainment or higher food prices so that all that stuff can be wrapped up into one.
So I mean it's fair enough kind of kind of fair enough.
But they they also he includes in that fireworks live entertainment and clean restrooms.
I'm hoping you would have clean restrooms regardless.
I'm sure of money.
You make them cheaper and now there's shit on the ground.
Jim Lohman also responsible for the barbecue skewers skewers at Bengal Barbecue.
And what VIP is this guy a Disney legend.
He was that he I don't know if he's still at the company but it was something like multiple decades like he worked worked for them was still working for them in the 2010s.
And he met his wife a long time ago at the at the Tahitian Terrace and then she like helped them figure like in their kitchen they figured out the Bengal Barbecue menu together.
So the whole family there's maybe there maybe there are PTR legends.
Yeah I think they are.
I mean we all have the official ceremony sometime this summer.
I assume we'll be at the Anaheim Hotel.
So yeah and be a distance with markers and you know it'll be it'll be perfectly safe.
Yeah very safe. Yeah.
See I can't. How are you even asking if he's a legend.
This is your Carlson you're a man with pure pure pure pure pure hatred in your heart.
I can't believe your heart.
I hate your heart.
I don't hurt her.
I hate in my heart.
That's not true.
It is true.
Stronger ice cream love.
Love the love for the ice cream is stronger in my heart.
That's all ice cream.
Come on ice cream is little baby.
I look I love ice cream.
But you say babies look sometimes for babies and I love it and I'm a big baby and I like to get I like to eat ice cream.
I think you're trashing ice.
So this is gonna be more controversial than your force awakens opinion.
Well Mike I know you love all three of those films very much.
Of course. Would you like to elaborate.
I said that I said that I loved Rondo wraps.
That is the truth.
I love that's the first thing you've liked in the Star Wars universe and decades.
Rondo wraps are look I thought BB8 was like an impressive toy and it was only until I found out that they turned him into like a police robot recently that I kind of.
I've been like everything I kind of caught this.
That was the idea of the technology.
The company yeah the company that made the BB8 is also now making like drones.
So now there will be like BB8 drones on the streets.
It's a if you see one don't go near it.
Yeah.
We live in a dystopia in many ways but yeah.
We already have to push the postmates bots into the river.
It's not going to be any river left soon.
Well these robots in it.
I have not I have not I have not written the I've not been able to ride the new Star Wars.
Rise of the Resistance.
Yeah I haven't I have not I have not been on that ride yet.
So my judgment of Galaxy's Edge I just still kind of wish that Galaxy's Edge was.
I like I said I wish there was a Cloud City restaurant and I wish that there was like Hoth and different parts of the like I wish they went so all out on Star Wars land.
Why wouldn't you.
You're Disney you own you have more money than anyone else on earth.
Why not go crazy with it.
I had more money than anyone else.
About two months ago it's mostly tied up in like Saudi Arabia at this point.
They got some fridge loans.
They bought a lot of the debt.
Mitch I'll have to dig this up and send it to you but there there there was an interview with a former like executive from the Florida parks and he talked about how Disney MGM studios there was a plan to kind of make like half half like I think it was often half Tatooine sort of leading back ending it around Star Tours or no I think was Tatooine and Endor.
And then that all kind of got scrapped once once Disney eventually bought Lucasfilm outright.
And so cool.
God damn it.
Mitch I sent you that video that when they were going to do Lucas port.
Yes.
That to me is that video is heartbreaking.
It's heartbreaking video.
Wait explain it for the audience.
So there was a new information to me that like Lucas was going to sort of oversee Tomorrowland in a way.
And it was going to be called Lucasport.
I mean I know he was he obviously with Captain EO and Star Tours was getting a more of an elevated profile.
But then there was a Star Wars roller coaster that I really wasn't aware of and it had photos from it like stuff that would have been on it and it was like you could choose your own path on the roller coaster.
And basically you were going through you know Dagobah you're going through the like the core of the Death Star.
It looked like sort of your ultimate like original trilogy dream for a Star Wars ride.
Like what it did seem like exactly what Mitch would be the intent of the end.
And I'm sorry you know I thought you're talking to Scott about his dream for Star Wars right.
Yes.
No no no no.
Well it was for me too because architecturally oh my God that was the most like Epcot 80s Disney future building.
I am upset that there is no Lucas board for sure.
Yeah.
Yeah no no that that that that is that 100 percent is that is what I I wanted more than anything.
And I still want and I hope that they I mean like whatever.
There's a lot of there's a lot of there's a lot of stuff that is that is for real impressive about Galaxy's Edge and it is it is cool.
I just I just thought it was going to be more and maybe that it will be more with that with the hotel and everything and that will change things.
But I think you'll rise of the resistance is very impressive Mitch and I'm sure you'll be down there soon as Disneyland opens back up because you've been a big proponent that coronavirus is a hoax and you're not going to get sick.
It's not.
Open back up.
That's what I said.
Day one I've been saying open back up.
The virus can't be worse than the cure.
Yeah.
The cure can't be worse than the disease.
Mitch said that and then trumped by I think saw his tweet and then started saying it.
Yeah.
I want to push I want to I'm going to I'm just going to tell people that.
Every time I'm down at the park I have a churro and I haven't and I haven't gotten COVID-19 yet.
Churro is a remedy.
I'm just saying there might there's something there there might be something there.
There's a curative name there's something curative about it.
Like hydroxy chloropin whatever that's called.
Yeah it did.
Do you know it doesn't made you get COVID-19 so very well maybe the cure.
I just that's that's all I'm saying.
So I'm sorry you go ahead.
No no no you go.
I was going to say like if there was a churro place nearby how like to your apartment how often would you get one do you think.
That's a good question because there was.
Oh I know exactly what you're talking about and I didn't like that place.
I didn't like that place either and it was like such a it was like such like a in the L.A. way of like oh there here is this like it was called churro burro.
And I don't want to say I didn't like a place that has now gone out of business.
I feel bad but they basically made churro ice cream sandwiches and that's all they did and they took over that they took over a place called I think it was called Ramekin.
Which was just a dessert place and I thought was like fantastic and no one ever went there but it was like they just would they they they serve like different desserts there and like we'll give you like like a like a bread pudding or something like like hot desserts too.
It was great and no one really ever went there and then churro burro opened up and it was strictly just like these churro ice cream sandwiches and I was like oh there's not enough variety for me.
And also like I said I don't like mixing the cold with the with the churro and I didn't and I didn't think the place was was that great and it's gone out of business and that sucks.
So every every now and then there is a street cart around in Los Angeles little street carts that have churros and they're really good.
Yes. Yeah they were.
Yeah they were yeah they were there I mean like BS Tacaria had great churros.
Yeah. And they have now since closed but I think they're reopening at some point there's there's places where you can get some great local great churros here.
But but I place.
Yeah.
There's one other Disney churro question I had for everyone.
Has anyone venture Mitch you've already made your feelings about downtown Disney clear.
Has anyone tried the California churro company carts in downtown Disney.
No.
It is like it is there's a lot of carts in downtown Disney which we barely mentioned in the downtown Disney ordeal because they're so impulse by but there there is like a different kind of churro in downtown Disney and
to me it's just not canon like they've got so many flavors of churro and I'm like there's no way this is going to be.
I'm like I'm liking what you're saying here I like this this is you're right.
It just doesn't feel right it just doesn't feel can or and then there's like you know popcorn filled popcorn like it's just a little off like it's not the same stuff as in the park it's a little strange.
They have like a fruity pebbles churro right or they yeah.
That's something I would try and it would be not as good as my mind would imagine it.
They have grape soda they looks like they have watermelon I don't know about any of this.
I don't watermelon sounds extra bad.
Downtown Disney failed me when I left the park and I didn't get a pretzel and I was really hoping to have a Mickey pretzel and then I got to the wet souls pretzel stand and they were closed to.
You shouldn't call it downtown Disney keep those things open when there's people around it's foolish and get them open ASAP.
Open them up now as fast as you can I mean you're saying that but then I also was seeing on some Disney Twitter account that I follow probably because of you guys.
There was the downtown Disney did open up today right like they were opening up shops and stuff today.
Florida I don't know when this is coming out but yeah.
These jokes could be not jokes by the time this comes out.
Yes.
Like everything could be open by the time this comes out and by the way if we released it tomorrow everything could be open.
I don't I have no idea what's going on anymore.
But the thing that will remain is that the grape soda churros at California Churro Company are probably questionable.
Oh Scott that's right up your alley like a fine wine.
Exactly the exact same thing.
I was thinking maybe we could do a little.
I don't want to dwell on any of these too long.
I'm just going to try to quick hit him because I couldn't believe when I once I started looking into it how many bizarre Churro variations there were and I feel like we've not been kind to Churro variations.
If I could just kind of list a couple of these and just see the ones that seem like the most experimental and let me just get kind of a gut reaction from you guys.
Let's see.
Apparently these are all for special events and stuff.
At some point they tried a banana pudding churro rolled in vanilla cookie crumbles with banana pudding dipping sauce.
I don't know.
It depends.
Like if a chef was doing that maybe.
But if it's like banana extract I don't know.
You need a precision that needs to be like precise to be good.
Yeah.
That's what you're saying.
So not teens?
If teens are making it perhaps not.
Let's go a little more savory.
Maple bacon churro.
This was in California Venture at one point in time.
Dusted with cinnamon sugar and topped with maple icing and crumbled bacon.
No.
My answer is going to be no for all.
But that is no.
Let's leave the maple bacon behind in the 2010s.
I'm a big maple guy but I don't.
You're playing a real you're really rolling the dice when you start sticky.
Who knows when that bacon was cooked or how good quality it was.
I don't know.
Yeah.
It does often seem like charcoal.
It seems like a year old.
Yeah.
I have some I have some churro facts open on my computer.
I searched fun facts about Disney churros.
Yes please.
And in the video section it says Disneyland churro facts and the video is marked for 47 seconds long.
So there seems to not be a ton.
There is there's another video.
There's another video of how long is the Disneyland churro which is somehow longer than the facts video.
It's 50 seconds long and in the preview of the video it shows that the Disneyland churro is 16 inches long.
Really.
That's bigger than I thought.
Yeah.
Hmm.
That's impressive.
I think maybe they started it like they.
Yeah.
They did it.
Like they.
Yeah.
They definitely again wanted something longer.
I.
This was kind of a difficult episode to research at this moment because if you Google Disneyland churro you just get bombarded with a million websites who got content out of like Disneyland releases the churro recipe which is it's funny for a couple of reasons.
One they put up a video of how to make them like two years ago.
It's not like it was this great secret.
And two it really feels like they're tempting fate because I think the one thing you really shouldn't gamble with if you're a home cook is heating a skillet of foot with a full cup of oil because that's just the easiest way to start a fire.
That's the easiest way to cause chaos.
And remember.
Jesus Christ.
If you're going to do that remember they did to put out a grease fire turn off heat put a lid on it or try throwing some salt or baking soda at the grease fire.
But in in doubt when in doubt just call 911 but be very careful if you're trying to fry chicken or make churros at home because I don't I don't mess around with like a skillet of oil in at least when I cook.
By the way Jason when you were talking that that little bit of audio that you heard was me queuing up the secrets of Disney origins of churros at Disneyland in 4k.
And an advertisement played as I had paused it but then an advertisement played.
And now I've completely but I I have this now bookmarked because this is the this is it's about four minutes long.
It's the longest thing I found.
But it seems like Scott it seems like it was some of the history that that you were talking about earlier or maybe it was a Jason who was telling us about the history.
The Jim Loman tale yes.
Yeah great man.
Yeah.
I let me do one more thing I discovered it's actually odd.
A while ago Mitch you you said something about the Taco Bell sure ask items being like what Thanos would leave behind and relatedly there was an event in 2019 where they did a set of Infinity Stone churros.
Yeah.
I'm going to text you guys.
This is a link that did it.
Forgive me.
There's that couldn't find like you know a worthy compendium of all of them.
You're just going to have to scan these articles that I'm sending you.
But you I feel like you need to see photos.
I can't just describe them because if I describe them they sound OK.
Let me do it really fast.
These are spread out all across the parks.
This is yeah it's it's it's rough.
I mean I think the one that you're looking at you know you got all of them here.
Soul Stone orange space stone blue raspberry mind stone lemon power stone blackberry time stone green apple and I think you're mainly looking at the reality stone cherry and that one I believe is covered in like pop rocks candy rock candy.
Yeah.
It looks terrible.
These are horrible.
Fucks.
These are so fucked.
It's a nightmare.
It's really it's like the purple one though if you click on the purple one it looks like it was like sitting in the freezer and like part of it froze and part of it didn't.
Yes.
Yes the top of it looks frozen.
Yeah it looks like it's just like somebody accidentally put it somewhere and now they're selling it like it or like the freezer was broken like half of the freezer wasn't working.
The other half was doing an OK job.
Oh that looks fucking disgusting.
And by the way this is the this is the Twitter account that the Walt Disney World News Twitter account was the one that I that I saw the downtown Disney thing and my my my my question is why did these have to be separate articles.
Why couldn't all these power in this power stone and whatever the infinity stone churros be in just one article.
Yes there's a new article for each review of each different color churro.
I'm tempted to criticize that but it does sound like something we would do.
That's true it does sound like that.
That's just like all these dozens of sites getting posts out of like the Disneyland just rewording the Disney parks blog or the rewording Joe roadies Instagram posts.
The the soul stone the orange looks like it's bleeding orange blood.
It's like there's a consistency like thick orange blood is oozing out of an orange churro.
Blood orange is popular but when does it actually look like it's bleeding.
That's true.
You know what actually it also could just be buffalo sauce.
It could be delicious buffalo sauce soaked in an orange churro.
Oh let's celebrate crispy.
By the way I want I just want I just want to give the headlines for each of these things.
Review new power stone churro lacks cosmic power at Hollywood land in Disney California Adventure.
And then here is and then the other one is review don't exchange your soul for the soul stone churro in Disney California Adventure.
All of them are like these all the headlines are like these suck.
In different dressed up you guys are the Marvel experts if you had to come up with a headline to describe your feelings.
Oh well I'd have to be about each stone I guess.
So what are we at the time stone.
You don't save time for one of these.
I was going to go for a generic for like the anytime a newspaper tries to write about comic books and inevitably the headline is Biff Bam Pow comics not for kids anymore.
So Biff Bam Pow these these churros will torture your taste buds.
Pretty good.
There'll be an infinity war in your stomach.
Here's my headline this one specifically made for all the listeners just like all the Avengers movies and Galaxy's Edge these churros suck.
Oh no Pete.
It's just going for cheap heat Mitch going to war with the Marvel fans now to bring it on baby.
Mitch is challenging you the military industrial complex the military advisors.
Yeah they're gonna be upset.
I found just we were speaking about teens and churros a little bit and because of that I googled Six Flags Magic Mountain churros and apparently Six Flags Magic Mountain had an event last year where if you bought a churro you could stay late in the park and ride special rides.
Special purchase a churro at a participating food location inside the park and you'll receive a special event wristband to an extent to attend an exclusive ride event that night.
So you would get like a special like after hours event if you bought a churro at Six Flags.
Everything going well.
That's how dire it is over there that you that they're that you they give a special park treatment if you buy a churro.
Basically yes what that is saying is that like let's look at let's break this down the special after hours event at Disney cost you know 100 $150 this event cost $5 and they're losing money because they're also giving you a churro.
So it's like you're paying like maybe two dollars to stay late at Six Flags.
Mike you sent a picture of all the different churros in an infinity gauntlet and it's kind of unpleasant look.
Yes that's right.
It looks like it looks like like some sort of fungus run amok or like like some sort of plant growth that's not natural.
Yeah.
What is the what's the Natalie Portman move annihilation Disney's annihilation.
That is very annihilation ask it's a very it's it's it's someone says it's so basically someone brought bought.
I wonder if they were just selling that it was it's the Thanos is glove and it's filled with every stone and churro infinity stone churro.
They were selling.
Yeah.
I mean it's like who wants to do that I mean whatever wants that bloggers people writing these things the bumper car boys.
They they're what they were selling a Thanos like mug like in his like infinity gauntlet which makes a lot more sense than this.
Yeah.
Like they're not in the shape of stones.
Why would why would they you know what I mean like they're not infinity sticks infinity sticks infinity stone cookies would make more sense.
Yeah.
Like it's just or a moose shells as we came as we were talking about on the treats episode.
You know what guys what I thought I was going to turn you around and say have you say that churros are the number one snack in the Disney Park.
But after seeing the infinity stone churros you've won me over churros suck.
Oh no no we can't have no it's like it's like a Thanos defeated us.
Mike lost his resilience.
No this is bullshit here.
Wait and I but I think I could turn it around.
I'm sitting on something that I think might help us have a happy ending here.
I'm going to check your phones one more time because I'm going to send you a series of three photos.
Mike you brought up six flags and I take you now to six flags Mexico a park I don't believe I realize existed until now.
It was formerly the park that had trapped free Willy.
That was before six flags bought it.
So don't hold that against these photos.
Yeah.
I'm not building a good case but I'm going to send you three lovable pals and they don't have an official name.
But you know what I'll make one up right now.
In an alliterative way.
These are I'll name them the churro chums at six flags Mexico.
You can take photos with three giant churros.
They're like avatar proportions if a human being is five to six feet I think these are like 10 to 11.
They look like will vinton claymation characters.
They kind of remind me they're sort of in the family of other characters I love like the walking Hershey bars in Hershey land or also they're a little bit like my buddy Charlie chip the mascot of fries electronics.
The greaser looks like a California raisin to me.
Very much so.
That might be where I'm getting the will vinton vibes.
He's got big old sneakers.
They've got sort of like Mickey Mouse s glims just the just the black little twigs and then big white gloves.
There's kind of a Mike said agree sir you might call him kind of an Elvis looking one.
There's just a guy in a big mustache and a sombrero and and then and then like a cowboy the sheriff for churro town and he's got a big gun.
He's got a gun.
It's like an unforgiven like Clint Eastwood and unforgiven he's seen too much.
He's killed too many.
It's it's it's it's it's there's two things that stand out about him.
One is that yes it is just it's just a straight up gun.
It's not like a fun churro gun.
It's a straight up just like fucking big ass gun.
And then she was that he just you just fall into his baby blue eyes.
He has these baby blue eyes.
Oh my God.
You're right.
The other one of them is wearing sunglasses.
You can't tell the other his eyes are not as piercing.
Yeah God this who is he like who's like who's an actor who's got some of the best eyes right now.
Who's like a classic blue eyed.
He's just he's such a hunk.
Who's got the best eyes right now in the business.
He's got the best eyes right now.
Actors with good eyes.
I'm looking at you actually you know what don't people who's the serial killer that people think is hot.
All of them.
Yeah.
But the one who's like especially hunky a lot of people were saying oh well.
Did Zac Efron play him.
Yeah.
Who's that.
Which one is that.
I got a picture.
I got a picture of Bradley Cooper that he it's very similar.
Well it's a little he's a little lighter than this guy but he's got the eye.
He's got eyes that really draw you in I think.
So this churro is like a combo Bradley Cooper and Ted Bundy.
Yeah there you go.
I agree.
And he's got a gun so there's sort of the threat angle.
And he's very macho like I bet he is I bet he kind of talks like what's what's his character in Star is Born.
Oh.
Oh God.
Jackson Jackson made.
Yeah.
It's scared as guys.
I mean yeah.
I'm just I just want to do right by you.
Want to take another look at you.
That's the lie.
Yeah.
There you go.
That's what Mitch says when he walks away from the churros.
I just want to take one more look at you.
I saw I saw Bradley Mike Carlson's Bradley Cooper and I raised him a crisp pine.
Yeah the crisp prying as the good he has the key is a good eyes too.
I think I think if I think I think Bradley's maybe a little bit more a little bit more hypnotizing.
I think I think those work a little bit better.
So the three churro eyes the three men were the most attracted to our Bradley Cooper crisp pine and this churro sheriff the churro sheriff slay me.
I would love to hang out with a churro sheriff in like in a Pizza Hut sort of fashion.
Wait what do you mean pizza in a pizza fashion like in that like you know I would I would eat them like how the how pizza eats himself and his little buddy there eats them too.
I think I would I would want to eat that.
Oh right.
Sure.
Like my friend.
But you're just lowering him in so you can take a big bite out of him.
Yeah yes I mean like I would be looking into his big blue eyes as I as I ate him but I mean I would eat him for sure.
How can you turn down eating a giant churro like that.
If he was a man.
I said I said that I'd feel bad as I ate him.
What if he what if he was like Joe stop stop.
I'm in pain you're hurting me you're killing me.
Or what if he was like keep it going.
You're doing the right thing.
It's a living.
And he is and he's like you're like hey put the gun to my temple while I eat you.
You know honestly what this has made me think is that Disney needs to have some sort of churro property.
They've got to do some sort of churro property.
Well you know that brings us back to Videopolis because they would to drum up churro sales when they first introduced them they would play.
She's got Betty Davis eyes but they change it to she's got piercing churro eyes.
Six likes really the six flags.
Yes like the piercing churro I've had six lights really skirting copyright here with the piercing churro.
Do you know what you know what.
Here's what I think.
What do you guys think of this.
Every churro stand there's it's Pluto's ass and then the and then the and then the churros are just come out of those you wrap them right from there.
What do you guys think.
Wait they come out of his ass out of the hole.
They come out of his ass.
Yeah yeah yeah they come out of the Pluto's asshole basically.
So he is like a long shits.
So yeah Pluto is taking these big long shits.
And then also like how people pick up dog mess with like plastic baggies those those white rappers are kind of like the baggies you know what I'm saying.
If the baggies are like kind of themed well I think I do like this idea.
Yeah Mike this is the what you were lacking in terms of Instagram ability in terms of visual panache with churros.
I think Mitch just just just invented it.
He fixed the problem.
If the Pluto makes a noise when it comes out to that'll be an extra little level of imaginary like like relieved.
Oh struggling.
OK yeah.
Yeah.
Because it's a long piece like you shouldn't be making that like 16 inch shits.
Wait a minute.
So Pluto suffering every time someone orders sure how he's screaming.
And then at the end and he's relieved at the end.
He's relieved at the end.
It's a good thing.
He's struggling while it comes out.
But also I just want to say that canonically then that's what the churros are then Pluto shits.
And I think that that is better than the alternative.
Right.
And they won't say shit.
So what are they are they Pluto dumps.
Pluto dumps.
Or make it alliterative as I like to do.
Pluto plops.
Oh that's cute.
Yeah that's a cute way to do it.
Here we go.
Churros anymore.
Right.
The most offensive thing you can do to its culture and where it came from.
You don't name it.
You don't call it churros anymore.
You throw that out the window and you call them.
That dumb old name.
No those are Pluto plops now.
Come on everyone.
Come back to the Disney parks.
Make a new mouth memories with Pluto plops.
Yeah it's great.
You did it.
You fixed it.
It's IP Mike Mitchell.
You survived podcasts the ride.
Wow.
A brilliant idea.
Thank you for spitting perfect imaginary ideas with us.
Straight fire straight fire from that.
I don't really have it.
I don't have anything to really promote except for that.
You know we should open that back up the parks.
Hashtag open the gates.
Hashtag Mike Mitchell.
I'm on the side.
We're going to lock the gates.
Of course something that and also I'm trying to get her eyes out of people by saying all
that stuff was bad.
Don't be mad at me.
I'm sorry.
Or the boys.
Boys.
Sure.
Gotcha.
Look you made everybody so happy with Pluto plops by the end.
I don't think anyone will remember.
You know we'll we'll make sure that you guys get to look at these big tall plops these
handsome piercing top lops and other bonus media if you go to our Twitter if you go to
our Facebook if you go to our Instagram and there's always a bunch of fun three bonus
episodes every month at Patreon dot com slash podcast the ride.
Anything else.
Do we do it.
I think we did it.
I think yeah I don't.
Look next time when the park when I feel comfortable going to the park next maybe I will first
thing try a churro to see.
Wow.
Maybe if that will change my perception I'm open to this moving up on the rankings.
It's just I'm going to maybe I'll try to experience it I'll get a I'll get a coke I'll get a
churro in tomorrow and then I'll see I'll see what happens.
You're starting your day off right.
I'm telling you.
Yeah.
Like Mitchell Speedball.
That's right.
All right.
Thanks for listening everybody.
That was a blast.
Thanks for joining us Mitch.
Bye bye.
Thanks guys.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson Jason Sheridan Scott
Gardner Brett Boehm Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts please visit forever dog podcasts dot com and subscribe to our shows
on Apple podcasts and YouTube.
And subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram at forever
dog team and liking our page on Facebook.