Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, The Second Gate.
Gather around fairies and sprites for Jason Sheridan is joining me today.
As always, I'm Mike Carlson, of course.
Oh, man.
Here we go.
This is how it starts.
Of course, Scott Gardner has also enchanted us with his presence today.
Punished.
Scott Gardner, what do you mean?
My name is Bumbleweb.
Bumbleweb, of course.
I apologize.
I didn't recognize you.
It was not my name until Pixie, until Pixie does hit my nose.
Oh, but I thought it was Jason Sheridan.
It indeed was not.
It was Skeetal Branch.
Ah, Skeetal Branch, hello.
Gonna write a big do not resuscitate on my chest for this one.
Your wit has no bounds, Skeetal Branch.
Okay, all right.
Of course, there's me.
I am not Mike Carlson.
Who am I?
Jason, you know.
Oh, yes, Jason, say his name.
Hopping Frog.
Oh, OK, all right.
That's right. It sure is.
It is me, Hopping Frog.
Hello.
All right. Are these?
Did you guys look up?
Are these actual?
Are you pulling from your notes or this orthodome?
I sincerely do not know.
I'll get out a little lie.
I consulted a list of fairy names, which you better believe will be read
later in the episode.
OK, I had to go to a message board in order to find the full list.
I found a partial list and that wasn't going to do it for me.
I did find the name of every Pixie in this
relatively obscure disliked parade.
Um, mine was off the dome.
OK, got it. Great.
Yeah, but I have seen the names.
I have seen the names.
You have seen the names.
You've seen that now.
Now you have seen the names.
This is very similar in the hearing.
Does Glitterwing or does Glitterwing not know the secrets of the Pixie Magic?
I appreciate it.
I appreciate that, Scott.
You were doing the running for president
a thumb in index finger kind of for a second there that you just say,
yeah, we're deploying webcams at the moment.
Yes, you saw me do a,
you know, the Bill Clinton impression, the tiny thumb.
Yeah. Mm hmm.
Thanks. Thanks for noticing.
You got to physicalize even in the audio medium.
What the hell is this bullshit?
What are we talking about today?
This is
light magic, light magic.
But also a spectacular journey.
Yes, correct.
That's right.
That's the tagline, a spectacular journey.
That was the tagline on the sign.
Give it magic, a spectacular journey, which we all know and love
as the replacement for the Main Street Electrical Parade
and as Disney said in a press release,
it achieved what they hoped it would be,
which is the longest running show in the history of show business.
It, of course, is that today.
Oh, wait, I'm confused.
It ran for a summer and was chased out of town like Frankenstein's monster.
Well, surely a few months, a few months.
Surely they only spent checks notes, 20 million dollars
to replace a thing made out of light bulbs and chicken
wire in 1972.
How much could the electrical parade have cost?
I mean, like, I don't think it cost one million dollars.
It probably cost like 10 grand.
At the time, I think it might have was just somebody's dad
banging it together.
I'll take care of it.
I like to quote the I was going to quote the Los Angeles Times real quick
from 1997, light magic or light tragic?
Question mark.
Uh huh.
A 20 million, the 20 million dollar dud, the L.A.
Times also said.
It's finally gone.
The Orange County Register, it failed to attract much of a following.
But, you know, why do we let the fake news journalists
have the word about this parade?
We should let Disney speak for it.
And in fact, our king, our hero, Michael Eisner, if you're
if you're currently confused as to what this parade was, what it consisted of.
Michael Eisner can help explain in Michael Eisner's words,
it is a parade and a show that features the magic of light and the magic of night.
So there you go. Got it.
OK, OK. Pretty good.
Rarely combined.
I mean, magic of light sort of siloed its own thing and magic of night separate.
But to mix them, that's that Disney bold spirit.
Yeah, well, I mean, look, we're all over the place already a little bit,
but I like the fact that it says in the actual soundtrack of the raw of the
excuse me, the parade, the Disney characters discover the power of starlight
and magic and pixie dust can make their dreams come true.
So that's also like how I like to think of it.
This is before the like big like all in on like pixie me,
like the direct to DVD pixie hollow stuff.
I should say. Yeah, yes.
This is this is the late 90s.
I also looked up.
I was very curious because I was like, what movie?
I was trying to think of an indie movie that you could make with 20 million dollars.
And the first thing that came to mind was Little Miss Sunshine.
So I looked that up.
The budget for that was eight million dollars.
So you can make three and a quarter
little sunshine for the cost of this six month parade.
Also, this was 96 or 97.
So with inflation, that's even crazy.
Maybe three, maybe three Little Miss Sunshine, three completed
Little Miss Sunshine's dear God.
What a what a bizarre waste.
If you so if you don't know this story at all.
And I've realized that a lot of people don't because you guys didn't.
I was kind of surprised.
No, you guys were not previously familiar with light magic.
To me, it looms very large because I grew up in
in California and really and love Disneyland and love the Main Street
Electrical Parade and was highly anticipating the the replacement,
the like the the enhancement over the dirty old
Main Street Electrical Parade that was going to come.
Another thing about me is that what I was probably, I think I was like
12 at the time, I used to go on Disney message boards and news groups.
So I, which is a very cool thing for a 12 year old to be doing.
Great way to be spending time.
Don't play sports. Don't go outside.
Go on all that Disney Disneyland.
And I got to watch it grow from.
Oh, wow. So they're almost ready with the replacement.
Huh? I'm not hearing very good things.
Oh, my God is the worst thing that's ever happened.
So the biggest disappointment in park history,
which is and it dovetail, it went.
This is 97, 98 was rocket rods and Tomorrowland 2001 was new
California adventure and superstar limo and all.
This was such a dark period, a very, very dark period to be a Disneyland fan.
Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, what was going on?
Like we didn't back in Disney.
Like, I feel like all eyes were on Disney World in the 90s, you know.
And if stuff didn't quite go as planned, it still was like
rolled with like Disney Quest or whatever, or Disney's America.
I don't think at my age, I was really like picking up on Disney's America.
I yeah, I was not even I was not so plugged in to the to the info
and the rumors and to the chatter online like I was to other things
I liked at that point, like when the Internet started,
I was very much into the comics and I was into video games and stuff.
I mean, for sure, honestly, it didn't even cross my mind
that you could go and do the same thing for the theme parks.
I think that's exactly.
Yeah, I didn't have a ton of like or any theme park friends.
People go occasionally, but I thought it was just a thing my family liked,
which is crazy because millions and millions of people go every year.
Let me ask, when did you guys have the Internet in your home?
Oh, good question.
Not long before that, probably like early 96.
So I want to say, oh, my God, I think that late or six.
No, that's early.
I we didn't have it.
I started using it in the library, I think, in like the later 90s.
I don't think we had an Internet connected computer until like.
Fall of 2000, like I was a sophomore in high school.
I think 97 or 98, maybe.
Huh, is well, because we had all day, it was AOL
and it would like slow load on the different AOL pages.
And I mean, yeah, like the worldwide web was.
I just knew that like you'd go to DC Comics is AOL page.
And I don't know, you could look at a picture of Batman or something.
I don't you couldn't really do much over six bit maps.
We'd like slowly load a picture of Batman.
I'd be like, oh, awesome.
And then that would be it, I think. OK.
Yeah. Now everybody.
Now everybody say when you lost your virginity.
Go. OK. No, that's all right.
Well, I remember years out 20, 2019.
Congratulations.
Thanks. Finally.
I mean, so I mean, this thing really is like
it I think it is considered one of the first times
there was a fan revolts that genuinely impacted
the release of of of a Disney attraction or product, because they
they really revolted.
And I think I was trying to think how to organize thoughts here.
And I think just to get people acquainted with what the show is,
maybe we should talk about what the show is.
And then I can go backwards and we can detail the history.
I don't know how much of the history you guys looked into.
But I think it's like I think it's sort of important to like know
like what it is and then then ask, how did it come to this?
How did this possibly become what they spent 20 million dollars on
and replaced the electrical parade with?
Yeah, I looked into some of it, but
I read the Yesterland roundup and I watched.
There's a pretty decent quality copy of it on YouTube.
You can watch it and get the pretty good gist of it.
So, of course, there's a great special that is online.
Yes. Yes.
Said by I'm sure Scott knows this Alex Trebek and Tony Little.
Oh, man. A oddly like not.
It isn't this like big budget ABC kind of special.
It's UPN. It was like it was for local affiliate KCOP 13.
Alex Trebek hosted it.
Seemingly at gunpoint, Alex Trebek.
I've never seen him look so miserable.
It's it's really so you watched the you watched that special.
I watched I mean, I didn't I didn't like study it,
but like I zoomed through and saw clips and then went to the parade.
It's it's a special that feels like it's
killing time and trying to not show you the parade.
Yes, because it's just a lot of history.
Yeah. Oh, they're just they're pulling out all the stops.
It's all and then Walton is Daddy's Day.
I went to the park and merry go round.
If there's a place for dads and kids to play together and is Disney.
Now, trains started by a mouse.
And yeah, they do all the shit that we all step through so many times.
It's just like how much time can we kill? And
and then there's a lot of buildup of the pixies.
That's it's like teases of the pixies.
Alex Trebek says the word pixie like 20 times
credit to our friend Doug Jones in his Disney mashup.
I believe the Golden Girls return to Space Mountain.
He did a like a mashup of every mention of pixies in this thing
and just increasingly miserable Alex Trebek pixie magic pixie dust.
Then the pixies will arrive and they will teach us how to use the pixie dust.
He's just like,
it gets worse and worse.
I yeah, I don't.
And which so to explain what this parade or whatever it is,
I can you even how do you would you guys explain your
perception of what it is, because it's not quite a parade?
Yeah, it's
it's and it's not street.
Misfier, there's a term they use, isn't there?
Street, tackler, street tackler.
Thank you.
You see, I, I, I appreciate you so much for telling me.
It's a street tackler that combines the magic of light and the magic of night.
I mean, I don't want to go immediately to the Craven interpretation,
but Michael Flatley and Riverdance were very big in the 90s.
Yes. And I mean, I think
it's a straight line from that to this. Right.
Like, I'm not crazy.
It's like when Disney like two or three years after the fact is like,
hey, check out our cronuts.
Like they get around to it eventually.
Well, it's like, you know, they were like a little bit after the fact
they they put Cirque du Soleil in Disney World.
And then a little bit after the fact, they embraced
yeah, Lord of the Dance and Riverdance.
And I I can tell you why they embrace those things.
Do you know where that idea came from?
So for Disney to do their own version of Riverdance?
Is that an Eisner?
That's straight from Eisner.
Is it? Yes. You got it.
Yes. Hello. Hello.
I have to say. Let's dance. Let's dance.
Cirque du Soleil was not on my radar until until that.
I guess it was probably in maybe in those Vegas specials.
I'm sure it was arriving in Vegas.
But the Disney World's
Lanuba was the first.
We'll get around to Lanuba.
Of course. Yeah.
Just in case there's a listener that doesn't know what Riverdance
or Lord of the Dance is, there was a gentleman named Michael Flatley,
who was very popular in the 90s, and he was in a group called Riverdance.
As far like that was the first big explosion.
And it was essentially like clog dancing.
How would you call it?
It's Irish step dancing.
Not clog. Yeah, right.
Irish step dancing. Thank you. Yeah.
And it's like a lot of high stepping where your knees would go up
to like your stomach and like you were prancing, prance dancing.
And it swept the nation.
And then Michael Flatley had a falling out with Riverdance
and started his own show called Lord of the Dance.
Oh, I didn't know any of this.
I didn't know he was part of Riverdance first.
Yes, there was a controversy.
And he left and started Lord of the Dance.
I see.
Which I'm sure we'll do an episode about.
Celtic Celtic music, right?
Celtic Celtic Celtic.
Yeah, I I knew I had that wrong.
There's laughter from the other room because I messed that up
the other day, too, in conversation.
The same thing.
I was trying to describe what this was.
Oh, Joe was and I messed it up then, too.
And then you were talking about Larry Bird and the Boston Celtics.
That's true.
That's probably what I get slipped up on.
Yeah, it is confusing.
Yes, they I mean, I'll go backwards in the history.
But like by the time they at some point had that they wanted to do
a show that involved Pixies and Eisner was shown
some of the early concept art of it and saying he said fairies are Irish, right?
Maybe you guys should make this show like Riverdance,
throwing some step dancing and tin whistles and stuff.
To even whistle tin whistles.
What does that mean?
Lord of the Tin Whistle.
So and I definitely one of the things that is the most unpleasant
about light magic is the the veneer of this music.
I don't look I don't want to like insult an entire culture or something.
But like this particular just what this is like
like 90s Yamaha
version of pan flutes.
Yeah, yes.
Synthesizer pan flutes is not my favorite genre of music I've ever heard.
Hmm. I don't know who I'm thinking is going to be mad at me.
I know that Michael Flatley is going to show up at my house
and stomp all over my face.
Can I kick you with his feet?
He's going to kick you with his feet of flames.
His hit show from 1999.
Feet of flames.
Feet of flame.
Wait, wait, feet of flames.
The victory tour.
Yeah.
After the Jacksons, he just did the victory tour again.
Yes. And he performed it in 2000 and 2001.
Yeah. Victory against what?
Normal stepping.
Feet. Yes.
No, no, not of flames.
He overcame normal walking.
Scott, you get excited because you hear synthesizer.
Mm hmm.
And then you hear a pan flute and then you like a real life Simpsons gag.
It's what I was saying.
It's what I was saying in Electrical Parade.
An electrical parade episode is I love I love how the old mohgs
don't try to sound like anything.
They're just their own weird computer objects.
And then in the 90s, everything starts trying to sound like shit.
Synthesizer strings, synthesizer horns, the worst.
Mike, you can agree we've seen McCartney live a couple of times,
and it's wonderful.
And the only bad element is he'll do got to get you into my life or something.
And then like the most like it sounds like this.
It sounds like light magic. It's.
You know what? I was shocked the last time we saw him,
which was last summer at Dodger Stadium, he had actual horns.
Yes. Good.
He's he's a notoriously cheap.
Is that why? Is that why the synthesizer?
That's the rumor.
Because like, you know, I've seen we've all, you know,
we've seen concert, I've seen Bruce Springsteen at a certain point.
He was touring off of that that album High Hopes.
He had like 30 people in the band, a choir horn section.
McCartney has like six people.
And you're like, well, why wouldn't he?
He has all these different he has all these different songs
that have like orchestration and horn parts and strings and stuff.
And that's that's the rumor.
I mean, I've heard also that he's just very cheap.
I heard he had a cash bar at one of his weddings.
I mean, that's the funniest thing I've ever heard.
Much respect, much respect.
OK, well, so to explain what the show actually is, you know,
and I could we could take 10 minutes to explain the pseudo plot.
Really, really what it is is a bunch of pixie bullshit.
That's that's the main thing.
It's a bunch of pixie step dancing or clog dancing or whatever it is.
And I guess an important thing to note is that, OK,
we never we didn't really explain what street tackler means.
It's not a constantly moving parade like the Main Street Electrical Parade.
It's these four big floats, these big barges of floats
that kind of look like like little miniature forests, these big trees
kind of as the bases of them.
And they roll out onto Main Street between the four.
They pretty much fill up the length of Main Street and they stop.
And a show is performed.
And then when the show is over, they keep rolling and go backstage.
And then they, you know, they do it again on the other side of the park.
So it's way more of a way more of a dance show in the middle of Main Street.
Yes, yes, that's what I didn't know either.
And then I basically one of the first things I read was this
Los Angeles Times article, just trashing it.
And basically, like people are just like, what we want more floats.
There should be floats if it's a parade.
They really overshot, they really, they really overshot,
over thought what anyone wanted, especially in the wake of the Main Street
Electrical Parade, an important word that was probably why a lot of people liked that thing.
I think part of what this came out of is that they done this this Lion King
parade called the Lion King Celebration, which stopped.
And there were there was sort of a show elements like
element like, you know, a couple songs were performed and then it kept moving.
But even that it was like floats with a lot of variety.
Here's Simba up on the rock and here's wherever Timon and Pumbaa are hanging out.
And with all that, I remember seeing that parade when I was a kid and thinking,
I hate this parade.
I hate that it stops and there is a show.
I either want to see a parade or I want to see a show.
The middle does nothing for me, especially because I can't see shit.
I'm small. I can't like I like
and I don't want to spend two hours of my day camping out a spot to see this show.
I hated it.
It seems like I was I was looking at a mice chat message board just now, too.
And one like most people are saying they did not like this.
But one person was saying, well, I kind of like it, but I knew where to sit.
So it's like, oh, the parade was it was dependent on like you having an optimum
position, like you needed to be exactly in the right spot to be able to enjoy anything.
Like seeing gravity in IMAX, like, well, no, you really got to.
If your third row center, it's going to be amazing.
It's going to look like shit anywhere else.
But you'll seizure if you're up in the corner. Yeah.
You'll lean against the wall by the Main Street Cinema
and make sure you bring like a little bit of an apple, like an apple box
and stand on the apple box by the Main Street Cinema.
And like, that's the perfect way to see it.
Oh, I wish Disney rented apple boxes by the like hour or the day, because that would I mean,
I even now, I don't have a great vantage point like.
I either need to be really far back or really in the mix at concerts, let alone theme parks.
Maybe that's like a new kind of a thing.
People could bring their own apple box and you can direct like you can call
or you can like decorate it however you want.
And like everyone will bring their own like apple box and it'll be sort of a thing.
You'll compare them.
Somebody will make a figment apple box.
Like it'll be very like a cool new fan culture thing.
That's a good idea. That's kind of like glamping.
It's like like glamping, but like like heightening.
You're it's like it's glite glightening.
Yeah, yes.
That word will take off.
That's as catchy as as streetacular.
I think that's really going to take off.
Yeah, I agree.
I do. I do want to say no shade to the dancers are all very talented Irish step dancers.
No shade there.
You know, and and of course, Disney and most part kind of infamous for underpaying their talent.
So impressive technically.
I'm not arguing that, but just overall, what a mess.
No, they're yeah, they're all fine.
And I like I said, there's probably the the 10 minute version
like Disney's version of what the story is, but let me just try to do it.
And feel free to stop me and add things, but let me try to do it from from my memory of what it is.
Four tree barges roll into Main Street.
If you're if you're 12 year old Scott, the barges stop with a tree perfectly blocking your view of most of it.
You're you're stranded in between the middle of two barges.
And then then out of the tree barges come a lot of pixies and they look around and, you know,
put their hand up on their face as if to see what is far away.
And then they dance and dance more.
And then the Disney characters come out,
seemingly, according to Disney, disturbed by the sounds of the pixies.
Like, what's all that racket?
And because they were keeping they were all sleeping.
So the characters all come out in pajamas and robes.
So out walks.
Sorry, sleeping, sleeping.
That's yes, that's the plot of this.
OK, yeah, I don't I think the video I watched was so grainy.
I did not pick up that the characters being woken up was extremely literal.
That's exactly what it is.
It's 7 p.m. and that's OK.
Bedtime. Got it.
Yeah, that's when Miko goes to bed.
That's when that's the head.
That's Donald's bedtime is seven.
So he's yeah, he's fast asleep.
So now we got Clarabel Cow and a nightgown and Timon robe.
And they're rubbing their eyes like, why the hell is all this?
And then they see that it was pixies and they go, OK, that's fine then.
And the pixies say hi and show them that they are pixies and they agree.
And then they hand all of the Disney characters
pixie dust and show them how to use the dust.
This, again, I've only only through the benefit of Cliff notes
do I understand that this is the story is pixies teaching our friends
like, you know, Eeyore and Sebastian the crab.
How how do you use pixie dust?
Right. Can I add that the pixies look like slightly less scary versions
of the Whoville people?
Slightly, slightly, slightly.
Good point. I think it is more.
I think you guys a picture.
I think we can all agree if you need to condense the criticism down,
just the aesthetics are all off like Jesus Christ.
Oh, this is horrible.
What you said. Which dwarf is this?
Is this like happy to me?
I think so. I'm not happy.
I don't know that he is either.
Happy is wearing a striped.
It looks like he's wearing a 1920s bathing suit.
Yeah. Full body striped for a larger gentleman bathing suit.
And he's next to a girl in like
you know, like pink leggings and a sparkle skirt.
She was she's it's like a an ice dancing costume that's three times too big.
It's like for like Mrs. Claus's outfit,
but it's like doesn't fit her and she has wings,
but she also looks like a Whoville person.
Yeah, she's got like very light, like Twilight's own
Eye of the Beholder makeup on
not full Eye of the Beholder, just partial.
Yeah, I mean, it's very like ventriloquist dummy.
It's like if you were if you were playing a ventriloquist dummy
in a in a film or for Halloween.
Or like, I don't know if there if anyone's I don't know why this is in my head,
but like people playing Raggedy Ann or Raggedy Andy.
Like the worst, if you've ever seen that, that's exactly how they all move.
Like with their like wobbly, like cloth, like doll arms or puppet arms
should never be done. Yeah.
I hate adults as like cloth dolls with yarn hair.
I always hate it.
I hate like big like rouge circles on cheeks.
I it creeps the hell out of me.
Do you remember the show?
I guess he wasn't a puppet.
He was a mannequin.
But the show today's special on Nickelodeon.
Yes, yes, I do.
But I don't I don't know where you're going with this.
Well, there was a mannequin that came to life that was like
he would move in a similar way to like what I'm describing.
And I was wondering if you had a feeling about him.
I'm sure it would be bad if I mean, I'm looking at photos.
Oh, that's right.
He would. Oh, he came to life.
That's OK. I mean, that's this is better to me than like.
Yeah, I don't know what you just described.
Adult Raggedy Ann, I is that's horrible to me.
But like I have the opening here and he is certainly a lot better than a dull
Raggedy Ann, but he's got the big when adults like would put their like
stretch their arms is like far out as they could and like wobble around.
As a child, I never liked that.
Let me find adult Raggedy Ann.
I didn't I didn't like that.
I didn't like a lot of segments on Weinerville.
I mean, I liked when you remember.
Oh, yeah, I was disturbed.
I was disturbed.
Yeah, I was really upset when they would transform people into puppets
because I was just like, I got to know that they turned the back.
How do they turn them?
Like, wasn't I?
Were you like 12 at that point?
I don't know.
No, that was in that was still like early 90s.
Was it early? Sorry, I can't remember.
I don't know, because I think they would just make such a show about puppetizing,
like turning people into puppets.
And logically, I must have known they were just sticking their head through something.
But then they would get so excited about committing to like the games and stuff
as puppets, I'd be like, I don't want to get turned into a puppet.
You hate the word puppetizing.
You give me a chill with that term.
That's what all of this is.
It's horrible.
I honestly, Mike, I have no memory of today's special.
I'm looking at pictures of this and I really don't remember this at all.
Like it it says a Canadian show.
It's listed as 1981.
Wow. It ran until 87, though.
So I just don't think I ever got this.
Wienerville was 93.
OK, so I would have been nine, nine or nine, eight or nine.
Yeah, not a good age to get puppetized, but no good age is a good age to get puppetized.
I mean, in terms of light magic, I was like thinking I was looking through
like stuff I put in my notes.
The only thing that I like is like, I kind of like that.
I kind of like the light magic sign that they hung over the like
entrance to Main Street.
The purple yellow. I completely agree.
Yes, that is a good sign that implies a cool parade.
That it is a good sign.
But once I stared at it for a second longer, I was like,
that said, there are four different fonts on this single sign.
And I was like, well, I it is a little too much.
I do like it.
Like, I think maybe it's just the color scheme of it.
I like the main to the words light magic.
I like and then, yeah, they could probably eliminate from there.
So the yeah, scary girls with like gumdrop hats and frightening angular masks.
They also you know what they all look like.
Who's the to Mr.
Rogers puppet with sort of like severe features?
It's so it's a female character.
You know, Lady Elaine Fairchild.
Yes. Yeah.
Imagine like if you were if you were an adult who wore a mask of that
only on half of your face, that's what it's like.
Lady Elaine, who I like that you're talking about.
She had the red cheeks and the red nose and she was mean.
Yes. Yeah.
It's like 40 lady lanes walk out
it's a hang out with Pumba in slippers.
And they teach the characters about pixie dust.
And then there is a long projected sequence.
They're just a movie plays.
Then that's why the floats are so long, because then a screen comes down
and they just show you a movie.
Yes, it is.
And it is something.
It but that's true.
But also it is nothing because.
All right.
It's a movie that's true, like it's about it.
So it's one of these.
I think this is maybe the beginning of Disney just going into like
wishes are dreaming and the power of magic inspires you to wish your dreams.
It's just like it's not there's nothing going on in this.
It's like it's a video.
The pixies come out and point with wonder.
And then they show you a video of children pointing with wonder.
It is. Yeah, I mean,
I don't want to say like these other parades have substance
because maybe they don't have substance, but.
There's I there's an aesthetic that's pleasing at the very least.
Yeah, there's a there's a beat and you can dance to it, you know.
By virtue of stopping.
That requires there to be substance.
Like if if a parade is going to keep moving past you,
it just has to be a bunch of nice shapes.
But if the parade is going to stop and say, hey, over here, look at this,
it's then they have to show you something that matters.
Yes. But this is my question is and I don't know.
I don't know if anyone would ever go on the record.
Was there someone when they were planning this that was think like
this actually meant anything to them, like where they were
without they were making some sort of big artistic statement or some like
inspirational thing that would inspire all the guests who saw it.
Like just did someone think that or it was just like,
these are the words that are approved.
These are the characters that are approved.
Michael Eisner wants his own Lord of the Dance and he loves pixies.
All right. What do we do?
Um, I in Doug's video,
Tony Little, he includes a clip of Tony Little talking to a guy
who was like one of the behind the scenes people, and I don't remember the quote,
but it is something like he does say like,
and that's when all the characters come out and the characters show them
the power of pixie dust and of wishing and and and Tony Little goes,
oh, I can't wait. And he says, I can't either.
This may be the guy.
This may be whatever whoever this guy is might be the guy who cares.
Can I ask, can someone just give me the short answer?
Who is Tony Little?
I'm not sure that I know.
So I looked her up.
She was like she did.
I think she did like L.A.
news and stuff, and I think she might have been this America pageant.
Right. Because I see the special was the UPN LA affiliate.
This is it's a weird time because the 1999,
like a Millennium special was also a different affiliate, like
or at least the version I watched was produced.
So I forget when the ABC deal closed and when they're like,
no, let's just show all this stuff nationally.
Well, that was 97. So that was after that.
So I don't know why this is.
Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, they just didn't think it was like prime time worthy,
like back when prime time really meant something.
It was only in L.A.
And she looks like she was a UPN anchor.
And it also looks like she was Miss America in 1976
and that she was married to John Schneider from Dukes of Hazard.
Wow. Got it. Got it.
Who is who has been a musical guest on Huckabee, Mike Huckabee's
talk show filmed live in Nashville, but that's neither here nor there.
That you do watch that every week, though.
Oh, yeah. I have to have to have it special or they send me discs
because there's no way to stream it from from my home.
I was wondering when you'd get around the Huckabee.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
I it's amazing. I haven't brought it up yet.
It's it's wonderful.
I've been highlighting it on my Instagram.
It's my favorite talk show now.
Sorry, Trevor Noah. Take a seat.
I'm a Huckabee man.
But I I don't want to get on a Huckabee tear.
The where were we?
The yeah, it's a bunch of fluff.
And and by the way, the movie's just full of clips of like
the unprecedented use in a Disney Parks montage of, you know,
Beauty and the Beast dancing or Aladdin and Jasmine on the carpet.
Like, come on.
How many more times do we have to see?
Yes, there's Simba getting held up.
OK, yes. Great.
Like no more. No more of this, please.
We've all seen them.
We'll get the subscriptions.
Don't worry. Stop bothering me.
Yeah, I I'm trying to think if I would have liked this as a kid.
My guess is I had seen I mean, the answer is no.
But my guess is if I had I would not remember it if I had seen it,
you would have said light magic and I would have said, huh?
And then it'd be like, well, you know, you saw it.
I'd be like, oh, I don't remember that.
Because like it looks it feels like nothing.
It feels like also like nothing.
I feel like most people, unless they're like insane like we are,
this probably went right in and out of their brain.
I feel like I would have been impressed by the projection screen between the trees.
I would have been unhappy to say, I mean, I don't
I don't want to ruin anyone's fun if you guys like this.
But the shot of real boy Pinocchio, I'm not crazy about.
I I much more prefer wooden Pinocchio with Pinocchio is real boy.
I am not wild about that.
Well, in the main street electrical parade episode,
you objected to our strip club idea.
Real boys.
So maybe it's I guess there's that's the connection, maybe.
But just the way they drew like he's extra apple cheeked.
Do you know what I'm talking about? Like, no, he's creepy.
I know exactly what you're saying. Yeah, he is.
But I because I find him so endearing for the rest of the movie.
And then at the very end, he gets upsetting.
Well, that's like the beast.
And then the weird like Michael Bolton man who the beast becomes.
Yeah, yeah.
It's like when Bart and Lisa, when Homer sees them as real, like looking humans
and they look very odd and you have any affection for them anymore.
You know what I want to what I want to say is that they're still using the poo bear
that has like the five o'clock shadow snout.
Like Homer, like a scratchy face.
Yes. Yes. His snout.
Like I don't that poo has always bothered me because it doesn't look right.
And his snout is like looks like it's it's got like two days of growth on it.
Well, that makes sense because he he just woke up.
He woke up in the middle of the night for him.
Who goes to sleep at four p.m.
They woke him up at seven and he's got a five o'clock shadow and bags under his eyes.
Yeah, this is getting too relatable.
This is getting too
too close to life.
I slept in the other day and then around five o'clock, I'm like, I could do with a nap.
You slept in and a five o'clock nap.
Well, I didn't know I'm taking it.
Oh, sorry.
I ended up no, I ended up working on other show stuff.
I have to say, I made these notes a few weeks ago and I kind of
reread them real quick today.
I forgot about the the narrator.
I think at some point says the dreams of today are the magic of tomorrow.
Did anyone else catch that?
I wrote that down as well.
What the what?
What are you talking about?
What does that who could possibly be moved by this?
That is some Mayor Pete soundbites.
He should narrate one of these parades.
He should know he should write it.
He should be the guy. Yeah, yeah, yeah, you're right.
Well, he's in the Disney family now because he hosted Kimmel.
Oh, yeah, that's true.
The first quarantine audience free episode was hosted by Mayor Pete.
He got a range is thing.
He played a lot of practice at his events.
Wow. You got a good bird in there.
Yeah, he played like he played a Star Trek talk show
game with Patrick Stewart and LeVar Burton.
What do you mean a talk show game with they were the guests on that episode?
Yes. Well, it was a it was trivia between Mayor
Pete and Patrick Stewart and LeVar Burton hosted it.
Huh? Yeah. Terrible.
Well, he got like Pinocchio.
He got his wish to be a real boy, to be a real celebrity boy.
Man, Jason does.
I got to say, Jason doesn't like his apple cheeks.
That's really what this is about.
Listen, buddy. I have the apple cheeks.
No one else. OK.
You're jealous.
No, I'm a repeat.
Here's another. Well, I also wrote down this note.
I don't care for the running children projection.
There's just a right.
There's like a copyright free shot, like a stock film shot of
just running children in between the trees.
This is sorry to get into a bad territory,
but this is like all of Michael Jackson's music videos post 1992.
Oh, yeah. They were all just full of arbitrary children
doing nothing like gone were cool styles and shoes
and light up floors and replaced by running children.
Well, and also like wishes and dreams also.
Yeah, that's true. Yeah.
Like these generic platitudes.
It the worst the moment where I should have bailed on Michael Jackson
was when I was shown the music, the video for the song Childhood,
which is a big short soaring shot where he's dressed as Peter Pan
and he sings the lyric adventurous dreams.
All right.
The worst to the worst thing filmed by a camera.
Well, I also want to keep up.
I want to keep up. Remember, the email address is Scott is pan at Gmail dot com.
No, no, no. Everyone forgot.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
They didn't. This is canceled.
Pan is canceled. Running children are canceled.
Make sure to register that, Mike, if you haven't already.
Jason, please, do you think I do you don't think I registered
at the day we recorded the episode?
Well, it's easy to forget when you've been talking for 90 minutes.
I forgot that was definitely forgot. That was important.
I was happy to forget.
I've oceans the email to sign up for like a duplicate
free trial for certain streaming services.
It's where we're all getting our quibi from.
Yeah, that's right. Scott is pan at Gmail dot com.
I have to. I have a new DC Universe subscription
for free for a week so I can watch Batman Returns for free.
Well, that's worth it.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Um, OK.
So, I mean, the only other note I have about what's in the show
is that goofy plays a big flower horn. Yes.
The only characters start picking up like like little
like lily pad instruments or whatever and like,
who would like this?
This is for no one.
And then really adding insult to injury, you know, it's been like
there's been sort of like Celtic versions of Disney classics,
and then they all step dance to a Celtic version of Baroque.
The mainstreetological parade song.
This is such a slap in the face.
It still makes me angry today.
I'm sure they were thinking, oh, what a nice way to show you
what was here before. No way.
Sucks shit is sucks.
Don't ruin that wonderful melody with
the only way.
The only way it could be worse is if there was like a new metal
or like Limp Bizkit version of Baroque down.
Like I was trying to think of a different genre that would be more unpleasant
for the Baroque, like such a step down.
If Alien Ant Farm had done it.
You know what? I think Alien Ant Farm would be OK.
Yeah, they're a little better than they're a little better.
I'd rather hear smooth criminal than Limp Bizkit Faith.
Yeah, that's sort of where I'm going.
Yeah. Or yeah.
So like West, if it was a West Borland, well, if it was just West doing it,
maybe he was trying to tribute it. Maybe that'd be OK.
I would I was going to say Buckethead probably does a version of this.
We've talked about Buckethead before.
Famous guitarist that wears a KFC bucket on his head
that played with Guns N' Roses for a while that loves Disney
and does a lot of Disney versions.
So we should look and see if Buckethead has a Baroque hoedown.
He's got to let me look.
The yeah, that seems like the kind of thing.
Yeah, like super shredding it really fast.
Yeah, I know that all sounds better to me than this.
I think they found the worst genre of music.
And I just what I remember is that like this
this it just like blasted when the parade began.
I was just fondly recalling on the other one that opening drum
that opening hit on Burlko down is so fantastic.
You light up.
And then this one, I just remember starting like
like these awful horns like I
and they cranked it so fucking loud.
And apparently on the opening night, the first time they rolled it out,
there was a problem and the music got stuck.
And it was just the opening fanfare.
Blaringly loud for like seven minutes.
Seven minutes.
I think so.
So the so the annual pass holders are mad right away.
Like this is how you butter us up to like this with the screechingly loud.
The in that in that old newspaper article I found from 97,
it mentions the term annual are pass holes.
Talking about the annual pass holders, I have found us.
I have found a clip, a medley of Bucketheads from 2009
where he plays William Tell Overture Pirates Life for Me,
the Main Street Electrical Parade and Beat It.
What? What? Yeah. Oh, shit.
Yeah. You know, recession still going.
We needed that from Buckethead.
And once once he's going to have to get us out of this recession as well.
Oh, yeah.
Again, though, I have another press quote.
Long Beach Press Telegram 1997.
Disney's Disneyland's Light Magic Street Show was unveiled
Friday night to overflow crowds and a lukewarm reception.
Oh, I mean, when does this happen?
Like like something is so poorly reviewed out at the gate.
And you know, there was a weird trickle in of people being disappointed
by Galaxy's Edge before Rise of the Resistance.
There was, you know, that sort of builds a little bit and it's kind of gone away.
This is pretty unprecedented that just we hate this instantly.
It's like I think the big it feels to me like
because of the beloved parade that that came before it,
people came with certain expectations
and that did not do this show any favors.
For sure. Like this, it just rolled out at Disneyland, Paris arbitrarily.
It would pretty it might still be there.
I don't know. Yeah.
But it would have just been like, oh, yeah, fine.
That's OK. Like maybe no one loves it, but like no one's like pelting it
with garbage or anything versus like this, which seemed like
everyone showed like showed up.
And annual pass, everyone was like, oh, my goodness,
they're going to replace the greatest parade of all time with an even better parade.
And there's just not a single element of the parade that's better than the original.
Well, in the element.
No, not at all.
Now, what about Mickey dancing to a Celtic version of Step in Time?
No one's mentioned that.
No one has mentioned that you're right.
It's something I like that.
And he's in a in a in a Christmas robe.
He's in a robe your dad would wear on Christmas Eve.
Yeah, this also Celtic music does.
I don't know this. At least this does.
It all feels very Christmasy to me.
Hmm. Sure. Maybe that's there's a there's an element of like, yeah,
I think it has to do with a lot of the pajamas as well.
That feels like Christmas Eve type thing.
Which I mean, that look, that's one of that's down the list of issues I have with it.
Yes, to Christmas scene, not on Christmas.
But that's it. It gives you a laundry list.
There's a there's a ton to be mad about.
Well, you know, now I feel like I'm going to try to rush it.
But here's the point where I tell you that everything we just talked about
was page one of my notes and I have like five more.
Here we go. I don't want to go.
I all right. All right.
You warned us. He did warn us. Yeah.
Yeah, because we tried to do it in a shorter amount of time.
And I was like, there's a lot here.
And and, you know, I'll try to, you know, breeze through it
and not just repeat material because credit to one, Mr.
Jim Hill, Disney podcaster, theme park podcaster, who
this might have been where I found Jim Hill initially a long time ago,
was he did this great article in like 10 parts breaking down
what happened to this show.
And it was with some hindsight.
I think he did it a couple of years later.
So he was able to like really collect what the hell the story was here
and how it got us to this point.
So so thank you, Jim Hill.
And, you know, at some point, you know, just to look up his article,
I'll try to not just, you know, recite it all or anything.
But you guys did not read this article.
I did not read this article.
I did not read the 10 part Jim Hill article.
No, I'm sorry.
I read it so long ago.
I loved it years ago and I love it today.
It's so wonderful.
So he explains everything pretty wonderfully and concisely.
As we sort of alluded to in the electrical parade episode,
they it was always kind of a weird stepchild
for some reason to the Disneyland Entertainment Group,
the Main Street Electrical Parade,
because it was janky and they rushed out and this was one guy
who doesn't even work here anymore, kind of threw it together.
And yeah, do people really care about this?
I think we could top it.
And by the time they got Fantasmic going,
that was such a shot in the arm for Disneyland Entertainment
that they thought, well, now you got to give us money
and let us do like the real nighttime street parade.
So they were super confident from that, super confident
from that Lion King parade that I mentioned.
And we can finally get rid of this thing.
Weird, right?
Like who, like what a disconnect with their own audience
to not understand.
It's interesting because it's kind of what I was saying
in the other one where I was like,
I bet they kind of felt weird about it.
I was saying maybe it was more of the people who made it, though.
But I'm always surprised.
It's Disneyland.
It's like the the 90s entertainment people didn't like this hokey,
stupid 70s parade.
I'm always surprised by stuff like that,
because I think that's more common than we think.
Things that you think are beloved or for the most part are beloved by fans.
Oftentimes, the people that are in the company
have a different feeling about it, whether it's ends up being
like some weird personal thing or like they have an idea to top it.
Like, yeah, I feel like I come across that a lot when I'm reading about,
you know, long, like long lasting companies with whether it's like movies
or characters or, yeah, rides and parades and stuff.
Yeah, it's almost as if, you know, it's it's a little similar to like
if there's, you know, old movies from the 70s and 80s
that are sort of like a little bit janky.
But that's that's sort of why you love them, because they have spirit.
And then they get remade the real way today.
Right. So much money, all the money.
We're finally going to do it right.
And then there is zero heart in the thing.
It's almost like that.
If you can think of any examples of that.
No, I do nothing.
Nothing comes to mind.
Let's never happen in movies, mainly parades.
Let's keep moving.
So anyway, you know, they kind of had nothing going after.
OK, so Indiana Jones is ninety five, ninety six, ninety seven.
They don't really have anything lined up.
So they go, oh, my God, in 96, we will get rid of the electrical parade.
That'll be a big event.
People come see that and say goodbye.
And in 97, we can introduce the new thing.
So now there's a ticking clock
and we just have to figure out what the new thing is.
And what they thought it was going to be for a while
or what the anchor of it was going to be was something involving Tinkerbell.
We should say Tinkerbell is not in light magic, maybe in the movie,
I think, at some point, but not really prominently featured.
Even though these are pixies, it would make sense for Tinkerbell to be there.
She is not. And here is why. Because
Disney was also never happy with the woman flying down the wire
as Tinkerbell during the fireworks show.
They were like, yeah, that's not really like the ultimate way
we could have Tinkerbell in the park.
And they were trying to figure out, is there a way to like
have a Tinkerbell that flies around?
And Tony Baxter, King,
cooked up an idea, which is basically a drone before drones.
Wow. Took a radio controlled helicopter
and attached it to a stray Alice in Wonderland
audio animatronic figure that was from the redone 83
Alice in Wonderland ride.
She he put a propeller on Alice, lit it from the inside
and flew it around Disneyland when it was closed one night.
Oh, my God. Yeah.
And people said it was cool as hell.
And it like went for a shockingly long time.
It was a little precision. It could fly right up to people.
They got it to like skim the moat in front of the castle.
This was a huge success of an experiment.
And they were like, well, let's this is so much better than the stunt woman.
This is the way we'll feature Tinkerbell in the parks.
We got to do this. Then the lawyers found out and they said,
well, what if the thing goes awry?
What if it flies off its path and like goes right into a kid's face?
This would be PR nightmare lawsuit city.
We can't do that.
So, well, what if all right, we can't like fly it over the audience's head.
So what if we all right, did it on the parade route?
So everybody's like lying.
Everybody's created a path.
So maybe it's part of a parade that at the beginning, Tinkerbell
does a straight line on a guide wire right through the middle of Main Street.
OK, that's cool.
Maybe we can do something with that.
Um, in the meantime, this is where I'm sorry I didn't get to all this sooner.
Have you guys ever in the history of learning about Disney things,
ever heard the phrase the light keepers?
I don't think so.
Shockingly, no.
This was all new to me.
Bizarrely, the light keepers are an idea that was part of Tomorrowland 2055.
Oh, I'm sure you guys have heard of this.
We've talked about this a tiny bit.
This never created the other version of Tomorrowland
that was going to have something called Plecto's Intergalactic Review.
And like it was going to kind of build out this whole world of alien mythology
that Alien Encounter was part of.
And they're to like promote all this and tell everybody,
go to the amazing world over in Tomorrowland.
There was this they had this idea called the light keepers.
And this is what I alluded to in our in the Main Street Parade episode.
Mike, you had an idea about like
beings powered by light or something and light is their blood.
Oh, right. Jason said that, I think.
OK, that's what the light keepers are.
They were a race of godlike creatures that created light.
It's sort of in a Prometheus manner. Yeah.
And there was going to be a big UFO that landed backstage.
You'd watch it land and then the light keepers would start crawling around
and a parade would kind of form behind them.
And then they would like leave on a comet
from back behind the small world area.
We were all having a lot of fun in the 90s.
Well, we were all watching the X-Files.
What we heard. Oh, man.
The X-Files River dance, Zima.
All of the heights of culture.
And then and then sorry, I'm confused here.
The light keepers went away because Tomorrowland 2050 happened.
So then they thought of a new thing called the lumens.
And the lumens were the keepers of the light.
And they traveled on a vehicle that was a cross between a sailing ship
and a gypsy wagon.
The lumens. So there's light keepers and there's lumens.
They're gods who created light.
I don't. This is all madness to me.
This is funny, because this is like like Marvel Comics,
like shit, the way they justify like, well, here's how superpowers exist.
There was a group called the Eternals.
And then the high evolutionary comes along.
So it is kind of fitting that Disney would go along to buy Marvel,
like 10 years later or so.
Well, Kumail, Kumail and Salma Hayek are eternals.
Yeah, I mean, they're going to be the light keepers, you know. Yes.
Oh, that's right.
And the light keepers also would have been super jacked. Super jacked.
Everyone, the light keepers were been just rippling.
Breathtaking. Yeah.
Look, the light keepers would have presented us both with fire
and mylar confetti, specifically mylar confetti.
I like like fun.
I'm glad. I mean, I know it was sort of over, but like the second
I'm glad we are we are in the keeper mythology, though,
because there's a lot of Disney keeper mythology.
And now we got this to it. Yeah.
Whoa.
A lot of we should ask. Yeah.
The next time we talk to him, we should ask if he knows the light keepers.
We really. Yeah. Whenever.
I don't know when we'll see him again.
I don't know. Oh, boy.
We have a boy, you know, it's been we got to start.
We start shipping away at all of those missions that we got sent on.
But, you know, with this damn lockdown,
I just don't know when we're going to get to it.
It's a good point.
We may have to push doing all of those.
Yeah, like push, maybe to never do them.
We don't have to push and not ever do that.
Unfortunately, I want to say, look, here's the thing.
If we wish that we can do them, though, our dreams will become magic
and we will be able to.
So I don't want to I don't want to stop wishing that we'll be able to do it.
I want to keep wishing so that our dreams do become real and magic.
Yeah, Scott, don't forget the dreams of today are the magic of tomorrow.
So something to keep in mind.
It is something to keep it. Jason's right.
It's something to keep in mind.
Something to keep in mind.
I'm I'm frightened by all this.
This is this is not a mantra I like.
Anyway, the whole so basically what I'm saying all that for is like
none of those ideas anyone likes, but Disney merchandising was like,
oh, my God, great.
We can have all of this.
The Electrical Parade didn't have characters.
If we do something with characters, then we can sell merch and dolls
of all of the characters.
And that is why the idea of the lumens and the light keepers
ended up becoming the pixies.
We if we come up with all these pixie characters
and everyone to love the pixies, we can sell dolls of all the pixies.
And that brought us to where this thing was called Tinkerbell's Night Magic.
And her name was in the title.
Like the point of it was you're going to see Tinkerbell do a flyby
and they're going to meet all the pixies. Right.
This might be a good time to talk about the pixies who do did end it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah. Although before you start, did they think they wouldn't make money
on stuff like turtles with a cute hat on
or like stuffed light up like neon snails?
Like, what the hell?
Yeah, why aren't they doing that already?
Why aren't there? Why isn't there that now?
I would buy that immediately.
A stuffed stuffed characters of a bunch of the electrical parade.
Yeah, that's great.
Get it done, guys.
Instagram ready.
Yes, yes, absolutely.
Much more so than gods of light.
I feel that anyway, they didn't do gods of light.
They settled on the pixies.
And I had to go into a a message board containing a press release
to find the full list of the pixies.
Are we ready for? Yes.
Let us know. Yeah, yeah.
I am curious.
Will you giggle with delight or will you groan?
The thickest groan ever grown.
Here they are. Let's meet the pixies.
Do drop glitter wing.
Penny whistle.
Mary Bella.
Tumble web.
Huckle web.
Cool. Yeah, there you go.
That's the that's the that's the first mouth vomit.
Bumble drop tickle top.
Well, now now you've got me back.
No, see, I I think I departed at tickle top.
The guy's name is tickle.
It's different strokes.
I don't want to go a guy of character whose life is about tickling.
I.
Perry twinkle.
Why now I'm struggling with whippersnap
pepper pop.
Katie did wiggle wink
pedal skipper.
Then we go down to one name.
I don't know why.
Cricket Piper.
And finally, snuggle bud.
Snuggle bud.
Huh? I'm trying to think.
I think I like wiggle wink the best.
I think my favorite is to see if that even was one
wiggle wink.
I like my favorite.
My two favorites are wiggle wink and skeetal branch.
Those are my two favorites.
What was the huckle one again?
Huckle web huckle web
huckle like huckle berries and then a web.
So it's like a writer's web.
It's a web that has a bunch of berries in it.
Hmm. And there were this two webs is huckle web and tumble web.
I'm not sure if they're related to Jack Webb from Dragnet.
Probably probably different web.
Oh, I forgot to note that snuggle bud.
For some reason, it says snuggle bud or sniggle bud.
What is two names?
Yes, two names.
Important thing about snuggle bud is he is also sniggle bud.
Huh? Snuggle bud bud is also sniggle bud.
Got it.
With recreational marijuana legalization in California,
the California Firefighters Association
does not recommend snuggle bud because you could doze off
with a kind roach in your bed.
So very easy to light fires.
So careful on that snuggle bud, folks.
Jay, I wouldn't be very surprised if you would use
the term snuggle bud in relation to smoking weed and sleeping.
I would not be shocked.
I know. I'm too sensitive to smell.
I couldn't. I couldn't swing that.
I'm too sensitive to time to become a snuggle bud,
to snuggle, to snuggle in the covers with a little joint of marijuana.
Too harsh on the lungs and too dangerous for fire safety.
What if it was like a long kind of elfin like pipe,
like a long pipe with a little like the some of the hobbits might smoke?
Well, the theatricality.
Now you have me back on board.
Would you use a long pipe if I bought it for you for your birthday?
Would you buy it for me?
If it's at a reasonable price.
OK, fair enough.
The long pipe, though, then your hand is really far away from where you light it.
Yeah, that's true.
But is there something with the long pipe?
Do you have to continuously light the long pipe just like a normal pipe?
Or is it a norm? Is it?
Is there some other mechanism in there?
You do occasionally have to.
My dad smoked a pipe for many years and you do have to occasionally tamp down
whatever is in there and relight sometimes.
Yeah. Hmm. OK.
Well, we'll investigate.
Maybe there's new types of long hobbit pipes.
Sure. Oh, I forgot to say that.
Yeah. Wait, there's one more hobbit pipe.
That was that was number seven.
Sure. Mm hmm.
I think actually all of these are probably weed varietals, right?
Oh, yeah.
I got a little is is bumble drop
harsh like I get a little or like it would make me paranoid
Am I better off going with the the pepper pop?
Katie pepper, pepper pop is a sativa.
So you definitely want the first one.
Now, we do have a pedal skipper tumble web blend.
If that sounds up your.
Oh, yeah. Go with that.
That'll mellow you out.
Hydroponic experimentation with the strains. Sure.
Yeah. I by the way, I said that as if that those words
actually meant anything to me.
So I hope that was close.
It works. Yeah. All right.
I bought it. Yeah, I don't know.
Um, well, that is it.
I am I'm drained from saying that list.
Why did they make this list?
No one's ever now.
People might know that that's like the most anyone's ever thought about.
These names is decades later.
I yeah, this is it. Look, this is a thing where I don't I don't hate all those names,
but I've seen the characters.
So like, again, I would love and what I love on the show,
when I declare I love characters, I just were made aware was made aware of.
Yeah, I consistently love that.
But much like Fuzzbucket, I don't like these characters.
I can't get into them.
No, it's hard.
I think I love baby Grinch.
I love Shrek's children, Fergal, Farkas and what's the third one?
Felicia. Thank you.
But I cannot in good conscious conscious,
conscious, you know what I'm saying?
Get behind these fairies and their names.
They well, don't forget.
Also, they look extremely scary.
That's why I think that's the number one.
I think that there's a there's a world where humble bud or whatever.
I like him a lot because I like I can like and I like the elf characters.
I like hobbits. I like all of that type of thing.
But I think it's their nightmarish appearance.
That is putting them off.
And that's why we haven't heard about them in 20 years.
That's why there's no nostalgia.
There's no retro T-shirts with any of these characters on them
that you can count as does it count as nostalgia?
If you were scarred as a child by meeting one of these characters
and you think about it nightly, I mean, that's like a little nostalgia
implies that it's a nice feeling.
Yeah. If you're haunted by the because I should say that
there is a part in this where children were chosen by the Pixies
to come up and dance with them and with the characters.
And so if you were five years old
and you're still getting a grasp on reality and then a character
in a strawberry hat and a big pointy
like a very, very sharp nose walks up to you and says,
I'm tickled top.
Want to dance?
I would. Would the character know name?
I don't know that I'm adding that.
I assume they would, but I just wanted to see if that was actually confirmed.
Mm hmm. That is like in Mission Impossible,
where Tom Cruise is just running at top speed and just going like, no, no, no, no, no.
Like that is I don't like any of that.
I think the the other thing that's kind of rubbing me the wrong way
is that, you know, this parade did sample Baroque down
like every nighttime parade is sampled Baroque down because they know who the king is.
But then some of the other songs like
be our guest step in time when you wish upon a star
a dream is a wish your heart makes part of your world beauty and the like.
It's the big it's so it's it's just too
I don't know. It's too much of the hits.
Do you know what I'm saying?
Like it's all done in this unpleasant manner in this unpleasant manner.
It's too like not condescending is too strong of a word.
But like, I don't know.
It's just rubbing me the wrong way.
It's like desperate. So many great.
It is. Yeah, it's desperate of like, you like all this stuff.
You like this, right?
Like you like this dance. Yeah.
Some of it like that's that's a criticism I would have in general
with like parades and shows like they do rely a lot on the big hits.
Like when the when Disneyland had their 60th anniversary,
the fireworks show had a lot of like these songs as opposed to the
I forget the name of it, the Disneyland Fireworks Show that has like
more like park space songs.
But I was like, why are these movie songs and this show,
which is supposed to be celebrating the history of the park?
So I feel like they I feel like they like I feel like they get it
like a little bit like people your average like vacationer won't be as engaged
if we don't give them like part of your world or we don't give them
the hits from the 90s.
Well, don't discount that there was an original song within Light Magic.
I will. I will discount that.
No, you can't.
You can't because we've been saying all these inspiring lyrics.
And here I don't have a clip cued up, so I have to do it for memory,
which I think I can.
And we can dream our dreams together.
Dream our dreams forever.
Open your heart and keep the dream alive.
Very profound.
A song that some for some reason has also not stood the test of time
in the fan community.
Yeah, I could be wrong.
We're going to get yelled at because some people are going to be really like
they're going to be like, well, like Magic Song was good.
I don't think so.
It's serviceable like it does its job.
But like, again, trying to replace the Electrical Parade, it is it's bizarre.
Yeah, it's just it's a very it's it's very paint by the numbers.
Generic last 30 years, Disney type of song like the like Tokyo,
Disney has a couple of different songs in the last couple of years
that are very much in this vein, but much better song, like much better songs.
Like the song they had when we were there for the for our trip
a couple of years ago is just as sort of generic, but it's just like
incredibly moving for some reason.
Maybe it's because we were so enchanted by going to Japan,
but this is like the the low end of that.
The the parade that debuted right before the parks
shut down for months and months and months,
because I was there, you know, a little bit before that.
And I don't remember the name of the parade, but I caught the song in passing
and kind of a banger.
They sort of figured out like a current pop song
that was pretty good.
I don't know if it's by Todrick Hall, who I'm not completely clear
on what Todrick Hall has done, but I don't know.
Look up this. If anybody caught it before the parks closed, and definitely
pretty good. They like tried a different thing.
And I think they got it.
Um, they they have I we haven't talked about it yet.
Mickey's mix magic, which they were doing,
which is that everybody get your ears on.
Remember this? Remember this song?
Yeah, I like that song.
Well, I like that song, too.
When we were there, when we were in Florida in the fall of twenty nineteen,
they were doing the parade.
Was it called Shake It, Dance, Shake It, Mouse Could Dance It?
Like Mouse Could Dance It was like really grim.
Like I was like, I don't know, guys, I don't know what you're doing here.
Move it, shake it, Mouse Could Dance it, shake it, Mouse Could Dance it.
Like I did not like that.
Don't know. I don't know about that made up word.
Yeah, so there's been ups and downs.
Check out the I don't remember the what is the parade called?
Magic Happens is the parade.
Yes, the Magic Happens song is good.
And it's a bummer they had to close so fast because I had a good feeling about it.
I actually haven't heard the song.
I actually had just not gotten around to listening to it.
I guess I wanted to be like fresh for the parade.
Mm hmm. But who knows?
Will magic happen?
When will the I don't know.
All I know is that the dreams of today are the magic of tomorrow.
Oh, yeah. So that implies the magical happen tomorrow.
Now you're getting it.
I'm hearing a little bit of it.
And I'm worried it's oh, it's like it's got a good beat.
Yes. Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Like they figured out current music in a not embarrassing way.
I'm catching I think Todrick Hall is like a famous person.
Yes, I believe so.
Well, it's like that.
It's like it almost sounds like that Descendants song that I like.
Oh, you remember, I said this to you a while ago.
It's this show, the Disney show, The Descendants, which is like a Disney
channel show about the kids of the Disney villains.
And I've never seen the show, but there's a couple songs I've heard, especially one.
And I'm looking for the title of it that they were playing at a Disneyland.
And I went, what is this song?
Oh, this is this is like almost there's like a little bit of a couple
cheesy parts in it, but I was like, this is pretty good.
And it sounds a little bit like that to me.
Are we is Disney music making a comeback?
Are they figuring it out again?
Yeah, maybe.
I believe that's a series of movies.
I don't think it's a show.
Oh, is that right?
I could be. I think so. Maybe you're showing.
We're sounding a million years old.
Extremely. Yeah.
If we hang on, if we knew everything about The Descendants, I think we
that would be more that would be more upsetting.
Yes.
And we're creepier than we're creepier than Wiggle Wink.
Here's the full here's the full roster of Hollywood records, everyone.
Jason is correct.
It is movie.
There are movies.
The first one directed by Kenny Ortega.
Oh, yeah. Well, he's the guy.
High School Musical.
He's the guy.
So all right.
All all of that.
OK, so we have ended up with this bizarre mix of it's a show.
OK, like it's I think it's all the departments are essentially,
you know, like adding idea.
OK, so it's got to be there's going to be characters so we can do merch.
It's going to be a show.
Fantasmic has this part with a movie and people like that a lot.
There should be like a surprise movie.
And then Tinkerbell is going to go by in the middle.
And so it's like it's all of these things and nothing all at the same time.
It's just it's it's too many cooks.
And meanwhile, the whole point of this whole thing, the Tinkerbell is going to fly by.
They did a test of it and Tinkerbell crashed and burned,
just like shattered in the ground.
So like, we're not doing that legal.
Like, forget it out.
Take Tinkerbell's name out of the thing.
We're not doing this.
So it goes from somewhere in that from night magic to light magic.
But with all of the sort of making it too many things at once
and they're really rushing the company that's building all of the floats
and, you know, we're baggots, exactly what happened in the 70s.
Except they're at Disney's completely at fault in this case.
And they cannot change the date.
They've announced it.
And they realize like, oh, we made so much money off those APs, you know,
having having them say goodbye to Electrical Parade, we can do a big event.
So they book an annual passholder event for twenty five dollars,
which now seems like a real steal of a deal considering how much they charge
for these very good.
I was. Yeah, yeah.
But this was this was new at the time.
But so people are paying extra.
And for that, they get to see the parade before anybody else sees the parade.
But it becomes clear as they're barreling towards this night
is not going to work, is not going to be ready in time.
So they send out Paul Pressler, who is possibly the reason why the park's
got so shitty for a long time.
It's a long story, but he's you know, he was way more merch than he was caring
about shows and stuff.
He comes out and gives a confusing speech where he says,
so what you get to see, what you've paid to see
is a rare peek at a rehearsal, the very first rehearsal
of our new parade, isn't that cool?
And he says rehearsal over and over and everybody starts grumbling like, what?
Why? I never saw the word rehearsal until now.
So something is amiss.
And and then and what I'm trying to do, I'm looking at what else they had fucked up.
They're also like selling
three hundred dollar light magic letterman jackets with
more optics on the inside.
Well, let me find that on eBay.
That rocks. Yeah. Yeah.
That's pretty cool.
And then like, what am I missing?
This is this whole like
they cut from the budget, this whole thing where
cast members before the parade started, we're going to walk up
and down the parade route and say, hey, have you guys seen any pixies
around here lately?
OK, because I hear that I was looking at these charts and it's the the,
you know, the astrology is showing me that the stars are aligning,
which means we could be in prime time for a pixie visit.
So keep on the lookout, everyone.
What?
I this is the thing that Jim Hill claims like would have helped everyone
understand what the story is and why there are pixies.
But that seems so confusing to me.
And oh, and that dialogue included this.
These characters were called pixie hunters.
What? Yes.
Yeah. Wait, wait. Sorry.
I flat past that hunters. Hunters.
The stars are aligning.
We could be due for a pixie visit anyway.
That'll put me in prime spots and nail one right in the head.
Here, I got I got a I got a loaded gun.
I'm on the lookout for pixies.
I'm going to nail me five pixie hides tonight.
Look, we be on the lookout for these beauties or X-Men or whatever you call them.
Hey, kid, take my knife in case you see a pixie, stab one of them.
It'll slow them down so I can catch them.
They'll try to trick you.
I'm taking them to the pixie flesh fair.
We can all take out our anger on pixies together.
Shoot them out of cannons.
Finding a lot of light magic denim jackets.
Yes, I see a lot of denim denim light magic jackets.
One hundred and twenty dollars.
Hey, would you buy one of those for me?
Fiber optics lights on logo.
Well, $90, a $20 shipping.
Damn. Make an offer.
How much?
Forty five, thirty five.
Maybe I maybe I maybe I will.
Hopefully we'll all forget it and then I'll try to buy it for Jason for his birthday.
Oh, OK. I was going to say, though, next live show, if we all come out,
if we don't like to break even.
Matching matching light magic denim jacket denim jacket.
I think like somehow that would awaken that would awaken the spirits
of middle school bullies who didn't have the chance to beat us up then.
No way.
Into the theater and find us.
If I got a light magic logo on the back and a universal
escape logo on the T-shirt, like a beat up universal
escape for the one round of merchandise, they did with those logos.
I think I'm the coolest kid in school.
Coolest kid. Yeah. Coolest kid in the city.
I am seeing a Disney denim embroidered.
Is this what you found? Light magic.
Premier Party jacket.
Oh, that's got to be from this May 1997.
It says, but unlike the other, the other ones don't say Premier Party.
This one says Premier Party.
How much is going for this one is one hundred and twenty to fifteen dollars shipping.
But it's all if they bought it for three hundred on the night of this is kind of
still a little bit of a steal.
Yes, really? Yeah, I would agree.
Yeah. Ninety or seventy five.
I feel like seventy five.
I'm seeing at least starting bid.
Hmm. Hmm. Give it a shot.
If we could do it. The problem is when you search light magic jacket,
you get some industrial light and magic crew gifts,
which would also be a funny thing to walk out wearing.
Yeah, matching.
I'll let him.
Yeah, for red tails, matching red tails, crew gifts.
Oh, boy.
Um, anyway, I the Pixie hunters hurry off
and they say we've got to go warn Mickey about this cosmic occurrence.
You know, those tunes, they hit the hay right after the sun sets.
If we don't wake them up in time, they'll probably sleep through the whole thing.
So so the Pixie, here's what you need to know.
The Pixie hunters need to wake up Mickey from his famously early bedtime
or else he'll miss the parade.
Where are we? What are we?
What is the logic like?
Is he like when people he's in his out his suit, like after dark,
it's happened plenty of times where you can go get a photo with Mickey
after the sun goes down all the time, constantly.
He's always yeah, he's he is clad in bowtie at midnight.
What is this new thing?
You know, those tunes, they hit the hay.
If it's daylight savings, the tunes are going to bed at about, you know, 455.
Right. It's like the tunes are like Jason's sleep schedule.
Yeah.
Are they just trying to justify why Toontown closes before the rest of the park?
I think that's still going on.
That still strikes me as weird.
That is a good point.
I wonder if that's that is part of it.
It's very it's it's very clear.
Hey, what's up, folks? I'm a Pixie hunter.
I've been checking the charts and the Pixies are coming,
so I got to go wake up the tunes.
They live in Toontown.
They close up shop at six because tunes go to sleep early.
And that's why the gate is always closed early.
So I have to go.
This is part of this like newer trend of like, and I know they didn't do this,
but like where we need to explain, it's like no one needed the backstory
of the Main Street Electrical Parade.
No one needed to know.
I like that Imagineering has stories for everything, but every now and then
I'm like, all right, guys, that's enough.
Come on now.
I like this with this magic magnification slash
luminescence machine.
We've taken an ordinary snail and made it giant and glowing.
Yeah.
Everyone get out of its way or it'll infect you.
Stand behind the yellow lines.
The seven dwarves are going through a midlife crisis,
and they've decided to dress a little bit differently from now on.
They want to see more hip and with it.
They want to be like their favorite rock and roll icons.
So be prepared when they're wearing your shiny pants or leather pants.
Hey, if Dopey's got his kids with them, they're on a visitation.
So try not to bother Dopey.
Get your picture with the six other dwarves.
Don't take pictures of Dopey Jr.
Dopey's the dumbest.
Dopey's the dumbest, so he didn't practice safe sex.
So he had too many children, too young.
Yeah. Yeah.
He had like 25 kids when he was 10.
And to have to pay for all of them using gems.
Well, those are very valuable, though.
So that's true.
But he's got to he's got to get like 200 a day just to make ends meet.
That's a good point.
That is why I get to them before the other dwarves.
You know what I was thinking?
There is a character that we came upon on a second gate episode
that really would be perfect for the light magic parade,
and they could have just plugged him in easily and no one would have.
Everyone would have been like, this is this character is perfect here.
Do we know who I'm talking about?
No. Leonardo Columbus.
Oh, it does me well to hear that name again. Yeah.
Famous Epcot character from Tapestry of Dreams
later in the Tapestry of Dreams.
Leonardo Columbus.
Who Leonardo Columbus from Tapestry of Dreams would have been right at home
in light magic, the parade that teaches you that the dreams of today
are the magic of tomorrow. Yes. Yes.
Exactly. So you put he would just be like hanging out in
in one of these different floats.
And it would have been great.
I mean, they would have gotten breathe new life into a classic character.
Banging on a giant gumdrop. Yeah.
Wow. There goes Leonardo.
You wouldn't think that Glitterwing and Petalskipper
would be good friends with Leonardo Columbus, but they're best buds.
Yeah, he's as his bumble bud.
Maybe he's like a pixie keeper or something.
There's now there's more story we have to more extra story.
Every millennium, the gates of time open up
and through it steps a pixie keeper.
He keeps them safe from the pixie hunters.
The pixie hunter, the pixie keeper.
OK, just so you're clear, the pixie keeper is different than the pixie hunter.
The pixie keeper is good.
The pixie hunters are bad.
But they also though they are bad, they're also the ones who go
and wake up the characters who go to bed at early bird times,
which is not necessarily bad.
Not so not everything they do is bad.
It's a symbiotic relationship, a symbiote.
OK, we use you can't get rid of the pixie hunters.
You need the pixie hunters and the pixie keepers.
They balance each other out.
Don't be scared.
Do it.
Whip or snap will be fine, as long as there are both pixie keepers
and pixie hunters.
My brain is so tired right now.
I know. We have to we have to end this soon or I'm like my chest is hurting,
as is my brain.
I don't need to.
Oh, wait, so wait, one more thing.
I'll say. Yeah.
On man.
OK, in addition to all this, we're talking about the gate of time
opening once a millennium in this on extra special nights,
a magical doorway opens between our world and the fairy realm.
And if we're lucky, the pixies might appear and teach us the secret
of making our dreams come true.
Wow. Oh, fuck.
They teach us the secret to the tapestry of our dreams.
Which and the tapestry includes both the magic of light and the magic of night.
Magic of light, magic of night.
Oh, God.
Oh, God. Brain rotting shit.
So long story short, this parade, which even when it's operating,
operated at its best, was disliked on its first night
when it was a sudden rehearsal that people paid to see operated very terribly.
As I said, the opening, you know, very jarring Celtic horns
just blared in a loop for seven straight minutes.
One of the floats was missing.
All kinds of shit went wrong.
And pass holders all there was a line out the door of City Hall.
People demanding their money back.
Does my God PR nightmare.
And one of the people in that line and in the audience is a name that you will know.
And that name is Al Lutz. Wow.
Oh, yeah. Yep. Yep.
Bizarre figure who keeps coming up on the show at that time
was a major figure in all Disney,
not Disneyland, a real big like fan complainer, real pass
hole, as you might say, and he got his review up ASAP.
He actually said, I'm sorry if this wasn't thorough enough.
I stayed up all night to write it. And it's six a.m. now.
He like drove home.
Let me please details.
And it was a gigantic write up.
He did the highlight of which is the beginning where he says,
I'm very sorry to have to say that as a show and concept,
it is a complete and total abject failure, folks.
Until last night, I had never seen an audience start to boo a show
at the park before ever.
He he also described it as Yanni meets the chieftains,
which is pretty damning in and of itself.
And he like he's he does.
It's a very like it's like a Twitter thread before there were Twitter threads.
He says, stop all caps ads for everywhere for light magic.
Now there are serious problems with how it runs and how it is stage.
It is not ready for prime time.
Cut the running time of the show in half now that there is too much dancing.
The choreography is limited.
It will not sustain interest.
It is a screed that this guy posts.
And then that's quoted in the L.A.
Times legitimately outlets helped kill this show right out of the gate.
Wow. That rules that rock so much.
Right. He stayed up all night like a real journalist.
This is a real the post scenario.
He got it out this time and the Disney scandal of the summer.
They never recovered from it.
A horrible PR right out of the gate.
And yeah, one of the biggest failures in Disneyland history.
I have a few quick things, and I am only saying these because Yesterland,
which is a great resource to kill a few hours.
I mean, it's very thorough about like long gone Disneyland and Disney World stuff
emphasize these points to the point where I was like,
this is kind of unusual for this website to like emphasize these things.
So I thought I'd call them out.
I mentioned this earlier.
One, the confetti they fired off was mylar,
which is a very like thin kind of plastic.
I thought you were I thought you were making a joke.
Oh, no, they fired off mylar confetti,
which was apparently very difficult to clean up.
You know, confetti, normally little bits of paper where if you don't get it all,
it doesn't matter because it biodegrades pretty quickly.
No, no, this was sheets of plastic.
I have something about.
OK, so in that Los Angeles Times article I keep bringing up here,
I'm just going to read these two sentences.
Pixies tossing about silver confetti,
pixie dust and larger confetti storms had most children squealing in delight.
But there were exceptions.
Look what she did to our food, exclaimed one little girl
after a dusting left her meal inedible.
Oh, my God.
They blasted mylar into somebody's food.
So that is the pixie dust.
The pixie dust is mylar confetti is mylar confetti.
They make balloons out flammable.
Yeah, that's right.
Um, the other thing is that so the long
the stuff you can still see from light magic,
those big light rigs over by small world sort of in the small world style
were originally set up for light magic.
And there's still that infrastructure improvement is still there.
So that's you can thank light magic for that.
You have to credit the and they they also tiered it.
They made it so like, you know, you could, you know, here's like increasing steps
so more people could have a view of the parade.
So, yes, there were infrastructural accomplishments that came out of this thing.
Yeah. So it wasn't all bad.
It wasn't all bad.
That there was still was more bad, such as that the five
Lazarus, the fiber optic company that they hired to put in all the for that.
I guess that's we missed that.
There was a lot of fiber optics in this and they've used that throughout to to.
They've used fiber optics to good effect in the fantasy land rides.
And so you can also credit it with like, oh, they got to experiment with fiber
optics. But anyway, the company they hired
sued Disney for hurting their reputation, for claiming it was all their faults.
The floats weren't ready and that event was a disaster.
They also Lazarus apparently was also owed half a million dollars
in unpaid labor by Disney.
Oh, my God. I forget how that played out.
Yep. But they got very hardcore sued by a fiber optics company. Wow.
Do you do you guys know the final fuck you of this parade?
Maybe not. I don't know.
When they retired it, they said it will return in the year
2000, which they said in the fall of 1997,
if an attraction goes down for three years,
that means the entire track is being gutted and redone.
If a parade is being retired for three years, it's dead.
Like that's such a fuck you.
That's so wild that they're like, it'll be back in the year 2000.
That is that is interesting that they would say that because like
they famously like kind of don't like to announce when something is done.
It's kind of just a quiet.
It's a quiet disappearing, unless it's some big famous thing.
Yeah, like, yeah, it's sort of like they don't want to like acknowledge it.
So like, yeah, were they thinking like, well, I'll just say it like
everyone's going to forget in three years.
Yeah, very similarly, they said the rocket rods would be back
and they did not return.
I mean, we got to hit rocket rods soon.
I know. Wow.
Yeah, that's a whole other.
It's all kind of like the at the end of Mac and me
where one of the aliens blows a big bubble gum bubble
and the bubble says, we'll be back.
Oh, it's like a threat.
It's more of a lesser sequel implication and more of a threat.
Yeah, she's kind of like this.
I think I find the Mac and me aliens cuter than Snigglewig and all these fucks.
We need I agree.
We need like we need inside inside
inside sources that would let us go on and talk about stuff like
was there a fight to keep it?
Was there actually like they're like, yes, we will.
We will actually make this vision a reality in 2000.
And then other people were like, let's just cut our losses here.
I want to know all that stuff.
It was that guy.
It might have been that guy.
We cannot kill the dreams of tomorrow.
The magic of tomorrow.
They must. The dreams must live on.
Huh? You can you can slash the it's up there.
It's easy for you up there in your ivory tower.
You can just delete an item in a spreadsheet.
But how am I going to break this to the to the people who matter
to tumble web to to pepper pop to wiggle wink
and not not little huckle web?
Please don't make me fire little huckle web.
Come on, man.
Bitty bottom just had a fucking kid.
Come on.
Huckle web like going like a slow,
sad movie scene of huckle web going home and telling his wife he got laid off.
Rubble, rubble, snug, rubble, snug, just bought a house.
He thought he was going to be here for years.
Giggle bottom wasn't just liked, he was well liked.
OK, we're going to have to move
back to the enchanted forest.
Cheaper than really Loman was a pixie.
It's a pixie among pixies.
What a topic.
I how can you do this to ripple, but
ripple, ripple, but is sick.
You just got diagnosed.
This is not the time.
After all, ripple, but is done for you.
We should do a challenge
for the social media where we give we give ourselves like two minutes
and we just come up with as many names.
As we can in those two minutes.
And then like, we'll post them or we'll post a video of it.
Hopefully, we'll remember to do this.
All right, we got to Hickle Dick.
Tummy, tummy toodles.
Toofy spooder.
Well, now, now you're making money if you're talking to spooders.
Toofy spooder is a good proven merchandise commodity. Yes. Yeah.
I think there's one more thing I could say that really that
sums up the spirit of light magic, and it's a moment
involving our friend, Tony Little,
who is interviewing a soap opera star who I've never seen before in my life,
who is one of the one of the only celebrities available for this event.
And Tony is interviewing this guy and his wife and his two little children.
You know, really young boys.
And, you know, she wants to get them involved.
So she leans in and like, well, boy, this is a pretty spectacular night, huh?
A new street, tackler.
Is there anything you're especially looking forward to tonight?
And the kid kid kind of like goes inward and says,
Oh, I guess not.
And then stops talking and kind of like goes like hugs his dad's leg.
Like, don't make me talk anymore.
And they let that in.
Well, it was live. Oh, no.
I don't know. Oh, no.
That's not.
That's the reason now that all these newer specials are so like polished
is because of like Regis saying weird stuff to the audience and like kids
saying that they're not excited about any of this crap.
They are making damn sure that Doug Jones can't do any of his mixes.
They're like the mixes he makes a bizarre moments in these specials are impossible.
There are they're designed to have no moments like that.
Yeah, it's a shame.
It's a real shame. No father.
I but that kid starting to tear up, mumbling, I guess not.
And then hugging his father.
That's that's sort of how light magic makes you feel at the end of the day.
Makes you want to call your dad, give him a hug.
Think about anything else.
Just try to hide from the world.
That's that's right.
You want to you want to you want to hug your dad, not see a huggle dad.
All that said, we would we would 100 percent by huggle dad merch.
I would buy a T-shirt.
I would buy a T-shirt if they did a throwback shirt with the light magic logo
with the logo they had on the giant sign
by the the kind of overpay the underpasses that lead to Main Street.
I know where you can get a denim jacket, Jason.
I think this needs to be done.
This needs to be, you know, let's make let's make some offers.
How long do fiber optics last?
Twenty.
Twenty three years.
Do they still work?
Twenty three years later, we should sue the fiber optics company if they don't work.
Sam, right. Oh, hell, you're us.
I well, let's order this item and then we'll ask how long before it comes?
When is the how long is the shipping take?
And and I bet their answer will be, well, all we can say is the dreams
of today are the magic of tomorrow.
Shipping twenty five dollars.
Fair enough.
I guess with that, what did we settle on again?
You you listened to podcast, the right you pay up with.
I think I said you put out you put up you put up with podcast, the right.
It would very true in this case.
Dear God, we really boy.
And we recorded these in the same day.
So we really we really ran the gamut from a parade of delights
to a parade of fright.
And the lights like the lights in this room are going down.
I feel like I've I feel like I've lived the whole three months at the parade existed.
Yeah.
I also dear Lord, I want to quick say that the song I was talking about
is called Chillin Like a Villain from the Descendants Two.
That's the song I like.
Right.
Um, well, sounds sounds better than dream your dreams together.
It is a lot better.
But I would encourage everyone listening to open your hearts
and keep your dreams alive.
And if you don't open your hearts, then, you know, Snickleweb
be in your bedroom.
We should I'll just do not say Snickleweb three times into a mirror.
Whatever you do.
I should just put in like random sideshow Bob getting hit with the rake noises.
This episode is like this very it's like the sentiment of most of it,
of what we're reacting to for sure.
Well, then you're right before you're right before we go.
Let me just remind of one more glitter wing.
Do it now, do it.
Somebody's got to do it here.
Glitter wing.
Oh, that about says it.
All right, folks, thanks for listening.
Thanks for tolerating.
Bye bye. Bye.