Forever.
Dog.
Morning, the following podcast features depressed children, photo ops that take place in a dirty
livery stable, and a really, really great pumpkin.
Sit down on top of a piano and gaze lovingly at your podcast listening device.
It's Camp Snoopy on Podcast The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the theme park podcast that...
My name is Mike Carlson, joining me as always, Jason Sheridan.
You downplayed what that was, and I love it so much.
Joining me as always, Scott Gierner as well.
Did you love it as much as Jason?
Oh, good grief.
Yeah, you know I did though, because I like things like that.
I like Snoopy sounds.
You know, I like the music.
There's so much aesthetically, you know, just little cues that make me so happy about the
Peanuts universe.
So I'm excited we're going to talk about it today.
Yes, there is.
Yes, there's so many different iconic parts of it.
I will say Snoopy's noises sometimes are unnerving to me.
Sure, sure.
Like when he cries, it's so like grating and it's like makes you so sad.
Oh, yeah.
Like when he like, he like kind of whines.
You know what I'm talking about?
That specific Snoopy whine.
I don't have a full soundboard over there, do you?
I don't have a full peanut soundboard, although we should just have that in general for the
podcast where we can soundboard like a morning zoo and just have any sort of Peanuts sound
effect ready to go.
But only peanuts, exclusively peanuts.
But just peanuts, yeah.
Just peanuts.
I do think Peanuts is like a good thing that encompasses like all, all emotion.
Like it is good for kids because it has so many emotions.
I would go so far as to say I think it's one of the few like big evergreen pieces of popular
culture.
You mean like it'll be around forever, always relevant?
It'll be around forever.
You can give it to anyone at any age and I think it like makes sense, you know?
It's got, yeah, it's got cute character designs.
It's got existential dread.
Yes.
It's got a mix of things for all ages.
It's very sweet without being cloyingly so.
Yeah, there's nice messages, but it's not like the most like moralistic in your face
thing either.
It's just perfectly pleasant.
Like who wouldn't love to take a little trip to Peanuts world as we're doing right now?
Right.
Sure.
So we're going to talk obviously about the theme park aspects, but I assume, yeah, with
a topic like peanuts, we should probably do a little up top about just our, you know,
growing up with peanuts.
I like many kids watched the Halloween special and the Christmas special and read the cartoon
strips.
I am not a peanuts nut though.
I'm not crazy because I think I just want to say that up front.
I'm going to probably get things wrong about peanuts because I know there are much like
there are Muppet people.
I know there are peanuts people.
So I just want to say I'm not an expert.
I feel like I've seen less evidence of that as I learned researching a little bit.
There's a very exhaustive peanuts wiki, but there's exhaustive wikis for all things on
this earth.
So I will.
You know, I think the peanuts people probably skew older.
Yeah, I think the Calvin and Hobbes people are more intense.
Right.
I think that's right.
But I found a lot of stuff online and tell me if you found stuff like this.
I found a lot of articles talking about Snoopy ruining peanuts.
What?
Yes.
Talking about.
So this I guess we should just I get this right out of the way because this is one of
the most fascinating things I found and it's not it's not theme park related at all.
But I found an article in the Atlantic.
Okay.
Defend defending Snoopy against criticisms of him ruining peanuts.
This argument needed to be made.
Is there enough anti Snoopy ism out there?
I get this is what I'm saying.
I open up a whole world for myself of like peanuts opinions.
Is it sort of an Elmo?
Yes.
In fact, is that what the idea that like it's it's silly and really the oracleification
there is, you know, there's this whole the specific world here and now it's just become
all about this single character is silly and there's not as much.
If I had to guess what the line of thought was, even though it's dumb as it is about
all those other ones, too, especially Urkel.
Yes. But I know it's it's fun.
We're taking over happy days.
It's Jimmy J.J.
Walker taking over Good Times, the Sector Keeper taking over podcasts, the ride.
Exactly. There are people that believe the podcast was better before the City Walk Saga.
If you took Snoopy out of the peanuts, it would just be way too bleak.
Like, I think his antics and whimsy help balance out like, you know, the dread, the ennui.
Yes. So, yeah, well, a world without a cute dog to counterbalance everything.
That's like the Trump White House.
Yes, exactly.
So I look, I agree with you guys.
I'm just saying I stumbled upon like the intelligentsia of peanuts who there's
a there's a multiple articles about Snoopy rooting peanuts.
Basically, like I think about 15 years into the strip is when they started doing more
of like Snoopy's flights of fancy.
Which is very Urkel-esque alter egos and little adventures that are entirely about him
and that leave the other peanuts in the dust.
This is all pre-date circle ism.
Right. I think this is one of the earliest examples of sort of a character like superseding
the other characters in popularity and sort of doing something that's just fun, that
more people probably respond to than the actual like original mission statement of the
TV show or cartoon strip.
Well, I've read the first few years of peanuts and it any comic strip that runs for
decades and decades evolved significantly as it goes along.
And certainly Charles Schultz's art style really evolved as the years went on.
That's true. But I'd like to say when I can you're talking about our personal connections
to peanuts. I don't know that I prefer it, but I really like the original peanuts
designs where they're they're they're littler.
They're kind of like squatter and blanker looking like if you if you just Google
peanuts, 1952 or 1953, you guys know what I'm talking about?
I know. I know what you're talking about.
Yes, I have some in front of I think the issue with some of that is a lot of the characters
aren't super fleshed out yet.
So a lot of them is kind of hard to track some of them because they all look a little
similar. But it is it is different but appealing.
The art style.
Yeah, I just find it. I wouldn't replace current Charlie Brown with it.
But Charlie Brown, 1953, I like can't stop looking at these.
So cute. I might I might be babies on the brain now, but he is more like a baby of
Charlie Brown. That's true.
The very first peanut strip is so funny.
Like, it's so it just hits the ground running.
Do you guys have peanuts?
Strip how I hate him.
Is that it? Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Here I'll text. I have it in front of me.
The first panel is Charlie Brown walking along and then two kids sitting on a step
and a boy says, well, here comes old Charlie Brown.
Good old Charlie Brown.
Yes, sir. Good old Charlie Brown.
How I hate him.
It's so dark.
Yeah, so that's what the purists were upset about.
Snoopy ruining is is that darkness?
Which I could see I could see some points about it, but, you know, we don't have a
fun dog adventure once in a while.
Absolutely. I also like puppy Snoopy a lot.
Baby Snoopy is very cute as well.
My baby, Aladar, but yeah, maybe a few things are.
My mom had the old dolls, the old peanuts dolls are based on more of like the first
designs and they were kind of beat up or they're still beat up.
But when I was in Japan, I found they like there's a they're called like ultra
detailed figures and I found original design peanuts figures.
They're new, but they're making them based on that original peanuts design that
you're talking about and not the newer ones.
How do you define this?
What do you call it? Is it just original peanuts?
Because I kind of want some some merch.
Well, right. I know I should look it up because.
I don't know if they even.
Oh, you know what? I take this back.
There's a company called Super Seven that just started making the same type of
designs with peanuts and they came out last year.
So I wonder if they I'm going to take a quick look.
I wonder if they designate or like they make it a specific like,
I don't know, brand or name for what the old style peanuts design.
Oh, I say, yeah, yeah, I got this in front of me now.
Yes, Super Seven.
Yeah, very good. Yeah.
And they come one of them comes in a package
with the strip that Jason just read to us.
Yes. So I guess there's probably I didn't find too many
like people arguing online about the differences, but like what's better, new or old.
But I imagine those people exist, too.
Mm hmm. But they don't they probably don't listen to the show,
so they won't be upset with us. Sure.
I do want to I do real quick want to read a couple just to see
illustrate the type of discourse around this.
Christopher Caldwell wrote in 2000, a month before Charles
Charles L. Charles M. Schultz, right? That's his name.
Died. He wrote an essay in New York Press titled Against Snoopy.
He wrote, but certainly by the 1970s, Snoopy had begun
wrecking the delicate world that Schultz had built.
The problem is, Caldwell saw it was that Snoopy was never a full participant
in the tangle of relationships that drove peanuts in its golden age.
He couldn't be. He doesn't talk and therefore he doesn't interact.
He's there to be looked at.
That's insane. That's insane.
I've got strips.
I've got a ton of strips in front of me of like him interacting with with all of them.
Like, I don't. That's bizarre.
Yes, I agree.
I was just Christopher Caldwell.
What a what a miserable man.
What do you think of the minions?
Oh, my God. We should find his minions, I say.
Although he might like them because there are inter
relationships between them and they they do speak to some extent.
Mm hmm.
Yeah, there is a tangled web as far as the minions relationships are concerned.
I will Google his name and minions right now.
Super seven has an action figure that is Snoopy
wearing Charlie Brown's shirt and a Charlie Brown mask.
And that is a little unsettling.
Oh, I've seen that. Yeah, that is unsettling.
Yeah, that's fair. That's from a strip.
Caldwell's nightmare, you call it.
The first article is like he's writing about like civil rights
revolutions and stuff right now in Wikipedia.
This is I assume this is the same man who wrote about Snoopy ruining the peanuts.
Huh?
He people are upset, though, like in that store, I bought those peanuts in Japan.
The the floor is not called peanuts.
It's called Snoopy town.
And that's cited as a that's cited as a problem.
And we know we're talking about Camp Snoopy today.
So that's another thing.
People are upset that Snoopy gets the brand over peanuts.
The name peanuts.
It's not by people.
By people, you mean 12 people.
People, nine of whom have since died.
It's possible they're like 12 intellectuals
are really the ones who are upset about this.
And they'd be upset anyway.
Yeah. I mean, I don't know.
Are they upset about like changes in the Beatle Bailey strip?
Perhaps. Yeah.
And I do want some gasoline alley.
And I want to say peanuts is not King features syndicate.
It's United Feature syndicate.
Yeah, at least it was when when Schultz was making it.
I don't know if it's changed hands now.
So but it is as long as it's a syndicate.
I don't trust a comic coming from a non syndicate.
Yes.
It's a syndicate, which I, of course, I think of the sinister syndicate,
which is another version of Spider-Man's multivillain gang
that tries to stop him.
But no, these are just nice companies that want to put comic strips,
cartoon strips out into the world.
Why does the Green Goblin get the attention over the rest of the Sinister Six?
We've overlooked their tangled web of right.
I mean, they would be upset like Hobgoblin would usurp Green Goblin's glory
because Hobgoblin was newer,
but he's just like an orange version of the Green Goblin.
So there would be anti Christopher Caldwell will write about Hobgoblin,
I assume soon.
About the injustice that was done to the Green Goblin.
Yeah. Yeah. Well, then I'll put a flaming bag of poo on his door.
That's what I'll do. All right.
I hate this guy. This guy's a stick in the mud.
He's like a it's like a mean principle in a movie.
He deserves to be to be pranked until he can't face the public anymore.
Mm hmm. I'm going to carry this guy.
You're going to become like a real bully.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. This guy around.
Can I see if he has a Twitter account?
I'm going to start responding to everyone.
But like with the most anti intellectual thing I could say.
Let's see. He is.
I'm going to try to find his Twitter.
His first credit on Wikipedia was editor at the Weekly Standard,
which is kind of a right wing kook publication.
I think more like a weekly more like the weekly shit turd.
Yeah, take that.
Caldwell. Yeah, boy.
He's going to rue the day he ever wrote something that Scott heard about
two decades later.
Snoopy is there to be looked at.
I mean, that's yeah, that's what I'm doing.
I'm doing that, too.
Yeah, that's true. He's right.
He's right about that.
Well, yeah, not every not every statement that don't Caldwell makes
it that far off base.
Oh, man, I just found another anti Snoopy quote by a different writer.
I shouldn't read it, but I have to.
I am getting upset.
I know. Let's get to the fun ice show.
Hold on. Hold on. I have to do a day.
I got to hear it.
Daniel Mendelsohn put it in a piece in the New York Times Book Review.
Snoopy represents the part of ourselves, the smugness, the avidity,
the pomposity, the rank egotism.
Most of us know we have, but try to keep decently hidden away.
All these psychos would be the people going like we've got to push on to Baghdad.
That oil is art like this in between their in between their warmongering pieces.
The writing about how Snoopy is a piece of shit.
This is insane.
Hey, you man, you, Lee Mendelsohn.
I was Daniel. Oh, no.
Oh, wait, Lee is a oh, I'm sorry.
I think Lee Mendelsohn is oddly it's the same name.
I think Lee Mendelsohn might be a Snoopy or a Snoopy, a peanuts producer, I think.
Wait, is he the opposite of Mendelsohn?
I have that name in my head. I think it might be right.
So sorry, Daniel. It's Daniel Mendelsohn.
Yes, Daniel Mendelsohn.
Yes, sure. That's so weird.
Yeah, the producer of all because I was just looking up.
Oh, my God, who passed away on Christmas of 2019.
Oh, my God. I guess I was.
It was a total mistake to say he is the one who Mendelsohn's
because this guy the opposite of because I was reading about how did Vince
Garaldi, the wonderful musician buying all the peanuts music, get involved.
And it was that this producer just like heard some of his jazz on the radio
and like, I don't know, should be him.
And then you want to do it.
And two weeks later, he called and just put his phone up to the
put the phone up to the piano and started playing the iconic
Linus and Lucy that we know today. Wow.
Yeah, yeah. We'll get a little.
We'll get some more of the magic very soon on the podcast.
Don't worry. We'll get we're going to get away from this.
This negativity, this is intellectual.
This is like this populism.
This is like people who like the Beatles but hate wings.
Yes, exactly.
What would be funny?
No, I don't accept that at all.
What are those people?
What do you mean?
Wait, on which side?
Oh, no, I just like wings a lot.
Like, yeah, hell yeah.
Fuck. Yeah.
You like wings and you like Snoopy as you should.
Yeah.
It's also I like I think of wings as just being like nice, you know?
I don't think of it as very.
Yeah, I don't know how you could have an agenda against wings.
I don't know. And it is only like snooty journalists.
That's that it's the exact same syndrome.
Only a snooty journalist because anyone else would just go, that's fun.
Yes. Yeah, it's crazy.
I mean, Paul McCartney solo career.
Yeah, he got so much shit.
And if you go through it, it's like, of course, there's some schmaltzy garbage in there.
But like the majority of it is good.
He was Paul McCartney.
It's not like he changed from the year the couple of years in the Beatles.
He was just making like good pop songs.
I don't know what people people's problem was.
The schmaltzy garbage didn't really start till like three years ago.
My Valentine, my Valentine.
OK, he has a song called My Valentine for his current wife.
And we saw him at Dodgers a couple of years ago and he played My Valentine.
And I've never seen so many people go to the bathroom.
It was in the middle of the show.
He sat down. Everyone was losing their mind.
It's hit after hit after hit.
It's like 15 hits in a row.
You're as high as possible.
We were lucky and had very good seats that year.
And he plays My Valentine.
And it was just a map.
People running to the bathroom.
Now, there's a flood.
There is suddenly on the field just a torrent of yellow.
And it swept Paul away.
And he wasn't able to finish the concert.
Whoops. Oh, boy.
Oopsie, Daisy.
Well, whoopsie, Paul.
Paul, you have to stop playing My Valentine.
It's ruining the plumbing systems of all the cities you're performing.
So what keeps up?
Is that what those little flood sees are?
Yes, you have to look.
I understand you want to play it for Dancy.
If you want to start the show with My Valentine, maybe
because they won't have a full bladder at that point.
So be my own opening act, you mean?
That's fine. If that's if that's what you need to do.
But you cannot have My Valentine be played
any more than like five songs into the show.
I think I'm going to play it seven times.
Paul.
That's just Paul. That's just Paul.
So, yeah, my val...
So, yes, he's got look, I don't know if any.
I think that's gone.
I think that's mostly gone, except for like grizzled, like
60 year olds who are still like hung up about wings and stuff being bad.
I think that we're arguing a point that was that
should have been argued in 1978.
We're mad.
This is an issue that was maybe settled before we were born.
We're still in the jungle fighting the war and the war is over.
Nobody told us.
We're still trying to defend the wings.
This is like the peanuts arguing.
I could see happening
because it feels very comic shop arguing, but it's the
it's the very niche of niche.
Like it's the narrow portion of the comics world
because most like classic comic strips have like the big ones
have collections from like fan of graphics or drawn in quarterly,
which has a lot of art, you know,
you know, acclaimed graphic novels, too.
And a lot of those people have very strong opinions about like
little Lulu and gasoline alley.
Sure. Yes.
I mean, we have strong opinions, too.
We know that, but ours are better opinion.
Ours are better. Yeah.
In general.
That's oh, yeah, of course.
And that's why you come here to listen to our better opinions.
Better opinions.
I do. I don't want to go right back to wings.
I just looked down and realized I'm wearing a wings jet shirt.
Yeah, I didn't realize that as we talked about wings,
I was sporting the merchandise.
And when I just looked down and I am in a full Snoopy bathrobe and slippers,
I assume Jason as well.
Oh, I am in my full Red Baron gear.
As I am every podcast recording.
You got the goggles.
Those are going to be fogged up by the time this is over.
OK, I guess the goggles fly off my head as I start going into Snoopy's
extensive family tree.
We're going to need some fan art of that.
That's all I'll say.
Who don't want to don't want to beg, just saying, putting it out there.
You got quarantine time.
Let's see Jason in the goggles and Scott in the robe, too.
Yeah. Well, I'll just do that and post a picture.
I'll do my own fan art.
That's good. That's a good point.
Well, what is there more misery?
No, I think I mean, there is, but that's that's the gist of it.
And that's just what I was I kept running into, which I found fascinating.
We saw stuff odd, and especially because
the Snoopy opinions at this point boiled down to
mostly like a three year old going Snoopy,
because, you know, in the in the theme parks, especially the presence is very
little kid. I mean, I think that's the is there a peanuts attraction
or show that isn't for the youngest children?
Yeah, that's a good question. I didn't see one.
I mean, there's a lot of there's the the peanuts are in a lot of different
places in theme parks.
But I find, yeah, it's a very confusing.
Yeah. Corporate breakdown where, you know, we obviously know it
primarily from Knott's Berry Farm, which we're close to in our beloved B Park.
It is also currently in Cedar Point.
It's in Carowinds.
It's controlled by the Cedar Fair organization.
Can we? But was also.
Oh, sorry, I was going to say, I can go into this.
I have the timeline on this.
Sure, sure. Oh, yeah, go for it.
So Camp Snoopy, the camp Snoopy area, Snoopy first showed up at Knott's in 1983.
And so it had it was there first.
And the camp Snoopy area at Knott's is very good.
A lot of big trees and like fun rides.
And there's a big cave you can walk through.
And then when Knott's bought,
Knott's got bought by Cedar Fair in 1997,
they were able to adjust the agreement, the licensing agreement
so that it could be used at all the Cedar Fair parks.
And the timing was very helpful
down the line because Cedar Fair would start to absorb
a lot of the former Paramount parks.
So the Snoopy stuff would go on to replace a lot of
Nickelodeon play areas.
And in some cases, I remember this specifically at Doherty Park replaced
Bernstein Bear play areas as well.
Oh, interesting.
But then also, and we're jumping all around, we'll go ahead individual ones.
But at the Mall of America,
the theme park in the center of the Mall of America was Camp Snoopy.
And then that got replaced by Nickelodeon stuff.
So Nickelodeon and Peanuts have been at war for many years.
It's been a turf war, really.
And I don't know who's winning. I think Nickelodeon might be winning.
I think there's more probably Nickelodeon theme park presence,
which we will have to get to at some point.
Yeah. And the American Dream Mall is Nickelodeon, right?
Oh, that's right. Yes, indeed.
Yeah, we've been we also have that's part of the the sector keeper.
There has also made us wants us to go do that eventually as well.
Oh, that's right. And we should say
Camp Snoopy is not Planet Snoopy.
They're different.
Own only Cedar Point has both Camp Snoopy and Planet Snoopy.
Most parks have Camp Snoopy or Planet Snoopy.
And wait, is you both separately?
Apparently from I saw some things and I could be wrong,
but at least Wikipedia was saying Cedar Point has both.
And what about this?
I it's it's indecipherable.
It I think there might be a little more space kind of stuff,
although Mike, you and I saw some of a Snoopy
space show at a camp Snoopy at the Knotts Camp Snoopy before.
So I think it all just kind of, you know, they they might rename some stuff
Planet Snoopy when they give it a fresh coat of paint or add a couple more new rides.
But also then confusing it even more.
So so peanuts are usually in these non Disney Universal parks.
But then in Universal Studios Japan, there is a kids area called Universal Wonderland,
which is home to Sesame Street, which is also all across
Splatter all across the universe.
Sesame Street, Hello Kitty and Snoopy Studio are things of that.
So we're the only in Japan.
It's a universal property.
Yes, because the licensing agreement Cedar Fair only operates parks.
I believe in America, maybe there's one Canadian Cedar Fair Park.
I could be wrong.
But mostly in America.
Right. So it's a big confusing web.
It's it's definitely hard to chart.
And you made it more confusing knowing that there's camps and planets
right next to each other.
Yeah. And then there's also like by the Schultz Museum,
there's like an ice skating rink.
As well. Yes.
Well, here, this might be I can explain some of this stuff that
because I didn't know the connection between I didn't know why all the ice skating
in not just I mean, obviously, in like in the Christmas special.
That's so iconic.
But then, you know, not to be doing Snoopy ice shows for a very long time.
And I think it's all a product of Charles Schultz growing up in Minnesota.
So having a very skate centric existence.
But since 1969 in his home in his town of Santa Rosa,
he has owned no longer as he's passed away, but owned it.
Still, his family operates this place, which is what's the official name?
Redwood Empire Ice Arena.
But then it's it's casually called Snoopy's Home Ice.
Yeah. On the website, it's Snoopy's Home Ice,
unless that's just a specific part of the website.
But I'm looking at the website that Snoopy's Home Ice.
And of course, it has a place to eat as well,
which is called, of course, the warm puppy cafe.
Adorable. So cute.
It's got a fireplace that sounds so lovely.
And the whole thing is very Swiss Alps themed.
It's that Solvang Madonna in kind of vibe,
which I always like anywhere in this world, the Matterhorn to love.
I love 60s Swiss Alps stuff.
Always. It's great.
And I don't know if you found this fact, but in 1973, Schultz
and his wife divorced, and a month later he married Jeannie Clyde,
a woman he met at the warm puppy cafe.
Whoa. He built his own pickup spot.
That's right. Wow.
That's interesting.
So so then the the ice skating connection is also what led
to the entire Knott's relationship, because it was in 1982
that they were poking around like, well, we don't do a lot with IP.
And, you know, it might be fun to try to do something with Snoopy,
but they had to approach Schultz.
And he was interested because he has such a big ice skating connection.
And his daughter is an ice skater.
I think his whole family are ice skaters.
So just kind of in him trying to seal the deal, he said,
all right, if you do the show, could my daughter play Snoopy?
And that sort of that pushed it over the finish line.
And then that show went over so well, they decided to expand
and do this do this whole area.
So there wouldn't be, I don't think any peanuts or Snoopy
and theme parks anywhere if not for this this tie to ice skating.
Wow, that's interesting.
Do you think that ties directly to the Snoopy on ice show?
Yeah, completely.
I mean, that's right.
That's what I'm saying.
They they were they did a they not they did a Snoopy on ice show.
I misunderstood. Oh, I see what you're saying.
Yes. Before they built the area, that was the very first
right pillar of this relationship.
Of course. Yeah. Makes too much sense then.
Mm hmm. Mm hmm.
So yeah. So we can thank this this series of events for
us seeing Snoopy dance the Gangnam style in an ice show a couple of years ago.
That is that is right. Yes.
You and I's first theme park hang.
Yeah, that was that was kind of the highlight of it.
That was extremely exciting.
Front row at the ice show.
We were getting hit with ice shavings.
Oh, I forgot we were front row. That's right.
Excitedly ran down to the front row of Snoopy on ice.
Better seats than McCartney for a better show.
It didn't have any my Valentine in it.
No, my Valentine.
There was a weird Al song in it, I believe was Edith in it maybe.
Yeah, that sounds right.
I think it was Edith and it was like they were throwing stuff in and out of the refrigerator.
And then the big closer was getting of a Gangnam style
done on ice skates, which that's not a dance.
That little Gangnam style step in place
doesn't really lend itself to ice skates in particular.
So no, it was very impressive physical feats on the part of the skaters.
Yeah, very impressive.
Great show. So, yeah, ice skating and obviously like kids ice skate
in the Peanuts Christmas special.
Yeah, which I guess is a reflection of his Minnesota upbringing,
which is very which then also
his Minnesota childhood is why he ended up in the Mall of America.
Oh, OK. Yeah, yeah.
And why I think it was considered a blow to the Mall of America
to have to shift to the Nickelodeon IP, because I think people really liked
that it was a Minnesota native property.
Right. I'm looking at Snoopy's home ice website,
and there's a live webcam of the ice.
Now we are still recording this in social distancing era.
You can just watch the ice.
I'm assuming no one on it.
There is I don't see anyone in the shot.
It's but the the the rink is lit up
and it's just it's got a timestamp on the bottom, which is
the exact time we're doing this.
And I guess, yeah, I guess any time you want to go,
there's something next to it called the Charlie Brown Cam that is not open.
It doesn't work.
So I don't know what that is, but the ice cam is working.
And you can see into the building right now.
I'm very so.
So we'll be recording this and we'll talk about other things.
And then in 20 minutes, you'll go, oh, my God, I just checked the ice cam again.
There's been a murder.
There's blood on the ice.
I'm the only witness to it.
But you like looked away when it happened,
but you're seeing other figures sneak around.
Oh, right. It becomes like a like a clue scenario.
There's eight different people skating away from a body on the ice.
Was it murder? May happen.
It may be happening at the Charlie Brown Cam, the one that's not working.
Maybe they disabled it to get away with the murder.
Like, yeah, like an Ethan Hunt style IMF team has disabled the Charlie Brown Cam.
So we cannot look and cannot see what they're going to do on the ice cam.
Wait a minute. The Charlie Brown Cam was previously used in Epstein's cell.
Oh, no. Oh, no.
Two guards.
There's no record of the Charlie Brown Cam.
This conveniently broken, named after an adorable character camera.
And the two guys who were working there weren't even like guards.
They were just people they found off the street.
And they said, hey, can you come in here and watch this for a couple of minutes?
Sounds good. I like peanuts. Sure. So weird.
Oh, man. Well, yeah, keep it.
Keep an eye on any potential wrongdoings.
I will have it open in the corner here.
Yeah. It means after we're done recording, too.
I think you owe Snoopy's home ice being an unpaid security guard.
Now that you know about it. You know what? I'm going to throw it up.
I have I have a little TV here now that I've been using to monitor like as a monitor.
I'm going to throw it up on the monitor and I'll take a photo of it
to let you guys know that I'm just watching the ice cam for any wrongdoing.
Wrongdoing.
Do we need to take shifts?
No, no, no, I want to tell you. OK.
Yeah, I only trust myself to do this.
I think somebody needs to watch it because I don't want something to happen to this place.
I know you want to go to that warm puppy cafe when all this current crap is over.
Exactly. I'm looking at the menu right now.
Oh, if I mentioned this flyer, I can get a free coffee, tea or soft drink with any meal.
Wow. This place is great.
Jason, you want to list some of the items you can get there, some of the food?
Oh, you can get the Schroeder sourdough breakfast sandwich.
Well, how?
Uh, let's see the home ice favorite turkey and Swiss on sourdough
lettuce, tomato and quote the best crunchy dill pickle on the side.
You can get the good grief grilled cheese.
That's good. You can get it's a good burger, Charlie Brown.
Oh, that's great.
Remember, you know, sometimes we run into these things where they
were excited about some themed restaurant and then they didn't theme the menu.
I was I was really worried about being let down here.
Thanks to a warm puppy cafe.
You got it right. Yeah, it's peppermint, patty, hot chocolate.
That's good. Wonderful. Yeah.
Fucking if fucking Caldwell went there, he'd be like,
the Snoopy sub is not a substantive meal.
It has almost no nutritional value.
Yeah. And then like, you know, Bill Crystal would say,
why, why doesn't Snoopy's brothers and sisters have any representation on the menu?
Where is the Olaf Chowder?
Well, I mean, maybe that's a good.
Oh, sorry. OK, I was going to say, I found another fact about Caldwell.
His 2009 book Reflections on the Revolution of in Europe,
which deals with increased Muslim immigration to Europe,
received mixed reactions.
Cool, man.
Hmm. Cool, man.
Sounds good.
You probably get mixed reactions from ladies when he gets in a bed with them.
Yeah. Take it to him.
That's right. Take it to.
Do you think you ever like in a book about something like that?
Do you ever just like he does a chapter on Snoopy just because it's still bothering him?
He just tries to like shoehorn Snoopy into any argument he's making.
The postscript is about the menace of Woodstock.
Woodstock is a hat on a hat.
Had a hat to almost too many, even more antics than Snoopy.
Disgusting.
Well, then, yes, truly, what would he think of Snoopy's relatives?
I mean, he must despise these characters.
And this is I mean, this was maybe a good transition point,
because when Mike, when you wanted to talk about peanuts for an episode,
I know you have a longstanding affinity for the aforementioned Olaf and
and Spike, but I'll let you take it from here.
Yes. So I realize, OK, I don't I don't want to make this even more negative.
In that article, it claims that Schultz believes creating these characters was a mistake.
What? What claims? Come on.
OK, so it says in 1980s.
OK, so basically, yes, Snoopy, after a while, they introduced his brothers and sisters.
And I guess let's I like the brothers and sisters.
I think most of us like the brothers and sisters.
I will say as a kid, I was a little creeped out by Spike.
Spike is like his like his brother who lives.
He has like a long like mustache and he was kind of like a drifter.
Yeah, Spike lives outside of the desert town of Needles, California,
and he's definitely a little squirrely looking for sure.
He has almost his mustache is sort of cactus spike esque.
It's a very prickly looking mustache and a real dirty hat.
It was a very dirty like, yeah, hat that like seemed like somebody stepped on
and he put it back on his head.
So as a kid, I don't know that I trusted Spike,
but I like Spike now.
And we'll talk a little bit when Jason and I went last,
because there was a peanut celebration and that's and we went to an event in January
and we tried very hard to get a photo with Spike.
And it was so hard and we didn't do it.
He kept like he kept going on breaks.
There were the line was too long.
Like we tried three times, Jason, am I right?
I yeah, we tried so many times and kept seeing the same employees,
probably to tell us that like Spike has to go has to take a break now.
It's it's possible they saw us coming and kept making up excuses
why Spike wouldn't take a photo with us.
Yeah. So wait.
And so Spike is is new at the Nats this year.
I I'm not sure if he's new this year, but they were really like,
I'm seeing an article indicating that.
OK, I think it is.
I think that it was his debut at this peanuts celebration.
So that might have been some of the mania you were witnessing.
Sure. Right. Well, he also had a silent disco.
We did not get to see the silent disco either.
What would it was silent disco?
You don't know about these things.
This is a thing where a DJ plays music, but everyone's got wireless headphones on.
So it just looks like a bunch of people.
Yes. It's so it's one theme to Spike.
Well, why does he have a why would he be a silent disco guy?
I mean, he likes he likes a party.
I think he's maybe like a Coachella guy because he lives out in the desert.
He lives in Needles, California.
Which side note from my looking into Schultz trivia,
Schultz grew up in Minnesota, but his family spent one year in Needles, California.
Right. So when he created Spike in 1975, that's when Spike came along.
Yes, he was inspired by his firsthand knowledge of Needles, California.
Bizarre. Wait, now I'm looking at footage of this silent disco, which is packed.
Everybody's in glowing headphones.
This is like one of those pieces of footage that's so distressing to watch
deep into the covid crisis.
It's bizarre. It's bizarre to me to look at this footage.
So many teenagers all jammed together in this little space,
all with headphones that were handed to them by a theme park.
And it's weird to look at that and then look down and see the date.
Twenty twenty just doesn't seem right.
I think that is a thing during this.
Your brain starts to like forget that stuff was made before.
Because I was watching.
I was watching.
I decided to watch 10 minutes of Lily Hammer
because I never seen it before.
Cool. And he's trying and like, look, you know, it's
it's the ultimate comedic setup.
An American gangster in Norway.
But he's trying to bribe people.
And he was like putting like touching money and handing money.
And I like my brain kept being like, oh, you got to.
He's better wash his hands after that.
Yeah, no, it's before it's before.
Yeah, I'm projecting it onto every single thing that I watch.
Absolutely. Yeah.
I'm going to go ahead and say I never have to go back to handshakes
except for like close friend.
Like I never need to do handshakes again, because you either get really squeezed
by like some aggro guy or you get a very wet limp handshake
and there's no common ground.
And I'm good. I'm done. I'm done.
I think we leave that in the before times.
Can I say I think this is a bridge that I feel comfortable burning
because when you say limp, wet handshake,
let me just say on the record that the limpest, wettest handshake
I ever received in my entire life was from Jamie Kennedy.
In some bizarre setting, I met Jamie Kennedy one time
and there's no it was like 50 percent limper and wetter
than any other hand I ever shook.
And if handshakes are a thing of the past, the main thing I've seen
I will associate it with is Jamie Kennedy and how dripping wet he was.
Wow, that is now gross.
That is a revelation.
That's is this going to become click bait?
Am I going to see this? This is going to bite me.
And some again, I think I feel comfortable burning the bridge.
I mean, hey, I'm just stating facts.
I'm not casting aspersions on Malibu's Most Wanted.
I just I shook his hand and that's what I could tell you.
What if we like what if like they bring like the original Star
Tours back, but it's Jamie Kennedy's voice and we want to have him on the show?
I guess then I will be
that will be one of his conditions that that bastard Scott
with the overly dry hands will not be.
I will speak to you, Mike and Jason,
but not to that, you know, Caldwell
esch judgmental freak, Scott Gardner.
All right, that's fair. So, yes.
So in the in the in this situation, we have to interview Jamie Kennedy.
Then you will set this one out.
And Jason and I will right now on the record say.
I think he probably has a great handshake.
Such a fan, such a fan.
I'm such a I think the I think his hand is probably the right moisture.
I think it's like perfect, kind of.
It's almost like you're feeling like you feel comforted when you're in his hand.
That's what I'm thinking.
I'm thinking that maybe my hands are just we're always too dry.
They were just brittle and chalky.
Yeah, no one will ever know again.
We'll never shake hands again.
So it's like getting it's like being in a hot tub and then getting in a regular pool.
And it's so cold, but it's not really that cold.
It just seemed extreme. Yeah, yeah, you're right.
Or it's possible that why haven't I put this together?
It's possible that I was getting the ultimate X.
Do you think right before I came in the room,
he dipped his hand in a bucket of water and I had been ext and I didn't realize it
until now. And maybe the show got canceled and then that never aired.
It would have been the last one.
His last prank they ever did.
The very wet handshake.
They ran out of money towards the end, and it was just him
dipping his hand in a bucket and shaking people's hands.
They remember is that he he laughed like he was a member of Gryph's gang.
During this wet handshake, he was like, ah,
ah,
this sounds like a memorable encounter.
This sounds like a scene from Son of the Mask.
Like this seems like he's like he's like being wacky, extra wacky or something.
Yeah, I mean, it'd be a funny scene, but not funnier than the scene
where the son of the mask performs a rip and rendition of
is just too good to be true.
Can't take my eyes off of you, but it's a rap version.
You're seeing this clip.
I know I have not seen what you're talking about.
Obviously, I like it already, but I've never seen it.
It's they're trying to do the like, you know,
the equivalent of the like Samba club scene or whatever the first one.
But they do it with a rap version of that song like you just do good to be true.
Can't take my eyes off of you. I love you, baby.
Oh, my God. It's something.
Bug main favorite.
Oh, I believe that sounds right.
Anyway, let's get off of this.
Back to us.
Back to someone else with what who looks like he has a wet handshake spike.
As a way to probably dogs get wet.
It happens. Yes, they get wet.
They they sweat different ways.
He lives in needle. It's the desert. It's hot.
Yeah. So he's the most popular, I think, of all those characters.
But the first I think that's right. Yeah.
But OK, so the rest of the characters, Snoopy has a sister named Bell,
and she probably has my favorite character description.
I'm assuming you're looking at it.
She is Snoopy's sister and has an unnamed teenage son.
I read that and I texted you.
This seems like something you came up with.
Snoot Snoopy's sister who has a teenage son,
an unnamed teenage son,
unnamed, and he's long. He's real long. He's tall.
He's long and tall.
Did she forget to name him?
It's unclear.
OK, Snoopy has a brother named Marbles.
He was a smart one.
Bell was from 1976. Marbles is from 1982.
He is the smart one, as Jason said.
And then we got to the I guess probably our second favorite, I'm guessing.
Olaf. Yes.
Hmm. He's a little stout guy.
It seems like it's a little chubs.
1989, he is the family misfit
and was originally referred to as ugly Olaf,
which I do not care for. I do not care.
I think it's too mean when they introduce him.
They introduce him as winning the ugly dog contest.
And Lucy is very excited, but Olaf clearly does not care for it.
Oh, yeah. Go.
People should go to peanuts dot fandom dot com and find this.
This is great. Lucy saying he won. Olaf won.
Your brother won the ugly dog contest.
And then it cuts to him and he says rats. Rats.
Olaf is cute, first of all.
He's not very cute. Yeah.
What is what's up with his his face, though?
It is like these like big they like liver lips, McGraw, like big droopy lips.
Is that what I'm looking at?
Yeah, there's one picture.
I think he's drawn differently depending on the one picture on the wiki.
He has got a weird mouth.
I will say I will agree with that.
I'm looking at a color photo, which I think is from the special Snoopy's
reunion that gets all these characters together.
And in this he's got like a bright red tongue sticking out.
So maybe that's he's just got a permatung a lot of time. Right.
But he said, again, he's a dog.
Certain dogs have a tongue that hangs. Mm hmm. Mm hmm.
Yeah. So that's do you do you
who what dog of Snoopy's family?
Who do you think is the closest to your dog, Edwin?
Well, Edwin is a very he's a small dog, but he is long.
I'm constantly commenting about how long he is.
So I guess maybe he's more most like Bell's unnamed teenage son.
Then in that respect,
as you said that he walked into the room, I swear you can't hear you.
But he walked into the room and is just sternly looking at me now.
Like just really focused on me in a strange way.
No, no, boy, I said when we've been recording remotely for so long. Yeah.
I will say Edwin does not miss the podcast.
Oh, I bet. I bet not.
Does the listeners know this?
How stressed out he gets when the equipment comes out?
Yeah, I don't know if we said that. Yeah, we figured out.
I mean, he he does not like people coming over.
It stresses him out.
And he has gotten to the point where if I just set up microphone stands
in the living room, he starts humping my leg like furiously.
And it's with things like that,
you would assume the dog would get more comfortable and used to it.
He's gotten worse.
He is not he has not gotten used to that.
So during quarantine, he's just living it up.
Do you feel comfortable naming the guest
who Edwin had the biggest amount of trouble with?
I think I know what you're going to say, but there's been a couple of people.
There have been a few, but I just I think the listeners
would might most want to know that he had a little bit of trouble
with a certain bad man.
Yeah, yes, it happened. Nick Mundy.
Mundy moves fast.
So what happens with Edwin is that you kind of have to come in slow.
You say hello to him.
He'll kind of walk over to you and sniff you.
And even then, sometimes he'll do what I call like a cheap shot.
He'll kind of try to nip at your heel a little bit or like grab
a little bit of pants because he's a coward.
But I think one of the first or second times that Mundy came in,
Mundy just barrels right into into the apartment
and Edwin went right at his pants, like just like
and like pulling on his pants a little more aggressively than normal.
And Mundy's funny. He's like, it's fine. It's fine.
Everything's fine. It's so don't worry about it.
Don't worry about it.
I go, well, just like slow down and maybe like greet the dog.
Yeah, it's fine. Don't worry about it. It's fine.
No, can't do it. Yeah. Yeah.
I'm on the move, Duder.
So so, yeah, when Mundy comes over,
he nipped a little at Rachel Bloom, I think.
I think so. Yes.
We made her talk about a water park for hours
and a dog nips at her and a week later, she's like doing bits at the Emmys.
What was the classier affair?
I, yeah, she, yeah, she and she did all the right.
She like was like gentle with him and then like, yeah,
he's very specific about like where you pet him.
Sometimes Jason has even done this and he likes Jason.
He wags when he sees Jason.
But Jason, you were petting him like on his sides.
Sometimes he gets weird about his sides.
Yeah, I'm to Mary.
He humped Mary Holland's leg to.
He it was accidental, though, because he doesn't do that with strangers.
But what happens is somebody buzzed the door right as she came in.
And she when he was like comfortable with her and he gets freaked out by that
buzzer and he just like on instinct,
just like started humping the nearest leg he could find.
I was like, oh, God, and I like pulling him off.
I say that one day Edwin
has the possibility of humping Michael Eisner.
I mean, well, no, we really hit the big time.
How many great things about Michael Eisner, I mean, to come over to my apartment.
Yeah, we never talked about that.
That's how it would be.
But I mean, it's you know, Obama went to the garage.
Yeah, the garage. Yeah.
So why not? Yeah.
And to be surprised by Edwin,
I'm in his leg and say, hello.
I mean, I we wouldn't even need to do the interview.
Just film that. Yeah.
Just him having to buzz in here, getting out of like a car.
He's like 82 years old.
Like like just him going, what am I doing here?
And then Edwin humping him.
We don't even need we can just tell the story on the podcast and we just as good.
Well, I think you just leave anyway.
So that's probably true.
That would be our only goodbye. Goodbye.
Bye bye. Goodbye.
OK, let's go. All right.
Oh, I was like, yeah, those are the siblings.
And then Andy is the last one who appeared in 94.
He is Shaggy.
He's a Shaggy dog and always appears with Olaf.
Yeah. And the family has been in his World War One Flying Ace fantasy.
Wait, there's two more.
Oh, am I missing two? Oh, I know.
Oh, yes, I see. I see. Yes. Yes. OK. Go for it. Go for it.
Yeah. So this is very, very specific.
There's two more siblings, Molly and Rover, and they are TV exclusive.
They first appeared in Snoopy's reunion and then kind of like
and later on mentioned in the comic strip Snoopy's dad says
he gets like a birthday card or a father's day card.
He says all eight of them signed it.
So eight would be Snoopy, Spike, Bell, Marbles, Olaf, Andy,
and then Molly and Rover. Molly and Rover as names.
It does feel like those are TV people phoning it in
kind of kind of simple names.
Let's fund an Olaf. Yeah.
You're saying it's a it's a it's a Helen test situation.
Yeah, kind of kind of.
I mean, Andy's kind of simple, too.
But I mean, Marbles is very fun.
Olaf is very fun. Bell is unique.
A lot of these strips with the I mean, these are definitely worth looking up
the way these characters get introduced, because there's some very funny moments
like when Snoopy writes a letter to Charlie Brown
about Bell and his nephew and says,
as I said, my sister's son is a disappointment.
This is OK.
Yeah, Marbles.
It's our when Marbles Marbles shows up
and goes to Peppermint's Peppermint Patty's house accidentally.
And there's a strip and she says, so you're Marbles.
I know your weird brother.
Thank you. I don't know why that's just so great.
That stuff, that stuff, that sort of flies in the face
of what the people are saying about the strip getting like less dark or like
that's all like kind of mean, weird humor.
Yeah, not like completely light and frivolous.
Yeah. Yeah.
But there was a lot of Fod, like mumbly darkness
in the one of the things that I watched, because I wanted to see something good
that spike factored heavily into.
And, you know, I think he's mainly from the strips.
But he has a very big role in the
the special Snoopy's getting married, Charlie Brown,
which just that in and of itself, that it's about
you don't even get to meet her, really.
You just suddenly in the special, you just heard the news that Snoopy's
getting married to a poodle named Genevieve Genevieve.
So you know about Genevieve already.
Well, I found an article called the 10 Peanuts characters.
You've probably forgotten. Oh, great.
Uh, on Mental Floss, that common Genevieve is number three.
Oh, oh, I'm so curious who tops Genevieve.
I don't I don't have much to say about this special, except that it's nice to see
where Spike lives, which is in a cactus with a door
next to a cactus that is a mailbox where he gets the invite
to Snoopy's wedding.
And then he has to he has no money.
He's like a bum kind of.
So he has to like do little odd jobs to have the bus fare.
He doesn't use a magical way to get to wherever the peanuts live.
He just needs bus fare.
So he has to be in a dog race, which is very humiliating for him.
And he's just sitting on a bus.
And and then and then at the end, especially get to hear like a really sincere
like wedding song sung by Sally,
who in this is one of the specials where Sally is voiced by Stacey Ferguson,
a.k.a. Fergie.
Did you know that? Oh, wow.
I know that. Yeah.
Fergie was was Sally in a couple of them.
So it's this it's this wonderful, sincere, like barely even referencing the dog thing.
It's just a nice love song sung to two dogs by the singer of Milk Money.
And then Genevieve is just ends up
cheating on him with a golden retriever, and that's it.
Wait, so I hear.
Well, I see Snoopy's fiance runs off with Snoopy's brother, Spike.
What? Not in the special.
Oh, oh, what?
That's what the the mental floss says.
That's what it says on mental floss.
And then so Snoopy's heartbroken and he receives a letter from Spike
after that saying that the ex fiance then ran off with a coyote.
Genevieve, she gets around.
I think that OK here, I think what the deal is that they cleaned it up for that special.
That's too that that's too grim.
Yeah. But this was the strip.
I think this happened in the strip.
Well, I mean, your brother stealing your fiance at the wedding.
That's that'd be a little dark.
Yes, this is crazy.
So that quote I was referencing earlier because they were talking about Schultz,
because Schultz said that he was going to be a little bit more of a
I was referencing earlier because they were talking about Schultz,
because Schultz said that he thinks he made a blunder in putting the siblings in.
But this is all very heady, dark stuff.
So I don't know what he's talking about.
He said he realized a couple of years ago when I began
to introduce Snoopy's brothers and sisters, it destroyed the relationship
that Snoopy has with the kids.
I know that it destroys the relationship.
This is just a different set of characters to have horrible things happen to them.
Well, and I also loved getting to watch the fun is less like dogs getting dressed up.
And more watching Charlie Brown like, good grief, my dog's getting married,
watching him have to like organize a bachelor party,
which happens.
I mean, that's great.
That's great. Charlie Brown business.
And it's like that's like Merv Griffin Seinfeld.
Like, yes, is it maybe the core idea of the original strip?
No. But is it great? Yes.
Yeah. Things have to stretch.
This is decades into peanuts.
We got to have some fun.
So here, I'll just read a couple of the characters
that you probably forgot about.
Charlotte Braun.
Do you guys know Charlotte Braun?
No, no.
I don't know many peanuts characters with a last name.
You mean Ava Braun's last name?
Oh, wow.
Charlotte Braun was written as the female version of Charlie Brown.
In fact, she looked just like him, except she had curly hair.
She, too, was ostracized by her peers, but it was because she was loud
and obnoxious, a fact she constantly pointed out during her appearance
in the comic strip.
That's too fucked up for me.
And she was introduced in 1954.
Huh?
I love Bram Brown.
The Brown equivalent being Braun is great.
Yes. I mean, maybe they what?
Maybe they pronounced it Brown, but it's spelled Braun.
Full disclosure, that took me a second to get that wordplay.
I get it makes more sense to me now.
There a little bit more about her in this in this article.
Shortly after her introduction in 1954, Schultz received a letter
from Elizabeth Swain, a young fan in Pittsburgh, who told him to get rid
of Braun because Swain found the character annoying and unfunny.
Schultz wrote Swain a letter saying that he would soon discard Braun as requested.
He he added a touch of dark humor by saying that Swain would have the death
of an innocent child on your conscience.
He wrote that to her.
Are you prepared to accept such responsibility?
Wow, Schultz rules.
Wait, one more thing.
Next to his signature, he included a sketch of Charlotte Braun
with an ax stuck in her head.
Wow. Wow.
Amazing research, Mike.
She showed up in the bronze showed up in the comic one more time,
but then never returned.
I have to go now. My planet needs me.
Yeah.
Whoa, that's amazing.
That's early, like letting fans drive it.
That's some pre-release the Snyder cut.
Yes, it is.
That was the original Snyder cut.
Oh, my God.
There's a character called Tapioca Pudding.
Is that a person that I like?
Let me see. I'm looking I should the images did not load on the website,
so I need to find separate images.
Here she is.
She just kind of looks like Sally.
So Tapioca Pudding was introduced in 1986.
She said that with her blonde hair, smile and catchy name,
her father believes they can make a million dollars by licensing her image
for products like T-shirts, lunchboxes and greeting cards.
She was created in the 80s purely to be licensed for use on products.
She was taking it was like taking a jab at like cash grab characters.
Wow. Her name, as well as other hints throughout the story,
suggests that the real target of Schultz's satire was probably
Strawberry Shortcake, a character originally featured on a line of greeting cards.
Oh, satire with your merch. Amazing.
Yes. So he was, yeah, doing some some satire of cash grab characters.
This is made me so maybe like Charles Schultz way more.
This is all awesome. Mm hmm.
Let's see here.
Some of these aren't as good as the other ones.
The goose eggs. Have you ever heard of the goose eggs?
No. After Charlie Brown took a bite of his old nemesis,
the kite eating tree, he received a stern letter from the Environmental Protection Agency
convinced he's headed to jail. Charlie Brown went on the lam.
He met a group of little leaguers, Austin, Ruby, Leland and Milo,
who asked him to coach their team, the goose eggs.
The kids are young and small.
The catcher's mask completely covers Leland's head.
Milo can't even lift the bat to swing it.
And Austin asks how he's supposed to get down from the pitcher's mound.
So they're underdogs for sure.
Of course, their first game is against Charlie Brown's friends
who refuse to play because they're afraid they'll step on the little kids.
It's here that Charlie Brown learns he can go back home
as the evidence against him was destroyed when the kite
eating tree blew over in a storm.
Charlie Brown is on the lam and meets a bunch of tiny kids.
What?
See, OK, so this is one of my.
This is one of my big things is I think as much as I like
the peanut stuff in the parks, I need a little more of this madness.
Like I went a little
a little more weirdness, a little more on we, you know.
It's all pretty sanitized in the parks.
That's very true.
So if that's our general, that's what this is.
All this is saying is this is a our plus up would be
let's get weird peanuts into the parks.
Yes, there's a there's at least this one more.
I have to because it's dark.
It's very dark character.
Emily in 1995.
Does anyone know Emily from Peanuts? No.
Charlie Brown met a girl named Emily who asked him to be her partner
in a dance class after they shared an enchanted afternoon.
Charlie Brown was smitten.
But at the next class, Emily was absent when Charlie Brown
asked the instructor where Emily is.
He's told there's no one there by that name.
It turns out Charlie Brown was dancing alone
and talking to himself the whole time.
Emily was merely a figment of his lonely imagination.
Dear God.
She is.
Yes, Charlie Brown is so sad, he creates a character in his mind
that he believes is real.
Wow. Wow.
I think that plot is in a TGIF show.
I want to say I wanted to say it was Urkel,
but it actually might be step by step.
The invention of a ghost at a dance.
So you're not alone.
Yes. I wonder if Schultz.
I mean, this was from 95.
I wonder if he stole it from TGIF.
It itself was a satire to show that he didn't like step by step.
Let's see. OK, there's Peggy Jean.
Charlie Brown and his girlfriend, Peggy Jean, met on the boat docks
at summer camp in 1990.
Peggy Jean gave Charlie Brown his first kiss, said she loved him
and wrote letters to him after camp was over.
Sadly, he never received those letters.
That's because upon meeting her, he was so nervous
that he introduced himself as Brownie Charles.
A mistake he was too embarrassed to correct.
So when the mailman tried to deliver Peggy Jean's letters,
Sally turned them away, saying no one by that name lived at the address,
which come on, Sally.
That's pretty close to your brother's name.
Sally, God damn it.
Brownie Charles.
Which, by the way, Brownie Charles is a great name.
Yeah, I'm going to use that as a pseudonym from now.
I'm going to use that as like an alias.
When you need to check into a hotel.
Yeah, when I check in.
When we're on the road doing shows.
Yeah, Brownie Charles.
I'll pay in cash.
Jason's too famous here in Pigeon Forge.
Better go by Brownie Charles.
Hopefully, the hopefully the listeners don't hear this.
No.
Ask for Brownie Charles.
I don't know the code.
Oh, I have to use Charlotte Braun.
So, yeah, that's basically that's the that's the next that's that's
wow, there's a couple more, but they're not as good as those.
Yeah, I this is this is all great.
It's it's nice to hear about this this expanded universe.
And I would like to see more of this in the parks.
You know, if I could bring it back to theme park world into Camp Snoopy,
I think maybe the segue back in is that there are, you know,
there's a couple of ways that the characters live, especially in
the theme park world.
There's you know, there's the camp Snoopy rides and then there's these
there's little shows in a very small little outdoor amphitheater,
which I find very charming,
because like I'm the most familiar with the Halloween one.
I think I saw it in person one time.
And it's it's usually it's the peanuts characters and then one actress
who is not dressed as a peanut,
who kind of leads them in some very mild choreography.
And it's really nice seeing Charlie Brown with a Frankenstein head.
You know, like just the adjust the green and the flat top shoved
on top of his head and doing like really slow dancing to Ghostbusters.
I believe we saw that the same day we saw the ice skating show.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, yeah.
Because there was a thriller parody.
Yes. Yeah. Yeah.
Call it which they night.
Oh, they changed it. Yeah.
They took out for a year and then put back.
That's how it. Yeah.
Because it's like, yeah, I believe it was like, because it's a spooky,
spooky night.
That's right. They did a parody to make it.
They like scarified it.
But then just to a diff, it's already scary. Right.
I don't know. I don't understand either.
Why changing Monster Mash to Zombie Mash?
Right. The lateral move.
Yes. I don't know if they like save some money that way.
I don't know what the rationale behind it was.
They have that. Yeah, there's this little stage at knots.
And they do that show and they do that.
I think Jason mentioned earlier, Space Beagle.
They do the show.
Jason and I saw a little bit of Space Beagle when we were there in January.
They have Space Beagle was fun.
Yeah, I like that.
It's a similar setup, though.
There's like one human three care, like Charlie Brown characters
that come in and out and they dance to songs.
And then what we saw, they had some fun, like Woodstock antics, too.
They would like pop up different Woodstocks around the theater.
I don't know if that's new. I don't know if that's a plus up, but
they would do like some fun stuff with Woodstock,
which I don't believe they did in when we saw the Snoopy Halloween show.
Yeah, because Snoopy had gone to the moon and the aliens were lots of little
Woodstocks. And that was great.
There there's a dude.
Yeah, there's a Snoopy in space, like series of shorts on Apple TV
that I watched one of.
And I thought like, oh, was that show connecting to this thing?
And then I'm like, oh, wait, no, half of this, like over half of the Snoopy
lands in the parks are called Planet Snoopy.
So yeah, duh, make up Snoopy in space thing.
But he went to space a good amount in the comic strip. So.
Well, he has like a connection to NASA, too.
Yes. Yes, he gets letters from NASA in the TV show.
Like Apollo 10, he was affiliated with the Apollo 10 mission.
Do you do you know what I'm talking about?
What do you mean by affiliated?
All right, there's here. I had to find the article here.
I completely forgot about this because they were like celebrating this
last year at Comic Con.
NASA and peanuts celebrate Apollo 10's 50th anniversary.
There was, let's see, the agency like he was like kind of the mascot
for the mission, I believe.
And hold on, I'm now I'm reading this is before the blimp,
because he's also met blimp guy.
Yeah, life. Yes.
Yeah. Vamp for a second while I just read real quick.
Well, let me what I was going to bring it around to.
And you you mentioned the Woodstock thing.
There's a lot of little Woodstock puppets that pop up in a show
that I think maybe debuted this year.
It's on a bigger stage further into the park
called Woodstock's Music Festival.
And I can't not read the these aren't original characters.
But of course, Snoopy had a lot of different guises, you know, Joe Cool,
among them.
And they introduce a lot of guises within this music,
this rock themed show why he shows up as Jimmy Houndrix
as as Fido Mercury.
Yes. To perform bone bone he me and Rhapsody.
He there is a rap section where he appears as Sir Barks a lot.
And the parody that they do there is just Snoopy got back.
They just keep it back.
And he kind of like shows you his tail.
So that's nice.
A little, a little body.
It's a tad body for me, but it's all it'll do.
And then Woodstock appears as Bird Cobain.
This is the Woodstock Music Festival.
Yeah. Yeah, that's what they call it.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
I do we think do we think Bird Cobain committed suicide or was he murdered?
I don't really want to explore any of these options.
All of these, these are all tragically killed.
Yes. But the pun base bases of these names.
And the one you haven't said had a bad end.
The one you haven't said yet had a bad end, too.
Oh, you're you're you're aware, Mike, of where I'm going with this.
Oh, yeah, yeah, I know. I saw him.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Because this show culminates in, you know, Snoopy keeps kind of disappearing
and then reappearing in different guises.
And at the end of the show, they want to wrap it up with him.
But where is he?
And then suddenly a blast of purple light and the familiar beginning
said sounds of let's go crazy.
And he comes out as paw prince.
I mean, Christopher Caldwell would be so upset if he saw paw prints.
He would be just his the steam would be blowing out of his ears.
If I could clockwork orange Christopher Caldwell
and just show him the full video of Woodstock's music festival.
Yeah, he would really every every Snoopy.
I should actually just Snoopy doing dancing to Gangnam Style
in a 24 hour loop. Yes.
I think I have a knockout blow for Christopher Caldwell.
Good. Great. Good.
Good. In 2020, he published a book called The Age of Entitlement
America Since the 60s, which seems to be mostly him
complaining about the passage of the Civil Rights Act.
Oh, my God. What?
Yes. And a review of the book quote from Jonathan Roche.
If you think Caldwell sounds like Bannon, the self appointed tribute
self appointed tribune of Trumpian working class populism, you're right.
So this guy sucks shit.
This guy's really bad.
We got to make sure we got to make sure it's the same guy.
That's how we have for one guy.
Is there anything because he doesn't like Snoopy
and then we say like shit on his grave.
He's saying it's like some conservative ghoul, and we're just running him down.
Contributor to the Atlantic Monthly.
Well, I mean, all right, if it is the same person
and that just goes to show that this is the kind of monster
who wouldn't like Snoopy.
A goblin, a living goblin.
Spooky, spooky guy guy.
I found the answer to the Apollo 10 Apollo 10 missions.
Call signs were the names of peanuts characters, Charlie Brown and Snoopy,
who became Apollo 10 semi official mascots.
And peanuts creator Charles Schultz also drew mission related artwork for NASA.
Oh, so that's great.
The space connection.
And that's why they did those space cartoons and stuff.
Real quick about Woodstock's music festival.
I think, Scott, you started to say there's a bunch of little Woodstock puppets in it
and they pop up and they have little instruments like a little trumpet
or a little harmonica.
And that's just so great.
I mean, it's so so good.
These little shows, if just if if anyone listen,
if anyone ends up at not very funny, if you go if you go to nots a lot,
you probably know about these little shows.
But if you're just in town and trying to hit parks quick,
do you carve out the time to watch one of these these charming little shows?
I find them so delightful.
There's a lot.
Scott, did you find the show Beach Blanket Beagle?
I didn't. I have.
There are some beach songs in the show Blockbuster Beagle.
But but these these are different things.
You go ahead.
Well, I don't have too much.
I just that there's a few Beach Boys songs in there.
So I would I would think that Beach Blanket Beagle would be a big
you'd be a big fan of it.
That does sound nice.
I was excited because Blockbuster Beagle has a big it's about Snoopy
wanting to make it in Hollywood called Well Be Damned.
And he there's a big sequence around Muscle Beach,
where you get a mashup of David Lee Roth's California Girls
and Katy Perry's California Girls.
Oh, I like that.
So that's that is that is a ball.
That's a blast.
There are there are like so many shows, especially during Peanut Celebration.
They have like a little they didn't.
Spike has obviously is disco.
They have that little space show they had.
I think there was a was there Snoopy on Ice still happening?
I mean, usually every time we even there, we saw a Christmas show this year.
We went to that Christmas event. Right.
So like there's like four different shows
potentially running at the same time at Nats.
Maybe between two and four, I would say.
Maybe more is during celebration.
Mike, you and I went down for it this year and kind of blitzed through it.
Like we didn't see everything.
The other thing that happened, we tried to get on the train
because they have little peanuts cutouts
on during like scenes in the train.
Like there's a scene of the Daisy Hill family, which is Snoopy and all his siblings.
That's their family band.
But we we try to get on the train.
The train was down, too.
So we couldn't get on the train.
We miss Spike. But but but but
we did we did get the get the thing we came for.
The number one thing which we haven't talked about yet,
which I've been excited about is that we made a beeline for it.
We walked around Snoopy taking pictures to get to this.
We shoved Snoopy over to get to this specific photo op.
And that was to get Jason with Pigpen in the livery stable.
Oh, boy. It was great.
Mission number one. It was mission.
Mission number one. I wanted a photo, too.
I have a photo with Pigpen in the livery stable.
Of course, I'm not a crazy person.
I'm going to get that photo as well.
So that yes, they were really they had a lot of things to offer.
And that was number one on our list.
And we did it right away.
He gave us hugs. He was so happy to see us.
Like he was feeling was mutual. Yeah.
He was we yes, we hugged him.
He was dirty. He was covered in soot, but it didn't like stick to us.
Because they now operate that area as Pigpen's Pigpen.
Yes. Right.
So there are pigs in there are actual pigs in Pigpen's Pigpen.
Wait, oh, yes, that's right.
There were yes, that is right.
There were horses.
I think horses or dogs.
They wanted to make sure that the smell was authentic.
When you meet Pigpen.
They wanted that extra bit of imagineering there to know that if this was truly a dirty,
messy child, that he would he would have some sort of unpleasant smell.
So I don't want to put you on the spot, Jason, but if there's any,
it does seem like there's a particular affinity you have for Pigpen.
Is there any way you could explain that to put your thumb on it?
You know what I like about Pigpen?
Pigpen always has a smile on his face and he's always fucking filthy.
And I just think that is such a great
one to punch. I just think that's so great.
There is a newer ride they a few years ago for the 30th anniversary
when they were redoing, I think it was 2014.
They would read it one of the Calico rides and they read it a lot of the
a little bit of the the camp Snoopy for the 20th anniversary to take out rides
that had height limits that like adults couldn't go on to put in rides
that families like there were no height limits, everyone could go on.
And one of them is called Pigpen's Mud Buggy's.
And I mean, that's just that's so great.
Well, it's Pigpen's not afraid to be himself, I think is what shines through there.
He might be the most well adjusted of all the characters in a lot of ways.
He's well adjusted. He's always got that big cloud around him.
He's very powerful.
Like who can harness a cloud of filth like that? But Pigpen.
The cloud of filth is almost like a sentient creature
that can also help Pigpen out.
Like there's a character in X-Men comics called Phantom X,
who has a nervous system that can like leave his body and turn into a ship.
Yeah, it's kind of the same thing with Pigpen in that cloud of dust.
It's funny, Michael, as soon as we start, you said the cloud of dust is
sentient, I started doing the mental math of can I describe
Phantom X in a very concise way? But you did a great job.
Thank you. Yes. We both love Phantom X.
He was created by Grant Morrison.
He's like French, but not really French.
He's a gentleman.
French is a gentleman thief,
and he has a nervous system that shoots out,
it kind of shoots out of his body and turns into a ship.
What do we say? Let's go around.
Let's go around the room here.
What is everyone who would you say your favorite Peanuts character?
Would it be Pigpen, Jason?
I guess either Pigpen or just Snoopy.
I mean, sure, it's hard to top hard to top the king.
I mean, I love Charlie Brown, too.
Well, we're not saying we don't have to put any of the other characters down,
but if you had maybe like when you were a kid, who appealed to you the most?
I think Snoopy, I had a lot of Snoopy toys.
I had a lot of Peanuts collections.
They were because you could just find them at like libraries
trying to get rid of books or yard sales.
There was always peanut stuff for like a quarter.
And I just had a ton of them.
I think I was I think I like Linus the best as a kid.
I think I like Linus because he wasn't as sad.
And I think I liked I liked the blanket for whatever reason.
I like the blanket, too.
Yeah, I had a blanket as a kid that I was very attached to.
I think everyone stressed me out a little bit, except for Linus.
Fair. Yeah. Yeah.
I think I think maybe now my answer is original Charlie Brown.
I think it is early 50s.
He is so cute.
I feel like if I the part of me that is not confident
about things that I enter into, it's like deep down, you take away all the layers.
And there's a little more baby Charlie Brown in there.
This little pensive stressed out guy.
I texted you the pictures of those Japanese toys.
Take a look at the because they are truly the old design.
You toys. Oh, gee.
Oh, so they are.
I like this Linus a lot.
Oh, yeah, I like the Schroeder.
I was so excited to see those because those are the real deal old designs.
Yeah, yeah. Original Charlie, I think, is my is my pick.
So, yeah, that's I mean, now do I like tapioca pudding?
Yes. Do I like the goose eggs?
Yes. I like all those characters.
And I like I like Snoopy's backstabbing fiance, Genevieve.
Yeah. So, I mean, are we thinking that they need to put in something?
Maybe they need to get Genevieve into a show like you're a show
that is Snoopy's wedding and you kind of watched all that.
You watch her, you know, walk out on him and then show back up with a new guy.
And then Snoopy gets mad and the peanuts hold him back.
She shows up a spike.
Yeah, let's just make it spike.
Yeah, let's go further than the special.
Yeah, I'd love that.
She's kind of like, you know, she shows a playfully
twirling his mustache around the biggest insult Snoopy could have at his own wedding.
I mean, if you went to a show at Knott's Berry Farm called Snoopy's Wedding
and then it had genuine drama in it, it was a little more of a
an immersive theater piece where your guests maybe are even handed a backstory
and you know, you could help Snoopy calm him down,
get him a drink, give him a number of, you know, a more suitable mate.
Yeah, I think I think that they should lean a little bit.
This all the Snoopy and peanut stuff is just so strictly for kids.
I mean, except maybe for Woodstock, which gets a little more of like an adult
reference, and I think here and there in the show, obviously, you said Snoopy's got back.
That's a little bit a little more adult.
So I think we need to get a little bit very.
Yeah, it upsets me.
Lean into that a little bit more for what you're saying
and give us some of these these stories that people might not be as familiar with.
Well, you know, the perfect place to do it is at the
scary farm, like at the Halloween events.
You know, these don't have to be literal horror shows, but just, you know,
if it's all adults, let's just, you know, let's let's have there be real drama.
I got it. So when Jason and I were at Nats, they also have, you know,
like like how they have in the animation part of California Adventure.
There's a spot where they teach you how to draw peanuts characters.
And I believe we drew Sally. Is that right, Jason?
We did draw Sally. Yes, we both.
And both of our they both turned out very different.
Yeah, I'm sure I have a picture of it somewhere.
I probably have the actual drawing somewhere, but
they should take that building at night and they should use a Peppers ghost effect
and have Charlie Brown dance with Emily, his imaginary girlfriend.
Oh, yeah. So you get like a little spooky like dance show with a ghost,
essentially the ghost of Emily, the projection in Charlie's mind,
his ideal woman, and you get to see his fantasy.
And then, of course, she's going to disappear.
And then we'll get to watch him sob for a couple of minutes.
And then he storms out at the end,
like that's his exit from the show and you think it's over.
But then she comes back right then.
And like, where did he go?
Like if he had just waited it out, she would have been back. Right.
And now she's now she's a practical character.
Now she's like just a suited up like in a suit.
Oh, she's human.
She's a human. Well, not well.
Oh, yeah, maybe it's just a human woman.
She's not a character.
Oh, that's interesting. Yeah, sure.
And then and then she goes looking for him.
But she uses the name.
What was it? Brownie Brownie Charles?
Yes. Yes. Brownie Charles.
He's like, I'm looking for Brownie Charles.
And then we all have to play along and say that. What?
Who are you talking about?
There's no such person in this theme park.
We all say that doesn't even sound familiar.
So it'll be one thing.
So whoever is like running the show before will be like, so we
you're going to be a very important part of the show.
There's going to be a line you have to say at a very important part of the show.
Now we're going to practice it along together.
Can you say nobody with that name is here at this theme park?
And then we all practice it together.
And then we say that to Emily and we prevent Charlie from having love in his life.
And it's the most haunting theme park show ever achieved.
Yeah. Scarier than any maze.
Yeah, because it's it's real fears.
It's the fear of being alone. And that's right.
Especially at like age nine.
Yeah. Being alone for your entire long life.
Well, that is you.
You survived. Fuck, yes.
The.
The darkest note on the dark.
I I yeah, I mean, check out Camp Snoopy if you're at knots or planet Snoopy,
if you're at one of the other parks, they had some real quick.
They had a couple little touches, dark, not dark touches,
but stuff I wanted to point out.
They do make a kite eating tree for peanut celebration.
That's very good.
And there is a standee child to teacher translator that you can speak into.
And it'll make the maw sound.
And then cool. Whoa. Yeah.
And then I those those super seven figures you can find on the Hot Topic website.
And if you type peanuts into Hot Topics website,
they have a lot of cool peanuts T-shirts and I might have to get some.
Oh, give yourself a little treat.
Of course, there's a lot of cool shirts.
It's like you don't know what topic is. I know.
The I will say like there there is still so much peanut stuff.
I mean, I don't let's not let's say like there's probably maybe in a year or two
when we go to not see all the peanut shows and do a second gate.
Because I'd love to dig into a few of these a little more eventually.
But there's too much.
There's just too much peanuts.
Meat on the bone is what I'm saying.
So we'll we'll we'll get I'm sure there's more characters, though,
also that we've never we don't remember.
Well, and this this episode is a lot of nonsense.
But to bring it back to the theme park.
And I do really like that stupid can be that came to be area.
I think I'm walking around there.
I always feel the 80s of it, that brown and pine green.
It's just so it's it's so charming.
It's like it gives me the same kind of
theme parky feels as parts of Frontierland or the
the Redwood Creek area of California Adventure.
I just think they did.
They did such a great job with it landscaping wise.
I really like it there. And the last time we were all there together,
I realized, oh, this is maybe sort of the in for me
to take my new son to theme parks, because I think early theme park
visits are tough because there are a lot of things they can't go on.
But Camp Snoopy is full of little rides.
As Jason, you just said now parents and kids can go on together.
So I'm really psyched to get to get to take my kid on some of these cute little rides.
And hopefully this is kind of the planting the seed
for bigger theme park fandom to come.
There is a ride and I'm blanking on the name of it.
It's a mini drop.
It's a mini giant drop.
Jason, you remember what I'm talking about?
It's like there's a postcard on it.
Is that right?
Is that called the kite because there is a kite eating tree ride
that might be called the kite eating.
I'll look it up right now.
But yes, it's basically like a kid's version of Tower of Terror.
OK, so you start getting him accustomed to it.
Start him early so he doesn't end up like me.
Do you that's look, we we all want for our children,
we want them to be better than us.
We want them to not have to do the same, have the same fears.
So let's see if I don't think there's any sort of launch
ride, child launch ride in the Snoopy area.
Yeah, because I don't want him to end up being a no launch
princess.
Yeah, step it younger.
Mini Queen.
Yes. I mean, I like Mini Queen more.
Yeah, Mini Queen is good.
The ride I'm referencing is called Woodstocks Air Mail.
Oh, yes. Yeah, yeah.
The little we haven't talked about the rides, they all seem very
there's something called Huffin Puff where you you have to push it yourself.
You're like going up and down a little lever and you have to move the mechanism.
And that seems like that seems good, like the mini version of Davy
Crockett's canoes.
And the one I really I remember going on this as a kid.
And I think it's in the other camp Snoopies.
It's not just at Knott's Berry Farm.
It's just the most basic name and most basic ride.
And it's called Camp Bus.
And you're just on a bus and the the Peanuts characters are in the window
and the bus is on an arm and it goes goes in a big circle up and down.
I really want to be on Camp Bus with my little boy.
You have to be 36 inches to be on this Woodstocks Air Mail.
Oh, no, that's right. Oh, there's still I haven't had to think about height
requirements until until this whole thing.
Yeah. Oh, boy, how big does he have to be for Camp Bus?
Oh, let me look. Let me look for campus.
This is why I'm saying we'll get back.
We'll get back to peanuts just because there's so much stuff.
I mean, we got a 36 inch tub boat.
Joe Cool's driving school.
Camp bus is 36 inches.
Well, it seems like if you're accompanied, you could be under.
Oh, yes, I see that. I see that.
Yeah. And he will be accompanied by a dad who's psyched to be on Camp Bus.
I mean, a little stressed out about the movement, but in general, psyched.
Yeah, mostly. I put my fears aside.
I got to be strong for him. Yeah.
And we didn't even talk about my mother playing Lucy
in a high school production of You're a Good Man, Charlie Brown.
I think my mom was in one as well.
I'm pretty sure. I think so.
You got to know what she was.
Did she play Lucy? You got to find that out.
I don't remember that. I'm not totally sure.
I don't think there's any might have been a girls school
where she was playing a male role. I think. Oh, interesting.
Yeah. Yeah. Not sure.
So she could find that out.
I've been Charlie Brown. We'll do that on peanuts, too.
Yeah. So for pants, too.
Hey, but for now, this is such a fun, fun world to cover.
I learned a lot. And Charles Schultz is the best.
And yeah, hey, more fun to come, as always.
If you follow us on Twitter, Instagram and Facebook.
And be sure to check out the second gate
for three bonus episodes every month at Patreon.com slash podcast ride.
Yes. And I would just like to say that all clear on the ice cam.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, OK, OK. No murders.
No, no bodies being dropped.
Not a single murder has happened.
Great. Great.
Not even like a pipe burst or a septic tank problem.
The ice didn't turn brown.
Not that I could see, though.
I will say I've been staring at it so long now that I start to think I see things
like maybe like you're seeing, I don't know, a ghost girl, a ghost girl.
I see the ghost of Charles Schultz dancing with the ghost of Emily.
That's bizarre.
Yeah, I don't know. It's weird.
That's what I'm seeing, though.
I think it's I'm hallucinating, though.
I understand what we're all going mad, but think about peanuts.
It makes us feel better.
Well, I guess I'll do it.
Sir, peanuts, he waited to wrap it up.
I can do the boy could do the voice.
Yeah, sure. Yes. Yes.
Say say goodbye. Let's have an adult say goodbye.
Did you run that back?
I dropped I dropped my phone.
It's a little too far for me, so I will just add it in and post.
You blockhead.
Hey, now I don't.
Now I don't have to do it.
Now I don't have to do it because that was good.
Yeah, that's the end.
All right. Hey, bye.
All you blockheads at home. Bye bye.
Blockheads. Bye.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson,
Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts
dot com and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify
or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter
and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.