Hi everyone.
This episode was recorded a while ago.
A simpler time with the only thing we had to worry about was a global pandemic.
We again want to voice our support for the protests against police brutality going on
across the country and now across the world.
The other day on Twitter, we linked to bail funds and mutual aid funds.
There's also links in this episode description to go fund me pages for the family of Breonna
Taylor and Darnella Frazier, who recorded the murder of George Floyd, as well as a group
called Bean that focuses on black mental health and the National Lawyers Guild.
Thank you for listening.
Stay safe and once again, black lives matter.
Ladies and gentlemen, good boys and girls.
The following podcast is presented with thousands of sparkling tangents and electro podcast
electromagnetic sounds.
It's the Main Street Electrical Parade on Podcast the Ride.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, where if we ever decide to end the podcast, we will do
decades worth of farewell events first.
I'm Scott Gardner joined by via electro syntho magnetic sound, Mike Carlson.
Hey, yes, I'm here.
We will pull a motley crew, a Rolling Stones, a kiss.
We will threaten to retire, but never do it.
Exactly.
We promise.
And Jason Sheridan is here as well.
Every time I stop talking, I will end my sentence with I am glowing away forever, and then
I will come back a couple minutes later, probably.
I think I think it would up the drama of the podcast from this point if we just if we say
podcast the ride is glowing away sometime in the next 15 years.
So this is your last.
This is what the episode you're listening to is one of your last chances to experience
the podcast, the ride magic.
I think that's I really think we should manipulate the audience more.
I think we should really play with their emotions.
So I think that's good.
I think we should actually just do it more aggressively, like threaten to quit, set like
because like Motley Crue just said they were going away forever and they came back and
it's annoying.
But it also makes a lot of money because people then feel bad and they feel like they have
to see us.
So from now on, every live show we do is our last show.
Sure.
Yeah.
Why not?
No, let's let's up the drama.
We can Elton John this is Elton John or like I feel like Elton John and Cher do this all
the time.
Like they're kind of in a perennial.
They're saying goodbye.
But maybe they are.
Elton is really now.
Elton claims he's really saying goodbye on this last tour.
I don't know about Cher.
I'm not sure about her.
The Who have retired a few times and they've come back.
There's two of them left.
So I think it's a common trick.
I mean, Jay-Z retired.
I think this is also sort of part of like legend and myth making.
Michael Jordan retired.
He's retired twice.
He came back.
It's part of like, you know, the legendary return is something like I never thought.
Oh my God.
I thought I would never be able to see Jay-Z again.
I thought he'd never make another album.
He retired at what, 33 or something.
Didn't he put out more albums post retirement, quote unquote?
I think that was like a midway point.
That was so long.
Was that like, it was like a decade over a decade when the Main Street Parade first?
Yeah, I think it was in 1996.
Now he's mostly Jay-Z retired.
Jay-Z said he was retiring in the first track of his first album.
He's a hedge fund guy now, mostly.
He's mostly just managing investments now.
Right.
You don't retire from that.
The smart move is to stick with it.
Sure.
Yeah.
So let's get retiring.
And you know, today's topic, the Main Street Electrical Parade, I remember a very dramatic
run, the first real farewell in 96, where they were selling the bulbs.
That was a very like, pieces of the Berlin Wall type, own history, make sure you own
a bulb.
What do we have that would be a legitimate piece of podcast the ride history, but is
also essentially an infinite supply?
The Mason jar water glasses at Mike's house.
Wait, hey, hey, hey, wait.
I'm just going to give away glasses at my house?
Yeah.
What?
Mike's dishware.
That's infinite supply.
There's a lot of them.
There's like, there's like eight.
There's like eight or twelve.
You got a couple pallets in there.
Infinite supply.
Let's try.
Well, how many glasses do you have?
How many glasses?
Yeah.
Yeah, I don't know.
I a few in the house.
I'm giving away Jason's ice cream glasses.
Yeah.
My ice cream bowl is Mike's glasses.
Scott's kind bars.
Infinite supplies.
Look, in quarantine times, those I'm not I'm not losing a seed of one.
Not a chocolate chip will be wasted.
I had as I was saying it, I think I figured out what it actually is.
Edwin's hair.
Oh, my God.
Edwin's shed.
It's everywhere.
Yeah.
OK, great.
So you got plenty.
But technically, it's not infinite.
There just is a ton of it.
So if we find like a nice little way to package that and then send little tufts of Edwin's
hair to our fans so that they can say goodbye to us, because, yeah, it's sometimes in the
next several decades.
But guess the ride is over.
It's blowing away forever.
I have to say selling the bulbs I thought was a very candy move and a ten dollars a
bulb.
That's a pretty affordable souvenir by Disney standards.
But it was the 90s.
It was the night.
I mean, I think today those are going for, you know, if they if they did it new now,
they'd be like 45 each.
Oh, and flipped.
Flipped immediately.
Yeah.
Were they actually the bulbs or were they other bulbs made to look like the bulbs?
Do we know?
I don't know that they could have been the bulbs because I think the bulbs were pretty
specific.
They were definitely weren't just bought at the store because we'll get into the history
of it.
But at the time, the more popular type of electric bulb of Christmas bulb was like they
were much bigger.
I saw it described as thumb sized.
It's like, you know, what's still at my parents house.
And then at some point, smaller lights came in vogue.
But at the time they were doing this, they were pretty specifically from Michigan Avenue
in Chicago.
So like a company gave them the bulbs.
So truly, that is a little bit historic if you're getting the bulbs from the 70s that
had to be hand dipped before the parade began.
That's not too bad.
But I wonder if at this point they just like went and bought a ton of bulbs at Dome Depot
or whatever.
Yeah. And you never you did not own a bulb.
I never bought a bulb.
I was definitely very aware of the the first glow away, the first farewell season.
Right. And I wondered if I should have.
But I never that would have been a apparent pester.
And I did not do that pester.
Have we looked on eBay to see what those bulbs might be going for?
No, that's a good move.
You want to check already on it?
The original 96 bulbs, which in theory could be from the 70s or it's all the biggest scam
they ever pulled. I don't know.
I have to say, I think that's like growing up with it like growing up on the East Coast,
I've been going to Disney World.
I remember this parade.
Spectro Magic definitely made a bigger, more upsetting impression in my mind.
But I think in my head when I was younger, it was like there's always a nighttime light
parade. And in fact, this parade inspired by the Electric Water Pageant, which looms
larger in my mind as like a a regular Disney world go where you always had to make a night
of like, oh, we have to make sure we're by the Magic Kingdom or go to the Polynesian
or something and see the Electric Water Pageant boat parade.
That is a question I had.
Is it are you guys as steeped in the Main Street Electrical Parade not having Disneyland
as your as your main park?
Well, in nostalgia wise, yeah, it was the doll face.
Spectro men were more of the thing I remembered because of Disney World, because I never
went to Disneyland. So it's more of this parade is more of like myth.
It's myth to me. I've seen it at this point now, the newer, the newest version of it.
But it was not something directly from my childhood.
This version we're like focusing on today.
I forgot that was the case for me.
My first trip was, I forget, 87 or 88.
I mean, it's like it might be one of the first things in my life I remember.
Like I remember my POV and I remember I really loved Pete's Dragon already.
So seeing the dragon in the parade, I mean, that might have been like the Disney
character I was the most excited to see just because that was the tape I had arbitrarily.
I'm not as fond of it anymore.
But truly, I like I remember hearing that first note.
I remember the vocoder and I remember the dragon going by.
It's like a really indelible memory from the first Disney trip,
which obviously left a gigantic crater of an impression.
And I can only imagine people, you know,
people's memories of it from the 70s and 80s.
I don't know.
I'm glad it made it to myth point for you, regardless of not having had that
that baby brain moment that I that I had.
Well, I mean, the music, I think I knew the music before anything else,
because the other thing is every parade samples that music, seemingly
every nighttime parade after it uses snippets of it.
The Pete's Dragon, especially that one is interesting just because it's probably
one of the more spectacular floats.
And it's funny because like that was supposed to be a temporary
like movie promotional 70s float that wasn't supposed to be permanent.
And it just stuck around.
Yeah, yeah, it's very odd, like a very sign of the times thing
that now is this kind of permanent place that Pete's Dragon has in the parks
that it probably would not have otherwise.
I don't know that there'd be any representation of Pete's Dragon.
No. Should there be?
I don't know.
Well, nowadays, kids are all about the live action
Robert Redford starring Pete's Dragon, right?
We're all watching and thinking about that live action version constantly.
Of course, I definitely remember that Robert Redford was in it.
I for sure was aware of that before you said it just now.
Did that come out 10 years ago or last year?
I don't know. I'm not sure.
It could be either.
The answer really in the nether realm.
The answer to the bulb question on eBay is that you can get a bulb
for like 30 bucks, 35 bucks.
OK, 30. Yeah, it's not an unreasonable markup, I wouldn't say.
And it comes in a little like box with that says Main Street
Electrical Parade also with a little like triangle shape.
So it doesn't seem like it's that hard to come by.
Some of them are a little more expensive,
but I'm not sure if it's like their special.
Maybe it was like Pete's like dragon, like the eyeball of the dragon or something.
That would be a extra expensive bulb, I assume.
This is from the A in to honor America.
One of the stripes.
It's the point of the A.
It's the peak.
One of the stars on the stars and stripes.
One of the states.
I mean, yeah, that's that's that's crucial.
Yeah, it represents Tennessee specifically.
Oh, it's worth a more important 100 grand.
Yeah, they should have like geo tracked them somehow.
But I found it so I find it so funny that they did this and they sold all the
but and then just like this thing was back so quickly.
I feel like it never really went away for that
much time, and it's sort of been in others, been versions in other parks.
If you guys had would it have been I actually I honestly don't
know this, I should have done this research.
Was it in Disney World before Spectrum Magic?
Oh, that's a good question.
I need to the timeline is so confusing to me and I looked at it.
Jason, you have an answer.
Yeah, I have. The answer is yes.
It ran in the Magic Kingdom from 77 to 91.
And then Spectrum Magic
debuted after that, and then it came back to the Magic Kingdom in 99 to 2001
and then came back to the Magic Kingdom from 2010 to 2016.
Wow.
Oh, yeah. It's I mean, it is like a world tour.
They start shipping it back and forth.
Yeah, it is so Paris, Tokyo.
I mean, they built other versions for it.
California Adventure, my favorite California Adventure.
I'll try to hold this up to the camera when they change the drum to say
a California classic like
come on, guys.
That's a that's a weak tie together for sure.
A bizarre way to explain why it's there.
Hey, and you know, it ended up in in Manhattan, too.
But I'll save that one.
I mean, that's one of the odder events that is.
The shit is wild.
Yeah, really.
It may have happened.
We twice.
Why? Well, we'll see.
Then we'll hear. We'll save it.
Yeah, let's let's try to go about this in an orderly fashion.
I mean, like, what do we do?
Should we sort of talk through the history of it?
I mean, Jason, you were talking about the electric water pageant
a little bit, which was its predecessor in in pretty much every way.
Yeah. I mean, this is one where one of my favorite
characters of the the Disney executive board of hunks, Cardwalker, shows up.
He you know, they were they were debuting the electric water.
They showed the electric water pageant
a on the seven seas lagoon in the Magic Kingdom.
And that was really that was another thing that like that wasn't supposed
to last a long time, but everyone liked it.
So they just kept it around.
And while they while they showed that there were like Disneyland reps there.
And I think the company edict was like, hey,
we we need to do some stuff for Disneyland, too.
We need to have some stuff there.
It can't just we can't just be throwing everything in Florida.
So some some.
Yeah, because it's early 70s.
Yeah. So like all the all company resources are going to Disney World.
And yeah, and I saw it explained to that they were doing a lot of concerts.
They were doing quick promotions like that.
But concerts are ultimately cost prohibitive
and only like some of the guests in the park in a given day can go see it.
So is there something that everybody can see leading to?
I forget the quote from who, but somebody somebody saying,
why can't we make Main Street our stage?
Why isn't it? Can there be a like a great nighttime moving concert essentially?
This is also like the technology was at the right time.
Nickel cadmium batteries play a big role.
Play a big role in this parade.
These like little portable batteries
that had enough juice to light all this stuff up for one go of the parade
and then get it backstage and recharge it for the second go of the parade.
That is so insane that they yeah, they could,
because if you've ever seen a parade at Disneyland or in a Magic Kingdom,
yeah, you know it like parade.
I forget the order, but it'll be like a parade leaves from the small world area,
travels south to Main Street.
Then there's another parade where it goes backwards.
And then there I guess that's the order, because then it gets stored up
up north up in the storage area in the northern part of the park.
So that that's a parade that is entirely about electricity
will not have any electricity if they don't charge every single battery
really, really fast.
That's like an yeah, it's like I'm trying to think the most power
sucking charging situation where it's like you're running all your apps
on the iPhone at once and like I just ruin the battery after an hour.
Like it's just it's crazy.
I really you would think that was like it would just be a panic
once all the parade floats got back there.
Yeah, yeah, truly.
And you know, I should say that's that's not how it runs today.
Right. It's just like in its janky 70s,
you know, formation, that's how it had to happen.
But I I also like seeing the breakdown of what they considered
because, you know, they they like this idea.
I think, you know, the the electric water pageant
was essentially a mainstream electrical parade, but on barges
like it's going along a lake.
So presumably there's just big power units like there would be on on any boat.
But in doing much smaller, more mobile
you know, little floats, how are we going to charge these things?
So there was talk of gas generators, but they make too much noise
and produce too many fumes,
a lot extension cords they went through.
But they would create trip and fall hazards very true.
Like where? Yeah, where are extension cords coming from?
The characters would have to run on a giant wheel to power it
like a hamster wheel.
Cinderella would be running with the mice.
Every character has one of those radios
that you charge with a hand crank to play.
Oh, down.
Everything is out of sync.
It just sounds like a horrible cacophony.
They're all just rubbing sticks together, kindling,
trying to create sparks.
Yeah, they're very, you know, this parade steps.
There could just be like a train's like a coal based engine on each
each float.
You have to show characters just shoveling hot coals into an engine.
You know, we're trying to bring coal back.
It's tight right now.
Twenty twenty is the best time to bring coal back.
And I think Disney is the place to do it.
Clean coal, clean coal, clean, clean.
We're going to take it.
We're going to clean it and then it's going to be clean.
And then it's clean coal, cleanest of all.
I mean, to be fair, all the presidents have said the phrase clean coal.
I don't know why.
What the hell?
Cinderella is going to take the coal.
She's going to clean the coal and it's going to be clean coal.
We understand.
Just as Disney pivoted during World War two to making
government propaganda and educational films,
Disney during Corona in order to get a financial like bailout
bridge loan has to start making clean coal, like like new ducktails.
David Tennant Scrooge McDuck has to talk about clean coal.
It's just a giant five minute ads in every episode.
But you know, Launchpad is a financial decision.
They have to take like a train ride and launch was like, gee,
did you know Scrooge, this was a clean coal.
It's really safe.
Return to like me could get to work in factories again.
I think I'm going to go get a job shoveling clean coal.
Star Wars, the Clone Wars, the final season, the search for clean coal.
The that's a lot of the delay in Avatar is they're having to shift
the philosophy like unobtainium is out and coal is in.
The Navi have agreed to this is this is the way of the future.
And we are going to start building.
Yeah, you know, fuck these trees.
Fuck the Hallelujah Mountains. Time to drill.
They no longer fly banshees. They roll coal.
They have the lifted pickup trucks run on coal.
Joe Rody is now doing the expansion of Avatar land
that's just based around coal and coal mountains,
large mountains full of coal.
And we first find coal in the myth of Santa Claus.
And everyone loves Santa Claus.
Santa Claus is a part of everyone's childhood.
And, you know, if we can if we can trust him, then we can trust coal.
Joe Rody has stopped wearing like his trademark, like hat
and vest and stuff, and just now has one of those T-shirts that says like,
don't mess with an Imagineer who was born in February and has a giant earring.
What?
There was like algorithm T-shirts that are really specific.
You ever seen those? Probably. OK.
Do you know he was born in February or is that?
No, that's just a guess.
You don't celebrate Joe Rody's birthday specifically. No, no.
Perhaps we all should. Yeah, we should.
I just watched a
one of these great channels that just uploads every
like piece of promotional material.
It might be cow missing on YouTube posted
footage of like the announcement of Animal Kingdom when they were still
calling it Wild Animal Kingdom.
And Rody does a presentation and he looks pretty much like he does today,
except in a very Eisner esque suit, like a double breasted with a big thick tie.
You know, he really dresses like Bruce Wayne.
He dresses like Val Kilmer, Bruce Wayne,
but still has the big curly mustache.
Do you think there was in like towards the end of Michael Eisner's reign, a CEO.
He wanted everyone to dress like him.
That's it very much felt to me like if it wasn't enforced on his part,
then he gave Rody unsolicited fashion advice.
Or like he'd call the Imagineers into the office and he'd be like, look, here's a deal.
I want to make some changes around here.
I've ordered a suit in exactly your size.
It's over sitting in my closet.
I'd like you to go over and I'd like you to wear this from now on when you're in public.
You did that to everything.
There's this thing, Magic Eye.
All the kids love it.
I want every tie to have a pattern like Magic Eye.
I want people to stare at your tie for hours on end
to enjoy the three dimensional spaces on your tie.
I've invested in all people into doing your bidding.
If you hypnotize them with the Magic Eye pattern on your tie,
I invested over three billion dollars into a Magic Eye company.
He spent more time focused on that Magic Eye company
than he did all of California Adventure.
He should have bought Magic Eye when he was CEO of Disney.
That's shocking.
Don't have been the Eiger move.
They're like the Eiger, you know,
all of the biggest properties of the time.
Should have bought that. Should have bought big dog shirts.
Stussy.
Big Johnson shirts.
Please welcome the newest member of the Disney family, pissing Calvin.
That's an empire.
Yeah, really.
They would be unstoppable now.
I like to praise him, but he missed out on the biggest purchasing opportunities of 96.
Although the Disney company did put through some, was it Hollywood Pictures?
I think they did put out the Jerky Boys movie.
Really? Wow.
I think so. I think technically, yes, I believe Jerky Boys is Disney.
Wow. And I was wanting to type Jersey Boys, but that's not right.
Well, because that's you like that.
That's the real music back when they made real music.
Back when we made that sound, our sound.
Ah, Jerky Boys, the movie
Touchstone, Touchstone Pictures in 95.
So in the same little run of time, Disney put out Jerky Boys, the movie and its Pat.
Oh, my God. Those are Disney plus now.
Yeah, I know. Really stuck it on board right now as we're recording.
Yeah. Where the hell is that?
Yeah, they got to loosen the standards.
Come on. They're sitting on so many.
Yes. I've never seen the Jerky Boys movie.
Neither have I. As of the time, I was too scandalized by them at the time.
So like the Jerky Boys could show up in a Star Wars movie.
Absolutely. The dream.
Or a Marvel movie.
As could the three ninjas.
Oh, yeah. As could Captain Ron.
Yeah. Yeah. As could Mikey from Life with Mikey.
Wow. They are making as could cabin boy.
They're making no use of the Touchstone 90s properties.
Captain Ron should come back.
And with Castle.
Yeah, that one's due for the kind of reboot
where everyone forgets that the first one wasn't good.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. No, we're so don't think about it.
Don't think about it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. It's epic.
Captain Ron is back.
Kurt Russell is returning to pass the torch to the new generation of captains.
OMG, epic.
Three ninjas to three ninjas should come back.
That's shocking.
Three ninjas has not been announced.
Yeah, we're going to get around all these.
Well, in the post Corona spending spree,
they're just they're just going to cycle through.
God, they own Kazam. Really?
Oh, my God.
Or it was like a copoly gram was also in.
Maybe they just distributed it.
Did they do they own surf ninjas?
Remember surf ninjas?
Probably not.
It feels very touchstone, however, for them to do three ninjas and surf.
I know they do not know surf ninjas.
Might be new line.
I think it was new line.
They do the gun in Betty Lou's handbag.
You know. Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
The gun. Yeah, yeah.
Penelope and Miller.
It took me a second.
Cathy Moriarty. It took me a second. Yeah.
You'll know it when there's a full Disney Plus series about it.
Anyway, I could look up touchstone pictures all day.
This is let's put this in the queue to do the full touchstone.
Yeah. So but yeah,
back to the parade everyone loves.
Yeah, I
though they even so here's another thing that they considered electrifying
the tracks along Main Street like cable car style.
That's interesting.
So like they would every flow would have gotten its power from the like what the,
you know, what runs along those?
I guess the the horse carriages or.
Yeah, the trolley tracks.
That would have been fine. Yeah, yeah. Electrified.
It's not like there is a baseball team
named after the act of dodging electric
sparking trolley cars.
It's not like. Right. That's right.
Yeah. Yeah. Why did we talk about this before?
Was it because of Dodger Dogs at CityWalk?
I don't remember what spurred this.
I think I took a double decker bus tour of like the boroughs of New York once
and the very New York tour guide was like, the Dodgers never should have left Brooklyn.
Even the name was about dodging the trolley cars when they came
careening around the corner.
Nostalgic for that.
They got to take the Main Street at Disneyland and put it on a slant.
Everybody's having to dodge all those cars.
More dodging at Disneyland.
More dodging.
That's what a real city's about.
They should run those Main Street bugs down at 60 miles an hour.
Kids got to jump at it away.
Make those horse trolleys spark like a real trolley.
And spook those horses before they go out.
Light off fireworks in front of their face.
Make them run down Main Street Hill as fast as they can.
Do a horse race. Do a horse race down Main Street.
Let the people bet on it.
Let people make money.
Oh, Disneyland's no fun. You can't play the ponies.
You should be able to play the ponies at Disneyland.
Most most American entertainment at the turn of the century
was about either startling or confusing horses.
The fact you can't do that on Main Street is a travesty.
You got all the fireworks right there.
Scare them. Scare them.
Scare them!
Scare them.
Scared a horse. The kids will love it.
Scared a horse.
We don't advocate for scaring a horse.
We don't advocate.
No, that's that's what the character.
That was that character. He was wrong.
That well-observed Brooklyn-y guy.
I imagine as we head into this we'll also have some well-observed
Chicago-y guys because a
Chicago company ended up getting hired to build these floats and install the lights and the nyCAD
batteries
Because the creators like liked the specific type of bulb like I said that lit up Michigan Avenue
at night
So they hired a Chicago company to do it great all it because it's like by this point
We're saying, you know, here's the timeline Disney World opens in 71. I think it's like
Summer of 72. I think it's sometime in 72 that
All right, we're we've announced this parade. Hey, not all the fun is in Florida. We got fun right here a new electrical parade
It's gonna dazzle you. Um, so they start building to this event
That's been set up and then they check in on the Chicago people and they haven't done shit
They just completely dropped the ball or so Disney says yeah, they I mean maybe they have a different story
They might I mean
If you were a Chicago factory worker and Disney caught you having built nothing with two months to go
What would you say?
I don't know. I think you could make up a couple different. What year was it was the 70s?
70s
What was happening in Chicago in the 70s? I don't know
Hmm. I'm just I'm doubting my own ability to do a Chicago accent is what I'm it's just the Bears just do the Bears
You know, I guess that is that that's all you got in the bears. That's all you gotta do. That's odd
Oh, yeah. Well, yeah. Well, and it's kind of that acroid. It's a little bit of that acroid thing. Um
I
It's all right, I'm too busy. I'm seeing I'm I can't wait look we got busy
We were seeing all these we were seeing all those shows at the second city. I
Would laugh it too much. I had to take a sick leave cuz my my ribs my ribs and my stomach hurt from laughing too much
This kid balloon she
Michael O'Donoghue Marone
Yeah
That's a good excuse
Yeah, that'll yes. Yeah. So yeah, every all these Chicago factory workers were too busy laughing so they didn't get
so Disney had to
Gather up all these floats just yank them away from the company drive them to
LA as fast as humanly possible and finish this parade in like half the time or less than they had
Established to do it assuming it was gonna be taken care of which did require that
So in the initial conception of the parade there were five hundred thousand
White miniature bulbs and they all had to be hand tinted
So they had to hire a bunch of ladies, of course
It had to be ladies who else but ladies could do this dead to dip the bulbs in in all of the colors
Wow, yeah, that's what it's well, it's like a weird. That's like ink and paint like the ink and paint gals
I don't know why Disney was convinced that men shouldn't be around paint. I guess
That's women's work is painting
Paint fumes are gonna get in anybody's brain men are far too ladies. You can't be trusted men around paint
They'll just start drinking it. They're far too dumb and crude
That was Walt's concern in the old days and he was right to think it
I'll say this for like in terms of the Chicago company trying to get this parade off the ground
It's not like they had a great inspiration to draw from because the electric water pageant floats
It's well documented that as you said, those are barges covered in chicken wire
Wrapped in lights so kind of rigged up and kind of has never really changed
I mean, I think they've upgraded it a little over the years
But the one night or one week engagement has now been going for decades and decades
But it's not like a technological Marvel. What's crazy essentially?
Oh, I was just gonna say what's crazy about it and it's all like the the rush to finish it
And I guess it's actually like the same when it comes to most projects and theme parks
it's like it feels like it's like I have a
Like some sort of project to in school and I'm rushing to finish it the night before and it's just like well
I don't know what we're gonna do. I don't know chicken wire and dip it in
like we're just gonna try to piece stuff together like with whatever we have and then
the difference of course being that like
the you know science project I made in high school fell apart like the day of
Me making it well, and then this thing but that's not far from how this played out. I wouldn't well, that's true
You know, you're right. They've have to reconstruct it. Yes. I
Mean yeah, it sort of was as janky as like a
volcano for a science seemingly
Less than a week before the debut a third of the floats were not ready
third of them and they and I I think it so then there was like a
Address rehearsal where I let's say let's attempt this
Let's try to get through one pass and they did not get through the one pass
I'm see you guys might have seen different versions of this story. I saw that a
Horse fell over a Brooklyn Brooklyn guys dream
Now that's funny that's funny that's like Belushi level funny
The Belushi falls down and the horse falls down
Float crashed into one of the buildings. Yeah went off the track on that
And this was I think the night before this is the night right before the very first performance
I feel like I'm forgetting another story. I had always heard that they got down Main Street and like died in the hub
Like the
Yeah, the lights turned off costume sparking is a big
Thing a big thing mentioned people just walking around with electric costumes sparking at each other
And I think I think Jason what you just said about that they made it down Main Street and then it went dark in the hub
I think that's that's not the rehearsal. I think that's in the that was the first night
That's like what that's as far as they could make it. I think yeah a guess and press there and that sort of thing
God which is a testament to how
Just instantly lovable and fun and kooky the thing was that it was like that's a if that happened now
Oh my god, all your all your news today's and your mice chats. Everybody's all up in arms
Service furious we'd be roasting the hell out of them
Yeah, but I like that it was that fun just for the like the one block that it made it that like who cares
We love it. Yeah, really?
Yeah, it's like I'm trying to think like what is I guess the closest thing in recent history is that float in?
Florida catching fire
The Maleficent Dragon float caught on fire a couple years ago at this point. Yeah, it's like the biggest like
Parade fail that I can think of in the last few years, but also that was awesome
Yeah, you're right. That was like that was great. What especially once you're like you're you're seeing it and you're like
Oh, I hope everyone was okay
Everyone was yes that rules
As long as you can call it then nobody was hurt yeah, that's the coolest thing ever
You know the last minute scrappy nature of this where floats are missing and we're like
you know, I think the other thing about the night that it debuted was that they were like the parade started the first float is
Leaving the station and the last several floats are not done and people are like screwing in bulbs
As it's going at like the parade is in progress and they're still finishing these things. I think actually
Oddly the most recent example of something being this janky unless they've just kept it secret from us is
The replacement for the mainstream electrical parade light magic
Which if we haven't said this officially on Twitter or anything
This is a little bit of a two-parter because light magic we're doing an episode about as well
If you don't know about light magic, I'm so excited to share we'll get into it later
but like oddly the whole story with that is
Let's do a super high-tech parade to replace this always janky parade and then that too the floats weren't working
There were major technical problems. It wasn't ready to go by the time they'd organized some big event
So like the same thing essentially happened in the 70s in the 90s. Yeah, I don't know
I think paint the night which is like really the like realizing that dream of the technologically superior
Parade, I don't know. I haven't read about any like big problems with that, but I'm sure there were I wonder if they just keep
Those problems hidden now not problems, but I thought there was supposed to be like that parade in
Japan I feel like there are more
Interactive elements or was there were at one point
Where like people had wands or ears that would light up and would bounce along to the music and I feel like they
Promised something like that for Anaheim and it didn't really happen
We did get remember a new a new
Mix of a classic Al City song. We definitely got that for sure. Well, of course we did. Yes
I am remembering now that I remember reading like mice chat articles about the issues with the paint the night parade
So there were some issues, but I don't know if they were as severe as like they were shooting sparks into the audience or anything
They just like they keep a lid on these things. I guess a little better. I don't know
But now but they've also leaned into
It's not like Disney hides all these stories of the problems at the Electrical Parade
I think they kind of love these stories now that something as as beloved to Disneyland fans as this parade had such a
like
Crappy messy start. Mm-hmm. Yeah, that's like it's kind of like adds to like the spunky nature
The can-do spirit of the Main Street Electrical Parade
That's really what it is. Yeah
even in all of its
Jankiness and crashing and lighting unfired for the parade
They did have to develop for the first time and now commonly used
System or just like the way parades happen now, which is an automated show control program
Where you know in a street light kind of way a parade a float rolls into an area
Sensors catch it and trigger a new music cue to start right which I don't I don't think had been done
Up until so that there could be like a seamless
Music flow from section to say now the Pinocchio part is starting now. The snow white part is starting
Yeah, that was an innovation for this parade that they still have. I'm sure it's more Wi-Fi than radio signals
Now but yeah, so there there was a lot of technology going around
Yeah. Yeah, pretty cool
Is now the points to talk about the song?
Yeah
Sure. I mean it is certainly potentially a final four
That we could do of best theme park music. Yes, and I don't want to spoil that but it's so it seems very possible
This could be if not number one then then in the final four. Yeah, it's got a hard hard competition with blood on the sand
Blood on the sand from country fairs
I mean it's children's children tap their toes to that rousing number
It's also it's blood on the saddle
But is it is it? Yeah
Okay, it's that the title of your asking Jason. I know I know
Right, he says blood in the sand and blood on the sand. Oh, yeah, maybe it might be a leader
It's I've looked it up and it's the blood on the saddle it's blood on the song
Is there ever blood on the song lyrics now? Sorry blood. Oh, no on the
saddle lyrics
There was blood that's just like a pre-recorded track by Tex Ritter
That's interesting and blood all around and a great big puddle of blood on the ground. Oh blood. Oh wait
I think there's sand I
Don't know what the blood on the sand is the sequel to the first 50 cent video game
There was 50 cent the 50 cent g unit video game blood in the sand was the sequel to that
You've confused again for a country bears song
Again I mixed up the g unit video games and country bears again
You have to stop so let's let's speak let's test you then who who did the song
Pimp 50 center the country bears Jason. I
Feel like that's the number Henry six, right?
Does sound like that I don't blame you at all but it is I will have to say it is 50 cent no
Dillon lose
It is we maybe will eventually do a final four with songs I
Think I think final four is for sure mainstream electrical parade Baroque. Oh down of course is the name of it
Really? Oh down. Yes, but I think also I think Sinbad is in that final four
That's that's pretty formidable
It's almost like do you have to separate instrumentals and
Lyric songs you have to make those different or they or those are the sides
Maybe this final four is like 32 competitors instead of 16. Oh, yeah, and it goes over three episodes
Yeah, yeah, I think we do it really soon because we're bored
Yeah, let's just let's expand why does it have to be 16
Yeah, the next final four will have 128 competitors
From the instrumental conference
phantasmic
The loop that plays inside the ice cream parlor on Main Street on the Gibson girl loop
the droid rooms from start to search
This is good we should do this
But yes the very possible winner
Baroque oh down which I'm so excited to talk about because it is the
Synthesis of two great loves of mine Disneyland and old synthesizer bullshit. Mm-hmm
There's a real chicken of the egg with me
Do I like this parade so much because it is so synthy or do I like synth bullshit because of this parade?
Is there any way to know I?
Don't know I think it's all like so as I said
I truly do remember hearing the first note and the vocoder is a three-year-old
So it feels like so tied into my psyche at this point
Right many I mean many classic movies
I like had some sort of presence at MGM studios
like that was my exposure and then I would go to video stores and
if I saw stuff I would rent it or if I like I would hunt it down because like
Oh, yes singing in the rain. That's in MGM studios a lot. I should watch that and it's if you
naturally prefer
Desserts and treats that are shaped like Mickey Mouse
That's probably because of theme parks that well, that's true. Yeah, probably
Could be from some others or maybe just like three circles together
But no, I have so many of those things where you really decades after the fact
Like oh wait do I at the end of the day like this because of
Because of Disney stuff when I was four years old. Mm-hmm. Yeah, the answer is probably usually yes
For with almost everything. Yeah. Yeah, I mean, it's certainly why I like
hotel lobbies and musaq and yeah, sure
Do you know wonderful texture? How hard do you go on?
Knowing about the synths in the songs in the song. Excuse me. Um, I
Don't I certainly don't know what was played when I look at like I've seen a list of what
Was used on it. I'm no look. I'm not actually a musician or a gear yet
But I know when I see words like prophet five, I know we're in I know we're in a good territory
I know what makes the sounds that I like and the list is pretty good
It's a pretty robust list of like 12 like great old analog since that were used on this thing
Do you I don't want to put you on the spot here
Do you have like a just a little bit of a vague like I know this is my favorite old synth
ooh, um, I don't I own a
This is a pretty different area, but but I bought off a craigslist a whirlitzer electric
Oh, which is this great like tan keyboard. That's what the Carpenter's played. It's on Queen
You're my best friend. It's on
It's the super tramp it's the logical song keyboard so that that's that's kind of different from
You know this like Moog area, but yeah, that's that's one. I'm especially fond of yeah, that's good
I don't go I don't know the tech spec. I don't know the stuff about since specifically
I'm a fan of the sounds I have like logic on the computer which has you know hundreds of synth
Pads you can use for your MIDI keyboard
Sure sure oh and we should say I mean the certainly the theme song of our show is very much inspired by
Yes, the major electrical breath. Yes, it is
It also it's I don't know it was kind of an accident that when I was when I was putting the thing together
I realized the song together. I realized that the opening and the drum is kind of like the opening to the
Disney sing-along tapes
Yes, yes totally the rhythm of
So it's a little bit of a combo of both of those things
Yeah, I
Remember well, that's a little like connecting the dots
I feel like you know we put out like five of these things and then maybe I realized oh, you know what?
That's kind of like yeah, that's a that's a cool little nod you did
I'm not sure if even maybe even new listeners don't realize you did the theme song
That's not so if we were at we should we is that something we should say in every episode like in that end screen
Should we credit you for the song and Aaron my wife for the art I
Mean, I don't know we don't have to say it. I don't know
I it's not like it's not like I'm seeing it attributed to like some sort of old composer on the internet or anything
It's not being wrongly it's not being attributed to these guys to Perry Kingsley
podcast theme unknown written by
Unknown
Public domain no way to know it's a it's a Shakespeare situation
Yeah, there was one person or 200 people and I don't know. Yeah. Do you ever you know what?
Oh, so good. I was gonna say do you have the artist name of Baroque?
Oh down because that was just a song that was not a Disney made song that was like
Yes a song they brought in seemingly or originally for inspiration
And we're like, well, let's just license this and now and at some point they did buy it Disney now owns Baroque
O'Down. Oh, is that right?
Yeah, I didn't realize that others but the person who discovered it
I know is Jack Wagner often called the voice of Disneyland or Disney World. Yeah
This is an insane if it's true
although I think I feel like I've seen different sources because I've seen that Baroque O'Down was maybe used in the electrical water pageants
Which maybe he found it for that too
But what but certainly there's multiple Disney stories attributing it to this guy Jack Wagner there were they were talking about
What is the score of this parade? Is it Fantasia music?
And then he said it just doesn't fit the or because the orchestral doesn't work with this for me
It may be it's a weird keyboard thing and I have records that are like this and he went and found
This record by Jean-Jacques Perry and Gershon Kingsley and that became the score but Jack Wagner if you don't know is the guy
I mean, he's mainly known for remain seated, please
permanecer sentados por favor and
He is he's the vocoder voice at the beginning of the parade he is the like, yeah ladies and gentlemen boys and girls
Bonkers so that got like the the texture this guy added to the park in general with his voice
But also that he picked this song and is the vocoder. What what an MVP legend
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah a literal Disney legend and
Probably a ptr legend to Perry you did say Perry and Kingsley was there a re in Kingsley so
Jean-Jacques Perry Gershon Kingsley
They I mean I I found that this was some connecting the dots that freaked me out in high school
Realizing that because they made this cool this really amazing record called the in sound from way out
Which is a weird kooky record from 66 of blippy bloopy keyboard music
That same title was and the cover were used by the Beastie Boys for an instrumental album
They you like borrow or whatever you want to call it the same that that phrase which is very cool
But this is from an album called the kaleidoscopic vibrations
Gershon Kingsley also did a similar like early synth song called popcorn
Which you'd know it from the melody which is that?
Bimp bump bump on a bump bump bump bump on a bump that feels like one of those songs like you know
But you don't know where it's from unless you guys don't is it in Tetra. Don't they use it in Tetris or something?
God, maybe my wrong. It's like I'm not sure my I don't know where song I'll look it up popcorn
I don't know where popcorn is is from but it's definitely it's just one of those like yeah, what is that?
That's some like 60s novelty thing and I don't know who made it. It was one of these guys
I think I believe it's used in Tetris
Uh, yes Tetris, yeah, it's in Tetris really a theme Tetris eating popcorn remade I think
Huh?
Yeah Tetris popcorn instrumental. Yeah. Oh
Geez Wow fuck
Yeah, so these guys like clearly like yeah like major figures in the history of synth music
Some of the first people ever to use a Moog synthesizer in any regard
And what I love about all this stuff so much is that I was I was trying to figure out like what's important about Moog
keyboard specifically and
You know a lot of it is like technical stuff
That's kind of above my head
But I think the main thing is that early keyboards were trying to sound like other things like can we get this?
You know electronic machine to sound like a piano or like an organ or like an orchestra or something
Like I think early keyboard stuff was like, how do we make sure we never have to hire an orchestra again?
can we get a machine to sound like an orchestra and
Robert Moog with his early keyboards said what if it's not trying to sound like other things?
What if we embrace the the art of fists in the electronic nature and they'll just be like these bizarre sounding things
They'll just sound totally kooky and weird and Perry and Kingsley were two of the first musicians to say that's great
Let's like twist all these dials and get bizarre sounds out of these machines, which is totally
What the parade is like every little every different little here's the deep one
Boop boop boop and here's like if you listen to their original recording all that character is in there
like and it's just amazing how much like
It's indelible now you like think of all these bugs and these little like kooky characters and their soundtrack was like
Just like inherent in this unrelated song made in 67
Yeah, that is very interesting how perfect that ends up being
I mean, I'm sure there's obviously there's a million different ways to you know, make creative decisions
But it does feel like it was completely written for this
It fits perfectly like a parade
It was completely like parade music already even though that wasn't the purpose of it and the original track is not that
Different from what they use in the parade like if you yeah, they re-recorded it
Yeah, but it's yeah, it's pretty it's pretty right on like down to that
Like that opening drone and that real wild pitch bends like boom
It's so great. It's so great. I think what I was saying was like that
The bizarre character of those old keyboards is the parade too. It's like
Weird and janky and kooky and of its era, but that's what everybody
Loves about it. I don't know. This thing is like it's like the mystery electrical parade isn't inherently a
Retro thing. I don't think that's why people love it, but there's certainly that
Error to it. It's like it's like so part of the DNA and I love that
Disney has something that's so of its time in so many ways. Yeah, because it's not retro
It's also not like retro Disneyland in the way that
You're like opening day Disneyland stuff is
It's retro in the way we I think talk a lot of on the show we like is like 70s and 80s retro Disney
That like is the I mean and obviously you Scott, you know what I'm talking about more than anyone but like the retro future
That's what it feels like
I mean since since in general have such character to them and and I think as a kid
Whether you knew it or not you were like thinking that this is the music of the future
This is suggesting just hearing a synth is like you're thinking about like robots and you're thinking about some crazy
technological like
Society like well, I got you couldn't I probably couldn't articulate it at 10
But if I heard those noises and beeps it was like whoa, this feels like some crazy cool like hundred years from now
It really as a kid you cannot process what these sounds are
You like don't like I don't know what this is but it is different and I want to hear more of this and I'm sure
this parade factors into the why like I
Probably the vast majority of music I listen to has some synth component. I bet that's that's true for you to some extent, too
It's just I don't yeah the just the texture these there's I provide as cool as hell
I was working on something yesterday and I was like I should see what synths they have in logic and there I
Was just saying there's like hundreds and I just go through each one and just like run my hands up and down the keyboard
Because it's so satisfying to hear these bizarre
Robot sounds that are in there. It's like which when you call me
Yeah, yeah, absolutely. Oh my god, just putting your hand on a key. How cool it feels instantly
and that's what the fact that these early synth guys were such like they were combo musicians and
Scientists like they worked in laboratories literally
And some of the early ones like it took an entire room to play it and I think the Moog
What this stuff is played on were some of the first keyboards that could actually you could pick up and take somewhere else
They weren't stuck in a laboratory. Yes, it really it's honestly it makes too much sense that these were scientists
Because there's something like so beautifully artificial and clinical and scientific about the sound as well
I mean that in a good way. Yeah
It's like what's kind of like it can be like a lot of them can be like kind of almost like cold sterile sounds
But there's something there's something beautiful about that too, isn't there?
Well, and it's funny it's still like I did this ever not feel current like when we were in
Orlando and I was staying at Universal I was walking around like
the the
City walking by the hotels like after the parks had closed but horror nights had started and the soundtrack of horror nights in
2019 was all like synthy
Like spooky like it I found like a playlist
I don't know was official or not on Spotify and it's all like a mix of weird horror music and like
Synthy like club music and stuff and I was just walking by I was like that sounds cool
Should I just should I go in should I should have gone in I should have bought a debt
But just standing outside it's like wow that seems like a cool party
Yeah, it's like I mean obviously like I think everything comes back into stint of vogue or whatever
But like stranger things has that very synthy
Synthy song we just watch good time for the first time a couple of oh, yeah
And obviously the Safdies love this this synth
They love using it to make you feel just constant dread
They love I mean like it follows like there's always like every year
There's some new thing that feels like the future by using a lot of synths like it'll never not be the future
This is what I'm saying. We always come back to this about Tomorrowland and Epcot like just there's no new future
It's still like it's it's still neon and since that will always be it's like a future that will never come
Getting out of date. What's that deep neon blue always the future? Yes. Yes
Color schemes of Tron legacy how to correct probably the digital thing
Maybe one of the things that is age the best in terms of like the look of the odds and 2010s
I can't remember the actual movie myself, but just like that blow glowing
Greenish blue is like yeah, that still works still like that
Yeah, and Daft Punk always feels like future music despite always nodding to 60s and 70s music
Tron the music by Wendy Carlos who also did a lot of these early experimental like a peer of Gershon
Kingsley and John Jack Perry with her switched on Bach
Records those were like also make a mix of experimental or and also fun and weird to listen to
Which that was yeah a lot of these early records were like
What if we took classical music and played them through these weird keyboards?
And in fact the guy who ultimately played the Disney version, I believe Don Dorsey is his name
The guy who made the new burro co-down for Disney in the 70s
He also put out an album in the 80s called Bach busters
And it has a cover that is delightful to look up where a guy playing Bach is like
Running somewhere or from something while holding a big keytar
Check out Bach busters
Do you have a keytar Scott? No, um, I only the the one that came with rock band. Oh, right
Technically I do have a little what do I have it says it a mini move I forget
but
also interesting about all this that John Jack Perry
Went to Disneyland in 1980 and saw the parade and this just started playing and he didn't know that his music was in the parade
Until that moment. Wow just started. Yeah bonkers like it was because it was run by the publishers
Disney didn't rip him off. He was making money from it. Right? Just they just like never
alerted him so he's just in the park and hears that his
Notes start and it freaks him out, but it made him very happy and kind of never
Stops cuz I don't know if we've said yet
like this is the backbone of the soundtrack of the parade and then as the radio cues like as
the floats cue the different music cues
Like electric versions of like Alice in Wonderland or and and the other songs kind of play on top of this
We're like mix that is a really bonkers thing about it that it was this other track that Disney didn't make and yet
It was the base that all of their melodies go on top of the fact that it worked as like a starting point
And now we'll do all the classic Disney songs and that they all fit. It's never like anachronistic
It's so crazy and probably helped make them a little more current at the time like bring them back into people's minds
Yeah, I mean they were re-releasing those movies every other month still but you know
Very merry on birthday is probably my favorite within that it's such a fits so perfectly in that particular variety of
Flake weird deep
That that one fits the best for me and that might be my favorite little musical stint
That's probably right cuz like the movie is a nightmare
Movie is a nightmare
Or like a
Psychedelic surreal I should say it's psychedelic more than a nightmare
I mean the movie is a nightmare, but that's not what we like about on birthday sure sure
Maybe it's time to start
You know we should maybe start talking about sections of the parade and floats and stuff
But just real quick before in the music section. I one thing I think is awesome
John Jack Perry Gershon Kingsley were both born in the 1920s, but they only died pretty recently
like Perry died in
2016 Kingsley died last year these guys made it so long
And when John Jack Perry died a relative said
No one should be sad
There's nothing he would want more than for his fans to be playing his crazy funny catchy moog music and smiling instead of being sad
He was the happiest guy so listen to his music and smile. He seems like the coolest
And this for you can watch footage of him not from not that long ago at the knitting factory playing Baroque
Oh down how audience goes bonkers?
Well watching him actually play the complicated parts of it so cool these guys are great
Maybe very happy to talk about these guys. Yeah, did you ever think about did you know you could see him live?
Did you ever think about it? Oh
Yeah, I don't hmm. I mean I was out my radar
Yeah, no not really
nor have I I've made no effort to see marauder probably the the biggest
you know the
Most looming I quote my own thing Lord of synth
I was gonna say there and we plug Lords of synth can somebody watch that Scott made a very funny
Was it a short I guess you call it
Adult swim special it was a 4 a.m. Special yes if you're interested in
synth and Lords and
Synth patchwork and that kind of thing
Please check out Lords of synths one of my favorite things that urban
Part of many past guests of the show on a part of it too, and yeah, it's it's great Perry and Kingsley not
reflected in it, but
Yeah, hey, it was it was so fun. I still can't believe it happened
Where is it available?
Just on YouTube for free okay? Wow isn't that insane? Yeah?
It's it's funny that works out
So many people have told me they like Lords of synth it because they saw it because they got to see it
It was not some weird paywall, so yeah go to YouTube look up words of synth. I'm very proud of it
Yeah, check it out
Yeah, so let's get back to the actual I guess parade
Yeah, yeah, what are what part what parts do we like what?
What's what are what are highlights in your your guys mine? I mean they're all kind of highlights
I always think about like goofy sitting on one of those balls
Mm-hmm, I don't know why that comes to mind
I mean the I think the Kings are the two turtles that hat turtle glasses turtle
Like I was trying to figure out if they have names, and I think via eBay at least if the eBay
Listings for like models of them you can get are accurate
And I think their names are lightning bug and twinkling turtle wonderful how twinkling turtle I have the
I have the Park Star
Turtle oh
That's great. Yeah, I have that one look at that
That's about that's a that's a top-notch Park Star that I guess is twinkling turtle that is twinkling turtle. Yes
I have twinkling turtle. Hi. That's there's maybe a disconnect for me that he's yeah high in the parade
I didn't know he was wearing a tie until I got the toy. He's wearing a tie the ones got a jaunty hat
I like the snails too both the snails are great
Yeah, snails and ladybug and if you had to pick something to do in this parade
It would be hard to resist
Driving one of these things around oh yeah, that would be spinning. Oh goddamn cool spinning that thing. Are you kidding me?
I would have a ball spinning that turtle I
was thinking in the way that
These are this the music's done on weird janky synthesizers the parade is chicken wire and chaos and the way the fact that these
There's such a human element to the way those things move around and spin around it is
You know it's not like perfect motion controlled rise of the resistance
It's weird and wonky and you can see the like antenna
No shake back and forth and you can imagine one of them driving into the crowd if they weren't careful
It's not that everything in theme parks has to be
Janky like these things are I just love that there's both. I love that. There's like the highest technology and
You know weird rickety technology, too
There's a human element to the turtle spinning flick flailing wildly in a seemingly dangerous way
And it would be so fun all right not to hit people
But if you lined up a bunch of like dummies a bunch of crass crash test dummies
Along Main Street, and then just got to like plow through a row of 20. Oh, just nail them. Yeah
Yeah
Like for giant bowling pins oh
Yeah, yeah, oh my god right in the middle of me. Oh, yeah, I'm down
See if you can see if you can get them all with that initial impact right
Hell yeah, I was gonna say I love the when dopey is driving the minecart with the diamonds or the jewels I should say
Yeah, that is a child of course the jewels and in Snow White and they perfectly
Made them as attractive as they were and the new minecart
coaster and I say new it's five years old, but the new ish minecart coaster and
When you see those jewels when you see those rubies and sapphires, I you know that's a nostalgic
thing for me
Gotta give it up for the fancy mice the waltzing mice that are all electrified
One of the top uses of the fancy Cinderella mice which is my wife Aaron loves very much
I don't know what it I never asked her to
Explain what it is exactly I?
They their heads are just so giant and they look so
Stupid they just look like such daft characters, but in a little tricorder hat. It's like they're trying so hard
It's like Homer putting on a tie
To be mildly impressive at work. That's that's how it feels like these dumb creatures are trying to look I dressed up
I'm doing a good job
About dressing up
I was noticing when I was watching the video that like the seven dwarfs have on like gold pants
Or like so like shiny pants like happy has gold pants and then like one of them just has like maybe purple pants
But they're shiny they're like dressed like the Rolling Stones or something
Like they're like they're like aging rocker kind of cool leather pants that are colorful
Which I really like it's like I don't know that it reads so well to people like I don't know you could tell
Necessarily, but maybe maybe it's something you subconsciously realize that happy's pants are gold
Yeah, and it's sort of like refracting light right some way here. You're noticing it in some regard the
We you know we should we should talk about the costumes the fact that all these costumes are electrified
And how insane that must have been in the 70s it did light people on fire the first time they tried it
But not so much anymore, and I it's it's very complicated with late to there
I think there's battery packs like in wigs often. Yeah, that's where they're hiding a
battery pack in a wig
Yeah, it's very cool
Some of very Liberace is what it is
Liberace he must have loved the Main Street Electrical Parade I hope he got to see it. Oh my god
There'd be no better audience
Oh my gosh
He would have been the like if he ever like could just like have joined the parade on one of the floats and played piano
on top
That might be the greatest thing I'd ever seen like this one like this big mouth
Yeah, it's like the mouth the big pleasure island. That's gone. I think from recent versions
Is that right or is that still there? That's there isn't it? I?
Saw it. I watched a video of them
Building it in one of the side like really rebuilding it and rebulbing it
In one of the like former parking lots at California Adventure like what's probably Cars Land now
They were like the parking lot was clear, and they're like putting you know they're putting the thing back together
It's kind of fascinating footage
I think it was a Martin's vids, but I know that face was in that okay
It was at least still around in the it's I'm looking at it in 2017 in the faces there. Oh all right
Some stuff is coming going though right like there was rescuers stuff. I think at some point I
Didn't see that I believe it
Yeah, there's a on the Pinocchio front
There was a big underwater section, so there was more Pinocchio
Which includes when you wish upon a star as the score which I forget if the other part had that
But there's a bunch of seahorses. There's a huge monstro. That's spouting and Gepetto's boat is in its mouth
And even Gepetto's there like he's about to get eaten or like he's just getting spit out. I don't know what moment we're seeing
But it was it was really cool like I could only find an old grainy video
But it was I don't know I don't know why they took this one out. It's super cool
Yeah, there's a lot of it's like I'm interested in yeah, if there's like some sort of resource that we're missing that has like every single
Little change and all the different versions. I mean there is a lot of there's a lot of documentation of it
But yeah the Disney fandom that it has a full list of floats
I don't know what was running at any given time and obviously
internationally they
Do not have the to honor America
section oh
Right yes is yes
To honor America yeah very interesting that's that's a very of its era thing too
It wasn't there for the bicentennial it was a couple years late, but it still feels like it was part of
bicentennial mania
Yeah
It is 77 it seems like it got an or 77 when it debuted
I have 77 as an important year and 84 as an important year
I think a lot of what we think of the parade as comes from 84
77 was the opening excuse me
so much so supposedly that I read that um
You know as fond as we are of it like some of what we a lot of what we love might be from those years
That you said and those refurbishments because Disney apparently likes to keep photos of the original on lockdown
Like it looks so bad in the early 70
It must have been like the you know the weird first season of mystery science theater where the robots are falling apart
It's not like the the still janky, but charming version
We know I think like Disney does not want you to know how bad it was in 72
yes, they want I mean because with any of this stuff with any of the Disney stuff like
What happens is is that your brain remembers the newest version of it?
Yeah, so it's like unless something was drastically different like in my mind. I saw this version
Forever this is the like the new verse the newish version like which I haven't seen I guess we saw Scott
I know we went to see it in 2017
It was one of the best Disneyland visits. So what a great one
Yeah, we went to blue bayou because we had to buy the pig package and then like you got a prime viewing spot for the
New per the new viewing of the parade
and a blue bayou dessert of
One of the bugs. Oh, yeah, I finally forgot about that. I have probably have a photo of that somewhere
Yep, which which we ate while in the wind that somebody checked their phone and said la-la land won the Oscar tonight
Yes, we had that dessert in the window where it was not yet clear that
it ended up being moonlight and had watched the
Oscars in the great moments with mr. Lincoln for a few
Awards, I believe right. That's the day. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, it's a fine ABC
production so they
some great cross-company synergy
So watching the Oscars in the Lincoln Theatre, so so great I got they got to do that kind of thing more
Can we just like we just watch you know, what would you do?
Um, oh, yeah. Yes bachelor in paradise from from the Lincoln shutting down
Yeah shutting down the Lincoln Theatre early to watch like all in the family live
My only complaint about it was that they should have like lifted up the screen to see Lincoln once in a while while we were
watching
He should have watched along and nodded and laughs and right
Made caddy comments about what the what the celebrities were wearing. Mm-hmm
Yeah, and then they like in between instead of showing I was always just you know, Joan Rivers style
Snipping and snipe course. Yeah, I was gonna say instead of commercials. They should have displayed two brothers
On the screen
Just we cute we got it queued up for you. We know what shit like it's
Just the highlights here. Yeah
But yeah, I don't think Abe has a queued up and uses it to play off people whose speeches are too long
Yeah, two brothers should be this probably some commercial campaign that is begging to use two brothers like one of these
What's the there's some commercial about where like the different?
The KitKat factory and like the
The brothers split into different
Lefts lefts and rights left wicks right wicks. Yeah. Oh, it's Twix. It's not okay
No, KitKat is a strong strong bond. You need all those all of those wafers
KitKat is a strong bond KitKat is a strong bond meet me familiar salute
Or maybe it should be like Coke or Pepsi should buy it and
imply that the other that their competitor is the Confederacy of
Sodas is blue
so coke
Would be
Yeah, yeah, I'm not sure the I gotta chart the math on this but it's it's dying it's you could change the colors. Yeah
Any products that doesn't have a catchy jingle right now
Two brothers is sitting right there waiting for you to grab it looking at you La Croix
Maybe honestly, maybe there is a synth version of two brothers that could be made
Like a well, that's the yeah
Maybe they yeah, they got to appeal to the you know, all the the hardcore American adventure fans out there
And yeah, they got they should do it in the middle of to honor America a Civil War
Section with lit up electric versions of the family and then the brother who dies goes dark
Oh, yeah, dragon. Yes, they
We've talked about mashups before they should start mashing up Disney properties like this
Yeah, yeah, I so it's like you're going from did it intend to do and ding ding ding ding ding ding ding
Ding ding ding ding and then
Right and then Ben Franklin and Mark Twain could be wearing gold pants
And they shake hands and then spark yes
That would be really great spark of American Brotherhood
I
Was saying but to honor America
I mean, it's like I I don't mind that it's fun
but what I didn't realize is that before that the
finale of this parade
was a huge section with
where characters were in like I
Got to describe them as like crystals essentially. It was like
like glass rectangle it was it was a mix of like
Glass and mirrors and the characters were done in neon and they spun
I got to show you guys this if you haven't seen I found like a really crappy old video of it
It was like it
I mean it looks like Logan's runners and a do or so like I it made me so mad that that's not the finale
Anymore it was like this the sleaziest Vegas mirror on the ceiling vibe
Um that was like a truly amazing finale before
It was like yeah real real grimy and cokey. I loved it. Hmm. Yeah, that's great
That's like that sounds bad. I mean bad in a good way. Sometimes it's good. Sometimes it feels good to be bad though
It looks to me like the only the silhouette that I remember seeing was was Pinocchio
So seeing like a neon silhouette of Pinocchio in a revolving
mirrored cube and it felt like what would be at the entrance if
Pinocchio opened a strip club
Which he could have I mean he was on the Pleasure Island
If he had liked Pleasure Island more you could see him opening up a strip club for sure
It might have planted the sea if he didn't quite learn his lesson, yeah, he might have opened
a
rural Italy's
hottest strip club
He could have turned into like a he could have turned into whole like wooden Bob Gucci Oni type
Well, if you know if it was him doing the stripping
Like if he grew, you know now that he's real he grows up gets buff
He's like Chippendale style and the club is called real boys
Hmm
You choked on that idea it's just the name they're all of a you only strip club they're all of a sorry I
Was joking on how much money we're gonna make on that idea
Yeah, well, I mean we've we've already got to make the two brothers burrow codown mash
We are known you know what I'd like to officially formally
Suggest that the listeners stop calling us good boys and start calling us real boys
No
No now now my choking is started
Well, we keep it real here on podcast. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, that's why we're the real boys the real boys
Yeah, that's that's it. Oh
No now I'm so now I'm upset I brought up the
Revolving mirror cubes. It's your fault. Am I gonna just let it die? I'm like Peter Pan. These boys are all grown up
Worse worse, but it's good worse, but it's good
Sometimes sometimes it's it's it's good to be worse
As we also talk about lost floats did you guys catch the
1985 and 1985 only
film tie-in float oh
I saw don't tell me just cuz I'm gonna I have I have so many tabs open
Is 85 the great mountain?
Oh, yeah, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry
Is 85 the great mouse detective
That is the year but not the okay
It's real it's we'd never think of it return to oh, oh, yeah, I miss it was a return
Miss this look up pictures look up pictures Wow bunkers
I'm very excited about this. I can't believe I didn't see this. Whoa
It's a it's similar in it's it's not unlike them I think mirrors were also deployed in I don't know why they aren't using
mirrors more often
It looks pretty looks pretty good
And also very like casino sleazy Biff Tannen's pleasure palace really does yeah
Yeah, this is not that far off from some of the original MGM grant
Oz
stuff I feel like
Well, do you yeah, it's a lot like that absolutely did you read about the incident
The incident oh is that on some is is it is it written in a way that is sort of?
Weird and misspelled well, I'll read it. You know I haven't proofread it. I'm just gonna read this sentence
I'm not gonna look at it again here
We'll see what it is the float that we're talking about return to Oz float the float barely lasted a single summer as the reflective
Mirrors suffered this floats fate as it caught fire and was completely destroyed
That's better written than what I read what I read I didn't believe because it was so typo
so the you're saying that the
The lights like refracted around the mirrors and it caused the thing to overheat
It sounds like it was cursed glare that it sounds like there was a curse or something
It burned itself down for the insurance money
That's what I'm getting it. Yeah, I
Were there care where their characters
From the movie walking around do we have any
They were on the float there was a Dorothy and there was a guy here if you google google image means your electrical parade returned
Oz you'll see it
There's that the the pumpkin head guy. I don't know who that is pumpkin head one of the jack pumpkin. I believe that's his name
And I see I
Dorothy is holding a chicken
Huh, is it a real chicken that a fake chicken? I?
Cannot tell from these there's a decent video of it
Um, I was looking for tick-tock
But tick-tock is my favorite character from return to Oz
He was sort of the round like copper I assume copper robot guy do you know him do you know I'm talking about I
Have never seen this film really still to childhood scared of this film. Oh, we got it. We got to do it. I
Haven't seen it in quarantine. We got to do it. Oh
Is it on
believe so
Okay, it looks like it is yeah, yeah, oh, yeah, I'm scared of it now
You should be currently scared while looking at it. You should be scared
There's a ton of Oz books like these are not characters made out of whole cloth
I believe like these are from the the bomb. Yeah. Yeah, those are from the books. Yeah
I think it's some ways return to Oz is a little more like the books than the the Judy Garland version. I
Think I always hate that whenever anything is quote more like the books. I always think it's worse
I believe I'm in point Willy Wonka
I'm not what I know jack pumpkin head plays a big part in the continuing books
Oh, yeah, I'm not saying return us is better than the classic Wizard of Oz. I'm just saying sure
it's like more it's interesting because it's more like
horrifying
Yeah, well I'd like to think that
In my mid-30s, I would not watch this film and be scared
But maybe I think I think maybe I'm gonna try to get Lindsey to watch it tonight with me
We've watched it. We watched it years ago, I think
Oof I'm getting a real my my never-ending story
Jeans or
Getting lit up here. I'm I am I never ending story phobia is kicking in. I look I feel like I
Know exactly what you're saying
And I think there's a sense you'll get a sense of accomplishment though when you do it because I've been trying to do that
Here and there with other movies. I've died the scariest one of course being Hellraiser
No, yes, where I watched Hellraiser because I was like, you know, you'd see the VHS
Copy of it sitting a blockbuster and just go
Never never how why why would I do it who likes it why
and then I was like, you know what let's try it and
There's some interesting stuff in it. It's a lot of like hooks going through skin
I don't necessarily need to see hooks going through skin, but the return Oz is so much less
Gross than that. It's but there is one thing that is so traumatic in my mind about return to Oz that I think you might know
You might know it's not gonna be that traumatic though for you now, but as a kid as a kid I saw it
That's why it's traumatic for me
I'm looking at pictures of the gnome king and I don't like this guy at all
You're not gonna like a lot of the characters. I really think I'm going to hate all of the characters. I think
Griffin Newman and on blank check I think nodded to this when they were talking about silence of the lambs
But I think in my head
It's just that that that one poster of silence of the lambs where them there's them like the moth is on her mouth
Yes, like I think I thought it was hellraiser
I think I thought it was like a movie about a villain who like puts a moth on your mouth who changes your
mouth into a moth
Or the or that I didn't know what it was when I was six
So maybe I thought Jodie Foster was like some kind of moth Queen. Well, she'd spit moths
I think that's because I think maybe I thought it was like the fly. Oh
Yeah, cuz I had seen cuz my friend Luke would his parents let him watch our rated movies
Am I it was that like I was like forbidden from it, but we just never saw it
So I thought that I couldn't see our rated movies. So I didn't really see our rated movies until I was in my like mid teens
Sure
So they felt like they felt like truly I would I might like I
Might die if I see an R-rated movie before I was ready. I
Yeah, I think I thought every one of these movies if you put it on would just be like plotless and it's just like
People getting like whipped and tortured and torn apart on a rack for 90 straight minutes. Well now there's no stories. There's no characters. It's just
Yes, from what I know of hellraiser. There is a lot of that, right?
I mean you go beyond the world hellraiser of hellraiser is a lot of pleasure and pain
There's a lot of again close-ups of skin
With a hook going through it and like tearing the skin
You're like, well, this is actually closer to what I maybe thought it was than some of the other movies where I went
Oh, this is fine. This isn't that bad, but hell raisers pretty intense
But not without some interesting not without some interesting things in it
Hmm. Hmm. Well, maybe it's time. Let's face our fears. You watched the scariest movie hellraiser
I'll watch the scariest movie returned which is rated PG. I think
Bullshit I hate this rating. I think you scary. She's scary for 34 year olds. Yeah
Here let's get back on the ground of some let's let's go to the opposite of
Let's go back go way more pleasant than this
Our our pal the dragon our else I have to make sure to say Elliot the dragon not it's one of those Frankenstein
Things I think I still even though the title is Pete's dragon. I still look at him and I think oh look there's Pete
I also know that's not right. I also think that
Yeah, yeah
I mean like truly special to me in a way. I can't further explain than I already did. I just try really
Remember seeing this for when I was three years old and boy it just it made my heart glow
I could not be more earnest in my affection for this thing and I I don't think I'm alone in that
Yeah, I don't know. I know I have never seen the original Pete's dragon, which might be blasphemous
And it's not because I was scared of it or anything. I just have never seen it
but that dragon
does
Feel like I saw it and have some sort of attachment to it from childhood
Very easy to mix up in my mind with sword in the stone
Sure, he's dragging sword at the stone similar
Yeah, well, I mean it's well like the era but then one is live-action and one is all animated right
But you could yeah all those from the round that era. I can kind of miss mix up a lot of things
Yeah
That's what is that within a few years or am I?
Wrong
They're a little they're a little far apart. That's like 60s and 70s. I think
I'm not sure. I'm curious if people think Pete's dragon is good. I haven't revisited in a while
I think I may have just liked it because it was around it might have been one of those. Yeah
Well, the character is so cute and friendly looking
It's like well and I mean as with all just like you know my any Star Wars affection
Comes from the ride first I think I like Pete's dragon because he's in this parade
Yeah, that's yeah, I could see that that makes a lot of sense. It might be better not to watch Pete's dragon, you know
Just like have your perfect memory of this dragon is the one from the parade and
He'll never go. Yeah, it'll never go away because the parade is gonna apparently come back for the rest of time
Like they'll never they brought it back last year
When the attendance was sluggish at Disneyland because of Galaxy's Edge
Yeah, I people lose it I mean I
Definitely have fallen for it, too
It's like oh the electrical parades back like how many times have they done this and I still fall for this crap
Yes, it's still and I yeah, but yeah when
Mike when we went with Aaron and Lindsay
Just like that that glow that comes from that opening note in the VOCA and and then you start seeing him look there they are it's
Yeah, I don't know even if it is like a crass marketing move. Yeah, it still triggers something that is very pure
It's yeah, they do it a lot. They're doing a lot. So I'm just saying yeah, you'll be able to see this dragon
forever, I think
Yeah
I'd like to say that when they brought it back this most recent time a couple years ago
I'll go out on a limb and say that commercial that they made in the warehouse where all of the characters live
Like like the room of Disney magic that you have in your heart and the girl puts the last bulb on it
I think that might be the best Disneyland commercial that there has ever been
Yeah, it's up there like it's up there with like that's original Space Mountain commercial. Oh
Oh hell which is such a
Now yeah, well, thanks for reminding me all right number two
Well, if it was a final four of Disneyland commercials, it would absolutely be in the final four. I think
That's not a bad idea. That's not a bad. We haven't thought about that yet. I don't think yeah
There's that Disney land Paris one with Donald running around with real ducks like that's very cute
That is cute. I do like what a different song eras that I'm going to Disneyland
There's like they've gone in and out of it. There's all the athlete things
Oh you you guys had that too. They sang I'm going to Disney World in the marketing material
I so I didn't realize they recorded both versions of it. They did both. Yeah
Trick this
But I don't know I that
You know that ad though. I really I think they nailed I like like when when all the floats are
Leaving like heading into the park with this glorious pink sky that really is like the ideal Disneyland we all
You know we all imagine is there as opposed to just like it's a boring like warehouse back there. It's they did such a great
It's what you want it to be backstage, you know
Yeah, the cloak like the closest to that I've probably talked about on the show before it was the maybe
2015 d23 where they had this Imagineering exhibit
And it was it felt like that it felt like you just walked through
The warehouse and it was like it had the big like it had the big weird Ben
Is it Ben Franklin float from that weird 70s parade?
Do you know what I'm playing? Oh, oh, right. All right. Yes. Yeah
American parade or something. Yeah, I forget the name of it, but it was a big sandwich
Yes, yes, it was a big sandwich. Oh, yeah now you have my attention
Rex like the full the full-size Rex the like ride vehicles that felt like walking through
I mean what I the commercial came after that but then I was like, oh, yeah that kind of reminded me of that exhibit at
D23 which they had never
The next year was like or the you know, two years after when they did the next one in 2017
It was like
Pirates of the Caribbean only and it was like half of the movie stuff and you're like, yeah
I don't know if this is quite as good as two years ago
Two years ago. I was so thrilled there two years before that
I mean, I was so thrilled to walk through all that stuff and then I was like
Well, it's cool to see like some of the ride vehicles and some of the pirate robots
But I don't necessarily need to see Barbosa's jacket
You don't want to see the headband that Keith Richards wore when he just shows up on screen for 30 seconds
I yeah, I was not as thrilled to see that as I would have been to see some other like
country bear busts or robots know I
So they this first one away
In 1996 in a very confusing way
I don't really still don't really understand why they took it away
But it was a big disaster and they replaced it with this thing light magic
Please go to patreon.com slash pockets right will explain light magic. It was so much emotion in it
Disappearing but but like why it was like it's felt like an absolutely arbitrary event to get rid of it
They completely backfired because now they've just been plugging it in to like fix, you know
Attendance problems ever since yes
Yeah, I wonder I mean I I would imagine that like the people in charge
Probably because of the janky nature of it, especially when it like when it started
Then the nostalgia obviously wasn't there because it was new
So I would imagine that maybe the people in charge and the people who were making it
This is a guess but we're like all they saw was were the flaws of it
All they saw were like, oh, yeah, this looks like shit like we got to make a much better version
Whereas like people that came to the park were like this is great. We really like this and
It's lasted for whatever reason, you know for so many years
And I think yeah, they I don't think they realize it's it's because of what they were regarding as as crappy or or
Tossed together. It's just what it's the character of
Of what it is. Some things are meant to be super high-tech and some things are charmingly low-tech and that's what this thing is
Yeah
And boy did it backfire as will explain because what they put in was supposed to now here we here's a real parade
Everyone hated it. I hate it. I'll say that
Yes, I have to give them credit. I mean the the farewell season marketing like this billboard
Now it's time to say goodbye. Okay, I get that, you know Mickey Mouse Club reference
The farewell season logo like I get trying to drum up business
This one with the two snails and the text we can't glow on like this is the grimace
Seen
Because they're smiling like they're smiling. It's saying we can't glow on like this
They're cracking that is so upsetting
It's a it's a forced smile. They're jokers
David joker
Bugs are joker fine joker fight. They can't go on like this. Oh, yeah, that's really morbid
Wow good fine, yeah, that is oh my god, what a nightmare. Yeah
We can't glow on like this like it's it's funny
Like, you know how they say Wolverine when he pops his claws out it hurt and he says this is famously in the first X-Men
Movie it hurts every time maybe these characters are just in pain doing this parade
No, no, Michael
Maybe the lights are just like it's really like hurting them. They're all kind of sentient
Floats and they're just in constant pain. They're dizzy
They're overheated and they just need to be put out to pasture
The light is their blood. It's supposed to be inside
Oh, they're leaking they're gonna run out they need transfusions the original the original Imagineers gave them consciousness
Imagineers gave them consciousness
Walt was working on consciousness for the robots before he passed away and then they finally perfected they have perfected it in the 70s
And the floats had the early version of the consciousness, but they could also feel pain. I
Have to say a that y'all get into it over on the second gate
There is a pre light magic pitch of what the the new parade was gonna be gonna be that isn't that far from
Characters who are whose consciousness is like
There is one of the creepiest worst ideas have ever and we'll I'll tease it for for over there. Yeah
Hey, it's it gets it gets grim
But of course the the parade
You know kept going kept reappearing and but pretty quickly in fact it what it was 96 it went away it reared its head in
1997 in one of the strangest events Disney ever did where it
Transformed it got a new name as it ran through Times Square in New York City and was called the Hercules
Electrical parade. Yes
Zero to hero, baby
I
This is so bizarre they did they did a whole deeply expensive weekend in New York City
Promoting the release of Hercules several years prior having done a
Like ginormous screening of Pocahontas in Central Park. So it was kind of a sequel to that
I think slightly less pleasant films
with
Huge New York events that get in New Yorkers way and make them mad
We got to do it again. I don't I mean, I'm not the first person to say this
But I don't understand why they used that parade like Hercules is a movie wasn't this like neon
light synth movie
Not really no, they also made original Hercules floats that they never used again
Like this one night one night one night this horrifying representation of Hades
Which I'm assuming is what the inside of James Woods is
Rotting brain looks like now
But like yeah, they did from what I was reading they did this in
1977 for the Pete's Dragon premiere
Oh in New York, yeah Pete's Dragon premiered at Radio City musical and they did
Some sort of whether it was the electrical parade, but they they did a similar event for that as well. Let's well document it
Whoa
That's crazy and I also found another strange
Outside of its natural habitat
Although you know what I'm realizing I think they made a big deal out of this thing and they said
This is the first time the Main Street Electrical Parade has been performed outside of Disneyland and that's it's bullshit if that
If there was a another New York one then that that's one and then I found another one
Which is it was the halftime show of the 1978 Orange Bowl
Which I think is in Florida unless I might be confused you're right moves, but I think it's for
and
It's
Find this video
So it's it's really strange
I mean like the floats will go through but the floats are obviously still extremely small in a football stadium
So what it mostly becomes is people with like big electric umbrellas or something kind of like making shapes
Just like walking around in circles and it only makes sense if you're in a helicopter point of view
It's an it's insanely boring
It was a pretty bad idea of a halftime show and then they bring out
Pete and Elliot and Pete keeps they they give him dialogue
He keeps saying like wow Elliot the Orange Bowl and he goes
Wow, I've never seen so many people
And just that
infinitely really strange
So it's a mixed bag seemingly the non Disneyland performances
Did you catch the detail about the Times Square
Turning off the lights for this. Did you catch? Yes. Yes. Go here. Go ahead this corporate
I forget where I pulled this from
but so they got Disney ran the electrical parade through Times Square and
They got most of the businesses to turn their lights off
So that parade could light up nicely all but one
All the businesses complied with the exception of Warner Brothers who had a Warner Brothers retail store at the crossroads of 42nd Street
And Broadway the lights eventually did go out at the Warner Brothers studio store when the chain went out of business shortly after that
So I don't know what to fuck you man. Like that's not cool
People lost their job. That's not a
Newspaper writer humor in the 90s was rough stuff like very bad
But maybe someone was like the light while someone was trying to like fill in the coloring book
screen of like a picture of Taz
Like maybe they needed to do that
That's my brother's stores where you were like coloring digital coloring books on screens
We we got to do the full Warner Brothers studio store episode because
did I share these with you or was I saving it for the idea of doing this that I found a bunch of
internal use
Music videos made by people from different Warner Brothers studio store franchises
There was like a music video contest for an award show
where like they all got together and like did a like a
medley of grease songs but changed the lyrics to be about like stocking shelves and like
We're out of Taz dolls
Wow
You told us about the award show I don't know that I dug down into it enough to see the music videos yet. Oh
It's so good. They're gonna be an episode just about the award show
Yeah, Joel Schumacher comes out in the middle of promoting
Batman and Robin and could not be more cocky about the suit and like you guys are gonna love it and there's so much
Oh the toys we're gonna make so much money you guys we are gonna be flush with cash. He's just like top tier
Most confident anybody could ever be no idea what's coming for that movie
Yeah, that's great. What yeah this I love those stores
I'll say a Trump is part of all that to Trump is it was an owner of several or they were like in his Atlantic City hotels
Yes, that's correct. It's yeah. Yeah, there's a lot there and we should do that one soon. Yeah
But as for this one, you know, what else about?
Time Square, I mean, yeah, they had to it took seven days to get it to New York City for one performance
And they you know, they filled in potholes. They paid
$500,000 to fill but I mean the whole thing cost five thousand five hundred thousand dollars
But like yeah, they had to do like they had to fix up the city to make this possible
This is a Disney vacation of Times Square era. So they were like spending money left and right on like family-friendly events. I
Will say the Hades float is cool is very cool. Yes. Yeah, I
Also am I also think it's they did do the to honor America at the end as well
Which is funny. Hey, which is like it's a promotional float for their movie
Do you need like the the patriotism at the end of your promotion for a movie a?
Movie set in ancient Greece. Yes. Thank you set in ancient Greece
I
Roam is it right? I always I never know who's who yeah, he's Rome. He's Roman I think
Yeah, that doesn't
Quite make sense, but I bet boy. I bet mayor Rudy
Watch that America float go by and remind him of the country love so dear and that he'll do anything to protect
Rudy should have been on the float with the gold pants
Oh
Rudy Rudy covered in Christmas lights with gold pants waving to everyone
With an electric toupee with an electric to neon electric toupee
What?
Alright calling for fan art
You know what? Wait, let me let me not call for fan art. Let me call for Photoshop
Let me call that. Yeah. Yeah, let me call it up. Be real Photoshop of Rudy Giuliani
With gold pants Christmas lights and a neon to pay
standing next to Mickey and Minnie on the to honor America float and
specifically the New York City
Hercules
electrical parade from 1997
That's my official. Yeah, it's
Specific assets. It's tough. But yeah, I I think everyone's up to the challenge and if you're listening to this still in quarantine times
You like us our board is held. Yeah, so get to work Photoshop experts fill your
Fill your time. I also
I would say a full episode about the Disney vacation of Times Square. Oh, yeah, that's good a very fun one
Let's put that in the queue, too
But yeah, this was certainly the one of the most fun zones of that
Seen by a million people it ran over four times the length of the typical Main Street electrical parade
They really did it. They really
Got some people to go to Hercules in theaters not enough but some but some
Oh
Yeah
Well, what else about this thing? I mean, it's hey, it's it'll be very happy. It'll be back
It'll certainly be back. It might be back. I would
Should I I'll predict it now I bet when
Everything opens back up dizzy. It's like hey looks look what's back come back, please
I would I would have to think so and we'll think that it's grass but
We're all
I'm gonna say I think they're gonna wait on it for some sort of a lull because I think like
For insane people like us when the park opens up
It's gonna just be like the biggest attendance day of all time that first day
So I feel like maybe they wait
To bring it back for like another lull a time, but maybe we'll see
They got to find some way to do it
digitally virtually for all of us sitting in our
separate apartments
There is a full 2019 live webcast of that version of it on YouTube
The official Disney parks channel
That's nice. Oh good
I'm glad to hear that I like that. They've been doing all this stuff like here's a really nice multicam
Tokyo phantasmic like those kind of things they've been digging up to to entertain us
Have been appreciated. I guess we hey we didn't say also that it was it was also used as like a quick fix
Fuck fuck fuck. Let's save
California adventure
Which has no Main Street they put it over in like Paradise Pier and
Called it the
Disney's electrical parade. Yeah, they had a rebrand for that quick a California classic a California California
Classic I guess that's really what you got to say about it at the end of the day
It's a California classic whether or not it's in New York or Florida. It's always a California classic
I was interested to learn I'm going through some random things
I was interested to learn the Baroque hoedown is used in the ending theme of a Mexican sitcom
From the seven from the 70s. That's fun
Yeah, Wow
One of those guys I forget which though
There's another Perry Kingsley song that I think is the theme song to the game show the jokers wild
Oh, I might be getting the game show wrong. No, that's it jokers wild. Yeah
I
Met check out that in sound from way out there all it's also good all these dumbles and songs are delightful
I can find no evidence just from a brief search that Liberace saw the electrical parade
But I will still I will hunt I will still hunt
He though when I googled Liberace Disneyland he did describe himself as a one-man Disneyland
Sure fair enough he has an out he has an album called my parade of golden favorites
He has an album called that so
He is also a one-man parade also Liberace episode eventually
There's no way
Like themed entertainment and Liberace places to go. Yeah. Yeah, I'm on board with it. I'm like writing them down
I got a little got a literal list
I'm excited for all of these
I
What do we what do we leave people with I'm tempted to
Mike you should screw around and see if you could do it
Maybe I could do it on top of the what I'd really like is to for the music on this to go out with
Like can we take the can one of us with our?
our keyboards at home
Incorporate two brothers into Baroque. Oh down. Oh, yeah, I I'll try. Yeah, I'll try I think I think it shouldn't be hard
I think it should be that hard. It's not gonna be amazing. I'm not gonna spend like weeks on it, but
Certainly not
You might be right
Yeah, the downtown Disney ordeal theme was getting into guns and roses Chinese democracy
Territory theme my god here's version 27 that theme is still only like 50% of what I wanted it to be to be honest
Yeah, I still at a certain point in length release the demos
Release the devos. I have a lot of said a lot of
Mix I needed a full real recording studio for that one and a full band honestly you becoming Brian Wilson now you and you
you've got that you got a theremin player a bunch of glockenspiels and
Lose every end up lighting the studio on fire
Losing my mom almost lost you to the downtown Disney ordeal theme. Mm-hmm. You brought in dr. Landy
Talk to me
Yeah, is it is it working out is dr. Landy jr. Getting you back on track? No, he's not as good as his father
He sucks dr. Lanny chance suck
He tried to smack a hamburger out of your hand that didn't go well. He was he was it was too light of a slip
Yeah
Well, I don't know I guess I guess with all that we can say our softer
Quarantine version. What do we settle on you put this into podcast?
I think you put up with podcast the ride you put up you put it you put up with podcast the ride
minister electrical parade edition
Boy, it truly as it makes me happy to think about the parade the commercial made me so happy
And then talking about it for a while made me so happy. This is hopefully in that
area of
Very earnest episodes. Yeah, is this it's this thing's the best and enjoy it
Enjoy it everyone because this podcast is glowing away forever
Until next Friday's episode for the magnificent return of this podcast
The long awaited long awaited. Hello season. You enjoyed the farewell season
We need to rise we can't we can't glow on like this
I wait I had another one earlier. I forgot to say oh, I feel like
Shots of smiling bugs and the tech line is they've lost the will to shine
What are you saying Mike I don't remember
But for
For more of the mainstream electrical parade story go to patreon.com slash podcast the ride the second gate where we
Will talk about its successor light magic the app ran for less time than the mainstream
I took a did the fuzz bucket of?
night-time Disneyland light parades
Amen absolutely and day for for more stuff
Which oh I so I say I said I was trying to say Twitter and I said twitch, but we're yeah
We're trying to do twitch stuff. We've been having fun, but Twitter Instagram and Facebook all the usual stuff
Yeah, check check us out all right. I got one
The new ad that just says it's the turtle and everyone it just says we're glowing to hell
All right well so enjoy podcast the ride before we all glow to hell, but also enjoy our triumphant return
Well, we'll talk to you soon all right glow to hell gentlemen
This has been a forever dog production
executive produced by Mike Carlson
Jason Sheridan Scott Gardner Brett Boehm Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts.com and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts
Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
At forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook