Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast contains discussion of an old, slow moving bucket that lazily carries
you through the air.
We love it!
It's the Skyway on podcast The Ride.
Welcome to podcast The Ride, the theme park podcast that is 100% wheelchair accessible.
I'm Scott Gardener, joined by Mike Carlson.
Hey, I am here and that is good news, yes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think we're the only one.
I believe we're the only one.
Jason Sheridan is here as well.
Yes, I am here too.
It's important to be considerate so everyone can enjoy the show.
Yes, indeed, indeed.
And I wish others were more considerate as well.
Folks, today we're talking about the Skyway, which basic primers, these were the gondolas
that took you back and forth between Fantasyland and Tomorrowland in the Magic Kingdom and
Disney World, originally in Disneyland, Tokyo Disneyland as well, from the 50s through the
mid 90s, where among the things, the factors that made them go away was the handicap accessibility.
But that's, you know, that's the main stuff.
And I'm excited to talk about the Skyway because this is like, this is some pretty classic
Disneyland stuff.
I feel like when I talk to my mom, this was a very important thing to her.
I think if you were an original decade Disneyland person, you really love the Skyway.
Yeah, I think, yeah, you when you think of the classic pictures of Disney or the classic
videos that Skyway, I guess it's probably looms large in my brain of the archived footage
because it's gone now.
So it always like I always look at it.
But I do think like that's such a huge part of what they call the kinetic energy, the
movement that you would see when you go into Disney.
Yeah, and such a great like in that first run of like attraction posters, like a really
good one.
Oh, yes, absolutely.
Yeah, the the posters that you see under the train tracks entering Disneyland.
Yeah, yeah.
Very classic one.
You know, yeah, you bring up a good point right away, Mike.
And yeah, how much the Skyway really hits you in early footage of Disneyland.
I'll say right away, let me look up the name of this on YouTube.
There's a really great film short.
I don't know what you'd call it called People in Places Disneyland USA.
And it's a lot of really beautiful film footage in color of Disneyland in 1956.
It shows you what the park was like then.
And I mean, the whole thing is great.
It's really beautiful and beautifully shot.
But, you know, they film from the Skyway as well.
And it shows you how it was a great way to see Disneyland from above to see it was another
way to see storybook land.
It was a way you could see that the old teacups, the original version of the teacups, where
you know, with like all the big spirals, like you really get a sense of the kinetic energy
of the spirals of the original Med Tea Party, maybe the best from up in the Skyway.
Yeah, it's all of that stuff.
Seeing it now, like in the footage when you see like because they I feel like they've
had footage of it shot from the Skyway, like you can sort of see the vantage point of the
Skyway.
That stuff is all exciting.
I also, of course, feel a sense of dread because of how scared I was.
Oh, good.
Oh, yes.
This is your area.
You don't like precarious dangling, I suppose.
You know what?
That's we have not branded exactly what it is about rides that I don't like, but precarious
dangling or precarious feeling, a precarious vibe, even though it maybe isn't, it's very
safe, but it's precarious.
It feels precarious.
It's, you know, it's legs dangling off of a roller coaster.
I don't love that.
It is Skyway, which is slow and I guess Skyliner, which is, of course, the new version of this
at Disney World.
It is a slow moving thing.
Wires don't help because it feels that does feel precarious.
And it's I know there's nothing under me.
There's something about that that sort of gives me anxiety.
I don't know. I think it's just some sort of inherent thing in my brain.
I don't think there was a traumatic incident or anything.
You really feel the movement on those wires.
Like if you hit a weird little bump or a sway, you really feel it.
It feels natural and it feels like it shouldn't be happening.
Like any little jerk kind of freaks you out.
Yes, that is right.
So when I saw we're talking about Skyway and this is still one that I haven't overcome.
I've overcome better, like crazier roller coasters.
I've overcome haunt.
I love haunts now.
I never did. But the Skyway type ride still has not been conquered by my brain.
And now, of course, compare that to me, who, as we've established in the past,
I am much like a goat want to be as high up as possible.
So I felt always would jump at the chance to do the Skyway or like, hey,
I know it's faster to walk, but we could take the Skyway to get to that part of the park.
You have friendly skies.
I do. Do you guys?
That's one of those weird little dumb pleasures that, you know,
barely has any impact.
But I always feel it.
The feeling of, yes, why walk when we could take that, even though taking the other transport,
because that's what else is like that the train train gets you to another part of the park
without having to walk, even though it could end up taking you vastly longer, depending.
It still feels like this dumb little cheat barely.
Like I figured out a better way, a more efficient way.
Well, I have so much affection for the Skyway.
And it's funny because what we usually so much we usually have affection for is like
theming and stuff. This besides the stations, which were very nice looking,
I think this ride could not be any less themed.
Like it's just giant gray girders and buckets.
Vehicles that were so quick, people just started calling up.
Yeah, those buckets.
Yes, never specifically referred to by Disney as the sky buckets.
But again, if you ask parents, a lot of parents might knee jerk, call it the sky buckets.
That definitely was the terminology for sure.
And I think there is like arguments to be made of like, OK, well, maybe put theming
like theming could take a back seat if it's really fun.
Like the Skyway is really fun.
Like the same, I think we were Mike and I were talking a while back of like, all right,
just sell baby Yoda shit in Galaxy's Edge.
Who cares? Everyone loves this little guy.
Just fill it. Yeah, do it.
Yeah, yeah, I know, because we we love immersive stuff.
And it's I'd like to think that the listener understands our level.
Why would we make fun of Kingda Ka at Six Flags having ads for a hair gel on the side?
But we would love just copious baby Yoda merchandising in Galaxy's Edge
and love these unthemed buckets.
I don't know. I mean, I'd like to think that the spectrum is clear.
But if we need to break it down further, let us know.
Yeah, I it's look, life is a contradiction.
That's what I always say.
So there's going to be some of it.
I mean, look at this.
I don't want to talk too much about the Skyliner.
There's enough there for its own thing.
But look at the contradiction with the Skyliner.
We're like, OK, they put they they put the the the pillars,
a lot of stuff backstage or on access roads.
And it goes by some of the very expensive hotels.
And it does not stop at them.
Like, if anything, it makes the views worse from those places.
But overall, a net positive.
Yes, sure. Sure.
Now, you know, you bring up a good point and we should break this down.
The Skyway is not the Skyliner.
The Skyway, as I said, was something from the from Disneyland
through the 50s through 90s.
And it's been gone for a long time.
The Skyliner is the new thing.
Disney World that takes you around Epcot and MGM Studios and some some of the campus.
The Skyway is also not the Starway.
The Starway is the big set of escalators
that took you from the top part of Universal Studios Hollywood down to the bottom part.
And if you want to hear more about those escalators,
we did an episode about it at Patreon.com slash by guess right.
So Skyway, not the Starway, Skyway, not the Skyliner and Skyway,
also not Ford's Magic Skyway,
which is a ride that did not take place in the sky at all.
That was something from the 1964 World's Fair.
And it is where you drove 60s Ford's through the time of the dinosaurs.
What I'm kind of saving, like I've never really dug deep on Ford's Magic Skyway.
And that's like neither I would like to.
As I say all that out loud, I'm like, why have we not gotten to that one?
Yeah, I was going to say it's also not the Minneapolis Skyway,
which is a series of elevated bridges.
Oh, which is that's what that's called.
Yeah. And that which is also the replacements have a song called Skyway,
which is what's yeah, which is a great song.
It's a nice it's like a sweet little song.
So it's not that jeez.
And it's also not I don't want to go overboard here,
but I was looking up all of the rides that have been built by the company
that built this thing, Skyway, with the company called Von Roll.
And they there's a list on Wikipedia of the other rides that they've built.
And most of them are called Skyride.
One is called Bayside Skyride.
One is there's Skybuckets.
That one's official Skyfory Skyway,
different Skyway at Six Flags Great Adventure, Skylift, Aeronaut Skyride.
It's it's a pretty dense network of the same five words to weave.
But no sky no skyfall.
I do. Is there a ride called Skyfall?
Well, it's a movie, of course.
They I think they'd like to minimize the thought of falling from these contraptions.
There. There's a type of it looks like somewhere called
Fun Time in Australia has Skyfall.
That's like it's a drop tower.
OK. Yeah, that makes more sense because that you do want to fall.
Right. That's fun.
Falling is fun in that instance.
In that instance, folks, if you got a drop tower and it's not falling,
something's wrong.
A fallout, a fallout like Mission Impossible Fallout.
That's a good fallout to watch, but less good, I guess, to experience.
If you were Ethan Hunt.
James Bond Sky Falls, Ethan Hunt falls out. Right.
They're both falling in different ways.
I think there's I think there's also a skyfall in Dollywood.
Is there is it called Skyway?
I'm sorry, it's called Drop Line.
I really need to I need to do that.
I can't just click on click bait headlines during the show.
I need to vet this info.
You got to have a talk, you know, or you're going to run into a situation
where you're you get like Camp Snoopy and Planet Snoopy mixed up.
And oh, yeah, I mean, we're still sorting that out.
And we're sure is the difference.
A indecipherable.
What?
It's pretty much depend on what the sign budget was for that any given year.
Sure.
Could we do a whole could we do a whole a separate spin off podcast
about sky based entertainment called Sky Guys?
I think the answer is yes.
Yeah, yeah, guys.
You went to college with one of the sky guys, right?
That is yes, that is true.
Yes, the sky guys.
Sky guys are not the try guys.
No, they're not. They're different.
They're they're us.
We are the sky guys.
We're not the bumper car boys who we hate and whose podcast is not wheelchair
accessible. That's correct.
We are the sky guys and also the podcast, the ride good boys
and the podcast, the ride guys who are good boys.
That well, maybe was there was we've talked about the rumors
that a third Tokyo Disney gate would be Tokyo Disney Sky, correct?
Yes. I'm in love with that name.
I know. I read.
So if I'm saying, oh, we don't hear what about Skyway?
I was just going to say I didn't realize that Disney had seen it
because Disneyland has land in it.
That. Oh, yeah.
It took me a few months or a few years to figure that out.
And I was like, oh, that's perfect.
And then I heard Disney Sky and I was like, oh, shit.
Really good. It's like a Mario level.
Where else can Mario go? There's sky levels.
And so that so the third gate
pockets are at the third gate could be in the sky, much in the Tokyo tradition.
Oh, yeah, that's great.
The third gate is the sky where we're the sky guys,
where the sky guys rise.
That's who we are.
That's who we are now.
Look out for rise of the sky, guys.
I mean, we should do
for the magic skyway, by the way.
Yeah.
But you know, you know what,
Mike, in terms of personal associations with the situation,
your your association is being scared.
My association is being scared also, but not because of the skyway itself.
I think the heights nature of it and the dams and the skyway itself
is the most important thing.
The skyway itself, I think the heights nature of it
and the dangly nature didn't bother me for some reason.
But I I viewed it as a good way
to see the abominable snowman and get a sense of the Matterhorn
before I was willing to go on the Matterhorn.
And I'm sure with this and some other things that we'll talk about,
there'll be some things we mentioned also in the Matterhorn episode.
So apologies for repeating material.
I didn't go back and relisten. I'm sorry.
But I you know, because if you weren't aware,
not in the Magic Kingdom or Tokyo Disneyland, which don't have the Matterhorn,
this ride went straight through the middle of the Matterhorn,
which used to have these two big holes in it for the skyway to pass through.
And it took you right past the abominable snowman.
So I was so excited to get to see the robot without having to do the
what I now know is the most terrifying roller coaster ever built.
That makes a lot of sense.
I'm trying to think how old was
that was like on your yearly trip when you were younger.
Yeah. And this well, the skyway was gone by 94 when I was like nine years old.
So and I when did I start?
I might have done the Matterhorn finally when I was like 10 or 11.
I'm trying to think of where I would have been at.
I think I would have been comfortable on the Matterhorn around 10,
but I may have still refused the skyway.
I don't know. I'll never know.
I I was trying to think of the like precarious dangling.
I was trying to think of a good way to synopsize
this little mini theme park syndrome I'm talking about.
And I think the phrase I came up with is scaredy cat samples.
It's a way like I got to sample the Matterhorn by passing through it
on the skyway.
Similarly, the people mover gives you a scaredy cat sample
of Space Mountain without having to go on Space Mountain for sure.
Oh, so there should be some like
Pope Mobile for you to drive around in during horror nights.
Oh, yes. Yes.
Being blockaded, knowing I can.
They're not going to get that close to you.
Yeah, there's, you know, going to be space.
You probably can't get in any like tight interactions with any scare actors.
Yeah, they can bang on the windows, maybe.
But, you know, how bad is that really?
And you can maybe even have like, you know,
those gloves when you're handling handling like nuclear rods.
You could like put your hands through there
and you could shoot people away.
Oh, yeah, sure.
You know, to make sure they keep their distance.
So you don't get scared as much as you would going through the regular maze.
I mean, this might be how we all have to experience theme parks.
Or life for the yes for the rest of time. Yes.
Horror nights are no horror nights.
We each have a little like mech suit,
like Pope Mobile that we get into that we have to get into
if we leave the house or apartment.
So each every theme park has the capacity for 25 people.
Yes. Slash slash their their mech warrior suit.
Oh, yeah, we all need the aliens suit, which is slash the avatar suit.
It's kind of the same thing.
I are there any other scaredy cat samples?
I mean, I guess sort of I used I used to feel this way, too, but like, well,
at least I get to see on the people mover, I can see the lobby of Star Tours
because I wasn't willing to go on Star Tours yet in Florida.
Yeah, the people mover.
Did you say Space Mountain already?
Yeah, I mean, that was one of them. Yeah.
Oh, because that one gets you right.
Don't you go between the lift hills?
That gets you right in there.
I've got one.
The train at Disneyland goes through the grand finale of Splash Mountain.
That's right. Oh, that was my biggest one.
No, it's for me to get.
That was the only way that I saw it for so long.
Yeah. Yeah.
Like this, just in general, like rides going through other rides.
Whenever it happens, it doesn't matter what the ride.
It rules. Oh, yeah.
It's the best. So good.
I don't know why it's the best thing, but it just happens to be.
If we break it down, like, what is it about that that makes it so good?
I don't know that you just get like another angle on a ride you like or.
Maybe it's like it's like good storytelling
where they weave together plots that you didn't expect to be weave together.
It's like the end of a Seinfeld where it all comes together.
It lets you know these rides aren't like separate little bastions.
They all they all connect. This is part of one greater whole.
Yeah, I guess that might be what it is.
I guess the same reason Marvel makes so much money with. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, it's like people are like, yeah, these two movies are connected.
The people mover is part of Space Mountain.
And it's also I guess it's like a good
piece of like hype for another ride you're going to go on during the day.
Like if you're going to Disney for the first time or you don't get to go that often,
you're going on the, you know, people mover and you're seeing Space Mountain
and you're like, oh, man, what's that?
I got to figure out what that is and we got to go on it.
You know, we've never talked about on the show.
Amazingly, it was the the Tiny Toons video, how I spent my summer vacation
where that where Plucky is in a vacation like struggle to get to.
What is the theme park called in it?
Do we know? Am I the only one of the three of us?
No, I know exactly what you're talking about, and I can't.
I know what you're talking about, but I don't know it well.
It was it was like a pretty epic tiny.
It was like a Tiny Toons mini movie, essentially.
I want to say my guess is Happy World Land.
I think that's what it is.
And it's it's it's the same structure as vacation, where it's this very frustrating trip.
But where he slogs through a terrible time with his friends, family.
And at the end of it, I'm going to get to a theme park and all of this struggle
will be worth it.
But in this case, instead of it being closed, he gets on a monorail,
which I think is is like a set of teeth.
And it takes him around to see everything in the park.
He gets to ride a ride like, and there's that and there's that.
And it's a joke bag of all these crazy, seemingly kind of violent rides.
And then they get off it.
And he's like, wow, a preview of everything I get to do.
And then they tell him, yep, well, that was a lot of fun.
We're just we're going to head back now.
And he doesn't get to go on any of the rides.
And they just went to go on the Toothmobile.
And that's it.
But it captured that.
Yeah, how frustrating is that?
But it really captures a little little syndrome of theme park visiting,
like anything like that.
You know, you know, it's like that is getting to enter Epcot via the monorail.
And it kind of takes you around a bunch of Epcot
and gives you a preview of what you're going to get when you actually land.
Well, there's definitely a bang for the buck, I think,
like like a perceived of like, wow, look, you get you get this and that.
But I think the other thing, too, is if you need like a little
like space mountain fix and it's an hour, 90 minute wait,
we just do a little people mover.
You at least get a little taste.
You know what I mean?
You get the theming, even if you if you're not willing to devote
three hours to get the thrill, you get the theming in five minutes.
And by the way, that ride is called the Tooth Fairy Fairy,
being like the vehicle fairy.
That's very good.
Had that entire episode in Happy World Land are very good.
Yes, I'm looking at the opening for Tiny Tunes here,
and I'm seeing, of course, that the great Frank Marshall produces.
Oh, yes. Tiny Tunes.
So I just want to shout him out.
Friend of the show, Frank Marshall.
I mean, yeah, why not?
You know, we're more likely to get him someday.
If we now we I did, I think, in a second gate episode talk about
I think he knows stuff about the Twilight Zone deaths, but
that's probably a deterrent to getting him.
But maybe he won't hear that or this.
Maybe he won't.
But I assume he will, because I assume he listens to as a friend of the show.
Yeah, he listens to me.
Seed does not subscribe to the Patreon, though, just regular subscriber.
Unless he uses a student.
We don't know who there could be all kinds of people just using fake names.
Yeah, that's a good point.
Maybe his assistant signed up for the Patreon and he listens to
the Patreon through the assistance log in an email.
Yeah, you got to be careful when you're as prominent as Frank Marshall.
Yes, anything is possible.
Can I say something about
bringing Disneyland vibes home with you?
That I mean, for sure, this is a thing that I, you know,
I remember my mom talking about forever ago, like, what if you could have a view?
What if you like in your kitchen, if your little breakfast nook
was a Skyway or a people mover?
But for the purposes of this episode, the Skyway, what a dream.
That dream, of course, lived by Richard Kraft,
who we do. We did the show at his gallery.
That's from Disneyland.
And I didn't realize that at that gallery and auction,
there was a sale of a Skyway bucket
that was the highest price ever recorded for a Disneyland ride vehicle.
Wow, really? Yeah.
That was like the top moneymaker for the auction or just for a ride vehicle.
I oh, I don't know that. I don't know.
It did sell for more than the D that sold to also a friend of the show,
David Copperfield.
He subscribes to the Patreon,
but he uses his real name.
Well, you want to do actually maybe a little mini
souvenir smackdown, the ultimate souvenir smackdown for the highest price.
You guys want to guess what the Skyway bucket went for?
Let me Skyway bucket sold for
the highest price ever of all time for a Disneyland ride.
Three hundred thousand dollars.
Listen.
I'm going to say that might be too high and say fifty thousand.
The correct answer is six hundred twenty one.
Oh, my God. Dollars.
I was under. Oh, my God.
Yep. Yeah.
Which, you know, that has to be somebody,
you know, probably closer to my parents age.
The first clue being that they have money and the second clue.
And they're like, of course, like, like to have that you own a Skyway.
But I don't know. I think it was a latter day sky Skyway.
I don't think it was a fifties one.
I think it was a post 65 when they they made a different shape.
But yeah, six hundred. Six hundred thousand dollars.
They yeah, it was a four seater.
Do we get a picture of that?
Isn't there a or was that a people mover car?
I was looking. I don't.
I I don't think we did in that unless somebody else has it.
OK, we must have gotten in the people mover car.
Yeah. But yeah, we are obviously far too young to ever see the circular buckets,
which also had uncomfortable looking metal chair things.
And you would face a direction compared to the post 65 ones,
which were a lot more lightweight plastic.
And they could expand.
They made it lighter.
And then they were able to expand the seating to four riders.
And you sit two facing front, two facing back.
Oh, oh, wait. So you were just on a bench originally.
You were on these weird like theater seats, kind of like fold down theater seats.
And there wasn't a back there like back of the bucket was sort of the back.
Yeah, I was reading about this and I thought about it like if you were to
actually go on all the rides opening day of Disneyland,
like how uncomfortable would they all be?
Yeah, because that especially like what you're describing
the original seating arrangement, it seems like it would be really cramped
and unpleasant.
But, you know, you weren't used to being on cool rides in a cool place.
So you didn't notice it was so bad.
I just saw a shark tank pitch.
There was kind of a weird product that was about, you know, like a cloth
to put on a swing so your baby doesn't burn him or herself
on the metal of a span.
I forgot about that sensation of being on a hot swing
and how much that would hurt on a playground.
I bet a lot of Disneyland was like a very hot swing all the time.
Oh, yeah. Oh, the other thing,
the original Skyway buckets had a pole in the middle.
Wow. Just a big old.
Like a party bus.
Yeah, I guess.
I that kind of I don't think. Right. Right.
Well, I don't think you're anybody stripping on it.
Those poles and party buses are load bearing.
So you have to be very careful.
Very careful script uses.
I yeah, I was credit to Bob Gerr,
who designed the new ones and and got them to be a little more comfy.
But yeah, that like brutal nature of the old rides.
I mean, Bob Gerr seems so cool.
I mean, it's a listener.
We've talked about him before, and you can see him in the Imagineering
documentary, and he was part of the early utopia especially.
But like for how crazy high tech everything is in the parks now,
it does seem like so much of original Disneyland was, you know, like, well,
it's called Bob.
Like something breaks down and like, I got old Bob out here
and he comes out with a toolbox and bangs it back into shape.
He's like the handyman in your building.
And like a handyman and so many of those early guys
kind of self taught how to do all this stuff.
Oh, yeah, right. Yes.
In the documentary, in the measuring story, I forget about what ride.
But he says, I'm a car guy, not a not a bot guy, not a robot guy.
I forget what that was about.
But yeah, he does.
Fair known of these people knew how to do anything.
Figure out trigonometry, I think, was his task for in the matter.
The big thing in the matter.
Oh, that's what it was.
Yeah. He designed as one of the major steel roller coasters in history,
despite his initial reaction while asked him being, no, I can't do that.
But now I say they don't know anything, but all these people all across the board
didn't know anything.
Figure it out and pioneered a whole industry like cracked codes
that everybody's still basing all their decisions on decades later.
Yeah. Yeah.
My favorite is
like an imagineering panel, and they'll have Tony Baxter and Bob Gurr.
And Tony Baxter is, you know, talking about like imagination and story
and how it places you in the story.
And you're the character, you're the protagonist.
And then Bob Gurr and you ask him about the ride and he goes,
yeah, we wanted to make a fast, fun ride and we did it.
Like I made the ride and I spun it around and it didn't work at first,
but then it worked.
And I guess it's fun.
The total contrast is very fun and amusing.
And honestly, they're both viable like philosophies with a ride.
Like you need both of those brains to do creative work.
Yeah. God bless those people.
I also last night ended up on a video where
I think the video is called two hipsters try to interview Tommy Lee Jones.
And it's like two press junket guys are coming in
and asking all these highfalutin questions about character work.
And is Tommy Lee Jones's answer is just like, no, what are you talking about?
I play a character, I say the lines and I go home.
But would you ever want to like live as one of your characters for a day?
No, they're false. I want to be myself.
Yeah, I kind of like that that brutalism.
Not not everyone should be that way, but it's it's refreshing sometimes.
It is. Yeah. And it's interesting philosophies and everyone's process is different.
It's like the Lawrence Olivier line,
like Dustin Hoffman in Marathon Man had to show up really haggard looking and stuff
and it's seen. So he stayed up all night.
And Lawrence Olivier said, Dusty, have you tried acting?
I got him.
There's a there's a story.
I think it was Don Rickles told a story about he was working on some movie
with two actors, and I don't remember what the actors who they were.
And one of them was definitely like process and character and like
really laboring over it.
And the other one was like, just say the lines and let's go have a drink.
Just say the lines and let's go have a drink.
Like that's the like, who cares?
Let's get this over with.
And I love hearing like philosophical bullshit about people's work.
And I tend to think like that, too.
But, you know, ultimately, you can probably simplify and be like,
just say it with a voice that's loud and I'm going to say it said louder, faster, angrier.
Yeah. Ultimately, I do think a lot of that
process is to, you know, because the actual amount of time anyone spends
acting, unless you're in a play which runs for hours, the actual
process of like acting in front of TV or even doing like what we do,
doing the podcast isn't that long in the span of a week.
So you do have to fill the hours and convince your brain you're working like,
well, this this is good.
This is contributing to the 30 minutes when I do that.
But maybe you don't feel like you have to fill that time and make up that work
if you're 70 years old, an Oscar winner already mad.
Yeah. Maybe you stick to the ships in the bottle you love so much.
We like our we like our our process people and we like our cranks, too.
Yes. Cranks and process people.
Good balance favor of both of those.
Yeah. Yeah.
Skyway stuff.
Oh, yes. Jason, yes.
Well, Scott, I had some questions for you because I'm assuming
you rode the Disneyland Skyway more than Disney World.
Like I have thoughts and stuff a lot on the Disney World one.
But I wanted to ask, like, it feels like the skyway going through the Matterhorn
was one of those things that like, oh, this is probably grandfathered
in because the walls look very close to these buckets.
Oh, yeah, sure.
Um, yeah, I guess it was.
Yeah, it did feel very close.
Yeah, you definitely felt like you could reach out and touch that that rock,
although you shouldn't.
And, you know, there's there's problems with reaching out of the skyway,
which we'll get to, I imagine.
Yeah, even though the skyway opened first and it was open for a year
and then they closed it to build the Matterhorn, which is bizarre.
Yeah, so crazy.
They opened it and then like 18 months later, they're like, all right,
put it on the shelf almost immediately.
And then, yeah, and then they built the Matterhorn where the main support pillars
were for the sky like so that I guess the matter is like in the dead center
of the where the skyway track used to be.
Yeah. Well, there is a big beam on the old holiday hill
where everyone would go to neck the dirt grass mound.
Yeah, Disney really should bring back some sort of a dirt grass mound
so we can all neck so we can do we can do more necking at Disneyland.
Skyway seems like it'd be good for necking, you know?
Yeah, because yeah, yeah, I mean, people will be able to see it, though.
It's not as good as like Haunted Mansion. That's true.
It was you can do it is just that like, you know,
people are going to look up and see people necking.
It was gone by the time I was doing any necking.
I might my neck career had not began in 1994.
Um, now the opposite happened, of course.
And then I know we've talked about this and I don't remember what episode, but
in one of the I want to say before any of the any of the TGIF shows proper
got to Disneyland or Disney World and most of them went to Disney World.
It's actually rare to see a show at Disneyland.
Blossom went to Disneyland.
Oh, I think I talked about it on Great Moments with Mr.
Lincoln because one of the characters talks to Lincoln,
who I think sounds like a Brooklyn guy or something.
I don't know. Am I making that up?
Or is he just like, no, maybe he's still Lincoln, but just like, I'm bolted to the floor.
I don't remember it exactly.
Yeah, yeah, I'm not sure.
But anyway, the the opposite occurs where Blossom and Six are in a Skyway car
and they look down and see Blossom's boyfriend
wait, not not necking, but hugging another woman.
And they get mad and they throw ice
at the boyfriend, but then it turns out to be a sister, I believe.
I think that's the story.
Cousin, I think. Oh, cousin. OK.
But again, I'm sure I said this before.
Sorry. Anyway, keep going.
I it's just so weird that they were willing to show that.
And then in the scene that they say,
like, you remember when we used to get up up here and throw ice at people.
So why would Disney agree to let them film a show or they encourage
throwing ice at people?
Yeah, that's yeah, that is weird.
Really off brand and off brand to let Lincoln talk.
And they might even call him the sky buckets.
I know they get some like facts wrong in that show.
There's definitely some like off brand stuff going on in that episode.
Really weird. It is refreshing because that's back when, you know, you
everything wasn't micromanaged quite as much.
So stuff would sneak through like that.
That doesn't happen in the modern family, like shoots at Disneyland era.
Right. They are big old instruction manuals before they can write a script.
You. Right.
The episode is about being safe on a ride and how good the ride is.
I assume. I assume I haven't seen these episodes.
But I don't know, is there well, so the
seeing the going through the Matterhorn and seeing the snowman in the middle,
that was that was sort of like a good middle beat of your
Skyway passage, no matter which way you were going.
Did you do you guys feel like the Disney World version was lacking at all
because there was not such a landmark in the middle?
Well, I'm going to I'm going to go out and say no, because for much of the time
of the Skyways life in Florida, you had
you had a lot of interesting stuff.
You didn't have a big like kind of set piece moment of going through a mountain,
but you got some amazing view of the twenty thousand leagues lagoon.
And yeah, I that that that looks incredible.
There's a lot of Disney World ride through on the Skyway
on YouTube.
And I think it is because it is one of the few rides that you can
you could in the late 90s pick up your brick of a camcorder
and get the whole ride and get some good footage.
And it's pretty clear because it's very sunny.
So like, but it's I mean, it's as good as standard deaf consumer video could be.
So it's also a little foggy, a little dreamlike.
But the big the big get for me was finding a 96 video
where you can hear like the people mover narration from the Skyway.
And then you go behind the Castle cake.
And yeah, this might have been the height of culture.
This might have been the high point.
The Castle cake in the Skyway, the Casper, right in the Skyway,
looking at the Castle cake, looking at twenty thousand leagues,
seeing the incomplete view of the Castle cake from behind.
See, yes. Now, they they should have followed the Steve Jobs
adage about like you've got to finish the back of the drawer, too.
You got to make the back, the very back of the drawer look good, too.
Especially if, you know, thousands of people are going to pass by the back of the drawer.
Yeah. But I found a lot.
I mean, clearly a lot of people took picture of like
of the Castle cake on the Skyway.
And yeah, I just loved it.
I have a very me story about it.
Oh, do you tell? Go ahead. Go ahead.
Yeah, I don't think I've told this on the show once.
So I think this would have been like ninety nine, like summer
ninety nine, like months before it closed.
When I would go down with my family, I mean, I would go pretty hard,
like sun up, sun down.
And eventually there would be a day where you would just hit a wall.
And we were in Fantasyland pretty early in the day.
And we were going to take the Skyway to Tomorrowland.
And I I had just started drinking occasionally iced coffee.
And I was like, I am I am not going to make it through this.
I need a little boost.
And so got out of the line and ran to the restaurant
right next to it to get an iced coffee.
But that took way too long.
So then I had to get back in line and weave through the line
with with a tiny cup of iced coffee.
And you have to think it's nineteen ninety nine.
So theme park iced coffee is probably mostly corn syrup.
And they did not think about lids and straws apparently back then.
So I am trying to find my family and guzzle this coffee
before I get on the Skyway, because it doesn't have a lid.
And they were I got there just in time.
It was like the the the Mark Twain Sunday
decades before decades later.
I relived the experience trying to get a Sunday before the Golden Horseshoe closed.
And I did it and I was probably just vibrating for hours after that.
Well, that's your idea. That's another one of your Ethan Hunt moments.
Yes, that's right.
He's a pursuit of treats and slow moving rides.
They should counteract each other, but you find a way to make them work.
That's right. I turned the Skyway into a thrill ride.
You were trying like when you were trying to finish
a whole birthday sheet cake and get on living with the land in 10 minutes flat.
Yeah, no one wanted any I offered.
Running through up,
got eating a sheet cake to get on living with the land before close
and one handed too, because I got to hold the sheet cake with the other hand.
So, yeah, of course.
But you did it. You made it.
I did it. Yeah.
I was about to I was about to home the Mission Impossible theme
and it was about to come out as the James Bond theme.
No, no, we went through this.
I know. I know. I can feel I'm confused.
Skyfall fallout.
You know, to mix up the metaphors more, I mean, I find all of this
to be like Indiana Jones barely escaping, but, you know,
reached through to grab his hat.
For sure. Yeah.
You know what Florida did have?
This is the real set piece was the turnabout station.
Hmm. Do tell.
Oh, well, much like the Skyliner has a point
where there is a station you do not get off at,
it is just purely mechanical for the path to curve.
So you can watch in the videos you had to.
There was a certain point where it's not it wasn't a straight line to Tomorrowland.
It had to curve slightly at one point.
So they had to readjust the cable.
So so you were when you were a child, you were excited about the turnabout station.
Well, it was just sort of like, well, look at this weird thing.
Look, look how strange there's a cast member waving at you.
Anyway, you can't get off here. Don't try to get up.
Oh, they would position a person.
There would usually be a person there.
Yeah. Keeping an eye on stuff.
I know what you mean, because it's so functional and unfriendly,
but they make it friendly with a little Wal-Mart greeter person.
I guess I would have felt the same way.
This is so like coldly mechanical to be in a theme park ride.
Yeah. I don't I I really have
very few memories of the Disney World one, the other than just like I see pictures
and I'm reminded of it because I think I went on it once when I was very little.
Maybe my first trip and then never again.
I think I went on it once.
And even when I was older and we went, I did not want to go on it.
So I have I have my memories of it
and from Disney World are just like one picture of me in it.
And I think I look a little distressed.
I'll ask my mom if she can find this picture.
Oh, you got it. Yes.
As much as your childhood content as we can get.
I hope it's as good. Yeah, I hope it's as good as I'm building it up.
There's also a possibility I went on one version of this at Six Flags Great America.
Yes. Hmm.
Well, let me see if that's in my chart.
I think it might be.
We OK.
We know California is great.
America is a different thing.
It might be closed, whatever you're talking about.
I think whatever I'm talking about is closed.
But so, yeah, so there's got to be something like that.
I always liked I always liked seeing it.
But I think it even stressed me out walking under it
because I was like, they're going to they're going to drop.
These are going to drop people like it's going to fall because look at that.
It's so thin. The cord is so thin.
The cable is thin.
It does. Yeah, it does feel weird.
It still is odd looking at it in anything like this.
The mechanics shouldn't make sense.
But obviously, there are not constant accidents on on Skyways,
on these Von Roll attractions or on on on ski resort chairlifts.
Well, this is once in a while, but mostly not.
This was one that Disney was the trend setter on,
because once they put this in Disneyland following that,
then they they've installed like hundreds of these in amusement parks
throughout the country.
And some of them, a lot of them gone, a lot of them gone because of,
you know, at the time, it was a very affordable way to get the the
oh, look, they have this at Disneyland and we have it, too.
But there's a lot of concerns about safety,
although not too many incidents at Disney.
That said, these the other thing is these things can get a little expensive to operate.
Yeah. I mean, just in my count of just the company
Von Roll that built the Disney one,
only that company alone, they there's they have built
30 that have since closed.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
And there's a list.
I was reading a list of ones that they have.
They're still open. And that looks like I don't want to count again.
But, you know, maybe like 12 to 14.
So I'd so two thirds of these that were ever open
across the world are now closed. Wow.
The one that I think of in this not it's a little different, obviously.
It's much more shaped like a ski lift kind of thing is
Santa Cruz, the Santa Cruz boardwalk still has
a cable thing, but it's much more like a bench with a lap bar
that goes on down the boardwalk that looks like this.
Santa Cruz boardwalk, which I've been told multiple times.
There's stuff worth talking about. There's dark rides there.
I don't remember the details now, but we got to hit that at some point.
Yeah, I want to go there.
It's it's just it's it's that distance where it's like,
ah, a pain in the ass to get to in California.
Little bit anything over like any further than Vegas feels like a big commitment.
Yes. Yes. Yeah.
I was going to say, I do think probably I think in the Skyliner type,
the enclosed gondola, I think is very in vogue right now.
I think that's sort of the new version of this.
And I think that like Disney was looking at ways with Disney World
to increase mobility and do it not with some expensive thing.
And I think that it seems like
that's the enclosed version of this now is maybe going to be something
that other places look at. Universal, I think there's a rumor that
they were talking about a version of this for Orlando.
Jason, am I correct?
Well, yeah, I heard that rumor.
Some sort of unconventional
or like forward thinking transit system.
I think the only thing with something like this, like you hear them called
like urban gondolas, is to get from like the main universal campus
to the epic universe plot of land.
You would have to send it over I for sure.
So a little complicated once you start getting into crossing highways.
Oh, yeah. And is the city really going to be fine with them
like sending a gondola everywhere?
Yeah, I mean, they got all sorts of transits
because they're building these high speed rails, this Virgin rails in
Florida, where like, oh, there's going to be a stop
in front of the convention center, so effectively by Epic Universe.
And then there's talk about a stop at Disney World somewhere
and the airport.
So we'll see what happens in Orlando.
That's one thing with these is that, I mean, the Skyway, like the people
mover, is one of those in the monorail is one of those waltz attempts at,
you know, displaying a potentially
future forward thinking way of transporting, especially in a in a city.
It's like a it was like a backdoor pilot for efficient
travel in the actual world.
Yeah. The sort of an ulterior motive he had is trying to improve movement.
The city plan and the transportation planning,
because I was looking at that that really nice Tashin Disneyland book.
Yeah. To see if they said anything about the Skyway.
And there was this one little this this place that I'd never heard of
that they name check. They basically say that
the Skyway came out of all its fascination with ski lifts.
And he was interested in ski lifts because he was associated
with a place called the Sugar Bowl Ski Resort in Lake Tahoe.
Have you guys ever heard of this in Disney lore?
No, I feel like it comes up in relation to like Mineral King.
Yes, which I've never actually sat down and figured out what all that is about.
And his association with I don't know.
I know these phrases and a Squaw Valley and some Olympics thing.
And I don't really know the deal with any of that.
I just I know I've heard Mineral.
I know the Mineral King.
I mean, essentially a very nice ski resort, but also there'd be country bears.
There'd be shows.
So that's another one for our docket that that and Ford's Magic Skyway.
It sounds like heaven on earth.
My God. So, yes, secluded resort where you hang out with them.
Was this somewhere and was this in our fandom somewhere on a Facebook group
or something, but I didn't realize that
there was like a little mini country bear show at Fort Wilderness
in Disney World. Does this sound familiar to you, Mike?
That doesn't sound familiar.
I don't I didn't see that, at least on our face.
I'm not always checking our Facebook page, but sometimes.
But I don't think that's where that was.
Was that in like defunct land world or something?
I got I don't know.
Yeah, I think there was some mini country.
Oh, no, wait, I'm sorry.
It was a show with either the buffalo or the moose.
It was like there was one of those characters in the hotel.
They would do. Yeah, yeah.
I again, don't let me.
It was these things before I talk about them.
OK. Uh huh.
Melvin the Moose, it was the resort.
It was for breakfast. It was like a breakfast show.
Breakfast show like character was a character breakfast.
But I think he was also just on the wall there.
Yeah, here's a picture of it. Oh, it's a great photo
that makes it look like it's from 1960.
But of course, it was not.
But here I'm sending that to you guys now.
Oh, this is Wilderness Lodge or the maybe that's what I mean.
Fort Wilderness. This is Fort Wilderness.
Oh, OK. Oh, yeah, I do see that.
I mean, it's interesting.
Those early like lodging places all kind of had their own
little cultural stuff.
The Polynesians has hung along the longest.
But like contemporary used to have like Broadway cabaret ship.
Like people would fly down and do like shows and stuff.
It's like a dinner theater kind of thing.
And Helen Reddy,
yeah, like Tommy Toon doing a show up there.
And just all the chickens soaking in heavy cream you could want.
Gel gelatin gelatin laced goose.
Yes. Domestic wine that tastes like just awful.
It tastes like paint thinner gelatin goose.
Lemon wine.
70s food.
That's a whole episode, too.
We should just like look at a lot of menus from Disney places and like 71.
That's not a bad episode in general.
Yeah. Gel gelatin everywhere.
Yeah. I don't know why.
Next to like cottage cheese.
Do you feel like 70s?
Yeah. He's at a Jello and cottage cheese everywhere.
Yes. Cottage cheese for sure.
We we had a cottage cheese in the house, like I think all the time as a child.
I almost bought it.
Really? Well, I almost bought the like the yogurt version where the other
like a few weeks ago where you dump the like fruit, the fruit goo
into it, you know. Oh, interesting.
We would have we would definitely my mom would make us cottage cheese and yogurt.
Oh, that was what we would have.
It's funny you say that because obviously that and I haven't said that phrase out
loud in 20 years, but that is what yeah.
She would just give us a bowl of cottage cheese and yogurt.
You know, I double dairy.
That does remind me I was not a peanut butter and jelly kid,
but at my house, we liked cream cheese and jelly sandwiches.
Yes. Which is not.
I mean, that was just fast track to be in a chubby child.
I'll tell you what, a lot less nutrients than peanut butter.
A real fast.
Nothing helpful for you in that.
Nothing. A real fast pass, a fast pass to chubbiness.
Fast pass to be in a chubby child.
Isn't that looking back how?
Because I don't think you were genetically so.
Well, I don't know. I don't know what you were like at three or four.
But like and you're not now.
And so that you so when you were, it was because of your parents.
So if you were getting made fun of at school, it's like not you're doing in the least.
Yes. Well, I was a kid who was like, I'm not really big on fruit,
but I love potato chips, like just a recipe for disaster.
I mean, that's been me during the quarantine.
Well, that's true.
Yeah. But I mean, I've I've I like I've trimmed all of that down.
It's like, look, if you still want to go hog on cookies and ice cream, which I do,
I cut back all the other stuff.
I drink soda like so little.
Like that was a big one.
I I stopped drinking soda one summer in high school and I dropped like ten pounds immediately.
Yeah, I would have I mean, I like this would be a lunch.
I would have a liver sausage sandwich,
a package of Lay's potato chips,
like a carton of like two percent milk.
That was like kind of gross because like pieces of the carton
would have fallen off a little bit into the milk.
So you'd have to use a straw, like hopefully not get pieces of the carton.
And then two Swiss cake rolls like a package of two Swiss cake rolls.
Yeah. Swiss cake.
I mean, that was dessert after your healthy lunch of white bread sandwiches and chips.
White bread, liver sausage, chips,
disgusting milk and then a chocolate dessert.
We I imagine I think all of us, every child between,
you know, probably before.
Let's let's go. But every child between like nineteen seventy two and two
thousand three, I think just reeked.
Is there just the gaseous, shittiest, like every element,
every auditorium or cafeteria must have just been like,
there was a kid who sat next to me and I think third grade
and he smelled like baloney all day.
And I don't know if that was just because he would have his lunch.
That was, I think, baloney every day.
But I was like, it's just the baloney smell so strong.
And I would eat baloney, too.
That would be in the rotation as well.
A baloney sandwich, a liver sausage sandwich, peanut butter.
And then once in a while, a turkey sandwich.
But this kid was baloney smell 24 7.
Towards the end of high school, I think everyone started carrying bottled
water more or would get like opt for the bottle of water at lunch instead of milk.
And I just remember going like, well,
a lot more homework and getting into college is depressing.
But I think I was dehydrated from K to 10th grade.
I think I would just end the day totally logy and dehydrated
from not having besides a sip of water at water fountains.
Yes. And the water fountains were all gross as shit, like just like lukewarm.
And like you smelled the metal when you were getting up close to take a drink.
And like, yeah, you would barely have any of it.
You might have a little after gym. Yeah.
But you weren't having like a glass of water.
You were just probably having like a lunch, a lunch milk.
And that was it.
The years you just described, Jason, this is a breakthrough because all those years
I feel the same way. And I had just a beet red face all of that time.
So much so that I thought I genuinely had the condition rosacea,
which I don't have today.
And I think it might be because I drink water. Yes.
Water is gross for the older generation, I think, still a section of it.
It's funny. I know this is correct.
I know I'm doing the right thing, but having a very young baby right now,
I'm like, you don't give them water.
So does it seem right?
It's like they need water, right?
But I mean, I know that's not how babies work.
It's just weird. Yeah. Yeah.
You know, it's all it's funny how like this isn't like 300 years
we're talking like 300 years ago.
It was what? Ten, 20.
And I know not long ago at all.
Well, it just goes to show that stuff can be, you know, stuff
that you think is true now can be overturned very quickly,
which is why I'm not vaccinating this child whatsoever.
Well, I don't know.
I don't know. This is a time to go around bragging about.
Well, we've watched everyone freak out about the sham disease
that's locked us, prisoned us in our homes for so long.
Why would I vaccinate this boy?
Huh? Well, we're going to do an episode where we explore that on the Patreon.
And we'll get to that later.
Well, the sky the sky boys also get into blue skying
a better world where we have more freedoms.
The sky sky sky trails.
Did you say sky boy?
Did you say sky boys?
Oh, wait, what are we talking about? Sky guys?
Guys. Yeah. Yeah.
That's your son is the sky boy.
Hey, look at the sky boy over there.
That's how he gets to Neverland.
No, no, no. He cannot fly.
You have that.
I will teach him the song.
You cannot fly. You cannot fly. You cannot fly.
No pan.
OK, wait, but let's go back into the sky.
Let's go in the sky into a ski lift, a ski lift at the Sugar Bowl ski resort
in Lake Tahoe.
There's one of the strangest avenues of Walt's dry fact I've ever heard,
but it's I found it to be such a strange rabbit hole.
So Walt's in the 30s took a trip to Yosemite.
There was a guy who is a ski instructor who is just a world class,
like one of the great skiers in the world, apparently named Hannes Schroll.
And he was not only a major skier, he was a major yodeler.
And he would do his jumps while yodeling,
just so you'd be doing you'd be doing your ski thing.
And then you just hear this yodel booming across the mountain.
And it's this guy. He's kind of crazy, sort of a kook,
you know, an Austrian guy and proud of it and, you know,
just kind of like spirited weird guy who, you know, helped since, you know,
helped to walk, get more interested in skiing.
And they met, really got along, stayed in contact.
And then this guy wanted to build a ski resort, started building a ski resort
in Lake Tahoe. And as he did so,
Austria got annexed by Hitler and all his money got locked up.
So he didn't have the money he needed to finish his resort.
He reached out to people he knew with a lot of money, such as Walt Bisney,
who paid him the vast fortune of twenty five hundred dollars,
which apparently went a long way in the 30s and helped this guy
finish this resort.
So indebted was this person to Walt
that he renamed what used to be one of the two mountains
that were part of this property.
It was called Hemlock Peak, and he renamed it Mount Disney.
Well, I had no idea about this in Lake Tahoe.
In our state, there is a Mount Disney.
Wow. I didn't know either.
Yeah, never heard any of this.
Clearly now something we have to do before the podcast is over is go ski Mount
Disney. Yeah, really?
But so one of the strange things about it was some of the Walt funds
went to building a chairlift, which was the open in 1939
and was the first chairlift installed in California was up and down Mount Disney.
And when Walt went to check it out, he was so fascinated by it
and the mechanics of it and was like, we should have something like this in the parks.
Wow. That's interesting.
Yeah, all a weird, interesting run in with this guy.
But it it doesn't quite stop there because there's one there's one more little thing
right around this time because of his interaction with Hannes.
Walt is Walt loves skiing and he starts to make a cartoon about skiing,
a cartoon starring Goofy, the art of skiing,
which was the first of the goofy instructional cartoons.
And he thought a cool thing for this might be to have a bunch of yodeling
strung through the short.
So he contacted Hannes and said, would you like to do some yodeling?
It just is kind of the score for this thing.
And he did. And if you listen, if you watch that that short, which is on Disney Plus,
it's this this guy, the guy who built this chairlift and established Mount Disney.
And not only that, while he was in the V.O.
booth, because this guy did all these crazy yells and yodels while he skied,
he said, you want to try some other stuff?
And he did. And he made the sound.
Yahoo, the goofy holler.
It was the goofy holler was not done by the voice of Goofy Pinto
Colvin was done by this this yodeler skier guy. Wow.
And that sound is in all of the goofy cartoons.
And now it's like something you expect out of Goofy.
But it was done by this guy and it was done for zero dollars.
Walt tricked him. Oh, Walt.
Yeah. The like the iconic goofy sound was done for free.
Wow. Yes, that's anytime Goofy gets hurt.
You want to hear that yell?
Yes. And now in the current voice, Bill Farmer learned how to do it.
He like that's like part of the repertoire and he can demonstrate how to do it.
And he talks in interviews about how it was this guy who who cracked it.
Wow. Yeah, interesting.
All of that, all of Walt's like interests, it all spreads out
through the whole history of the company.
Like he loves like nothing is random.
They all like fine.
He found a way to incorporate all of his interests somewhere. Right.
Although, when people would probably just white knuckling it,
when Walt would go on vacation, they're like, oh, God, what's he going to come back with now?
What's what sort of whirly bird gizmo is he going to be like?
Build me one of these five stories tall.
Yeah, that is true.
I think that is in that what he was about the Matterhorn or something
where he was like, build me one of these boys.
The Matterhorn, the petrified tree will buy that.
He was just like, buy it, send it to Disneyland.
Just anywhere he would go.
Yeah. Yeah.
What would be the biggest problem to figure out?
I mean, if I guess if he, you know, anything dangerous,
if he saw like sword swallowers or something.
Yeah. Figure out how to figure out how to inject swords into the guest's mouths.
Yeah. Or like he went to the Grand Canyon and was like,
dig a big hole in Disneyland to get rid of it all.
I want a big hole. I want a big hole.
Yeah, it's probably less dangerous, more just frustrating stuff.
Like I want the streets of New Orleans in this park.
And it's like, oh, man.
Like, what? All right.
Just make them little fine.
Yeah, make them smaller.
But he said they had to be like full size and they have to be the exact same size
as the streets he went.
Yeah, but just build it this way.
And maybe he won't notice.
He'll forget about it.
We have to build northern lights here and they can't be done with lamps.
Walt says we need to harness real sky power.
Disneyland needs its own sun.
We don't even know what he means by that.
He wants his own functioning sun and he wants that.
He wants to control the tides somehow.
Does it have to block the regular sun or can it work in conjunction with it?
No, he wants he wants he wants two sons, the real one and a fake one.
Does it go opposite the regular sun?
He didn't say he didn't say he just said he just said he wanted one and left.
I'm afraid we're going to start doing it and then it'll be the opposite of what he wants.
And he asked if I was wanting to join a union.
And I said, of course, no.
And then he left good. And then he left.
He just walked out.
And I don't even know anything about mechanics.
I'm his paperboy.
I got to build a I got to build an artificial heat source in the sky.
He did, though, that paperboy.
And that paperboy's name was Bob Gurr.
That's right. And you overlook that.
Disneyland's second son for the first four months of operation,
which which crashed to the ground and crushed the original castle
that the variable from scratch. Right.
Yeah, that's a little that little known fact about it.
Don't believe any of those weird Facebook posts you see about the
grandchildren of the people who were crushed.
They're all liars and truthers.
Yeah, I'd never have no one died.
What are they talking about? Yeah, that's yeah.
Don't Facebook is a cesspool.
Obviously, yes.
For that reason and that reason alone, Disneyland rumors.
I don't know anything else about anything else.
I don't know what's going on.
But I know the Disneyland rumors and memes are out of control.
Except our Facebook group, which is nice and good.
And you should it is and go join it.
And they'll save me a plug for the end of the show.
Speaking of
danger at Disneyland,
the this attraction ultimately closed in 1994.
And it's a little muddy why it did,
because and I you'll definitely listen to people who say,
well, somebody fell out of the thing into a tree.
And so they had to close it.
You will maybe even hear people say somebody fell out of it and died.
And thus they had to close it.
And I imagine we all looked into this a little bit.
Yeah. And found what hopefully is the the truth behind it,
which is certainly that nobody died.
OK, well, someone did die.
What? No, not at all.
I'm sorry. Well, not the what is in 94.
Nobody died. Not 94.
No, not 94. It was far more boring.
No, I'd explain.
No, sorry. The reason they closed it, it seemed like it seemed like money stuff.
It seemed like they got on a trend, especially,
well, I guess more in Florida, where when a new thing would open,
they would close an old thing.
Yeah, which in this case, in Disneyland,
it seemed to be an Indiana Jones adventure
based closure. And it's not like it was one to one.
It's not like all the Skyway employees went over to Indiana Jones.
It's just kind of, well, if we're going to increase cost over here,
we have to cut costs somewhere else.
Right. They were talking about maybe even like changing it
and increasing the amount of people that could be on one car.
Oh, really? Like sick.
They were going to see if they could do six.
Well, but I think ultimately they just were like,
low hourly capacity and expensive to run.
Mm hmm. OK. Factors. Sure.
And it does. I mean, like the incident you're talking about,
somebody slipped out of it.
And some people like they think it was on purpose.
Well, if maybe the the the falling wasn't on purpose,
unless he was just like fishing for a lawsuit or something.
But when the when the lawsuit happened, it seemed like an accident.
It seemed like maybe he leaned against the door and fell out of the door.
But what counteracts that is that the handle on the outside is such
that you'd have to reach around and grab it and unlock it
and fiddle with it before it to open at all.
Like you could not open it from the inside.
And then I think there was actually video from a guest of him
fiddling with the handle, too.
So for sure, he reached outside and did it to himself.
Right. So I would assume like all these factors maybe add up to like,
you know, maybe the ride isn't like so secure.
Yeah. Like and in addition to what its low capacity and money and blah, blah, blah.
They're like, yeah, maybe not worth it.
Not worth it. I found a good little quote, though.
I was just talking about Austria.
And here's a quote from a German tourist, Burget Klein.
I forget what article I found this in, but maybe in the L.A.
Times about about the accident.
And just somebody ran him at Disneyland.
They were talking to like, are you upset about this this accident?
Does it make you worried about going on any of these rides?
And she said, well, while the man's fall was unfortunate,
well, actually, sorry, the article says while the man's fall was unfortunate,
it would not have dampened her frolicking.
Nothing too terrible can happen on such a wonderful day, said Klein,
slurping on a strawberry ice cream in the parking lot.
Delightful. I imagine she skipped away.
Gladden leads it later, Hosen.
Nothing can dampen my fro.
What was it? Dampen my frolicking?
Yeah, I can't honestly say this was her quote.
I wish it was like nothing could dampen my frolicking.
Jason, if you could say that from now on.
Oh, nothing will dampen my frolicking.
Yeah. If that could just be sort of in your repertoire of phrases.
Yeah, got it. We'll do.
All right. Great lodged in there.
Surprised us with it when we at least expect.
What what I came across for the closure,
it seems like, you know, a lot of people talk about the ADA issues.
But because it was so old, it was grandfathered in.
So that was like not the front at the front of their minds.
The other excuse was stress fractures
inside the Matterhorn supports and metal fatigue at various spots.
Well, people kind of sounds like bullshit.
Well, but also, though, I've read that the Matterhorn is kind of falling apart.
I mean, there was a piece not long ago that just fell down.
Yes. On the track.
So from what I've read and understand,
and you know, it's probably from some message board,
Mice Town dot net.
I don't remember which one it is
that I think the Matterhorn will have to be torn down within the next like 25 years.
Like it's decaying.
So they'll have to rebuild it or put something else there.
Oh, my God. So I don't know.
I don't know if this is 100 percent true, but it does seem like the building
might be falling apart anyway, so there might be some truth to that as well.
Oh, this is that's pretty crazy.
Do you think it's do you think they can take it down in an implosion
kind of way? Because I love implosions when they blow up,
you know, Vegas casinos to build new ones.
But maybe it's not maybe it's built in such too weird of a way to do that.
I wonder. Yeah, I don't know if that's the way to do it.
I feel like stuff is pretty close to it
that you might not want to chance something flying and hitting something else,
but maybe a tiny implosion.
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know if there's a size you have to have for an implosion.
But it would be I also think like with buildings sometimes,
I don't know, like a building is,
you know, structured in a certain way and maybe like a symmetrical way
that leads to a very organized implosion.
Oh, that's a good point.
Yes, because all the floors are identical and there's probably a center
and elevator banks and the matterhorns very like chaotic and fake natural.
So I could be wrong, but I feel like we're not going to get a crazy matterhorn
implosion in the next 25 years.
I think it'll have to be like taken apart in a much slower manner,
though that would be fun.
It would be fun if they sort of made
like a phantasmag show or one of the firework performances
culminate in the matterhorn blowing up.
Yeah, yes, yes.
An AP event to go watch the matterhorn blow up.
Oh, and here. Oh, oh.
And like the like this like the sword in the stone,
you have a bunch of kids go up to like a TNT box.
And like maybe they don't like it doesn't push down for every kid,
but then one special kid pushes down on the TNT box and it blows up the matterhorn.
Oh, yes, yes.
Like the knots, those knots TNT boxes over at their their.
I can't think of the name of it.
The rapids ride, the river rapids.
Yeah, Calico River, Calico River Rapids.
And if they I don't want to endanger anybody,
but if they could do one last Tinkerbell flight
from there within like five minutes of the blow up.
So it's so it seems like Tinkerbell escaping.
Oh, it should be like Mission Impossible.
The first one when Ethan is puts the gum on the helicopter
and blows it up and he like shoots off of the helicopter
from the explosion and lands on the train. Yeah.
It should be like something like that.
Yeah. And I almost don't, you know, look, I as I've established,
I'm not the biggest Peter Pan fan, so I don't even know if I want to give
such a cool moment to Tinkerbell.
I kind of want this to be Mickey Mouse.
I want to be the man himself.
Red light, green light.
So OK, so Mickey is going to fly on a wire now.
Does he have a jetpack?
Does he have like a jetpack or something?
Because you have to Tinkerbell can fly, so that's why she flies.
Space Mickey, Space Man Mickey, the silver suit with the fishbowl.
Yes, yes. Bring that back. Absolutely.
OK, that's good.
I mean, I guess he could.
You know what? I guess he also he could still be space.
Mickey, I guess he could just scale the Matterhorn.
And then the wire is him flying away as it blows up.
Yeah, it's just Mickey is just becoming Dr. Oppenheimer.
I've become death destroyer of worlds.
Just watching it from a distance.
I built this. I can destroy it.
I like create life. I take it away.
I would be I'm a little concerned because I watched a document,
a short documentary on YouTube recently about one of the last standing
casinos invade like old, old casinos that they blew up maybe three years ago.
And it had multiple towers and the older tower they found asbestos in.
And they're like, OK, we can't blow that one up tonight.
We ought to just do the one and then we'll do that one another time.
Unfortunately, the tower they did blew up hit the asbestos tower
and released asbestos into the air.
Oh, no. Do you know what show Tellus was?
Oh, God, I forget. Let me I'll try and find it.
Oh, man. That's I think we've talked about this.
Can we do an episode about Vegas implosions?
This has been an obsession of mine for so long.
And the fact that they as I'm sure I've said before, one of the great
Jason, you said the peak of culture was seeing the castle cake from the skyway.
Yeah. And well, right around the same time was when the Treasure Island
pilot pirates blew up whatever hotel was on.
What is the now the Bellagio spot, which was I we discovered also
in a made for TV movie starring Steve Wynn or where he acts.
I and then another one of these implosions is in Mars attacks.
I mean, like when they use the implosions in other things
and the news would do a full like two hours on it,
just the greatest television ever.
Emmys every year should still be given to 90s Vegas implosion coverage.
Yeah, I mean, I have not actually had that as much of an active thought,
but I know exactly what you're saying.
But I haven't like it wasn't in the forefront of my mind.
But as you're saying that, yes, I do have a lot of affection
for all this, these implosions.
It's so great.
And we're obviously also terrified by buildings exploding.
I mean, what could be scarier than that sort of do it on purpose
to wrangle it ourselves and have no one get hurt
except for when asbestos was released into the Vegas area.
It was the Riviera.
It was the Riviera a few years ago.
Wait, what? This wasn't in the 90s.
This is the recent blow up of the Riviera.
That was just there.
I was I was in that not long ago.
I think it was 2016, 20.
This was uploaded in like 2060.
It's a local news like documentary.
Wow. Oh, my God.
That's so stupid.
I was I was sure this was these were heathens
who didn't know better in 83, not did just happened.
I didn't I didn't know when I went to Vegas.
I was like, what is that white building?
And I'm like, the Tropicana is still standing like the like that.
I feel like is one of the handful of ones left.
And there's a Tropicana in Atlantic City, but a totally different
like logo and aesthetics.
So I they might be owned by the same people, but you never know.
Feels feels very old.
Yeah, that you feel the 60s in that building. Yeah.
Wow. OK, well, that's a feature one.
I'd love to do that. Were we on some other point?
We're talking about taking it down.
Oh, wait, sorry, Jason, somebody not to dwell on it,
but somebody died in the in Disney World.
Yeah. So I mean, the Disney World closure happened in 99,
like five years after Disneyland.
And it seemed like a pretty similar sort of,
you know, we're building new stuff.
So we're going to close old stuff.
And there was it was like a cast member either fell or was knocked off
the like loading area
in Fantasyland, I believe.
So that did happen.
But otherwise, these operated for decades, seemingly without incident.
It seemed like it was a workplace
death in Florida, but it was really just kind of like the
in a string of stuff being torn down at the Magic Kingdom in Florida
between Mr. Toads and 20,000 Leeds and the Skyway.
And most of it just cost cutting, like less concerns about safety,
more concerns about cost cutting.
And they're like, well, we're closing this,
but we're going to open something real soon, something new.
And Yesterland noted that, however, no new attraction
came to the Magic Kingdom Park until May 23rd, 2001,
when the Magic Carpets of Aladdin opened in Adventureland,
which is such a fuck you.
Can you can we how can we describe the Magic Carpets?
Well, it's like it's like Dumbo, but Magic Carpets like worst Dumbo.
Yeah. Yeah.
Just like tossed in there, barely themed in a bad way of barely themes,
not like the Skyway.
Or Dumbo, I mean, Dumbo is like, like, I guess, well, Dumbo is
a little bit a little bit of design work there.
Yeah. Yeah.
And we went on Dumbo not long ago, and I was like, I'm going to fall out of this.
I am sliding to the side.
I am going to fall out.
Oh, yeah, you do lean. Yeah.
And if you go all the way down, it feels like you could just tumble real easy.
And especially if you're an adult man.
Like I'm all my center of gravity is a little higher here.
Yeah, we just feel like an SUV tipping over.
Yeah, right. I'm like an SUV.
I can tip over at any moment. I'm so tall.
I yeah. Well, in terms of in terms of accidents, which were, you know,
there were there weren't a lot until the 90s.
It was more just high jinx, much like Blossom.
I think there was a lot of spitting.
I think I said in the Matterhorn episode, my my now father-in-law,
when he was younger, threw a smoke bomb into the Matterhorn,
which is a thing that would put him in jail for years for terrorism.
Yes. He'd be on the list.
In this case, he just did it without incident and was really, really satisfied
with himself, but then got to the station and there was just a very stern
security guard waiting for him, knew exactly who it was.
In the book More Mouse Tales by David Koenig, I saw a story about
what was that? I think a guy I think I think a kid spit down from the Matterhorn
or, you know, just from the skyway somewhere,
landed on a pretty like buff guy who then just ran to the station
and just waited right there for the kid to show up.
And as soon as he walked out, like just went in to beat him up.
Security had to break it up.
Luckily, this kid did not get not get brutalized.
Gosh, it's so funny because like, I was so scared to do anything like that
in real life, let alone in like the happiest place on Earth.
I couldn't even imagine.
Yeah, yes, truly.
An extra level of fear I would have of like,
and then the people at the park theme park will be mad at me.
Yeah, because you can't end up on some list that doesn't let you come into Disney.
No, it felt like you were in like heaven and God was watching you
if you were in Disneyland, like you're right here.
How is he? Mickey will see me.
My God, Mickey, I make life, I can take it away.
You just have to go to Disney Confession.
Oh, yeah, which I guess is this podcast.
We're doing here.
I'm confessing our sins.
One of the one of the more notable rabble
rousers in Skyway history was future president Barack Obama.
And we talked about this before.
I feel like we have.
But does this ring a bell, the the Obama Skyway incident?
No, no, have we not?
Oh, my God, I don't think so.
So he did some event in Anaheim a couple of years ago,
and he said he's been here before because he went to Disneyland in the 80s
when he was attending Occidental College in Eagle Rock, California.
So which so what the story was that he
I mean, it was I think was just that he smoked.
He just smoked on the skyway.
That was possible.
And, you know, what you just described, Mike, your fear story did not come true.
He just like got back to the station, much like my father in law.
There was a guy waiting for him, said, Sir, come with me.
He and his group were escorted straight out of the park.
But they did on the way out say, come back any time you want.
Oh, I do. Yes. OK. Yeah.
Yeah, this does seem familiar.
I forget if we if we've talked about it before.
But one thing that I like a lot about this
is that he declares, you know,
and I guess what is sort of like a attempt and a posture to be cool,
but one that works on me because of what he's talking about.
He's he's make sure to say he was not in Disneyland for rides or kid stuff.
He was there to see cool in the game.
Which I think that's very cool.
And I started thinking about this like, I wonder, could you place the exact
date that this was when he saw cool in the gang?
And I attempted to do this.
He went to Occidental from 79 to 81.
And I looked up cool.
Cooling the gang played Disneyland a number of times in that era.
But it was mostly grad nights.
And to go to grad night, you have to be a high schooler.
And if Obama was in college, the only way he would have gotten into that
is if he was dating a high schooler.
So I became concerned that Obama was dating a high schooler at the time.
Luckily, he overturned this theory.
I don't want to put that out there.
I'm not accusing him of that because I found out about another event
called Saturday Nights in the Park.
There was a thing called Saturday Night Pop on June 6th, 1981,
with performances from Cool in the Gang and one of my favorite bands
of that era, Shallowmore.
We talk a lot about if you could time travel and go to Disneyland
at a particular time, this is my version of that.
I want to go to June 6th, 1981, go to Disneyland, see Cool in the Gang
and Shallowmore, smoke a cigarette with Barack Obama
and get kicked out of the park.
Yeah. Wow.
I don't know. I mean, they probably had no smoking signs at the Skyway stations.
But in the 1980s, especially the early 80s,
you were still smoking at offices, cars, restaurants.
Everyone was smoking everywhere, you know, doesn't seem that.
Yeah, it is.
It could be for I don't know how much of a troublemaker he's trying to be.
Now, he doesn't clarify what he was smoking.
I mean, maybe he does.
He might. He might.
I think there might be a laugh from the audience and he's like cigarettes.
Talking about cigarettes.
So I don't think it was a joint.
But anyway, still, as cool as all that is,
you know, it still was him breaking a rule.
It was showing that he was like a little bit of a of an anarchist
at the time.
And I don't know, I'm a little offended by this incident.
And you know what? I'm going to start referring to it as Obamagate.
Oh, you know what?
You're right. I don't like him breaking the rules at Disneyland.
So I will also use that phrase that I've never heard before
to refer to this incident.
Yeah, yeah.
And I think we should tweet about it, get the word out.
And not all because it was bad.
I just I want to spread the word about Shalimar,
because I think Shalimar is cool.
So in order to do that, I'm going to start tweeting a lot about
hashtag Obamagate.
I think that's good.
I don't know.
Encourage the listeners also to do that.
Yeah, yeah.
So instead of our regular plugs, don't don't I mean, go to Twitter,
but then just, you know, whatever you want to tweet, but also hashtag Obamagate.
Yeah, I support that.
Great. We got a good plan going forward.
Yeah, great plan.
Um, anyways,
what else we got? Any any further thoughts about?
You know, I this is a very simple, simplistic thought that I have.
And it's really the last thing I'll say about this.
The Skyway, that's the last thought I had about the Skyway is that
there is something there's a fun game that I always, especially as a kid, would play.
And we've talked maybe a little bit about it with like the Snow White Ride
is being excited about which color car you're going to get or which color bucket.
There would be a that would be a big deal when you were a kid,
because you'd sort of it was I guess it was like a little bit like gambling
or like you would be like, I'm betting on red. Come on, red.
And then if you got it, it was like it was an extra big celebration.
And then you would get to go on the ride in the same way on Snow White,
where you're like, come on, dopey car. Come on. I want the dopey that.
I would always want dopey. That's what I wanted.
But there was something fun about wishing for a color car or bucket
that is I don't I don't even know why it's so fun, but it was especially as a kid.
It was. And to Jason's point earlier, while there is not an immersive theme
to the cars themselves, those bright, vibrant candy colors
were sort of plenty.
And for for that reason, to the anticipation of which one am I going to get?
I'm trying to think what what I would have wanted.
Did you guys have color preferences?
Oh, blue would be number one with a bullet.
You know, always blue.
I was always a purple kid, but I know did they have a purple bucket?
I don't know. I'm not sure that they did.
I didn't see that. I didn't see that in any of the photos.
There's one hanging above the entrance at a store at Disney Springs.
I think that's blue.
Um, colors. Yeah, that's a good call.
I think, yeah, I think if I'm waiting for the skyway, I want I want that candy up a red.
That was such a such a bold, bright red.
And I think that felt the same way about Octopia cars.
Fair. Yeah, I got that.
But it's I mean, I guess I mean, the Skyliner, we were still like, oh, it's cool.
I want this like because they have characters on those two,
which even though like the characters kind of block you from seeing things,
you're still hoping you get like the character you like.
Like, there's maybe I think I may be adjusted to what I really want
is characters I like in the car in front of me because I get to look at them
for the whole. Sure. Good point.
That's a good point. More important. Yeah.
You get to look at Rocket Raccoon at Timothy Green.
It's a Jeff Goldblum star of the Val.
Artemis found his friend Dumpy Chumper's
with his name. It's not his name.
Dumpy Chumper is Dumpy Chumper.
I'm not that far off.
Yeah, I exaggerated for the sake of humor. OK.
But I sent you guys the name of Josh and Artemis.
What is the name of? Yeah, we have to find it.
God, it's it's it's close.
I want you to play Dumpy Chumper's and some TV show, please.
Write a show about Dumpy Chumper's.
I think he should be like a boy detective.
Oh, yeah, that'd be great.
OK, so here I'm on IMDb.
Josh Gad plays Mulch Digums.
I really was not that far off.
I like I like Dumpy Chumper's better, much more pleasant name.
I like Dumpy Chumper. Yeah, I like Dumpy Chumper's a lot better.
Demand that before this is released, the character's name is changed
to Dumpy Chumper's on Twitter and demand it hashtag Obamagate.
This is part of Obamagate now.
We're looping it.
I mean, it's nebulous what Obamagate is.
So there's plenty of room in the tent. Put it in there.
The law. Oh, you know, I have another one more thought.
I am I'm a little sad that they got rid of the Skyway station at Disneyland.
Oh, this is good. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Because it was it stayed there for a long time, even though the ride closed in 94.
It was just a little like Swiss chalet.
There was nothing for decades. Right.
And it was still like it was tucked back.
You could see it if you were on your way to Casey Jr.
And I liked it there because I didn't even realize it was still there
for the first so many years I was going to Disneyland.
And then when I realized it was there, it kind of felt like a little hidden
secret, a little bit of Disneyland history and lore.
And then when they finally like remove the rest of it,
I kind of felt like that was a bummer.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
A little sad.
And you know, what was weird is that they
when they sort of did the implosion of the area that became Galaxy's Edge,
they didn't take the Skyway building down at first.
And that point of view that we would always go get from the Mickey
and Friends bargain garage,
I think from there, if you looked really closely,
you could see right on the border, like sudden because all that space was cleared.
Now you could see from the parking garage to the Skyway building.
And it it sat there just as a little
microscopic little shack for a long time
until they filed a permit to destroy it on where they have the date in front of me,
a date that will live in me.
May 11th, 2016, we also the worst thing to happen in the year 2016.
Yeah, yeah, it was a dark year.
I don't know. I couldn't remember why.
But I mean, that seems that rings a bell.
Cost them $67,000 just to blow that up.
And once again, I don't think it was a cool implosion.
No Mickey stunts, no nothing.
No. And yeah, those the stations were real.
The Fantasyland stations were really beautiful.
And the Tomorrowland ones were like kind of fit in the aesthetic perfectly.
Just these kind of blocky metal cubes almost.
Which all of which are sort of nothing now.
If you go to Disneyland, you know, there's kind of those.
I mean, really, what's there now are the the secret
better Tomorrowland bathrooms than the sort of overcrowded,
stressful ones over by Space Mountain.
But if you have to go there, it's just kind of these high walls
because it's where the Skyway used to be.
And now it's sort of nothing.
Well, yeah.
So in Japan, there was a pretty good plus up
where the Fantasyland station turned into Pooh's Honey Hunt.
Yeah, that's true.
That's a good trade.
The and the Tomorrowland station became a candy store.
All right. I like that.
Tomorrowland Skyway, notable Tokyo Skyway, notable
for kind of being more enclosed with plexiglass.
Because they have much more chaotic seasons over there.
So, yeah, it was a rainstorm or whatever.
Yeah, more like the Skyliner, like the eventual Skyliner.
Right. And how nice that there is the Skyliner now, the keys of this tradition
and maybe does it in a safer and
but to go back to the beginning, more wheelchair accessible way.
I think we actually missed that during this.
I think you could only do the Skyway via stairs.
So there was really no way for handicapped guests to access it.
But the Skyliner all takes off from the ground and lifts up.
So it's not a problem with those.
So everybody can enjoy it.
And this is a pretty big, spacious
handicapped cars in the in the Skyliner.
You saw a lot of those take off just in the couple of days we were using it.
Yeah, it is fun to see like an old thing come back
and it's a better version of it and it's a cooler thing.
And now it's like being used in less of just a ride capacity
and more of a practical capacity.
So, yeah, it's like I'm trying to think of like it's like as if they were to
like build a better version of the rocket rods.
But it was for transporting you to hotels.
I mean, the the rocket rods are so we're so weird and clunky and problematic.
And now I know I feel like it's something like Garcetti with green light.
We're doing public transit, but it's rocket.
It's Elon or Elon Musk would be saying we're building.
The tunnels. Yes.
Actually, he kind of did invent the rocket rods.
Yes. He's like, well, the tunnels are I've invented these things,
rods and they are rockets.
And we should open up the economy immediately
and build these rocket rods underneath Los Angeles.
And he'd start building them and then tweet three years later.
Rocket rods are overrated.
Our stock price should go down, probably.
Hello. Well, yes.
I lost fifty thousand dollars.
From everyone, but him loses money. Yeah.
Honestly, I think we should tweet at Elon to see if he will
bring the rocket rods back.
I think we present them like blueprints, present them like we invented this
and see if we can trick him.
You know what? If if we can get a rocket rod on an episode of
Rick and Morty, I think the chances of Elon seeing it will go sky high.
So I think that might be the best way we can do it.
OK, so we'll slip that in there.
Let that in. Somebody get it.
Just somebody get a job animating there.
Oh, OK. The design.
Jason, that's you.
Oh, I love animation and software.
I had one closing thing, which was,
you know, that obviously these these all closed a long time ago.
And you always hear when they're closing attractions,
you know, every attraction is someone's favorite, you know.
But you always hear them say, like the Walt quote about like,
you know, Disneyland will never be finished.
It'll always be changing and update that that sort of thing.
When they were closing this,
I think the spokesman was a little more harsh.
There is in the L.A. Times in 1994,
they quoted a spokesman named Scott Swan.
And he said, you know, demand for the ride has fallen.
And then he said, quote, it's an evolving change.
You look at one attraction and say, it's time has come.
So I don't know why that's maybe laugh so much.
It just seemed like the inverse of the optimism of the Walt Disney quote.
And then just this guy who's like, you're on the chopping block, buddy.
You're out of here.
It's like he had to put a horse down or something. Yeah.
Like, yes, the attractions are open and then there is attractions hospice.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, that would not fly.
Robert Iger would have his ass if he said that. Yeah.
Really? I mean, that quote is so grim that it sort of sounds like
God makey. Yes, it does.
Well, sometimes, sometimes in the cycle of a ride,
you got to take it into the field and shoot it in the head.
I'm tired of these people.
I'm tired of being wrapped up in their problems.
Just pointing ominously at the skyway.
Your time has come.
I have said so. I have spoken.
When you need to put a riot out of its misery, I use the gun.
But of course, Dr.
Manhattan Mickey implies the existence of a Rorschach Donald.
So he's really going to be the truth.
Get the truth out there.
Yeah, I am sure.
I think if I do, you think there is already a fan art of Rorschach Donald?
I feel like we'll give it a look while we're at it.
Yeah, Rorschach Donald Duck.
Let's see here.
And if so, how big of a seat did they get them?
Depends on where the source of the fan art.
If it's on DeviantArt, then the seat is huge.
The seat is huge.
The inkblot is not on his face.
His face is normally inkblot is on his seat.
All right. All right.
I have it's not fan art, but it is a Pinterest picture of Donald in a party hat.
And it said all the whores and politicians will look up and shout, save us.
And I'll look down and whisper no. Oh, my God.
So there is pretty close.
Whoa, whoa. Pretty close.
Here, I'll send it. I'll send it to you.
You know, we attempt our bad versions of these character voices.
I don't think anyone does a lot of Donald.
Does anyone want to be so brave as to attempt?
I can do the noise, but I really can't talk like him.
Like I can go.
But I can't.
Here, let's just all audition it really fast.
Now that it's now that it's in front of us here.
But since you just did that, go.
OK, with all that, I have to bring it up again.
This is going to be interesting.
I can. Whoa, it's impossible to do it.
I'm not sure I can either.
It's like, really, I can't even.
Like it doesn't work.
My mouth doesn't work.
What I'm trying to do.
All right, you try. Don't don't die over there.
You try it. Let me gear up again.
We're not with you. We can't give you a time.
No, no, I don't want to choke on my tongue here.
No, it's like it's like Jason Stitch.
Yeah, yeah, it's like hard to talk.
No, that's like a gremlin.
I'll go with it, though.
Oh, the horrors.
Politicians, all the horrors and politicians
will look up and shout, save us and all look down and whisper no.
It's F.
All right.
We have a quick talk.
It doesn't work at all.
It's just gibberish.
I'm trying to get it in that because that's how he talks with that noise.
Yeah, you're putting a lot of mustard on it.
We're getting so much mustard.
We're not getting the words.
What are you doing?
You're not getting the words.
Now, I just sound like an alien.
I sound like the alien in Independence Day talking to Brent Spiner
telepathically.
Call the horrors a baby.
I can't do it. It's impossible.
Can't do it. I can't do it.
The this episode is going to come out and it's going to be listed as 11 hours long.
And the listener will be horrified to discover the last nine are blank
because we all suffocated.
Recordings kept going.
Choked out our own spit.
Jason, are you brave enough?
Yeah, I'll try.
All the horrors are back.
No, it's too.
It's Stitch.
It's getting too DeVito.
It's getting too Penguin.
I'm worried about you doing this, actually.
I'm worried about Jason.
Because there's no line.
Like when I've done impressions in the past, I latch on to a few words
or a sentence or even goofy.
You can go, like, there's no like Donald like.
Day.
Oh, the horrors and politicians.
It starts to for me, it starts to get too high and then you just slide
right into stitch.
My plan is to go.
I think you got to just pick it and stick with it.
Yeah, I'm going to try. Hold on.
Let me try to do it.
I'm I'm like there's phlegm shooting up.
This is not it's look, it's not that important.
Not the best time to spray.
Are you saying the words in your mind?
Are you are you hearing the words?
Because this is just not you're not.
You I think you pick the gurgles or you don't get the words.
I will say this. I you guys are not.
I am talking and I'm recording remotely also on a zoom.
And I am a little bit far from the computer, so we will see once we go back
on the zoom, because I do think you could hear a little enunciation
on the zoom if you're listening.
So we will see when we go back and hear this.
If you could make out any single word in that sentence.
Yeah, yeah.
I think in that in this case, just so we don't die and I'll hear
I'm going to I'm going to try to do it because mine was murdering me less,
but was much worse than what you were doing, Mike.
So let me in my terrible voice like.
You you survive, but gets a ride.
This is not what it's this voice.
You survive, but has the right for.
Well, it's my guess.
I go to Twitter, Facebook and Instagram.
Hashtag Obama gate.
Who is that character?
I'm not sure what does that sound like?
One of the guys who works at M.I.B.
headquarters. Oh, yeah.
One of the aliens. Yeah.
Yeah. Actually, it sounds a little bit like on The Simpsons
when there's the film festival and George C.
Scott is in a remake of Hans Mollmann's movie.
Oh, my groin. Oh, my groin.
So I guess in that this is this is Donald Duck saying,
if you want more bonus content,
this three bonus episodes of the Patreon dot com slash podcast
arrive. We're.
It's like Baby Herman, too.
Awful, awful ending.
And I'm having a great time.
The worst thing I had fun.
It's good. It's not.
Maybe it's not awful to listen to, but I feel bad about myself.
I'm coughing. Oh, no, no, no, no.
And let's be clear, it's because we've been
fucking with our own throats and it's not because of Covid 19.
Everybody's safe for the moment.
You stay safe as well. Listen, yes.
Any other thoughts?
Uh, no, my brain is just I'm I'm really you know what?
Honestly, I'm waiting to get off this so I can try it privately.
Try the voice privately. Great.
OK, well, yeah, I mean, look, feel free to add an addendum
if you get it better.
But for now, let's all get a glass of water, clear our throats, clear our minds.
Thanks for listening to podcast the ride and we'll see you on the third gate
soon with the Sky Guys. Yeah.
Goodbye, guys. Goodbye.
Yikes.
This has been a forever dog production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts
dot com and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify
or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter
and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.