Five, four, three, two, one.
Alrighty then, it's Podcast The Ride, The Second Gate.
My name is Mike Carlson.
Joining me as always, Scott Gardner.
Smokin'.
Yeah, and joining me as always, Jason Sheridan.
Do not go in there, right?
Well, Scott said smokin', you know,
which is a mask reference.
So I guess to play the pattern,
you should have done another Jim Carrey movie.
God, you know what?
My brain has also been retrained to be broken in that way,
Michael, where I was doing those calculations in my head
of like, okay, should it be what?
Should it be the same Jim Carrey movie?
Should it be a different Jim Carrey movie?
Like, said, what are you gonna do?
It obviously, if I'd gone third
and had to think of a different one,
I would have said, it's okay, don't worry, Simon Birch.
Everything will be fine.
I would have said, welcome to the majestic.
All right.
I have never, I don't know what,
I don't know one second of what happens in that movie.
I believe it is a blacklist, a Hollywood blacklist movie
where a man has to retreat to like a small town.
Is that Jim Carrey, he has to open up the theater,
the majestic?
I think maybe he starts working there
and he falls in love with movies all over again.
That would be my guess.
So a movie that's a love letter to movies.
Pretty cool.
Usually the best, usually the best ones.
Okay.
Today is a love letter to what I think we can regard
as one of the great shows in theme park history.
We all know it.
If you're listening to this, you definitely know it
and you've been wondering when are they gonna get to it.
It's just like, how many more months do we have to wait
before they do Ace Ventura Pet Detective live in action?
Really a love letter to licensing
because Ace Ventura, not at Disney movie,
not a Touchstone movie, a Warner Brothers movie.
Yes.
Why was this here?
Why did it happen?
They just reached out and was like,
would you guys wanna do this?
Cause it opened day and date with,
well, when nature calls came out,
which was only a year after the first Ace Ventura movie.
Yeah, so I guess for the listeners
who might be a bit younger, Jim Carrey was a big movie star.
He played Dr. Robotnik in the new Sonic the Hedgehog movies
and he made a movie called Ace Ventura Pet Detective.
You know him as Dr. Robotnik
and you know him from his satirical paintings
that are saving our democracy one at a time.
Yes, you know those probably the best,
but he also had a bunch of movies in the nineties.
He was the biggest movie star.
We all, I assume loved him.
America loved him.
I didn't remember that
cause I watched a lot of these movies on VHS
because I was not allowed to see them in theaters,
but Dumb and Dumber, The Mask and Ace Ventura Pet Detective
all came out in the same year, 1994.
That's insane.
That's insane that one man had three massive hits like that
in one year.
Yeah, I don't know that you ever get
such an all star year ever again.
Not out of nowhere, obviously,
cause we knew him from living color,
but he had not like,
well, anyway, he had starred in movies secondly,
but they were kind of like smaller shadier movies.
He was in Earth Girls Are Easy,
which Jeff Goldblum was in.
Yes.
Which he played like an alien.
And then he was in,
like he played the bad guy in that Clint Eastwood,
is it called the Deadpool?
The Clint Eastwood movie called the Deadpool?
Right.
Oh, I don't know this at all.
I believe this is right.
Let me just double check that.
It's not Deadpool.
It's not the Merc with the mouth.
It is Deadpool.
I got it in front of me.
Yeah.
It's a Dirty Harry movie.
Yes.
There were so many of those.
And Jim Carrey is the bad guy in it.
Wow.
I believe maybe not,
maybe not the main bad guy,
but a bad guy.
And it's where the phrase opinions are like assholes.
Everybody has one initiated.
Wow.
Famous.
Famous line.
Yeah.
I don't think I knew that was a,
that was Clint Eastwood.
Hmm.
So yeah, Jim Carrey,
legendary career.
Yes.
But that's sort of in a way,
neither here nor there
cause he wasn't part of this in any way.
No.
I'm not sure he was made aware of it.
Yeah.
He is not, yeah.
There's no like kind of voiceover from him.
There's no like video before the thing even saying,
Hey, it's Jim Carrey here.
I'd like to welcome you to the Ace Ventura Experience
at Disney's Hollywood Studios.
There's none of that.
It's no, it's very lo-fi.
This is very, it's like as barely there as a show can be.
Yeah.
So yeah.
So was there any,
I didn't find any like evidence that this was advertised
cause you would think that their idea would be,
okay, we need to bring in like the hottest property we can,
Ace Ventura.
But like, did they have it in commercials?
Was there a commercial saying,
come to Hollywood Studios to see three minutes
of an Ace Ventura show?
I don't think so.
I think this was-
I don't think so either.
I think this was just on their run of licensing stuff,
like the Ninja Turtles and I mean, the big ones,
Star Wars and the Muppets stuck around forever,
but the Ninja Turtles hung out for a little while.
I was just texting you guys about,
I didn't know about the Goosebumps.
There was a short run Goosebumps thing,
which is crazy that I missed that like as a kid
because I loved the Goosebumps books.
Yes, I did too.
And I had no idea.
There was like a little show
and a little walkthrough fun house.
That's crazy.
Yeah, this is hard.
We gotta get to that one.
Yeah, I think I'm only aware of that
because I watch all these parades all the time,
which I was watching one last night
from that era where the Ninja Turtles were around
and Aaron turned to me during it and was like,
I really hate that the Turtles are there.
Like she's a fan of the Turtles overall.
It's just like, I don't know,
them being in Disney World just bothers me.
I don't know what it is.
I know what she means.
That's certainly not my favorite iteration of Turtles anywhere.
All of these are sort of strange.
Then none of them feel right.
Was she more okay with the Universal Turtles?
Does she seem familiar with that?
Because there's not a lot of documentation of it,
but the like Turtle Lair that they built
in the parking garage at Universal?
I think if I had to ask her,
I think there's something about Universal
where the properties all feel like free for alls more.
Yeah.
Like you know, it's just kind of,
if you want to see your Disney characters,
you go to Disneyland.
If you want to see a grab bag of all the other characters
besides the Looney Tunes, then they'll all be at Universal.
Yeah, no, that makes sense.
I think maybe part of it is the juxtaposition
of the not, I guess pandering might be the word
of like the golden age of Hollywood, you know,
MGM, Disney MGM studios, Hollywood, how movies are made.
And then pandering stuff that we know kids like
the dinosaur TV show, the Turtles, Goosebumps,
a few years later, the Power Rangers,
but well after the peak.
Really?
Yeah, there were Power Rangers.
Because Disney owned and still,
I think they may have sold it.
Disney bought the full Saban library
and owned it at some point
because they aired on ABC family for a little while.
Oh, that's right.
Right, right, right.
Have you guys seen the new Power Rangers?
Well, still still.
The Brian Cranston, the Brian Cranston.
Oh, I have not seen it.
I can't, I just got this check of like,
do I bring this up or not?
I have to, there's parts of it where like,
everybody speaks in a weird alien language.
Like Brian Cranston's barely in it
and just kind of in like weird hologram ways.
But he's Zordon, right?
He's Zordon, yeah.
It was just kind of this bad effect
in a tube in the TV show.
But now it's this really intricate,
but still boring CGI gloop kind of way of doing it.
And he does most of his dialogue in the movie
is not in English,
but through whatever alien dialect he speaks,
which sounds basically like,
ock, knock, bug, glock, ock, galock.
These are like deadly serious scenes in the movie
where all the Power Rangers are acting like they might die.
And then the dialogue is,
g'donk, glock, bug, glock, rita, balonk.
It's just, I don't know how this movie feels.
I feel like I made it up.
I feel like I hallucinated
these several years ago Power Rangers.
I gotta see this.
I can't believe I haven't watched this yet, honestly.
I like the first Power Rangers movie
because of Ivan Ooze, of course.
Well, and that song,
the Uh-Oh, We're in Trouble song rocked.
Yes, I like that song too.
Scott, you know Ivan Ooze, right?
I don't, I wasn't really a Power Rangers kid, so no.
But do you even know what he looks like?
No, I'll look it up now.
Ivan Ooze.
Ooh, well, yes, I'm sold pretty fast.
And he's like a kind of a like
eccentric British character actor.
It's like a piece of purple green goblin.
Yeah, exactly.
Very much so.
And then sometimes he becomes bad CGI.
Oh.
Yeah, you gotta, the Power Rangers movie
looks pretty good except the like
five minutes of like CGI stuff
that clearly cost a fortune and looks very rudimentary.
Oh, hell yes.
I'm seeing pictures of it.
Oh my God, it's so lawnmower, man.
It's very, it looks really a lot like Xavier Renegade Angel.
Yeah. Yes.
I've sent you a picture of Ivan Ooze and Goldar
with Ivan Ooze drinking like some sort of drink
with like steam coming out of it.
And then it's a signed photo from the actor,
Paul Freeman, who played Ivan Ooze.
This is great.
That looks like a good beverage.
He looks, he's got a crazy straw coming out of it.
Yeah.
So. Wow.
All right.
I love to check out Ivan Ooze.
I stan Ivan Ooze.
All right.
Well, probably that's the safe to say Ivan Ooze episode
coming once I do my homework.
There's in a, he's in here.
I'll send you another photo.
He dresses up.
He dresses up and he sells his Ooze at a carnival.
So that's like a perfect podcast to ride synergy.
This is him in a wizard costume.
He's like put some white powder over his face
as if in like a white chick's manner
to look like a regular, like a Caucasian person.
Yes.
But he didn't put enough on.
So it's still kind of a purple tint.
Yes.
This is amazing.
He sells his Ooze to children at a carnival.
Yeah.
For whatever reason in the movie,
like in the TV show, all of the robots,
the Megazords that the Power Rangers use
are all like models and costumes.
But in the movie, they're like, let's make these CGI.
And it looks, it's aged.
I think it looked bad a year later.
The designs are still fun,
but I have seen little clips
of all the Power Rangers and stuff.
Because when I worked at a post-production house,
they had all of the Saban shows in,
that was another thing in like six different languages.
Right.
Yeah, sure.
I mean, those, there's like 30 Power Rangers TV shows.
Yeah.
And I imagine that they're just repackaged
every single place they can be.
Well, they are.
I mean, what they do is they make a season in Japan,
and then they reuse a lot of that footage
and then shoot stuff.
I think production is in Australia or New Zealand now.
And then they cobble together a different storyline,
but still trying to make the fight footage make sense.
And then they make those episodes in English,
and then they redub those in like other languages
and resell those to other markets.
It's true.
Well, we'll investigate this on the I have a news episode.
Yeah.
We'll correct the process.
Well, it just makes you appreciate that here for America,
that they filmed, they didn't do it in this lazy way.
They gave us Cranston, they gave us Bill Hader
as the little stressed out robot.
We all know it.
Yeah.
Well, I'm actually blanking on the character's name,
but I do know it.
Yeah.
It's one of the great franchises.
I'm like hypnotized now by these CGI.
I can't wait to watch this.
Oh boy.
Oh, he turns, he's like, he's a bug and then turns.
Oh my God.
I can't wait.
Okay.
Focus on the task at hand,
talking about one of the worst shows.
I mean, this is,
this will be a major case of our episode length ratio
extending way beyond the show.
Cause the show is like seven minutes long, I feel like.
It is not a long show.
It is.
I will, you know, they do pack a few things in
that might be worth going to see, but yes,
it is very, very short.
I don't know.
I would say like the character of Ace Ventura
is pretty faithful to the Jim Carrey version
from the video I saw.
Yeah.
I will say that I've never seen Ace Ventura
look so jacked.
I think it's a stunt man first
who learned an Ace Ventura impression, I would say.
That's probably right.
Yeah.
It seems to be.
I don't know.
Ace is like tall and built
and I assume very handsome, I assume.
Yeah. Yeah.
And yeah, which is odd to see somebody,
like this was before all the best comedians
were fucking jacked.
Like now this is very common.
Of course everyone's in perfect physical condition.
The funniest and the most jacked at once.
But yeah, at the time Jim Carrey was kind of way fish
and sort of see this like lunk of a six foot six man
play Ace is a little jarring.
If they were, yeah, if they were to do the office again
today with the same cast, Rainn Wilson would be
about 250 pounds of pure muscle.
Which he might be anyway.
I don't know.
Maybe he's gotten like that.
I haven't seen him in a little while.
Well.
I think everyone's.
He's good.
He's very zen.
He harnessed the power of his mind to shape his body.
Yeah.
So the office, yeah, the office, I would,
one of the, the office is a perfect sitcom,
but I wish everyone was jacked.
I wish Stanley was jacked.
I wish Toby was jacked.
I wish they all were jacked.
You make a new show now and kind of the schlubby character
is someone who, you know, has like 3% body fat.
Yeah, right.
Yeah, exactly.
Yes.
And they can't look foolish.
They don't look foolish anymore
cause they're very handsome and jacked,
but every now and then they do something
slightly embarrassing or they say that's not even a thing.
And that's how you make comedy.
Unlike Ace Ventura kind of doing more like three stooges,
rework three stooges physicality.
Yeah.
No, no, no.
That's no good.
A bunch of hot people standing around and asking
if whatever has happened just happened.
Yep.
This is the way we let the ridiculousness,
when Ace put on a tutu and a Hawaiian shirt
and like this, that Ace Ventura was ridiculous.
It was random.
I don't get it.
Get it out.
This is not for me, previous generation comedy.
So I guess we should say, okay,
so let's give a quick brief setup of the show.
So there's a back lot or there used to be a back lot.
I don't know.
Is this part of the back lot still there
at Hollywood studios in Florida?
No, this is in the streets of America.
The facades you could walk through and around.
Oh, right, right.
Yeah.
And they bulldozed that pretty quickly
for a giant Star Wars attraction.
Right.
Yeah.
So it was basically, you know,
like a set with like the exterior of an apartment building
or whatever with fire escapes and some other things.
As if you were-
You go into an alley,
an alley where Ace Ventura has set up a temporary office
and a shed.
Yes, with a slide nearby.
With a slide, yes.
With a very short playground slide, yes.
The office shed looks pretty good.
That looks all right.
Like they built a themed shed for this.
So they built two whole walls for this show.
Two whole walls.
They built some photo backdrops.
And then they built and they put like,
they got like a riser and two sets of stairs
as the main stage.
They got a man, a very wide tie.
They got the MC, a very wide tie and a very blousy shirt.
How would we,
because Mike, as you're trying to say,
just the premise of the show where we got this far
that Ace Ventura has an office
and we're getting all this information from,
what is he?
Who is the host?
Why is he talking to us?
That's a good question.
He talks like a random theme park character
that would be on a street.
And that's really all I can associate him with.
Maybe is it sort of creating the universe of,
it's like the NBC pages kind of scenario
where there's studio helpers around
and they're experts and they know everything.
They know what movies are filming and they can say,
we, they're part of the grand we.
Like we've been working on a lot of new productions.
And I guess he's kind of in that world.
I think that's right.
Ace Ventura calls him Ron right towards the end.
Oh, so we got a name.
He's Ron.
Ron, Ronny.
So Ron, the headset mic'd man tells us
that Ace Ventura has graciously agreed to stop by
and talk about his movie career.
Yes, which is okay.
So we've talked a lot about this.
Okay, so, but this reality is not,
we're shooting something for a new Ace Ventura.
Ace Ventura is real, but he's also an actor
that's in the movies, Ace Ventura.
So it's like he's playing himself
in the movies in this reality.
Yes.
Yeah, so this reality has no Jim Carrey in it.
Right.
Or it's kind of a, as he would later explore
a Andy Hoffman, Tony Clifton scenario
where the lines are blurred.
Is there a real Tony Clifton?
Is there a real Ace Ventura?
I see.
That's true.
I mean, if you would have kept going with this show
and maybe made different versions,
I mean, I guess there wasn't another version,
but if you made different versions,
they could have explored that.
But I'm not sure that was in the plan.
That was in the grand plan here.
Do you think that the six foot six stunt man
lived as Ace Ventura for the three straight months,
maybe one month?
How long did the show run?
It's unclear, I believe, how long this ran.
For five weeks, he lived and breathed Ace Ventura.
I have to imagine.
Yeah, he was method.
How else are you gonna do it?
How else are you gonna really know
to tell people to not go in there?
I saw on, and I don't have this source backed up
or anything, but I saw on WDW Magic,
people said that this actor was Robbie
from the Adventurers Club.
And also one of the hosts of the Hyperspace Hoopla.
Oh, interesting.
So I think he's been around a long time, if that's true.
And he probably is method when he's playing
any of these characters.
Whether it be Ace Ventura or Snig.
Snig, he might, yeah, when he's playing Snig,
he's just Snig for those five weeks.
Yeah, I knew that Snig had to come back
and do his Hyperspace Hoopla.
Yeah, there should be like a making of documentary
about him getting into character as Snig
and how he acts when he's Snig.
And yes, presumably Hyperspace Hoopla,
like Man on the Moon,
is directed by a beleaguered Eastern European man.
I don't know what to do, I cannot deal with Snig.
Can you talk to Snig?
Please, what's his name?
Larry, what was the guy's name?
Which guy?
The act, do we know the name of the stunt man?
Or this performer?
Let me see, I think I had it actually.
I feel like you said it.
I have to think there.
Robbie, Robbie, Robbie, Robbie, you must talk to Snig.
I cannot deal with Snig.
It is Milos Forman.
Milos Forman direct comes,
he directed every Hyperspace Hoopla before his passing.
Yeah.
Robbie.
You did a great job.
Robbie, let me ask you, is Snig here with us right now?
Is he here, is Ace here with us?
Is that his James Lipton interview?
Well, yeah, they're doing a retrospective
of the golden years of MGM Studios.
It would, honestly, you just stumbled on a fantastic idea
of James Lipton interviewing some of these actors
who've played like 30 different theme park roles.
Oh yeah.
Yeah, so can you summon, you know,
like the silly Waterworld guy whose pants fall down?
Right.
Is he here?
Can we speak to him?
Can his pants fall down?
Is a recording engineer in the rock and roller coaster here,
the one that ushers people in and out of the recording studio?
The one that says you're going to need a bigger limo?
Can we talk to them, to that person?
One of the most challenging roles to play
in theme park world, absolutely.
Maybe we'll, yeah, we'll do that.
We'll have Jason host a show like that.
Yeah.
I know there's a, because you know, we've talked about,
there's like a scene, there's a circuit down in Orlando,
if people make a living just doing all these shows and stuff.
But I'm blanking now, Jamie Denbow,
I talked to her once a little about,
she was a citizen of Hollywood and did,
not adventurous club, I think did Comedy Warehouse
in Pleasure Island, but she said that like,
they had a term for people who would join the shows
but also did the Renaissance Fairs,
like in the area, like there was like,
not like dirt munchers, but there was a teasing term
they had for the people who branched out
and also did the Renaissance Fair,
like the dirty outdoor Renaissance Fair shows in Orlando,
in the Florida area.
Well, we got a, well, when you,
when she's on that version of the show I was describing,
we'll have to find out. Sure.
Yeah, yeah.
So, okay. Dirt munchers.
Dirt munchers, geez.
I got a, I can't remember the term, it was very funny.
But like, it's like anything else where you're like,
oh, I don't want to do improv over there.
I do improv over here.
Like, you know, that sort of
packing water happens everywhere.
I mean, I would always prefer to do anything where
I don't have to munch dirt.
Yeah.
And I prefer to do improv everywhere.
Well, right now you are allowed to do a crazy happening
in your living room, in your bedroom, in your bathroom.
Oh yeah, yeah, don't worry.
Yeah.
Wearing no pants has less of an effect
when you're just in your, your dwelling.
So, okay.
So have we set the scene for you vividly enough at this point?
There's a man on a step and he says Ace Ventura is coming.
And he asks if we,
there's any Ace Ventura fans here today?
And people, the 20 people go,
sure.
Okay.
And then he asks Ace to come out and then he doesn't.
So then he asks everyone to shout Ace.
Then you hear a crowd all go Ace.
And then he, and then he does come out.
And when, once he lands,
you can still hear somebody next to the camera say,
everybody goes, yay.
But one person still says Ace.
That's just a specific detail from the one video available.
Which, you know, if you want to watch it,
you don't really, you really don't have to.
I'm not sure that I recommend it,
but if you want to know what we're talking about,
wait, what is the name?
It's called, I mean, I guess if you just search
Ace Ventura Disney MGM Studios,
I think it's called like Ace Ventura Visits Disney MGMs.
Yes, Ace Ventura Visits Disney's Hollywood Studios.
It is nine minutes long.
Maybe less.
It's very quick.
It's a real easy go.
I would like to one day repel down a building like that.
That looks very fun.
Really?
You don't think that looks fun?
That looks fun.
No, I'm not saying it doesn't look fun,
but I don't picture you being comfortable enough
to repel down a building.
Oh, I think that many carabiners
and like strong cord and glute.
I would want some proper training first.
I wouldn't just do it willy nilly.
Wow, that's, I mean, I'd love to make this happen
if we have anyone out there who knows why,
like is into wire work and can get Jason
on the top of a building to repel down it.
You know, I like, I love heights.
I'm like a goat.
I like to be on the highest point.
I like to be high up.
Do you love heights?
I do, yeah.
Huh.
You're a real height muncher.
Yeah.
You're a real.
You're a height.
Hashtag height muncher.
Wow, I guess I kind of knew that, but I don't know.
I just pictured that being such kind of an intense thing
that I wouldn't think that you would want to do it,
but all right, let's make it happen.
I love heights and I love enclosed spaces,
like little tight little, like I find it very cozy.
All these, these very common fears.
I'm like, yeah, sign me up.
You want to be like, your dream would be to be in a,
like in a giant burrito.
Oh, that sounds nice.
A burrito. Tucked away in a giant tortilla.
Yeah.
On a very high shelf.
All right, so, okay, let's make this happen.
Let's get you in either a tortilla costume
or an Ace Ventura costume and get like
on the Warner Brothers lot where they still have
these type of backlots and let's hook,
let's figure this out.
Getting you to repel down the side of a fake building.
I think we can make this happen.
That sounds good.
Once we're out of our apartments.
I mean, we got to, yeah, when we do a live show again,
we got to come out with a bang.
So Jason, yeah, Jason doing wire work
is a hell of a way to come back.
It sounds better than this.
Like there's like a trend now of like climbing gyms
where people are just climbing rock walls inside
for exercise, but with no ropes or anything.
So I've just seen videos of people I know
just falling like 10 feet onto mats.
I'm not into that.
Huh.
Yeah, I would want a rope if I was climbing.
Yeah.
I'm not going to do a Tom Cruise Mission Impossible 2,
no rope climb.
No, he did that so we didn't have to.
We did that for our sins.
He suffers for our sins.
I think it's possible, I think it's possible Tom had a rope
but Ethan in the movie didn't.
Right.
If Ethan were, if Ethan Hunt were real,
he would like swallow all the coronavirus and sacrifice.
So he'd like somehow get everyone to cough into his mouth
and then he'd have all of it.
And then, and he would like,
he's like suicide bombing himself
with all of the world's coronavirus,
but then he'd like still survive somehow.
The way that I've read that Tom Cruise
and Christopher McQuarrie make these movies,
like on the fly, I don't think that's out of the realm
of possibility that they add that
into Mission Impossible 7.
He fixes the virus by getting all of it.
They've shot a little of it,
I think then they had to shut down,
but I feel like they just have to adapt now
and put something ripped from today's headlines
in the new movie.
Yeah, and you're right that Tom,
well, yeah, Tom would do it too.
So I'm getting the virus.
I'm the first person electing to get it.
Like it only makes him stronger.
I was having this discussion with Lindsay and she,
I was saying, if you were, say you were like shooting
a movie or involved in a movie and John Travolta said,
hey, I'll fly you back to LA on my plane, would you go?
And she's like, no, I don't think so.
I go, well, what if Tom Cruise said that?
She goes, oh yeah, I would do it for sure.
That's it, I could not agree with this statement more.
Yeah, but Travolta is a good pilot.
That's not why I'm not getting on a plane with him.
There's some baggage.
You think this has to do with the plane part?
He's gonna be very friendly.
He's gonna be nice.
He's a nice guy.
All right, all righty then.
Let's just go, let's just propel.
Let's just fast forward, can we do this?
All right, yeah, let's go, let's go, let's go.
All right, so yeah, he comes down on a rope
and he's not really miked in the video
and the host has to mic him.
That's really funny.
He's got a really funny line
cause a spider appears, right?
That's what happens.
That's the impetus for him to do his antics.
Yeah, he's gonna come talk about the movie
and then he just evades all the questions
and says, nonsense, poopy pants and spank you very much.
And he refuses all of his responsibilities
to the filmmaking curious audience of the show.
And then a weird puppet bug appears on the roof.
This is a weird, by the way,
I don't know if we've explained so much.
The show's taking place in an alley,
but it really is like a pop-up.
There's no seats.
It's just kinda, you're just like
craning your head everywhere.
Yeah, it's like extremely, not unorganized,
but I think Aaron said,
it feels like they rehearsed this once
and then like, okay, close enough, let's go.
It's a happening man.
That's a great way to put it.
Much like improv everywhere.
Yeah, it's just suddenly occurring
and people have to react.
Yeah, there's a weird bug.
He has to go back up the, he's propelled down a rope
and then he's gotta go back up the rope.
I also, in my head, this was a stunt show
and it is a stunt show.
What he's doing are stunt, but I,
is it though, maybe this is where it's important
to have words like stuntacular.
Because while this is a stunt show,
I would certainly not call it a stuntacular.
So that vocabulary is helpful.
Yeah, it's no stuntacular,
but there are like, the repelling is cool
because it's a high up place.
It's not two stories.
It feels like it's what, four stories?
Am I wrong?
Looks about, yeah.
Four or five stories maybe.
There's a zip line.
Yes.
Across two big build, like two high up places.
That's not nothing.
I think legally they have to classify this performer
as stunt work because he has to repel the zip line for sure.
It certainly is stunt work.
It's just funny how it's like, it's one person
and it's stunt work that's all being done very slowly.
I mean, I guess the Alice would you do it,
but it just feels especially, it was belabored.
I don't know.
Everything takes a while, I feel like.
Yeah, him crossing, he goes up a wire
and then like walks across a fence
and he stops in the middle to talk out of his butt.
So I appreciate that.
That kind of ups the butt talking that he does it
on kind of a high wire situation.
Here's my question about the butt talking.
Do you think, cause it's a very brief
and it feels like that would be off limits
for a Disney environment cause that's very crude
when Ace Ventura talks out of his butt.
Now again, if you're a younger listener,
Ace would sometimes for no reason bend over,
grab his own butt with his hands
and open up his butt to make it talk.
Now he's not naked, but I'm just describing
what happened in the movie.
And the stunt performer does a little bit of it,
but not a ton.
Do you think, do you, yeah, sorry.
That's me.
Well, in the movies, Ace Ventura is at like a nine or 10.
In this like street show, he is at a one or two.
It's very tamped down, it's very tame comparably.
But that's what I'm saying.
Do you think there was a conversation
when they were putting this together
where there was a longer butt talking segment
and the powers that be were like, all right,
we know that's one of his signature moves.
You can do it for exactly 1.5 seconds or two seconds,
but no longer.
Oh, for sure.
I'm sure that happened.
I mean, there was an Ace Ventura Saturday morning cartoon
very briefly too.
So like they just took the cartoony stuff
and took out like him covered in shit
and being very horny.
Like there's no horny stuff in this.
Yes.
I just, I would love to have heard them
of like timing the butt talking.
Yeah.
You can do the butt talking as long as it's very lazy
and half committed to.
Right.
You can't actually make your butt move with your own hands.
You can't be as, you can't grasp it as firmly
as Jim Carrey grasped his own butt.
It's about inches.
It's about, you know, yeah, how close do you get
to the actual center?
This is one of those times where I do wish
Walt Disney was alive to have signed off
or not signed off on this.
Where like this would have had to come across his desk
and he would have had to approve Ace Ventura
talking out of his butt at Disney's Hollywood studios.
And how would he, was Walt moralist enough
to not approve of this?
Well, here's the thing.
Here's my impression of Walt.
My impression of Walt is that he was, yes,
kind of a stodgy uptight guy
when it came to any sort of crudities.
But he was also, if you could convince him
that it was like good for business
or if like times were changing, he could be swayed.
So perhaps a younger executive could have explained to him
why butt talking was so popular at the time.
Yes, now the butt talking in this was not good for business.
This had no effect on business.
Because as we said, they did not advertise the show
in any way, no one came to the park to see this.
I guess if maybe butt talking,
maybe it was good for business because people saw it
and were like, I don't want to watch this anymore.
And then went and got a soda.
Right.
So it could have been good for business in that way.
Made them thirsty.
Mm-hmm.
There are some real animals, you know,
that's Ace Ventura's bread and butter.
That's true.
Some birds fly out when it's implied Ace Ventura
goes into his office to take a shit real quick.
Yes, another crude moment.
Yeah.
Another moment you'd have to convince a 90 year old
Walt Disney to allow in his park.
Implied pooping.
So Ace Ventura, this establishes that not just in the one scenario.
Well, first of all, in the in the context of the film,
he didn't poop.
That's a cover.
Right. Right. Yeah.
So in this case, this actually is maybe the first scenario
of Ace Ventura taking a big shit and then saying,
do not go in there.
Woo. Right.
So this is adding to the yeah, this is this is adding to the canon, I guess.
He really did take a big dump now in a way we didn't get to see him do
in the first movie.
Unless that's interesting.
Unless the birds made a big mess.
Unless it's like, oh, don't go in there.
The birds made a big mess in there and they're getting out of here.
There's a flushing sound, though.
So unless and this is birds are aces, pets, by and large, are kind of smart.
So maybe the maybe the birds did poop in the toilet
and then flush it and then which in that case, saying, do not go in there
is I don't know if I agree.
It sounds like it's probably kind of clean.
Do go in there.
You should have said be impressed by these doves that know how to use toilets.
Please go in here.
Woo. And then the woo is a happy woo.
Yeah, happy woo.
Did OK to eyes their head to approve this, though.
Maybe I this is low stakes enough.
You might not have known.
You think this could have snuck by him?
This is we have to we have obviously a big list of questions.
Someone write this down when we get the interview with him,
which I'm sure we will,
that we have to ask him about Ace Ventura at Hollywood Studios.
If he remembers it, if he remembers approving the length
that Ace could talk out of his butt and the shit joke.
This is where it's all because this is 95, though, and it's all unraveling a little.
And he's dealing with Frank Wells' death in the movies or maybe his play.
He might have been like
he might have been recovering from the heart attack while this.
Maybe that's why this happened, because he was asleep at the wheel.
And they were like, well, just get I don't know, get something in here.
Maybe without his poor health, this show wouldn't have occurred at all.
Is this is there a chance that like when he was in the hospital,
they tried to force this through, like they had him sign off on him in there.
Like when they did during the Bush administration,
when John Ashcroft was in the hospital
and they tried to get him to sign off on things while he was like under anesthesia.
Oh, yeah.
Do you think that's pretty much what happened here?
That's the way the entire
paramount Viacom world has been run for many years.
OK, it's some of the redstone.
Like if he drools on a piece of paper, that means it's approved.
We got some of the rest still alive, right?
Yeah. Yeah. As of recording.
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
I think it feels like it could change any second.
Do you think he would do the show?
Again, if if the right person asks
and if like if a moan from him is interpreted in the right way, then,
yeah, I suppose so.
Hmm. Well, we'll work out. We'll get our booker on that.
And then we only ask him questions about like the.
So why did you drop the Kings Island branding?
I'm sure he's I'm sure he'll have some way to signal us with answers.
I all right. So that's on the to do list.
We'll get some nerve.
But I think we figured it out.
Eisner was in poor health and this happened in like the,
you know, the couple of days where he was dealing with it.
And that's so this thing was like a this.
This was a huge health related accident. Yeah.
Yeah, that's a good way to think of it.
But so, yeah, so, OK,
ace, whatever you can not covered, ace takes a shit.
He talks out of his butt.
But he fire escape.
Yeah. And then the the bug that he's trying to rescue.
It's a big like wiggly puppet bug.
And it ends up on his face and then he rips it off of his face.
And he says, I think I just got engaged. Yes.
And then the spider
or whatever it is, ends up on his back.
And there's some like classic I think Park hijinks of where where is it?
It's on your back.
Hey, so you're back.
And he doesn't believe them.
Ace is a real jerk throughout this.
He doesn't trust the audience.
He refuses to do almost everything that's asked of him.
Well, he does.
He gives him what he wants, what they want.
He does say all righty then, like 20 times and nine.
A lot of times, a lot of times.
I do have to say I did like the line.
I don't know. It's probably in the movie.
If I'm not back in five minutes, just wait longer.
I think that's a solid line.
I did like that. Yes. Yeah, yeah, that's right.
Yeah, I was.
Does a good job.
The actor does a good job. Yeah.
I wasn't crazy about the bit where the host says,
could you give us some some of your impressions of Africa?
And he just makes animal noises and then they play a Tarzan yell.
I that was a little bit of a reach.
The audience didn't understand.
I think they were just like, yeah, impressions of Africa.
And then he does impressions of animal like that didn't think the wordplay was lost.
They were just like, this is a reasonable answer to this question.
Yeah, I don't think there's not a ton of like there were.
There were two versions of the show overall,
and there's not a lot to see if maybe they had tweaked some of these jokes.
It's not a lot of documentation.
Apparently, sometimes Ace Ventura, in lieu of repelling down a building,
would just get out of a car like a car would drive up
and he would get out of the backseat.
And in that version, it was going after a white bat like he was in the second movie.
Like Chicago. Yes. Yes.
Oh, it was just the plot of the second movie. Right.
So they they changed that at a certain point
because of because people would people were just confused, I'm sure,
unless he was doing exactly what he did in the movie.
They do play the rock and roll Chicago song from the movie.
That's what that's what a music cue is.
This is an original song about the bat named Chicago.
Yeah, it's just some rock and roll guitar.
And then occasionally a voice goes, Chicago.
That's the song.
You know, speaking of people being confused about this show,
I don't know if you guys came across this, but I saw a post somewhere
from someone who was an employee
or like a like a helper with this show was like part of the crew of this show,
probably among other theme park duties over several years.
And he kind of like corralled the audience for this show for a little while.
Did you guys run into this?
No, no, I didn't.
I forget the website.
Apologies for not sourcing it.
But the yeah, somebody talks about the brief
summer that this occurred.
And he kind of alludes to the low budget,
low effort nature of the show.
And I'll I'll, you know, synopsize this.
But he he says the following is my recreation
of the sort of conversation I'd end up having with a guest
just about every show.
Excuse me, but what time will he be here?
The A's Ventura show begins at 2 p.m.
Oh, will he do photos and autographs or is he just doing the show?
Ace will be available after the show for pictures and autographs.
Wow. So how did they get him to do this?
I mean, it's really him, right?
Guy. Well, Ace is very busy.
And he decided to set up a temporary office here at Disney MGM Studios.
No, no, no. I mean, Jim Carrey.
I'm so excited to meet him.
Well, Jim Carrey portrayed Ace Ventura,
and we really wish he could be here to meet Ace.
Wait, so Jim Carrey's not here.
You said you just said he was going to be here at 2 p.m.
No, sir. I said he's been to it will be here at two base.
Ventura would be here to be. I'm not Jim Carrey.
That is not what you said. Kids, let's go.
Jim Carrey is not here.
They'd walk away and not see the show.
Wow. I mean, you got to get you got to get that training.
You got to be able to answer those questions.
I mean, this is a tradition that is, you know, still alive at the galaxy's edge
that replaced this setting in this very park.
People having to use bizarre phrases
that don't allude to what's actually going on.
Tortured employees having to play these little games.
Like when I like when we went to the Mickey meet and greet on Main Street
in Florida and he didn't talk and I had to go.
I went to City Hall to complain and they said, you know, Mickey,
Mickey's not feeling very talkative sometimes.
And then I was like, right, but he talks, right?
Why didn't he talk? And they're like, he's not always feeling so well.
I'm like, wait, wait a minute.
Some heads, I go, so like some heads talk and some don't
because there are multiple rooms and they're like,
you could maybe just ask in line if Mickey's feeling talkative.
And that might help you out.
And I'm like, what is this game we're playing?
You fucking freak. Get out of here.
All right. In my version, that's the line about this in my version of this.
Well, I got a fast pass for it.
And that's one of the, you know, I used a fast pass up,
but I'm going to better get my talking Mickey head.
But did it say it was going to be talking?
Well, if you go on YouTube and it's not happening anymore,
but if you go on YouTube to this meet and greet,
there's so many videos of Mickey talking to people.
And apparently the head malfunctions a lot and it's not always talking.
And they only have one out of three.
Like there's three different rooms I think you can go into.
And only one of the rooms has a talking Mickey.
Like always. Well, at least at the time I was going, I don't know.
I think it's done. I think I don't. It is done right now.
Yeah. Because the head is too, too.
The technology is not there yet to make Mickey talk.
Well, this is a real Russian roulette then.
You're going to use a fast pass on a, what is one out of three,
two out of three chances, not a talking Mickey head.
Well, to be fair to me, I didn't know it wasn't,
I thought it was like sort of an advertised thing because I had seen so many of
these videos.
So I just thought it was a foregone conclusion that Mickey would talk.
I didn't realize it was sort of a random thing and it was still in testing mode.
So that's why I was so confused after we had done it,
because I just thought it was common knowledge that Mickey talked.
But so you use the fast pass to save time.
And then you were mad that a fast pass was used on this thing.
So then you took time to stand in a line and complain about
how your time was not being valued.
That's right. Well, I didn't, I mean, I didn't say something like that in a funny way.
Sure.
But then I got, I did get a fast pass back for the same attraction.
And they told me the secret code to basically say,
and then we did see talking Mickey.
OK, all right. So it's a happy ending.
Yeah. But he really mostly talked to Lindsay and he didn't address me as much as I'd
like him to.
Well, they can't all be Minnie grabbing your ass.
I would I would have liked a little more attention is all I'm saying here.
I guess he's mad at me.
Minnie's all over you like you're on a flight with John Travolta.
Anyway, it's a.
It's a.
So the very end, he does catch the spider and then they say is ventura will be down
in a second and he falls through the roof like there's a crashing sound effect
and a puff of smoke.
And then is it a flock of birds gets released or a flock of bats?
I don't think it's bad.
It's not that you can't trade bats for a theme park show.
I hope not.
I think so. It's like I just be confetti or something.
It's like a plume of like black birds kind of flies.
At least I think it was.
It's hard to tell. It's not the best.
I got to go back and watch this.
Have they released bats?
Go back and watch it.
The camera catches the smoke smoke puff and then like very quickly tries to whip up
and like and there's a bunch of stuff like looks like birds flying, you know,
another batch of birds released, I think, unless it just happened to be a bunch of
birds or bats passing by at the perfect moment.
I'm going to try to check this out here.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
It's yeah, it does feel like.
But I can't imagine that they're releasing.
I don't know that bats can be trained to that extent.
Yeah, I don't think so.
Also, I've heard that sometimes when they release birds, they all just die.
Is that you heard this like when you release certain birds, like they like it's
they don't go back anywhere, they just like end up dying because they're not trained.
I think some of them are trained to go back.
But I got to think the it's not 100 percent
return rate, you know. Yeah.
Anyway, I don't know. We have to we'll do a whole bird episode, I guess.
I keep I'm watching it over and over and it is very tough to do.
They do. It does look black, but I think it might just be it's either.
I think it's either black birds or just black confetti.
It could be a wind drift, maybe.
It's all kind of going the same direction.
It's very hard to tell. Hmm.
Yeah, I'll I'll look.
I don't want to get too distracted now.
We're wrapping this hopefully wrapping this up.
I guess I certainly hope so.
I think I literally this never happens.
I think I've hit every one of my notes.
Yes, it's quite easy, pretty tidy to do.
Still had time to talk about Ivan.
Ivan News and Brian Cranston.
And yeah, we've one of my favorite a lot in
my my last thought really about this is that
it is a shame that that Ace Ventura didn't line up with the opening of Animal Kingdom.
Oh, yeah.
Because wouldn't that have been great if we could have had like a Joe
Rody created Ace Ventura attraction or show at Animal Kingdom,
which is obviously a place Ace would love the most. Sure.
So I was thinking, like, where do you put
where would you put a sin animal kingdom to do a show like this?
Would he be on the tree of life?
You know, in the 90s, would he?
I'm trying to think, because, you know, like obviously Pandora wasn't there yet.
Dinosaur.
It'd be a whole area, probably.
It's Camp Ace Ventura.
Oh, OK, that's good.
And then he I mean, also, maybe maybe you'd actually you know what?
Maybe you'd want him sort of goofing around on the safari.
Yeah, well, if he could be born out of a hippo, like in the movie,
you're on that. Yeah, that's the perfect one.
Perfect one.
So obviously they put if you've never seen Ace Ventura to
he is in a like robot rhino naked.
I think or easy to take his clothes off in there.
He may take his clothes off in the robot rhino because it's too hot.
And then to try to get out of the rhino, it's like malfunctioning or something.
And then he has to like squirm his way out of the rhinos.
But essentially, and it looks like the rhino is shitting a naked Ace Ventura out.
So I think Scott's hit on the perfect situation here.
Solution is on the safari.
You see in the distance a robotic rhino
shitting out Robbie, the stunt performer
once every tour.
Yeah, he's got he's got to reset the lot.
And they're going to go through a lot of prosthetic hippos.
So maybe a couple a couple different performers, maybe.
So you can you can quickly reset like you can quickly
like there'll be like three different rhinos with three different naked
Ace Ventura's.
Yeah, obviously, this should have happened.
And then, you know, probably one out every four times.
Then a real hippo stomps the stunt man.
And that he's out of commission in the early days of animal
animal kingdom when things were going wrong more often.
Yes, that might have been a more dangerous thing to do.
Yeah, yeah.
And that's serious stuff and harder to laugh off with a with an all righty then.
Right. But the audience still would have appreciated it.
Yeah, so they missed out.
They this this tie in was waiting.
I don't know if they should have bought the rights for more than three weeks.
Yeah, that's.
Yeah, I don't know.
Maybe, you know, maybe there's a chance it'll come back.
Well, obviously, you know, if it was going to happen,
it would have happened to celebrate the release of Ace Ventura, Jr.
Yeah. How many years ago is that?
That was surprisingly long.
I think it was like two thousand nine.
Wow. I was shocked that it was that long ago.
If you've never seen it, there's a they made a kid version of Ace Ventura
called Ace Ventura, Jr.
It was about his son and you know how somebody somebody's son always acts
exactly to a T like their dad
and dresses exactly like them,
even though their dad is not around and will not be around.
They still behave exactly like.
And the thing that I didn't remember about that movie
is that the official name of the movie is Ace Ventura.
Pet Detect. No, wait.
It's Ace Ventura, Jr.
Pet Detective.
It's it's not they didn't like think of a new like a pun
in the way that from from Dumber to Dumber did whatever that was called.
It's just Ace Ventura, Jr.
Pet Detective.
Like they didn't like no joke.
You're not going to add anything there.
I say that makes me suspect that Ace Ventura, Jr.
Pet Detective is not a quality film.
Huh? I'm not some.
I really go and sequels for these.
Ace Ventura, Jr.
Son of the Mask, Dumb and Dumber.
Or we end.
I would I sadly would have to say Dumb and Dumber, too.
Yeah, it went dumb and Dumber, Dumb and Dumber.
Er, and then just Dumb and Dumber, too.
Is that the sequence? OK.
Kind of disavowing Dumb and Dumber a little bit.
And then Cableboy also, of course,
direct DVD Cableboy, the cable guy.
So Simon Burch, Jr., even littler.
The Truman Web series.
That's well, yeah, that's Quibi.
That's that's been out for a little while.
Yeah, that's true.
And the Truman Jr.
show where his son gets trapped in, they they've like been like,
we've got this giant sound stage.
All these people are out of work.
We got to get his kid and drag him back in here.
Right. And then it's about
not Jim.
He's you hear phone call your off screen phone calls
that are probably original Truman.
But he of course, Jim is not in it.
Right, of course. Right.
And the kids, the kids web,
the kids thing is a streaming it airs on a streaming platform
that the kid cannot access.
Yeah, I like that.
But they had to make up like other streaming platforms
to replace it, like there's entire other things
just to complete the ruse for Truman Jr.
They should team up all.
There should be a big crossover between all of these little Jim Carrey's.
The Avengers of all of all the little Jims. Yeah.
Oh, I've got another one.
The the number 24, the sequel to the number 23.
That will know it should be prequel.
It should be before you think it should be 22.
Yeah. Yeah. Let's keep let's keep blue.
So it should be like it should be like eight.
It should just be called eight.
Hmm.
Well, he was literally really little.
Like 15 years earlier, he was obsessed with the number eight.
Just call it eight.
Well, but then people might be confused.
People might think that's the prequel to the Fellini movie Eight and a Half,
which itself inspired the musical and movie musical Nine.
You know.
And how does it and both of those are related to the movie Ten, right?
With Derek. Yes.
I assume all the numbers are.
Oh, my God.
The numbers.
Ocean's 11, of course, then is next.
Yes. And before all of it, lucky numbers, Levin, of course,
still counts even with a misspell. Right.
13, 13.
The shocking your teens are having sex movie 13.
I don't know if it might stop after that.
I'm not sure.
No, it's not.
Aerosmith Nine Lives album.
The sequel to 13, of course, is 13 going on 30.
Oh, yeah.
That's right. Yes.
And don't forget our pal Kevin Spacey in nine lives.
Oh, yeah.
It's all if you watch all these in the correct numerical order,
they are it's all one big story.
The number of the number verse.
Yeah, the number verse.
If you can make all the connections, you get into like a number
23 type of psychosis of like that is showing up everywhere.
Don't you see it's all the same, man?
It's one thing, man. 24 hour party people.
It's one movie.
Well, that's good.
Hey, we left people with a good theory to investigate.
You know, when you're as you're bored in quarantine times,
if it's still quarantine times, when you're hearing this.
Yeah. Watch all the watch the watch the full number verse. Yeah.
And, you know, I guess watch a video of this Ace Ventura
stunt show if you want, maybe.
But we might have we might have done it for you.
Just watch and see if you think it's bats.
Let us know.
Hashtag is it bats? Hashtag is it bats?
And then just you know what?
Everyone watched I've news clips online.
Yeah. Do your homework, as well.
I for the probably soon to come, I have a news episode. Yeah.
Yeah. All right. That in the next 24 hours.
All right.
Yeah. All righty, then.
That'll do it.
Yeah. And does wait, does he have a goodbye catchphrase?
I don't know that he does really.
Huh?
I mean, what if I don't see you?
Good afternoon, good evening and good night.
Perfect. All right. All right.
All right. So long.