Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, the second gate,
where today we're in treat country.
I'm Jason Sheridan, joined digitally
by Mike Carlson.
Mm, smell the fresh air of treat country.
Mm, delicious.
The freshly mined fudge.
It's mined, fudge is mined?
It's extracted.
I guess it's kind of like the consistency of oil,
so I guess extracted.
Like, is it fracked?
Can you frack fudge?
Oh, boy.
Let's introduce Scott Gardner before we get into this,
because yeah, this is a conversation I could have all day.
Yeah, hi, and there is mythology about this,
and I was scrambling right before we started
and discovering some recent factoids
about the logistics of the Keebler tree,
including that they call it the fact tree.
Yes.
The fact tree, so it's T-R-E-E at the end.
Yes, yeah, that's late breaking for me.
Do you have the diagram, the drawing
that goes down into the earth?
I do not.
I'm very glad that you do.
Okay.
But you drilled deeper in your research, in fact.
Well, you know, I gotta give a lot of credit
to Advertising Week, because they,
very in-depth series on the Keebler universe.
Yeah, they seem to, is that the primary reason
for that publication existing?
Yeah, I think, you know, convincing people
within advertising that advertising is moral and good,
and that they're doing something, right?
I mean, hey, there's no argument for me
on it being moral and good when we're dealing
with these magical creatures who help deserts
taste uncommonly good.
Sure.
Yeah, no, this, look, the Keebler elves,
I think of them in the same way.
I think of great heroes in American history.
I think of, you know, who are the greatest heroes
in American history?
Well, George Washington, Abraham Lincoln,
Buckets, the Keebler elf.
Patrick Henry, that's a guy, right?
Patrick Henry, yes.
The furniture.
Thomas O'Leary.
What?
I don't know.
Thomas O'Leary?
Was he the cow guy?
Oh, Mrs. O'Leary?
Were they related to Thomas O'Leary and Mrs. O'Leary?
I'm not sure.
Are you excited?
Sounds Irish though.
This is a hero from a different land.
I don't know if he counts.
I'm thinking of Mrs. O'Leary who had the cow
that knocked over the candle that started the Chicago fire,
which I guess is not a hero in American history,
if I think about it.
I guess I'm sounding like an idiot now.
Did a cow also knock over a vial and cause COVID-19?
Oh, yeah, whose cow was it?
It's not a question of was it a cow, it's whose cow was it.
Yeah, I didn't even acknowledge that that was the actual fact.
I just said yes, I agreed with you
and started speculating on the owner of the cow
that created this horrible virus.
We gotta find this cow and if not kill it,
then just punish it, just make it feel real bad.
Shame it.
Yes, yeah.
Shame a cow.
Cancel the cow, you are canceled.
The first cow that's been canceled.
What you caused.
Yeah, should Mrs. O'Leary's cow have been canceled
for starting the Chicago fire?
I think so, but they didn't have that word back then.
Yeah, you might say that canceling was not a thing,
but now that it is a thing, Mrs. O'Leary's cow,
you are most definitely canceled.
Yeah, although now that I think about it,
the cow probably perished in the fire.
So I guess that happened.
Anyway, that's too dark.
That's too dark, yeah.
We'll save that for the full Mrs. O'Leary's cow episode.
We've done a cow episode already on the second gate.
We have.
Oh, you're right, second cow episode.
Wow, second cow on the second gate.
That Kamini moo definitely not canceled,
unless you consider dying being canceled.
It kind of do.
I'm not sure.
I think it's if you die,
you can be canceled post death, such as Michael Jackson,
but I think people sometimes are more of heroes
in their death.
So you wouldn't call that being canceled.
Yeah, that's true.
Which is true of the Keebler elves,
if they ever passed away, and let's pray that they don't.
No, I think they're immortal.
Yeah, seemingly, although somewhere in the mythology
in looking into this, I believe that when these ads debuted
in the late 60s, it was not the same elves
that we see today.
That doesn't negate that they're immortal.
You're 100% right.
Those 60s Keebler elves all looked like
they had been in the war.
They looked hardened.
They looked like either World War II or Korea.
They had seen some shit before they came back
to the home front.
They came back to America.
They got good paying factory union jobs.
But they all look like when the comedian Todd Glass
does that joke about how his father used to smoke
and he scrunches up his face real tight.
That's what the Keebler elves look like in the 60s.
I'm not familiar enough.
Do we think that if they are immortal
and if this factory has been running for a long time,
was it started in the 50s in a post-war,
now we can enjoy ourselves and eat cookies,
or did it exist before and during the war
it converted to make artillery and bullets?
I'd like to think they were helping with the war effort.
I think probably, probably with small things like shells.
There's no room to build a tank in the tree
unless there's a subterranean area
and we'll get into that.
But yeah, I think they made little stuff.
Yeah, like they were rationing sugar and flour
during World War II.
So all of the baked goods companies switched
to small caliber bullets,
similar to how all breweries switched to dairy goods,
milk and ice cream during prohibition.
Makes sense.
Did they make fudge bullets?
Well, my question was,
did the shells have a chocolate shell on them?
I think that maybe just out of habit,
that's what they were doing.
So if you were shot by one of these,
that would hurt because it's coming at you full force.
It would kill you.
But if you just picked up a chocolate shell bullet
off the ground and ate it as a snack later,
then deliciousness is your reward.
Yeah, exactly.
It's like if you jumped from very high up
and you landed in the ocean and you got hurt
because you were so high up, it's the velocity.
Water itself is delightful to jump into.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, similar also to keep it in fudge factory terms,
it's buckets.
Buckets, as I'm sure we all learned, spreads the fudge.
But if you dove, yes, from an airplane
into one of buckets of fudge,
then that would hurt very much.
Right, yes.
That is exactly the, yes.
You're 100, as Jason said, you're 100% right.
If you fell into the fudge river,
I believe there is a fudge river.
I assume, Jason, it seems like you discovered
all this same stuff, perhaps via advertising weekly.
Yeah, it seems like, well, deep underneath the tree,
there's a fudge spring.
And I texted you guys, there's a cutaway illustration
and you can see them getting the fudge.
There is a fudge submarine in the underground.
Oh, I had to miss the fudge submarine.
Oh my God.
If you look closely, I guess that's an aqua filter,
is that what that's called?
The underground reservoir, essentially.
They've got some advanced technology,
but then they've also got classic buckets
pulling the fudge up.
Yeah, it's a mix of high tech and ingenious low tech.
I mean, yeah, oh my God, what a delight to check my phone
and see what you'd passed along.
That, okay, there's the tree up above the earth,
but then down in the core, it keeps going and going
and like widens out to be twice the width of the tree.
And there's so much going on in there.
Yeah, big like revolving bucket machine and conveyor belts.
It's hard to read the writing.
This is like a quickly drawn sketch.
I think this like came to Ernie the elf in a dream.
He and just like, all right, let me just get it down
or I'm gonna forget.
But there's a baking room, there's a spread the fudge room.
What's the bottom, is it described as a fudge spring?
Yeah, to the left in the picture, it says fudge spring,
but it's clearly pooling.
I have another picture too that says the hollow tree
also has a deck where the gang gathers to celebrate
fresh baked townhouse crackers
and seems to only be accessible via trap door.
So that's a little bit of confusing planning on their part.
Is this, are these drawings going to haunt your dreams
like Richard Dreyfus in the, what's the movie?
Close encounters.
Close encounters of the third kind, yes.
I start building the tree.
Like you're gonna be just building tree
and building a fudge submarine.
I think you know the answer to that.
When Jason's eating his mashed fudge for dinner,
he will form the shape of the fudge tree
in the subterranean fudge mine.
Before we get too far, should we just remind everyone
like the impetus, like what inspired us to do this?
Well, this was our second, we're currently recording,
this is the second time we've recorded
during the 2020 quarantine.
And the first time we recorded,
Mike was eating the old fudge cookies.
Yes.
Yeah, I haven't had them in a few years.
I don't have treats in the house,
but when I put an order in for the grocery store,
I said, you know what, let's do something fun.
And I got a yellow fudge.
This was when you were in like a pit,
you're thinking I'm maybe loading up
for who knows how long groceries could be tough to get,
only necessities and I need them fast if I'm to survive.
And you put on that list EL fudge cookies.
Yes, 100% that is what I did.
That wasn't the first thing I added.
I may have put like, you know,
peanut butter or like oatmeal first,
but maybe four or five, fourth or fifth.
Yeah, yeah.
It makes sense because desserts and treats
have certainly been helping me get through all this.
And I've had a high preponderance of,
it's been like chips and salty snacks
and stuff I don't usually have at home,
but at the moment, fuck it.
I'll be honest, I haven't had much of an appetite.
I have lost like four pounds in two weeks.
Well, congrats.
Yeah, thank you.
Yeah, thanks, it's great.
Has Jason's treat intake increased or stayed the same,
that being that there's like 10 chocolate buckets
in your apartment at any given time.
Yeah, I think my intake has stayed the same,
but I kind of went on a buying, not a buying spree,
but I definitely stocked up.
I was surprised though, because there has been,
the stores have been well stocked with like treats.
You know, you always hear during times of trouble,
people go for like salty and sweet snacks quickly, you know?
So I thought, but Trader Joe's has been pretty well stocked.
Well, I think, yeah, there's been not a lot of,
all the pictures I see are the toilet paper gone,
the water's gone, the milks are gone.
They're not showing pictures of the aisles
of like all the Nabisco cookies are gone.
I think so far people have maybe only gotten,
like their priority was maybe essential things, I guess.
Yeah.
I guess.
But maybe there's more, maybe there's just more stock,
I don't know.
This by Mike Bear mentioning,
I did a little Google hang with a friend of the show,
Buzz Buzz, and he pointed out that he had to do a target run
in a pinch like, oh, I better actually stock up.
And the only thing resembling like milk or something like,
like liquid with nutrition in it
was something called Ripple.
There was a shelf that was full of so much Ripple.
And one of the boasting points of Ripple
was that it is high in ripatine.
What?
I don't know.
But if anyone out there, if you're feeling low on ripatine,
if you have children with you within this trying time
and they're running out of ripatine,
I do have the product for you.
The good people of Ripple have presumably just
are overstocking the shelves.
It can't be that there's no interest in Ripple.
Well, I hadn't thought about my ripatine levels,
but now I won't be able to sleep.
It's the first thing to go and you can't go outside.
You get it from the sun.
So all of us being cooped up,
we're not soaking up sweet ripatine.
Maybe there's ripatine in EL fudges.
Could be.
I gotta go-
In this chocolate.
I mean, this isn't a controversial opinion,
but I'm gonna say EL fudges, one of the goats,
one of the greatest of all times when it comes to cookies,
at least like big mass produced cookies, delicious fudge,
solid cookies in the shape of fun elves,
but that shortbread isn't overwhelming.
Sometimes I find Milano's,
like you're tasting so much cookie
and not enough chocolate kit.
You don't really have that problem with EL fudge.
Right, and they also have double EL fudges now.
Well, I like that.
I didn't know that.
Yeah.
Were you wearing a hat and did it blow off when I said that?
Unfortunately, all of the recording equipment
has blown across the room.
So my channel is gonna sound like shit for a while
while I collect myself.
Let's do a little, like before we get into the elves
and what they're like and who their best friends are,
maybe let's do a little,
like just our relationship with these cookies
and a little history of the actual company.
Does that sound like a decent spot to start?
Yes, yeah.
I mean, obviously like Keebler cookies, a big staple
at all of our childhoods, I assume?
Yeah.
I would say so.
I'd say so.
I haven't like thought about them or had them
in a long time and truly there was a big just spark of joy
when you brought them up the other day.
I feel like my grandma got them for me the most.
I think, you know, that's a little like treat that,
you know, way that parents and grandparents
can differentiate themselves,
those treats that are only at grandma's house.
And I believe that EL fudges were only at grandma's house.
Interesting.
And fruit by the foot.
That's what I remember.
Really, grandma would buy fruit by the foot?
Yeah, she knew I liked that.
And I think my parents didn't wander around all the time.
So yeah, grandma's house is a special place
where I got fruit by the foot.
Where I ordered fruit in a different way.
I feel like fruit by the foot
was not on my grandmother's radar.
I think maybe I made her aware.
Maybe I just like was talking about it
for, you know, half an hour one day.
And then it has shapes.
And then as a reward for eating it,
you get like trivia games and mazes.
Isn't that right?
Like you peeled it off and there'd be
you know, like little stuff on the paper.
I just think that like fruit by the foot
was too new of an innovation for my grandmother
to be aware of it.
Not that, I mean, she, you know,
she used to more of a traditionalist
when it came to like snacks.
We would have the like chessmen cookies at her house.
Oh, of course.
And those are a classic cookie.
My grandmother's tended to be whatever kind
of like basic snack you could think of blank.
Like chips or cookies, but stale.
So chips, but stale.
Cookies, but stale.
Because she would like have like chip clips or whatever,
but would never quite put them on very good.
So everything would just get a little stale or soft.
Yeah, that's, I feel like what's funny about it,
is that my grandmother would have like
a lot of expired salad dressings.
And a couple of years ago, I went home to visit my parents
and I noticed they had about five expired salad dressings.
And I was like, oh, you're turning into your parents.
It's happening.
It's, yeah, it's happening.
The more, yeah, if your parents have a bunch of like packets,
if you start, you know, having a lot of packets
in the drawers, that's maybe not a good sign.
Yeah, like three-year-old packets.
Yeah, yeah.
Like, you know, hot sauces from, or like, you know, like,
what P.F. Chang's gives you to go for many years.
Like I might use this sweet and sour sauce in seven years.
Yes, so I think, now you've got me thinking.
I don't think we had a lot of Keebler at my grandmother's
house as much as we had at home.
I think it was more of a home base, Keebler.
Jason, where were you at as a family?
I mean, I love the Keebler commercials.
And I think we would get it sometimes.
I feel like we defaulted to Nabisco a lot.
Or, I mean, Little Debbie is the cheap,
Little Debbie is barely food.
Like they can barely charge for that.
There is so little actual food in it.
But my, the portions.
So we would definitely have Keebler stuff.
My memory watching, Scott, you had found a compilation
of commercials and stuff, and then that just auto-played
a million other commercials.
That brought back a big memory for me,
which was the 90s trend of something that's like a chip,
but not quite a chip.
Like everything was so, there was like a war
to sell chip alternatives.
Like it's a cracker, but it crunches like a chip.
Like chips were insanely popular,
but everyone knew they were bad for them.
So everyone would be like,
well, this cracker's a little better.
That said, as a child, I think I was about 90% pizzerias,
if you remember.
Those commercials were in here.
Pizzerias were like the cracker chip pizza flavored one.
And I loved those.
Oh man, we were, I'd never heard of pizzerias
until watching this commercial now.
And I was so grossed out by the idea of them.
I don't think I ever had them either.
Yeah, I had them a lot.
Had them a lot.
You will.
They don't make, is there any,
what is the closest thing that is made that's like these?
Do we know?
Like that exists today?
Only like Pringles and Combos
have like pizza flavored anything anymore.
Pizza, I hated everything pizza flavored.
I don't think it's a reproducible.
The flavor was so far off.
It was some other thing that didn't resemble pizza.
Well, I think I agree with that.
Pizzerias were the exception though.
They were really good.
Missed out.
Well, we'll be covering pizzerias
because that is the main source of,
that's where JJ and Zoot factor in, the young people.
Gen Z of the Keebler factory.
And Dude?
There is a, is there Micro?
Was Micro one of the newer ones too?
Well, he had the shrink powers.
He would shrink stuff down.
He had shrinking powers, right.
But no, let's do a quick history.
A quick history before we get into the else.
Quick history, yeah.
Sure.
It was started by Godfrey Keebler,
Godfrey Keebler of German descent.
He started it in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania in 1853.
Does that make the pride?
Did you know that Jason?
I did not know that.
A lot of bakeries, Philadelphia had a big bakery business.
My grandfather was a security guard,
bakery and confectionary.
My grandfather was security guard at the Whitman's factory.
Whitman's samplers.
I know, yeah, yeah.
So did you ever encourage him to, you know,
get into those places where he's not supposed to sneak into
and bust out some treasured goods
for his beloved grandson?
I mean, I would have, I think he had retired.
I think that was, he was the kind of guy
who had like a million jobs.
I think he had retired by that point.
He may have known where the Chocolate River was though.
That's true. The chocolate stream.
Yeah, yeah.
So they opened the bakery in 1853,
his bakery network with several other local bakeries
around the country over the years.
And then in 1927, they merged into
the United Biscuit Company of America.
Hell yeah.
United Biscuit. You absolutely,
you love to see it.
God bless the UBCA.
The stars and the cook, the fudge,
the fudge stars and fudge stripes.
United Biscuit.
And then, you know, there's some, some business stuff there.
And then they, oh, and they made Girl Scout cookies in 1936.
The official baker of Girl Scout cookies.
Oh really?
Not always, but when they started.
I think it says here by 1978,
four companies were producing cookies.
So Little Brownie Bakers is the Keebler division
that still is licensed to produce the cookies.
The Little Brownie Bakers.
Now I think the actual bakers of Girl Scout cookies
might vary by region.
I think that might be correct, yes.
I think the Carmel Delights, is that their current name?
The ones that used to be called Samosas.
Some stuff is called different stuff in different regions
and tastes a little different, apparently.
So Keebler basically, they like changed hands a lot
and then they were acquired by Kellogg in 2001.
Oh, I didn't realize that.
But there's some new,
there's a lot of different changing hands of this brand.
But I believe, did anyone catch this?
The last thing is that they were sold to the people
who make Nutella?
Oh, interesting.
Let me find this.
I have too many, again, I said too many notes
for the Keebler company and the elves.
Too many things, too many things.
Too many things.
Keebler sale, Ernie Keebler and his cookie factory
housed in a tree are being bought by the Ferrero Group,
makers of Nutella.
And that is from last year.
Okay. The Ferrero Group.
The Ferrero Group.
Is that the German company that owns Los Pueos Hermanos
where the guy killed himself
with the heart-zapping machine?
Yes, that is the same.
That is the exact same, yes.
This is April 1st, 2019, or 2019, yeah, 2019.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
And that's Kellogg sells Keebler snacks to Ferrero
for $1.3 billion.
Wow.
And they also got the six US manufacturing plants
in the deal.
All that history is important backstory,
but the main thing to say is that when they started
making cookies in 1853, it was reported
that there were elves on the scene
and that those were the ancestors
of the famous Keebler elves known today.
That is some official copy that I read,
which again implies that they are not immortal.
If there's such a thing as ancestors,
unless you just hit kind of an age
where you're no good to make them anymore,
and then you just like live out
thousands of years in retirement.
Well, you know what?
I know elves and gnomes aren't the same thing,
but as we've discussed on the show, David the Gnome,
the finale of David the Gnome is that the cartoon series
from, I guess, the 80s is that David and his wife
essentially die in the finale
and become one with the earth.
So maybe it is similar with the elves.
I would think.
That they go somewhere and they make their pet watch
while they die, which is what David the Gnome did
with his pet fox, Swift, as Swift watched in horror
as David and his wife turned into trees.
I have to think it's somewhere between a Viking funeral
or the end of the Lord of the Rings
where they just get on a boat and sail away into the horizon.
They did, you know, when it's an elves time to go,
they just get on a boat and an arrow is shot at it
that's on fire and it just slowly burns up
and then sinks into the fudge spring
and then they become fudge.
So we're eating the elves, really.
It's like the circle of life.
It's like the antelope eat the grass after the lions die.
Either that or there's a transference of energy
and they just get shot with the rainbow cannon
and they become energy.
Well, a lot of the cookies look like elves.
There is that one variety.
So it is that could be that we are,
those are like sarcophagi and the fudge inside is them
that you are eating their body.
Oh, like the stone soldiers in China.
Like that tomb that has all those stone soldiers.
Exactly, yes.
The Terracotta army, I believe.
Yeah.
And just to mention P.F. Chang's for the second time.
Yeah, if you see those statues outside of every P.F. Chang's,
those contain the actual remains of soldiers.
Big statues like that ever since I was a kid
and I saw Ghostbusters and the animals,
the statues in front of the New York Public Library
come to life.
That always freaked me out as a kid.
And I was like, I don't like those big animal statues.
Could happen, could happen anywhere.
It could happen.
And those, and every cookie you bite into
could come to life if you, again, if you wait long enough.
So it's imperative that you chomp them all
as quickly as you can. That you gobble them down.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, hurry up or they'll swarm.
They'll drag your whole body down.
Mike, you brought up a good point
that they are different than gnomes.
And in fact, in the copy that I was just reading
right above it, that specifically is specified.
And this is coming from Ernie, the primary Keebler elf.
Ernie wants to be clear that the Keebler elves
are not leprechauns, gnomes, or dryads.
Dryads I've never heard before.
That's new mythology to me.
I had to look up a picture of what one was.
They are freakier than elves are, certainly.
What are they, they're in, I'm looking,
and then folklore and Greek mythology.
It's a nymph inhabiting a forest or a tree.
Oh.
Not inhabit, not like bringing,
it's not like if a tree is alive
and a dryad is what's operating it.
Like if you live in the forest, you're a dryad.
Are there any dryads in fiction?
That's what I'm looking for.
I'm trying to, there's like, there's pictures of them,
but I'm trying to see, like, who's the most famous dryad?
Examples of dryads.
They're mentioned in Paradise Lost.
Yeah, but I'm looking for like what
the DreamWorks movie is about dryads.
When is there gonna be a dryads movie?
They're in The Chronicles of Narnia.
Well, they're in Barbie Fairytopia.
I know that.
They're in Lev Grossman's The Magician's Trilogy,
which I believe became the TV show The Magicians.
Hmm. Right?
Okay.
Yes, yeah, the Syfy Channel show.
But that said, there's an area,
I mean, it feels like in a couple years, you know,
we could be seeing a DreamWorks,
or maybe I should keep this to myself
and go pitch it to DreamWorks, but like,
we'll be driving by a billboard that says dryads
with a huge list of celebrities playing,
all playing the different dryads.
We got Meghan Trainor in there, Kumail,
Kumail's doing a dryad.
Yep, yep. The Baby.
Oh, sure, The Baby would make a great dryad.
The Baby, King Princess, Billy Eilish, all the young people.
If you're, yeah, if you're a pop star and you're under 18,
it's imperative that you play a dryad.
Jojo,
Siwa, Siwa, how do you say it?
Oh, sure, yeah, yeah.
And then like Alan Arkin.
Yeah, yeah, there's gotta be an old cranky dryad.
Absolutely.
He obviously gets the and credit, and Alan Arkin.
End of the list.
There's Potts.
Oh, I'm seeing here that male,
like dryads are usually female,
and the male counterpart to dryads are called Druze.
Druze, how do you spell Dru?
D-R-U-S.
Druze I have heard of.
What, why?
You know.
It rhymes with Gru, it's spelled like Gru.
I realize I don't wanna get off on too much of a tangent.
I didn't realize there was another Minions movie
coming out this year that's called The Rise of Gru.
Well, yeah, it's gonna rise.
It's all rise, everyone's rising in these movies.
Everyone's rising, you see the end of the-
And the rise.
At the end of the first Minions, they meet Child Gru,
and now they are, I think, learning, feeling each other out,
figuring stuff out.
And this is Gru's rise.
Yeah, this is his rise
to become an all-powerful super villain.
So it'll be like the end of Rise of Skywalker,
and he'll name himself,
or he'll say, I'm evil or something at the end.
No, your last name.
I don't have one.
Is that a good Gru?
That's a pretty good Gru.
I don't have a last name.
Jason, could you say that line as Stitch real quick?
Yeah, hold on.
Okay.
Hold on.
He's gotta prepare.
It's trick and water.
Yep.
Or he just left.
Jason Sherwin's left.
I don't have a last name.
That's great.
I think Jason as Stitch just sounded like Gru.
Yeah.
That's kind of my point is that
Stitch kind of sounds like Gru.
And a little like Subulba.
That's true too.
Anyway, that all to say,
so let's be very clear.
The Keeper Elves are not dryads.
Not dryads.
They're also not shoemakers, fairies, or sprites.
They're a uniquely American strain of elves.
Gotta love hearing the word strain
at this point in time.
They're not leprechauns either
because one of the commercials leprechauns show up.
A lot of people show up in the commercials
and inconvenience the elves or deny their existence.
I have a list here.
Leprechauns, cops,
a reoccurring pest named Dude.
What's Dude?
What kind of person is Dude?
Dude is a teenager, like a cool teenager.
I think he was a recurring character in the 90s
where they just gave up.
Yeah, I mean, he's pretty cool.
He looks like Roy from The Simpsons,
the one episode character from the Poochy episode.
Of course, yeah.
There's a skydiver shows up at one point
and they all show up at the kitchen,
tree, door, demanding answers from the elves.
Yeah, and then when Ernie comes out on the perch,
on the porch or whatever, the veranda,
and he seems to be the size of their head.
He's pretty surprisingly big.
I find the scale weird.
I feel like the size of the tree changes a lot from ad to ad.
They really need to pick a scale.
Maybe the Ferrero group will really clamp down
on the mythology.
Yeah, Task 1 standardized the scale.
I also saw some ads where my favorite interrupter
at the factory is like a kind of like a,
he's like a Euro, you know, like Playboy,
gadfly, like old race car driver, like the kind of guy.
He's got like, you know, a mustache and a long nose
and a big scarf, just like cool cocky as hell,
50s race car driver.
Oh, I saw, yes, I saw him.
Yeah.
These side characters are really good
for a commercial especially.
We don't have a ton of information about that.
I mean, well, I guess we just said the information
about that, but there's no further information
about them or where they came from,
but the elves, there's certainly a ton.
Right, and like, unlike maybe Chuck E. Cheese,
which does have a lot of like extra material,
there's not a ton of extra material outside
of the commercials and the packages for these characters.
Yeah.
They never did some like McDonald's style,
let's make a home video or a video game.
They didn't really expand in any significant way.
Well, okay.
I did find evidence of some sort of little extra thing
that anyone, does anyone know what I'm talking about?
No. No.
I have found that there is some sort of 22 minute
anti-drug Keibler elf video out there from the 1980s.
Perfect. Oh boy.
There's an article about it in the Chicago Tribune
from 1986 about a 22 minute video
where the Keibler elves convince kids not to take drugs.
Ironically, getting them hooked on sugar,
which they say is more addictive to kick than some drugs.
And more likely that a kid would have a problem with it
than like crack.
Yes.
Apparently, it might be based on a puppet show
that was staged in 10 cities.
I believe that's what this article is saying.
And the tape has a three pronged plot.
The first part shows a,
I don't know why they have to mention this,
a pretty and talented girl confessing to Ernie
that she feels pressured to be the best of all time.
The second segment shows a track star
who is tempted to use drugs to win a race,
but is shown by Ernie that people like him for what he is.
People will like him for what he is,
not for him being on drugs.
This is also a weirdly written article.
The last segment points to an 11 year old girl's
misconception about the use of drugs.
She fears her older brother is on drugs,
but through elfin magic,
Ernie allows her to overhear her brother talking to a friend.
And this is what her brother says.
I'd break my sister's neck if she ever got on drugs,
but she's too smart for that, the older brother says.
Jesus, like a Bane kind of statement.
I'd break my sister's neck if she ever did drugs.
I'll kill her.
You think drugs hurt you, I'll show you hurt.
So we have to find this video.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
It doesn't appear to be on YouTube,
but somebody has to have it.
Fuck.
I, oh my God.
Like, yeah, walking in, the guy walking in on his sister,
like slightly puffing a joint.
Don't you realize what that could do to you?
That could cause permanent damage.
Cracks her neck.
He was serious.
It's where you were headed anyway.
You know what's scarier than drugs?
Me threatening to murder you.
And then, yeah, so imagine all that,
and then imagine like Ernie Keebler counseling her.
I mean, he is like a good guy.
Like Ernie Keebler, I mean, he's a real, he's a king,
you know, he's a good guy.
They did have a profile essentially,
like a 10 things you didn't know about Ernie Keebler
in advertising week.
I got some good stuff out of there.
His nickname is Mr. Sincerity.
When life gets Ernie down,
he responds with his three favorite folksy expressions.
Mercy, gracious,
and what in tarnation,
which I know I can relate to.
Yeah, I saw that same fact,
and I was thinking how you should make a point of,
if you can remember, to switch your default profanity
or exclamation to be what in tarnation.
I know my mother would prefer that.
Like all of our mothers, yes.
My favorite fact about Ernie
is that the marketing people created this.
Just as Maslow's hierarchy of needs
has been established for humans,
so has Keebler created quote, need states for Ernie.
His five biggest needs include.
What?
What in tarnation?
His need states, you know, he needs socialization,
nurturing, relaxation, indulgence,
and fun slash creativity.
What?
Isn't this weird?
Like, he's not my baby.
I don't have to raise.
No, he's your God.
You should be telling me about needs states.
I don't think I'm getting them.
I wanna be like him.
Jason, do you have a picture of him in the house,
like how Catholics would have a picture of Kennedy?
Jason bows down and says, gracious.
Jason, are those your picture of grandparents?
Oh no, that's Ernie Keebler and Little Debbie.
Your slash fiction between Little Debbie and Ernie Keebler.
And they're gigantic,
like those portraits of the knots at Knots Barrymore.
Oh, Little Debbie, you fulfill all of my needs states.
Let me look, is there any slash fiction
involving the Keebler elves or Little Debbie in general?
You know, yeah, I didn't get around to looking that up.
Did you guys look up the multiple actors who have voiced him?
I sure did.
I did.
I got a lot about one.
Okay, good, cause I didn't, there were so many credits
and so many friends.
We haven't even gotten to the friends yet, but if you ask.
Let's cover Ernie, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, the main thing,
well, there's two interesting things in the credits list.
His current voice is a guy named Richard Hensel
and Richard Hensel is primarily known in media
as the guy, the first guy of the two who says,
okay, campers rise and shine
and don't forget your booties cause it's cold out there.
The DJs in Groundhog Day, the first one,
I believe it's the first one is the current voice
of Ernie the Keebler elf.
Yes.
That's a pretty fun crossover, I feel.
The most interesting one to me though
is his original voice, Parley Bayer.
Did anyone else look into Parley?
Rhymes with Marley, Parley Bayer.
I get a little bit.
They all had interesting careers,
all of these like character actors.
Yeah, yeah.
He has got an odd thing where he plays
several notable racists in media.
There's like where he's like a racist who gets redeemed
or learns his lesson.
One where he's like teaching a dog to be racist
and then another one where it's an episode
of a very special episode of Bewitched
where he is Darren's racist boss.
Were you familiar with this before?
I have not seen this episode, but he's not Larry Tate,
that was Darren's boss.
So he's a different boss?
He's a client probably.
Oh, maybe so, okay, okay.
Cause you, Darren work, of course Darren worked
at an advertising company, we all know that.
Sure, yes.
And it's, yeah, it's this strange, I mean,
I don't even, we don't even need to get into it,
but it's a weird where he like, he mistakes
like a friend of what Tabatha's the daughter,
he mistakes like somebody who's over at the house
for being their daughter and he thinks,
is this an interracial family?
And he has a problem with that.
So Samantha puts a spell on him to where he sees everyone
as black and he learns a lesson about racism that way.
Very bizarre episode and considered important at the time,
so much so that it had like a message from a star
of Bewitched, Elizabeth Montgomery,
and she's delivering this message in front of a sign
that says Oscar Meyer because they were the sponsor
that night.
So she gives an opening speech about like tonight's episode
my friends at Oscar Meyer and I believe
that tonight's episode can teach you a little something.
Well, you've got my attention.
We gotta watch that episode.
Yeah, the clips are pretty bonkers.
But anyway, that's the- It sounds like it's good,
their heart was in the right place, that's good.
Oh, it seems really, yeah, and for the 60s
to devote an episode to racial tolerance,
yeah, is fantastic.
And to get our pals at Oscar Meyer involved.
But the main thing that I have to say about Parley Bayer
is that he apparently was, before the war,
he was a circus ringmaster and in doing so,
he met and married a trapeze artist and bareback writer
who stayed his wife his whole life.
Then he went to war, then came back
and got sort of a related job as a wild animal trainer
at a place that is difficult for me to talk about
because that place is called Jungleland USA.
That's in Thousand Oaks, California.
And do you remember why Jungleland USA is notable?
Oh, I'm trying to remember.
No, say it.
Jungleland USA was the primary home base
of a fellow named- Oh, yeah, yes.
Yes.
Chukko.
Yes, yes, I knew.
And I knew when you said that.
Yes. Yep.
Yes, yeah.
Wow.
I, it's obviously, I'm shaken to even discuss this right now,
but some of the pure unadulterated evil at Jungleland USA
caused by the presence of Chukko,
I think is offset by my good pal Parley Bayer,
the voice of Ernie the elf being around.
Wow, man.
Do you think, side note,
do you think a full Chukko episode is better
if we're sequestered, if we're separated,
or do we have to wait until we're all together again
for the Chukko episode to finally happen?
Oh, dear God.
I don't, well, I don't know if I wanna be alone.
Oh, yeah, that's a good point.
Chukko may visit us.
Exactly, that's exactly what I was thinking.
And if you say his name three times,
then I'm gonna be stuck here alone with him.
Oh my God, let's, oh, oh, wait a minute, wait a minute.
I have, I maybe have the best idea I've had ever.
Let's do a digital seance to summon Chukko.
The podcast.
I will look up how to do a seance,
we'll all light candles,
and we will try to talk to Chukko
and see if we can get him to make peace with Scott.
Oh my God.
Look, if there was, my first objection is,
if there's anybody who's just full of pure COVID,
I think it's Chukko.
I think I want him to get tested before this,
before he's gonna end up in my body.
He's a spirit.
But we don't know how far this reaches.
I don't know.
We know dogs can't get it, but what about spirits?
Look, I don't know the answer to that.
We'll ask him.
We'll ask him when we do the seance.
We get five minutes in and Scott's like,
there is a single red balloon
floating outside of my window.
Oh my gosh, okay, even better, okay,
even better idea that I just had.
We're recording this a little bit before
we're gonna do our first Twitch live show.
How about we do it on Twitch and all the listeners,
all the listeners light a candle with us
and we all try to summon Chukko.
Oh God.
That's a lot of people.
We need to get out of this sequester as quickly as we can.
This is, you know, this is a great-
Scott develops a vaccine real quick.
I figured it out.
I don't know, it just came through me.
It chapter one and two where big hits,
Candy Man is coming back.
I think it's time for Chukko to come.
Digital seance.
I know we like bringing back obscure IP,
but this isn't the IP I want back.
Digital seance of summon Chukko, summoning Chukko.
Oh God.
Well, how about this?
Here, I'll add a, what if, as we did this, I took acid.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
Should go fine.
It's probably just chill me out,
not make things horrifyingly worse.
I have a, there's, you know, Ernie Keebler would tell you,
you probably shouldn't do that though.
So what are you, what's gonna happen?
What if I go buy some acid, what are you guys gonna do?
Are you gonna break my neck?
Hmm.
I would break your neck if you did acid.
I would just find the most unpleasant videos
of people reviewing new pretzel carts at theme parks.
Like new pretzel carts, new like bathrooms,
that sort of thing.
That I have to watch them?
And you have to watch them while on acid.
I'll be looking for ones that like the aspect ratio,
like the camera keeps changing,
they're holding their phone vertically,
and then horizontally the audio keeps pitching in and out.
Dear Lord, I'll take the neck break.
Get breaking.
Now I'm quarantined, but I'll just open the door a crack.
Break my neck, please.
Wow.
I've learned my lesson.
Fine, we'll summon Chukko.
We're gonna summon Chukko.
That's exciting.
Digital say.
That's the most excited I've been
since being locked in the apartment, honestly.
Oh no, but I think that for a digital seance to work,
you need like a lot of, you need like a thousand people.
You need like everyone who subscribes to the Patreon, right?
Oh yeah, I think you're right.
Well, that's, there's no way we're gonna get that many.
Oh, I don't know.
Maybe.
We're gonna have to set that number at a certain point.
Let's see what.
Life finds a way.
Yeah.
We gotta pick a stormy night in Los Angeles too.
Oh no, it's storming tonight.
Can we just do it tonight?
Oh God.
I'll announce this on the show tonight on Twitch tonight.
Jesus Christ.
But I have to learn how to do a seance first.
I need to do some sort of prep.
Yeah, whatever.
I'm sure it's very complicated
and requires months worth of prep.
Requires 18 months of prep, by which point,
you know, we'll hopefully be done with this whole thing.
Okay, well it's possible.
It's also possible I have nothing else to do,
so I will learn it very fast.
And then you're just like sending spirits
into bodies all over the city.
Yeah, that'd be cool as shit.
Mike became a witch.
It just took like being in his apartment
for a week and a half.
Whoa, I thought Mike became a dryad, is that wrong?
No, a dru, he's a dru.
A dru, a dru.
He's not a dryad, he's a dru.
Witches are not drues.
Dryad, drues are not dryads.
Basin is now Sanuk.
So that's exciting.
All right, well, I guess, dear God,
let me pray for the vaccine, pray for the vaccine.
Okay, does that cover Ernie?
Should we talk about Ernie's friends?
How do you guys feel about new,
Ernie is kind of smooth, he's kind of CG smooth right now.
How do you guys feel about that?
I don't care for it.
I don't feel good about it.
I think it confuses the age, it muddies it.
Yeah, I think he's kind of less friendly, less jolly.
It looks like he had work done too.
Yeah, kind of does.
It looks like he had some plastic surgery.
He looks younger.
I like him being kind of a Tom Bosley-esque figure.
For sure.
Yeah, be proud of the wrinkles, too you are.
Yeah.
Did we talk about, he was not the original,
it was JJ?
Yeah, I think there was another guy.
Or who was the original leader?
It was not Ernie, JJ Keebler, yeah, in 1969.
JJ Keebler.
He was the original head elf.
And he looked like FDR or something.
He had a much different look.
He looked like kind of a...
Very square.
Yeah, he was not kind of as like cute of a cartoon.
He was almost like a caricature of like
some like captain of industry or something.
Yeah.
But then wait a minute,
but then isn't one of the nephews JJ?
Yes, I believe so.
That's confusing.
It is.
That's probably a little nod.
Yeah, but JJ, the original JJ is not around now.
Yeah, yeah, so they can die.
Well, or retire.
Yeah.
Or maybe JJ is working in a different capacity at Kellogg.
Oh, he's corporate now.
Yeah, he's just not a spokesman anymore, a spokes elf.
Sure, sure.
So yeah, he works in the corporate office
and he does paperwork.
He has to like jump on all the keys
of his computer one at a time.
Right, but he gets it done.
Yeah, yeah, eventually.
Yeah, and he has more fun than we do,
just pecking with our fingers.
Yeah, jumping on a giant keyboard is awesome.
That sounds pretty great.
Well, that's what Rob Dyrdek got to do
on every episode of Ridiculousness.
Of course.
Who could forget?
He had as much fun as a keyboard elf.
Yeah.
Our Carson.
Our Johnny Carson, the most charismatic host.
I think that's really where,
that's why all the shows are shutting down
and there is no like united voice during this crisis.
And yeah, we need Dyrdek to weigh in
and say like, man, this coronavirus is crazy, y'all.
That was a big client at the old post house
I used to work at.
So not only was I running tapes for Ridiculousness
up and downstairs all day,
it was in six different languages, I believe.
Wow. Oh my God.
So there were foreign,
like there's like somebody out there
is the French voice of Rob Dyrdek.
Oh yeah.
And like people would get in trouble
because it's like, no, Latin American Spanish
is different than Castilian Spanish.
Guys, we gotta get this right.
Very important.
Yeah.
French Rob Dyrdek just would play clips
and then say, Sacre bleu.
It's like Lumiere.
Yeah.
So JJ retired,
JJ had the same voice as Fred Flintstone,
Alan Reed senior.
But he's not, they aren't related, I don't believe.
Ernie and JJ?
JJ, yeah.
I don't think so.
There's not a familial relation.
I didn't come across that.
But he does have a mom, the mom is Ma.
Right.
Yeah.
She doesn't really have,
she's kind of just like all the Ma,
she's like granny in Looney Tunes.
She does not much going on character wise with her.
Yeah.
Yeah, there's not too,
yeah, they should really, Ma should have more to do.
I agree.
If that's what you're saying, I agree.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm gonna go through this advertising week 360 list
where they have them alphabetical.
And this is just, you know,
I think this is gonna be educational for everybody
to just like, let's take this downtime
and get educated on who each of them are, their hair color.
So that when we're watching compilations,
we don't get mixed up again.
Let's learn this once and for all
and know who every one of these characters is.
I agree.
Yeah.
No more confusion.
Elmer is the apprentice.
He's the freckly one with kind of a big swirl of red hair.
And he know that he's the apprentice
because he wears the smaller style apprentice hat.
It's not a big puffy chef's hat.
So he's just learning.
Right, so that's how, yeah,
that's how you make the distinction between the like,
professionals and the people that are learning
is the hat size.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Buckets, however, is an established chef.
Buckets reminds me, I'm looking at Buckets right now.
He reminds me a little bit of Jeff Garland.
Okay, I could see what you're saying.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm, a little similarity there.
The thing I say is somebody calls him the muscle
in one of the things I read.
Yes, because he adds so much fudge to the cookie.
A Buckets worth of fudge.
So he's doing the most heavy lifting.
Uh-huh, I like Buckets.
Yeah, I like this guy. I like Buckets too.
Well, we all reap the rewards of what Buckets does for us.
Mm-hmm.
Fast Eddie. Oh yeah.
An elf of few words, just ask him to bake anything.
And before the sentence gets out of your mouth,
he's already off doing it.
He also has red hair.
It's a little confusing,
but he's like twice the size of Elmer.
And he has the real big hat.
Yes, yes, not an apprentice hat.
I think these three and Ernie map pretty well
to the main members of the DeMeo crime family
and the Sopranos.
I think Ernie is clearly Tony.
Elmer is Christopher.
Buckets I think is Polly Walnuts.
And I think the Fast Eddie is Silvio because-
I would switch those around, I think.
You think, but I think Silvio is more,
I think Silvio is more reliable.
Do you think Buckets is more reliable
and trustworthy than Fast Eddie?
I think Fast Eddie though goes so fast.
He's, they're both reliable,
but I think Buckets is steadier than Fast Eddie
because Fast Eddie is impulsive.
Yeah, then that's what you think of with Polly.
So yeah, that's right.
Polly a little more explosive.
Silvio is much more like measured in general.
Yeah, I would agree with that.
Okay, so now that we're glad we squared that away.
Yeah.
But they're all important.
You couldn't do any of this without them.
They're all crucial members at the same time.
Yes, yes, yes.
They're crucial.
The next one on the list, I feel like less so.
Roger?
Roger, something about Roger, I don't know.
I'm getting a bad feeling.
I think he is, I think he is Ralph Zafforetto.
I think he is Joe Pantaleato's unhinged character.
What don't you like about Roger?
I don't know, I just get a weird vibe from him.
Maybe it's the green.
There's a shiftiness to him.
I think he looks nice though.
I was thinking he looks a little bit like Sam Waterston.
I can see that.
Yeah, I see that.
That's fair.
He's a nice guy.
He's a climate change fighter.
If Roger's anything like Sam.
And he's, look, he's been around forever.
I don't know, what a type of a boss is Ernie?
Is Ernie somebody who's gonna keep people around
just because of like loyalty?
Or will he give somebody the axe
if they're not pulling their weight?
I feel like he's gonna give people the axe.
He's nice.
He's, what's his nickname again?
Mr.
Mr. Sincerity.
But obviously-
It's better to tell it like it is.
Yeah, he has to tell it like it is.
So I feel like he wouldn't maybe keep Roger around
unless he was valuable to the team.
I'm the most confused by Roger's role.
Yeah.
Something describes him,
the Wikipedia describes him as the jeweler.
What do you mean the jeweler?
Yeah, what does that?
Is that like putting in the rainbow chocolate chips
for the rainbow cookies?
Yeah.
Rainbow chips deluxe, another goat, another great cookie.
Oh, rainbow chips deluxe.
Oh, I loved rainbow chips deluxe.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So exciting.
So if Roger is jeweling them-
Yes, he's jeweling the cookies.
With chips, then we gotta be, we gotta like this guy.
We gotta like him.
Maybe that breaks the Sopranos metaphor.
Maybe he's more like Adam Sandler in Uncut Chips.
These are real chocolate chips.
Ernie.
Yeah, we got the green and the yellow.
Ernie, I need you to just hold onto these chips for a week.
Just hold on, give me 20%.
I'll give you 20% when I pick it up.
Now we got the spring colors.
We got the different colors for Easter.
The Easter colors were so lovely, I have to say.
I agree.
You gotta bring those back.
These cookies have enough chips already.
They're deluxe enough as they are.
I disagree, I disagree.
I don't think I see them in this list,
but I wanna make sure we hit everybody.
I'm also seeing Sam the peanut butter baker.
Oh, I miss Sam the peanut butter baker.
Yeah.
That's in the Wikipedia.
There's some lists that claim to be exhaustive
that I don't think are.
Right.
In fact, the list I was just looking at
didn't explain that Fast Eddie wraps the products,
which I think we mentioned in our previous episode.
That's a vital role.
Yes. Extremely.
Yeah, that's the whole production line.
Did you come across Leonardo?
Yes, yeah.
Leonardo's the next in the list I'm looking at.
Yeah, and Leonardo factors into the recent CGI ads.
They've still been using him recently.
Right.
And he is the paint, he paints.
Yes.
And he's got a big beret and a paintbrush.
And you gotta say he's a little bit similar to,
from the Duffy Gang, Jelatoni.
Jelatoni, of course.
First thing I thought of.
Yeah.
So it would stand to reason then
that also Leonardo fucks.
Nice.
I think 100%, you can say it, Leonardo fucks.
Yeah, yeah.
Sorry, parents.
We'll start switching to tarnation
as soon as we adjust to it.
Then we got- Next up.
Are you gonna say Doc?
You should say, yeah, you say Doc.
Doc is the character's name.
Wow.
Yes.
Who adds a sprinkling of wisdom into every creation
he makes in the big, what does that mean?
Wisdom.
I don't know.
That seems inessential.
If there's any weak link on the team, I think it's Doc.
Yeah, although now I'm cross-checking with the Wikipedia
and he's described as the doctor.
And then they're extremely crucial these days, obviously.
So maybe they can't get rid of Doc.
He's a dual role guy.
But why is he dressed up as a baker then?
Shouldn't he have like a stethoscope?
No, well, he's the doctor and cookie maker.
Which now, now that sort of bugs me about Ernie
if he's making people double up on jobs.
Right, maybe Ernie isn't as good as we think he is.
Seems possible.
Might be sort of a tyrant the way we discovered
Tony Solaroni is.
Right.
You gotta have some amount of distrust
for before the owner who really controls the press
who puts out these press releases,
who represents the company in media.
So it's all kind of slanted to him
and to make him look like a real hero.
Yeah, that's a good point.
So yeah, who knows what, yeah, we should do some,
we really need to figure out if Doc is being mistreated
at the tree, at the factory.
Mm-hmm.
Cause it's possible.
I mean, a number of elderly employees.
Yes, yes.
And so does that make you question
whether there are robust enough retirement plans
at this factory or do these people just have to,
you know, work their fingers to the bone?
Yeah, it's like Ernie a Bezos, is he a Jeff Bezos type?
Is he somebody who underpays the employees
and has gotten rich off their backs?
It's possible.
Maybe so, doesn't give them bathroom breaks.
Just asking, also, I'm just asking questions.
Just asking questions.
That's all I'm doing.
A phrase you're always happy to see.
Like it's always good vibes when you see that phrase.
Mm-hmm.
I'm a skeptic, that's a cool thing to be, right?
A skeptic. Oh yeah,
professional skeptic, hell yeah.
No vibes there.
We got Sam, oh wait, oh, sorry,
I said Sam, Sam is the peanut butter baker,
which again, this list does not say.
I've become disappointed as we've gone
by the advertising week 360 list,
but there are nice helpful pictures, so I'll give it that.
Well, Sam was in the Weedables commercial.
Weedables, another food we had a lot in the house growing up.
I think I had two.
I think we had a two.
Yeah, they made like a lot of not just cookies,
they had club crackers, they had the pizza.
Always had club crackers.
Club crackers great with soup.
Pick up a box folks, if you're stocking up on canned goods
when you're at the store, club crackers, delicious.
Do you have some? Very buttery.
I don't have some.
Those though, I feel like, well they come in sleeves,
but once you open a sleeve, I feel like the clock
is ticking on those club crackers.
Like they're gonna lose their crunch quick.
Their essence?
Their essence, their crunchy essence.
Can I bring up some of the other products
that in their product line, which there are,
elf starring commercials and you guys might have run
into these.
I think it makes sense that today we don't see on shelves
a product called Oh Boyzies,
which is sort of a double, it's to get oh boy,
because they'll have you saying oh boy,
but they're also potato chips and it's meant to be
it's meant to, the Boyzies is meant to make you think
of Idaho and Idaho potatoes.
Right.
Weird name.
Very strange name.
I never had those.
And I was not dying to eat their line of tortilla chips
called Chachos with a weird cinnamon flavor
called Cinnamon Crespagna.
I think Crespagna is potentially a fictional,
I could be wrong, I didn't look it up in any
Spanish dictionary.
The Nina, the Pinta, the Crespagna, the three ships.
Columbus, the New World.
Such early education stuff.
Also educational was the Chachos ad where I learned
how they make the chips, which is that all the elves
gather in a circle and throw a tortilla up in the air
three or four times and then somebody,
one of the elves cracks the whip, cracks a big whip
right in the center which splits it into many different
chips.
Like Indiana Jones?
Yeah, yeah.
It's a big old crack and if you don't do it right
in the center, I bet that's a problem.
That's a very special kitchen skill.
Sounds efficient.
Which elf cracked the whip?
He was very far away in a pretty poor quality
YouTube transfer so it's hard to see, I'll pull it up
while we're talking, I'll see if I can, this will be
a good test, can I identify after this lesson
which elf it was?
Yes, that's good.
What other, I was looking at the list too of items.
There's a lot of stuff I forgot from the 90s that they had
that we had in the house, like cookie wise.
Jason, did you go through this list too?
No, send it to me.
I looked at a couple lists, yeah.
But if you wanna go ahead, hold on, yeah, let me,
now I'm losing my list here.
I think that, I'm now looking at the Chachos commercial
and I think this might be a lot of one time,
one use only Hispanic elves.
Oh, interesting.
Yeah, I think.
They're all in sombreros so I think these are not
the typical, these are not the people we've been covering.
Right.
So we had the, oh man.
Now I'm just, now it keeps pulling up dry ads on my phone.
All right, here we go.
They had Keebler Fudge Shop cookies, which I remember.
They had, now Rich and Chips used to be their like
chocolate chip cookie.
Which would just have like a lot of chocolate chips
and it was just Rich and Chips with like an N, not an and.
Well, in the midnight there was Chocolate Lovers.
I think that was a variant of Chips Deluxe.
Right.
I watched a 1995 commercial on that
where Ernie rings a woman's doorbell
and asks, do you like chocolate?
And she goes, honey, I live for it.
Um, that's fun.
Let's not forget to give some love
to Zesta Salteen Crackers.
Of course.
I don't know which elf works primarily on Zesta.
Zesta, yeah, I don't think it says.
The, there was, did you get,
oh wait, we still have more elves, right?
There's like two or three elves left.
Well, there's two left.
There's Elwood, the teenage elf.
Who's different than Zoot and JJ.
Yes. Right.
Elwood looks a little squirrely to me,
so he would be Jackie Jr.
He's the one who holds up the card game
and then Vito kills.
And then Florence, Florence I feel like
does not get enough screen time.
Well, right.
All the elves are white except for Florence, who is black.
Yes.
And I have never seen a commercial with Florence.
She is, she's wearing shoes with heels
and maybe she's the one who puts the little like,
she steps all the holes into the Zesta crackers.
Oh, yes.
Look, you've already given her more of a backstory
than the people at Keibler have.
So you've actually paid more attention to her
than they have.
Yeah, yeah.
It's a good job.
You're getting your steps in.
It's, you're on your feet.
There really should, look,
there's room for a lot of new Keibler elves.
And I feel like let's up the diversity.
That's what I'm saying.
Yeah. Yeah.
Let's bring back the Chachos characters
who apparently were only used for Chachos.
Yes, that feels-
Gave them to temporary, temporarily employed.
But they're all, as we know, they're immortal.
So they're running around somewhere.
So bring them back, Ernie.
Yeah. Come on, Ernie.
You know what? I don't like Ernie now.
Uh-oh. Hey.
I'm sorry, Jason.
Sounds like you're fake.
Are you a fake friend, Michael?
Turning on Ernie this hard, this fast?
I don't know.
I'm just saying a couple of things
have added up in this discussion.
And I think maybe,
maybe Ernie's not the guy we think he is.
That's all I'm saying.
This is the kind of rage
that only someone on drugs would have.
Do you need me to come over there and break your neck?
I'll be, all right, I'll be honest with you.
I am on drugs
and I would really like you to come over here
and break my neck.
It's the only cure as we've figured out.
We're gonna have to, we're all, all right.
I know gloves are hard to come by right now,
but we're all gonna have to buy some gloves
so we can visit each other's homes
and break each other's necks.
There are, like our telephone booths,
I think in South Korea for testing for the virus,
where it has like kind of holes and like those,
you know how like when you're handling
nuclear material in a movie or TV show,
those gloves that kind of go through,
like that's the protective way that you can touch it.
Yeah, yeah.
I'll build something like that in my window by my kitchen
and you can just put your hands through the gloves
and then break my neck that way.
It'll be very easy.
So we'll pass, and the kitchen counter
is probably where you're doing your snorting.
It's a nice clear surface.
So I'll walk up, I'll do a spot check on you,
see if you're doing a snort, and then I'll reach,
yeah, you'll feel some gloves on your neck
and that'll be me saving your life by breaking your neck.
And I'll say, thank you, sir.
And then you'll be on to the next neck breaking
that you're scheduled for.
Oh, wow, South Korea thinks it's so great.
They've got testing booths.
Can they get Trolls World 2 on demand real quick?
You tell them, Jason.
That's American.
We might be low on testing kits,
but we stocked every home with the movie Lovebirds
on Netflix.
We have Lovebirds and we created the Keibler elves.
This is America.
What was the phrase about American in America in the,
Jason, you read it, right?
The way, well, the elves, they're uniquely,
they're an American strain.
Oh yeah, that's right, sorry, they're an American strain.
Non-drews, they're a uniquely American strain.
And a uniquely American strain of cure
is immediate release of Lovebirds and cats and Frozen 2.
And Invisible Man.
The man who was, they were just keeping these movies
arbitrarily from us.
And when duty called, Hollywood acted.
Now toilet paper, not so much.
Not so much.
But our ironic cat's viewings can flow forth.
Well, now I'm depressed.
Now I'm depressed. Oh no.
Well.
Well then we gotta think of something fun.
I came off the high of the Chukko seance
and now I'm sad again.
So there's kind of the more like one-off elves.
There's micro Keibler.
He was the elf who would shrink cookies down
to like when they had the little sized cookies.
Oh.
There was a professor, there was very clearly
an Albert Einstein kind of elf.
And then my favorite of the people who show up
to bother the elves is the cop who arrests,
I believe it's Buckets.
And the cop says, he's not the front man
for a fudge smuggling operation.
And Ernie says, no sir, he's our middle man.
And that's a cute joke.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, that's very good.
I however am the front man
for a fudge smuggling operation.
So.
You're proud to admit it.
That's the point.
Yeah.
Yeah, Friar Tuck who was mainly promoting Munchums.
As he said, Zoot and JJ were, you know,
excited about pizzerias, pizza chips.
They didn't make them, but they were,
they're Ernie's nephews.
And if Zoot, if, you know,
nephews who are so judgy and opinionated,
if they like pizzerias, why wouldn't everyone?
Yeah.
Zach, the fudge shop supervisor.
Flo, wait, is Flo the one we were talking about?
Florence, yeah.
Yes, oh, here wait, I found her job on Wikipedia.
She's the accountant.
Boo, boo to this, boring.
Yeah.
Give her something, in a fudge factory,
she's just like working on a calculator.
Give her something fun to do.
Give her something fun.
Let her drive the fudge submarine.
Yeah, I agree.
And do we, oh, Elwood, I don't think we said
runs through the dough.
Right.
And then I don't really know
what's up with Larry and Art.
I got no info on Larry and Art.
I don't either, yeah.
Yeah.
No qualities, did they have?
Larry and Art, what commercial were they in?
It doesn't say what I'm looking at.
Who were the guys in the pizzerias commercial?
Are those the regular elves?
That's, they're the nephews.
Okay, that's JJ and?
JJ and Zoot.
Zoot, Zoot, yeah, yeah.
Yes, yeah, yeah.
But, you know, that's not the end of the mythology
because we got to the end of these characters.
You know, I was thinking how, you know,
I mean, the second gaze where we talk about things
that aren't necessarily super on themed experience topic,
and I was like, well, this is a little outside
of the confines of what we usually do,
but then I realized it is not, and I'll tell you why,
because several years ago,
there was a factory pop-up experience in New York City.
There has been a themed experience
based around the Keebler factory tree.
Wow, I didn't know, I didn't see that.
Yeah, it was done for the sacred holiday
of National Fudge Day, which let's never forget it again.
It's June 16th, which happens to be my mom's birthday.
Wow. I had no idea all these years
my mom was born on National Fudge Day.
Wow, National Fudge, wow.
Yeah, I'm so lucky. Do we know any other
prominent Americans who were born on National Fudge Day?
Ooh, that's a good question, I'll look that up.
Yeah, what's 16th?
16th. Celebrity birthdays.
Celebrity.
Tupac, y'all. Wow.
Wow.
Wow. Born on National Fudge Day.
Roe, isn't there, his book is something about,
oh, the rose that grew from concrete.
Why, the title should have been the rose
that grew from concrete on National Fudge Day.
Mm-hmm, yeah.
Wow, he might be the most famous,
oh, wait a minute, the ultimate warrior,
I believe, was born.
Let me make sure that that's right before.
Surprise National Fudge Day is in a warmer month,
because, I mean, if you're not careful with that fudge,
you're gonna end up with your own fudge spring,
inadvertently. Yeah.
Yeah, ultimate warrior.
Ultimate warrior, born June 16th,
professional wrestler and noted racist.
Oh man, there's a lot of good ones.
OJ getaway driver, Al Cowlings.
Wow, really?
Yeah.
Wow.
Geronimo was born on National Fudge.
Really?
Yeah, this is quite a day.
I wonder if my mom knew about any of these.
Phil Mickelson, one of the greatest golfers of all time.
You're gonna text your mom,
did you know you were born on the same day
as the ultimate warrior?
No, you're saying that assuming that my mom texts.
Oh, fair enough, fair enough.
That's a big leap that you were wrong on.
Send her a letter that says she was born.
The primary communication, yes.
Oh man.
So yeah, wish all these people
happy National Fudge days slash birthdays next time around.
But let's talk about the themed experience,
because the themed experience fleshed out a lot of stuff.
And I think this is where Jason,
some of the expanded the logistics of the factory,
I think were made especially clear by this event.
That being the really important piece of knowledge
about the factory that the tree was built on top
of a flowing fudge river called the fudge terrain in spring.
Whoa.
Yeah, yeah, that's right.
And I don't think they knew it always.
That's what the story seems to tell that they were like,
maybe they were running out of fudge or something.
And then they like, you know,
dug a shovel in or something.
They were like building a new wing of the factory.
It's like a Beverly hillbilly set up
where they're in their holler and then they strike it,
strike it rich because they find oil.
Brown gold.
Brown fudgey gold.
Elfin tea.
They also, they have a magic oven.
I'm a little unclear on what,
how it works and why it's magic.
And there's also, Jason, you alluded to it,
the rainbow cannon.
Yeah.
The rainbow cannon,
when Ernie calls the team,
when a non-believer in elves has been spotted.
And when that happens, the rainbow cannon is fired up
to send an insta rainbow in that person's direction
to sway their minds and make them believe.
It's sort of a back signal.
Only in America do we gotta change this guy's mind.
Get the gun.
Shoot it in the air.
Shoot it in the air above him.
Make him dance.
I should say also that, you know,
all of this was done and the pop-up event was done
in order to celebrate the release of a new type of cookie,
Keebler Whoopsie fudge stripes cookies.
Usually the cookies just have carefully painted stripes
courtesy of Leonardo, but in the Whoopsie scenario,
it was their first cookie that was covered fully in fudge
or as they put it in a hashtag, hashtag fully fudge.
Wow.
This was a viral event that really got people talking
three years later on a paywall Patreon.
That's right.
They really should.
Due to disease boredom.
Right.
Throw away, us not wanting to waste a good topic
on a quarantine episode.
That being said, I mean, how long have we been going?
I mean, this is a media topic.
There's a ton here.
I, yeah, there really is.
Yeah, yeah, quite a bit.
And actually, you know, I have a little bit more.
I mean, I hear this, this might be a good way to end it,
but I don't want to, you know, cut you guys off.
If there's any important facts you want to share.
I really, Jason, you go ahead.
Well, I would just want to point out,
like if you are craving like Girl Scout cookies,
Caramel Delights or Thin Mints and stuff,
Kepler essentially makes those varieties of cookie year round.
I don't have the names in front of me,
but like they basically make them.
Yeah, you can get versions of the famous cookies.
Yeah.
Yeah, under different names.
Or like the generic Kroger, I mean,
your grocery store likely has the generic version
of all these cookies.
Sure.
So.
I like the tag alongs.
We're talking Girl Scout cookies,
the peanut butter patties, tag alongs.
Those are my favorite.
Always have been.
You got to dock at points that they aren't being made
by a little Elfin peanut butter baker.
Well, of course.
They don't have a Sam on their side.
I agree with that.
Yeah, it's a little more fun.
Can I do this little segment here,
perhaps to close this out?
Of course, yes.
Well, you know, because there's not a ton
of Google results for these folks,
some of the ones that I found ended up being on eBay.
And it occurred to me, this might be a good opportunity
to do a quick mini version of our rarely done
this segment, Souvenir Showdown.
I think it's SmackDown.
SmackFuck.
That's what happens when you don't ever do it.
Yeah.
So, because two of these items are so odd,
I just had to have you guys learn about them
and guess the prices.
So the first one is a lot of 200 vintage Kepler Elf,
Super Elf sail kites from the 1970s.
This is a box that contains 200 kites.
These were promotional items.
Wow.
They feature Ernie bursting forth in a Superman fashion.
It says Super Elf really big.
And then in smaller text, it says,
who in reality is Ernie Keibler?
Ask him the tough questions.
Yeah, that's sort of what Mike is getting at.
Huh, who is Ernie Keibler?
So how many of these are there again?
It's, you get a cardboard box and there are 200 inside.
200, wow. Unassembled.
From the 1970s, at some point in time,
they were free with a purchase,
with two packages of Keibler crackers or cookies.
This one just was never open.
So how much would it cost to get 200 kites?
Is it a buy now or is it the auction starting price?
Do you know?
Oh, I'm seeing it as buy it now.
Okay.
You can still offer, but they have a buy it now option.
Right, right.
I'm gonna say they want five grand for that.
Guess I'm wrong.
I think $50 for that box.
I think you've got the under, that is $219.
Oh wow. That's not bad.
That's pretty good.
I feel like, I mean, the last I saw kites anywhere
somewhere in a Fry's Electronics,
some of the products still available there.
And I'm sure they're letting kites go for $20.
I don't know the quality of these kites, but I don't know,
200, that's only, that's a dollar and change per kite.
Yeah, that's okay.
Pretty fair price.
Maybe once this whole thing is over, we'll buy that
and we'll have a fan event
where we all fly these kites together.
We end out, let's go fly Kepler Elf kite.
Sounds like a good first way to be outside.
Yeah.
Yeah, we'll make sure it's a fan meetup.
Right.
Let's not test the waters by just going out
with four people we like.
Let's bring all of our fans in one place.
Immediately.
Yes, as soon as, in like, what, two weeks from now, right?
Yeah, two weeks.
We'll set the date.
It's gonna be fine.
Yeah, sorry about it.
Professional podcasters and their listeners,
famously in good health.
Famously sturdy stock.
All, what?
Super athletic.
Very athletic, yeah.
Especially the hosts.
There's podcasts with jacked people.
Yeah, yes, that's true.
Yeah, like the dumbbells.
The dumbbells are jacked.
The dumbbells.
Yeah.
Riders podcast.
Major wrestling figures podcast.
Those guys are jacked.
Yeah.
So they'll be out there too with us flying the kite,
is what I'm saying.
The dumbbells and rider and Hawkins.
Beating us up.
Beating us up and taking our kites.
Breaking our necks.
Yeah.
Oh, I want them, I want any of them to break my neck.
Sorry, Scott.
Oh, damn.
What if you don't do it full,
like what if you don't fully break my neck?
What if it's half broken?
I'll get you part of the way there.
Oh, you mean like if I'm not gonna do it all the way?
Yeah, right.
You could ensure that your wrestler friend would?
Yes.
Yeah, that means just practically.
That's gonna, what I care about is you kicking drugs
and if that's what it takes, then great.
That's right.
There's another good cause that is depicted
in the second and final item.
It is described as, well, it's a pin
and the pin says, feel the urn, ERN,
and that refers to Ernie, obviously,
and it is clearly a reference to Bernie Sanders,
apparently no longer viable presidential candidate
for some fucking reason.
Bernie Sanders, feel the urn, Keebler Elf presidential pin.
It says very rare, so keep that in mind
when you make your guess.
And in the center, it's more the CGI style of Ernie,
which I guess implies that it's more recent.
Is this official merch?
I don't know, I don't know.
It seems, it does not feel like Keebler
would make a reference to Bernie Sanders
and I can't tell if this is from 2016
or the current campaign.
So feel the urn, it's a pin.
I don't really have a size on this,
but it was a pin, it's a pin.
But I care to take a guess.
Jason, go first.
$40?
Mike?
I'm gonna say 99 cents.
This costs $240.
Oh my God.
More money than 200 kites.
What?
I do not understand this pricing whatsoever.
What the hell?
I don't know, that just doesn't,
you get one pin, it looks like pretty low res by the way.
And then, but for less money, you get 200 kites?
It's crazy.
Yeah, madness.
This is like when you try to buy Keebler cookies
at like 7-Eleven and you're like,
this box isn't normally 8.50.
Yeah, yeah, I don't know.
Yeah, maybe this is quarantine pricing.
When I was looking through to get some EL Fudges,
I thought about just shipping them via Amazon
the normal way and they were like up charging for two boxes
for like $13.
I think Ernie's setting the price.
I agree.
Yeah, I think maybe even like juxtaposing him
with this people's hero like Bernie Sanders is,
I think it's like the weird way to like ride on his back
and make him seem like somebody who cares about
the rights of the every elf, just the little guy.
And I don't think, I think they're very different people.
Yeah, sorry, Jason.
Yeah, well, what are you gonna do?
I mean, Keebler is usually like Hostess,
one of the more expensive snack cake cookie options.
How expensive are they?
You're talking about like a box for four or $5
versus two or $3, you know?
Okay.
But you're trying to feed a family of four,
I'm sure that was my mom's thinking, that adds up.
You're gonna feed a family of four with cookies.
Well, everyone's gonna, there are cookies in the hat,
everyone's gonna want a little taste, you know?
Yeah. That's a good point.
Everyone is gonna want a little taste.
And maybe a nice way to go out
as we attribute this factory's fine work
is to read another bit of mythology
provided by the New York City Fudge Day pop-up exhibit
that as you walked around that experience,
you could see a plaque that contained the Elfen Creed.
And it's pretty inspiring.
It might make Jason shed a fudge tear.
Let's hear it.
Let's see it.
We pledge to pursue our goal of baking cookies,
crackers and snacks that are by whatever measure
one chooses to apply, uncommonly good.
Wow. Uncommonly good.
That's the slogan.
They say uncommonly good a lot.
I mean, that's beautiful.
I will say.
Jason, reaction to that?
This is the way.
This is the way, as they say on the Mandalorian.
It's pretty beautiful.
Isn't there part of the Hippocratic oath
that's about like...
This is the way.
No, what's the, what's the, what is it?
First, do no harm.
Oh, okay.
Oh, it's not about good.
That's right. Okay.
Well, so the Elfen oath is first to do uncommonly good.
Yes.
Yeah. It's really nice.
An important one to live by.
Keep that in your hearts, dear listeners.
Yeah. Yeah.
It's a great thing.
And boy, as there are shortages
at the moment and grocery stores are crazy,
if you know, all right,
you, the Patreon subscriber especially,
we've provided you a lot of entertainment
and I just wanna say,
if you're bored around the house in this stretch of time
and you discover that you have a fudge terrainian river
under your property, just a fudge terrainian spring,
just loop us in, let us know.
Yeah. I mean, I would say too,
it's possible you don't even know about it.
So get a shovel out and do a little digging.
Cause we're like...
Everyone listening, just start poking around your yard.
Yeah. And it may be like, if maybe just like find a room
and even in your house or apartment
and just start digging that way too.
If you have like just maybe, you know,
like a closet or something,
dig a hole into the floor of the closet,
if it's right, like on the first floor.
Yeah.
So then you don't even have to go outside.
Yeah. This could be an indoor activity.
That's absolutely true.
Because a fudge terrainian spring,
with the contents were shared with all of the other patrons
and the hosts of the show,
it could save us through this crisis.
Yeah. So let us know.
Yeah. Send us your fudge.
Send us your fudge.
Hashtag send us your fudge.
Well, it works for me.
Hey, that was a blast.
Nice taking a trip to the factory with you fellas.
Yes. Likewise.
All right. Well, stay subscribed, stay safe,
and we'll be back for more soon.
Yeah. ChocoSaiyan's coming soon.