Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, The Second Gate, a podcast that, unlike today's topic, is available
on both land and sea.
I'm Scott Gardner, joined as somewhere else far away by Mike Carlson.
Pretty far, I mean not far away from you really, but far away from the listener perhaps.
Far away possibly from the listener and from our guest who will introduce us in a second,
but first Jason Sheridan.
Ahoy, permission to come aboard.
Oh God.
We're excited, we're hitting the water, we're blasting off to sea.
This is an episode, I mean, I think we'll cover some general stuff about the Disney
Cruises, but specifically it is an episode about the in-room entertainment on one of
the Disney cruise ships, or maybe all of them, I don't know, we're gonna get some clarification.
This is a topic that was conceived over a year ago on the main feed by today's guest.
He's the creator of the very popular YouTube series, Defunct Land.
Please welcome back Kevin Perjurer.
Thank you, I'm broadcasting from the worst and longest Carnival cruise in the history.
I'm stuck on the ship, they didn't care about us.
No, since March, no.
Yeah, yeah, I'm just waiting off the coast of San Diego, just going in circles.
Re-catching COVID from each other?
Yeah, yeah, people say you can get it twice, that's not accurate.
You can get it four times, five times.
How many are you up to?
I got my fourth badge the other day, but some of my suitemates are going up to five or six.
It's pretty incredible, it's like a two week refresh.
They keep adding to the numbers, you now have COVID-25.
But they never close the buffet, so I can't really complain.
Yes, the good thing is if you like your dinner entree, you can just ask for a second dinner
entree, so there's pluses and minuses, you know?
Oh, I love cruises so much, I'm so glad we get to talk about them.
I was supposed to go on one, it was canceled.
Oh, did you have one ready to go before the ship went down?
Yeah, yeah, I mean, I guess this would be good to mention because I brought this topic
up is I'm a huge Disney Cruise Line fan.
That's our family trip.
My family does not go to Disney World, we go on Disney Cruises.
Interesting.
And so we were in denial pretty hardcore.
We were like, oh, ours is in May, we'll be fine.
And then we moved it to December and now we're not going.
Even if it's open in December, we don't want to be on that.
Yeah, that seems like the correct move.
But they're building three new ships.
They are, really?
Yeah.
Well, they were going to build two and then the rumor is backstage at D23, two years ago,
Bob Iger's like, I'm going to announce three.
And the shipyard had no idea.
And then he walked on stage and said, we're building three new ships.
Have they announced the names of these?
I love the names of the ships.
I love the Disney simplification naming system.
Because they are what currently the video that we saw that we'll talk about is from
the Disney fantasy.
And then what are the other existing ones?
The first one was the magic, then the wonder, then the dream and the fantasy.
The fifth one is going to be called the wish.
And I know they've run out of abstract nouns, so there's no sixth or seventh name.
It's just the because that's what's great about them is they're not verbs, then they're
abstract nouns, fantasy wish.
It's not the Disney wishes or the wished.
I have a pitch.
The Disney yearn.
Yes, that's too.
I feel like that word is too complicated.
I feel like there's too many.
Yeah.
How about the Disney longing?
The Disney adventure.
The Disney adventure is adventure is good.
Longing has a tinge of melancholy to it.
So it's from when you wish upon a star.
Secret. The Disney secret longing.
Yeah. The Disney secret longing is good.
Disney star.
Wait, what was that on Kevin's?
The Disney obey.
I don't know. I feel like.
I mean, that gets their message across.
Well, that's domineering in a way.
I think that's that's the subtext of all the ships.
Sure. Yeah.
That's the Dismaland cruises.
The Banksy cruises.
Oh, yeah. When's he going to brand?
When's Banksy going to branch into parody cruise ships, too?
Also, regional entertainment, regional Banksy, like
our regional.
Banksy restaurant, Banksy quest, like.
Yeah.
Jason should be. Club Banksy.
Club Banksy.
Jason, you could be the San Fernando Valley Banksy.
Oh, I could be. Yeah.
Just really subverting like the Chili John's restaurant.
Yeah. Send up Chili John's in Burbank.
Send up send up the multiple BJ's.
That's the worst restaurant ever.
Hmm. I don't know.
I don't want to get off and I think the Pazuki is very good.
No, they're not good enough.
They are.
Kevin, they are good enough.
I think they're good enough.
That's a cut to a warm cookie with ice cream.
Jason, Jason, back me up here.
I mean, a lot of quarantine Pazuki.
Have you really?
Yeah, because for a while they were just including it
free with your meal with like any order.
Wait, and then you're also on top of it, doing a lot of BJ's.
Well, you get what you do.
You get you get the BJ's dinner and then you get a cold entree
that you can heat up the next day.
That was like five or six bucks.
And then you get either a free you get a free Pazuki.
I went to steal.
How many Pazuki's have you eaten since we've been in quarantine in March?
Well, I've shared them, but the answer is still three to four.
To yourself or is that Tota?
Do you think just your halves?
I've had like half of each one.
OK, OK, OK.
But there's time.
This this curve, much like the real one, is not necessarily going down.
No, it might spike again any day now.
No, but they do have a big banner saying the dining room is now open.
So they've scaled back on their delivery and takeout options.
So so the deal isn't as good.
Yeah, the deal isn't as good.
Oh, bummer. So they're so it could diminish.
Yeah, how's that?
OK, I'm BJ's just like trying to race to beat
Cheesecake Factory to every town in America.
Is that what you say?
Well, BJ's has like a very large menu, like a thick hundred
hundred page menu, it feels like.
So but it's not as good as Cheesecake Factory. Right.
But I assume I don't know anything about the corporate structure.
I don't know what their business plans are.
Which in and of itself, I Cheesecake Factory, I've done takeout
during the quarantine, and I think it's made me aware that Cheesecake
Factory is not good.
I think you like the atmosphere.
I think it's fun to go to one and you're just lost in that cheesecake magic.
And then when you just bring it home and it's just in a tin, it's not there.
I disagree.
Have you have you been to quarantine cheese cake?
No, I just have never been in Cheesecake Factory and been like,
hell, yeah, this food's whatever. But look at this place.
Wait, so how would you wait?
You have not been to know you've been to one.
You just haven't been in raptured by it.
I haven't. I haven't. Yeah.
Right. I have not been raptured by the enraptured enraptured.
Yeah, not raptured as if it killed you, if you were killed.
Well, it's being brought to heaven.
Yeah. And enraptured as you're getting on the boat and de-raptured
is when you're getting off the boat. Is that right?
The Disney Rapture is a good name.
Disrapture. That's what it would be if you went on one currently.
You well, yeah.
It's the Disney Cruise is the place I would at least want to be in the world.
And I think that might be my statement before the pandemic.
It's not my deal.
So maybe Kevin, it's a good and we haven't really talked about them
on the show at all.
So is what I don't know what if you could sell us on the
Disney Cruise experience, what's what appeals to you and your family?
So there's something for everybody.
So I'm not going to sell you that hard.
But the Disney Cruise Line, in short, is the last place
where the Disney difference exists.
That idea that Disney is superior in their service and their quality,
that still exists on the cruise.
It does not exist in the parks anymore.
I mean, ignore this whole quarantine thing, but it does not exist in the parks
because they're just too crowded.
It's there's too many people to be able to create those special moments
and to really interact with people.
And the Disney cruise ships only have a certain number of staterooms, obviously.
And so even on the largest cruises, it is still extremely personal.
The Disney I like Disney cruises.
They do things that other cruises don't do.
The rotational dining is pretty genius
where every night you like rotate through the main restaurants,
but your waiter moves with you so you get to know them. Whoa.
That's bizarre. That's how do you get?
So like on every ship, there's three signature dining.
And every night you have like there's two there's two different reservations.
You can either have the early dinner or the late dinner.
And then you just rotate.
And so and then your servers move with you and you get to talk to them
and you get to know them.
And if you're lucky, they're great.
And they usually are because they they you have to work your way up
to get to that position anyways.
The diversity is great.
They get a lot of people from all over the world.
So you get to ask them about their experiences.
So that's always fun.
Oh, as in this in this video that we'll talk about.
Yeah, it's like it's very international.
Everybody. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
And suspiciously,
well, you're wondering if there's a loophole somewhere in some of the like,
yeah, let's talk about loopholes and cruises.
So cruise ships tend to be
registered in countries with very flexible legal systems,
either the Bahamas or
different ports in Africa.
You don't see a lot of cruises like cruise ships that are registered
like their home port is Newark or New York City or Port Canaveral.
Right. Because then you have to abide by the home country's laws.
And if there's more wiggle room in that country's laws,
I it gets complicated.
If you've seen succession, this comes up.
That's why I mentioned suspiciously when I referred to how the the employees,
the cast members are awesome and they get them from all over the world.
But I just wonder if certain American ideas of work periods,
you know, because there are a lot of Americans on the ship, obviously,
that are working.
But yeah, it's in countries that tend to not have the strictest labor laws.
I think that's one of the reasons.
Oh, that's what there I was wondering where you guys were going with this,
what they're trying to get away with.
So I don't want to sound like we're like, what's with all these,
you know, people from Australia on these cruise ships?
Saying suspicious about that.
Yeah, that's not what we're saying.
What's up? What's up with all these Australians?
No, but it's that's that's what that's what I think.
It's like if you're here, if you're on the boat, you should be working 24-7.
That's what they're trying to get away with.
And this is across cruise lines like this isn't exclusive to Disney, I should say.
Right. No, no, it's not.
But it does run into some issues.
It's going to get really dark.
You can you can cut this out if you want.
I guess we're on the second gate.
There are things is the Villains Park of podcast.
All right. Oh, I like that.
That's what I'm describing that way before.
So are you bringing up the simple art of murder, Kevin?
Murder at sea?
Yes, I am.
If you have a murder at sea or just a death at sea, as the Disney wonder did
with one of its cast members tragically falling off the boat, supposedly to their death.
It has it will be investigated by the governments of the home port.
So the American family of the cast member,
it would cause this whole thing where they could not get NASA to properly investigate it
or something or other. I didn't research this very well.
Do not take what I'm saying verbatim.
I just remember it was something with it gets complicated
when there's something of that nature.
But yeah, that was the biggest.
Yeah, sorry. I probably should have brought that up.
Oh, no, no, this is very intriguing.
Well, so is Disney or the Disney Cruises registered in some other city
so that they can all bodies as much as it's all NASA?
Well, well, well, well, well, well, I feel like this is going to be like
you called Australian suspicious and you said NASA is the best place for murders.
I'm going to get super not good feedback.
All our listeners in NASA are going to be curious.
I'm not trying to be weird about this.
Well, can I bring up another thing I know about cruises?
I think I've talked about this on the show.
Does everyone know about the lifeboat guns?
Hmm. I don't. This doesn't ring a bell.
So feel free. Yes. OK.
So when you are on a cruise, you are assigned to a lifeboat.
There's a couple of things to know about the lifeboat.
So this is your day of embark.
Embarkation is getting on the ship.
Debarcation is leaving the ship.
The first day you get on a ship.
I went on a Norwegian cruise line once with my family when I was 12.
One of the very first things you do after lunch is find out where your lifeboat
and your life vests are.
And and in case of an emergency, this is the lifeboat you would have to get on.
A thing I learned later on as an adult, I knew someone who was in the entertainment
staff and they are usually on cruise ships, the ones trained to man
the lifeboats because they're, you know, they have a presence
and they're good with people.
And that means they're also some of them trained to use the handguns
that are on every lifeboat because you have to.
If a lifeboat is like launched, you have to abide by the rules of maritime
like nautical law.
And if a passenger says like, no, I can do this better.
I should be in charge of this ship.
They can legally shoot that passenger.
So you could be shot by someone who was just playing
Lumiere, the singing candle, potentially just leading a limbo contest.
And now that doesn't happen in all the studios.
No, it doesn't.
Whoa. I see.
Can you play?
Can you play Russian roulette with the gun, too, if you're at sea for a while?
Well, I mean, I guess that that's how cool your lifeboat captain is.
Depends on that.
If Lumiere is cool, he'll allow it.
Huh? Well, that's a that's a real dark start for this.
Can you tell us about the macaroni and cheese at the buffet?
What kind of macaroni and cheese is the buffet?
Or jello's, please. Let's get into jello's.
It's the cheese kind.
No. Yeah. Anyway, so there's this great rotational dining system
where your server follows you and if they go missing, it has to be investigated.
Yes. No, wait. No, no.
Our diving. No, too dark.
It's a great rotational system with a waiter who follows you
and he will shoot you if he needs to.
My podcast GPS is messing up.
No. Can you tell us the name of it?
Because you you get some names of restaurants and stuff.
Is there was there a restaurant you were especially fond of?
Oh, well, no. No.
I think there's no.
We're remaining dark.
They're all very good food, but it's there.
I'm pretty sure. And again, I I this is I'm a very researched individual.
I go into every all my videos, very scripted.
So I really don't like to be like I just looked up the Disney
Wonder thing and it was had it did have to be investigated by the Royal
Bahamas Police Force, so I wasn't completely off on that.
But with it, but I think all the kitchens are pretty centrally located on the ship.
So on the wonder and no, sorry, on the dream and the fantasy,
which are the two newest ships, there's animators, palettes,
Roy, which is their big Disney one.
That's the one that slaps you in the face with Disney.
And it's the animation one.
So one night if on a fantasy, the first night you are in that rotational dining
on a seven day cruise because you'll go into each one multiple times.
The first night is Turtle Talk with Crush, which is an Epcot.
And I believe it's also a DCA.
And it happens this little show or to crush the turtle talks to you
happens at the restaurant.
Yeah, happens. There's screens everywhere and it's actually really cool.
And the lighting is really fun.
And it totally ruins the experience if you've ever done it at the parks,
because that one's way better.
But yeah, it's super cute.
The crush will, you know, go up to kids and it'd be like nautical
and they'll be like crazy.
And, you know, I don't know what happens, but it's it's very cute.
Crush goes table to table like at a wedding.
Yeah, yeah, he does. He does.
There's only one crush.
And if there's two, then they really far apart in the restaurant.
So you can't see them. But he does go.
That's exactly that's a great way to explain. Wow. Wow.
And he did.
He keeps some of the conversations quick if it's, you know,
you know, somebody's aunt, he doesn't really want to do it.
It's sort of a black sheep of the family.
Yeah. And there's it's obviously some poor cast member
that has a good impersonation of Crush wedged between one of the walls
looking at monitors.
But it's weird. It's it's it's super fun.
And then the second night you're at animators palette,
which also has tons of Disney, you know, like
film strips and different things.
The second night you're there, you are
doing a draw your own animation.
So they bring to your table like a a blank person
that is like kind of like the Da Vinci man with giant spaces.
And you draw in the arms separately and they put it through a computer
and it comes together and then it superimposes them in a big Disney montage
at the end of dinner. And it's awesome.
I know I know I'm very I like Disney.
It's fine. Like I like to make fun of it a lot.
But that one was I was like, I'm into this.
That's pretty wild.
That's it. While you eat your you draw some weird little character,
you really a forky, if you will.
You invent a little wonky thing and then it's put into a movie.
Yeah. Unless it's something that looks inappropriate,
then they just take it off, which has happened to me.
But whatever. What are you going to do?
There's like a quality control person or there's a sensor.
There's a there's like a boat sensor.
Yeah. Yeah. It goes through the sensor board.
You have to explain why you think it's appropriate and don't listen.
Bob Iger has to click yes or no on a computer remotely.
Give me another ship. I love this.
Is this there's other there's other restaurants like I think
a enchanted garden or royal palace and enchanted garden is the one
where it starts at night and then the flowers bloom while you eat.
And it's day, I think, by the time you leave.
Wow. And then Royal Garden is the one that's like, OK, this is
there's no gimmick, really.
It's just kind of it's somewhat themed to Cinderella.
But they really want you to feel like that's a very nice dining restaurant.
And there are two fine dining restaurants on every ship that you can.
You have to pay an upcharge to go.
But kids can't go in those. But yeah. So anyways.
Sure. Do with that what you will. That sounds nice.
It all it all it all sounds really nice.
And maybe if we could dovetail, I mean, some of these things,
a couple of them now I know about because I watch the very informative video
that is really the basis of this thing that you brought up when you were on
and when you talked to us about Tarzan Rocks a while ago.
It was quite an obscure proposal.
And we love obscure proposals,
specifically the morning show that plays
in in your cabin on the ship that is hosted by the cruise director.
That's really what we're here to get into.
Can you describe for us your discovery of this broadcast?
I turned it on while I was on one of the ships accidentally.
And I love looking at hotel media, the state room media.
It's fascinating.
Yeah, at the parks, it's usually very well produced, but very old.
On the ships, it's very new and terribly produced.
Disney's creative control does not like make its way into international waters.
Like their quality control measures are out the window.
And so their cruzicles, which are the cruise musicals.
Yes. Are are weird as hell.
Yeah.
And the weirdest one is not actually filmed.
But they are. But anyway, so the the cruise musical, the cruzicles
and are on the state rooms.
And so are these morning shows, which I kind of just stumbled across.
And you all watched the one that I sent you.
I think it's the only one that got recorded.
Yeah. If you want to follow along, listener,
go to YouTube and type in Disney fantasy cruise director's show.
It is from the user Puckfly, who has posted a lot of high res,
you know, materials from Disney cruises.
And so I'm glad that there was a very like coherent one of these to watch.
But, you know, of course, this isn't the same thing that you saw, Kevin.
You saw one that was tailored to your specific cruise.
Well, it could have definitely been this one because I was on the fantasy
this year of the year this was recorded.
So, OK, OK, this one.
But I've seen there's very there's variations of these.
I think every time a cruise director,
I was going to say, goes missing.
I'm that's every time a cruise director.
What are you accusing Disney of? Oh, my God. Sorry.
Every one of them is dumped off the ship.
Yeah, everyone. Well, it's the one segment was hosted by Agatha
Christie's Hercule Poirot, the consulting detective.
He seemed like he was trying to get to the bottom of something.
He didn't really tell us about activities on the cruise that day.
Y'all were waiting for the Hercule Poirot
reference that was inevitable on the show.
Look, Kenneth Branagh's he's doing round two.
He did murder on the Orient Express.
He's doing death on a Nile next year.
You know, everyone's wild for Jason is hype for it.
I'm hype. And then death on the Disney fantasy the year after that.
The big mustache.
That's handguns from the lifeboat.
Yeah, that was the murder weapon. Yeah.
So OK. OK, wait.
So yeah, when you go on to one of these things,
the cruise director is a person who that's like the concierge.
That's somebody who's, you know, helping you out.
And if you see them walking around the ship, they can give you recommendations.
They can tell you stuff to do.
And they put this person front and center by having them talk to you
in a show you can pull up anytime all day in your in your room on the ship.
I don't I think the cruise
director's job is a bit more elevated than that.
I think they're doing they're in charge of all of the activities.
So like you could see them maybe walking around, but they're really
I think they're planning and producing all sorts of different things.
But they are the face for the big events.
So they you will see them at the start of every cruisical.
They'll do the whole welcome to our show.
We're so glad you're here, by the way, your seats, functions,
flotation devices in the case of a disaster.
And they're told that before a play starts.
Well, obviously not that, but that's the same place
you have your safety demonstration on, because, you know, every cruise,
they have to be like, look, this thing is not going to sink.
But if it does, here's what we're going to do.
We're all going to rush to the theater, which is in the center of the ship.
We're going to give you a debriefing and then we're going to rush back out.
That's actually the plan.
Well, that's that's how it would win this like ornate Disney movie theater.
You have to run in there to tell you how to save your life.
Yeah, because and then they're going to be like, all right.
You know, that's where say if you there is that you are in group C or 13
or whatever, rush to the theater and then we'll give you your debriefing
on what to do next.
And then there's some people by the lifeboats, but I'm sure that's
you have to pay more for that.
Donald Duck will give you a presentation.
Why we choose that character?
Why we choose the least discernible character?
I wish I could do an act of his voice.
We all just learned that we cannot.
We just ended an episode with the worst impressions you've ever heard.
But yes, so this director is the very there's the captain
who's not steering the ship, by the way.
Oh, sorry. You've unlocked my brain.
I'm super bad at this now that my brain's unlocked.
You'll find this interesting, though.
There are like five different captains
legally or at least promoted on each Disney ship.
There's the real captain, the human being Captain Mickey.
Mickey, he counts.
Yeah, he counts Captain Hook, Captain Jack Sparrow.
I they Disney likes to say, like, you know, our ship has like five captains.
We have Captain, you know, Stewart.
And we have we have Captain Mickey and they go through the whole thing.
I don't want to Jack Sparrow in charge of anything.
That's not a trustworthy figure.
Yeah. So this is the cruise director every morning.
She gives a debriefing and it's I'm pretty sure it's the same one every morning.
But I just wonder.
And I've also had this cruise director multiple times.
So. I can't really say, but I feel as though
I think they would have to switch out the whole video if it's not her.
So the video that we all watch, the like 40 minute video, that video plays
every day because I was trying to figure out, like, wait, does each five
minute segment is each one from a different day or that just loops forever?
It is very hard to answer that question.
OK, I do not know, because I found I found a video with that same
cruise director that was just debarkation procedures.
That's just because you have to check so many boxes.
You have to do so much to get off the ship.
You have to get your luggage picked up.
Breck, you get off the ship at like 7 a.m., right?
Depending on how many how long your cruise is.
That was shocking. That was ghastly information to learn in this video.
And even she is defensive, like, well, there's reasons we do this.
OK, there's reasons to get you to the airport and customs.
They pretty much tell you how to fill out your customs thing,
which that I think was helpful.
So keep looking on the Puckfly channel if you want to watch a customs form
readily informational video produced by Disney.
So I just checked this video is the one, the 41 minute one that we watched.
That is the video specifically for Kazumel on, I think, the Eastern Caribbean itinerary.
So there are there's one of these for every day.
Well, it'd be like, welcome to Nassau again.
And like, welcome, welcome to Castaway Key.
You know, welcome to Tortuga or Tortola or whatever it is.
So, yeah, so they do.
I'm not sure if they keep some segments, if there's some sort of like
this is segment C and we can play segment A every day because the coffee shops
always open, but we can also play segment.
We have to change out segment C, you know what I mean?
So it's like, well, because there's like a goofy guy who works on the ship
also, who is bothering the mainly the host is just this pleasant lady.
In this case, Natalie is her name, and she's giving you information
about all this fun stuff you could do on the ship.
But then sometimes there's like this there's this doof who bothers her
and like, you know, waves a fake sword in her face.
There's these little skits.
But so do they have to refilm the skit every time?
Or do these people have to redo this skit every time that this cruise embarks?
That might be best answered by the audience.
Have you been on a Disney cruise and have you seen this man holding the sword?
Or was it a different man holding a different sword?
Yeah. And did you film it off the TV?
And can you send us a copy so that we can check it with the puck fly version?
We need to cross reference some versions here.
This is like the David Copperfield question where like we had to talk
to other people who did the show to see who was a plant and who was right.
Who was a repeat? Right.
So we'll have to. Yeah, we'll have to get other people who saw this.
Well, the we should also mention that this cruise
director show is horribly shot.
Yeah. Yes, yes.
This is not well produced.
A large portion of it filmed in a starkly empty and frighteningly lit cafe
that is like the cafe in the Black Lodge from Twin Peaks.
I give you panned over for the lounge chairs.
There's a coffee bar that poor Kyle McLaughlin can sit at.
There's a it's a very odd composition
with a very prominently featured trash can.
That's like it.
I just saw everything you were talking about, Kevin.
I was like, oh, I get it right away from this first shot because, yeah,
Disney things when you watch the video in the Disney World Hotel room,
it's so polished, it's so super edited.
And this thing is just this flat shot for 10 minutes
of this lady talking to you in front of a trash can.
It looks like it was made in like I movie in 2008.
It's like so basic seeming.
I just so I'm scrolling through this video again.
And this is it seems that this is a compilation of the multiple messages.
So this is multi day that we're seeing.
Because she's also in later on doing a Star Wars Day at Sea.
Interesting note about that.
The Star Wars Day at Sea is a huge hazard for the cruise activities of the day
because and so is the Marvel Day at Sea,
because they market it so heavily and it's at sea.
Everything that happens on the ship that day has to be Star Wars themed
to the point that once you become friendly enough with like the bartenders
and your waitresses, they'll be like, yeah, that drink today
is an R2D2 Coke and rum.
And they're like, what?
And it's like, it has to be that today.
If it's not, you know, we don't fulfill Star Wars Day at Sea and we're in trouble.
I'm like, what?
And yes, so they're like everything they do like it's like, hey,
can you stop playing Star Wars music if you're like in a like a very small
environment, like take requests?
No, we can only play the Cantina band song today.
That's all we can do. I'm sorry.
Just in a loop for 13 hours. Dear God.
And it's a fun song, but there's a limit.
Is there a new Star Wars related name for every drink that day then?
Like, do they have to completely overhaul the menu with names?
I don't recall.
I don't know if they change up the actual menu items like at dinner,
but it is pretty exhaustive.
All of the kids clubs, which is another thing about the cruise,
if you're traveling with a big family like I do, you know,
they have different age levels like some of the kids, they have their own clubs.
And they have a teen club and they have a preteen club and they have a kids club
and they all their own activities.
And those on that day are even Star Wars themed.
And so you like see you'll see a bunch of kids with lightsabers
like marching around and, you know, all sorts of different things.
So it's it's very exhaustive on those Star Wars is see.
But anyways, yeah, so this is multiple days.
This television loop. Wow.
Do you ever find it ever like over structured?
It seems like a lot of like every hour is planned out to me.
The Disney bed. Yeah.
Is that essentially like I know most people go on cruises and they like, well,
I mean, I can see like, OK, dinners, it's five or six every night, whatever it is.
And then in the one video, they're like, well, the dinner
and the movie are at five and eight and whichever one you didn't go to,
you go to that like so you don't miss out on anything.
But it really does seem very heavily scheduled.
It it's all optional.
The only real things that impede your schedule are dinner.
And people will line up the day of if they don't get the dinner reservation they want.
There's only two. It's like five fifteen and eight fifteen.
And if some people got eight fifteen and like, I want to eat early, you know, they'll
you can go and ask.
And there's a line of people wanting to change their dinner reservations.
But other than that, and that also affects when you watch the show
and you don't have to go to dinner, there's other dinner options every night.
But it's expected somewhat of you like to go to dinner for sure.
Yeah, I remember there was some flexibility on like where you could go for breakfast
and lunch when I went on a cruise.
But the big food thing I remember is the midnight buffets every night.
Just a full service buffet at midnight.
They don't have that. They don't do that.
They don't do. And one one of them was a midnight chocolate buffet
of all treats it eats.
You know, we haven't recorded an episode in a while where we can see each other.
We've been doing just audio.
And I'm glad we're on video now because I got to see Jason twiddle his fingers.
Made chocolate to buffet.
As if he was about to like just pluck a little piece from one of the plates at the buffet.
No very who's the Popeye hamburger guy?
He was extremely wimpy.
He was very, very wimpy move of you just now.
Not wimpy as in wimpy.
Wimpy is in character. Yeah, yeah.
Capital. I get it.
Wimpy is Jason's favorite character in fiction.
Sure. So they do that one night on one night.
And it's a pirate night.
Pirate night is is very greatly called night because the thing with the Star Wars
Cruise and I should mention that when I was hearing all this like, hey,
we got to do this, this and this, that was when they first introduced them.
And all they really had planned was a few kids activities and like a
like a nighttime kind of like Star Wars esque thing.
And so when they said when they pitched it as Star Wars Day at Sea,
they did not have enough plans, so they were overcompensating.
But Pirate Night has this brilliant Jack Sparrow stage show, which they changed it up.
But he used to jump off the top of the ship and like propel down and like bungee
cord stop himself.
And then he would like fight for a gauntlet and then he'd shoot out the fireworks.
And that's the fireworks at sea night, which is beautiful.
And you can see in the distance all of the Royal Caribbean and Carnival
Cruises purposefully circling around you because they want to watch the
fireworks show because. Wow.
So that makes you feel special.
Wow. The leech in their firework leeches.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, it's bad.
I mean, Universal Studios would do that, too, if it was if they can move.
But there's no Universal Cruise someday.
I think I'd rather go on the Universal Cruise for whatever reason.
Universal Studios closes at 4 p.m.
anyways, but the as with their ship.
Yeah, we don't have dinner service.
No dinner service.
But yes, so they have after they have that big fireworks show, they have Club
Pirate, which is this really awkward dance night where all the families get out
there and dance.
And there was one fantastic night.
And I've been on many of these where there was one dad who was so into it
that it made it all worth it because they have these cameras around the area
to show on the big screen of the people dancing.
And he the entire time was just like going hard as heck,
just in the middle of the dance floor.
And it was it was spectacular.
But anyways, you just did a robot move.
That's not what a pirate would do.
I disagree with this guy's dance move.
I think you mean integrity.
And then they have the pirate buffet after that, which is really bad,
which is just the only night they serve Mexican food. So.
So that's the only difference with the pirate.
Does that name pirate things or anything?
Do you remember?
They have I don't know if they have drinks at the bars that are pirate themed.
They usually have a good drink of the day.
Maybe it's pirate themed, but everybody gets dressed up.
Everybody's dressed in pirate regalia.
Except for me, this is where you're losing me, Kevin.
I don't love this either.
It's all waggered figures.
Dressing like a pirate is a tough one for me.
I don't do that.
OK, you didn't bring pirate.
So they don't throw you overboard if you don't dress like a pirate.
Yeah, no, they don't.
They don't coerce you into saying you're planning on taking over the ship
so they could use a handgun on you. Right.
Would it count if you dressed like the pirates from Captain Phillips?
Oh, my God. Would that count as dressing like a pirate?
Or just just an I am the captain now shirt with that suffice?
That would be enough, I think.
Yeah, I have another question about the pirate day, which is.
Yeah. All right.
A Star Wars dance party, I understand, because
you know, you get your disco version of the side.
I get this. I mean, maybe sort of vaguely.
The I just don't know how you flesh out a pirate dance party
because there are not very many songs about pirates and piracy.
Does it just become whatever music?
Do they just bail on the theme at some point?
So it starts out with like a he's a pirate cause but that remix.
So it'll be like, did it done?
Don't did it done?
Dada done. And then after that, it's just flow right up.
This is just a Kylie Minogue really quickly.
Yeah. So they run out really quickly.
And so, yeah, you're right. You're right.
They don't even try.
Honestly, they don't get like a pirate.
I mean, maybe they have like a they have like a really bowling for soup
ask a pirate's life for me was like, yo, yo, yo, a pirate's life for me.
Oh, this I do not care for.
It's a very classy cruise besides this one night.
Like it's you can totally have an adult time
and just, yeah, it's fine.
Now there is the level of adult bars that that like, you know, the district 18 and up.
Yeah, the district that does how.
I know you said they push the drinks, but like, can you escape like
a pirate doing the floss dance?
Can you like, I'm just going to go downstairs to the bar to get away from this?
So, you know, that's that's when you like enter your typical cruise life
where they're going to be like, all right, we're doing the whatever that couples
game show is. And it's like, where do you have, you know,
where did you have love?
Make love for the first time and like newlywed games.
Yeah, the newlywed game.
Like, where did you make love for the first time?
That's where your whoopee tacos.
This is this is like me, like I'm having every moment in this podcast.
I'm having this ratatouille flashback or like I take a bite of the ratatouille
and I go back to my childhood.
Oh, my gosh.
Wait, because how long were you when did you go on on one of these ships
for the first time? I've been on like seven.
So, oh, my God. So, yeah, it's been a bit.
Have you ever decade?
Did you go on the big red boat, the precursor to Disney's own fleet?
No, I wish I wish I could have been on a cruise ship and gone on to the
that's the big red boat.
I did not get to.
And I've yeah, if only that was for listeners,
if you don't know what I'm talking about, that was when like Disney
contracted with another cruise line to kind of have Disney asked cruises.
But it was before they owned their own fleet of ships.
And there was also that weird, that whole weird thing
where they were going to build a Disneyland on a ship
and pull it around to places as Disney.
Whoa. That's Disney, which I'm sure would not have worked,
but also might have.
I don't know.
I wonder if it would have still been, you know, had a port of call in Nassau.
Just to just like laws.
Just laws.
It would have been taken over by pirates at this point.
These are ours.
A stronghold somewhere down in the Caribbean.
This mini haunted mansion be ours now.
So so so Kevin, they have the new like they have a newlywed game,
so they will get a little body around these ships.
Oh, Disney like once theme park experience.
And they're and so that's when again, you walk into the world
of your typical carnival, Royal Caribbean cruise.
And then they you know, they they do recognize that they're on a Disney ship.
And so you'll have to put up with one or two like,
oh, that's not very Mickey from the host.
Yeah, that's great.
So you get a little you get a laugh from that.
But other than that, it's like my favorite.
I had the flashback, my favorite moment on any of those newlywed games.
And I go to all of them because they're they really are fun.
Like they're unapologetically a really fun time was
was when they're like, what's the craziest place you've ever made love?
And they were like in the spa on the cruise ship.
Jesus Christ.
No, no.
This is why I don't go.
And it was just like, I mean, it's just it made me very happy.
Just because I have to look at the people in the eye who spread
their fluids where I said I just know there's one person
that's like, I saw you in the spa today.
I was there.
I do want to mention, I wrote down what I think is the family
friendly version of like that newlywed style game.
It has a very unfortunate name and it's called
Do You Think You Know Your Family?
And that that seems like a recipe of disaster.
Like I had to rewind that segment of the video where I was like,
I don't know that I want to play.
Do you think you know your family?
I may want to see the where is it?
The comedy and magic of Dale Kane.
I don't know why that would count to me.
After the crusades against comedy magicians in the late 90s and early 2000s,
they were all banished to sea where they still live happily.
They're only allowed in the Bahamas.
That's what the NASA.
After we outlawed them.
Comedy magic is still still illegal here.
It's a lawless land.
Yeah, it was.
But yeah, there there was there was one magician one night.
And I go to all the shows because they're garbage.
Except for like one or two.
They're garbage fires.
There was one show.
This magician has a slideshow going behind him.
And it's kind of like that.
You know, when you set up your slideshow really poorly to our pictures
just kind of fly from one screen to the other.
And what he didn't tell us is he's both a juggler or no,
he was both a magician and a motivational speaker.
And so he's like, you can have this life.
You can have this kid.
The kid would fly by and you could have this wife and unexplained
this woman with two ninja swords and a sports bra and like complete
like camo outfit, like camo sportswear with two like ninja swords
flew by the screen unexplained.
And I'm dying of laughter.
And then the end trick was I'm so going to spoil this if any, if this magician.
So if this magician is listening to this, I apologize.
Dale Kane or someone else?
I don't know. We don't have a name.
His big thing was like Charlie's trick
because there was like this little girl named Charlie and she was
dying of something or or she was just not feeling good about herself
or she was bullied or something like that.
And she was like, she always wanted me to make it snow
because she lives in California or something.
And so while he's doing this, he's unsubtly ripping up a
thing of paper in his hands and then
very clearly, very clearly
I'm at it.
Ripping up the paper, he's folded and he keeps ripping it up and he's like.
And so I said, I'm going to make it snow for this girl.
And I'd like to make it snow for you.
And then he takes out a fan, like one of those like foldable fans.
He throws up the crumpled up paper and then he just fans it
for like a minute.
What?
It's not magic.
It's not magic at all.
Is it a laugh? Is like he wanting a laugh from it or is this?
No, this is the emotional climax.
He's shown us how to get the wife.
He's shown us how to get a child.
And now he's showing us how you can make it snow.
And this is the emotional climax of the piece.
And the music is like, you know, like almost Jobe from Arrested
Development, like final countdown-esque, like, oh,
and he's just fanning the snow up in the air and he keeps throwing up
more of the paper from his hand.
And I guess the impressive part was how much there was, but that wasn't
that impressive either.
And he just kept throwing it up and just kept and it was
spinning paper around.
Yeah. Yeah. So that might have been him.
The framing device was it was like a sick child.
That's what I remember.
And he's that like wanted it to snow.
He wanted to see snow before he passed or before because he was bullied at school.
It was either something as drastic as death or as dumb as like
he was picked on.
Also very similar to the David Copperfield show where every show
he does like a tribute to someone whose sister
someone's sister dies of cancer in the show.
Yes. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think so. That's a repeated moment.
He every every day, there's a new person whose sibling died
that he's now going to do a trick with them in tribute, which is clearly cast.
Yeah. Like, yeah, it's not real.
Well, maybe that is Angel does a lot of like dying children based magic.
I think this guy went to the Chris Angel School of Magic. Yeah.
I get him on board if you mention somebody who's sick.
Yeah, I think there's I think there's some sort of old old magician play.
Like, did Houdini ever do a show where he was trying to inspire you?
He's locked up with a sick child that he was going to get.
He's going to get out of these these chains
in honor of a child with an illness.
This bike chain belonged to Suzy. Right.
The real magic trick is convincing people that there is there is a real dying person.
That's the trick Copperfield pulls every night.
Nobody expected this to be as dark as it is.
Also, just to back up the he's he it's an aspirational inspirational thing
where you cannot you can have a wife wearing camo with ninja swords.
And also you can have a kid like my kid.
I mean, of course, anyone can have a kid.
What do you mean? Like, why do you have to be inspired to do that?
It was just like it was like a I I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know.
It was a very odd thing.
And you got to remember on these cruises, at least the fantasy and the dream,
the newest ships, the biggest ships there, they're, you know,
on their little cruise itineraries in the same location, the magic and the wonder.
They're going to Europe and Alaska and everywhere.
But these ships are going Caribbean back and Bahamas and back. That's all.
And the dream is a three to four night cruise.
So the first night embarkation day, they have a musical
showing you what you can do on the cruise. It is.
It is. It is the biggest garbage fire of a production
I've ever seen in my life, and they didn't record it.
No one's recorded it yet.
It is incredible to the point where like they'll show you like
the big water slide, they'll have a loop.
And the graphics are terrible.
And they have this loop of the water slide going and then up from the trap door.
Like because it's a family of like, you know, it's like a mom, a dad and a two,
a daughter and a son.
And they're like, we're going to have a great Disney cruise.
And the girl's like, I sure hope I find a guy.
And then the guy's like, I don't want to be here. It's Disney.
And then he gets up on the water slide and they have this terrible sequence
where they're all fake going down the water slide with the PowerPoint
water slide graphic in the back.
Oh, yeah. They wait. They're theatrically replicating the water slide experience.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
So like it's supposed to give you the illusion that you have been transported
just in front of him on the aqueduct.
Wow. Very, very odd.
They're trying to sell you on this boat.
You are trapped on like, OK, you're here.
Like, I don't know that you need to keep selling.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It just take the win. But yeah, so they have that.
And then they have three musical productions, one of which is always a big number
that's either Tangled, Beauty and the Beast, Aladdin or Frozen,
depending on what ship you're on.
And then there's two others which are musical review shows.
Also, complete garbage fires, because if they just came out and been like,
hey, everybody, we're going to sing a bunch of Disney songs, have fun.
Then it'd be like, great.
And then you get to be like, oh, they're very good singers.
They're very talented performers.
But what they don't they they don't do that.
They say, you know, we need to connect these random
Disney songs together based off of some sort of conflict.
So I think Wishes is that's a great one.
You want to watch it again? These words, there are only seven words in Disney.
Wishes is a show, and I think this is the right one,
where the three best friends at Disneyland growing up,
it's a brother and sister and a girl he likes.
And they have a bunch of Disneyland graphics
that they project behind them, so that looks like they're at Disneyland.
And that's a garbage fire, too.
I watched this. I think the same channel might have this show.
It's about they are it's three youngish people
who are going to graduate from high school soon.
And they're, you know, forgetting about their graduation stress
by going to Disneyland.
There is a virtual, as we just said, again, a staged version
of both Splash Mountain and Space Mountain.
So there's like vehicles that come up and they kind of like, whoa.
And then it is I think it seems like all of them, yeah, are just excuses
to tie together, you know, Beauty and the Beast and the whole new world.
And you'll be in my heart or whatever.
And this one I skipped.
I only watched scenes involving the teens.
I like I know what the Snow White sequence is going to be.
I've seen that before, so I only wanted to see, like,
what is the story of these guys?
And it ends with their graduation ceremony,
where one of the protagonists we've been following gives a speech
where she says, it's just it's just like my hero.
Walt Disney once said, oh, man, they like deify at a fake graduation.
She's deifying wall.
Walt Disney. Very bizarre.
Well, they don't set up in that until it's way too late
that these are not three siblings.
Oh, so when there's like a love story between them, you're like, oh, what?
What's going on? What's going on?
And they're like, yeah, no, ever since we met at Disneyland with my sister,
I was like, oh, I felt the same thing skimming through.
I saw a kiss and like, wait a second.
Don't worry. International waters.
Anything goes. You know.
We're registered in Alabama.
Yeah. Now head up to deck seven for the big sibling kiss.
There's another one where it's like some old gardener dad that like
gets cats in the cradle with his child,
and he can only learn that he's ruined his life by like the genie going like,
well, you sure don't know anything about the bare necessities.
Oh, come on.
So if that guy had to do the game, do you know your family?
He would he would fail.
No, you'd fail.
The reason I mention this is because that's it.
You have the embarkation day one.
You have the two musical reviews and you have the one big showstopper
on the five nights on the dream, which is the max for the dream.
They'll show the big showstopper twice.
But with the fantasy, their minimum is six to seven days usually.
So they have to fill two nights that were not planned by the production schedule.
And they do that with motivational speakers, comedian jugglers
and all sorts of screening of Rogue One.
Right. The one thing I saw like dinner at five, a screening of Rogue One,
the most depressing Star Wars movie at eight.
And yeah, so and sometimes they'll show if there's a premiere at sea.
And yes, premiere is spelled with EAR.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah. They'll show that in the main theater that night.
Oh, my gosh.
Well, that's that's a ton.
And, you know, we're jumping all around.
We'll give I'll get back to this this morning.
But since we brought up the musicals is another thing.
And we might just need to do a whole episode about cruzicles.
The phrase you made me aware of via DM.
I didn't know there was this term.
There wasn't. I made it up.
You invented cruzicles.
Yeah. So what I did is I took Cruz.
Uh huh. Yes.
Musical. And I put it together.
It was between that and cruzicle, but spelled differently.
But why don't they say cruz?
Disney should use that. That seems so Disney.
Yeah, it does, doesn't it?
Yeah. Very 90s Eisner Disney.
Extremely well.
And that segues into my next point.
I saw a different show that's yeah, I guess you didn't get on your ship.
And that show is called The Golden Mickey's.
Yes. And the Golden Mickey's and Mike Jason, you can listeners.
You can watch this, too.
I was so delighted to discover The Golden Mickey's is an award show
that's like for Disney stuff in general, like they're given an award to Pluto
or whatever the best dog goes to.
And like all the other shows, it's just an excuse to string together
songs. But this one is very special because there's I don't know why,
but a host has to drop out of the host isn't there.
The host got shot by a lifeboat guy dumped to sea.
So there's somebody who's like scrambling around with a clipboard
and she suddenly has to host the show and she's very nervous.
And then she gets a check in from somebody who heard that
she might need his help.
And who is that? But the big cheese himself, not Mickey Bob Iger.
Bob Iger filmed original sketches
that you can only see on this cruise ship thing.
And he's like looking down, he has an eyeline sort of down into the left,
like where the actress would be.
And he doesn't call her by name so you could shuffle anybody in there.
But yeah, in a very Eisner fashion, Iger does bits.
It's it's great. And then introduces an award.
He's like, you know, the next award goes to the
the, you know, fantastic short that brought sound to the cartoons
for the first time, a steamboat willy.
It's I honestly seeing him do some Eisner isms made me so happy.
This is what we demanded from him for years.
And we didn't know he's been fulfilling it, but only at sea.
Wow. He only does it at sea.
Where you think it's like when actors used to go to Japan to film commercials
because they were embarrassed before actors just made commercials
nonstop all the time.
They should really go.
Oh, you go ahead, Kevin.
No. OK.
What's interesting about the Golden Mickeys is that this is the last
bit, I think, of the contractual obligation that trapped Whoopi Goldberg
and Tim Allen and all of these like 90s era Disney superstar limo stars.
The superstar limo cast.
This is the last thing.
They show up to to present awards.
Oh, I didn't see Whoopi.
I see Tim Allen.
There is a bit for Tim Allen.
You only want from Tim Allen.
You only watch on the cruise ship.
Maybe there isn't Whoopi, but I see.
I see Whoopi. I'm looking at it right now.
She's in here. OK. Great.
Angela Lansbury is in here.
Wait, I missed her, too. Yeah.
Yeah. It's a fan.
It's a fantastic show.
And what they do, which is actually very clever, give them props outside
the theater, they have a little red carpet.
And while you're walking in, they have some there.
They're the camera with a live feed to the theater.
So as people are walking in, little kids can go, Hi, where are you from?
I'm from Tennessee. Like, that's great.
Enjoy the show.
And you'll see him on the screen, they'll walk in and it's it's fine.
It's cute. That's nice.
It's very nice.
We should maybe we can cover Golden Mickey separately.
I think that might require reviewing.
Let's bring it back to this thing.
Unless we don't want to.
Unless this is too limiting of a thing.
But I feel like we should do the topic that the problem is, is this thing
is just a thing about everything on the cruise.
That's the yes, it leads you into it.
Well, that's it. That shows that it's doing its job.
Its job is to tell you about all the fun things you can do on the cruise.
And it does it.
But I enjoyed just watching this in and of itself.
Natalie, the cruise director, was very charming.
She is British when and it's a delightful British accent.
And it leads to wonderful things like when she tells you about the like adults
only district, which is at least in this case is called the tube.
But in her very British way, it becomes the tube.
It's the tube.
And I really liked when she would refer to C Club host
Joshi to find out what you can do on the tube.
Meet Joshi in the tube.
Got like a Robin Leach style.
It is a very female.
Unless that's just my only default British accent.
That's possible. Yes. Yeah.
Oh, there's also the one bar becomes adults only after a certain hour.
It's called the D Lounge.
And that's disgusting.
You sick cruise fucks.
It's no we know what you're all getting up to.
You're disgustingly named.
It could be it could be the big D Lounge.
It's got pulsating lights.
That's why we call it the throbbing D Lounge.
Well, you're going to love this.
The the teen club is named the Vibe.
I am the tea.
Even hearing teen and tween clubs made me uncomfortable.
But it's then she says now, now for all of you, tweens, for tweens, it's Vibe.
And for teens, it's the edge.
It's not comfortable with hearing about tween clubs.
Yeah, the oh, here's it's just I don't know.
Are you SCA fans, society's explorers of adventures?
Oh, sure. Yes.
The organization that binds together all of the Disney explorers. Yes.
The Ocean Ears Club is Mary Ocean here.
She runs it.
And there's a bunch of SCA references in the Ocean Ears Club.
Oh, is that her main where she lives?
That's like where that character exists.
Yeah, only there, only in a sign on a cruise ship.
Everyone else gets their own attraction.
Well, wait, doesn't she have the water slide now?
And didn't they add yet?
They added something. Yeah, they added something for her.
Because I think she's right.
She is she possibly the only female member of C.
No, now the the Soren, the Soren Japan character.
Yeah, I forget the name of her, but they were like,
maybe we should have more female characters and not just one on a plaque on a boat
who has no, yeah, no represent.
It doesn't do anything fun.
Yeah, she doesn't like a cool ride.
So let's give her a slide and a plaque.
Well, they should also give her the Tween Club vibe
presented by Mary Ocean. Yeah.
I think it's funny, though, we got to get good representation
in our colonial cast of artifact stealers.
Yeah, it's a horrible, horrible tyrants.
Yes.
Pith helmet wearing more female criminals.
Hire more female tyrants.
I'm flipping through notes just to find others like little bits.
Oh, you know what?
Also, another thing, we missed the very beginning of this.
I also saw exactly what you were seeing in this whole show
right at the beginning.
The opening graphic is also extremely rudimentary.
It's like a it's a shot of the ocean.
And there's titles coming up that say our courses set second star to the right.
What is your Disney dream?
And there's a ship slowly rising the whole time,
but not in the way that animation needs perspective to change.
It's just they took a little ship clip art from zero percent to 100 percent.
Keyframe here, keyframe here.
And it just moves up very evenly.
And then more mundane copy.
Remember, all it takes is faith and trust and a little bit of pixie dust,
which that's another one faith.
And I found that odd to hear the word faith said in a Disney setting.
It seems oddly religious, which maybe that's again allowed.
It's yeah.
Oh, Scott, you're talking about the text on screen at the very beginning.
Yes, the opening graphics of this, which is it's a paragraph.
It's a lot.
They got a lot to go through.
Is this I'm is this part of the show?
It's what I saw is this puck fly.
Yeah, this is the puck.
Oh, no, I don't know.
I don't know.
This might be what played in the room because it is all a little Orent.
Our course is set first, start of the right and straight on till morning.
What is your Disney dream?
Remember, all it takes is faith and trust and just a little of pixie dust.
Let your dream begin.
It's just so long.
Each one of those has its own thing.
It's and you know, it's weird about it.
And I don't know if this is just the recording.
And I don't know if they play this on the fantasy, but this is clearly a graphic
that should only be shown on the Disney dream.
Oh, right.
Is it the wrong boat?
Yeah, it's on the wrong ship.
What? Which I am not putting the past in that they play it on that ship.
Geez, get your act together.
Well, because then very clearly right after it says the official,
what I guess is really the name of what we're talking about.
Good morning, Disney fantasy.
That's like actually, I think we'll still call this episode
the clunky title Disney Cruise morning show.
But let's be official here.
It's good morning, Disney fantasy.
They also tell you to make sure to have your key to the world card.
Yeah, the room key.
But that name doesn't make sense unless you're at Disney World.
Like, well, it means the real world.
That's the that's the that's the card you use to get on and off the ship as well.
So they can identify. Right. Yeah.
So that's so like which they really should call it the key to a few ports
in the Caribbean and also our private island.
And also the tube.
That's too good vibe and edge.
Right. But only for tweens.
Don't be sneaking into vibe if you ain't a tween.
He's becoming a little more Mary Poppins.
I there's one that I there's one stint that I like where she
describes the day's entertainment.
And she says that today is a big day
because we're getting ready for Jack Jack's Incredible Diaper Dash,
which made Erin ask, did she mean to say Jack Jack's Incredible Diaper
Rash? But I guess I guess not.
It was not. They did mean dash because what this is and she says in a great line,
what we're going to do, you're going to bring your babies to cabin 15
and we're going to race them.
It's in the it's in the it's in the main part of the ship.
It's in the atrium. It's not like, you know, like a back area of a cabin.
It's not somewhere where the babies could fall off the ship.
Bring your babies. It's not a plank.
Your babies are going to walk the plank.
The one place on the ship you can smoke.
Are you tired of your baby?
You it's legal to get rid of them here at sea.
We're gambling on babies.
Throw your cash on the ground.
Five thousand dollars on the three month old.
Winning baby take all.
Well, now hold on a second.
That's the thing that I saw on one of the other information loops.
There are no ATMs on the ship.
You have to bring cash and every guest may cash
a one hundred dollar personal check once per cruise.
What? Yeah.
I bitterly regret it.
Yeah. I bitterly quickly writing a check
made out for the Collins baby.
Kevin, are there casinos on this ship?
Because most cruise ship have casinos.
There are no casinos.
And that's that's the main difference.
And I like that because I'm not I'm not a big casino guy,
which I know is going to upset a lot of my fans.
They want a real sleaze bag, isn't they?
I'm not a big casino guy.
But yeah, so no, there's no I don't know what this like what the space is
replaced by, because those are pretty big on some ships.
Yeah, probably the kids clubs now that I say that out loud.
Or maybe the D lounge.
The D lounge is where they play all the game shows
and it's where the high stakes bingo is and where and all those kind of games.
Well, then what are the stakes of the bingo if not cash money?
Wait, what? Wait, that's an X gambling.
Oh, what?
So there is no gambling.
Yes, there's no casinos.
Oh, different questions.
So you can gamble on these things.
Yeah, I'm like I'm like a bridge troll.
You have to ask me exactly what what it is to give you the information.
Monkey's paw wishes like we phrased it wrong.
Now the wish is weird.
He doesn't like slot machines, but he loves high gal poker.
OK, got it.
Do you have to pay into the bingo or is that just something you can do?
You do. If I remember correctly, you have to buy every card.
Really? Yeah.
So that is gambling.
That's like standard bingo, though.
That's like standard bingo rules, which is gambling.
That's just a cuter Disney way to gamble.
Yeah, right. Wow. Interesting.
This is how much you can do at sea.
How much do you think you win?
Ten grand, maybe? I don't know.
Wow. Really?
I guess I'm guessing maybe.
If somebody showed up and just oddly put down like
two hundred thousand dollars on this Disney bingo.
When my numbers come in
and letter and corresponding letter.
Yeah, bingo is a bad one.
Bingo is too random.
That's kind of a bad one to do.
High stakes bingo is definitely a bad idea.
Yeah. I already lost so much money on the baby racing.
Trying to make a back on the make up.
Dumbass baby.
Just turn around, just spun around and
birthed.
That's what happens during the baby races.
I love the baby races.
You know, I enjoyed it.
Then I watched.
I will say then I watched video of Jack Jack's incredible diaper dash.
I laughed a lot.
It's really funny.
And I but it did disturb me how many videos were available
to watch of Jack Jack's incredible diaper dash, because if you're available,
if you're able to take video of this, that implies that it's not your baby down there.
So why are we filming and posting to YouTube the baby race?
There are so many different diaper dash videos from just looking right now.
And then there's also other non Disney diaper dashes
from different like from men's basketball, college basketball games.
Oh, I watched one on the floor of a of an NBA game.
Like that was pretty exciting to watch babies like.
Yeah, like being on the floor of an arena
and with the whole crowd cheering them.
I don't maybe I'm a fan of this genre.
There's a.
Corrin's. Yeah.
Diaper Derby also.
Diaper Derby is there anything different about the rules of a diaper derby
or is it essentially a dash?
I'm assuming there's a lap.
Yeah, there's got to be a lap system.
Yeah. Wow.
I didn't realize that baby racing was so popular.
And there's diaper decathelons where you have to do others.
You have to then get on a bike and fire a bow and arrow.
Shoot a gun.
Since quarantine, they've just been replaying the top tens of the
the diaper races on ESPN.
Yeah, yeah, I'm sick of watching star
diaper dashes from 2004.
The 2000 babies aren't going to be babies anymore
by the time that we need to reopen the diaper dashes.
There's zoom calling like, what was going through your mind during that race?
They're like 18 now.
Seems like you didn't have it today, would you?
They're going to put all the babies up at Disney World and keep them
quarantined so we can get diaper dashes back on TV.
Their families will not be able to visit them.
Unfortunately, that is the sacrifice that they're making.
The higher seated babies will get better resorts.
A machine will will just spray milk into their Grand Floridian room.
And that's how they will get fed.
Little rings they wear to monitor their health
or keep falling off their little baby fingers.
Too big to put them on their wrists.
Too big. Yeah.
Are we starting these diaper dashes too soon?
But America needs to be entertained.
America needs them.
You have to think about all of the commentators for the diaper
dashes and all of the the crew.
Like, it's not just about starting the sport, it's about really
simulating the economy.
The diaper dancers, you got to put them to work, the cheerleaders.
Yeah, it's a whole economy.
They're very good.
Surprisingly coordinated, the diaper dancers.
Go to the sport.
We'll go to the sports book in Vegas and start betting on them again.
That's a whole other part of the economy.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
It's got to come back.
We can't do this forever.
No. Yeah.
And what do you think?
What do you think my plan was as we head into a depression?
My I need to get my baby racing and making me sweet dollars.
Well, Vegas is open, Scott.
So hey, you're right.
We're going to your babies.
Can't get it. That's fine.
We're yeah, we're heading to the cosmopolitan.
They have a small there's a small shelf life for a baby in diaper dashing.
So, yeah, you got to get him started.
Yeah, I know. God, clocks tick even right now.
Why am I even recording this thing?
I should be on my way to Vegas.
Yeah, come on, kid.
And they just do it on roulette tables.
Go.
The diaper dashing prepares them to have the winner's mindset
when they roll over to become professional gamers, like when they go
from diaper dash to Fortnite.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We knew we were missing that pre step just to make sure.
Yeah.
Did you all happen to see what I sent you?
The zombified.
Oh, no. Yeah, let's let's talk about this.
So this is a tween activity that you made us aware of on the ships.
And this is a thing where tweens cannot just hang out and watch movies.
They can hang out in and be in a movie.
So, I mean, feel free to jump in and explain any of this.
But it seems to me as though there is a there is a preset film
and it is a zombie film is called zombified.
And half of the movie has been shot before.
And the other half is remade on every voyage starring your tweens.
Yeah. So I've been dragged to these by like, you know, family members
have been like because they show them for the whole families.
And everybody goes to the movie theater and they play the seven
or 11 minute thing for everybody.
I've seen multiple versions of this and they're all insanely bad.
But it's this weird like it's it's almost it's very 80s
in a way where it's kind of like you can be in the movies
and the pre recorded character will be like, look, there's a zombie behind you.
And then it'll cut to a very different location of you turning around
and a zombie will be coming at you.
And a lot of the movie is just the pre recorded tape after rewatching it.
It's most of it is there's just a few shots of the kids.
There's there's two main characters.
There's there's like there's a young guy and a girl in a science lab.
And most of the movies about them running from zombies and your kids
are the zombies in the relatively unchallenging dialogue free role of a zombie.
So yeah, I guess they didn't want to put a lot of dramatic weight onto the kids.
And the thing I recognize most about this is how weird the high school
and the pre recorded tape looks.
It looks like they shot it at the Walt Disney, like around the offices
at the studios in Burbank.
Like if you go back, it does not look like a high school.
No, it's a very officey high school. Absolutely.
It's strange. And I was like, is this on the ship or did they build like
pseudo sets on the ship?
They know that was not on the ship.
I don't know what the story is there.
The Cruiser Coal Training Center, which I saw some clips of, is in Toronto.
I think I think that's where they practice and recruit actors in Toronto.
So maybe because it looks the most like New York. Yes.
It looks like it looks like all the great cities of the world.
You can learn in theater.
Generic. You can learn in theater.
Yeah, I really liked I'm so glad you made me aware of zombified
and you can watch performances of zombified on YouTube.
One of my favorite things about it is the little the preamble,
maybe with a cruise director typers and who says, you know, it's been so great
hanging out with your kids, your amazing kids all week.
And now we're going to debut the film that they made.
Ladies and gentlemen, here it is zombified.
And then it starts and the lights go down and then there's a bunch of murmuring still.
And then you can in the version I watch, you can hear one one kid go, shut up.
Which is something I haven't that really that ratatouille
flashed me back to high school because I feel like middle school.
That's like what every day was people needing to hush.
And then somebody say, shut up.
Yeah, it's a very it's the way I would describe it.
If there's hundreds of versions of this online, hundreds of versions of zombified.
I would just describe it as sweaty.
Yeah, it's just uncomfortable.
Both the prerecorded tape and the tape they shoot on the ships.
Yeah, yeah. You know what I like a lot?
This genuinely got kind of a laugh out of me is that you're following
these two prerecorded characters and then they decide, well, to get away from the zombies,
we have to put on some makeup because they know what we look like.
And then they put on makeup and then there's a reveal
of just two people you've never seen before.
And they go, did it work? Do we look different?
And that's the way they weave in the people who like the two, the new people on this.
And I'm like, this this I like.
That's like an aware meta joke. That's a lot of fun.
Yeah, the I've watched a lot.
I watched it not a lot, maybe four clips of him.
And this is a huge hit.
You can tell because all the videos are just people in the audience
taping them because they're in it.
And every time they show up, there's just glee.
It's just pure glee from the audience and people around.
There you are. There you are.
Like just this must be the most exciting thing.
This is probably I guess like the that Star Trek thing they did at Universal.
It's exactly the same thing. Yeah. Right. Yeah.
But there there are so many.
It reminds me of how if you type in any musical, if you type in like guys
and dolls, high school, you will just find dozens and dozens,
if not hundreds of different productions.
And yet never one starring Jason Sheridan.
We got to find out. We got to digitize them.
I, you know, that you're in guys and dolls.
No, unfortunately, no, I was in a lot of like
the good videos I have copies of are all like
from this one drama company that makes these plays that are cookie cutter
plays with a set number of songs and like 30 characters.
So everyone can have a line.
Just for a recap, I know a lot of those there's no just a recap.
List some of your roles real quick. What have I played?
I played a Nazi saboteur
who is masquerading as a British hypnotist at a USO.
I played an island of Dr.
Moreau creature. I played.
Oh, I played a small town southern sheriff
who did not like this 60s music festival coming to town. What?
Is that a new one?
There you there's so many reveals of these. There's so many reveals.
And then I played an ascot wearing beret wearing film director.
Yeah, that's right. Please.
It's time. It's time.
You were an adult.
Or was this when you were a kid? No, this was like 10 to 13.
So like that's a hunk range.
What's that? What?
That's like that's like honk range.
That's like prime honk time.
I don't think I know what you're drift.
What word are you saying?
Honk? I know honk.
Like you guys seen the musical honk?
I've seen like seven versions of it. No, no.
Honk is probably well, maybe it was just the easiest
musical to license in Kansas City when I lived there,
because every time I was dragged to some like, oh, hey, my sister's cousins
in a musical and we have to go watch it.
It was always honk.
It was the musical version of the Ugly Dunkling.
Oh, I still wasn't sure if you were saying honk or hawk,
like the bird or hawk.
I was just saying honk weird, like I couldn't say it like.
Or honk. Have you seen honk?
It was honk with a bizarre accent.
The tubes. And honk.
Have you seen it going in the theater? Catch honk in the tubes?
He has a real honk.
Yeah, it's about a honky man.
OK, clearly this isn't as universal as I thought it was.
This happens a lot.
There's a lot of regional things in the Midwest that did not translate well.
You just thought honk was like maybe honk is huge in a certain region.
Honk did play the West End,
London's version of Broadway.
It doesn't look like it ever had any Broadway runs,
but it did have a lot of regional runs.
So, yeah, I guess so.
They probably made a fortune licensing it to it.
But yeah, did you say this was your sister or who was in honk?
I saw it was always like my girlfriend's sister or my cousin's daughter
is in some version of honk.
And do you remember if any of them played, you know,
Dot's husband, Greylag, or the domesticated chicken, Low Butt?
Well, no.
No, no.
I remember that it was always the reason I remembered it
is because there was that kind of role that you were talking about of like,
I'm the news reporter in this one scene and the ensemble in every other scene.
And so that's it was always like something like that.
Like, I really like this sentence from the Wikipedia also.
The US version is called J.
Bird rather than Jack Daw.
And the TV show is renamed America's Most Feathered.
I'm into honk.
I like honk already. Yeah, yeah.
Sorry. That's really off track.
But yeah, so honk on the tubes.
I do. I do really wish Jason had been honk. Yes, I do.
Yeah, I wish I had been in honk or the kids version of honk.
Honk, Junior, honk, Junior.
We found it at the same time.
Jinx and a lot of characters do not appear on Junior.
Wow. Low butt.
They get a low butt in honk, Junior.
Now, that is a very common thing for musical licensing.
There's like junior versions of musicals.
The most famous one I know is the Into the Woods, Junior,
which stops at the end of Act One, where everyone ends happily
and no one has died yet.
Like the second half of Into the Woods, everything goes to shit.
And if you are like doing a middle school production,
you just do the nice stuff.
Sweeney Todd, Junior.
Sweeney Todd, Junior is just a regular barber.
Yeah, he's just cutting hair.
He's just really good at his job.
Man, I'm looking sharp. Thanks, Sweeney.
This is the age range where when I went on the cruise,
I was so excited to see a scaled down production of 42nd Street at Sea
and very upset that the other nights of entertainment were just kind of standards
or like, yeah, standard, different musical numbers and stuff.
And I was like, I want to go see 42nd Street again,
which I have seen productions of multiple times.
In fact, Mike, I think I drove you to 42nd Street at the Pantages once.
We definitely did see 42nd Street at the Pantages a few years ago.
Yeah. Wow.
Why? How come? Why do you love it?
It's just about a bunch of people putting on a show and it's got a lot of great songs.
There's not much to it.
It's just sort of like it's sort of like kick lines and like dancing and showbiz.
Kick lines.
The in the original Jerry Urbach, very famously, was the director in the original cast.
Hey, Lumiere.
Yeah, that's right. Neat.
Well, that's cool.
We need to get Jason back on the stage.
You're telling me we got to re what's that?
What do you re stage honk?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
License honk.
Yes. The Jason Sheridan led reprieve reference when that reference was so much different in my mind.
I thought I was just going to be like honk and you were going to be like, holy crap.
Are you serious? I'll be like, yeah, we're going to become best friends.
But no, or we or we just take honk.
So for granted, like, yeah, yeah, yeah. Honk.
Ever look, that's an obvious reference. Yeah. Yeah.
Oh, man. No, hang on.
But that did happen.
I think we're all very excited about honk.
So don't sell your honk reference short. Yeah. Yeah.
OK, back to the ship.
I mean, I'm just I'm just giving through random things that happen in this.
I want one quote that I like a lot.
And speaking of adult versions and junior versions, there is a bibbidi
bobbidi boutique on the ship.
The like the what is mainly a princess and pirate,
you know, makeover place that is at the parks as well.
And in the video, there's a moment that I like where
the guy in charge of it clarifies that for the most part,
you can only get your pirate makeovers if you're under 12.
But on Pirates Day, as you mentioned, Kevin, the rules change and quote,
that is when we can take anybody from three to dead.
And it's said with about that much mustard on it, like the nothing that I just did.
And then and ignored by British Natalie, who just says, wow,
like there's no he doesn't emphasize it as a joke.
And you're just like, what?
Three three to dead.
What a disturbing phrase.
I think they also said they could make you up to be sailors or captains
at this bibbidi bobbidi boutique.
So you could look like seagoing Mickey, who Mickey
in his captain's outfit looks a little like Elron Hubbard.
Can I say Captain's Mickey is maybe my favorite Mickey
next to that 80s polo shirt Mickey?
Yeah, that's true.
Captain Mini. Oh, yeah.
Maybe his first mate, Mini.
Yeah, what are their position? Yeah, I'm not sure.
On the ship, do you get to do you get a lot of Mickey and Minnie time?
Yeah, no, there's it's great.
And the lines are short because there's not as they're everywhere.
They do meet and greets pretty frequently and they have a good variety of characters.
So, yeah, there is a Donald seat sticking out of the one
the one part of the ship.
The port. Yeah.
Is there is it a regular size Donald seat or is it a giant one?
You seen Donald's like Donald Butt? His butt.
Yeah, yeah.
That's the thing we say seat.
We call it a seat. Oh, sorry.
Yeah, it's yeah.
Let me go to my podcast, the right second gate show Bible.
Yeah, I got it. Sorry.
It's when I guess by that logic, then because they're birds,
then all the characters in honk would also have seats.
Yeah, that's right.
Low, low seat. It would be low seat.
Oh, yeah. Let's get butt out of there. That's offensive.
Yeah, low seat.
Um, the that's the aqueduct.
You see his seat, similar to how Mickey's fill our magic ends with him
with his his seat.
The seat. Yes. Now you're doing it. Great.
The aqueduct is supposed to be like that part where you're
it's he was supposed to fly out and then you it's actually like a post
show with a water slide.
There's a pre show which you see all the little duck feet going up
into the slide and there's a little pre show comics panel
explaining the story of the aqueduct.
The main show is you riding the ride and the post show is you seen
where Donald ended up is that because you get off and you walk around
and you see the post show, which is just Donald's seat.
It's a very interesting narrative structure.
Oh, the aqueduct.
Oh, there's a plot to it. Essential.
There's a plot to this water slide.
And the pre show rhymes.
So, yeah, go for that.
Geez. Oh, that's cool.
What else? What have we missed about this?
This this show?
I I'll say it made me a little uncomfortable anytime that they
I think the constant use of the word adult is bothersome to me.
I guess they know they need to clarify that some of these things are adults
only when you hear phrases like adults crazy karaoke.
Adult just implies doesn't it sound seem like it's going to be pornographic?
Like, put your keys in the bowl.
Yes, the nightly swing.
These keys to the world open up a whole new world for you at sea.
Oh, that's what they're for.
That is fantastic.
So what every newlywed game, that's their big Disney joke, is they say,
will you describe your sex life?
And then they say, is it this Disney song?
And it's like a whole new world.
Oh, gosh, what is it? It's like a whole new world.
What even would be applicable in this?
Yeah, it's like it's like it's a whole new world.
Like, it's good.
There's one that's like it's fine.
And it's a small world is the one that's like, oh, yeah.
Do you get it? Yeah.
Do you get it? Yeah, no.
That is the kill. That is the kill every night.
Yeah, it does every night.
And then about the morning show, the one thing that's very jarring
is the morning in which she is in the spa, because it is not immediately
recognizable as the spa.
So it kind of just looks like she's coming to you from her stateroom in a robe.
Yes, I did notice this.
It looks just like, yeah, she's in her bedroom. Yeah. Yeah.
The way it's framed is a very small looking space with just a mirror.
And there's nothing that would you would just look at it and go,
oh, it looks like they have shitty twin beds in all the cabins. Yeah.
So this is how it begins.
And then a couple of Russian women appear on screen
and talk about freezing your fat and analyzing your skin.
And the best part, the ship is rocking while that's happening.
We saw we caught this when we were watching it.
You can see the like curtains in the background start to wave.
And like everyone kind of like trying to get their footing
because they are clearly at sea. Weird.
It's amazing.
There are more problems inherent in the production of Good Morning
Disney fantasy, just constant tripods tipping over and boom,
like operators barfing.
Well, there are in so many rooms that have echoes that are just it's like
there's there's some rooms where it's just like there's like three echoes.
Hello.
You know what I was thinking, though, is that, yes, this is so unpolished
and we're watching kind of this badly shot thing that's just in rooms
and boring rooms where the sound is bad.
But it's July 20, 20.
This is what everything looks like.
All TV is good morning Disney fantasy.
Now I'm so used to blown out sound and tired looking people
and shots not changing and no editing.
This would the Disney Cruise Morning Show predicted the entire virus world.
Yes, it really prepared a lot of people for it.
It was a slow easing.
Yeah, Natalie really with Natalie, the cruise director
could have given some tips to your Seth Meyers is and your James
Corden's about how to keep things engaging in an unmoving,
badly composed shot for 15 minutes with the headroom.
I think Colbert to just watch this
when he was learning how to use a camera a few weeks ago.
He's like, oh, well, every shot needs about half the screen of headroom.
That's very true. And if everybody's been zoomed, I always like.
Meanwhile, he's he's he's far he's way, way, way in the corner.
I guess nobody's going to see that visual gag that I just know.
You see, you know, you see you had about like 60 percent up at the top.
It's like you were hiding from your own shot.
That's the whole thing.
There's people who never figure out Zoom headroom.
I guess those people are called parents.
I also this we were probably, you know, in the last section of this episode.
But Jon Stewart just did a round of press for this movie he released.
They didn't send him a USB mic.
Yeah, like I keep clicking on interviews and it's the same as just this computer
audio and you'd think like to do like a press on major shows.
They would have sent him an 80 dollar mic.
If you're going to be on every television show, yes, perhaps
you should think about a microphone.
It's crazy. Amazon Prime him a mic, for God's sake.
And he was I think he was too close to the camera.
I think he we're all learning zoom camera etiquette.
I don't think no.
I think no one knows where to be, like what plays.
I don't know how to make jokes land anymore.
It's all we're all trapped in this box.
It's crazy.
This is something I know for sure.
That's a movie I will be able to resist.
Applause from me.
I was learning to work remotely with like, you know, pitching ideas to people.
Yeah. And you learn very quickly that your social cues about like
when someone wants you to stop talking is not immediate over Zoom.
So, you know, I'd be like, and here's the idea and here's who I am and a lot of
a lot and I love this.
And then after a while, I'm like, oh, wait, by now I would have checked
to see if they were zoning out.
They've been zoning out for a while.
So, yes. Yeah.
Everybody looks very small.
None of it. None of it makes any sense.
I don't I was thinking how I've felt for months and months, honestly,
like I'm trapped in a cabin on a Disney cruise with like
mild entertainment offerings being put in front of me tonight.
The cast of Ghostbusters will be reuniting with your host, Joshi Gad.
Join us on Deck 7.
Don't get coronavirus.
Did anyone encounter the digital portholes?
Kevin, did you have this in your room?
OK, so this is interesting.
Yeah. As with everything.
So digital portholes, for those that don't know, are TV screens
shaped in a circle that give the illusion that an interior room
with no windows or a deck is has a window to the outside.
And Disney characters come through.
It was their way of adding a bit of magic and a bit of actual, like,
you know, life to the staterooms that are on the interior of the ship.
It had a adverse effect.
And those rooms are often more expensive and more heavily booked
because of the porthole room, because of that porthole.
Kids are like, I want the magic porthole.
And so it's this weird reverse effect where in order to compensate
for the problem, they actually overcompensated.
And now those rooms are in demand.
Wow. So have you experienced have you seen it?
No, I haven't experienced it up front.
Up close, I would like I like to see the real world when I
and not and not like Stitch going by on his little rocket ship.
Well, you're not going to like this Star Wars hotel
then that they're building in Florida.
But that's another I don't want to get us off.
I'm only going to be I'm now realizing I'm only going to be on board with it
if there is a British lady telling you what you can do on the ship every day.
What's it called?
What's the what's the ship called?
The Galactic Star Cruiser.
Good morning, Galactic Star Cruiser.
There will be lightsaber training and some comedy magic provided by
Dave Willis.
I think there's a cantina for tweens.
The Star Wars.
The Sabre.
A wretched hive of scum and tween villainy.
The Star Wars series does have a fine history of British character actors,
so they're going to have to like shoot footage with them and go like,
no, you got to be stiffer.
You got to be stiffer.
Like we want this to be real.
So it's like a real cruise ship.
So this should be Fesmer.
That's the British one.
Yes.
Oh, yeah.
Cruise director Fesmer.
I'm good now.
Just a jolly host.
Well, that's the interesting thing of the Galactic Star Cruiser
is it is a cruise ship in the world of Star Wars.
And Batuu is like one of your ports of call.
Right, right.
Which is odd, but it makes sense.
But my most interesting thing about the Galactic Star Cruiser and Batuu
is Batuu is already like this weird like cruise port,
because every time if you've ever been on a cruise, you know,
when you land on that port, the entire economy that surrounds
the dock of the cruise is based off of you.
You are made to go buy this, get in this van, you know, buy this,
buy this merchandise.
And Batuu is like that.
It's like you like what are these cruise guests like that are coming to Batuu?
They like Luke Skywalker and Sleight Sabers and we'll make them build a fake one.
And it just it comes in my head.
Cannon, everything you do in Batuu is not canon.
It is just put on by the people of Batuu to make you feel like you're getting
an authentic Star Wars experience.
Interesting. Oh, you mean like so they don't even eat Bronto wraps there.
That's just like touristy food.
Yeah, they eat it up.
Those lightsabers aren't real.
They're toys, but you just tell the kids they're real.
Like that's why Rey looks so different is because it's just some actress
on the planet. They're pandering.
They're pandering to idiot tourists.
Yeah, that's what Batuu is.
Yeah. Oh, Batuu is a crappy port town where you buy a T-shirt and there's like
there's weird like class structure that's kind of unsettling.
And oh, man, I'm not going to be able to look at it.
The same way when we go.
Literally everything like you even the rides are like,
oh, they want to ride the Millennium Falcon.
Yeah, there was that time that they wanted to do a shitty music festival
on Batuu and then it fell apart because the guy was a scam.
Well, it was Hondo Anaka.
Hondo Anaka tried to start a festival.
But Max Rebo dropped out.
It wasn't. He was never really on board.
Yeah, they never. Yeah, they never actually.
The Star Wars influencers scammed everybody.
All as I know is, if I'm paying that much for that galactic star
cruiser, I better get some death sticks like they're better via death stick area
where I can just like light up like Obi Wan.
That's what I want.
Death sticks is the very on the nose name of cigarettes and the prequels.
Correct. Yes.
Yeah. In Dexter Jeksters, is he lighten up inside Dexter Jeksters?
In the diner? No, no, they're in the they're in the club at the start of
the clones. Yeah, OK.
Isn't that like club?
No, Indiana Jones.
Obi Wan is in Temple of Doom.
You know exactly where I know where you're going with it.
I just want I honestly, I just watch the scene like two weeks ago
and attack of the clones.
They're they're trying to find Zam Wessel, I believe.
Obi Wan and Anakin. Yes.
But I can't think of the name of the club.
Oh, well, vibe in the tube, in the in the space tube.
The cruises are an entirely different world of fun,
like the Star Wars stuff they do on there.
It's just everything is backwards from Walt Disney World. Everything.
It's every Walt Disney World.
Nobody goes to the live shows at the cruise line.
Everyone does. At Walt Disney World, it is all designed.
So you are in the center of an experience and all the the warehouses
and the facades are facing inward and on the cruise are facing outward,
which changes the flow of traffic.
Because everywhere you're going, the interior of the ship
is the guts of the organization versus when you're at the theme parks.
Those are on the outside.
So the way it's designed is backwards. It's just.
It's weird. Interesting.
It's like a whole paradigm.
It's like a completely inverted way to do themed entertainment.
And what is your opinion of Castaway Key?
I love Castaway Key.
Is that what they don't have Walt's playing there?
No, they have some.
So what Castaway Key is a really fun, fun place.
There's not a ton to do, but it is nice to have beaches to yourself.
Serenity Bay, which is the adult beach, which they like design.
So it's like a walk in pool so you can just keep walking.
And so you'll see adults like it takes probably like, you know,
100 yards before it even gets up to your to your thighs.
So you'll just see people way on the distance with standing up.
And that's when they have barbecue, which is terrible.
But I'm from KC, so all barbecues terrible.
But that's not there.
But yeah, so it's it's fun.
And yeah, it's it's very bare bones, though.
I'm hoping with this new island, they do something to give a little bit more.
Because if you're not into generic sports type activities,
like if you're into snorkeling, congratulations, you're going to go
see the 20,000 League sub that they sunk in the back.
And you can see Mickey Underwater.
If you are into bicycling, bicycling, there's the Castaway Key 5K,
which always happens on the last day of the cruise.
So that's awesome.
But I believe I read, unfortunately, Castaway Key is prone to being
in the path of tropical storms and hurricanes and that
20,000 Leagues sub may have been washed out to see one of them.
So there was one of them.
And we lost one of them.
OK, there's still one still there.
One of them is gone.
It was lost a video of like a couple who went and they're like,
well, this was the island the last time we were here.
And we just missed a storm by a week and all of the beaches were covered in like
red tide, seaweed, dirt, like stuff.
So it is susceptible to Mother Nature.
Yeah, it is. And it also it doesn't dock a lot of times.
I've likely never had a day where it doesn't dock, but they're very set.
They are very open saying because of the way
because it's only so deep.
If the waters are too choppy, we can't dock and the very end.
So they have a they have a backup day of activities.
If that happens, I've never that's never been triggered for me.
Like it's never like, oh, here's my backup day.
So that's never happened. But yeah, that's the case.
But, you know, they're doing what is the new one called Lighthouse Point?
They announced a D23.
Is that the Joe Rowdy Island?
Yes. And I've never been so.
I don't want to upset people intrigued by a project
because they were when they said a populated island,
I was like, what?
Wait, wait, what do you mean populated?
Like there are people that live there.
They they bought it.
And they're then the people aren't leaving.
They were they don't they didn't really give me the logistics of what's happening.
But, you know, with with Castaway Key, it was an old pirate island
that I'm assuming was then, you know, bought by some real estate developer.
It was super wealthy and it was eventually given to Disney.
It's very small.
Nobody maybe a few people live there over the course of its history.
You know, it's point I'm pretty sure is a populated island.
That's very strange.
Guess who bought your island?
So this might be like the apcot dream come true.
Yeah. Of an actual Disney owned island city.
Yeah. Strange.
I mean, should we move there, though?
Maybe.
I need to look this up.
Perhaps I am.
You know, I just I just googled this and let me just give you a little bit of warning.
If you Google roadie island,
Google is very confused because it is exactly a seems like a misspelling of Rhode Island.
Oh, yeah.
Did you mean Rhode Island?
No, amazingly, I did not.
Well, what the heck, Agluthora.
Weird. Maybe it's just maybe like maybe it's similar to Castaway Key.
Where there's a it's a smaller part of a bigger place.
Does that make sense?
So like Castaway Key, I think Castaway Key has another island where the cast
members live and then they commute via boat every day to the island
to get it ready for the cruise as they come.
So maybe they bought an island off of a larger island.
Hmm. What if, though, this has me thinking that what if the island
that they bought is like full of these these kind people who live off the land
and they work together and there's a lot of community?
And then roadie, the maker of the Avatar ride, comes in to destroy the island,
blow up the town square, like, get them off.
I want them gone.
And roadies marching around in a big robot suit firing bombs.
Wow. Way to practice what you preach.
Yeah. OK, I just I looked it up.
They're buying a parcel of land on the Bahamian island of Aluthora,
if I'm pronouncing that correctly.
So they didn't buy the entire island just not yet.
OK. But so then they're going to need some person to go into the body
of an Aluthrin to stop meksut roadie from. Right.
There's a there's 11000 people that live on this island.
Wow. Really? Wow. Yeah. Wow.
Which is which is too small to do this.
You know, if it was bigger, if it was like this,
they're buying a small beach on an island of 10 million people.
You'd be like, whatever.
But that's too small of a population to not be
drastically affected by whatever Disney does.
I've been told Ja Rule is consulting, so I'm assuming it's legitimate.
Let's be legends.
We're going to. I don't want to bring that up.
That's roadie.
Oh, no, Joe, don't get caught up in Ja Rule's magnetic personality.
Joe and Ja are toasting champagne, riding pigs around.
Yeah. Oh, my gosh.
I was going to say I want to I want them to rebuild Fordlandia.
Was that have you ever heard of that?
No, Landia, the islands that Henry Ford like made people
build cars or whatever or some.
He built like a factory island where only men were allowed and all like women
were banished and men row to another.
Anyways, it was in Brazil.
Oh, dear God, Fordlandia.
Yeah, Fordlandia is like not a theme park, but it sounds like it.
That's when I'm just ready to lose subscribers because I really want to tell
tell this story.
Well, as long as you're not pro Fordlandia,
as I scan through and see phrases like anti-semitism and well.
Well, I mean, people, people, you know, in my most recent episodes, I've been very
they've been more dense and people have been like, get back to doing.
Oh, the tea.
Oh, they want to share the to give you.
I thought the Coney Island episode was fascinating.
I didn't know that whole epic story.
Yeah. The elephant brothels and and anti-semit
semitic beaches and yeah, yeah.
Oh, no. So now, so well, here's another lengthy anti-semitism related topic.
Well, yeah, it is not a theme park thing.
But as we know here on the second gate, doing things that aren't theme park
things can be very satisfying.
And we land when if it's very long, we love it.
Everybody loves it.
Before this goes crazy longer, we should maybe begin the debarkation presentation.
I have one quick I have one quick thing to point out from the video.
I in the in the where she's sitting in what I assume is what you would call,
I don't know, the cockpit.
What would you say the control room for the boat?
It looks like the technology on the 1960s Star Trek.
Isn't it not look like control, like control panel with but like, you know,
it looks simple, like very like 60s.
Hi, sure. Like 60s high tech.
Like I don't I feel like like cockpits of planes look more sophisticated.
This is sort of just like big buttons and like a couple of levers.
I was very interested.
Well, the boat, like all Disney rides, is operated by teens. Right.
It's got a four program up there.
So it's got to be simple.
Like when you see people, when you're on a ride
and you see like they open the thing and they hit that button,
you don't know what it is.
I assume it's just a go button.
I imagine a lot of these are just dummy buttons like on
Smugglers Run.
Yeah, a lot of them are.
They don't even push in. Right.
There's they're just blink.
Are there are there only six positions in that room that you can go on?
Yes, yes. There's two.
You know, engineers, two gunners that shoot the guns off the side of the boat.
Yes, which two pilots.
Firework night when there's lurkers in the in the distance.
So they don't steal your fireworks for you.
It's just fireworks. Don't worry, folks.
We aren't using those guns to clear out that Rhode Island.
That's that was the thing they said.
Disney Cruise Line is the only one that shoots off fireworks at sea.
That's why they're all like, you know,
swimming around, you know, the other ships.
It's pretty amazing. Yeah, yeah.
Well, I want pilot next time. That's all I know.
OK, I've been I've been engineer plenty of times.
I don't want Gunner. It sucks.
Barely. Closing thoughts.
So last last minute things.
This is this is fun to have a big free range conversation
that's sort of stemming from a video you watch in your hotel room on a ship.
But do we like that?
Do we like the low rent nature of it?
We always talk about how we want the specials to be more low rent.
We want mistakes to happen. Why are they so overedited?
And I'm very charmed by that.
This is this is its own unique little, you know, sort of crapily done thing.
Yeah, it's fun when you get to see because we've we've we've
yeah, we've been talking about this where it's like the old stuff
and old sitcoms where they don't like maybe what was it?
What was the sitcom where they were saying they would spit off the skyway
or throw ice cubes, throw ice, blossom, blossom,
would slip by that they throw ice cubes off the skyway.
And that would never fly in a shape.
Iger world where you'd give people bad ideas.
Yeah, it is. It's nice and charming that this is produced in house.
And I mean, let's have more.
Let's have more of it.
Let's have this production value for some sort of ABC special
promoting the Galactic Star Cruiser.
Yeah, just some just some lady, which which with the current
production possible that it's might be what it has to be.
Yeah, that's true.
So what's your name again?
Cruise director Natalie, get ready.
You're going to you're the face of Galactic Star Cruiser.
Yeah, I love I mean, it does make it really fun.
And there's been other I've seen another version of this
where there's this really great joke that I forgot to mention earlier
that like they poke fun at themselves more on the cruise ships,
like they're like their quality control really can't reach international waters.
Like there's one video it was on one of the days like Will,
like, you know, we're we are Disney, but we can't control the weather yet.
Oh, sure. Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah. So like that.
Yeah. So that's the way.
So we can't control the weather, but we're working on it.
And it was like, ah, and so, yeah, but like the it's like
it's very home like you feel you feel like, you know, they produced it
this morning. Right.
And that's that personal touch that you're talking about.
You have the waiter who takes you, you follow around from day to day.
And you might see the host of this thing walking around the ship.
It's all very personal.
Yeah. You know, you know, they're making these videos fresh.
They're baking them up fresh for you.
And it is it is like, like I said, the last bastion of the Disney difference
of just like it really they really do go the extra mile compared to other cruise
lines because they really do have to compete with other cruise lines.
It's not just enough to be the kid cruise.
They do a really good job and they're really highly rated
across the board as far as cruise lines go.
But yeah, they do a great a great, great job.
I like them a lot. Yeah.
It's a very positive sentiment for me.
Usually I remember our last podcast, it started with Mike
reading to me a quote from Michael Eisner
that I were like a quote that I said about Michael Eisner. Ah.
And it was like it was like a breaking my knees before the
the game.
I was like, we had to defend our hero.
Sure. Yeah.
I've been stewing for a while, but now we've met.
We're friends. We're getting more positive.
We had fun thinking about a cruise for a little while.
Kevin Perjury, you survived podcast, The Ride, the second gate.
And thank you for this topic.
This is a lot of fun.
Let's exit through the let's disembark through the gift shop.
Is there anything you'd like to plug?
I make a show called Defunctland.
Also, I you could go.
I really should plug this themed alternative.
You can look it up on YouTube.
Themed alternative is a like avant garde
random series, experimental theme park based series.
We do. We watch old Disney specials and do commentary on them.
We have a an audio drama type thing.
So, yeah, it's a bunch of experimental theme park comedy adventure content.
Oh, cool. I was not aware of that before.
That's yeah. Yeah.
I'll check that our listeners should too.
And hey, what's up with this
Halyx movie or you're producing a documentary that we appear in
and that we we seemingly helped inspire?
What's this? What's the status of it?
Is this on the air? Yeah.
Yeah. OK. OK.
Oh, it's a reveal secrets because it doesn't matter
because I would have said the same thing regardless.
OK. No, no, no. I'm just kidding.
But it's a it's going well right now.
We are trying to fit the good boys into the week
because there's so much of you watching in the interview
that was done before quarantine many months ago.
There's so much of you watching like almost a commentary track
of the footage we found.
So we're trying to fit that in.
Well, you might be revealing that that with.
Yeah, there's you know, we for listeners who don't recall or haven't heard it.
There was this 80s space band at Disneyland called Halyx.
We sort of discovered it and talked about it on the show.
And now there's this whole documentary coming from Matt Serrano,
this director, and you're producing it.
And we were interviewed and they and Matt surprised us with.
We found all the footage of a full concert by this Tomorrowland
space band from 1981.
And it's really well done.
And I'm really happy with the documentary.
I think it documentary filmmaking is always a crapshoot,
for lack of a better word, as far as like, is there anything there?
And there was a lot there.
And we got almost all of the band members on camera.
That's kind of a that's kind of a reveal, I guess.
But they they're there and they're talking about it.
And we also got like major people that were involved, execs at Disney, Mike Post,
who every theme song you've ever heard in your life.
I always forget what all of them are.
But the one that always rings in my head is greatest American hero.
Believe it or not.
You talk to this guy, you worked on those songs and you for Disney a long time ago.
And you interviewed him for this for this doc.
Yeah. So it's a really fun doc.
As far as what I'm assuming your question was, was not casual as in when was it coming out?
Oh, no, I'm just curious.
I would just say I would be having fun editing and stuff.
Yeah, it should be out in late July at latest early August.
We were going to do festivals.
We were going to do this.
You were going to do a little theater tour, maybe.
And then the world ended.
And our dreams of making millions off of a documentary
heavily tailored to one of the strongest copyright holders in the history of the world was diminished.
So we're going to be millionaires.
Damn it. We're going to be millionaires if it wasn't for this one thing.
You'd be as rich as if you had bet successfully on a diaper dash.
So it'll be on YouTube.
That's that's very exciting.
I you know what?
And that knowing that we all are in this movie, I feel like the twins in zombified.
This is going to be a big debut.
And we're in the movie.
Depending on where you're placed, you might feel exactly like the twins.
Oh, no. All right.
Oh, man.
It might just be like, where are we?
And then the hey, that's I know how it goes.
Yeah, we're we're working our our darnedest to to fit in.
So you're going to you're going to be in it.
But I don't be surprised if it's like the credits move over and it's 10 minutes
of you watching footage from statler and Waldorfing
footage that appears to find.
Well, if you recall, that's the majority of your interview.
Yeah, pretty.
The audience is going to be audience can be really upset because they're going to go,
you know, we don't want to hear from the people in the band or the people
who wrote the songs. We want to hear from those guys on that podcast.
So I think they're going to unless you put us in a significant part,
I think people are going to be very upset.
Well, then I'll try to I'll try to work you closer to the climax.
OK, thank you. Yes.
Yes. It's a bit what bigger payoff could there be than us in a room of Funko Pops?
We thought it was cool. We like the band.
It looks good. They look the best part of any documentary about some
culty thing is when the three dweeb show up and then I like it.
Well, I'm glad you understand that.
We want to make everyone look good.
There is a it's a really
take the rug out from it to be like, and we found it.
Unless we put you at the very, very top.
No way.
Unfortunately, you you cannot control an audience going like,
oh, that's how podcasters move.
Yeah.
So all of America said about the HBO pod, same America show.
Anyway, moving on, wrapping up the show, disembarking.
Kevin, thanks for being here.
This is a blast.
Come back any time.
This you've set the bar high with bizarre topics.
Tarzan rocks Disney Cruise morning show.
I feel like now. Oh, I haven't even began.
Fordlandia, perhaps, if you don't feel like editing the documentary about it,
whatever. Yeah. Come back any time.
I feel like I should give you my next like the next topic in two years
that I'll come on with if you have anything planned it, please.
I the the the cones.
Do you remember those cones that used to have it up?
Got the cones.
Wait, maybe I don't like it was like a sandwich cone.
It was like an ice cream cone, but it was like meatball marinara.
Well, did it have some name?
I feel like I've read recently about some something that I've read about.
Yeah. But yeah, what was the name of this?
I know what you're exactly talking about.
We've stumbled across the park.
Before.
Can we just do an episode of catch all that is all about all the cones?
There's the cones at California Adventure.
Cones. Yeah.
Cones. A parking lot cones that create lanes for you to drive in.
Just cones. Exclamation point with Kevin.
Oh, my gosh. This is going to drive me crazy.
Not beaver tales.
You're not talking about the Canadian delight beaver tales.
And it's not a hand which it's a hand which.
Oh, that is it is a hand.
OK, that's what I just saw. Yes.
Hmm. OK, we could do a hand which hand which is with Kevin Persger coming.
Yeah. In a while.
All right. In two years, boy.
Yeah. Yeah. Looking forward to it.
Everybody else, you know what to do.
Keep subscribing to the second gate as you already are.
Be on the lookout for the Halyx documentary, which we play a giant, giant part in.
And we're saying and well, we'll talk to you with some more bullshit soon.
Bye, everybody.