Five, four, three, two, one.
I'm just gonna say it's morphin' time.
Welcome to podcast the Ride the Second Gate.
Joining me as always, I'm Mike Carlson by the way,
I'm really screwing this intro up.
I am of course the purple ranger, sorry Scott.
Scott Gairdner here, what color ranger are you?
Orange because I looked at an orange item in front of me,
so therefore orange.
Orange ranger!
And Jason Sheridan is the what ranger?
I always liked the red ranger because in the original cast
he was named Jason and had a sword,
and then when they asked for more money
they immediately recast him.
Is that what happened?
That is what happened, yes.
Very sad, it's the cruel.
Hype Saban, what are the worst men in America?
Power Rangers famously made very cheaply reusing footage,
and then once it was a huge hit,
some of the actors decided they'd like to get paid
real TV money, and he said no,
and fired the ones who were gonna walk away,
and then recast them, and of course like,
idiot kids like me were like, huh,
I like those other characters,
but okay I'll keep watching.
You proved Saban's point.
Saban, the company Saban made a lot of our beloved
90s children's entertainment,
but again, just screw job after screw job,
made so cheaply, and I'm sure people made a fraction
of what they should have been paid,
because just churning out the merchandising too,
merchandising huge for Power Rangers and X-Men.
Right, these people who were on the show
should have made a lot of money for it,
because there was a ton of money to be made,
and they were making, and Power Rangers is still going today,
and they've been in different forms,
there's been many, many different series.
I'm not a huge, I was very into the first two series,
and now I have not followed it since then,
but yeah, it's made so much money,
and I'm sure, I don't actually have the numbers
of what everyone was making on the first season,
but I'm sure it's just, I'm sure it's like $1,000
an episode, it's criminal, I think it's that low.
And probably for the film as well, I would imagine,
it's just like a favor to them to let them be in a movie.
I would assume, maybe they got a little bit of a bump
because it was gonna be on a bigger screen.
But to be clear, and to just cut through,
this episode is not about the Power Rangers in general,
I don't wanna take things off the table,
but I'm not even sure that it's about
the Power Rangers at all.
I think what we need to focus on,
what I'm excited to focus on,
is the villain of Mighty Morphin' Power Rangers,
the movie, and that is Ivan Ooze.
Yes, of course you're right,
Ivan Ooze is not responsible for these problems,
these grievances that we have.
Ivan Ooze is bad, but he wouldn't give all his riches
to the Clinton Foundation.
Right, oh, Bernie Sanders, I hate him.
He would never say that.
Even I have limits.
He seems like a nice man.
I think there's gonna be a lot of Ivan Ooze voice today.
I was thinking that and prepared to do so,
but it's a little in question how you do an Ivan Ooze voice
because it's pretty different.
Yes, that's true.
In every scene, in every line.
Yes, that's a good point as well.
I'm doing the one where he's obviously imitating WC Fields.
That was what I was thinking too, that was my plan.
That seems like the most fun one to do.
Yeah, the Ooze is back.
Just having a ball in this movie.
And I mean, I don't know about you guys, Mike,
I know you said you had a little,
I was all in on Power Rangers for a few seasons.
And when this movie came out,
it was probably one of the highlights of 1995 for me.
Yeah, no, I was, I'm in all this garbage,
this kid garbage with robots and monsters, I love it.
It came on the air and I remember thinking,
I knew it was not, I knew I was old for it.
I knew I was too sophisticated maybe to really enjoy it.
That being said, I loved the monsters, I loved the robots,
and I watched it for a few seasons.
And when this movie came out,
I also was very, very excited about it.
I read a bad review in the newspaper
and I was just upset before.
And then I was like, no, it has to, it should be good.
I'm sure it's good.
And I saw it and I was like, it was good.
And it was, you were completely justified.
100% right, yeah.
Incredible performance.
Have I explained my Power Rangers connection on the show?
I feel like I might be repeating a story, but.
No, I feel like you said you had less affection for it
than either of us.
What happened was it was starting to build
and everyone around me was getting into Power Rangers
and watched Power Rangers a little bit.
And then there was this one time
where I started explaining it to my parents.
And it's so cool in this red one
and why won't they all have different colors?
And they all do fighting and they're all part of a robot.
And then the robot forms into a bigger robot
and there's toys of all of these things.
And my parents wheels started turning
and then they just laid it out real clear to me.
They said, Scott, you just did Ninja Turtles.
We just got through Ninja Turtles and that was fun.
And you got all those toys of all the different kinds
and the cartoons and the movies.
Do you have to do this one?
Like, do you think this is so great
and do you really feel like you need to do it?
And I thought, and I was like, no, no, that's a good point.
Maybe I don't.
And so my parents just like coldly talked me
out of being into Power Rangers.
They just used logic on me and I listened
because I'm a good boy.
Wow.
I've never, you have not told that story.
It's pretty old showing.
That is, yeah, I was much more of the,
listen up everyone, we're doing this now.
This is the way it's gonna be.
This is complimenting the X-Men
and they are all going to fight each other.
I will be reasonable in my request.
I was not a kid who had to have all of them.
And I was not a kid who like, I would,
I was like, no, I don't need the big Megazord.
I will take just the Dragonzord.
Well, that's fine.
And that'll be the big Christmas present.
You're talking to a kid who needed all of it.
I made, we had had the Dragonzord on a hold from Toys R Us
cause they didn't have it and they put it on hold for us.
And this is a story.
I don't know what was going on in my mom's life at the time,
but she was very, it was a night
where she seems very stressed out.
And I very rudely demanded we go to Toys R Us
because they just called saying it had come in.
So I forced my mother to take me at like 8 p.m.
over to Toys R Us to get that Dragonzord
cause I was so obsessed and I was so excited about it.
I'm so rudimentary.
I don't know what a Dragonzord is.
I was so hard out when my parents, what's a Dragonzord?
Well, so the Dragonzord is Tommy the Green Ranger's zord
and it's sort of separate from the other zord.
So the Megazord-
You gotta, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Let's back up.
What's a zord?
I don't know what a zord is.
Okay, okay.
Let's establish some language.
So the Power Rangers, like the core five Power Rangers
are like red and then they have a dinosaur
that's affiliated with them.
Or like, I guess Mastodon is not a dinosaur,
but like, you know, when they put up the,
like those coins with the little communicator,
whatever you call it.
It's not a communicator.
It's a-
Sure.
Well, and that's the, those are the robots
they individually inhabit.
They're all based on different creatures
and then they all form into one.
So they each have their own little robot
that forms into the big Megazord.
Then they introduce Tommy the Green Ranger
and he had a separate zord called the Dragonzord.
And then that thing could combine with the Megazord as well
and make a bigger thing.
It would make armor.
It would make armor that would surround the Megazord.
Right.
And then there was a third zord called Titannus, I believe,
which was like a white kind of a dinosaur robot thing.
And then that would form on top of the mix of Megazord,
Dragonzord would form on top of this other zord
and make this Ultrazord.
I'm not gonna say that my parents were wrong.
I'm not sure that they were wrong.
I think I'm siding with them more than ever.
Well, you're a parent now.
So I think you're, you may be especially,
you could see the writing on the wall of like,
when does this end?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
At least we have the internet now too,
where like you can scrounge this stuff together.
Like this was the start of the like toy, the toy, you know,
the toy mania that you saw in like Power Rangers toys
and Tickle Me Elmo and Furbies, Tamagotchis.
Like I feel like I could be wrong.
I know Cabbage Patch dolls were really big too,
but in my mind, this is the start.
Scott, we should also explain to you
how Power Rangers still gets made to this day.
Well, I know some of this.
I know that it's, you know, the films,
not with the actors who do the dialogue,
but it's done with like stunt actors in another country.
Yeah, so it started in Japan as a show called Super Sentai.
And then what would happen in America
was they would take the action footage
and then they would reconfigure it, dub over it.
And then they would film like connecting scenes
of the characters and totally change the stories.
And this has been going on for over 20 years.
No, how long?
Since like-
Yeah, over 20 years.
Over 20?
Okay, yeah.
So, and they have to do this every time.
So like, if you see what the current Sentai show is in Japan,
you'll probably, it's like, oh, okay,
the Zords are trains now.
So in a few years, you'll know the American one,
they'll have to justify its trains.
It's like-
And in our case in America, at least in, you know,
when we were kids, the filmed in America,
connective tissue scenes was done with a sheen of
saved by the bell lights, broader than broad sitcom acting.
I'm not sure any two actors that have been broader
in front of cameras than the people who played bulk and skull.
Who are still the dumb bullies who were, who bumbled around.
I believe bulk is still around on the new series.
Tommy still around a lot too.
Really?
He's also like, he does MMA as well.
Yeah, other characters will come back sometimes.
The movie filmed, like the movie is original.
The movie is original in the fandom circles,
it's apparently known as alternate canon,
meaning it is not directly tied into the TV show.
It kind of runs parallel to the like second, third season.
That's why you have the cast.
But that's why Ivan Ooze is exclusive to this movie.
Does not show up on television,
which is a shame because he's great.
Yeah, it seems like I'm not so much of a fan
of the broader thing,
but I imagine it makes this movie very special.
That there's this one off who wasn't made less special
through, you know, duller day to day
TV appearances.
Right.
Yeah, although it did drive me insane in the movie
because they used like the Power Rangers whipped out
like some handheld weapons that do not exist in the TV show.
And I was as a kid, I was like, the hell is that?
Why does she have a jump rope
that she can launch at someone?
Like that's weird.
I remember being a little confused
because they shot the movie thing in Australia.
And I remember going,
that's not what Angel Grove looks like.
Angel Grove.
Looks like, yes, as Scott was saying,
the saved by the bell set and then like a park playground
and outdoor scenes from Griffith Park.
Yeah, I think it was largely shot in Valencia is what I saw.
And if you knew, which is the city that Magic Mountain is in.
And it's a very that's like a city with no skyscrapers,
essentially, it's very suburban.
So then weird to see this city with, you know,
with a huge observation deck with the with the CN tower.
And a lot most of this movie is in this one pit.
Yes, 40 percent.
Yeah, it doesn't feel like Valencia whatsoever.
Yeah, I was confused as a child, but I was willing to go with it.
Also, CG, so much CG in this movie, which I'm sure we'll get into.
And I loved it.
Well, which is sort of what some of what we talked about
when this came up before.
I this was so long ago because we're doing this
because it came up in another episode.
I don't remember why you brought this up before, Mike.
I don't even I'm pairing someone to I have a news.
Oh, yeah. What was it?
Because I think I was specifically referencing the scene in the movie
where I have a news dresses up as like kind of a huckster at a carnival.
And I can't remember why it was it was it
light magic pixies is that why it's very possible.
I actually this is one of those where I just don't think I'm going to remember.
I don't think so either.
I don't I know we in an episode you exposed me to Ivan who's for the first time
because I I stopped watching by the time the movie came out.
And I was so instantly smitten.
The image that you sent, which is rare, because usually when you guys
are texting me photos during episodes, it's something horrifying
and skin crawling that 85% of the audience loves and thinks is cute.
But in this case, I fell in love with Wizard Ivan who is so quick.
I've been dying to do this episode, and I was delighted by my viewing of this film.
My first viewing of the movie.
What how how long ago is next year?
Any 25 years after it came out?
Mm hmm. I am interested.
I I thought, yeah, as long as I have a news wasn't a baby,
I thought you would like him.
Shockingly, with me shockingly, not a baby, because he takes on a lot of forms.
He does not become a baby.
Yeah, yeah, he is a shape shifter.
It's kind of weird.
You don't see any sort of it seems like a move they could have done.
And I think guys, just imagine what this movie, this movie's vibe,
what how they would have portrayed a baby Ivan ooze.
I think it's guaranteed that you guys would think it was cute
and I would think it was weird.
I think there's a good chance you're correct.
It would depend if he really like so.
So we haven't even really for anyone who doesn't know what we're talking about
and doesn't want to Google it.
He is like a purple man with like almost like kind of claw,
like twisted little claws coming out of different parts of his head.
I was having trouble figuring out how to describe what he looks like.
Yes, he's very purple. There's definitely horns.
He has a like two swirling horns that swirl into a point on his chin,
like where a beard like a devil's beard would be.
And then he's just very craggy.
And I called them like flesh thorns.
That seems like what's all over his head.
Flesh thorns. That's very good.
Yeah, I mean, he's he's he's not dissimilar to like a Star Trek alien,
but he is a little bit more like, I don't know, it's a little more even aggressive,
I guess, because he's like bright purple and it's a good design.
I do believe that that's it's cool.
It's a cool design.
I think he looks great. Absolutely.
I think the costume's good.
He's got a lot of stuff going on.
And as and as we keep implying, the performance is good.
This is about as good of a scenery chewing
90s kids movie villain as you're going to find.
Yeah, he he almost deserves to be in like a better movie.
Yeah, like, yes, good point.
He should have been I'm trying to think what where he would fit
in a better what better movie it would be.
But like, I mean, he would like a like he could be in like Star Wars or something
or I mean, he should Star Trek, honestly, is probably perfect for him.
Yeah, this this is you could just plunk this character
and performance and put it on next gen and like for for five episodes.
I don't think you'd bat an eyelash.
Yeah, I think I know.
I think I think maybe we could like like memory hole this for people
and just like start acting like he was on five episodes.
And people would be like, oh, yeah, I think I remember that.
Can we talk about the actor for a second?
Yes, sir.
He's a guy named Paul Freeman.
And I had written that name down and I knew he had done a bunch of roles.
But I did not until I just double checked it right before we started recording.
And I was like, oh, my God, he's that guy.
He's the other archaeologist.
He's Renee. Yeah.
Is it Belac Beloc from Raiders?
Yeah, the French guy in the white suit who's always snake and indie.
Yeah. Yeah, he's great. Mm hmm.
He's great. This is so funny.
OK, apparent. This is a quote for the L.A. Times.
They describe as one of Britain's best regarded actors,
classically trained with stints at the Royal Shakespeare Company
and the National Theatre.
Yeah, as soon as this movie was done,
he went back to the British theater to play Prospero in The Tempest.
Yeah.
You went straight from that to this, and you could find
snooty British theater reviews that are like now he was just in the
Power Rangers movie, yet he manages to pull off a decent performance.
They were. Yeah, they don't get the artistry of Ivan who's.
I mean, he's so committed.
I just think he's all in on this role.
Yeah, he's really good.
Maybe I should maybe I'll play a little taste here.
Let me remember how to do this on on the zoom.
The this this is the introduction to his character.
You guys see in video there? Yeah. Yes. Great.
OK, so just just so you get a sense of of his vibe.
And this is the this is when the Power Rangers meet him.
I guess it's not his introduction to the movie.
He's already met the typical Power Rangers villains, Rita Repulsa and Lord Zed.
They've awakened him from an egg that he's been in for thousands of years.
But this is when he meets the Power Rangers and they have just run into
a security guard who seems a little suspect.
And then he morphs into the man who will introduce himself.
Oh, gross.
Too kind.
Allow me to introduce myself.
I'm the galactically feared, globally reviled, universally despised.
They call me Ivan.
Well, pack your bags, because we're sending you right back where you came from.
This scene, I think, is important and illustrates a lot
because you get a sense from that of how fun he is
and how comparatively flat the Power Rangers actors are.
It's like he just dives in and it's this huge performance.
I was green goblin as you might say.
And then like, well, pack your bags, because you're going back where you came from.
This guy could not be more sedate.
I think that's the Red Ranger.
And not only that, but it's so he like points his arm
way out in a very stiff way and his pointing finger is out of focus.
Which that's kind of par for the course for this movie.
This is like things that are very well done and other things where they're like,
let's just get through it.
Let's get it done.
Like, hey, do you want me to do another take of my line?
No, no, no, it doesn't matter. Let's keep going.
We got to keep going.
We're going to leave. They start filling up this pit in two days.
We got to get out of here.
It's that that really is the contrast throughout the movie.
God bless these actors.
They're great and fun and fine.
And I think work well on a syndicated type television show.
But something about you,
put you film them with a film camera and put them next to a Shakespeare level actor.
And the contrast is clear.
Yes, that's true. I mean, I think
I think of all the Power Rangers actors, I think the
Amy Jo Johnson was the Pink Ranger, was on Seventh Heaven, I believe.
She she is Canadian and Felicity.
Was it Felicity? Am I wrong? Yeah, maybe it's Felicity.
It's Felicity.
And then she had a career in on like Canadian TV shows.
So, yeah, they're very much like T.
I don't want to say this is insulting, like TV actors, as you're saying.
And then, yes. And then you have like a man who's
been entertaining thousands live for years.
He's trained.
And here he comes.
And I think that probably just like do whatever you want.
Do the lines however you want. We don't care.
I think you're right.
And as we noted, you know, that voice that we just heard is very W.C.
Fields, as Mike said at the top.
But it changes throughout.
Sometimes he's more British than other times.
It's all over the map.
And he I found an interview where he justifies it in an in an acting sense.
He he says that in the first script, there was even more shape shifting going on.
Like what just happened where he was a security guard and then he turns
into I have a news. I think that happened left and right.
So his take before the script changed a bunch was, well, I should just do
my lines different every time.
It was like a choice he made.
Like, let me just be all over the map because they can't pin this guy down.
We don't know. You know, we don't know his vibe exactly.
I mean, that makes sense.
And actually, his interviews revealed something else,
which is perhaps a good thing that changed about it, which is that he,
you know, in that case, he was just kind of like a white security guard.
I think that that's that's regular Paul Freeman.
But he says in the first group, he read that he would morph it
from being other things such as a woman or a black man.
Oh, my goodness.
It is probably for the I don't know what their plan was with any of that.
But the idea of that scares me.
So I'm glad, glad they cut some of that morphin.
Yeah, that sounds like a good call.
Probably. Yeah, I miss some bullets there.
The I think the voice changing so much is also justified in
just how powerful he like his list of powers online
are shape shifting, liquefaction, shrinking materialization.
He can create simple objects out of nothing.
Hypnosis, lightning, henchmen generation and immense durability.
He really is just everything.
It's all the things.
It's just everything because not only does he make ooze men from lightning,
he makes Tengu warriors, which are weird bird men.
And he like
towards the end of the movie, he's created these
these big robot beings that seem to be like they are.
As with the Tengu war, he creates life like all the time constantly.
But he makes these big robot creatures that seem to be autonomous,
like they work on their own.
But then the Power Rangers weaken them and he fills them back with life by.
I'll describe it as a missing himself into the center of the robots.
He like becomes a big purple worm
through very 90s CGI,
injects himself into the middle of the robots and now they're alive again.
And the robots take on his face as opposed to their previous robot face.
So he changes metallic structure also.
Yeah, I read his zords are I had never seen this term before.
Ectomorphicons.
Mike, did you come across the word?
Oh, yeah, I have it written down right here.
Morphicons are the evil monsters.
Yeah, I have. Where did it go?
It was a school of Scorpotron or something.
And Hornet or Hornet or there it is.
Yeah. Yeah.
Scorpotron and Hornet or
amazing words.
We're new. Good words.
Yeah. And those were new.
We had never we had not seen those characters before.
We had not seen those.
And the ninja zords were new, although
in some form get worked into the TV show,
because like in the movie, the Power Rangers do get ninja powers
in the TV show, but not from the woman they get them from in this
from a giant blue guy named Ninjor.
OK, so they don't.
Scott, Scott, they don't get them from Dulcea.
The warrior woman in this movie,
they get them from Ninjor.
OK, OK.
You know, Dulcea, now you mention, I'm glad we're mainly talking about
Ivan who is and not the rest of the movie because the scenes with Dulcea,
who's sort of a proto Wonder Woman.
Like, how would you describe what is she?
She's kind of a Xena like warrior woman.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yeah, that very 90s depiction
of an ancient goddess that mainly involves like a leather bikini.
And that
it was a pretty illuminating
behind the scenes that I watched of this movie that revealed that
they shot for a long time with Mariska Hargitay
in that role, who then was let go for unclear reasons.
I she tells the story on Seth Meyers
and says that it was to do it had something to do with scheduling,
that she wanted to go home for Christmas and they had her locked.
And then just because of that, they were like, no, you're out.
And they re-filmed everything.
But the director says that all the scenes were bad and not necessarily
because of her, like they were sort of poorly designed.
They were so instructional and involved, no fighting.
And kids were getting bored.
So they just yanked it all.
I think she got some of the stink on her of the scenes being bad.
So one of TV's most successful actresses, Mariska Hargitay,
not in this film.
I still if the whole idea was to make those scenes more interesting,
I was bored as a 34 year old.
So I think we should.
I think what we should do now is because it's very successful.
Campaigns have been happening to get different cuts of the movie released
of movies released.
Let's release the Mariska Hargitay cut
of the Power Rangers movie. Let's get this going.
I would like to see.
And in the in the world of no in quarantine world
where nothing's going to get shot for a long time, this is all we have
is things that are long in the can that can be re-edited and slapped together again.
Yeah. So yeah, release the Hargitay cut.
Release the Hargitay cut.
Hashtag, let's get this going.
It's too bad this is a Patreon episode because it'll be a smaller audience
to get this army built.
Sure. Maybe they're more motivated.
That's true. That's true.
And we can spread it.
We can spread it to the to the general audience as well.
There's a ton of like really produced photos of her.
They show them all in her Seth Meyers interview.
And I like this is like an Eric Stoltz situation and Back to the Future.
This might be one of the bigger
they shot a ton of firings and then dumped it all.
Maybe there's there's ever been.
Wow. They should also release the Stoltz cut.
How huge would that be if they let us see some?
There are. Oh, my God.
You've seen a little of it, right?
Yeah, just like silent shot.
I don't think I've ever seen him speaking lines as Marty McFly.
I think there are scenes online. I could be wrong.
Let me look. I think maybe I think I've seen.
He's in a different outfit or is he in the same outfit or is he in leather?
Is that right? Is he in like all black instead of like the puffy vest?
Maybe more often. That sounds right.
Maybe. I can't remember if I'm just misremembering.
I've never.
Look myself. I've never seen him speak as Marty.
I mean, I'd like to release anything that's in a can anywhere.
Put it out. I'm just thinking of maybe the footage because they did show
footage in those like behind the scenes things.
I'll look it up later.
And then, of course, that's also a conspiracy theory that I like.
I don't like for poor Eric Stoltz is that they were just they used him
to kill time until Michael J.
Fox could be out of his family ties commitments.
Oh, my God.
And that they added then they edited around Stoltz to make him look bad
to show the studio that they needed Michael J.
Fox for six months.
It was a six month ploy. Was it six months?
I think it was a lot.
Maybe not. I think it was like I think it was like a month and a half or two months.
I think maybe some of the six weeks I could be six months.
Six months is crazy.
I don't know if the whole movie took six months.
Well, speaking of releasing things that have been trapped for a long time,
that's kind of the story with Ivan Use.
He is he's in an egg that is in that happens to be in this construction
pit where the majority of the movie takes place.
He is explained by Zordon,
who is the mentor figure to the Power Rangers and kind of an ancient being.
His backstory is explained.
And I'll do it sort of in Zordon voice.
Six thousand years ago, a morphological being named Ivan Use ruled
the world with a reign of terror.
So he's like this.
Ivan Use and Zordon have old beef going way back.
And it seems I think Zordon trapped him in this egg.
But now the other villains are releasing him.
So he's swearing vengeance and he goes and destroys the command center
where Zordon communicates with the Power Rangers and then wreaks greater
havoc on this on the earth.
But first, Zorda, his eyes is revenge is set on Zordon.
Right. So because he takes out the Power Rangers base and he takes out Zordon,
who's in case you don't know, Zordon's like just the floating head in the like.
I don't know what you would call it.
Like it's not it's like a tube.
It's like a giant. It's very it's very Wizard of Oz.
Yeah. Kind of projected.
So that's so that stops
the Power Rangers from sort of having access to their regular powers as well.
Yeah. And there's something in there that I sort of got caught on
that I just want to explore a little bit, which is that, you know,
they have this ancient conflict and the conflict happened 6000 years ago.
6000 years ago is pretty specific.
That's not that long ago.
Oh, why have I heard that number before?
I don't know. Oh, I have heard six thousand before.
Oh, isn't that what people isn't that you track back to the.
Like creationists think the earth is only 6000 years old.
Oh, weird.
Is this from a creationist point of view?
I don't know that.
Is that implying that Ivan Ooze and Zordon were like
warring around the time of Christ or that they are?
Or wait, if this is the beginning of man or sorry,
maybe they are God and Satan.
Oh, yeah.
It could be. And the Power Rangers, the power Rangers are Christ
because they're sort of the children
serving the greater power that Zordon is sort of leading them on.
And it's sort of the eternal fight between God and Satan,
because obviously they had they've had conflicts over such a great span of time.
It'll never really end.
Yeah. Maybe I've a news morphed into the snake in the Garden of Eden.
Oh, man. That's 100 percent what happened.
He looks like a devil.
I mean, he's he's a devil guy.
Ivan Ooze also alludes to the fact that, oh, like Zordon,
Zordon, you're a teenager is like, yeah, like, like that seems to be a common thing, too.
Zordon always recruits some kids to do his dirty work.
Yeah, this is sort of an odd.
That's what's what's the phrase.
He's not to call to mind too dark of a thing.
Oh, I don't know.
I don't know what you're trying to think of.
The what's what is Michael Jackson do?
Oh, grooming. Oh, yes.
Zordon is grooming the
not to get to not to get too dark.
Meanwhile, the darkest one of the dark.
Yeah, sorry.
Lots of us try to avoid saying that, yeah, we're already dealing
with a very dark character.
I have a news. I didn't want to say the darkest character, Michael Jackson.
They do have to deal.
They do eventually deal with this.
I don't know the full solution,
but I think after 20 years of Power Rangers,
which I believe Disney owns now, of course,
or did for a while, I forget.
But they they did like
at some point go like, by the way, all Power Rangers seasons are canon
and they're all back for one.
But like there's there's an episode where like every Red Ranger
comes back for a big fight.
Oh, oh, they all.
Yeah, which sort of this things like that in Turtles where they all
multiple types all hang.
I believe I believe Hasbro owns Power Rangers right now.
OK, at least it did own it briefly.
I believe that's right.
But I 2018 Hasbro purchased it.
OK, yeah, because all this Bond stuff,
Big Bad Beetle, Borg's, V.R.
Troopers, that all falls under load of crap.
We should we should probably do a Big Bad Beetle, Borg's episode,
because it's got that weird guy who looks like Jay Leno.
Oh, yeah. Oh, that's right.
That covers so good. Yes. Yes.
Yeah, I would love to.
Can I say something else on this 6000 years point?
Yeah, if we aren't if we aren't
using the creationist point of view and we're going by
like the generally agreed upon is this historian timeline.
Like it just feels to me like a sort of like kind of like setting
Tomorrowland in 1986.
It's like a little too close to because 6000 years ago.
There's there's a lot going on.
It's really specific.
Like I was like, what was the earth on 4000 B.C.?
We're talking about the it's the copper age.
You're seeing like wheeled carts for the first time.
Plows are are getting used.
The potter's wheel was invented around this time in China.
The Yangshou culture is is in effect.
You know, people are in huts and eating millet.
And, you know, under the backdrop of all this is all under the shadow
of a purple devil man who sounds like W.C.
Fields, who controls all of it.
And and and this is also this is pre,
you know, civilizations all traveling and meeting each other.
So so Ivan Ooze is in charge.
And you've got the copper age over in Europe and Yangshou in China.
And then California, which is where Angel Grove is, where he was
ended up being trapped in an egg.
That's like just a little bit of indigenous culture.
You maybe got some, you know, you've got like indigenous peoples,
you know, trading spears and shells.
And then every once in a while, this purple man shows up
and like steals their shells.
But then like, I got to go, I got to go check on.
Hey, don't worry about that.
There ain't nobody else. I just got to go see.
So he's keeping the different nations separate,
but controlling it all at the same time.
It's really complicated. Wow.
I never thought of that, Jason. Sorry. Go ahead.
I was going to say, and he he helps place it time wise about he.
There's a quote where he says, oh, the things that I have missed.
The Black Plague, the Spanish Inquisition, the Brady Bunch Reunion.
So like he's not only aware of the Brady Bunch,
he's aware of the later reunion special.
Yeah, not only which I don't know why he finds that so egregious.
The Brady Bunch reunited several times.
And to me, they're all varying degrees of fun.
I don't know why that's the maybe he just isn't.
It hasn't been exposed to enough terrible culture to know like that's
hardly the the nadir.
I think he knows.
I think he knows it's bad and he's making a joke.
Yeah, that's a joke for mom and dad.
You know, we know that's totally what he's doing.
I just you know, it's hardly the worst thing.
Oh, sure.
I that's you know, that's not only this, but there's a lot of things where
ancient villains then know pop culture stuff like they'll know.
You know, they'll know to do to do like clap on the clapper.
Another 10 million years old.
I maybe is this a common move with villains to like
bone up on pop culture to sort of, you know,
is that sort of a manner to ingratiate yourself with with people and make it?
Oh, he's one of me. He's not some weird warlord guy.
He knows about stuff I know.
Yeah, I think that's to make.
Yeah, to sort of because this you have to sort of be
like you have to be seducing to be a villain.
You have to be seductive.
And what better way to do that is that know some of our best pop culture?
Like that was it's a little bit akin to the police doing the Macarena.
Yeah.
Some of our best pop culture, relevant culture.
If we learn this dance, then we can trick them.
It's classic Ivan who's tactics and we're seeing it left and right.
Ivan who's invented Ivan who's invented all these tactics.
The only thing following the Ivan who's handbook down pat, we can't trust them.
The fandom page for Ivan who's notes this in.
There's a couple funny instances of like, oh, yeah, this is this is kind of
charming because there's clearly like not an editor.
It's just fans.
This is what they say.
He could also become bored easily as the adults were taking too long to dig up
his ectomorvacons.
Ivan ordered an adult to dance, quote, do the swim showing he knows modern dances
and music. I love taking up some hacky movie line like that and then dressing it
up with like serious essay formatting.
The swim, that modern dance of 1995.
My other my other favorite little bit of language from that page.
Overall, Ivan could be described as insane and megalomaniacal.
Damn, that's harsh.
I am looking at that page as well.
And my favorite part is where they they list like, you know, his powers and his
skills. They list his goals and then they list his crimes.
Yes.
Serial abuse of power, attempted destruction, usurpation, brainwashing,
enslavement and attempted universal hegemony.
What is that word?
Hegemony, hegemony, hegemony.
Is that what it is? Hegemony.
Yeah, hegemony. Sorry.
And then says this type of villain, tyrannical alien.
They're not wrong. Yeah, they are wrong.
It's all accurate. Yeah.
I also spent a little time on some some fandoms or some Wikipedia's because in
trying to figure out the historical context of Ivan Ooze, I was also like,
wait, OK, so all right, if he's if he's in an egg and he's buried in California,
then what was going on in 6,000 BC and wait, Angel Grove is in California.
So what and I was like, what else is up with Angel Grove?
And some posters have found some other historical inaccuracies because
there's an episode where the Power Rangers, you know, got a time stone
or some shit and they go back to Angel Grove back during the Revolutionary
War when it was occupied by Britain.
Right. You know, this California town in 1775
that was occupied by Britain.
And there's scenes that take place in lush forests, you know, like the kinds of
like what you'd see in Virginia where the Revolutionary War was fought.
But then there's other episodes where they time travel and Angel Grove is a desert
or it's like the old west.
So Angel Grove makes no fucking sense.
And if you're going to have a time stone, then why don't just get like get
get like a travel stone to to get you to the East Coast?
Why is why does the Revolutionary War have to be in
fucking like next to San Diego?
I like that idea of the travel stone.
That's good.
I'm around a lot.
Just if there's going to be one stone already dealing with magic and stones,
the second stone, that should have been one of the Infinity Stones
and the Infinity Gauntlet in the Marvel movies, the travel stone.
That's nice.
Who doesn't love to travel?
Yeah, I'd make a nice stone.
I agree. It would be a nice.
It would be a nice stone.
A nice stone. Agreed.
So, yeah, but his plan
kind of becomes
he's I think I missed that.
And I forgot that the construction site that he's buried, but then also is.
Would you say ectomorphicons?
Yes. Well, he is.
Yes, he's ectomorphicons, which also need to be dug up.
That's why he mind controls the parents of the town.
Well, OK, yes.
Yeah, because not only are they used for that, but they're also used
to to make his his booze to they're used on an on an assembly line in a in a.
I was going to call it a sweatshop, but honestly, the besides the mind control,
the circuit, the situation is not that bad in there.
It's not like they're so cramped together.
I mean, they're not getting paid either.
I'm just saying, like, like in terms of like personal space,
that's not the worst factory I've ever seen.
Right. There's worse human rights violations happening in factories
across the world right now, and especially with Covid-19.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. It's probably as bad as it could be.
And Ivan is very humane.
He's like if he was going to raise a bunch of chickens, he was he'd kill them,
but he'd give them like space to be able to turn around.
He's not a monster. He's not. He's not a monster.
He they should really we should add that.
Can we add that to his fandom?
Monster gives ample space to his mind controlled factory workers.
Let's see how do is fandom.
Can I add to it or I have to get it approved?
You probably just have to make an account, but
too much work, too much work.
Power Rangers, the Power Rangers fandom site is either
either that hasn't been touched in six years or you will run a foul of some
little, you know, a little mini Ivan ooze.
Making that page is personal domain.
It will be furious that you meddled with his empire.
Some guy who's like has had his face surgically altered to look like Ivan ooze.
I think it died his skin purple.
Man, how much would you love?
You know, I don't think there's a show like that on right now, but, you know,
when there's like shows called Obsessed or something and somebody
takes their thing too far, if you watch an episode of a guy who became a
a permanent Ivan ooze.
Oh, my God. How cool that.
How awesome.
Would you settle for a tattoo?
Because I've got I found one.
Oh, I thought you were about to say you had it.
I know. I wish I wish known you for all this time.
I've known you for a decade and I've never seen it.
The giant back tattoo of Ivan ooze.
Yes. But before we start recording, Mike mentioned is allergies might be acting up.
And I was like, oh, I really didn't know you had allergies.
Meanwhile, I reveal I have an eye of very detailed Ivan ooze tattoo.
Says it's ooze and time.
It's really big on your back.
I am looking. Look.
Whoa. Deal in 1995.
OK, I've been who shows up any fucks up Rita Repulsa and Lord Zed and Goldar
makes Goldar bend the knee and Goldar Goldar, the wolf guy, the werewolf guy.
Yeah. Goldar is the one in all gold. Yes.
I love Goldar.
The pig man exclusive to the movie, I believe.
And you have the pig man's name.
I know his name. More. OK. Mordent.
Mordent, the tattoo is amazing.
Not to not to breeze past this.
Yeah, it's very good. Why not purple?
Yeah, that's a good question.
Maybe this was just the first like first run at it and they were going to
keep their pass. Yeah. First pass.
And it's on it's kind of on his his cav.
It's sort of a muscly cav and it's got a big your calf.
I couldn't.
I like Mordent, who is a pig man, because he also
Mordent, the pig man, who is original into the
or is unique to this movie as well, I believe, is funny.
And I like his voice a lot.
When like Lord Lord said it, when I have a news is saying like, you know,
he's he makes some big proclamation and Mordent's like, how can I forget?
I never knew he's got like that kind of like squealy guys,
squirrely guys voice that I really like.
But I'm surprised there's other great characters from
like Zed and Rita's base that I really like, that I wish they had included
like Finster. Jason, do you know Finster?
I know Finster. I can't picture him.
All right. I'm going to send everyone a photo of Finster right now.
And I'm upset that Finster was not in the movie.
Here he is. He kind of makes he makes the villains.
He like makes them out of clay.
Oh, yeah. And he's he was always one of my favorites.
He's like a big babu frick.
Yes. Thank you. Yeah.
Fin. This guy's cool.
Yeah. He was. So while I don't want to take anything away from Mordent,
I would have preferred Finster to Mordent.
I am, you know, all of this makeup is pretty amazing.
Mordent is great.
And the the Tengu warriors, all of the crows
are really cool who fly in a practical way.
They actually like swing them down on wires way from way in the sky
down in this construction site.
It's really freaky and genuinely scary.
And this movie was being filmed in Australia and potentially at the exact same time.
I don't know the time, but around this time, they're making a movie
with similar costumes, and that's the island of Dr.
Moreau over in New Zealand.
And like, I just I don't know what I'm getting at.
I just like me. I wish maybe they'd all like met or switched or that like,
you know, Mordent could have gone and been in a scene of Mureaux
and like a dog man could have switched out to be in Power Rangers.
It should have just they should have comboed these.
They were all in the same part of the globe.
And I would say equally well done makeup in both films.
I and you are equally great villain performances
between Paul Freeman and Marlon Brando.
Have you read there's an article about making of Dr.
Moreau, how it's basically like everyone is cursed from the movie.
I watched the documentary the other night.
I rewatched it's Lost Soul. It's unbelievable.
Yeah, it's just reading about all of it.
And like what did the director like just disappears for a while?
Is that right?
It would be Richard Stanley, that the first director.
Yes. Yeah. Yeah.
Who is like, you know, who's a crazy art weirdo
and was replaced by a much more functional John Frankenheimer.
And and then he just like left,
but stayed on the island and just like smoked massive joints every day.
And then the animal creatures went to find him
and him like told him of what had the chaos that had been occurring
since he left because he never directed Marlon Brando even for a day.
So he's hearing all the stories of mayhem and then was like, can I come?
Can I visit? Yes. But how do we get you in?
What if I was a dog man?
He snuck back onto the set of the film he was formerly directing,
but as a human dog and he's in the he's in frames of the movie.
Like he he like fought really hard with Val Kilmer,
which is partially why he's out of the movie.
And then there's seen this frames where here's Val Kilmer in the foreground
and here's the former director secretly.
I don't want to just say all the stories from this movie, but lost soul.
Everybody, it's on iTunes.
Everybody look, it's the greatest documentary.
OK, not to make this episode go really long.
I guess this is the part where I need to tell a story of my past.
One of those, you know, paint by number middle school plays.
Oh, my God. Island of Dr.
Murrow. Oh, my God. How did I not know this?
Your plays are crazy.
What a crazy list you got to do.
And I was a dog man.
Whoa.
Oh, man. The best part of the Richard Stanley part.
It was called the Coney Island of Dr.
Murrow and I guess it had entered the public domain.
I guess that's how they got away with it.
Wow. Does this was it about hot dogs or something?
I know it was about a guy who wanted to make
who had made an island of like goblin people of like dog people.
What? Coney for some reason.
In fact, Mike, that what was the name of my character?
What? Yeah.
What was the name of your character?
A dog made a dog man named what?
Because I really couldn't say many other words than what was it like a who's
Jason, quit messing around.
What was the tell me the name of the character?
What?
Yeah, no, don't ask a question.
I asked already. Tell me the name of the character.
Now, hold on a second.
I've told you the name countless times now.
So listen, listen up close.
Listen up close. What is the name?
I'm asking you. That's right.
That's right. Third base.
Did it was that those lines in the show?
Jason, I feel like there had to be.
Why would you do that?
Right. Yeah. Why else would you do that?
Is there a video? Is there a video?
There is probably a bit.
Yes, I believe there is a video.
Oh, my God. I will try to find it when you got to dig all this up.
You have to.
I was so happy that I had to like
reconstruct a broken VHS to get the footage of my dad on the news.
And yeah, I think I got ripped off.
I had to like compare a broken tape to what a functioning tape looked like.
And like, OK, so this screw would go here and so on.
So I'm just saying it can be done.
Like we can overcome big disasters.
Wow. Yeah.
Get more content out there.
We got I mean, I wanted to watch the play the first play, the play
where the Nazi saboteur.
I tried to watch.
I have a digital copy of it and I've tried combing through it.
And I really got to.
What happened was I was trying to do it with headphones on.
And unfortunately, they set up microphones on the stage,
which was mostly plywood.
So you can just hear children in ill fitting dress shoes
clomping, overriding a lot of the lines.
So we got to we got to figure out something to do with this.
That really rings a bell.
That is so I've never heard that said out loud about why it's
impossible to watch school plays.
It's entirely clomping.
Yeah, it's entirely comping.
They would extend.
It wasn't like the full there was a regular stage and they would extend it
with these plywood extensions.
And then a couple people may have had lavaliers, but not a lot.
But they had these floor mics that would pick you up.
But they would also pick up the clomping
because everyone's like when they would tell people like, no,
for what walk confidently, like walk like you're an adult.
And so like every which is default to clomping, I guess.
So just to be clear, and we can't build this up too much because footage
might not be available, but just to reiterate the fact that you,
Jason Sheridan, played what the dog man in the Coney Island of Dr.
Moreau. Yes, that's right.
In a sea of dog, like there was, I mean, it actually became an issue
because for like ensemble numbers, a lot of times they would have people
like change outfits just if they would be like, oh, you're just a guy in the city.
We don't want this character like,
you know, they would need to fill out the ensemble.
And it's like, oh, that's harder to do in this because we need to put
make these children look like dog men.
So I guess the ensemble is always the dog men.
Yeah, this is insane.
If it can be found again, well, a running theme through this is releasing things,
release. So what is this release? Release the dog men.
Yeah, release the dog man.
Who let the dog try to let the dog man out?
Yeah. Or let what the dog man out?
Yes. Let's take man.
Let what the dog out?
It's very clear.
People know what they're seeing when they see it on Twitter.
They'll know this is not this was not a direction I pictured this show.
I don't have any notes on that.
I was not prepared, but since this is probably more interesting
than talking about the not great movie Color Out of Space
that Richard Stanley directed last year.
Oh, no. Which is which is very purple.
And everyone everyone seems to be doing an I've a news impression
because everyone goes insane.
Hey, wait a minute. I'm back on board.
Yeah, well, everyone in the movie, everyone goes insane.
And it's it feels like they gave the direction of like, well, you're going insane.
And every everyone got to decide how to do that on their own.
How Jason, how many more school plays have you not revealed to us?
Or there's a few.
There's a couple more.
And you will have to see when they come up.
How many total were you in in your whole like junior high and high school career?
Well, that lasted eight years.
So I was in a play every year.
Eight year junior high.
You had four years of junior high.
Well, we did fifth through eighth.
Oh, OK, because we did.
We did seven and eight.
Oh, OK. I did six.
We're all different.
But that's I'm glad it's expanded.
That means there's potentially eight plays worth of material.
Oh, man. Well, the high school plays were like Broadway plays,
and they don't usually come with a license to record them.
Although now everyone just shoots it on their iPhone.
So they were a little more hesitant for recording that.
So I don't know how much footage there is of those. Right.
But the middle school plays were weirder.
So it kind of worked out.
That's wow. Wow.
I can't back on track, so we aren't so crazy.
Going forever.
The because and also because we have to talk about sort of really the meat.
And I think why this guy came up before it must this must have been
light magic unless I'm crazy because, you know, that's all, you know,
they're they're they're fairies.
They're in weird, flowy costumes.
And that must have led into the comparison of Ivan news,
not just as regular Ivan news, but Ivan news dressed as a wizard.
Yes. Yes, I think you're right.
I think that's that's got to be what it is.
I think so.
So it's it's it's a wonderful reveal.
One of the one of the great scenes in cinema.
It's a scene that starts on a close up of two purple containers of ooze
that just say ooze.
And I think like fun for kids keep away from parents.
And then he sort of like parts them.
And it it zooms out to reveal that he is a wizard.
And that he, you know, because he can't just walk around
and be a purple devil guy.
He's going to get caught or people are going to be suspicious.
He has to be something that people trust like a wizard.
And he can't be a purple guy.
He's got to have a more regular skin tone.
So what he does is he takes pure white face
paint and puts it on top of the purple,
landing his skin tone in a in a nice lavender.
Yeah, very normal.
Very normal looking.
Not suspicious.
Yes, definitely.
He looks like a human being very much so.
I guess maybe the wizard was chosen because he's got that thorn beard
I described and as a wizard, he can take a big,
fluffy Merlin beard and put that on top of the thorn beard.
Right. And no one will be the wiser.
Yes, that makes sense.
I mean, that that part.
Yes. Cover your thorns.
I think that's a wise decision.
If you're trying to pass off as a human.
Yeah. So you got to be thinking.
So his options are what, you know, Abraham Lincoln,
he could be like, you know, the very the cartoon Christian idea of God
with the big beard.
But that's weird. Why is God walking around?
That's even more suspicious.
And he hates God. God being Zordon. Right.
So I think he got to the right place with wizard.
He could be like a lion man.
With a big, big man.
The Zubali zoo.
Yeah. Zubali zoo guy, which is still that patron is still coming.
We yeah, yeah, we got to do that.
I'll be terrified of that one.
That's for sure.
Speaking of Dr.
Moreau and Dogman and he looks so fun.
I love a costume on top of a costume.
This this reminded me of one of my favorite human giant sketches.
Shout out to Paul Scheer and Jason Waller.
There's this one sketch.
I don't know if you guys have seen it where
Scheer is a Star Trek wharf type actor
who has to put on crazy prosthetics every day.
And it's a big pain in the ass.
So he gets them permanently welded to his face.
And that cuts down on he then he gets fired.
Like the show ends and he has no reason to have these things on his face.
So now he can't get other work.
So it ends up with him having to put on lots of prosthetics
to be a regular human being.
And there's a scene where his clearly alien
perma makeup has been painted over with skin tone.
And I think he has a weird like Van Die Heela.
Scheer looks so much like I have a news as a wizard in this mode.
It's so the multi costumes just what a what a delight.
I mean, it is with people, you say hat on a hat is a bad thing.
Not in this case.
You can logically construct a hat on a hat.
It's maybe the best thing.
Sometimes when people say hat on the hat, I go, hey, good.
More hats. I love hats.
A lot of things have no hats. Right.
Like, at least I'd rather have two hats than no.
I would also rather have two, three, four hats more than no hats.
Yeah. Come on.
Um, so no, no, hold on.
Listen, you don't think the game night getting out of control
isn't enough hats.
That's like it sounds like it's to stay to two hours.
It's a hat. It's it's a type of hat, I guess.
If a comedian is telling you the story of when his standup career
wasn't going so good, how many hats do you consider that to be?
Is that is that a hat?
Is it more of a visor?
They won't have you insulting visor.
Oh, I'm sorry. Yeah, I'm sorry.
You are one of the biggest visor advocates on the planet.
I am. And you know, when I saw I wondered if anyone would notice this.
And I did see some comment in the wake of me having a child.
The visor is no longer ironic.
And I would say to that it never was.
I have always worn visors because it reminds me of my dad
and going to the beach with my dad.
So that when I started wearing them, it was a nod to my dad.
Now that I am a dad, the visor use will only increase.
I've seen a big push, especially in some from some pro wrestlers to
re sort of like renormalize the fanny pack as well.
Oh, no. Is that how our visors viewed?
Why next to are they equal to fanny packs and culture?
In my mind, they are.
Oh, man.
Zoomers are into fanny packs, too.
That's true. Yeah.
Yeah. We're wearing them diagonally, like wearing them across the chest.
Like those are big. That's true.
I've never felt insecure about my visor visor use until realizing that they're
if they're viewed part and parcel with fanny packs.
That's a bummer to me.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to.
I didn't mean to bring it down.
I thought I was doing a good thing there by bringing that up.
Well, but then again, you know, I mean, I bet I will learn soon
why a fanny pack is a good functional thing to have. Right.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
You got to have stuff on you was as a father.
I think I will.
I just.
Extra masks, you know.
Yes. Well, in the being a COVID dad, you
it's extremely necessary.
Mm hmm.
Uh, I just maybe it's that phrase I have to get over.
You know, I got you got to macho it out.
I'm going to start calling the manny packs.
Oh, good. Yeah.
That fixes it.
You're worried about your masculinity.
You do a theme park podcast.
Me, those of the theme park podcast, who loves to wear visors
and worried that my masculinity is viewed as less than traditional masculinity is dead.
I'm declaring it here.
We're all we're all masculine.
We're all feminine. It doesn't matter.
I'm wow.
I'm tearing down the barriers right now.
Yes, I am now on this Patreon episode about even news.
Yes, on the Ivan Ooze episode of a pay walled podcast.
Let the word go forth.
We should all be able to liquefy, liquefy and reform and whatever form we want.
Toxic masculinity is dead.
Get rid of your old impressions of what it means to be a man.
Why am I a man can be cool?
Why can't a man be cool?
A fanny pack is all right for anyone to wear.
Let me say the other thing that I like about this
who's selling sequence that he had a logo made.
He went to a he went to a graphic designer and he had to like,
I mean, he has some magic abilities, but not all.
I don't know that he can just point at nothing and then a hundred jars are there.
I think he had to like deal with some outside contractors.
Yeah, he he definitely hired someone.
He definitely had to like put an ad out,
which at the time would have been in the newspaper, I guess.
Unless that's like, let me go back to his fandom.
Maybe it says he is a graphic designer. I'm not sure.
I don't know.
That's true.
He does. But how does he?
Oh, wait, you see that.
But then I just don't know where the jars come from,
because eventually his employees are the brainwashed parents.
But the first time that you see the jars, the parents have not been brainwashed yet.
Oh, that's a good point. Right.
Maybe Goldar is a graphic designer or Mordant.
I don't know.
Or Mordant is a graphic designer, Mordant the pig man.
I threw it all around in my stir-torn.
What do you want the art style to look like?
Who should I look to for inspiration?
Well, it should be dripping.
The font should be dripping like it's made of ooze, you see.
Isn't that clever?
Is there any typeface that looks like it's doing a little drip drip?
I get what you're saying.
I got to finish up this poster for an ice cream social first.
And then I'll get right to work.
I want six mockups by the end of the day.
I'll turn you into chicken wings, she or in your case,
bacon, I suppose.
Yeah, that's right.
All right. Get off my back.
I'll eat your back when it's made of bacon, she.
Don't don't don't do it.
But just get to work.
I will admit it during that last improv, I got distracted
because Edwin came into the room.
There's a big piece of like like packing paper and he just lied down in it
like it was his bed.
Making a loud noise.
I've taken a photo of it
and it distracted me so much.
It's worse behavior than what the dog man.
Yeah.
Uh, anyway.
So then he was I mean, this scene is great.
And he so he puts on this show again.
He's a he's a being who's at least 6000 years old.
And his scheme is is like, you know, what a shuckster would have done in 1905.
He has a weird tonic.
He's peddling and he is at the seemingly the beginning of his pitch.
He is already a master group of 70 children who require no cell.
They're immediately convinced that the ooze is great.
They ask, like, what do you do with it?
He says, show it to your parents.
That's true.
Kids love to show stuff to adults.
Check it out.
This guy's wizard gave me ooze.
OK. And then they all just without thinking
kind of, I don't know, sniff it, eat it.
And then quickly, there's an army of parents.
And the spread happens without a lot of scenes,
and which is a bummer, because this is all that I want to see.
I want to see the logistics of making the labels.
I want to see him pricing it out and talking to specialists.
And I also want to see him getting the permit to open
what seems to be a brick and mortar location of Ooz City.
I mean, you don't really see a sign of is a science is free ooze,
but in his very local TV Larry H.
Parker kind of ad, it certainly implies he says, come on down to Ooz City.
Let's get sticky.
Is this, you know, we
Scott say tomorrow you get a call and they say, look, we want an I've news
origin story prequel show.
Are you on board as long as finally
as long as it can be
mostly boring?
They say, look, it's what it's mostly whatever it's whatever you want.
If it's anything that I want, yes.
And then it's going to be him like going to talk to the city council
just disguising himself as an old man, putting on putting on a disguise
like I'm a pillar of the community.
See, and then you got to give me Ooz City.
It's been my dream since I was a boy.
And then they're like hearing him out and like, well, decide in six weeks.
And then he hypnotizes them.
He doesn't have time to wait.
It's time
to go to City Hall and file to open up a business.
They should you should.
You should get for Paul, free Paul Freeman at 70.
He's 77 years old now, as long as he can still play the character.
Yeah, I wouldn't settle for for anybody else except for me.
Maybe I just do it.
Oh, wait, that's that's tempting.
But I'd rather I'd rather have Paul.
But, you know, Paul Freeman has addressed this already.
I found an interview with him in a newspaper
where the interviewer said, with a new generation of Power Rangers
having launched this year and the recently released reboot,
would you ever consider making a big return to the franchise
to show these new kids whose boss?
And his response was only for an enormous amount of money.
Yes. Hell, yes. So great.
I mean, it seems like this guy had a good time making the movie, but not
he's in good spirits talking about it now,
although implying that you'd have to back up the bricks truck to get him to do it.
But also there was a lot of bullshit going on for Paul Freeman.
Did you guys stumble on any of this?
And I don't know exactly what you're talking about.
I know he was saying like the first makeup process was like seven hours.
But I think you're talking about something different.
Oh, I saw that. Yes.
They got it down to three to four hours a day, you know, just three to four hours.
But the first time they tried, it was seven.
And he just had to go into a trance state like, how do you
how do you manage that every day?
But he the they did get the makeup better,
but it was still really bad for his skin, so bad that he got horrible rashes
and eventually just had to like take him off work for a couple of weeks
to help him recover because it was just destroying him.
And then at some point during shooting
and this is him telling this story and laughing about it now.
But he fell down some stairs in a scene on camera and sprained his ankle.
So they had to get him to the hospital and to an ankle specialist specifically,
which is, you know, it was a little bit out of town away from where they were shooting.
So like, OK, let's get him out there.
Wait, he is in makeup that takes 90 minutes to get out of.
So they settled on getting him out of costume,
but not the makeup because it would slow down fixing his ankle.
So in Ivan, whose makeup he was rushed to suburban
Sydney to like a little like cottage hospital where he checked in,
was given a wheelchair,
was shot dirty looks by everybody else in the waiting room and then told,
oh, actually, the ankle guys up the street.
So he had to be wheeled through the streets of suburban
Sydney in a wheelchair in full Ivan, whose makeup to fix this issue.
That's that.
That's just par for the course.
That's the show. That's the show.
That's it. Yes.
Now we got. Yes.
That's at least one hat.
It's the if I could make.
Yeah, because they're going to give me a lot more control of that.
If I could tell the story of Paul Freeman shooting Power Rangers,
the movie as a miniseries, I, you know, in.
I'm an eternal fan of the late shift.
This would be my entry into that genre.
Cheap movies about the making of movies.
Would you make a seven season television show based on the late shift?
Oh, if I could expand the late shift.
Oh, my God. Oh, now we're talking.
If we could get I want the original guide, want Daniel Roebuck to play J.
Leno, of course.
And that'll be prosthetic city.
John Michael Higgins might have grown out of it, though, obviously,
incredible to have him back as Letterman.
But imagine like a prosthetic Conan, like getting like a like a
maybe Paul Freeman is Conan.
But to teach him, oh, yeah, I know he's great in prosthetics.
You know, he can dive into any part.
Yeah, I'm Conan.
She I'm getting screwed.
See, I'm just trying to do my string dance and they're kicking me off the air.
Rich Little would be back as Johnny Carson.
Is he still around? Oh, yeah, he still does.
They he does Vegas shows.
Jesus is it did Fred travel, Lina, that other one die.
I think he died. Maybe I don't.
I let me check, Fred.
I would like if it was all
impersonators, as many impersonators as it could be.
I don't think there's some just like broad Conan impersonator out there,
but obviously you'd want to have him.
I I mean, yeah, stack it to stack it up with them.
But imagine like getting to see people in prosthetics
who look like the Duracell battery people doing the scenes of,
you know, you bump and cone
in of like even just just getting Jay Leno's garage started.
I would just do an hour on the tree.
I don't know. I had this idea.
I was driving around and it'll just be fun and little.
And I that then I can't know how much it would grow.
And now we got the president on it. Got George W. Bush.
I honestly, I really, really would like to see you do multiple seasons of this.
Oh, man. Yeah. Well, they hand me the reins.
But like you doesn't it doesn't even really matter.
I mean, you could you would want it to be called like late shift the series, I guess.
But like also, you could just do it.
It doesn't like because they're public figures.
Can I do that? Maybe? Yeah.
I mean, I can do this as a podcast or something.
Maybe that's the idea.
Oh, man. Just to dramaticize every single
because you'd have to do like the Hugh Grant thing.
What the hell are you thinking?
That's an entire episode.
Not Bradford.
Kevin Eubanks. Well, no, certainly.
Yeah. Yeah.
And you're replacing Bradford, Ricky Miner replacing Kevin.
These are all that each everything I'm listing is a full hour.
Yeah. The rumor that Max Weinberg offered Jay to be his bandleader
after Conan lost the Tonight Show.
Oh, no.
We thought he would just be grandfathered into the Tonight Show.
And I've never heard that confirmed, but I'd like to believe it's true.
Sounds right.
Oh, man.
I'm just we have to end this someday.
I'm so like I'm going to be lost in imagining the 10 the 10 part
dramatic. Honestly, you're saying many seven seasons, I think.
Yeah. Honestly, entire life story of Lena.
We should probably just do it as like an eight episode podcast
and then try to sell it.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. You lay out the plot.
You kind of prove it on its feet.
And then we, you know, because prosthetics cost money.
And this is going to need a lot of them.
Yeah. Well, you could have a different person play
Leno every episode like that Bob Dylan biography.
That's good, too.
And in this one, it's Tilda Swinton.
I honestly. Yeah, exactly.
And this one, it's an eight year old boy.
You know, maybe this comes out of this episode and we don't we just do this.
Yeah. Yeah. We don't want to give these ideas away for free.
Yeah. All right.
This really I really like the idea of this.
Yeah, I know. More late shift. Holy shit.
Late guys, I guess late shift the podcast.
Late shift the podcast.
I have one more like big Ivan Use thing that he shows up in.
And this is just probably I'm
I'm very curious to see if other people remember this.
In the Power Rangers movie, there is a song called Trouble by a band called Shampoo.
And this song just glued into my brain as a young child.
And it just for whatever reason,
1995 stuff, songs associated with movies stuck in my brain, like very weird ones.
It was this and the song by the band Elastica, the song Connection.
Is a connection or connected?
It shows up in the movie Hackers and Hackers.
I just remember being advertised so much
and they always played this song because it's about connection, you know.
Anyway, when we started talking about doing this episode,
I went and found the music video for this.
And it's it's that aesthetic that I just love that late mid to late 90s.
Millennial optimism, aesthetic.
We got oval sunglasses on heads.
We got a lot of CGI, but there's some dance in Ivan Use.
There's some dancing Usemen in this video.
What is it filmed for the video or is it for clips from the movie?
There's clips from the movie in the music video.
The music video is made in conjunction with the movie.
The song was a year old.
Like they re-released the song for the movie.
The song had already charted in Europe and then they put it in the soundtrack.
But here I'll send it to you guys.
I mean, the very first shot in the music video is Lord Zed.
And then the singers show up.
Oh, in front of this like sort of too busy
screensaver kind of background. Oh, this is killer. Yeah.
And they're like kind of a they're like a blonde ship.
More chipper version of tattoo.
Yeah, yeah, that is true.
Kind of they do this song on top of the pops like it was it charted.
I I'm not sure how many albums, whatever happened to shampoo.
Elastica only had two albums, but yeah, this was a great video is great.
We've talked about this soundtrack on the show before, even before I have a news,
because I had this on a cassette and I loved it.
And it's where I was introduced to the Van Halen, Sammy Hagar, Van Hagar song
dreams and higher and higher.
Yes. Yes.
That ends the film with fireworks.
It's it's very triumphant.
You get all the feels in the on the soundtrack.
The Power Rangers theme.
You know, that was kind of like a dopey studio musician,
kind of whoever did the music for the show.
And they they had to get some pros to do it for the movie.
I know who dubbed themselves as the Power Rangers Orchestra,
which is comprised of Matt Sorem, the drummer of Guns N' Roses,
the singer of Mr. Big, the bass player of Pablo Cruz,
the famous Discovery Island lovers, Pablo Cruz and
perhaps uncredited rumored guitar appearance by Buckethead.
Yes. And for the solo on the track,
Firebird is supposedly Buckethead.
So what is this song?
What is the song they they skydive to?
It was another hit song, I feel like.
Oh, it's also theme park lore.
It is the Red Hot Chili Peppers cover of Higher Ground.
Yeah. Yes.
Uh, that's on there.
Which you're from, by the way, which was used in Disneyland.
If you didn't hear our episode way back when they put rock songs,
chili pepper songs into Disney rides, Space Mountain had a higher ground.
Higher ground. Yeah. OK.
There's a funny Devo song called Are You Ready?
I have it queued up, actually.
I found this so I found the song so bizarre and then it dawning on me
that it was Devo.
It's so strange. Here's here's a quick hit.
Welcome to my nightmare.
Action boy.
Now, it's a.
Have another.
That's pretty much that action bar.
Now it really sticks out.
And then you go, wait a minute, I know that voice.
Oh, my God, it's Devo.
And by the way, that's a scene where they're fighting.
Ivan Ooze has kind of made a bunch of offspring and they resemble.
I would say they look a lot like grown versions of the the Muppet Clifford,
the host of Muppets tonight, because they have dreadlocks.
I don't have dreadlocks. Yes, exactly.
Yeah, I didn't think about that.
We were talking about the Ooze men.
They dance in the music video.
At least one of them dances in the music video.
It's great. It's so the music video is just so fun.
Yeah, there's a whole world of culture around this movie.
Clearly, I think I was sleeping on it.
Maybe my parents were wrong.
Maybe they led me astray because I could have had the joy of all this great music
and I have a news in my life this whole time.
Yeah, I think I think for sure you would have liked all these monsters.
You would have been a Finster fan.
You would have been a Goldar fan.
Yeah, yeah, I think so.
Have we missed anything about.
Ivan himself, I well, you know, you know what maybe
bears mentioning is the I mean, first of all,
I like that his plan is to he gets all his parents, these parents to work in his factory.
And then once there's enough
booze, when they get a supply, he's just like, all right, we'll go kill yourself.
Yeah. He commands them to go back to the construction site and quote, leap to your doom,
which they do. And then it's a pretty heady scene watching many
mind controlled parents try to jump in a pit while their own children push them back.
Yeah, that is a little intense.
It's a it's a metaphor for the
the right wing mind control that many parents are under.
No, we're trying to save you. Don't you see?
No, Tucker Carlson said so.
He said jump in the pit.
I love bits.
He said we should.
He said he said we should kill ourselves.
He said he said Nick Kroll is freeing the rioters
looting won't be over until we get Nick Kroll.
And he said, we are fine.
We don't have to think about anything in a different way.
We shouldn't get different perspectives on any issues.
Our world comes out later.
We're at a bad point that we're recording it.
That's our world view is correct.
And then just like the, you know,
there's there's not a lot to say about it in this audio format,
but the CGI. Oh, my God.
Because when you essentially end up with this big robot creature
with the sort of face of Ivanu's and it is such
the rock scorpion king, early CGI, not even early CGI.
Like CGI was good and then got really atrocious as if he was trying to do it en masse.
This is the same summer that saw the release of another movie
that really imprinted on me, which was the live action Casper.
And I feel like that's at least I feel like that probably holds up
a little better CGI wise. I'm sure.
Probably not amazing, but I have to think a little better than this.
This CGI looks like they took like character models from reboot
and put it in live action.
Yes. And without changing their shading.
Yes.
Without changing their shading, without making them like lighter or darker,
whatever they had to do to fit the environment.
Yeah, none of that.
They were just like, get us the reboot effects.
And they did.
That'll be fine, which is so jarring, considering that, like this,
the CGI is pretty roundly awful.
And then some of the acting is kind of weird and wooden.
And then there's other aspects that are pretty fantastic.
Like we said, like the costumes and the makeup.
And I would say that the production design is very good.
And I watched a behind the scenes where the director spoke really highly
of the of the art director who said he had no budget to make Ivan
Who's his factory and what a great job he did.
And he was one of the great art directors working in Australia
at that time.
And not long after this movie, he hooked up with George Miller
and stuck around in Australia where he had a robust career,
making many great looking films, including Mad Max Fury Road.
This film has the same.
The art director became the head of production design on Mad Max
Fury Road, which won him an Oscar.
You know, he all he did on that movie were the cars, you know.
No big deal. The fucking cars were like, yeah, well, it's incredible.
This is one of the great talents of the of the century.
So, yeah, they found amazing crew in Australia.
Yeah, that's crazy.
And it does because we're watching the movie, honestly, like everything looks
except for the CGI, everything looks a lot better than my memory is.
Like remembering it.
I was like, oh, some of this is all right looking.
It really is. Yeah.
This is like this is where you want kind of a retro,
you know, snark watch to sit where there's things you can make fun of,
but there's enough just watchability and good performances
to keep you strung along. And there's definitely that.
Well, and did you guys see director Brian Spicer
had a busy time a couple of years later, two movies in one year?
Did you catch this?
No, only for Richard or poor and Mikhail's Navy.
Oh, yikes.
The Mary Kayden Ashley for Richard Purport.
Oh, no, you're thinking of no, this is Tim Allen.
Tim Allen and Kirsty Alley, right?
Yeah, where they hide out with the Amish.
Oh, man, I was thinking the Olsen Twins, Kirsty Alley movie.
I knew Christie. Oh, my gosh.
Oh, those are oh, those are some barfie movies. Oh, my God.
Since then, he is the major director
and EP on the new Magnum P.I. and Hawaii Five.
Thus making him a trillionaire.
I was very, very wealthy.
Just if I had to ballpark it.
I think I'm going to go ahead and say my mom watches both of those shows.
Just a guess. Just has to get guess.
I mean, these are the shows people actually watch.
Good for him for being part of the things that are viewed. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. So some major talent.
They did great.
And they all came together to make a movie that culminates in taking the villain,
who is a best himself into a robot, into space where their robot
slow dances with his robot.
Essentially, they like lock arms and drip through space together
until they hit an emergency button,
which causes their robot to knee his robot in the groin,
which releases him and makes him fly at a comet,
which blows him up. And that's the end of Ibanez.
Yeah. A groin hit is the end.
You know what? That feels like that's a common thing.
Am I wrong? Like movie groin hits being like the final the final.
Hmm. I could be wrong.
Maybe I'm I'm just maybe the 90s felt like it was a groin hit decade.
I know I don't doubt that you're wrong.
I'm trying to think of climactic. Yeah.
Groin hits. That's very specific.
And there's got to be more.
There definitely have to be. I'll do some research on this topic.
I think today we have done a groin hit
to toxic masculinity.
That's true. Yes. You're right. Yes.
That's right. And in this case, literally toxic.
I have a news is is genuinely toxic, but it's not so simple in the real world.
The toxic men aren't out there making ooze.
They're just oozing, disgusting backwards thoughts.
That's right. You really tied that together.
Yeah, I think I think this is beautiful.
I also I have a news.
The robot picks up the CN tower type observation building
and uses it like a sword. And I like that a lot.
That is. Oh, yeah. Yeah, that's very good.
So well, with that, you survived.
You survived. But guess the ride.
I just you know, I feel so I had so much fun talking about him.
I want to I wish I could celebrate with you guys
the way they celebrate at the end of the movie,
which is watching fireworks and eating lobster.
There's a really funny thing at the end when the kids
like says there's a kid there and he's the one who like helped save the parents.
And he's like, they're like, you know, we heard like you're going to be a Power Ranger.
And he's like, yeah, the Silver Ranger.
And they're like, oh, yeah, that's great or whatever.
And then he goes, so Gold Ranger.
And they all go, oh, yeah.
Like they all go like nuts and like high five.
And I confused was was that anything in the movie?
That's something that happened.
I don't I don't know. Yeah.
Was it a setup for something that didn't ever I was sequel?
Maybe. Or yeah, they do eventually have a Gold Ranger. Yeah.
Right. But is there anything worth watching in turbo a Power Rangers movie?
I have never seen it.
We've kind of done with it by that point.
Yeah, I guess I think the no, not the world was because it's still going.
But our generation was that's where I felt like we'd we'd all moved along like my parents wanted.
Yes. I think that I think, yeah, maybe as far as Power Rangers,
I'm sure there's other worthwhile characters to talk about.
But I think probably in the Sabanah verse, it's going to have to be Flapper
from the Beatle Borgs that we get to next.
Who, if I recall, I'll look them up as we wrap up here.
But isn't he because we've talked about him before.
And he's a little Lennos, right? A little.
Extreme. Oh, yes, indeed.
Yes, indeed.
Wait, he's wait. Flabber is what I said.
I said they call him flap. Yeah, yeah. Flabber.
You're right. Sorry. OK.
My in the seven season expanded late shift
the in the shift diverse, the makeup will be much.
He will look exactly like Flapper.
We'll get the genuine the actual prosthetics.
And this is how Jay will be portrayed.
Man, I can't wait. I'm excited to do that.
Here's a picture. I sent a bunch of pictures, but here's here's one with Flapper
where he has a mic like a stand up.
Oh, man. But a little more of like a way.
We're really wearing like a James Brown kind of sparkle jacket.
All right. Somebody's compared him to Liberace as well. I see.
Oh, man. This is a great look for him, too.
Well, this will be the this will definitely be the spiritual air.
Oh, my gosh.
Here. Wait, describe this look.
He's wearing like he's wearing a toupee on top of his regular flabber hair.
He's right. Yeah. So he flabber looks like Jay Leno.
He has blue skin and he usually is wearing like a very purpley Liberace coat.
But in this one, he's wearing like a vest and beads
and a yellow dress shirt and like a giant belt buckle.
Joey, Jason, you've just sent that is a very low.
That's Liberace, I think.
That's a trading card flabber, I believe. Yeah.
I'm just distracted now because this I'm realizing this.
We're in such a similar area, both in his name and his appearance
to the sworn enemy of Bible man, the Fibler.
Oh, man. Who I will send you.
And we've definitely we got to hit Bible man at some point, too.
We're over doing that.
But oh, my God, flabber and the Fibler are in the exact same neck of the woods.
Oh, yeah. The Fibler.
We we these are all such this is because this is I feel like sort of grows
out of Green Goblin.
We got Green Goblin, Ivan, who is the the flabber and the Fibler.
Anything else like this, please make us aware.
I don't know what you call these guys.
If there's one uniform term, not just kids show villains, but like they're all
they all look like plastic or clay.
They're all such abominations.
They're all so broad.
Well, they're kind of like in theme park terminology, the big item,
the big castle or whatever kind of colloquially called a weenie.
These are kind of the weenies of the shows, you know, these are landmarks.
They're all there.
What draw you to it? Yeah. Yeah.
I could be I'm sure there's another thing before this, but they all do feel like
they've come out of the tradition of the 60s Batman.
That and that might be why we like it so much.
It's keeping that alive.
It's just for kids. It's for it's goofy.
We don't there's a time and a place for serious Batman, but there's a time
and a place for this shit to like what I'm looking at, which is
flabber with an angel and devil flabber on either side of his shoulders.
Oh, man. Oh, all right.
Well, a bunch more of this shit to come, we promise.
Assuming you enjoyed it and I hope you enjoyed it as you know, keep it tuned here
at the second gate, patreon.com slash podcast, right.
And more crap always at Facebook, Instagram and Twitter.
And there is something else.
Oh, you know what?
And let's just remember to put it in the show notes.
We should have said this very conveniently.
Mighty Morphin Power Rangers, the movie is up for free on YouTube,
at least as of this recording.
It's a pretty decent quality copy that has not been yanked for some reason.
So if you're wondering which of the many streaming services can I find it on,
need not worry.
It's it's it's free on YouTube thanks to some kind soul.
And yeah, I don't for whatever reason, somebody's not concerned
about this movie up there for free.
I don't know why.
Not a crown jewel, I guess, but it should be this.
This this should be protected.
It belongs in a museum.
I agree. HBO Max should have paid big money for this or something like.
It looks from the copy like this was on each.
I think this may be the pulled HBO copy.
Oh, yes, it is the HBO rating at the top.
Yeah, right, right.
And I do remember watching it on HBO a couple of years after it had come out.
So it probably had a long life on HBO.
Yeah, yeah, as it should.
And well, let's give it a long life in our hearts.
This this might be cued up badly, but let's just here.
I'm just going to try to end this as the as the film ends.
Take us out, Van Hagar.