Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast contains a frank discussion of current hot button issues,
but also non-current references to Jimmy Stewart and the Moody Blues.
By episode's end, one of the hosts may be replaced, while another may drive his significant other
away forever.
Kick your socks off, we're discussing the Splash Mountain reimagining and answering your
questions on Podcast the Ride.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, your virtual theme park fix during quarantine.
Think of us as your little audio Disney quest.
My name is Mike Carlson, joining me as always, Jason Sheridan.
You know, I hope whoever makes like the Oculus stuff is making a virtual podcasting simulator.
You hope that?
I hope that.
I hope like you put on the helmet and then you see like a cluttered coffee table and
then you have to record like you got to do ads, you got to say everything, you got to
make sure to plug your social media accounts.
Yeah.
And they have like a little like haptic feedback thing you wear on your ankle and Edwin the
dog can hump you because he's so stressed out that you're podcasting.
That would be very realistic.
Let's bring Scott Gardner in also here to pitch on this idea of a VR podcast.
Well this is all assuming that there is anyone who would buy such equipment who doesn't already
have a podcast, assuming that there is anyone at all who doesn't already have a podcast.
That's a good point.
I think at this point, podcast penetration is about 90 percent.
Is that right?
Is that is right statistic?
Yeah.
And I think if you lined it up with the coronavirus curve, I think it shoots up at all the same
moments that the virus does.
We're trying to hit 99 percent podcast penetration.
I know that's a that's a weird way to put it, but I podcast penetration.
You seemed uncomfortable just saying the word.
Yeah.
I mean, I look, you know, this is not a body podcast.
I don't I don't think I have I ever said the word penetration on podcasts the right before
you're up to two now.
I don't think so.
I think this is a first.
I think whoever like whoever keeps our wiki, please tell me if I've ever used it before.
I think podcasting is in general a medium for people who are at some point have been
uncomfortable with penetration.
I think that is an overlap for sure.
Yeah.
But I'm not using it in a in a sexual connotation.
I'm using it in a sure, you know, penetrate penetrating.
No, this was all about like VR stuff and, you know, what's the one of the main applications
of that or will be at some point.
So, yeah, you're describing you want to create a VR scenario where people have sex with their
favorite podcasters.
That's not what I said.
And it's not what I was going for.
It's not what you it's what you meant.
So it was in your heart.
That would be honestly that would be scarier than Nicodemus, scarier than a horror, any
horror VR.
That would be that. Yes, that's the horror character in the void, which we'll talk about,
which is having some some difficulties lately.
But yeah, if you if then it was like now you have to kiss Nicodemus.
And then, yeah, you had like what I was saying, haptic feedback like like face mask where
like your lips would tingle when you had to kiss Nicodemus, the demon, the void created
original IP demon.
Well, that's just the first jump scare.
The ultimate jump scare that the climax of it is you have to be emotionally intimate
with Nicodemus.
Oh, my God. You have to like share with him about your like deepest childhood trauma.
Well, you had no you do. Yeah, you just have to be vulnerable.
You have to open up to Nicodemus.
I don't like that.
Do you really love your parents, though?
Have you really gotten over what happened to you as a child?
Why can't you just tell me what you're feeling?
Why is this such a rigmarole?
Your eyes are darting all over the place.
Look at me. You're always deflecting.
Why are you always deflecting?
Stop by the way, that's what Nicodemus sounds like.
I think so. We haven't. Yeah, we're too scared to have done this virtual reality demon
thing that we're describing and now creating a scenario where you go to him as your
therapist. Mm hmm.
But look, they hopefully the void survives what we'll eventually start talking about.
But I think multiple updates to Nicodemus are possible.
So we just we could.
There's a main topic we're going to talk about.
We could just jump around and say that that's we're catching up on a little bit of
topical news. We're post the Fourth of July holiday.
One of the weird things we found is, you know, we've talked about this thing several
times in the podcast, the void, this VR experience, and they are it was even part of
our downtown Disney ordeal.
That was one of the topics and they're out of Disneyland, gone out.
Yeah, it's evicted.
It was like such a harsh way to put it, too.
Mm hmm. It seems like, yeah, it felt very landlordy.
So like, it felt like the void fucked up somehow.
And when was the last time downtown Disney evicted?
It's like won't like Sunuk didn't get evicted.
Basin didn't get evicted.
I think they were chased out with torches.
No, it's.
I yeah, I don't know.
Wait, yeah, and it was just like a it just seems like the Disney relationship is
severed because this is the the the place that does VR experiences of we've talked
about them Star Wars and Wreck-It Ralph.
Yeah, we did Marvel and Paul Sheer a few months ago.
But now before quarantine.
Yeah, right. Yeah, right before.
Is it one of the worst things you could have done, you know, the day before?
Yeah, yeah, because, yeah, it's.
You're putting on a lot of equipment.
You don't know where it's been.
They weren't cleaning things at the time because nobody knew we we had to.
Yeah, but it's like, yeah, drop all the Disney stuff.
You're done. I so harsh.
Just just a kick to the curb.
Well, yeah, it said it was a violation of the licensing agreement, which
I I guess the licensing agreement entails paying your rent on time.
But I can't say I've heard about any other downtown Disney businesses
that have been essentially served like there's papers taped to the window
like that you have to like publicly display this stuff, I think, for businesses.
It's it's very strange.
And it's just a creepy thing to see at downtown Disney, like the, you know,
as if like this place has lost their liquor license.
It feels such like I didn't know they did that kind of thing.
It's like a health board shut them down.
It's like if you build a bear, had like a big condemned sign or something.
Like, you don't expect to see sort of real world things like that in downtown Disney.
No bears will be built here anymore.
Yes. No, don't don't come and steal the stuffing.
I'm trying to find the Forbes talked about it.
Are they are they going to be out of Orlando to just
Disney evicts the void, withdraws Star Wars and record Ralph licenses.
And and they as Forbes supposes, without its own IP, Nick Adidas.
Hello. We just did a lot of great Nick Adidas material without its own IP
saddle with expensive leases and no path to revenue revenue anytime soon.
It's unclear how this pioneering company will survive this.
So no, that's why we've like really liked some of these things.
So this is a bummer.
Yeah. And that's the those are the people behind Evermore as well,
which is that very immersive park.
Where is it again? I always forget.
Oh, and I'd like to know it's in Utah, nowhere close to an airport.
So that should they should survive.
It shouldn't be a issue.
So, yeah, I we don't have the full story here.
I'm very curious.
But it is a bummer because I like we were.
Yeah, we were very happy with a lot of the void stuff.
And it feels like I don't know what's going to happen.
Now that the actual location is a void.
That's true. Will Nick Adidas here?
I mean, I don't want to this seems like I'm already like
trying to like be a vulture or something.
But like, will Nick Adidas come up for sale as an IP?
Is that something we can add to our collection of characters?
Hearted, unwanted, right?
Like Muggle McFay or various other characters we've mentioned on the show.
Yeah, yeah, there's there's there's one coming up that we do.
I don't think we discussed buying it, but you'll hear something on the second gate.
You know, I mean, I want all of these.
I think we mentioned that one in tandem with Leonardo Columbus,
who I would like to own very much. Yeah. Yeah.
I think, you know, we talked about this like Disney traded
Al Michaels for Oswald, the Lucky Rabbit cartoon.
Sportscaster Al Michaels was traded for a cartoon.
So could we trade Jason for Leonardo Columbus or Nick Adidas
for these various like with Disney accept Jason for Nick?
Sorry for Leonardo Columbus, the character we discovered that was in the
and I'm forgetting the Millennium Celebration.
You have caught Millennium Celebration in 2000.
Wait, so we're we're selling Jason.
I'm just this is hypothetical.
I live to serve.
It's a trade. It's a trade.
Al Michaels was traded.
I mean, I guess, Jason, in this scenario, you don't get to be on this theme
part podcast, but you do like you are a Disney character.
So that's right. Better, right?
Sure. If it comes with three hots in a cot, you know,
three hots, three hot.
That's what they say about the army, right?
Three outs in a cot. Oh, meals. Yeah.
You know, I thought maybe you meant dogs, which could be the meals.
Oh, there are a number of.
Yeah, I'd get I'd have any number of dogs to hang out with.
Huh? I yeah, I guess.
I mean, hot dogs. But right.
I don't think it was hot dogs. Yes.
Yeah, lots of those do.
So I guess seems like you're open to the idea that we could maybe
trade you to some sort of giant company for one of their IPs.
I mean, you know,
we can see it's not like film and TV is rushing to get back to shoot.
Animation is the only viable into so if I want to be,
you know, put into some sort of tune world at Disney's behest.
You're going to be tunified.
Ah, you know, I'm just keeping all my options.
It's up to them to decide what to do.
Yeah, I guess maybe they might want to run you through the cartoon machine.
Plusified. Wow.
Which makes you immortal.
Maybe maybe you get to live forever once you do this.
Yeah. Yeah. Well, I look, we'll see.
I'll see if I can get in touch with some sort of a lawyer
and see what we can do as far as drafting up some some proposals for these companies.
And it's no offense, Jason, it's just that we would love to have Nick
Ademus host the show with Scott and I.
So now are the third co-host is the Voids Nick Ademus,
demon of a vanishment.
A vanishment of vanishment.
Yes. The demon of a vanishment.
A demon who, you know, we haven't talked to.
Maybe we don't.
I haven't said a lot of the context, and I haven't.
You didn't even know the story.
It's about a he comes from a demonstration at the World's
Colombian Exposition, like a World's Fair thing.
He's from 1893.
So he's like an electricity experiment gone awry
that brought a demon to this earth from the he's a steampunk demon,
I think is what he is.
So hosted by my childish
and his childless man in his 30s, one child, full man in his 30s
and a steampunk spirit, evil demon, steampunk demon of a vanishment
who of a vanishment, a demon of a vanishment who's like the second Darren.
Right. There were two Darren's on Bewitched Mike. Yeah.
Yeah. Mm hmm.
And look, you know, we're hitting your we're going to hit year three or four,
I guess, soon.
So this might be a kind of a cousin Oliver situation
where we need to do this to bump up the ratings.
Would he though give us Nickademus?
And I'm also still here.
He is just like cousin Oliver.
Oh, just a totally new. Yeah. Yeah.
Honestly, I think that's going to be too many.
Yeah, I think so. I got to agree with you there.
Sorry, Jason. It's K. I have four hosts.
I don't know. That's a time.
It's a three host kind of thing. We have guests.
Yeah, I kind of like though that maybe he because it, you know,
well, as with Darren on Bewitched, just keeping the name
just for consistency, I think it would make the audience more comfortable.
So it is Nickademus, but playing Jason.
And I'm just sure.
OK, well, you're starting to lose me now.
But what if I have an affinity for ice cream?
I love naps in the Orlando sun and humidity.
Yeah, the people won't maybe even some people won't notice.
I engage in marijuana use slightly more than you, Scott and Mike.
If I am made the subject of fun, your souls will be sent to the combine.
The electricity combine, the property of this earth, me, Jason.
I know youth slang more than you do.
Accept it or die.
Yeah, I look, I
a lot of big changes coming to the show, I think so.
Any of this stuff is on the table.
I keep it fresh, folks. Yeah.
So big, big things coming up.
Something else is undergoing some changes.
Yeah, well, you know, from the the fairly sensitive topic
that is that we came here to discuss after having talked about changing
out one host for a steampunk demon.
Well, isn't that the fun of this show?
The whiplash it gets now on to Disney correcting a 30 year oopsie
and easily correct it.
They really have to be adding that up at this point.
Like, why did why did a log flume
need to be about our most problematic film?
Yes, of course, we're talking about Splash Mountain.
And the Internet has been very normal about it
changing as expected.
Although, you know, I will say this, not as bad as I thought it could be.
No, I don't think it has been.
Yeah. Yeah, I don't think it has been,
but I have not been clicking Seymour replies under any tweets about it.
I've been actively avoiding it.
But for whatever reason, reading through people's remarks,
I feel like maybe it's like five to 10 percent better
than it would have been five years ago.
I think that's yes. Yeah, I think that's very true.
Yeah, as are a number of these kinds of, you know, I feel like this has been
a such an era of changes that were talked about four or five years ago.
And now they're just happening.
Changes like shoving a bunch of statues into the lake,
which has been fun to watch.
We of course are there's no way someone listening to this doesn't know this.
But Splash Mountain, which is a ride that is based as it currently stands,
is a ride based on Disney's extremely problematic 1940s film Song of the South.
They have announced a refresh, a plus up, as they called it in the actual
press release. They're going to re-theme it to the 2009 film Princess
and the Frog.
So which way and I guess maybe the bigger story here is that there was a
Twitter discussion about doing this very thing.
There were petitions going around suggesting this.
A gentleman had posted a Twitter thread proposing how this could be done
and how it might play out.
So somebody we know, we've met with Freddie Chambers, is that correct?
Got a lot of Freddie. Yeah, yeah.
Got a lot of traction off of that.
And so this was like the momentum was building on this throughout a couple of
weeks. And then suddenly one morning out of nowhere, seemingly Disney comes in and
says, yeah, that's exactly what we're thinking.
Yes, we're actually good.
Totally thinking the same thing.
Jinx. And here we go. We're doing it.
Totally. We've been thinking about it for a year, they said.
It's out of sight for like a year over a year, really like five years.
We're totally do you want to see?
Do you want to see what we were working on?
Because we have it all in behind us.
It's all there. That's kind of the I think we probably all agree that this that
the refresh is going to be good and we're excited about it.
And we'll talk a little about what we think it could be.
And I think the thing that's a little funny is this, the Disney like, OK, well,
so look, we're way ahead of you.
And the newest Jason's heart.
Go ahead. Oh, Mike, I was going to say, and Mike, you pretty early on called like
they must have had these plans in a drawer for a while.
Like you don't just have concept art overnight.
You know, I think that the probably the reality of it is that and I think Jim Hill
and there was a recent Disney dish podcast and Jim Hill talked about, I think,
especially after they changed red, they did the they changed the bride auction on
pirates. He says that they had a list of things.
Really? Through. Yeah, there's a list.
And, you know, there's plenty of stuff we all Peter Pan.
It's time to change the native depiction.
Yeah, Peter Pan. It's and get rid of the ride entirely in the character entirely.
No, there's a movie coming.
There's a coming.
And the good news is that on this podcast alone, we've got casting for a pan,
a smee and a very tall lost boy.
So sure, I think we're all set.
And I don't want to sell myself short, but some of us will work for scale.
We know Scott is pan. Yeah.
So let's make that cast me in it.
I have to do it. I have to wear the thing.
And I've got a number of tweets saying Jason is me.
Right. Which Mike, you know, we talked about it.
And I think you've been trying to will that to exist for nearly a decade, Michael.
So can I be a pan who says why?
In fact, I did grow up and I'm happy I did.
I still now I haven't turned my back on childish things.
I enjoy them very much.
However, I refuse to run around and mock little girls
and say, I'll be a little boy forever, because that's weird.
Unfortunately, the great Robin Williams already gave that performance.
No, no, no. What? No, because he turned his back on it.
No, because he
moved on. He's like, I'm a lawyer and I throw I'm on my cell phone
and I miss my kids baseball game.
This is a well rounded pan who, you know, is a well adjusted adult, but also,
you know, flies around as well, too.
I hear what you're saying.
And that's a good idea.
But could you just do the lines from the Disney cartoon
just for us right now that you did on the Peter Pan episode?
Just one or two of them.
What were they?
I don't know. You just did some pan impression.
Here I have my notes in front of me.
So I have to you like my take, but I'm going to do.
I have to do the same lines.
Just we want both versions to see, you know.
OK. All right.
I thought the only one I have written down is girls talk too much.
Well, get on with it, girl.
Tink says you're a big, ugly girl.
This is see, this is what I view.
Anyone who wants to make fun of me for saying Pan is canceled now,
do you like hearing these lines again?
Huh? There's a reason I have an issue here.
Right. Well, look, thanks for doing that.
We're still going to take it under consideration at the pan committee,
at the Peter Pan movie committee over here.
So, yes, so there's a list.
I will say Country Bears is on the list.
But as a bear, it is on the list
because some of those songs are like body by like modern children's standards.
Well, the one that Jim says is for body.
I don't know. Jim didn't say body.
Jim says mama, don't whoop little Buford,
which is a joke song about like hitting a kid.
So like stuff like that is going to go.
And like you're on the saddle.
I think one on the saddle might stay.
But but so I'm just saying, all my point is, is that there is a list of this stuff.
Yeah. The Disney knows.
I think, though, that what it seems like is Splash Mountain
might have been at the end of the list and is now at the front of the list.
Why would it have been at the end?
Because it's expensive.
Yeah, that. Yeah, that's true.
And that's some of what, you know, there's things that were like
out of our depths to talk about a little bit.
But one thing we can talk about is logistics.
And that's one thing that I flashed to.
I think this thing will be really cool when they do it.
But I'm also like, this is going to be the most expensive thing
because it is such it's a very long ride.
And it is a ride with hundreds of animatronics.
And assuming that they were going to keep it that way and not reuse animatronics,
although maybe they would if it was going to be entirely new.
Like, oh, my God, that is so much space to to populate,
which I, you know, a year ago, I would have felt like they'll do this.
No problem. Now it's I don't know if you've heard.
It's been a really rough time financially for the parks.
I'm just curious how it'll how it'll play.
I just I want this to be like the full tilt version of what it could be
and not like full of screens and, you know,
how fast because it has to be.
I think of what Jim will.
So Jim has a full rundown of at least one of the plans kind of for it.
So I think it is sort of taking some of the scenes and just changing them around
and putting the alligator in where the bear was.
Like, there's certain things I think that they're going to
keep the bones of the actual ride.
Perhaps the like like literally the bones,
because the bear is kind of rotund
and then the alligator is kind of rotund.
So will it? Yeah, maybe they can just do some reuse there.
So I think that's probably part of it.
But I would assume Disney would put a lot of money into this
because this is not that's not a good idea if they they cheap out on this.
Well, I mean, clearly they, you know, they can't cheap out on this.
It clearly reached the point where it's no longer
a financial plus. It's a liability.
It's weird that they did this in the 80s.
I think the idea was maybe we can separate
some elements from a problematic thing.
And I assume it's also pre Internet.
And they're like thinking, well, we're not going to put this out.
And like at a certain point, people will come to know it just as this ride.
Oh, again, as I said, the mind blowing stat, I said the first time around
that this movie was re released in the 80s.
Well, that's crazy. That was a test.
It was a test to see if people would be a gog at it.
And they went and saw the re-release and they're like,
I guess we can make a ride out of it.
Let's just make the TGIF stars ride it a lot.
So everyone associates it with our Friday night lineup and not the
weird historical artifact that makes people think that everyone was
a wacky character in Reconstruction RSL.
Well, and like yearning for the days before that,
the movie was so controversial at the time it was made.
It's not like in hindsight.
Yeah, big end OSP protests.
Monarch release. Yeah, it's bizarre.
So my assumption about the 80s is they were like, well, you know, we could.
It's the Mark Davis characters and it's nice and we can sort of take
these things out of context and maybe people won't know
because we're not going to put the movie out on home video, which is still crazy.
I'm not making excuses for people, but I'm assuming that's the logic.
But when you get to an Internet era, the Internet never forgets.
Yeah, this is the thing.
And if anybody's on the fence about this, I think it's fine to feel nostalgic
for this because we just grew up with this ride.
But like this is what I was imagining.
You imagine a kid who's like us, a weird nerd kid who's black,
who loves Disneyland, goes on Splash Mountain, loves it
and then goes home and Googles it like that sucks.
Yeah, that's what I've been flashing to is anybody like going on the ride,
having a good time.
So what's that right about?
Who are those characters about in the conversation that ensues
and that that conversation could lead you to a very like
grim film and some bad stuff.
And with this remodel, you will go on the ride, have the same thrills,
the drops in the same places, a bunch of happy songs.
And then you'll say, what were those characters from?
Oh, this like this nice movie that's very charming
with a lot of great black artists in it.
And that's a better conversation to have after.
And I think that's why you do it.
It'll make people feel good.
Yes, absolutely. Yeah.
I think if you feel like the ride was in a gray area,
it is based on a film that is not in a gray area.
And I think that's ultimately the reason to not. Right.
And the parks are different than movies, too, I think.
Like there's a lot of debate, of course, about movies and censorship
and like movies, like they are like a document.
And you should put a thing at the front of them
explaining the context of the time.
But the parks are living things.
So I see a lot of arguments of like, well, it's been here for 30 years.
And it's like things change in the parks all the time.
That's what's going to happen.
And you should get used to it happening more because it's going to happen.
Absolutely. And in fact, if you think about it,
Splash Mountain 1.0 will have ended up having a longer run
by far than Jurassic Park, the ride
way before it switched to Jurassic World, the ride.
So, you know, it's like that's a gigantic ride.
That's that's longer than a ton of things get.
And I think it's fine to feel sad.
I mean, when you're 10 years old and going on this and have no idea,
you just get nostalgic for a thing that's a fun experience.
But as an adult, you go, yeah, it's time.
It's time for this to go.
Well, so you could be sad, I think, if they were going to take this
ride down and replace it with a lecture or like, you know,
or like, remember when there was some dumbass senator
who people chose to elect said something about what if they
are they're going to rename the Washington Monument, the obelisk of wokeness,
which a lot of people said is actually cool.
That's kind of a neat, neat, cooler name.
But also like, no, it's not.
If you were taking out a fun ride and replacing it with a bummer, perhaps
this is going to be the same ride.
It's going to be a happy celebration.
That is, I think, according to the official literature, like a Mardi Gras.
It's going to be like a happy party.
It's still going to make you
there's no reason to be sad.
I watched the movie last night, Princess and the Frog.
I hadn't seen it in a long time.
Very catchy songs.
There is a giant swamp gator playing a trumpet.
I mean, what else?
He's what else do you want?
I mean, that's great.
I'll say sorry, Mike.
I will say, I'm very curious
for a movie.
Uh, a lot of voodoo in that movie.
And I'm curious to see how that is.
Like, I'm curious how much they put of that in
because they just kind of use voodoo as like a catchall.
Sure. I mean, I don't know.
I think that the movie is taking.
Excuse me. The ride is taking place after the movie.
So they can sort of create a fully new narrative
and even put characters in different contexts as well.
So that which makes honestly, it seems cooler.
I mean, because it's being headed up by the woman
who did Runaway Railway, I believe.
I looked up some stuff about her.
Sharita Carter, the senior creative producer on this.
She worked in engineering for a long time, worked her way up from accountant.
She was an accountant for a long time, then moved over to the creative world,
managed a concept lab that was like testing out different technology.
And the thing that came out of that was projection mapping
and starting to deploy that in the parks, which is all over the parks.
And if you watch episode five of the Imagineering story on Disney Plus,
she talks about all that and implementing it on Mara in the Indiana Jones adventure.
I think she kind of spearheaded that project that now when you go up that ramp,
that, you know, Mara looks mad and the lightning flashes
and all those cool effects they do.
And then it seems that was I mean, imagineers do all this stuff.
You don't even know what it is.
You know, they aren't credited usually.
But she's associated with that.
And then Mickey and Minnie's runaway railway, which I haven't
I purposefully not watch yet because I don't want to spoil it.
I don't either.
It seems that people seem to love it.
So I think this this plus up is in very good hands.
So, yeah, I think you're doing you're using like the characters and they're
going to get to do a new story with them, which is cool and exciting.
And it's also like good that it's not the book report.
Oh, yes. So there I because I saw I maybe didn't read that initial
press release that carefully and I saw people saying
I just hope it's not one of those that just steps through all the events
of the movie. But quote the official press release.
We pick this story up after the final kiss, which implies that the main characters
are not frogs, at least when we meet them.
Perhaps they would be frogs again, but we don't know.
And we join Princess Tiana and Lewis, who's the alligator on a musical adventure
as they prepare for their first ever Mardi Gras performance.
So it is a it is a new story,
which I think will make this thing more fun.
And yeah, that'll I think determine is is the villain Dr.
Facilier in there.
He died, but he's like a magic guy.
So maybe he can come back like Farquaad, like the ghost of Farquaad.
I mean, it's a great performance from Keith David.
I mean, he's great. Oh, yeah. Yeah.
I think he'll probably I think I think Jim had a real a rundown of at least a version
of of it in their head, and I believe he was in it.
I think he's in the in the in the lift hill.
That's what you'd have to think.
And that was that was in Freddie's notion of it.
And that sounds really cool, especially I I Jason, you really watched it.
I had never watched this movie and I thought I should before we talked about it.
And it made me more excited about this whole thing, because I found it very charming.
I thought it was great.
And there's there's a lot of like crazy business with his shadow
and like big, scary shadows getting projected.
And that's sort of what happens already on the hill a little bit with rare Fox.
So you could do things in that spirit.
So you had the lift over and the drop being, you know, like the villains
rise before the the the sheer pleasure, as Tony Baxter
described it, that that follows after the drop.
Yeah. I mean, and then you go out of Mama Odie's house, I believe.
That's what the sort of the set piece of the ride is.
Or I guess what do you call it?
I guess that's what the that's what you're leaving the log and the big drop.
Yes. So that means so that because in the movie
they go to visit her in this big tree as it has a boat sticking out of it.
And in the concept art, they released.
That's what it is. So it is.
It is crazy how much overlap there is and how much they already had the bones
to do this, because that was a lot of the question.
Like if you were ever going to replace it with what?
Because are you going to find a thing with a big tree?
Oh, this. Oh, my God.
So that's cool.
It begs this question, though,
that in in current Splash Mountain,
it is a big like tree stump, essentially.
And that that it is also, you know, the ride is called Splash Mountain.
That thing is called Chickapin Hill.
In the movie, this is in no way a mountain.
That is purely a tree.
It's not on top of a hill or a mountain.
It's a tree.
So can you still call this ride Splash Mountain?
That is a question because Splash Mountain has nothing to do with Song of the South.
No, we can say definitely.
Yeah, Eisner name.
Yes, because of the mountains.
It's a good well. And after
Darryl Hannah, the Darryl Hannah film, that's really why it's called that,
which, as I texted to you, my the only sin of splash with Darryl
Hannah in Disney's eyes is its depiction of the dirty, dirty female form.
Well, of course, there I have to agree.
Disney Plus, of course, censored Splat.
They like put more mermaid hair and blurred her body.
This is one thing I don't understand about Disney Plus is the puritanical
nature of it and the creepy like getting rid of things.
And it feels a lot like when Blockbuster would scrub movies
because like Southern morality groups would make them up.
I'm not keen on all that stuff.
There's such a tight leash on everything in Disney
where it's like it's just I mean, it's a struggle.
Like we obviously like all this Disney stuff, but we also talk about how crazy
and fucked up things are.
It's like it's just a struggle to get a gay character in a major movie.
Like it was like Black Panther at Marvel when Ike Perlmutter was in charge,
was like that was going to be hard.
Like that's not going to work. We're not going to do that.
That was a struggle for years to get made.
Cut to it, making so much money, being a massive cultural phenomenon.
So it's it's very similar.
I feel like where they're just like it's the most conservative.
We don't want to make anyone mad and we need to preserve.
And it's like, is really are people really going to be mad about
a little nudity and splash a side boob a little bit?
That really well, that's really
that's why Splash Mountain was so odd for so long.
It's a company that always has all its ducks in a row.
And then there is one very odd like this hugely popular ride,
partially largely popular because it's a water ride and the parks are in
very warm climates for the most part, at least in America.
And yeah. And if you say, well, so that's based on this
and that the Haunted Mansion's original, what's this based on?
Oh, don't worry about it.
It's great. It's based on the T-shirts you can buy at the gift shop,
which they are trying.
They are simultaneously like we're redoing Splash Mountain.
We also have a lot of back stock to sell off.
We have a lot of stuffed animals and little guys that sit on your shoulder.
And oh, yeah.
Well, look, yeah, it's not like completely virtuous or anything. Yeah.
And it's also it's going to be weird for a while because the, you know,
the Magic Kingdom is opening.
As you're listening to this, the Magic Kingdom is opening back up tomorrow
and it will be open with Splash Mountain as is.
And that's kind of one of the weirdest things about all that.
I mean, especially as is could be open for a really long time.
So this making this press release is kind of just it's like
getting their foot in the door. It's like, OK, so even if you go on the ride
and it makes you mad in any way, eventually some time from now.
But it's just going to be odd.
And you feel like, you know, it's the worst thing
it's going to happen is that the park's going to open back up in Florida.
And the worst people on earth will proudly go on Splash Mountain
and film it in a way it's like, see, it's fine.
And also not wearing a mask like see, it's fine.
And breathing in the splash air
to make a point, the sweetest smell
tried to stop me, please.
And you know what?
We'll come back to the idea, the name of it real quick.
I will say that water smell ain't going away.
Don't worry. Yeah.
I saw people saying like, it's just I'm going to miss the stuff, you know,
the you know, the the you know, the drop and the smell and like,
well, that's all not going to this.
I'm convinced it will have the bones of what we like a lot.
I like I swear there's going to be so much of the of the vibe.
I think like I really believe like 70 to 80 percent or more about what
like what you dig about this ride is still going to be intact,
mixed with up to date, like better technology and,
you know, been very good songs and all that. Right.
And it's like everybody.
There's a lot of people throw fits when stuff changes. But like
I want cool new stuff in the Haunted Mansion, too.
I want cool like everywhere.
And like, I'm sure they're going to throw a lot of money at this.
And it's going to be very cool.
I'm sure of it. Yeah, I am just I'm all for this.
I'm excited to see what they're going to do.
I think they give it six months to a year of the
old version of Splash Mountain staying open because people have not been able
to ride it. I don't know about that.
I'm curious. I'm I wonder if because people aren't like people
are going to trickle back to the park.
I don't I don't know.
Jim Hill was saying like, oh, there'll be like farewell events,
but I don't think that sits right right now.
I don't think they will do farewell events.
No, I granted I was wrong.
I said this I was guessing in our text, I was like
they will probably when people started talking about Splash Mountain
going away online of like they should maybe do that.
Like I said, I think Disney thinks they can probably get five to
10 more years out of it.
And I was wrong and I was happy I was wrong.
Yeah, I mean, I was I didn't think
it's partly because we've just lived with it so long
and it's just like, oh, yeah, that's weird.
OK, you know, like as opposed to like really sitting down
and thinking about it and going, yeah, of course, this has to go.
So I am I was surprised, too.
But yeah, I don't think it doesn't feel right to be like and say goodbye
to all your good friends.
Oh, yeah. Any official art with that?
I think the thing that surprised me about it was, yeah, I yeah,
I felt like this won't happen just because, you know, less because they
they aren't sensitive to the issues and more just like they're not going to do it
because of Twitter.
I really didn't think that was the case.
And now, and did they do it because of Twitter?
I don't think so.
Did they get this announcement out of what they were doing anyway
because of Twitter? Absolutely.
So you do have to credit the discussion with shaping it
and forcing their hand, getting them to just come out and say, all right,
it's coming. Don't worry about it.
Right. And look, major media companies
and politicians, by and large, do things when there's pressure,
not because they're like looking to make the absolute right move
before the pressure comes.
So, yes, absolutely.
It's like it's a storm, a perfect storm of things.
And I'm going, yeah, it's out. It's done. We're doing we're good.
Yeah, we were. We're we swear we're doing it.
I'll say this.
And this is just speculation right now.
This is just a rumor. Unrelated Splash Mountain.
All for Splash Mountain.
Can't wait to see it.
If after the job they did flipping guardians,
I'm just so excited to see what they could do with this.
I am begging them, please imagineering.
I do not think weird Al Jankovic and Lin-Manuel Miranda
can save the Hall of Presidents.
Please just demolish it and build a sleepy hollow thrill ride.
Build a headless horseman indoor thrill ride.
I am begging you, please do not try to make a fun
and funky Hall of Presidents.
We were did weird Al enter into the picture.
Weird Al, I get the Hamilton reference.
Well, why is weird Al in there?
That is just the rumor I saw going around.
Weird Al and Lin-Manuel Miranda possibly
fixing Hall of Presidents.
Why don't you?
I don't know that it's I don't know that it's sourced.
I think that's a fan fan service.
Full banking. Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, American Adventure is going to change.
I don't know if weird Al is going to go in there either.
I would like the I would like to see the hall of Lin-Manuel Miranda
talk show host friendship.
I I'm not convinced enough that Lin-Manuel is friends
with each and every person who hosts the talk show
and that you'd consider any of them those real bromances.
So I would like to see just a 20 minute show
telling me all about his individual relationships
with Jimmy Fallon and James Corden.
And, you know, do they hang out for real?
Do they text each other?
We need to know these ants and we can tell we can we can
reveal these answers via animatronics.
Scott, I like the idea, but I think I'm going to have to poke holes.
It's going to have to just be Jimmy Kimmel because of the synergy.
Oh, that's the only one that they would.
Yeah. Yeah.
You know, now that it now that I think about it, I don't
I associate Lin-Manuel less with Jimmy Kimmel, which is a shame,
because I think he's he should have equal
bromances with every single person.
Look, I couldn't agree more.
See them wrestling and play fighting and musing each other's hair.
Yeah. Can't get enough of that content. Right.
I will getting back to your first question, though,
I do probably think Splash Mountain as a name is gone.
I think it doesn't really make sense.
But I if it's a tree.
Yeah, I don't know that it's there is no.
Yeah, it isn't a mountain.
There's no the no the no way is what happens in the movie.
A mountain. But if I were on a board of directors,
I would cast my vote for keeping the name.
Why? For stupidity.
It's so silly of a name.
And I and as has been discussed on Twitter and, you know,
Jenny Nicholson was funnier about this probably than I will be.
But the Disney's names are so fucking complicated these days.
So if you're going to make it something simple,
do not make this a paragraph of a title of a.
That's the problem, too, I think, with calling a splash mountain
because they can't just call it splash mountain.
It will absolutely have 10 different words after that.
I'm OK with that.
Even an amended splash mountain.
The thing in the headline and I think this is wrong, but I think
in the headline of what Disney released and a lot of
scuttlebutt and blogs and stuff seem to believe that what
this phrase that they put out is the name or as a code name,
they're calling it right now, which is New Adventures with Princess Tiana.
And they they cannot call it that.
That is the dullest. That is not fun.
No, no, no, no.
Yeah, I I wonder.
I mean, it's like is it so a splash mountain?
But it's a parentheses, but it's a tree really.
And it's Adventures of Tiana.
Then the adventures are new.
Something like that is not quite that, but something like that.
Tiana's ultimate swamp.
Fantastic adventure celebration magic.
How about parentheses magic wish?
Like tree tree mountain.
Yeah, it's still a mountain mountain.
I thought Bayou Mountain.
That's a funny.
What about what about splash Bayou?
Oh, splash Bayou.
Oh, OK.
Has the simplicity.
I like that. Yeah.
And isn't the song on the bayou,
there's a song on the bayou, right in the movie?
Yeah. No, no, no, it's not.
It's not in the it's like it was just here down in New Orleans.
Down in New Orleans, they play a snippet of on the Mark Twain.
I think the big ending number will probably be dig a little deeper.
That's so catchy.
Oh, going down the bayou is going down the bayou.
Yeah. Yeah.
Jim Hill does say, I believe, dig a little deeper is the end is the big finale.
Sense to me, that sounds good.
Well, that's the thing we talked about.
The finale feels like it could be a lot, you know,
a lot of what it currently had.
And probably you could still reuse the riverboat.
There's riverboats in the movie.
I think that's right.
I think they're going to reuse some of the animatronics for sure.
I'm not sure the gym, the gym, gym, seem to have a lot of details.
I don't know where Jim gets the entire proposal.
Also, we got to have Jim on.
I don't know. He's not going to give up his sources
because he's a professional longtime journalist.
But I'm very curious because he has this whole proposal that he read off.
So I'm very curious.
But if you want to listen to Disney dish with Jim and Len,
if you want to hear more about the specifics of what's being proposed.
Is it now is it weird, you think, to reuse the.
Animatronics to, you know, listeners probably know this,
but the history lesson is all, you know, besides the Breyer characters,
most of the animatronics in Splash Mountain are from a defunct
attraction called America Sings that was in Tomorrowland for a long time.
More of a country bears style, like a little review with all these singing
critters. And so they were from another ride already.
They moved into a ride.
They they've all those animatronics have to feel like they just they got their
photo taken in the wrong place.
Like they didn't like we didn't know we did.
Like they have a photo of the guy that had racist tweets later.
Like we didn't know any of that at the time.
We just were in the wrong place.
And they should they, you know, they shouldn't be held accountable.
But are they too well, they just not matched.
Do they feel like too old of animatronics like are too unrelated?
I wonder. I yeah, I don't know.
That's a good question. I don't know. I mean,
like I know the vultures that are on their lift hill are not from the movie.
Those are from America Sings.
I assume. Yeah, it's interesting.
I just I've read a lot about this and there's a lot of, you know,
very interesting pieces
that maybe we could find that are linked to about like the different
what's from the movie, what is
like what's directly from the movie, what they like, just like
completely whitewash from the movie, which also is horrifying, too.
But then what characters and stuff is not it's just from America Sings.
So I think maybe all the stuff that has nothing to do with the movie
might still be on the table.
But I bet they're still figuring that out.
I bet this is still not really any of this. Yeah. Yeah.
And like, will you still see the
are the pigs dancing in a style like with like a petticoat or something?
Will we see them? Will they come back?
I think they read dress.
I mean, they had to rerecord all the audio.
They have to do new audio.
Yeah, maybe more more fun
like Mardi Gras outfits for the animals.
You could update the looks. Yeah.
If you look in the concept art, Tiana is in a boat
with a bunch of Mardi Gras masks and costumes and decoration.
That's kind of the only hint you get of what's common.
So that might make sense. Yeah.
Maybe you throw a bunch of Mardi Gras stuff on them.
And if you if you guys have any more thoughts about this,
I do have a proposal as well, and I shouldn't give this away for free
because I don't work for Imagineering.
But now the now the situation is such that critter country
has lost a large piece of real estate in Disneyland.
It's going to be New Orleans is going to extend out.
And now Poo is sort of in his own little spot back there.
Thoughtful.
In is. Yes, exactly.
And that's technically technically critter country.
And that Poo ride is fine.
It is not as good as the Tokyo one.
I think here's my proposal.
You get rid of Poo and you put in a bear show.
But it's a jazz band bear show.
Oh, huh.
So that's New Orleans Squares all the way back to the Poo area.
That's they're never going to do that, because I'm sure Poo makes them a lot of money.
But then you bring bears back into that spot
and you make it thematically all New Orleans.
With with Louie, Louie the Gator in there playing with the bears
and flip the restaurant to Tiana's place.
I feel like I've seen people speculating of like, well,
the movie ends with a character getting a giant restaurant.
So I feel like that's a missed opportunity if you don't use that.
Now, I've thought about this, too, because but I think maybe the issue is like,
isn't that like sort of a it's like a quick service restaurant
as opposed to Tiana's restaurant, which is like nice and good
and also not like
country fried, like it's more New Orleans City vibe.
So I feel like maybe the only issue there might be like
it might do a disservice to Tiana's place.
If it's like a place where you get shitty chicken fingers,
you could read theme one of the what's that one restaurant?
That's not it's pretty close to Haunted Mansion.
I can never remember the Riverbell Terrace.
Or no, that's sorry.
Cafe Orleans is next to Haunted Mansion.
OK, can you read them that?
I mean, that's still kind of quick service, but it's a little bit more dressed up.
It can be a little bit more.
Oh, wait, no. Cafe Orleans is table service.
French Market is like Buffeteeria.
So you can easily flip one of them. They're pretty generic. Right.
Maybe maybe that maybe that's the answer
because there's just not a lot of real estate around there.
Or you just demolish Poo and put the restaurant back there.
That would be a big hit if you made a fully cool themed
restaurant, almost like be our guest style with just like elaborate theming.
I mean, people love that stuff.
We love that stuff.
There's one candy store shop back there.
Sure. That you could easily, you know, rebuild.
You are well, you mean the Poo, the Poo gift shop, essentially.
Yeah, the Poo gift shop. Right. Sure.
I don't know. I don't. Yeah, there's not.
You're not losing too much getting rid of the Poo gift shop.
Yeah. No offense to Poo.
He can find a new home somewhere.
Yeah. I just wonder if they will do because I think it's good.
I think the pure ride is going to be so expensive.
So will they do?
Probably. I mean, I don't think, you know, I'm sure they
because all the imagineers are nerds like us and think about something like that.
Well, you know, critical country is only this small.
It's really not a full land anymore.
But is that that probably goes way down the list of changes?
I'm assuming maybe they all probably have it in their mind of like,
yeah, we got to make sure this is all one stretch of New Orleans
or whatever other ideas they have.
But I would imagine that, yes, that's going to go down the list,
especially when they're like getting bankrolled by Saudi Arabia
to keep them out of debt right now.
I assume a minor 500 million dollar infusion.
Yeah. So
so that I mean, is that a place to start transitioning to?
You know what the hell else is going on?
I because it's a crazy.
I mean, I, you know, I maybe found it sort of like a nice
arkening back to a simpler time to get just a story about a new ride
that's coming instead of all the parks news being like, OK, so we are putting up
partitions in the like the train will have plexiglass dividers.
Every everything's been such a bummer.
So it was nice to see a piece of art.
It's like, look at that smile and alligator.
Well, I'm sorry, I told you guys I had this beforehand.
Unfortunately, you've set me up for the very dumb news story I have.
This is from the Disney Food blog,
a very thorough theme park website.
Do you guys know about the blue wall?
The Grand Floridian's brand new blue wall?
I thought you meant politically.
Well, no, that's a blue firewall.
OK, so I saw the headline about this
and I truly thought it was another Instagram thing.
And it is not.
I'm going to send you guys a picture right now.
This is.
So what this is, the Grand Floridian has been cut in half
by a giant looks to be about eight foot blue wall.
Bright, bright blue, right?
Bright blue.
Not in keeping with the theme of this like
charming Victorian hotel whatsoever.
Not at all.
So this the hotel has essentially been bisected.
The reason being half of it is for NBA teams
and half of it is for guests who are staying there.
And I don't know why these pictures of the like one of the most expensive
and if not the most expensive hotel, the Orlando property,
I just could not get over this massive wall
that will probably be here for a while.
And the blog pointed out
the wall completely wipes out the view of the Magic Kingdom
from the main building.
Shh. We were we were able to just spot the tippy top of the highest spire
of Cinderella Casper Castle from Gasparia Island Grill.
Normally you have a nice clear view of the castle when leaving the spot.
So the most expensive hotel now doesn't offer one of the main things
you spend money for.
No. And they were already there was already construction in back of this hotel
because finally, after decades, they were completing a path
where you could walk from this hotel to the Magic Kingdom.
You have not been able to do that due to waterways.
A whole time you've never it's that close and you've never been able to take a walk.
Only the only the contemporary can you walk directly to the Magic Kingdom?
You have to go the other way.
So this will finally complete the loop.
Only 50 years later.
Only. So you know, a big wall.
Look at this guy.
Yeah, there's a lot of bummer stuff
about the situation with the covid.
And there you sent us a clip of a loudspeaker
announcement of a cheerful person just telling you to wear a mask.
Yeah. And that's that's Verhoeven ask.
That's a very great fun.
Well, yeah.
Remember, wear your mask and keep away from each other.
Oh, and have a nice day.
And have a nice day.
Your magic band guarantees citizenship of the Magic Kingdom.
That is if you're hearing this today, this episode's coming out.
And tomorrow the Magic Kingdom is reopening,
which they're heading for and they've been doing cast member tests of.
And the they're also heading for
reopenings of Disney parks in Japan and in France.
These are all the Japan plants.
Japan is open. Japan is open.
OK. Yeah.
Well, I was just curious about a couple of some some numbers,
you know, with if these are the places that they're trying to get back open.
How is the disease going there in the country of Japan?
They're hovering around 150 new cases a day, which they're they're very alarmed
about. France has been spiking recently at about 1500 a day.
It's sort of shot a little back up and they're trying to get it under control.
The state, as opposed to the country of Florida, the state of Florida,
10,000 new cases, the country of Japan,
150 new cases, the state of Florida, 10,000.
Anyway, have fun.
Happy to play center.
Yeah. Born down in a dead man's town.
First step I took is when I hit the ground.
Yeah, it's a it's very I'm I'm depressed.
Let's just put it that way. I am depressed.
I'm still scared.
It's crazy what's going on.
It is crazy. Like like China shut down,
I think, like the city when there was like 50 more.
And yeah, if you're going to do this in Florida, please mask.
I don't want to.
I don't think that's political.
Just please mask.
Mm hmm. Is there anyone listening to this theme park
nerd podcast where we call ourselves good boys?
Is there any is any listener an anti mask person?
And if so, I'm not too worried about offending you.
I think it might be only one right now.
So if you the one person put it on, dude.
I think you're opening up or, man, I think you're
I think you're calling it out.
Please tell us about this.
No, no, I'm just saying.
Don't listen to the show.
Fuck off.
Please tell us about the other doctors.
You folks are always on about.
I want to hear more about the other doctors.
That's always so fun.
Tokyo, Tokyo mask wise.
It's like they were mad.
That seems to be the difference is the masks.
So I'm begging you.
I'm begging you with peace and love, as Mr.
Ringo Starr would say, please.
Yeah, boy, because, you know, shit's going awry.
And it's not just in theme park world.
It's also in themed entertainment world in general.
We discussed the voids issues.
And one thing that we haven't talked about is the
the recent bankruptcy declarations of two
themed adjacent organizations related to the pandemic.
The first one being Cirque du Soleil
has declared bankruptcy and they are claiming that they're going to get things back open.
And they they they claim actually that the Florida one
because they've been working on a new show for Disney Springs.
And they're claiming that that's not down for the count.
And that'll be back open.
And that, you know, claiming bankruptcy is a thing that helps.
But who knows? It doesn't sound good.
And this was apparently broken
to the employees via.
Let me just share my screen really fast.
This is a this is just a still from a video.
This is this this guy you're looking at is the CEO of Cirque du Soleil.
I forget his name, but he delivered sort of a grave little address about how this is.
Imagine you are fired via a video that's emailed to you
where a guy in like a cravat
and lavender tinted Bono glasses
talks to you in front of a fancy abstract painting,
which has even like a tag like telling you the artist, which implies it's like
a expensive, nice painting.
Anyway, this is Cirque du Soleil.
This is who I'm very sorry.
Your shit that I like.
Yeah, I I am interested.
What? Because how many shows the Cirque du Soleil have around the world,
like 30 or something? Yeah, it's crazy.
I mean, Vegas alone has like six.
Something like that. So and it's and they involve a lot of performers,
a lot of talented human performers,
which makes it a more heartbreaking firing in some ways, although I
whether that may that you guys can tell me how you think it compares
and contrast to the other place that has had to declare bankruptcy,
that being Chuck E.
Cheese, which is affecting.
I mean, certainly human employees as well, but on the entertainment
and animatronic entertainers who have already had a very rough decade.
And so true.
I don't know where things stand for them.
I was I was looking at a list.
I actually this is on our somebody posted this on our Facebook group.
There was a list of which stores are are closing.
And I didn't have time to go through the whole thing,
but there are five in California.
And I thought this was important work to do.
And I got that I crunched the numbers.
Two of the five full munch, two of the five are stores with the full set.
Original animatronics.
Now, the other three, that's I say, that's what you get.
You switch to Studio C where it's only Chuck.
And, you know, that's what happens.
But these ones are the full that still have munch and Pasquale.
All right. I'm sorry to see them go.
Yeah, I mean, they were on their way out.
And this obviously sped up what was going to happen.
I really think I don't know what's happening to the Chuck E.
Cheese right over here, but that one already got rid of the full munch,
I believe, which is a tragedy.
But if it was going away, would I be hanging out in the dumpster?
Yes, I would absolutely be hanging out,
seeing if they just dumped munch's body in a dumpster.
Yes. Now, would you attempt to go in there?
Because is it the safest thing to go near a closed Chuck E.
Cheese dumpster?
Because it would be maybe your or all of our chance to have one of the robots.
And you mean as far as COVID is concerned?
Yes. Yeah.
Well, I am not as concerned about touching because I would, of course, be masked up.
I would probably, especially if it's a dumpster, I'm going to have gloves on.
No gloves. And I don't I don't from what I've been reading,
which is read it every night for two hours about COVID
before bed.
You know, Mike, I have an idea about that depression.
No, no, no, no, no, no. I think it's fine.
I think it's normal.
I think that there's no way that COVID is going to jump off of munch onto me.
I would take munch.
I would rescue his robot body.
I would put it in the car.
I, of course, would not be touching my face the whole time.
I would dump him in the little storage unit we have by the parking
spaces in our apartment.
And I'd let him sit there for maybe a couple of days to let the virus die.
And then, of course, I would bring him in my house and treat him as my son.
And then Edwin would stress hump for,
you know, 10 months to a year.
Right. That's true.
No, well, Edwin, I think he would.
Edwin would eventually see him as an equal, I think.
Everyone eventually would sort of earn
or munch would earn Edwin's respect, is what I'm saying.
Sure, sure. They'd learn to coexist.
They're they're fuzzy things and they should get along.
My two sons.
I guess Edwin and munch, you know, really, this list, this is in USA Today.
Chuck E.
Cheese.
I don't know. It's I don't need to read the headline.
Look up the article.
And if you're interested in getting one of these robots,
see if one of the stores is near you.
If you're you live in Vernon Hills, Illinois, if you live in Natick,
Massachusetts or Danvers
or Lima, Ohio, there's many.
This is this is your shot.
Lima, it's your time.
You might end up with a with a Helen or even just a just a ski ball.
Right. You could take a whole ski ball home.
A very difficult task.
Take 10 ski ball lanes home.
Someone did send us a photo of like the back area outside
dumpster area of a Chuck E.
Cheese and there was rotting games like I didn't see.
I don't know that games that there were any animatronics,
but there was definitely like a small carousel,
you know, a quarter operated carousel and like a yeah, you know,
whack a mole kind of thing.
I bet the company is savvy enough to know they could like sell all those
robots on eBay and make a lot of money, I would assume.
Well, I think now is the time for a hero to swoop in.
Go ahead. And the hero is.
The man from showbiz pizza who has a massive warehouse in Orlando.
Oh, yes.
His name again.
Aaron Fector. Right. Yeah.
That that's that's an interesting idea you have, Jason.
Factor and, you know, a group, a group of local businessmen.
I thought you were going to say us and I was going to be fully on board
to reimagine Chuck E.
Cheese for a new generation.
No, no, it will be a reimagining of showbiz pizza for a new generation.
All right. Do you have both good ideas?
Yes, both good ideas. I don't want to discount yours.
You guys check your phones.
Maybe we could do a little sudden flash version of
souvenir smackdown.
Sure. You're about to get a photo of I went to eBay.
I haven't done this a long time.
Went to eBay, searched for Chuck E.
Cheese and went to most expensive.
This is not the most expensive, but it is in the you know, there's a little hint.
It's in the top, let's say, 20.
And what you are looking at is Helen, the bird characters close.
This these are clothes that were removed from an animatronic.
It is, you know, kind of like some feather fuzz.
It is like a hair scrunchie.
It's a very like, you know, what a seven year old girl would wear
to be fancy in 1988, like a fuchsia sparkly skirt.
I mean, it's, you know, one of the main Helen
wardrobes.
So how much you think you're paying for
Helen's clothes?
Well, how much would I pay or how much do I think they're offering?
Because money is no object for me.
But what I think the eBay, what they're asking, I think, is.
Seventy five hundred dollars,
only five hundred, Jason.
I'm going to go lower. I'm going to go one thousand dollars.
Much closer is Jason.
It is six hundred dollars.
Wow. Oh, my God. Send me the link.
I got to get these clothes.
I hope they fit.
Mike, not only do you win this auction,
you win a spot on a list on a government watch list.
Congratulations to Michael Carlson.
Benzie, I brought you a summer gift.
I brought you some clothes for summer.
Now go ahead and get yourself ready.
I'll read Reddit theories for two hours and in two hours time.
I won't call you Lindsay anymore.
You'll be Helen. You will be Helen from now on.
Lindsay, pack a raincoat.
According to Reddit, some sort of storm is coming.
I don't know what that's about, but I'm starting to dig.
Lindsay, here's our Helen as you are from now on.
Here's a song. I'll just watch this video.
I'll teach it to you.
There's a little bit of it.
How could he say that I'm just one of the guys?
Listen to our Chuck E.
Cheese episode if you want to know what that's all about.
I've used this joke, I think, before in the show,
but it's the scene in Vertigo where Jimmy Stewart is remaking.
Oh, is it Kim Novak?
Yeah, yeah.
It's remaking her to look like
the original woman he fell in love with.
No, it's a you got to wear the Helen hair the right way.
The dress is fitting all wrong.
We have to go get it hemmed.
Oh, there you are.
There's the Helen I know.
I fashioned a beak out of some old cups.
No, it's not right. It's not right.
I want to hear you say buck bucka.
God, I'm like a week or two away from this actually happening.
The way that quarantine is going.
Lindsay, get out, get out, get out now.
I texture.
You guys keep riffing about something.
I'm like, there is some very distressing information.
Oh, it's not coming out until Friday, but I'm giving you a head start.
He's joking, but we're not sure he's joking.
And then his eyes looked on the zoom.
She leaves and then you drive by in like a couple of months
and it's just like Helen's in the window and it's me dressed as Helen.
Coming mother.
Hi, Scott.
Hello, Scott. It's Helen.
You're making Edwin wear the little bowler hat.
Chuck's red bowler hat.
When's he introduced me, Chuck?
I want to do my song.
One of the guys.
What are they going?
Oh, wow.
Here you want to you want to do a little fake break
that might even have nothing in between it.
But when we come back, we'll answer some of your questions,
which hopefully won't lead us to some of the creepy areas
like replacing your girlfriend with an animatronic with an animatronic chicken
and replacing Jason with a VR demon.
It's all right.
We all have a little shucky day sometimes.
OK, we'll be right back.
Welcome back to the show.
Once again, it's time to open up the PTR mailbag.
Post offices are very branding that we always remember.
Our branding, we always remember.
It's like souvenirs.
I had to think about what souvenir Smackdown was like every time.
Anytime I go like, yeah, I got this.
I'll roll this back in.
I always stub my toe very hard.
And we always don't let it go.
We always attack.
You always the blood is in the water.
Oh, and we love it.
It's I'm only it's usually fine.
It's usually all in good fun.
But now I'm scared Nick Ademus will crave will smell that blood.
His favorite beverage.
It's your last chance.
I do. I can bump it back in.
No problem. All right.
I know the names of all the segments like Jay Leno hiding in the closet.
OK.
This email comes to us from Taylor.
I'm going to mangle your last name, Basabe Basabe.
What's the one thing you want to get the most from downtown
Disney when it opens and Disney or DCA, Merch, Feud, Merch, Food, etc.
What do you guys think?
Does anyone have that?
That covers downtown Disney or the parks just in general.
Yeah, I think it's an and or the parks.
Anything come quickly to mind?
Either you guys talked about with Mitch Ronto rap pops right into my head.
Yeah, I just I just want to walk around with that plastic glass of wine.
So bad. I want that more than Cartier because Cartier's inside.
And I and you actually can't.
You know, I've been making Cartier, Manhattan's once in a while.
And you know, not the same atmosphere, but like,
I just want to like walk that plastic cup of wine over the Ferris wheel
and look at it.
That will be the first thing that I do and maybe just that and then go home.
I do like I of course talked about my my sprinkles cone,
my sprinkle waffle cone with two scoops of ice cream.
I think they'll hand it to me and I will just burst into tears when it happens.
I'm pretty sure just like, oh, my God, thank God.
I didn't know if it would happen again.
So I think probably the old standard stuff I really like to begin with,
I don't think there's unless there's, you know, whenever I decide to go back,
unless there's some sort of new merch thing that I'm excited about,
I think it's probably treats.
Jason, I'm imagining I think I'm going to go a little out of left field
and like, say, like trying something I had never gotten around to, like
and maybe something that I can't easily make it home,
like go to Katal and finally get some suckling pig paella.
Whoa, that's out of nowhere.
Well, I mean, because I'm not really doing fine dining right now.
I mean, lots of nice restaurants doing takeout, but like it is a little,
you know, warmer wilted when you get home.
I'm also very excited to see Disney Springs in Florida.
He's getting this place, Gideon's Bakehouse,
which apparently makes amazing cookies.
I've never had them.
But a cookie based establishment in Disney Springs only just adds to the appeal.
Interesting. So Scott's answer, wine, my answer, a big ice cream.
And yours is suckling pig.
OK, got it. Those those staples of theme parks. Sure.
A nice glass of wine, an ice cream cone and suckling pig.
OK, well, hey, we have to look forward to something to each their own.
Yeah. Mike, you got one.
I have one.
Hold on. I've lost it.
All right. Rubin at CubicsRube3 on Twitter asks,
do you think we will ever get an original IP Disney right again?
I think the answer is no.
It's over, baby.
Yeah, especially with sort of like risk assessment
and in full swing way after a financial blow.
Yeah, I know. I'll take it back.
I will say if and when there's ever a new park built,
I think we'll get maybe one original IP run.
But I think that's truly what's going to have to happen.
I think we'll have to get a full new park,
which I don't think there's a new park being built for a decade at this point,
as far as Disney's concerned.
So the answer is no for a decade, at least.
Does that like fucking spirit or whatever
that's going to be in Spaceship Earth count as original IP?
Oh, they've already cut that from the schedule.
Oh, that's gone. Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, yeah, that one's not too necessary.
I just keep Spaceship Earth and its claustrophobic, bumpy, clunky glory.
Weird video screens.
Yeah. Yeah. Oh, yes.
Very, very out of date animation with your head.
With your like, what's the what was the flash animation thing
where you would like put your head on it and send it as a greeting card
that people use to jib jab?
Yes. So extremely jib jabby. Yeah.
So, yeah, Spaceship Earth, it's jib jab technology.
They're still going strong, baby. Jib jab still around.
In parent world. Yeah.
They're probably thriving right now.
Wow. Patreon about jib jab.
I guess. Yeah.
Can I ask the question that if anyone just feel free to email or will I?
Because I this I've I've added up how little original Epcot
that we've done in Spaceship Earth to be a fun one.
But I'm just curious, like, what is what the listener wants to hear?
What are you like?
What can you not wait for us to do in terms of like big Epcot?
Because I'm like taking stock of everything.
I'm shocked at how little we've never done living seas,
never done Journey into Imagination, I've done Horizons, I've done World of Motion.
So Spaceship Earth.
So, I don't know, let us let us know that one.
I'm turning the post office back on you.
Oh, wow. Reverse post office.
But now you're going to have to comb through all the people go in like,
I don't wear a mascot to find like the nice things go in like
to World of Motion, please.
I like the overturned cart.
Well, they don't get a vote.
That's what you rescind the vote with your mask thing.
I have a question that this won't take long because I don't have much to say.
And in fact, the user or the Twitter really says it all themselves from Theme Park ASMR.
Have any of you seen the film Characters with a Z by Hard Rock Park creator John Binkowski?
If you think back to our if you if you heard our failed parks episode with Jason
Waller, John Binkowski, one of the true tours of the park,
world that you can credit him with this Hard Rock Cafe theme park.
And he yeah, we discovered a little while ago that he also made a made a film,
made a feature film.
You can watch the trailer on YouTube.
Let me let the park ASMR continue.
OK, so can we have your thoughts on it about it?
It's about a guy who wants to be a ride designer working in a theme park
and features an appearance by a member of the Moody Blues and it's filmed in Kissimmee.
I have no more to say to that.
I haven't seen the movie.
You said it all.
And I don't know.
I have no good answer for why we haven't seen it because amazing details.
Huh?
It has to be.
I mean, there's still stuff we've been teasing forever.
We've been teasing Lance Burton's movie, Billy Toppett forever.
We haven't done it.
But characters we are aware of and we have not seen it yet.
And of course, that's got it's a must watch.
We're going to watch it.
A great reason to have our friend, Jason Waller back.
You know.
Oh, yes.
Well, I think it's a must watch.
You know.
No, yes.
Well, himself a great director, so he can sort of come at it from the directorial standpoint.
Maybe no jokes on that episode and it's just sort of a critical analysis of film.
Sounds good to me.
Like a French Cahier du Cinema.
I like that pronunciation.
How is it pronounced?
I have no idea.
Cahier du Cinema.
I only ever have seen it written.
I've never heard it spoken.
Uh, yeah, I'm sorry.
I'm like that.
I'm sorry.
This film was filmed and I'm seeing it being filmed in Celebration, Florida, even better.
Disney, which was once owned by the Disney Corporation.
It also says the main character in the movie is a big fan of the Moody Blues.
And as such, the film sees several of their songs.
If you don't recall, there is the Hard Rock Park that this guy built had a Moody Blues ride.
So his partnership with the Moody Blues extended.
Oh, wait.
And we didn't talk.
We text about this and never said it on the show.
There's a bunch of different mascot characters with Z in this movie.
And one of them is a punk bulldog.
He's a holdover from Hard Rock Park.
And is it the is it Winston the punk rock dog?
This guy's described as just the punk bulldog, I think.
I bet it's the same.
I bet it's Winston.
I think it's probably exactly the same.
Yeah.
So we're sorry to let you down.
Thank you for jogging our memory and we will fix this error of not having seen this film forthwith.
We will.
We will get right to it.
Jason, do you have anything?
No, not yet.
OK, I have one.
It's from Ben Stryker at Stryker No Strikit.
I don't know why I have to name that, but it's been Stryker.
Hey, thanks for the question.
On Twitter, he says, if you could do a mashup of two different rides, what ride would you make?
An example is Haunted Mansion and Space Mountain into Haunted Mountain,
which I think is a fun idea.
I think we've talked before about just putting different ride cars on the different tracks.
Yeah.
For another ride.
But a true mashup is an interesting question.
If teacups spun around the deck of the Mark Twain, that'd be pretty cool.
The Mad T Twain.
The Mad T Twain is good.
I would like, let's see here, like aesthetically, vibe wise,
Space Mountain is so great and such a cool ride.
But, you know, maybe the cars don't move as much as we'd want them to.
So maybe you attach, and this is kind of technology I think is coming.
Maybe you attach the Harry Potter Kuka arm to the Space Mountain track
and then put a bunch of like space death eaters.
I'm realizing I'm bringing up Harry Potter now,
as Harry Potter, as far as I'm concerned, was created out of thin air.
It's just a thing that existed.
Yeah, it's been around for generations.
Not sure who did it.
It's like a Shakespeare, with Shakespeare, a bunch of people.
It's who remembers even.
Just don't even know.
Yeah, you put the Kuka arm and then you put like
death eaters hanging from, you know, around the Space Mountain track
and you should see them pop up.
And then you can sort of like the creepier aspects.
I guess you could put the Weeping Willow also on Space Mountain.
And now you have a ride that's like completely crazy.
The arm is flipping around and now you get to see a little show scenes as you whiz by.
And of course, this is called
Forbidden Mountain.
Space Journey isn't anywhere.
Forbidden Space.
Space.
OK, we'll get this.
Forbidden Mountain, I guess, is kind of cool.
Yeah, that's pretty cool.
Yeah, I dig that one.
So I think that's fun.
Jason, what do you got?
OK, I think I'm going to go real in my wheelhouse.
I'm going to combine the train and the sourdough bakery bread tour.
And it's a bread train.
It's a red.
It's a train you get on and it takes you through the bakery
and the bakers wave at you and you're handed little pieces of bread to enjoy on the train.
Wow, delightful.
A pretty cut and dry bread train.
There's a clip that's been going around, Scott.
I don't know if you've seen of a movie called Money Plane.
With Kelsey Grammer.
Yeah, I saw that clip.
Kelsey Grammer and WWE superstar Edge.
And it's the bread train reminds me of Money Plane.
Jason would be the Kelsey Grammer in that movie.
That's the bread train.
Now we're on the bread train, baby.
Yeah.
So sourdough loaves, sourdough croissants, sourdough
puddings, any kind of bread you want, you can get it on the bread train.
But at a price.
That's a whole your soul.
That's a whole IP.
That's a whole franchise for Disney.
This isn't why I don't have the answer, but this makes me think we should have an answer.
Melissa, add lemon honey XS.
Where can we send you physical treats?
Not food, of course.
Thank you.
That's awful.
I stitched this for you guys and would love to have a PO box or forever dog office.
I could send it to and this person stitched us a little stitching.
I don't know what you call it, what you stitch, but it's us in shirts that I very much recognize.
It's so clearly a shirt that I have and you guys have.
And then a little ghost.
They make the sector keeper green, which is an adorable color, an old purple hat.
And it says boys, boys.
And it's just great.
We all got nice, cute smiles.
This is the most adorable things I've ever seen.
So that's a good idea.
We should figure that out.
Is there a dog?
We've done this before.
There is.
I don't have a close by, but I'll make a note to send it to this person.
There is a forever dog office.
I'm assuming someone's getting the mail.
Very nice face.
Only I have been to because two weeks later, everything shut down.
That's right.
I'm also going to put out a call.
Someone made a replica of the Hormel sign, the Hormel glass side,
from a very, very early episode that I found on eBay.
What was it?
I think from Main Street.
Is it a stained glass thing?
Yes.
It's one of our listeners who has made stained glass.
Is a stained glass enthusiast, I believe, has made some stained glass based items based on
show stuff that he sold for charity.
Can you email the show account and I will give you the address
because I do want that stained glass.
All right.
Well, we'll figure that out and respond.
But thank you for doing that.
Anybody who draws a thing.
I think I get a little greedy sometimes by just calling out like I'm a king for fan art.
Create for me.
Create for us.
But thanks, Danny.
That's that is very nice.
Yeah, boy.
Yeah, very sweet.
And we very much appreciate it.
I don't want to we can run Robin it certainly, but I want to call out one while I have in
front of me because like the stitching and as a picture, this from Nick Hoffman,
Hoffbeast Efteling recently added a mechanism where fries are delivered to customers by a slide
to allow social distancing.
What whimsical additions to theme parks can you think of to brighten a pandemic day at the park?
I don't know if you guys have this photo in front of you.
Let's talk about this first.
So it's a nice little wagon.
And then, yes, this wooden ramp that's kind of charmingly just what a really handy dad would do
and fries slide down it.
And then it's there's plenty of plexiglass.
And I mean, this is this is wonderful.
I'm like distracted enough by this where I don't have my own idea at the moment.
It's great, though.
Good for you, Efteling.
OK, here's my pitch.
Every single cast member is in those Avatar mech suits.
Yeah.
And that goes if it's Haunted Mansion, they're in a big mech suit, but then they have like the outfit,
the Haunted Mansion outfit, like stretched over the big mech suit.
Massive.
Size XXXXXXXXXL.
Right. It's that great retro space mountain uniform stretched over a mech suit.
Wow.
That keeps the distance a little higher up.
That keeps some distance.
And then they can also if they have to take something from a guest
or whatever, they have their robot arms to do it.
Geez.
Huh.
What could you I'm trying to think of like I mean, a character still can't hug you even with giant arms,
but I'm certainly flashing to well, if you gave they prove that it was
they were disposable each and every time.
What I'm getting at is many gloved characters and a lot of them are Mickey and Minnie.
You know, since character, you know, they still come out and wave to us.
And that's nice.
But a kid wants a hug from Mickey Mouse or an adult wants a hug from Mickey Mouse.
So I think big six foot long pipe cleaner arms on the characters
and mixed with that, they have sort of an endless stock of disposable Mickey hands
that they kind of with their big with their long arms, like pop those hands on in sort of a Lego
change out manner.
You line up and get a hug from like a bit, which this already, you know, kind of a freak of nature,
giant arms.
Mickey Mouse is cool in and of itself, but this sounds safe and also bizarre and surreal.
So I want to see some extremely long Mickey arms.
I am picturing how they would do arms for the sketch on Saturday Night Live, ToonSys the Cat,
where the cat would be there.
And then the arms would just be these long things similar to how
Triumph holds a microphone on Conan O'Brien.
Yes, very much so.
Long, odd looking straight things that you would tape whatever you're holding to it.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, autographs might get tough in this world.
Now, autographs might have to go away.
We can't have it all.
But I think you could get some hugs, you know, albeit kind of sloppily achieved ones.
Well, you know, what did you say?
Maybe I've missed this.
Maybe the person who gets the hug gets to keep the arms.
Oh, sure.
So or just or hands, you know, because the arms are tough to sort of slide in and out.
But if you're just popping those little white hands on, so you get a hug and then you and
then you keep those and you can fill them up with popcorn.
Hug.
OK, OK.
Hugs change.
Here's my pitch.
Hugs change from like a full hug where, you know, you wrap your arms around the person
to what the what Jack Nicholson Joker does to Bob in Batman, where he just kind of grabs his shoulders.
You know what I'm saying?
Where he goes, you're my number one guy.
He just kind of grabs you by the shoulders and that's it turns into that.
So all the characters grab you sort of by the shoulders to show affection.
And then the hands leave their body and get stuck to your arms.
So you take the hands with you.
And that's now a souvenir is that you have like Mickey's hands or Pooh's hands.
And then, yes, you won't have to share a touch with another person because the hands leave
with the guest.
Wow.
It's cool.
Safe.
Get a souvenir.
There's something more meaningful than an autograph.
I really love it.
Did everyone know exactly what I meant when I said what Jack Nicholson does to Bob?
I didn't know, but it's a nice scene to hear about.
Yeah.
It looms large.
I made a joke that any time, especially I'm feeling depressed during quarantine,
I basically just come downstairs and want to watch one of the four Batman movies.
The original four.
Yeah.
So I'm just like, I'm like Batman forever again.
OK.
I would watch it like three times a week if I wasn't living with someone.
So what you're saying is that HBO Max is essentially the bartender from The Shining
and you are Jack Nicholson playing Jack Torrance from The Shining.
Yes.
100.
Yes, completely.
Another.
Yeah.
Let's see if the barkeep is like, are you going to watch Batman and Robin again?
The usual.
No, you would just say the usual.
Slides Batman and Robin across the bar to me.
Allow me to break the ice.
Oh, it's just the greatest movies of all time, all four equally good.
What else we got?
Maybe we start winding down.
I just have a silly one.
What's the what's the most obscure?
This is from Brendan Wadlow.
Where's Wadlow 21?
What's the most obscure Marvel character you want to ride based on?
Not a realistic one, just your dream ride.
I immediately think of Dazzler.
Scott, are you familiar with Dazzler?
No.
Dazzler was sort of like and they've changed sort of what she does, but she's like sort of a disco
roller skating pop star from another dimension or another planet.
And it's very Xanadu.
It's Xanadu all the way.
Oh, here we go.
All right.
And yeah, I assume you're seeing classic, classic Dazzler.
I think we've talked a little bit about this before.
There was like a pitch.
Was it Jim's shooter, Jason, who had a pitch for a movie?
Yeah, I believe so.
Kiss was in it and it was an insane like 70s, I think cocaine or acid trip type situation.
And I would love some sort of a disco Dazzler ride or at least even like
rollers like just a just a skating ring, obviously, where people could go roller skating
and listen to like disco and then they would have you could have like a monster attack once in a while.
I think that's good.
I want to piggyback off that and go for another even more obscure Marvel Comics entertainer.
Lila Cheney, the teleporting intergalactic rock star.
She is a rock star.
She is a very popular musician in the Marvel continuity in the comics.
It doesn't show up that often, but her whole thing is that like she can teleport like large
numbers of people.
So I think that would be a good a some sort of show where they use that sort of scrim
technology like at Knott's Berry Farm where you're going down a hospital hallway and
lightning flashes and then you're in hell.
Like you could transport like so you're at a concert venue and then she teleports everyone
onto a space station and continues the show.
Great.
That'd be great.
You could do a double bill with Dazzler and.
Oh, sure.
Yeah.
I'm kind of a music zone.
I'm no Marvel expert, but if you're talking obscure, I would love to see a live rocktacular
based on specifically the David Hasselhoff portrayal of Nick Fury, Agent of Shield.
Of course, we all remember that, you know, it was this role was originally played by
Hasselhoff in 1998 in a TV movie, him in an eye patch and, you know,
Only popular portrayals with Apple and Samuel L Jackson.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think they they land about even.
So it's time to give Hasselhoff Fury his his do the only one.
The only thing that pops into my head is because I'm furious and, you know, just the
super enunciated Hasselhoff style of singing, I think would be a blast.
Obviously, he wouldn't do it, but he'd supervise and pick, you know, a cast of six foot six men
to sing in the most enunciate of manner ever.
He should have his own, not his own X-Men, but his own six foot six men,
his own super team of tall men.
All right.
This was we could do like a rock and roller coaster where you're trying to get to a
triple bill concert of these three characters, you know, of list them off again.
Nick Nick Fury, not Fury as a lot.
Fury Lila Cheney and Dazzler.
Yeah, so it sounds good.
That's a dream, honestly.
Yeah.
And then, yeah, let have it have the actual one of the big complaints we have with rock
and roller coaster is that you don't actually see Aerosmith.
You don't see robots at the end of the ride.
You see a little screen at the end of the ride.
Let's have robots doing the concert.
Oh, sure.
And then you kind of round a corner and see the audience and they all boo.
They don't care for it.
Well, we really shouldn't rush to get here.
This show sucks.
And yeah, you leave feeling sad.
Anything else you're having up?
I think, yeah, I don't know.
I don't have that was the last one I had I had noticed.
Well, on a hard rock and note, you survived podcast ride part post office edition.
Thanks for your questions.
You can always send us stuff at the email at podcast, read a Gmail dot com.
You can interact with us at Facebook, Instagram and Twitter to address one that got a lot of likes.
How big did Scott's head when he went viral?
Obviously, extremely, extremely big.
Very important crucial moment in my life.
I think the biggest thing that happened to me in 2020 was that I had a viral tweet.
I can think of no other no bigger changes in my life.
I'm coming up empty, too.
I can't think of anything.
It's my pride and joy.
And sometimes I late at night just stare at that tweet and the amount of likes and just think how lucky I am.
I did a tweet about shooting for the July thing and a bunch of weird, you know,
Chrissy Teigen retweeted and stuff.
It was very bizarre.
And obviously, I'm in I've ascended to another plane of humanity and you can look at that on on Twitter.
But but also I just in the plugs list, I also just want to say I got to be part of a very
wonderful story this week.
It's a story called Is Anyone Watching Quibi?
And that was on in New York magazine by Benjamin Wallace.
It's I legitimately feel very, very lucky because I'm the first thing in the article,
which an article that then contains the best quibi anecdotes of any quibi hit pieces,
which is saying a lot because there's been like 50 of these.
And while I'm proud of my own participation, I'm really just I'm just a pre show.
To the wild roller coaster that is the rest of the squibby article, please, please go.
Just put that in the plugs list.
Please read.
Is anyone watching Quibi?
Oh, yeah.
If you love the old Eisner anecdotes, you'll love some of the anecdotes about what one of
person on his what I'm assuming is a mutual enemies list is up to today.
I guess I hadn't put together really that I am I am I have this outlet where I'm so actively
pro Eisner and then I've gone out of my way to be anti Katzenberg.
I mean, if that doesn't help butter up Eisner to be on the show, I don't know what else will.
Well, please.
We may need to do a big groundswell at a certain point.
Now is not the time.
But if he reads that article, maybe maybe that'll be it.
Who's this young buck getting into the getting into the game of slinging mud at Katzenberg?
It reminds me of a young me.
I wonder if he has a podcast.
You know, with no questions asked, I will just go on it without listening to anything else.
That's how I think it'll play out.
How long is an average episode?
Two and a two and a half hours.
Whatever they need.
I like this.
I got a feeling about this.
Scott Gardner.
Hey, and speaking of long episodes, you know, we let me just also as always,
plug the second gate, patreon.com slash podcast, the ride.
And we've we let's just say we have three of these in the can that I think fucking rule.
I think we've got really good ones.
And that's always true.
But just especially you guys knowing what we've done recently,
extra employer people go check out the second gate.
We could tease.
We could do a little quick tease.
It's a there's an episode coming up about a villain that we really enjoy.
Let's say that not Jeffrey Cassidy.
Not Mr. Katz.
So, yeah, that's on soon.
So get ready for it.
Awesome.
Well, that'll do it.
Fun stuff.
And look at the calendar of what day it is next next Friday.
And I might give you a hint what we're doing next week.
Every special episode that should be fun.
So stay tuned and thanks for listening, everybody.
Bye bye.
Bye.
This has been a forever dog production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Bohm, Joe
Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.