ществ
Tally ho and welcome to a podcast.
The ride's European vacation hosted by three guys who are excited to learn
there's a whole country that's like the Austin Powers bar in Glendale.
I'm Scott Gardner joined by Mike Carlson.
What?
Imagine the bar, a whole country of the bar.
Okay.
There's this really nice bar in Glendale that's themed to the film
Austin Powers that I love.
And I'm surprised to learn that the location from that movie is actually
a real place in real life.
I can visit.
It's a, it is a real and it is just as swinging.
Wow.
Cause that Glendale Austin Powers bar is so swinging and not shady at all.
It's definitely, it's, it's very not shady, very not sticky.
It's a fine establishment that I'm sure will survive the pandemic.
Jason Sheridan, can you believe this?
Uh, I just can't imagine a whole country that's as cool as that Austin Powers bar.
Have you been to the Austin Powers bar, Jason?
You know, I actually haven't.
Okay.
I don't know why you didn't go.
I think I invited you.
I went with Anthony Geo and a, uh, biz, biz friend to one night.
No, several.
Yeah.
I think he's a frequenter.
Um, and it's all day.
It's all, um, black light.
Is that right?
Or like,
you might call it that.
I don't know if it's like a cheaper version of black light, maybe.
Like Austin Powers liked.
Uh, he liked to be in a, in a haunted house all the time.
Like, uh, yeah, like a velvet Led Zeppelin paint, you know, poster.
Any, if you make it out to Glendale and the pandemic is over and the
Austin Powers bar is still there, just take a look at it, but don't stay long.
Yeah.
It might be, it might've been going this entire time, by the way, they might've
never closed seems very possible.
If any bar was, was to knock,
you would just go up to the door, knock and say, do I make you horny baby?
And they'd let you in.
If you had a secret word,
they know the obscure code.
Very obscure.
Um, we, we actually, we are talking about a, uh, a, a British themed
environment that is, uh, uh, a lot more, uh, ornate and well done.
If you can imagine then the Austin, then the Austin Powers bar, I think so.
We'll decide as we go.
Um, the, uh, the second stop on pie guest rides, European vacation, or I guess the
third, if you, you know, head to the second gate to check out the day trips.
We just went to the Popeye village and Malta and had a good time.
Uh, but we're talking today about a place, uh, that is a Southwest of London.
It's a place called Chessington world of adventures.
I had never heard of this park.
I don't know if you guys had before.
No.
But I'm glad I have now and we were made aware of it by our guests today.
Let's bring him in.
He is a staff writer for the Atlantic and along with PCR legend Griffin Newman.
He hosts the excellent podcast, blank check.
David Sims is with us.
Hi guys.
I just want to say something about this Austin powers bar that I didn't know
existed until you were talking.
Oh really?
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
It's called the electric pussy cat.
And I'm seeing here.
Yes.
Um, that's correct.
You know, so I just Googled while you were talking just to see like, all right,
what are they, you know, how, how Austin powers are we talking to things?
One, obviously Britain, just like this place, just in general, the whole vibe.
Mostly black lights, black lights, union Jack's everywhere.
But you know, velvet and velour and like squiggly lines.
You know how like Austin powers, it's all like, you know, they love like zigzags.
Oh yeah.
It's a real zigzaggy country and a lot of double decker buses, uh, both
inside and outside, right.
Two, uh, for my podcast, we recently ish.
I mean, like six months ago now, uh, went to something called trolls, the experience
that was like a sort of a themed interactive, uh, whatever inside park, like
themed experience.
Sure.
Pop up an activation inactivate.
Yeah.
They, they sure.
They'll take a heck out of, you know, an empty office in midtown.
And it had the basic, it didn't have the same like items, but the same visual
aesthetic as this basically, like a lot of purple and pink, you know what I mean?
Um, and like in the dark, does that kind of maybe get you around, um, you know,
having to do a very complicated themed environment, right?
If it's mostly in the dark with just some splashes of color.
Right.
So, you know, right, you know, you can, you can like, that's, that's.
Cutting you a lot of corners, right?
Yes, absolutely.
It seems like it.
Yeah.
Um, I don't know about this trolls thing.
Where, uh, what else can you tell us about that?
Uh, it's basically like, you know, it's the, it's, it's centered on the movie
trolls, so there's a lot of like lore and characters from those movies.
If you haven't seen them.
So if you go in and expect in like the toy trolls, you're out of luck, but they
like do your hair and you have to like, I don't know, you make a, like a mix tape
and you gather up some, you know, glitter and you have a dance party.
It's all very fun.
And when we did it, it was three grown men and they very clearly like.
Made sure we were alone.
Like they were like, you're not going in with a group of kids.
Like you guys are going to have to deal with this by yourself.
We're going to sort of like hermetically have you have the, it was very,
everyone was very professional.
You can listen to our episode about it.
It was a very, they did the best they could with three, 30 something guys being
like, uh, Hey, we're here for trolls.
The experience we hit a Patreon goal.
So we have to do this.
Like they were, they were all very.
Well, they do your hair.
They do.
You have to pay extra if you want a physical wig.
Otherwise you get a paper hat essentially in the shape of.
Okay.
Yes.
And did you not pay for the way we did not pay for the way, but I did get a lot
of glitter on my face.
I don't know.
You know, I, I, I did as much as I physically could.
You got wrapped up in the spirit.
Uh, you, I'm sure we're singing the timber lake song.
Yeah.
Pop me and, uh, branch.
I believe those are the names of the, the lead characters in trolls was
hanging out with them.
Did the trolls fart glitter?
Uh, they didn't in front of us because mostly it was just a bunch of like eager
20 something you imagine like Broadway, you know, aspiring Broadway actor types
like leading us around, but I have seen both of those movies and they do fart
glitter, right?
Okay.
They saved that up that they had that effect in universal studios.
I think Florida.
Oh, that's impressive.
So they must not know they didn't roll it out, I guess, to the, uh, startup
experience, whatever that experience was.
Yes.
Um, this, you know, it's going to be exciting for, we'll, we'll all know the
mythology very well when trolls world tour wins best picture at the front
of the movie lists Academy awards.
It's at the highest grossing like of the year with an asterix or is it Sonic?
I, oh yeah.
No, no, no.
Sonic's Sonic's doing good.
Right.
Sonic still has, he had those solid three pre COVID months like to, to all
do so Sonic was this year.
Yeah.
Jesus.
Sonic was this year.
Valentine's day surprise.
Yeah.
Sonic and, uh, do little, do little is this year.
Little is going to be nominated for best picture at least little.
It's not going to win because maybe there was some problems with it, but it'll be
in the top 10 at five over 10.
Right.
There's some politics.
So yeah, maybe, maybe it'll, it's too polarizing to win, but it'll, it'll get
a good chunk of nominations.
There's, there's animal, uh, ass play in both troll and troll.
I guess trolls aren't animals.
I guess they're create magical creatures.
I apologize to the trolls.
Wait, you can see.
So farting glitter is ass play and reaching up into a dragon's
asshole to get, what was it again?
I think it was
bag.
Yeah.
Bagpipes.
Oh yes.
Bagpipes were the button.
That was the funny punchline after pulling out like multiple suits of armor.
Seat.
I should have said seat play.
I apologize to all the,
Oh, well yes.
Yeah.
We call butts seats.
So we have to call them seat holes.
Uh, it reached into a seat hole.
COVID has made me a dear, uh, filthier in my language and I apologize.
Well, that's the old, as part of this European vacation, we're getting, uh,
we're getting a lot raunchier.
We're getting a looser European attitude.
I'm going through character development now and I'm becoming a little bit less,
uh, uptight when it comes to certain material.
What?
Less of a brood.
I see.
Yes.
My awakening.
It's my awakening with language and with sexuality.
So apologies, David, if it's, uh, we aren't, you know, it's the most proper
hosts support you on all your journeys.
Thank you.
Well,
you're skeptical.
You're imagining journeys that we shouldn't be supported.
We want to encourage them too much.
We want to encourage them, but we don't want to push them too far.
Um, okay.
Well, before we get into the park, uh, today, we're, we're, we're talking about
this, this partially because, you know, I, uh, David, I listened to blank check
and there's a, there's a fact that comes up, uh, pretty sparingly.
It's, it's always handled very tastefully if it comes up, which is rarely.
Uh, and that is the kind of obscure facts that you actually grew up in Britain.
I did.
Yes.
Of course, anytime it comes up, everyone's very charmed and very delighted to hear
it.
And everyone's really nice to me about it.
Uh, everyone lets it pass in a very, very sweet way.
Griffin couldn't be cooler.
Um, but yes, I did.
I did move to England at the age of nine and I lived there till I was 22, um, in
London, in North London.
So yes, I spent all of my adolescence there and certainly I've never been to,
uh, you know, Disneyland, Disney world, like the, the, the, the King American
theme parks, cause we just weren't here, you know, and like, you know, but I have
been to Britain's excuses for theme parks, some of which are very, I shouldn't,
I shouldn't, I shouldn't be too mean, but, uh, it's a little,
I was going to ask, you know, you brought this, this main topic to us, but I, but I
was curious any, any, since we haven't really done a lot of, uh, London or
England, or if, you know, knowing that, um, uh, the three of us all really enjoy,
uh, stupid and named themed experiences, um, were we to, uh, go to London or
anywhere else in England, is there anything, anything else you would recommend in
the world of the, you know, the dumbest themed entertainment possible?
This is the problem.
Cause like, I feel like you got, you know, like Alton towers, which maybe you've,
uh, dug up in your research.
I'm not sure, you know, that's kind of like the King park in England of like,
you know, it's got great rides.
Like they're, you know, that, that's sort of, if you're a Briton and you want to go
on like, you know, hair raising roller coasters, that's where you're going to go.
And then Thorpe park is kind of number two.
Chessington is a solid third, like very much not challenging, but I don't think
I'm so glad that's our choice for the third best part, right?
Third best park, same parent company.
Yeah, yes, exactly.
Three.
And honestly, if you're throwing Lego land in there, like Chessington might not be
able to match Lego land, like, which is another, you know, but like I don't like
same parent company on that too.
I don't, it's a monopoly.
Yeah.
Really?
See now, now you're, you guys know more than me.
I did, I did know that there was this, this one parent company controlling so
many of these places, but there's not like a lot of places that have the sort of
extensive really thought through theming, right?
Like the worlds with like characters and like all that stuff in Britain at all.
I think, like, I can't think of the best place to go for, for that.
I can, you know, I think your, your option would probably be Disneyland
Paris or Euro Disney, whatever, whatever it's branded as now.
Oh, sure.
Yeah.
Which is pretty fairly close.
Like that's, and like, that was a spot where when I was a kid, I think my
parents were like, well, maybe we could go there, but it had such a bad reputation
in the nineties is kind of like that the launch had sort of flopped and you know,
they weren't really figuring, I feel like maybe it has a better rep now.
I don't, I don't think it didn't.
When I was a kid,
I've made my mixed opinions known on the podcast.
I, there's some wonderful things there and I think it was designed with the best
intent, but man, there is, there is some trash.
There is some big time trash around that place.
It was on the way up before the world shut down.
Really?
It was getting some new stuff.
Yeah.
I believe they finally closed the Armageddon themed experience.
The there was a little, there's a corner of the park that's Armageddon and Aerosmith,
which in Aerosmith did the song for Armageddon.
So it's really Aerosmith alley.
And Armageddon obliterates the city of Paris in a scene that has nothing to do
with anything else, like essentially a visual effects demonstration.
They're like, oh, let's check in with Howesworth doing.
And you just see Paris getting nuked with a meteor.
Is that right?
And then you don't see any like human fallout?
No, no, no, no, no.
It even brings up like, by the way, millions dead from that.
Like everyone's just like, we did it.
We blew up the asteroid and everyone's like waving American flags.
And like it's that it's funny that in Paris they were like, let's, let's,
let's highlight this.
Like, let's bring this up.
It's cold, callous destruction of our entire city.
That's kind of true in a lot of disaster movies, I guess.
That you just you see maybe Stoke cities that we care about
because it's in America or something.
But then they'll just toss off like Mumbai is gone
and everybody just looks down for a second and that's it.
That happened in Independence Day with Chicago.
I think they say Chicago has been destroyed, but you never get to see anything.
Right. So when I was a little young, not that little, but I was watching
and I was like Chicago destroyed.
We don't even get to see it.
We don't even get to enjoy Wrigley Field being blown up.
What a bummer.
Yeah, you're left out of the hum.
And Jason, you got a certain brand.
I just I just watched the scene.
I just cute it up on YouTube and watch it's 30 seconds long.
That's that's that's what Paris gets.
Paris just getting blown up.
You know, Chicago, I think, doesn't get anything.
I vaguely remember.
Yeah, you don't. Yeah, you don't see anything.
You don't get any grad. Yeah, it's just like, yeah, all those
all those cities are gone.
We don't have the budget off screen.
Rope them off.
All right. OK, let's get on with this.
Like a soap opera character.
Yeah, I'm sorry. They had to go.
But so, OK, so you so you're implying that,
you know, the theme theme parks are different.
Themed entertainment is different and perhaps like maybe a little
a little lesser than in in England.
I mean, I don't want to be too rude because I'm not an expert.
And I haven't been to Alton Towers or Thorpe Park since I was a little kid.
And like, you know, I'm sure they had, you know, with Alton Towers is on
like a big old there's like a big old castle there that they bought.
Like, so I think that's really nice.
You know, like I think there's lots of there's nice things.
But I always think of those places and they would advertise constantly on TV
when I was a kid because I'm a kid.
I'm watching kids shows. They're advertising roller coasters to me.
It was always about like we got we just got the the gnarliest new ride.
Like, you won't believe how intense this thing is.
Like, that's what they were always leading with, not like come to a magical universe.
And it's fun for the whole family.
It was like, we're going to you're going to die.
You're going to it's going to be awful.
You're you'll be so upset after you do this.
And the kids are like, I got to ride Nemesis.
Like, I got to ride this this insane thing that's going to warp my brain.
Well, David, since you bring that up, I feel like I should let you know,
since you are a film writer, Alton Towers in the last couple of years
introduced a roller coaster based on the Wicker Man.
Wow. That goes through the Wicker Man.
All right. I'm into that. That's kind of fun. Yeah.
That's cool. By the way, that's cool.
I'm assuming it's a wooden coaster, right?
I would assume. Yeah, it's a wooden coaster that goes through the big wooden guy.
I think generic. I don't think it's cage.
I don't I don't know that you get a lot of Nick Cage.
Right. I think you just get like smoke effects.
They don't like throw toast at you.
I'm trying to think of like the bees.
No bees. No bees. Right.
Yeah. Yeah. No writhing beeheaded animatronic.
No, he's not like punching women like like throughout.
Oh, that's right. Is there a I don't I haven't watched this montage of insane parts
of that movie in a while, but does he is he in a bear costume and punches a woman?
Well, because it's a Neil LaBeouc movie.
Neil LaBeouc, a famously chill dude. Yes.
And he is like his like revamp of the original movie is like this is like a female only colony.
And that's why they're like be obsessed.
They are they're they're farming honey or whatever.
But it's all women.
And so when Cage has to like start trying to fight his way out, he's just like throwing
women against the wall and punching people.
And he's wearing a bear suit for some reason.
So it's not he's not targeting women.
No, what can he do around a bunch?
Neil LaBeouc doesn't have any problems with women.
And if you look throughout all his work,
he'll definitely not see anything like that that would alarm you.
I have the Wicker Man now as my background.
I just want the Wicker Man coaster if you can see it looks and it looks cool.
No, it's got Google.
It is cool as shit.
It is so cool looking.
It's like a weird they made this crazy wooden Wicker Man in the middle of a wooden coaster.
And at night, especially if you watch a ride through, it looks incredible.
Honestly, I mean, that's the thing.
I think Britain's got good coasters.
There's no national shame on that front.
I just think it lacks for the more thought through themed universes.
Whimsy fairy magic.
That's the type of, you know, imagineering we're looking for dark like wind, like cute
little dark rides that have more.
That's what Chessington brought to the table.
I mean, maybe one reason also that Britain is light on whimsy is that Britain's a fairly
whimsical country.
And if you go to many a small town in Britain, it feels like you're in a theme park.
They're very cute.
They have these old town squares.
You know, there's lots of old architecture.
You can buy fudge.
It's not that far from, I don't know, like a whatever.
You say hello to Paddington on your way to work.
Exactly.
So maybe that's why.
Maybe that's just not something people really need from a theme park.
Oh, and how many theme parks and how many theme parks is the theme London?
Now that I add up what you're saying, like how many big bends are out there?
How many little fave and like Universal Hollywood is it a little fake London?
Like if it is the place that theme parks are emulating, then how do you go one step beyond
that?
Right.
There's lots of old timey villages you can visit where it's, you know, they got that
here too, right?
Where, you know, pretend it's the days of your you were all going to go to a tin line,
you know, all that stuff.
But I'll say this, you know, since we're starting to, you know, talk a little about
Chesington, this, I don't know why this struck me as very like British, but they have three
different attractions based on books.
That doesn't happen in America.
Very literary.
Ew.
I mean, kids books, but still books.
Okay.
Nonetheless.
All right.
You got me back on board a little bit.
One thing.
There's pictures.
Is Britain going to have like a Harry Potter world?
Cause that does seem like something like that's sort of a layup and I don't, I don't
know why that hasn't been, but maybe it has.
They've got, they've got that tour of the set.
Right, right, right.
Still, right?
Yeah.
I think that's really all they have right now.
Well, and they have something coming called the London resort, which is selling itself
as like a world-class theme park, like trying to compete on the Disney and universal level.
Oh, I'm looking at this.
This looks fancy.
Wow.
I don't know why it's called the London resorts.
Clearly not in London, but like whatever.
I guess Disneyland Paris is not in Paris.
True.
Right.
Oh, true.
But I guess London, that's a, that's a national and that's a global brand.
Everyone knows London.
Yeah.
It's close enough.
But that makes sense to me that someone's like, you know what?
There's a bit of a gap here for like a true Disney world style place where people could
actually stay and, you know, have a great time.
David, I had a question since you live there, if you could explain a little about how people
kind of do vacations because the Chesington website has a million, a million different
spots where it is advertising come here for a short break.
And I didn't know about short break.
Yeah.
So from what I can suss out is a short break is one or two nights away
and a holiday is anything longer than three nights.
Is that stupid and wrong?
No, I think that's absolutely right.
A short break is just as far as I would think of it as a weekend, you know, right?
A weekend break.
I don't.
Yeah, it is funny to think of that.
Like, you know, I grew up in Britain and even though I always had an I was always the American,
like I always retained an accent, et cetera.
Like there's all these like idiomatic ways of speaking that you forget about, such as
saying like I'm going on holidays, like things like that.
There is this sort of obsession.
There's a place in Britain, a chain called Buttlands.
I don't know if does that I assume.
Does that mean anything to you guys?
No, no, no.
Which is there.
I'm sure there are American versions of it, but it's like, you know, that's a place you take your kid.
It's like a tented city where you will stay.
There's water parks, there's rides and like it's it's going to be a whole package deal,
like maybe for a weekend or longer where you can essentially just let your kids run wild while you
go to the pub.
Again, not to stereotype the country I grew up in and I'm a citizen of, but that is absolutely,
I think, how a lot of Brits approach their holidays.
And like that's rooted in like what I think of as the classic British vacation, because it's an
island nation that only really started entertaining Europe as a great place to visit in the last few
decades.
So like the classic thing is you go to the British seaside, like Blackpool, Skegness, these kind of
like Margate, these sort of, you know, boardwalk towns and there's a Ferris wheel and there's a
helter skelter, you know, like there's stuff like that.
Like that that kind of bleak thing is it was British seaside vacationing until eventually,
I think it was like, oh, we could go to Spain.
Like it's like an hour on the plane.
Like we can go to like we can go to like Umbria, like, you know, these beautiful like we can
Sicily, like, you know, this is all incredibly cheap.
Like once like low cost flights started happening, that's that sort of upended everything.
Interesting.
But you were you you think some of these seaside places there was something depressing about it
closer to 1900 or so.
I mean, again, not I feel like I'm just coming on and I am getting in every stereotype that
Europeans have about Brits.
But yes, like they're incredibly depressing places like they're like a Blackpool, which is kind of
like the king resort town in Britain and probably I think a lot of people still go there genuinely
to go on holiday.
Like it could be raining the entire time.
Like the food is the food's not going to be very good.
Like it's I don't know what you're getting out of Blackpool apart from that you can see the North
Sea, which is a freezing lake in between Ireland and Britain.
It's a freezing body of water.
And like there's the very classic unfair British stereotype of like people going to the beach.
And it's that they drive up to the beach and never leave their car and eat a sandwich.
And then they drive home.
And like, of course, that's not really how Brits experience the seaside.
But that's how Europeans think British people experience pleasure.
That's how I'm going to the beach these days.
Literally, I've literally done this driven to the beach, eating a sandwich, not gotten out of my
guts.
How we have to do it now.
I feel so bad.
I want to clarify like Britain actually has lots of good food.
The weather isn't so bad.
You know, like all these stereotypes are a little exaggerated.
But at the same time, you know, in Britain, certainly people make fun of them.
You know, like these are the jokes.
You know, because you lived in it.
She was a Blackpool as a fake Eiffel Tower.
See, I don't know if it's I don't know if it's specifically supposed to be the Eiffel
Tower.
It's very Eiffel Tower tower like that.
That's kind of their thing.
They got the big tower.
I forget what it's called.
But can we all something we could all do maybe is a future tournament could be fake Eiffel
Towers.
There are a number of those across theme park world at the Americana again to bring up
Glendale, home of the Austin Powers bar.
Do you have an e-jerk what the best fake Eiffel Tower is?
Me?
I've got to stand up for Blackpool Tower.
Absolutely.
I mean, like, I don't know.
Like, I'm trying to I mean, I think of Vegas, obviously.
Where are other fake?
I think it seems like Vegas is a good one.
The Disney World one's too small.
I think I think that one's not competing.
Every Lego land has a fake Eiffel Tower, too.
I've been to I think two Lego lands.
They definitely both had them.
The land.
We've not done one Lego land anyway.
And there is.
Yeah, there's one in England as part of the same corporate umbrella is very nice.
I remember I went there a couple of times.
I remember having a great time at Lego land.
Lego is great.
It's hard to argue with Lego.
Yeah, yeah.
People seem very fond of those places.
Dina, do you think that you would have
was your fondness for Chessington purely proximity or if all of these places were closer,
do you think you still would have chosen Chessington for your theme park needs?
My fondness was it was partly out of proximity, certainly.
As a teenager, I could just take the train there.
I would not even need adult adult supervision.
Like it was, you know, it's a day trip away.
But so was Thorpe Park, which is a, you know, has more intense rides,
probably like a better theme park overall.
And as a teenager, I was such a scaredy cat that I definitely gravitated towards Chessington.
Chessington was about the speed I could handle where, like,
the most intense rides at Chessington, even I was like, oh, OK, this isn't so bad.
Whereas Thorpe Park kind of freaked me out a little bit.
And there's also just like you guys know, like when you're a teenager and you're going with like
four male friends to a theme park, there's that weird egotistical one-upmanship of like,
well, I can do anything.
We're all going to do this because this is the scariest thing.
And I was such a I was very I remain, as I believe listeners in my podcast will know,
we did a Six Flags episode.
I'm not a huge fan of speed or heights.
Like, those are not things I like I need to feel in my life, like great heights and great speed.
And so, you know, like as a grownup, I'm just like, great, I can avoid that.
And Griff, you know, Griffin Newman, my co-host, he wants to take me to Disney World.
I'm excited to do that because as he's kind of made clear to me, like speed and heights are not
really the primary experiences there anyway.
Like that it's sort of a different vibe.
But yeah, yeah, it could be if you were seeking it.
But yeah, there is plenty of soft stuff to do.
Yeah, you're in good company here with that, except, well, you know, Jason's a speed demon
and a height devil.
I was going to say Miser.
You know, truth hurts sometimes, you know.
Height Miser, Jason Sheridan.
Height Miser.
That'll stick.
I like that.
Yeah.
Do you remember anything you were avoiding in Thorpe or something that you did or Alden
Tower, something that you like pushed your limits and did it and then hated it or something
that is still is frightening to you and you'll never do?
I'm now trying to see if they still have it.
Thorpe Park definitely had a ride called X No Way Out, which I believe may be gone,
which now that I say it, I love it.
It's sort of a threatening like, but that was a famously backwards ride.
One of those, you know, it goes backwards instead of forwards.
And I remember doing that, like kind of.
Whatever.
Like, you know, I would being pressured into doing that.
And I like my experience with roller coasters is always like, you know, if I do it, it's
it's fine.
It's not the end of the world.
I survived, but I never have the feeling like it has just never sparked for me where I'm
like, oh, you know what?
Like, I get it now.
I got to do this all the time.
It was always more of a thing of like, well, I did it to say that I could do that.
I, you know, I did it to check the box.
Colossus.
That was a big one.
I don't think I ever did Colossus.
Now they're all different.
Now they've got something based around saw.
Are you guys seeing this?
Yes, they have a saw because I looked up Thor Park.
I read up because they had like the same sort of website and as this one and they have saw
the ride.
What?
Whoa.
Which is just.
There's the little puppet guy.
He's like taunting you.
Yeah, he's taunting you.
But it's it seems like it's just an off the rack roller coaster with the saw logo.
Yeah.
That's a waste of the saw IP.
Well, I mean, you guys might know, like, you know, Chris Rock is relaunching saw.
The exciting new movie Spiral is coming to theaters next year, I guess.
Now, do you think they'll seize the opportunity to like to, you know,
make it to kind of a prestige rebrand of saw the ride?
Yes, they'll add a different puppet to the queue and that'll be it.
Done deal.
And yeah, the puppet says, I think I love my wife.
Wow.
Be careful.
You might discover you love your wife.
Is saw part of the rock averse?
I think it is now, right?
That's part of the deal.
Wow.
That's great.
The Chris Rock averse.
I was like, what is rock?
I mean, we just said Chris Rock, but I couldn't wrap my head around Rock averse.
Well, if you have a better name for it, I'd like to hear it.
I know.
No, I certainly don't.
I do.
I prefer calling him not Chris Rock, but the Rock Mizer.
That's why I got confused.
That's fine.
OK, but let's head into Chessington where you need not be afraid of.
Well, I mean, there's frights.
There's definitely frights as well as delights.
Yeah, you could easily be startled by Professor Burps bubble work.
We're going to talk about Professor Burps.
I mean, we just head right into it because, OK, here's my overall take,
not knowing anything about this park and starting to dig in.
You know, we just came for David.
The last episode we did was basically in Italy.
There's an entire ripoff Universal Studios where they're like, you know,
pulling IP that they clearly don't have the rights to.
And they like use Doc Brown or Mary Poppins until someone complains
and then they hide them in a shed and never use them again.
This very desperate grab for other people's IP.
They're just so chasing it and craving for it.
And it didn't really work out.
Chessington, I feel like, is full of original IP that is very delightful,
very creative, very British in a lot of cases.
I find this place so charming.
And I mean, just what I view as like the primary three that really jumped out at me
are like, I think some of the most original theme park rides we've ever come across.
So tell me the three.
I'm excited.
Well, I mean, we should kick it off with.
I mean, certainly we could build to it.
But I mean, what we just mentioned, Professor Burps bubble works.
I mean, if the audience isn't excited already by this phrase,
I mean, we could say the very short sentence about it is
that Professor Burp invites you to a tour of his wacky soda factory.
Am I missing anything that it had kind of a vague, I guess, Willy Wonka vibe to it, right?
Like it's a it's a water ride.
It's a dark ride.
You're in like a tube floating around.
And it's a it's a factory making soda.
So there's all kinds of bubble stuff to be clear.
It no longer exists, which I was sad to learn.
I think I vaguely had heard this, but it was open when I was like, yeah, 1990.
Right. And it ran for like 15, 16 years.
And when I was when I was going there to Chessington,
obviously Chessington had a real ride.
So like, you know, when you're with your friends, they want to do.
We're going to talk about some of them.
But I remember when I was like 10 being like, I think that's the best ride.
And that not being that controversial opinion, even among my friends trying to seem cool
going on the nastiest rides, like they were like, yeah, there's something about bubble works.
Like there's something about it.
It's just kind of just kind of a blast.
It had a strobe light section.
I think that's what we all like the most.
At the end, where they're like, we're going to show you how we, you know, whatever.
Here's the final step to soda making.
And then you were in this like big open hall and there would be strobes going.
So all of the like all the water looked crazy and you would, you know,
It's like big fountains like shooting over the your ride track.
And you're in like a they might even call them tubs.
You're in this like circular round thing.
So it's like a it's like a whitewater rafting ride that isn't rough.
You just like casually float and spin.
So you get different views of everything as you go.
It's like a tea.
It's like you're in the tea cups at Disneyland, but it's in water.
Yes, exactly.
And right.
And they like Chessington had like a log flume, like it had actual water rides.
But this was gentle.
But still like it had atmosphere, which I guess most Chessington rides had less.
Most Chessington rides were pretty basic, I feel like.
And like, you know, maybe they had a little color.
They had like some cute theming or whatever.
But like this was like this was something where there had been actual thought invested
in like the progression of it.
And it always felt very satisfying at the end when you went through the whole strobe universe.
It sounds great.
I was going to say it is like, I mean, probably the base, you know, on the Wonka
Willy Wonka scene where they go through the boat and it's like an acid trip.
It feels like even like teenage even like jaded teens would be like, man, it's like being on drugs.
Yes.
Like it's crazy.
So like that feels like for teens, that might have been the appeal because it would it would like
look from watching the video, I feel like, you know, it messes with you a little bit.
I think that's right.
Now, that's exactly it.
As a teen, you could still argue like, well, it's trippy.
Like, so that's cool.
Yeah.
That was kind of the way you could get into a pretend tub for Professor Burps Bubbleworks
and not feel like a like a fool.
Like, you know, you'd be like, no, we got it.
We actually got to do that.
And the other fun is I remember it's right next to the vampire, which is one of their rides that I
think is still going.
And so the vampire would always be going right by you as you were in line.
So there was it was like and there's a lot of trees around.
I just remember it being the best area of the park in terms of you feeling like you're in an
actual little universe.
Maybe the most themes, maybe the most like Disney universal caliber little zone they had.
Yeah, I think this this thing looks so delightful.
I think it has the the spirit of Willy Wonka without being a ripoff of Willy Wonka.
Is it's it's I mean, certainly inspired by that, but very much its own little universe.
Some some details I wanted to point out that I like you see a lot of posters of different
experimental types of soda that Professor Burp is working on, such as Luminous Pop,
the bedtime drink.
It I think I think it says under that somewhere it glows so you can read with it.
So if you if you're drinking the soda in the dark, it is also a nightlight.
That's great.
I don't there's something I don't have any further details about it, but something called
jackpot juice.
I assume there was some money going on there, right?
Like there's a well, yeah, Professor Burp got bought out.
His contract got bought out by the Jones Soda Company with all their wacky flavors.
They outbid Chesington.
They sort of generic genericified his operation.
Not sure if Jones kept the juice jacuzzi.
There was like a tickle thing.
I remember like I guess that's to test.
Lickle test.
If the if the bubbles are tickling you and I don't I don't know.
Like they found every angle on this that they possibly could, which it's so specific.
A soda.
So like how do you think of, you know, dozens of jokes about weird sodas?
Right.
And they did pull it off.
I want to talk about the soda.
They did pull it off.
I want to talk about a guy who I think is the main person behind this ride,
a guy named John Wardley.
I found an interview.
He I think did a lot of the rides that I found so charming.
The dark ride kind of things and a lot of stuff at Alton Towers too.
I found an interview with him where he's on the ride and kind of pointing out stuff.
He explains the impetus of it, which was he thought about doing a ride about a brewery,
seeing how beer gets made, but you can't really do that with kids.
So this became a soda factory.
And then he does a little part of this.
I think will be better coming from him.
I'm going to screen share here.
And this is him talking about a part of the ride that I think is is very fun.
And here's John Wardley.
When we were considering the actual processes of testing the pop over there,
that is the far tester that tests the fart ability of the pop.
Now, we actually had a board meeting to discuss whether we could use the word far.
That was a good one.
That's that pretty much with the hard egg, a bad egg.
I'm looking at the the fart meter here.
There's a man in a little chair who, I guess,
farts in the chair and it propels him up like a carnival game,
like a ring the buzzer carnival game.
And he hits different levels of fart ability.
Wait, if I move the play, a whiffy is one level of fart ability.
Whoop, whoopie, whoops.
I think it says bad egg Heinz 57.
Sure.
What is that?
Oh, I see.
Oh, yeah.
Why Heinz?
OK, OK.
He's a British.
He's a big beans.
Right.
They love it.
Oh, I get it now.
I can't see what that top one something about splitter.
But I don't know what it's pants.
Pants, splitter, splitter.
Yeah, that's great.
The big like fart joke zone of this ride and this like I love this stuffy guy.
Like we talked about if we can actually use the word thought
and more painting, apparently.
A board meeting about British words.
How delightful.
Yeah, this thing is so fun.
And then what happened with it is that they kept the same ride,
but they kind of couldn't keep it going unless there was a sponsor.
Thus, it became a different ride, still a bubble oriented place,
so still a bubble works, but now called Imperial Leather Bubble Works,
which is a phrase that makes no sense to me.
But I guess you would know that that's a variety of soap.
It's like a big soap brand in Britain.
All these British companies, like they were formed in the Victorian era,
so they all sound like incredibly fancy.
Imperial Leather is just like, I don't know, it's like Dove.
What's like a common soap here?
It's just a regular old soap.
Yeah, but dressed up with you put Grand and
the old and Victorian in the title, then it seems like something.
But so they redid it as now a tour of a soap factory,
which people did not like as it was just like a big ad for this brand of soap.
I saw it referred to as monotonous,
charmless and at best a highly irritating advert for its sponsor.
And among the people who hated it was this guy, John Wardley,
who really like disowned the ride, was so disgusted by what they did with it
and spoke publicly about how they removed all of the charm.
Mike and Jason, this is a syndrome we've seen before.
The creator of the ride being publicly disparaging of the bad redo of it.
This is so much like Tony Baxter.
David, we really revere this one Imagineer who's behind
Splash Mountain and Star Tours and all this great stuff.
I was thinking that anyway, and then the season pass podcast,
I think had this guy in the show and they referred to him as the Tony Baxter of Britain.
And the ride itself is very like Journey into Imagination trippy.
A lot of fun stuff going on.
It is very similar.
Like it's exactly the same story really for what happened to those two rides.
And stripping it in stripping the ride of its wonderful main character,
in one case figments the dragon and another case, Professor Burp.
Professor Burp, which we love him now.
And again, is he available?
Can we now access him and make IP movie and TV shows with him?
We would like to investigate that.
Have we seen that he is now there is a Chessington cinematic universe.
Mm hmm.
He's connected to character on another ride.
Really?
Well, wait, I haven't got.
Oh, I like that.
So let me hear.
I have it here.
There's a character named Zappo Matic.
Did you see him?
Did you find him?
Yes.
And this is this is on the ride, the fifth dimension.
Right.
Which is rethemed to Terror Tomb.
So this says, although they only got to know each other for three years,
Burp and Zappa Matic were incredibly close friends.
Zap was his first friend.
And they regularly regularly met up every month after the incredible
rethemed of the fifth dimension to Terror Tomb.
Zappa Matic mysteriously disappeared under strange circumstances
in which he left the professor distraught and upset.
And I have a picture of his tombstone.
They canonically killed Zappo Matic.
Yes, I have it right here.
This is a fun robot character from a dark ride who they have murdered.
They have murdered the character because of a retheme here.
I'll just quickly.
I was just about to say this all has a happy ending,
but I guess it's a lot more complicated than that.
What?
Zappo Matic's grave.
Oh, that epitaph is like poochy.
Sadly, left this world for another dimension.
Oh, no.
Geez.
I guess maybe he survived.
Maybe they're trying to soften the blow for kids.
He went to another dimension, guys.
Don't worry.
It's all right.
You know, he's not dead.
I would argue that the headstone, though, is a bit traumatic.
It is.
Yeah, that was definitely Terror Tomb when I was attending Chessington.
That's what I remember.
Terror Tomb.
That was like a laser gun shooting at targets at a ride.
Yes.
Yeah, that's kind of Egyptian themed.
Now, OK, now there's two.
There were two versions of this ride.
Yeah, they became a shooting ride, but there was a version that was not
shooting oriented thing.
Were you ever there when there was a character named Abdub?
Remind me of Abdub's role in Chessington.
OK, so in Terror Tomb, I'll read a description.
I copy pasted a harrowing journey through the booby trap filled catacombs with Abdub,
a greedy tomb robber bent on stealing a priceless emerald.
So you're taking a tour of a tomb, but there's this guy who keeps yelling at you
because he wants this emerald to himself.
Sounds like the British.
So he's kind of like trapped there.
It sounds like essentially he's like constantly looking for this emerald.
Yeah, essentially.
Well, and ends up truly trapped.
Mike and Jason, did you catch this ride or watch a video of it or anything?
I actually didn't watch a video.
I didn't know.
This is so great.
I think one of my favorite moments, honestly, in a ride that I've ever seen,
and I'll show it to you guys, that's build it up too much.
But so you're going through this.
You're going through this too.
Abdub is just a crazy creepy animatronic that people on YouTube have bought
and are trying to like people are like resuscitating Abdub with,
you know, like toss together electronics in their apartments,
which is very creepy and odd.
And you can watch that.
But, you know, the fun effects through this ride,
there's like an ever flowing amount of snakes in this one part.
Like it's like a spinning wheel that's covered in snakes
that just goes in an infinite loop.
So it looks like thousands of snakes are pouring out,
but it doesn't stop Abdub.
He's still after the emerald.
You see a big like statue of a Anubis.
It has big scary heads and vortex tunnels.
There might even be a boulder like Indiana Jones.
It's all a pretty like serious, scary ride.
And then you get to you're getting towards the end of this thing.
And there's a lot of heads all in canting something.
And then I will play what happens from that point.
And this will we'll have to back up and explain it to the listener.
But this will be, you know, probably more fun to experience visually.
But check out what happens to Abdub at the end of this attraction.
Scary heads.
Let me pause and say there is now a mummy playing guitar.
Oh, my God.
He has a light up headdress or collar or whatever you want to call it.
I'll play it for there.
Oh,
I mean, that's great.
That's fantastic.
Really good.
Yeah.
The way he yells cool is fantastic.
Now you've done become a cool.
This rules.
This is unbelievable.
You get a rock concert at the end of this ride and poor Abdub stuck in a what you think is a tomb.
But then the lid raises up and it's covered in spikes and he gets locked in it.
And what that is is an iron maiden.
The metal music that we are hearing of Abdub is impaled to death.
And I it's like, again, multiple characters in Chessington die.
This rocks more than anything at Hard Rock Park.
Yeah, I'd have to say so.
Yes.
That legitimately is that the most actually rocking song made for a theme park attraction.
For yes, specifically park specific.
I'll say right now.
Yes.
But I bet you're hedging your bets because you don't want to put it above Aerosmith.
Well, of course, Aerosmith's changing the lyrics slightly to love in an elevator to
love and roller coaster and kind of counts as an original song to me.
Sure.
So I don't want to fully knock it out, but they're tied.
Let's say they're tied.
Yeah.
So yeah, this is cool.
Going to spike your brain, going to spit your soul.
You'll be a slave under my control.
Dark stuff.
Genuinely dark road.
Wow.
You know what?
That maybe takes, I don't know, does it beat the Halloween overlay for the Knott's
log flume ride with the alien band at the end?
Oh, yeah.
That is really fantastic.
That's really fun.
There's a specific Halloween song from the Timber Mountain log ride around Halloween time.
And they're playing like a really jaunty, fun Halloween song.
And it's like a bear and an alien.
And I think the bear turns you and goes trick or treat.
Yes, he does.
He sure does.
It's like one of the greatest moments in theme park history.
So with these being so awesome, why aren't there more just creatures playing guitars
all over theme park worlds?
This rules.
It's so good.
Yeah, I think.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Where would be just a brainstorm?
What would be the best ride to just throw a bunch of guitars on the animals or the robots?
Maybe.
I mean, obviously Princess and the Frog coming to Splash Mountain.
But if you give a guitar to all the animals on the riverboat at the end of Splash Mountain
and they were all just soloing, that would be pretty cool.
I mean, rock and haunted mansion would be great.
That'd be a nice new overlay.
Just all of them shredding just 300 ghosts.
999 happy haunts and they can all shred.
They can all shred.
You could give a big guitar to the man or the creature who replaced
the Imperial Leather Bubbleworks, the Gruffalo.
That's right.
He's that would be fairly metal.
The Gruffalo, right?
I don't know.
Yeah, the Gruffalo is cool.
I like the Gruffalo.
We zoom fast that which is your background, David.
That's what this ride is now, the Gruffalo.
Yeah, it seems which I have not been on the Gruffalo River Ride Adventure,
which is what Bubbleworks is now.
But that seems better to me than just like SponCon, right?
I'm sure that's a little more thematically whole.
It looks very charming.
The Gruffalo book was published in the late 90s and it kind of has a...
Oh, God, who's the Where the Wild Things Are guy?
Maurice Sendak.
Yes.
Yeah, Maurice.
It has a sort of whimsical animation style like that.
And I thought this, I couldn't believe, oh, this is very charming too.
Like, we don't have...
That was the happy ending I was alluding to.
Like, well, if they redid Journey into Imagination and replaced it with something,
like in the way they replaced Bubbleworks with the Gruffalo River Ride Adventure,
it's like, well, that's nice.
This looks nice.
It's maybe not as weird as the original one, but it's like, well, this seems charming.
Yeah, yeah, and better than a soap ad, I'd say.
Yes.
Yeah, for sure.
I'm reading, like, you know, it has less animations and props,
so there's some sort of consternation about that.
I think it's a lot more screens, right, which is a little less...
Whatever.
Unique, but that's fine.
But apparently there are smell pods to make it smell foresty, which that sounds cool.
Sounds nice.
That's one of the drawbacks, obviously, because we haven't been there.
Does that forest smell like the ET forest in Orlando?
Other famous forest fake smells.
We did a fake smell Final Four where we argued which was the best smell.
So I would like to...
When we eventually revisit that, I would like to have experienced the smell at this park,
just to make sure we didn't overlook it.
Do you remember smells in the soda factory?
I think there might have been like orange, one of the classic theme park smells.
Right, there was definitely lots of smells.
It also, like, you know, if it was a hot day, like it was like kind of just...
It was like cool and misty.
But yes, I remember all smells like that.
And like, I guess just also, you know, the joy of being in water.
Like it was always like a nice sort of chilled out thing that you should do
right in the middle of your visit, right?
Like to kind of like, you know, reset a little bit.
Sure, sure.
That's a good thing to ask if I was like,
do you remember anything else, atmosphereically, about this place?
Is there anything like non-ride that jumps out at you or...
Do you remember like, is food any good to this place?
The food is bad.
I mean, British fast food is fairly underwhelming.
Like it's gotten better as it gets more Americanized,
but that's like, which is not a particularly charming thing.
Like, you know, what Britain has to offer on the fast food front is fish and chips.
That's always been like, that's like the classic British fast food,
like fish and chips in a newspaper or whatever.
But I remember like the food being like, you know,
totally ordinary kind of like chicken fingers, right?
Like, you know, all that kind of stuff.
And the, I'm now trying to find a map, like in the sort of like,
it was a slightly subdivided world and it had,
well, I'm sure we'll talk about Beano land.
I was just going to bring up Beano land.
Yes.
But like, you know, it was, it's more like a six flags where it's like,
the sun's kind of beating down on you if you're there in the summertime,
which you probably are like, there's not a lot of shelter
and there is a cool little monorail thing like that.
You could sort of take around to look at stuff and there is a zoo,
but I remember the zoo being sort of a bummer again, much like six flags.
Like you don't really want to go to the zoo when you're at a theme park.
Yeah.
Do you have any memories of like just weird childhood stuff,
like drama between friends that would happen there?
Because I feel like that was always kind of a pressure cooker when you'd go
with your friends to a place like that for a long time.
It's what I, that is what I associate with theme parks is going with my friends
and then the weird, it's like how now everyone has to negotiate their personal
comfort with the pandemic where it's like, some people are like,
I'm not going outside at all.
And other people are like, well, I wanted to go to a restaurant.
And like, there's all the weird arguments within that, you know, like,
you know, it's like, some kids just want to like ride the gnarly rides over and
over and over again.
And like, I feel like I was more of a wanderer.
I liked kind of the weird freedom you have as a teenager in a theme park
where you can kind of like, you know, act independently and like, you know,
I'm going to go get some food and like march off by yourself.
And like, that's all I remember about going to Chessington is like everyone
fighting over the order of the day and how, how like, you know, we have to
prioritize the vampire over the rattlesnake or whatever, you know, like
the weird kind of it's like, it's like a little fake town.
It's like a little fake life for you to live as a teenager, right?
Like you get to pretend to be a little grown up for, for an afternoon.
Now, see, I, I mostly went to theme parks with my family and everyone
knew what everyone else liked.
We were all very cordial about it.
If me or my brother wanted to do different stuff, usually one parent
would take one.
One would take the other.
So the one or two times I went to a theme park on a school trip, I just
remember going like, you're all insane.
There's an efficient way to do this, to make everyone happy.
And I was immediately, I'm like, you know what?
I'm just going to go off on my own because everyone's being really weird
in this heat.
Jason, was it just that they weren't catering to your every whim?
Well, it wasn't catering to my every whim.
I was just like, well, guys, this, it was things like, well, this has a
shorter weight and that has a longer, why don't we do the shorter weight one
for, and, and trying to convince like six or seven year olds.
It's like, well, no, when then we'd have to double bat, not six, six or seven.
I was going to say you're going there by yourself at six.
Like trying to convince like, well, no, if we do this for it, we're going
to have to double back.
That doesn't make sense.
We're going to be crisscrossing the whole thing.
We only have six hours, you know.
You just unlocked a memory for me, which is taking like, it was some like we
won a, the classroom won a contest or something and got to go to Disneyland.
My dream, that's great.
But then we get there and it's like a six hour thing.
It's pretty short, not nearly enough time for me.
And I swear the gen, the consensus of the class of, of 11 year olds or
whatever was we got to spend like an hour and a half of this in the starcade.
You're fucking kidding me.
How dare you do this to me?
I'm like remembering the faces of the kids now who were like, no, I want to
be in the arcade all day.
I think I snuck away.
I think I like left the chaperone so I could go on the people mover.
I was so
worried.
God.
Yeah.
I was not supposed to be on my own, but I'm like, well, I'm going to go do
the monorail at Hershey park and I'm going to get a chili dog and then I'm
going to ride the super duper looper.
And we broke protocol.
We like disobeyed adults for the, we were bad kids in a way for the first time at
theme parks.
You know what you were doing?
Like you were, you were being a little grownup.
That's how I was too.
It's like, you're like, guys, let's be efficient about that.
Exactly how I was.
Whereas I feel like some kids, you know, it's, it's like candy.
They're like, I have to do the best thing first.
We have to do it right now.
Like, I don't care how long it takes, which I, when I was in it for the long
haul, I have the long game in mind.
Yes.
What year, Scott, what year was it?
What was there a hot arcade game that year that like was mortal?
They didn't have mortal combat in Disneyland.
Did they?
That doesn't seem right.
God, I don't know.
Was it just a word where people just cruise in USA?
Where was it just a cruise in USA?
I, I specifically, I think it was like 96 or 97 because I remember all of
Tomorrowland was construction walls because they were like all it was like
nothing but plywood.
It was very depressing, honestly, around and they had just closed EO, which made
me think about all the weirdness with that.
It was just very, very sad time to be there.
And I was made more sad by all these arcades.
I think I maybe said out loud, you have arcades at home.
You can go to arcade anytime.
I could go to the arcade like, yeah, it was an arcade like 10 minutes from my
house.
Who cares about arcades?
I can play Street Fighter whenever.
We see each other every day at school.
We hang out on the weekends.
We're at Hershey Park like once or twice a year.
Fry are let's get our priorities in order, folks.
I'm going to be angry about this decades from now.
Yeah.
Anyway, this is why all the media you consume, ladies and gentlemen, is so weird
because it's all made by weirdos like us.
Odd angers that we hold on to.
I actually you know what?
What is also maybe this is fine in terms of remembering, like pulling out specific
memories.
I found a from a website called Surrey Live.
I found a fairly spelling and grammatically questionable listicle called
15 things you'd remember if you if you I don't have in front of me, if you grew up
going to Chessington.
I didn't write down all of them, but I'm curious to throw these out and see if
you agree.
Of course, you did.
Do you have memories of these things?
Feeling really queasy after going on Ramsey's Revenge 20 times in a row.
Yes, I certainly never went on Ramsey's Revenge 20 times in a row because that's
an awful idea.
But that was the hottest ride when I was a kid.
That was what the advertisements led with.
I don't know if you guys saw it, but it's sort of like, you know, it's like
spinning.
You're in a thing.
You're spinning you.
And then there's a bigger arm that's also spinning you.
And there's water.
I'm bad at theme park lingo.
I assume there's like a word for the kind of a ride Ramsey's Revenge is.
I think.
Does it still exist?
I was trying to remember.
I don't think I have the terminology either, but yeah, you're like it.
They call it a top spin ride on there.
There you go.
Whatever that means.
That's the kind of thing we should have more at our disposal.
And yet I don't.
It's fine.
Nobody's.
It's a glorified flat ride.
It's glorified kind of carnival ride with a few effects.
Right.
Exactly.
And it was kind of dressed up in because I believe that's also where the Tomb Blaster
and the Rockin' Mummies were.
There was a whole kind of ancient Forbidden Kingdom zone.
You know, like and Ramsey's Revenge was that's like the barf ride.
That was the ride that made you barf and directly opposite it was a ride called
the Magic Carpet that even when I was a kid, it doesn't exist anymore, was so obviously
wildly unsafe.
We would look at it as kids and we'd be like, I don't think that anyone should be getting
in that thing.
And then they closed it kind of quietly.
Oh, no.
I don't think anyone got on it, but it was just one of those very old fashioned.
It would just go round and round and round and then stop and smash your face into a bar.
Like it was it was just it was no fun.
It was like a ride because like I always forget the one at Knotts that they closed down where
you went on it and you were like, this hurts.
It was like why?
Yes.
Yeah.
This isn't pain.
This isn't something that would last, but you know, maybe for a little while.
The tense in this article, again, very strange.
You spent the rest of the day walking around with a wet bum after going on the Dragon
Falls ride.
Sound familiar?
Any wet bums?
Oh, a wet one.
When?
Oh, yes.
Yeah.
Yes.
To be British about I'm sure you say bum.
You do.
All the way.
We've been saying seat.
We should be we should change the lingo for this episode.
Bum play.
Yes.
I mean, sure.
The dragon with the dragon's fury.
Now I'm trying to remember what it was called.
The Dragon Falls.
Right.
That was it.
That was the log plume.
You have to do that late because otherwise you will be wet all day.
But I mean, Jason, how do you feel about a wet bum?
You like wet feet.
I know that you wet socks.
You like that.
I think I think, yeah, I think a wet bum is more uncomfortable.
I think that might be worse to me.
Yeah.
Is there any reason why anyone would like that?
I specifically like a sopping wet bum.
Sex stuff, I guess.
You know.
What was that, Jason?
I said sex stuff.
You know, probably is probably someone out there.
Everything's a thing.
Everybody's into something.
I'm open to it now that I'm so free with my body and mind.
So I'm I'm I'm open to the idea of it.
I just haven't I haven't experienced it and liked it yet.
Mike's Mike's got a big wrench just opening up the fire hydrant on his street
and taking a step in front of it.
Shaking.
Yeah.
Shaking my butt at a fire hydrant that's open on the street.
Getting launched a few feet to get a wet bum.
Worth it as far as I'm concerned.
Sure.
As mothers and children stare and point and you say you wouldn't get it, it's a European thing.
I've I've grown as a person.
One more of these.
This seems obscure.
I'm curious if you this seems very obscure.
The chewing gum tree in the vampire ride queue.
That feels like something too deep to remember.
I do like I remember that.
I do remember the vampire, which I definitely rode.
And that was always next to the bubble works.
And it was it was you know, your feet are dangling.
One of those which at the time was still a novelty.
I know that's like run of the mill now.
I do not remember chewing gum tree.
Don't really know what that would have to do with a vampire.
That whole area was called Transylvania.
It was sort of odd that bubble works was there because bubble works didn't have anything to do
with Transylvania.
But for whatever reason that they were next to each other and
Chessington was like it's Transylvania the vampire.
So I remember, you know, some, you know, some crosses, right?
Like, you know, some like some gravestones maybe maybe that's where they buried the alien guy.
But I do not remember.
Oh, yes.
So could be.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's a robot buried in a vampire cemetery.
There is a I think the tree was just used like people just put gum in this one place all the time,
which is disgusting.
And why?
And why would you put more gum there and touch other gum as you do so bad?
But anyway, there's also I think that area also has something called I noticed on a map
Vampires Burger Kitchen.
Pretty good restaurant name.
I dig that, which is listed as being on Leatherhead Road.
Hey, good name.
And Counts Cauldron, maybe two men.
I like all these.
But where do we head from here?
Maybe over to maybe over to Beano land.
Yeah, yeah, I just wanted to ask, did everyone see a video of Zapomatic?
Oh, yes.
Yeah, I did.
I have something queued up.
Were you going to bring up something specific?
OK, well, I just it's just a video.
He's terrified.
He's so terrifying.
Is the video what you're showing?
Yeah, I believe.
Yeah, he'll be on frame here in a set.
How do we describe?
Yeah, what does Zapomatic look like?
He reminds me and it's not quite right, but he reminds me of like
a Return to Oz type character.
He's a little tick tock esque.
He's taller.
He is kind of like a what would you call it?
Some sort of scarf.
Is it a cravat?
Technically, what English what English neck dressing does Zapomatic wear?
Yeah, I guess it's a cravat.
I like a loose fitting tie.
It looks like basically like a bandana that's not around his face.
An ascot?
Yeah, sure.
I don't know.
It's funny to think like that when they open this because this was the first edition,
right?
The fifth dimension.
They were obviously like sci fi is the thing.
We got to have aliens.
We got to write.
And then they quickly pivoted to like ancient Egypt in the 90s, which is not a pivot.
I would say like you would automatically guess like what was hot in the 90s was like tombs,
but I guess I guess they were tombs were kind of hot as theme park areas, right?
Maybe not so much movies, but like that was just kind of a classic theme parky thing,
like a haunted tomb type.
It's one of the themes, I suppose.
It's like, yeah, yeah, you've got, as we said, you got a lot of things are
London themed and a lot of things are Egypt themed.
I mean, Chasington is technically themed to like areas of the world.
There's like an English area and a Mexican Wild West area, Pirates Cove.
Yes, there's unfortunately, they may have changed this, but there was once a Mystic East,
which I feel like they should probably spruce that up.
I don't know if there's so many theme parks have weird,
like East Orient.
Yeah, those should all start getting dismantled.
Let me play this quick clip of Zap-o-matic.
This ride, the fifth dimension, this was a dark ride and it was open for about a year
and then guests started complaining that the plot was too confusing.
What I'm going to play you is from the second version.
So this is what this is a little snippet of the less confusing story.
Let's see if you get the gist of what this ride is from this.
As I told you, I am Zap-o-matic and I was sent in here to repair this TV.
But would you believe it?
There's a gorg in here.
Horrible creatures, gorgs.
So we got that he's Zap-o-matic is a TV repair robot.
He's now the ride is called the fifth dimension, which so that what that means is going into a TV.
And of course, yes, your TV contains dimensions.
But when you know what, there's a gorg.
And I don't think you get any more info about what a gorg is.
Horrible creatures, apparently.
Or they're, yes, you're right, you do.
You get the info that they're horrible creatures.
What year, Scott, is the video you just played?
Does it say?
88.
OK, because I have I have I was going to play the exact same clip, but a different year.
And they shoot it like it's a horror movie a little more.
What? Oh, OK.
Wait, is that that's a little hype?
I'll I'll put it up just to show you.
Yes, I'm hyping it up a little too much.
But you'll see what I mean when I'm like, especially this made an impression on me.
As Mike said, it's like this scary return to Oz creature and he's in front of a weird
like a frightening grid, but that's not symmetrical.
It's all like amorphous and it's it's all it's all very
it's kind of like Lawn Mower Man a little bit.
Very long, a lot of green, a lot of laser grids.
OK, so here are the Bendy grids.
Audio and audio not as good.
Jesus.
It's just so that's why I was really scared of him.
He's a really zoom in on his creepy eyes.
That is that is a better video for that angle.
He's basically a robotic Jack Skellington.
Right. And only his head is moving really like everything else is pretty limited.
So it almost seems like he's kind of like stuck or zombified or something.
Yeah. Tied up or like and in an uncomfortable position.
Yeah. So it looks like, yeah, he's he's like about to die.
And only one part of his body is working.
We don't have to be scared anymore because he is dead.
Yeah. Oh, you're right.
He's been killed.
Why are we upset that he's dead?
We should be we should be celebrating this.
You know what? Yeah. Good Zap-O-Matic.
I guess for Dr. Burp, whatever they were friends.
Professor Burp. I'm so sorry.
He doesn't deserve to lose a friend.
Is Zap-O-Matic gone?
The Gorgs are just going to run rampant.
They're just going to run rough shot over this place.
Well, yeah, because he was the one monitoring the situation.
And here's here's what the plan is.
This is what you're supposed to how you're supposed to help control the Gorg population.
It's hiding in one of the five dimensions from the video.
And it's definitely not in this one.
At least I don't think it is.
Now, if you can find the Gorg, I can make a laser gun to destroy it.
But only you have the power to fire the gun.
Well, that's settled.
Then I'll go to the workshop and get busy.
And I'll leave you to find the Gorg.
It's out there somewhere.
Jesus. Whoa, that was a dramatic ending.
Yeah. Lightning strikes.
Only you have the power to fire the gun.
But to create you have to create the gun first.
I'll build the gun, but only you could fire the gun.
He's also barely giving you time to respond.
He's just like, anyway, so you fire the gun.
Got it. OK.
Like, you know, there's not a lot of call and response here.
Are you prepared to fire the gun?
It's like it's the warning getting on a plane of like, are you ready to
use the exit row?
Yeah, people exit.
All right. Good.
All right. In case of a crash landing, are you prepared to fire the gun?
I guess. Wait, guns are involved.
Yes. Hurry.
This plane is full of Gorgs.
Over that endless loop of.
Is this all like, yeah, heralding.
In Star Wars, a Gorg is like what they it's like the little
froggy creatures that Jar Jar eats on Tatooine.
I remember that.
That's fun. Right.
I don't know.
That is fun.
Could that be the same thing as Gorg found in some sort of myth?
Yeah, maybe. Right.
Yeah. Maybe that's where George Lucas got the idea.
I don't know.
Do you think there's a lot of children around this time who
went on this ride, didn't even really perceive it.
And then like to this day, have nightmares where Zapomatic type faces
appear to them through the clouds and and Gorgs and swamp spines.
That's another thing that shows up.
Zapomatic holding like holding a gun out to them and be like,
you will be the one to fire this.
You only you.
You have the power.
For a queen and country.
But Zapomatic, how do you have the power to build the gun but not to fire it?
It seems like if we're talking about your hands, because if you
have hands to build, you have hands to fire.
I was not programmed to kill.
Right. There's the Asimov's law of robotics.
You like means that you have to pull the trigger even though he can make you a gun.
Only little boys and girls can kill.
For Albiad, for the king.
Perhaps you'll develop a taste for it.
Perhaps this won't be your last kill.
I'm not encouraging you to do so.
I never would.
I'm I'm merely a builder man.
But if you need more guns, let me know.
Her Majesty Secret Service is always hiring young children.
Zapomatic was recruiting for the British government.
Zapomatic was recruiting for the circus.
Zapomatic was on Twitch.
He kind of looks like remember when there was that fake meme or fake like sort of scandal about kids
seeing some video of a creepy demon that was like telling them to do crimes?
Am I the only person who remembers this?
Yeah.
That's what he looks like.
That's familiar.
Yeah.
Now I can't remember.
Wow. I guess I hate Zapomatic.
I mean, I didn't you know, it's all it really shows you the power of film.
Momo.
Right.
There we go.
Momo.
Yeah.
Momo is a demon telling children to do bad things.
Momo is not Slenderman.
Momo is a different demon.
Telling Momo you will.
It's just there's a vague similarity to Zapomatic just because of the stretched mouth.
Jesus.
I'm afraid to see Momo.
Momo is a little.
Yeah.
So I know Momo.
Of course.
Momo is like a frightening cartoon version of Shelly Duvall in The Shining.
I was going to say it shows you the power of filmmaking because I didn't hate Zapomatic
until I saw Mike's angle where it zooms all the way in.
And that close up now is very scarring.
And yes, I'd have to agree.
I hate Zapomatic.
But again, he's dead.
Yes.
Thank God.
Now I'm not upset by that.
And yeah.
Hey, kids out there, if you have nightly nightmares about Zapomatic.
What he forces you to do.
Yeah.
Now at Chessington, they just have nice stuff like Elmer's flying jumbos.
Everyone's favorite patchwork elephant.
Right.
We all know Elmer the Patchwork Elephant.
Jumbos.
Elmer.
Is it?
Do we like Elmer's better than Babar?
Probably is less like colonial overtones, right?
I don't know.
Yeah.
OK.
Elmer just kind of looks like a heffalumper woozo.
Right.
OK.
A quilting beast.
Is there any Babar representation in theme parks?
Do we know off the top of our heads?
Is there like a...
I think there might be like a French one, maybe.
I don't know.
No, I don't think so.
And here's an article from 1989 that says plans are underway for a Babar theme park.
But obviously that did not occur.
And also, where is the representation of Muzzy?
The language teaching monster from it was ubiquitous on Nickelodeon for so many years.
Where's Muzzy?
Yeah.
Muzzy.
Hashtag where's Muzzy?
Where are the refrains of...
That's it.
That was the phrase.
I was trying to remember the phrase.
Burned into my brain.
Muzzy.
Yeah.
How have we not said the word Muzzy on this show yet?
That's the first instance, I think.
I don't know.
There should be a Muzzy land where all the rides are available in multiple languages.
What was Muzzy?
Whenever you saw clips of it, it looked frightening.
Muzzy looked extremely depressing.
Yeah.
Muzzy seemed like an experiment gone wrong.
You remember Muzzy, David?
I do remember Muzzy only as a commercial.
I don't think I ever participated in Muzzy's language learning.
But yeah.
Do we know anyone who did Muzzy?
Did Muzzy teach anyone French?
Did he have successes?
I've never heard anyone like, well, I did Muzzy.
And that's why today I am a UN diplomat.
Most people in that room, almost every one of them.
Now I'm thinking of Park Asterix.
I'm thinking of European parks.
Maybe you guys are doing Park Asterix.
I have no idea what your European adventures will take you on.
Do we spoil it or do we not?
So I don't know.
I'll leave it ambiguous.
That is sort of like if there were a Bar Barland.
That's like a specific French cartoon character with some international fame.
Who gets a whole theme park to himself.
Right.
Did you have any of the did you grew up with?
I guess you were there from nine on.
So it wasn't like so much early cartoons.
But do you have affinity for characters who we would not?
I had a younger brother, so he was watching all the kids cartoons.
So like Postman Pat.
I don't know if you guys know Postman Pat.
But no, I know he's a mailman.
British kids cartoons are pretty good.
At least the classic ones.
Because they would do a lot of puppets, a lot of stop motion.
It's the BBC.
So there's like that sort of like veneer of class to like classic British cartoons.
Postman Pat's very gentle.
He's a mailman.
He has a black and white cat.
He drives around in his mail truck and like the biggest disaster would be like,
the bridge is down.
He's got to like go around it.
Something like that.
Very low stakes, chill.
Very relaxing.
Sure.
There's also like pauses.
There was like the weird stuff like the clangers, which is like their little like,
you know, felt mice who live on the moon and like they talk like,
all that stuff where you would watch it and be kind of bewitched.
Even as like a nine or 10 year old, I'd be like, what's what is this?
What's going on here?
There was nothing like that.
I had grown up on a steady diet of like Cartoon Network cartoons about people
shooting each other, like which I was like, that's children's
entertainment.
Like that's what I'm here for.
Like I would like to see the guns.
Yeah.
David, do you have an opinion on who was better?
Mr. Conductor on Thomas the Tank was it Ringo Starr or George Carlin?
I, I unfortunately, I grew up with Carlin.
So he was to me, I understand.
I mean, like it's and I was a big Thomas the Tank engine fan,
like, or a big Shining Time Station fan.
So unfortunately for me, it's Carlin, like maybe not unfortunately,
but I wish I had grown up with that just because it's such a cool thing.
Right.
I mean, I think that's, look, they're both great choices.
I know Alec Baldwin was in a recent.
Yeah, I think in the, in the film, there was a movie where he's the conductor.
I have not seen it, but I haven't seen it either, but I, I, I just took them out of
the running because I went with the two classics in my mind.
Get back in the train yard, you little pig, you disgusting little piggy.
You call yourself a caboose.
Right. He, he was the conductor until he retired from public life, of course.
Like, you know, so he had to run, but then of course, as we all know,
Alec Baldwin retired from public life.
Yeah, we see those headlines every six weeks.
Like I'm not doing the conductor again.
I can't, they ask me, they ask me so over and over again and I can't, I can't.
It's hell for me.
I can't do it.
He got fired from the rail, the Sodor Railway because he kept trying to play words with
friends while he was conducting.
I'm trying to think of every Alec Baldwin scandal as quickly as possible.
Alec Baldwin crushes the larynx of a local photographer and then it's like,
I'm retiring from public life.
I do love his Mr. Conductor voice.
Hello, I'm Mr. Conductor.
I am the conductor.
And he makes that little, that little purse mouth.
Everyone loves to look at.
So Mr. Conductor, it's like, it's, it's such an accurate Mr. Conductor that he does.
That old mouth.
Emmy deserving, Emmy quality performance.
Oh, well here, if we're talking about, you know, sort of odd British children's characters.
What the hell's Beano Land?
What's going on with Beano Land?
All right, okay, let's roll up our sleeves because I feel like this is the final big
thing we have to tackle.
I'm going to change my background here.
Wait one second because I.
Oh yes, take us to Beano Land.
I found a.
British comics.
Yeah, so all right now, where is it?
Wait a second.
I got to find this.
So yeah, so the Beano and as far as I know, it still exists.
All right, here we go.
Yeah, still going.
Yeah.
All right.
Is is like I used to read it.
It's a little like paper cartoon that comes out every so often.
Is it weekly?
I that seems crazy.
It must have been.
It is weekly.
So crazy.
Because it's like.
Weekly magazines, weekly comics.
Magazines are still very popular in Britain.
That's how they got comic books over there after the war.
Exactly, and so it's existed for forever and it's like, I don't know, it's probably
like 16 pages long and it's sort of like one page for every one of the characters.
Maybe the small characters get half a page.
Dennis the Menace is the big character, but it is the British Dennis the Menace who has
no relationship to the American Dennis the Menace.
I think they were created independently and it was just because Dennis rhymes with menace.
But like what I feel like the American, they both have slingshots, but like the American
Dennis the Menace is pretty chill.
Like I don't think of him as like a dangerous boy.
He's kind of just like a bit of a prankster, whereas like the British Dennis the Menace
is terrifying.
Like he has black hair and this red and black stripes.
He has a dog called Nasher who is like who bites like that's why he's called Nasher.
And he like, I mean, and this is why I changed my background.
His enemy is a boy called Walter the Softie who is, you know, wants to like have tea parties
and like do his homework or whatever.
Like he's like a nerd, but he's specifically coded as like an effeminate little boy.
Like and I don't know if Britain has caught up to this and is now like, okay, all right,
we're going to like tone down the Softie stuff.
This is essentially just a comic about a heroic boy bullying a poor little effeminate boy.
But like when I was a kid, it was 100% like Dennis was like, right readers, you recruited me,
Walter the Softie, he's got to go.
We're going to get him.
Like that was 100% the vibe of Dennis the Menace.
And then there are other characters.
I mean, there's Roger the Dodger, there's Billy Wiz, there's Minnie the Minx.
Like it's like a lot of prankster kids.
It's that sort of like post-war British fantasy of like kids just like roaming around causing trouble.
You pull up a background.
Me not really understanding what Beano Land is.
And then my explanation that I'm offered is a sign that says no Softies.
That's Walter.
With a cross through it.
Okay.
That's Walter the Softie.
I don't know who this is.
I can't remember her name, but another Softie, I suppose.
And there's little, yeah, they're smiling.
And there's flowers floating near them, which I guess is what makes these characters Softies,
but they smile.
It's like if the cartoon Doug was about Roger the bully.
Yes.
And he was the hero, unambiguously the hero.
Right.
And you were just like, yeah, I want to see him beat the shit out of Doug.
Fuck Doug.
Which like, I almost admire it.
It's not like Dennis the Menace in America where it's like,
this kid's pretty anodyne.
He's not really causing any trouble.
Dennis the Menace in Britain is like, I am on the road to jail.
That is what's happening with me.
I don't want to go to school.
I just want to beat people up.
I want to be the kid who, if you see me coming around the corner, you cross the street.
Dennis the Menace, British Dennis the Menace, the star of Trainspotting 2.
Yes.
I mean, and like there's other characters, the Bash Street kids, I really liked them.
I remember like, and they're definitely pranksters.
Like they're a bunch of school kids who cause trouble.
But they're, Dennis is the only one I think of as being like malicious.
Usually they're more just pranksters or trying to stay one step ahead of the grownups or whatever.
I'm looking at Beano Land itself though, which I do remember visiting.
And it was basically just like a pretty simple, like they had some, what do you call them?
Dodger cars.
What do you, you know, what do you, geez, is there a bumper car?
Which they call Roger the Dodger's Dodgums.
Yeah, Roger the Dodger was like, he's a little kid, but he's like a huckster.
Like he was always like swindling people out of their money.
I don't know why he's called a Dodger especially.
And there was Billy's Whizzer, which was like one of those, you know, spinning,
you sit in a chair and you spin around rides.
Like the rides themselves seem pretty basic, but they just were sort of given the Beano skin.
The Beano skin.
It's just such a great example.
And when I was a little kid and I moved to Britain and I was like, look,
I got to get into British culture if I'm going to survive at school.
Like I'm going to need to know like what these kids are interested in.
So obviously I got into soccer, got into football because that's the easiest way to
have a conversation in Britain is to just know about football.
But the Beano, I was definitely buying the Beano to be like, I
guess this is what they like.
And I was like watching Saturday morning cartoon.
You know, I was just trying to sort of like get acclimated to this new kid culture.
So did you get into it successfully or was it just like, were you just tolerating it to get by?
I think I got into it.
I mean, the Beano, I think I quickly realized like, oh, people don't talk about the Beano.
Like I think I soon was like, I guess this is not cool anymore.
I would still buy it just because I don't know.
It was a kid. It was a comic book.
I liked any comic book, but Jason worries.
Oh, I was going to say the conflict for me is that Walter the softie is the antagonist.
From what I was reading, one of the other big weekly magazines, I think for kids is called Dandy.
So Dandy's cool, but softies are bad.
I'm so confused.
It's a fair question.
I don't know why it was called Dandy.
Dandy was like the other Beano and its main character was Desperate Dan,
who is like a cowboy with a giant chin.
I encourage you to Google him.
I was just looking at Desperate Dan.
Yes, who eats cow pies, which is like a whole pie with horns coming out of it.
So he's like some weird post-war parody of Americans where it's like
these Americans, they're all giant and all they do is eat.
And they're like these sort of like, you know, consuming, all consuming colossus people.
It's very strange.
He's kind of like a Paul Bunyan type, I guess.
Yeah.
I'm looking at other characters like Lord Snooty.
Lord Snooty.
Yeah.
Yeah, he was not cool by the time I, he's like a classic Beano character.
Right.
Bifo the Bear.
Okay, was he popular at that time?
No, those are like original Beano characters.
Ivy the Terrible, she was a big deal.
She was like a little kid, even smaller than the other kids and caused even more chaos.
But you know, where did, go ahead.
Sorry.
Where did, oh, I was going to say, where did Dan Dare run?
Did that run in, or that ran in something else?
That was its own thing.
But yeah, that right.
Because that was like, that's like action comics, right?
That was, I think that's very cool in the sixties and seventies.
And then Britain has that legacy of comic, like, because 2000 AD, right?
Obviously, like all that stuff.
Yeah.
Its own little sort of universe of, and so it's nice that there was a Beano land,
but I don't remember Beano land really being that exciting.
It doesn't look like it.
It didn't even like last 10 years.
They, they, they kind of got rid of it.
But was it?
Is it gone now?
Yeah, it's gone.
Yeah.
Well, does it make, does it make any sense that in the 2000s they go,
how do we get kids in here?
I know, Beano.
Beano.
It doesn't help that in America, Beano is like anti-fart medicine, right?
Like that is what Beano is here.
Yes.
I don't know why it's called Beano.
And we know this place, this park will do entire attractions based on soaps.
So why would they also do,
why not do an entire themed land to flatulence medicine?
I'm looking.
This is like the.
No, go ahead.
Yeah.
I was just going to say it's like the English Toon Lagoon, which is in Orlando,
which is all Kingfisher Syndicate comic strips.
I guess you could maybe argue those are a bit more relevant,
but how much more relevant?
I'm not sure how much more relevant Dagwood is in America.
But it's like, it's that kind of thing though, where you're like,
does this just exist?
Cause it's always existed.
Like, I know, like when I was a kid, I read the funny pages.
I don't so much anymore, but right.
Like as a kid, you're just like, yeah, I get it.
Dagwood, he likes big sandwiches.
Like that's just a thing that will never change.
Like if they got rid of it, it would be a problem.
But like, does anyone care about Dagwood anymore?
Has Dagwood caught up with the times?
No.
Yes.
He sees Dagwood making commentary on what's happening in the world today.
Right.
Like is Dagwood in quarantine?
Like for all I know, he is.
I don't know.
Honestly, now you've got me intrigued.
I would like to know how is he getting his food?
How is he getting his big sandwiches?
They still is blondie still preparing them?
Right.
Is he like not ordering take takeout?
He wants to take out.
He wants to wipe everything down before.
Has there been a shortage in big olives?
I'm looking at it looks like Dagwood still going to work and arguing with his boss.
So I guess he's not respecting quarantine at all.
Well, Dagwood and Blondie, unfortunately, are one of the couples who have broken up
in the midst of quarantine.
So they did not.
They did not make it.
Oh, God.
Yeah.
It'd be funny if you looked in all of the classic characters are dealing with COVID-19.
Like comics unilaterally have decided, yeah, we're going to.
We're making it happen in this world.
We got to show the reality.
I just tried to go a week back in Blondie and it asked me to go premium.
And I'm now I'm genuinely wondering how much it costs to get unlimited blondie in my life.
Like a blondie streaming service.
Blondie.
I'm on the same website.
We have to figure out how much this costs.
We're all going to share a subscription.
Is that allowed?
Share a go comics subscription.
No, no, we have to give it directly to Blondie.
Right.
We're only paying the CIA.
We're going to get a piecemeal it.
If you learned in comics world that John Arbuckle was past COVID-19 from Garfield,
cats can get it and transmit it.
Right.
And the Odie's safe.
Thank God.
But Garfield's been miserable lately.
They're all just staring at each other.
They had to quarantine.
They went to different houses.
Right.
And they were for a while, they were like, you know, they were putting Clorox onto the lasagna.
It was like a weird, you know, they were like, and then it was like, oh, we don't have to do that.
But the first few weeks were really stressful.
It's like, I didn't know we're getting information from every
Garfield was watching different YouTube videos than John was.
Look, okay.
Nermal.
Yes, she left the city.
She went in quarantine with the barnyard pals, but she quarantined for two weeks.
Okay.
She's not a super spreader.
Leave the box.
When Nermal gets to Abu Dhabi, leave the box outside for a full 24 hours
before bringing him in.
Excuse me.
Because you don't want the virus living on the Nermal box.
I used to hate Mondays, but now I don't even know what day it is anymore.
I guess I hate all days.
I have an answer for how much this service costs.
Hit me.
Blondie Plus?
It is $2 a month or $20 a year.
That's not that much.
And it's got 60,000 comics.
I mean, we're all charging more than that for the Patreon.
You know what?
I'm in quarantine.
I'm not really going out much.
I'm just going to go to the first issue of Blondie and get the first ever strip.
And we're just, we're going through it all.
Yeah, that's where this is heading.
We're all going to end up doing crazy things.
Like, yeah, I read, I read every Beano.
I went back to the beginning of Beano.
I didn't enjoy one second of it.
I didn't understand it.
I'm just, I have nothing to do.
A new podcast where we read a Beano every week and talk about it.
We're all going to have, we're all going to like do all this nonsense.
Comics from 1931 all the way up till now.
We'll all have multiple.
Every one of us is going to have five podcasts by the end of this.
There's no other choice.
Deconstructing Foxtrot.
I mean, like here's crazy and crazy and Ignatz and Jason Sheridan.
Here's what's weird about Beano.
Or here's, I guess this is the biggest indictment of Beano land is that
it was turned into an area called Wild Asia with all rides intact.
So like there was not a lot of work that needed to be done to revamp Beano land into Wild Asia.
Really?
All the same, you know, it has whatever bumper cars.
It's got a spinning around ride.
It's got all the stuff.
It's, it's better themed.
I'll give them that.
Like it all looks like ruins.
It's not that far from like Joe roadie animal kingdom.
Some of it's kind of well done.
Which interesting you bring that up, Scott, because there is a hotel here.
There's two wings of the hotel.
There's the newer Azteca hotel and then the Safari hotel, which seems very much like a more
budget conscious is the nice way to say it version of the animal kingdom lodge.
Like you get views of the giraffes and the animals and stuff in this Safari.
I'm seeing you can have the Gruffalo.
You can have a Gruffalo room.
With a well themed room over your, your, your bed.
Wow.
Yeah.
And in the, in our, one of our traditions on the show is making sure to distinguish
between very similar named things.
Chessington has a few things that we, we indulge in on the show.
One, they have a lot of long named rides like the Gruffalo river ride adventure.
Their Safari ride is called zoo, Fari dash ride into Africa.
But I want to be very clear that it is not the restaurant in the hotel.
That's the Fari bar and chill.
So zoo Fari is not the Fari.
They just changed the second letter, but those are different things.
That's a very confusing one.
Is it because they have pizza like za?
No.
Looks like a pretty regular old place.
Yes.
They have a full, they have an English breakfast in buffet form.
You can do a full English in a buffet.
That's a thing at European hotels, I believe.
Right. They include breakfast in your stay.
At least here it is.
I don't know if it's widespread, but you don't necessarily get a big cow pie,
cow pie, much bigger than you like desperate Dan would eat.
No, but the guys from Madagascar are around sometimes, it seems like.
What? Yes.
Why is desperate Dan desperate?
Is it for friends?
I mean, he has plenty of food.
It shouldn't be food.
One cow pie you'd have to imagine could last him a week.
Right.
Well, we'll have to investigate that further.
I'm looking at another.
I'm looking at another thing where he's said there's other foods around him.
One of them is owl hoot juice.
OK.
Also, you guys should just see this, too.
Let me let me share the screen.
This is some very odd.
I'm dealing with weird sodas, got owl hoot juice, got rocky mountain rock cakes,
grizzly stew, cactus soup and rattlesnake rings.
And the whole family of mice are like eating underneath him.
Like, do you think there's so much runoff from a desperate Dan meal
that there's like colonies of mice?
And he's got a cactus in the shape of his own head.
He's a pretty cool guy.
I don't think I like desperate Dan.
I don't know if Dandy still, I think Dandy died.
I think Beano survives partly maybe just out of nostalgia,
like it's sort of like an institution.
But I think the Dandy is now defunct.
OK.
Does it have does Dandy have a tombstone?
Yeah, they buried it right next to Zappomattoch.
I guess if we're winding down here, I think, you know, a question we're
trying to figure out with this whole Europe month recovering places we haven't been to.
And we're wondering if we were if any of the three of us were to take
a real European vacation and, you know, eight years or so from now,
were we to go to the place you live for a long time in England?
Is this worth is it worth a trip to Chessington?
Should we make time to actually go there?
Were we to do a British vacation?
I think yes.
I think you should do it.
And I think part of the argument is that you could very easily combine it with Thorpe Park
or Legoland, like any any nearby British theme park.
Like there's a few down there.
If you had well, I know I think it's worth it.
I think it would be better to go to Chessington for this show
than Alton Towers, where you would just ride a bunch of, you know, very professional rides.
But maybe there's a little less weirdness to dig into.
If you're going to Britain, Chessington, it's a day trip.
Like, you know, you can be in London, you can do other stuff, and then you can, like,
devote one day to Chessington and easily conquer it.
Sure, sure.
If we were to go to Chessington, what kind of flowers would we lay at the grave site
of Zappomattox to pay our respects?
Poppies.
Do you lay a poppy?
Do we wear the poppy?
That is, of course, a classic in memoriam.
Yes, for Brits, yes.
We could start a tradition.
We could turn Zappomattox's grave into like kind of a happen and scene,
Jim Morrison's grave, you know, where people drink and party and have sex on it and graffiti it and
stuff. Although I think it's probably been blocked from doing that for a long time.
But yeah, you know, we can turn it into a spot of rivalry.
Yeah, it sounds smashing.
I will say I feel like they're trying to keep away too many guys like us,
because when I tried to look up like book your trip and I tried to do more than one night,
it broke the website.
Like it would not let me put it.
Maybe you don't want to do that.
Yeah, it's like, all right, all right, back off, podcaster.
So they made the decision for you, I guess.
So perhaps one night and no more is suitable.
One, because they give you the second day free.
A lot of these British parks right now are doing like buy a night and then you get a second ticket
for the day you check out.
I will say real quick, I was on the website looking around and I know this is probably
just a change of terminology from us to England or it's just a difference.
But it says a magical short break awaits, and it's Santa Claus.
And it says plan ahead and make your family's Christmas wishes come true with a magical
short break at Chessington World of Adventures Resort.
Your overnight festive package includes access to the resort's Christmas event.
Meet and greet with Father Christmas in his grotto.
They have stuck to Father Christmas.
That is still what Father Christmas and he has a grotto.
He's got a grotto.
Not a cabin.
He has a grotto.
So he's got a grotto.
All the guys are in there.
You know, Jimmy Khan.
Scott Khan in the grotto.
I'm reading it looks like they are not making you wear a mask right now, but there are certain
rides that you have to wear a mask on, such as the Gruffalo River Ride Adventure.
You have to wear, though you do have to wear a sex mask in Santa's grotto.
That's like a nice white shirt thing.
You got to wear like a Harvard.
Exactly.
All the stars.
Everybody's hanging out there.
Professor Burp is hanging out and they'll be, you know, he set up since he got kicked out,
he set up his juice jacuzzi in Father Christmas grotto.
And then sometimes they'll be just like a little bit of a little bit of a bubble up
and people go, oh, geez, Professor Burp Spartan again.
And Desperate Dan is in the corner just eating a big pie.
Prince Andrew.
He can't sweat, though he has a problem.
He can't be sweating, though.
So you won't know if he's nervous or not.
Sorry, we didn't even mention the connection to a very recent episode we did before we went abroad.
Um, it, Chesington is owned by Merlin Entertainment, which owns Alton Towers,
Madam Tussauds, Legoland, Gardaland in Italy and Sea Life Aquarium.
And I bring this up because Sea Life Aquarium was one of the attractions
slotted for the American dream in beautiful New Jersey.
Oh, the mall, the New Jersey Mall.
Oh, wow.
This entity, Merlin Entertainment was going to create the New Jersey
Mall Aquarium.
Have you been, David, have you been bothered by this American dream thing
in any tangible way being out on that coast?
I'm bothered by it.
Is it going to start like affecting my day to day life?
Is that part of the plan?
How I imagine it is that all New Yorkers are just furious about this thing all the time,
throwing rocks at it.
Right.
Like it stinks.
It's emanating a smell that makes its way to your apartment.
It's near the like the the giant stadium, right?
The MetLife Stadium, right?
I have not.
I have been affected by American dream.
Well, I'm praying that you will have the opportunity to go there and to see some fish, I guess.
And I don't know, maybe, you know, Santa's Grotto could get built there as well.
It's like a good way to attract some attracts and people as their mall fails in the case.
Awesome.
Well, this has been a lot of fun.
What a fun, indeed, a world of adventures to check out David Sims, he survived podcast,
The Ride.
Thanks for joining us on our European expedition.
Let's exit through the gift shop.
Is there anything you'd like to plug?
Thank you guys for having me.
It was really a delight to find a way to fit into this podcast.
Which I believe I host Blank Check Griffin and David's movie podcast.
I'm sure Griffin has mentioned it, obviously, when he's on
where we go through directors filmographies.
And yeah, you can read I'm a film critic at the Atlantic.
You can read my stuff there.
Not that there are many movies to write about right now, but we're doing our best.
That's me.
Yeah.
Are you doing like do you have to like come up with a thousand ways to do like remember when?
And yeah, 1999, some good movies.
Blood from a stone at this point.
I think you should just keep writing about do little until the pandemic is over.
Yes, that's what I'll swing back around to do a little.
A 10 part essay on extraction.
Well, and I'll say, hey, we just found one.
Be no land is is waiting for you.
I'm sure I'm sure you're going to enjoy and explain the be to everybody.
As many essays as possible.
And oh, wait, guys, I forgot we have to get now that we have covered England,
we have to get our passport stamped.
And there it is.
Cook chunk.
What is what does that look like?
Well, I think this actually resembles Jason.
I think this is Jason in his new mode as the height miser.
Or it's it's it's it's like a new form of of Jason.
He's got very high hair, just like the heat miser from whatever that Christmas thing is.
Yeah, he looks he looks great.
And his eyebrows are going up real high, again, indicating how much he loves his height.
And and he's smiling a big smile that honestly kind of resembles our pal.
Wait, why did I forget the name of the robot?
Or is that dramatic?
Diplomatic.
He's smiling a big smile.
You know what?
I'll take it because I've been really worried this whole time.
Staring, looking at Walter the softy, going like, oh, no, another theme park character.
I resemble Walter the softy.
No, you're your own character.
You're the height miser.
I'll take it from.
Well, I thought you should play.
Who was the guy who would trick people from Beano Roger the Dodger?
I thought you were more of a Roger the Dodger, Jason.
Oh, that's fair.
Yeah.
So honestly, although Jason could play any of the Beano characters, let's be.
You know, on my one thousand episode, Beano podcast, you know,
when we all have conflicting Beano podcast, Beano dissection podcast.
Sure.
There'll be plenty of time to sort all of this out.
Hey, as for us and for the rest of our European vacation, keep following us
and our progress on Twitter, on Instagram and our Facebook group.
And you can join us for bonus day trip day excursions over at the second gate
at Patreon dot com slash podcast.
The ride we just went to to Popeye Village.
Also not that far out from Griffin's last appearance on the show.
I don't know if you know this.
Griffin Griffin broke the record.
We always knew it was his to break longest episode now over on the second gate
about race through New York with Jimmy Fallon.
Where's your guys record at this?
But you've you've gone over three hours.
I think it over three hours.
God, and we just just yesterday we did another one that was insanely long.
And it's like one of those things where like now it's just like,
well, if we do under two hours, we're going to like, I mean, what are we even doing here?
Like, it's we used to do an hour long episodes and it was fine.
I don't know what we've done to ourselves.
Bruce Springsteen concert.
Just as good.
We all have just as much talent.
That's what I have to have the charisma.
We're all as a Super Bowl halftime show.
There will be some where we're still stuck in this in January.
The Super Bowl halftime show will be just like cutting different podcasters.
Now a thousand zooms.
So now a thousand zooms.
Oh, boy.
Well, anyway, yeah, lots of hours of content available over there.
Hey, and if we missed anything about any of these parks,
sure to let us know an email us at podcast, right at gmail.com.
Anything else, Mike and Jason?
No, I just just keep that Zapomatic in your prayers, I guess.
Yeah.
And watch out for gourds and watch out for gore.
Watch out.
Gourds.
Oh, I don't know.
Gorgs.
OK, it is Gorgs.
Watch out for Gorgs.
Gorgs.
You like watch out for Gorgs.
Well, there you never know what's going on in those squashes, you know.
Decorative gourds are very scary.
Gorgs.
Good tip to live your life.
Bye.
All right.
See you next week.
We'll go elsewhere.
And you're actually going to stay around this neck of the woods,
perhaps the British Isles, if that's a little bit of a clue.
And we'll talk to you next week.
Bye bye.
Bye.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a Forever Dog production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Silio, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit ForeverDogPodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple Podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at ForeverDogTeam and liking our page on Facebook.