FOREVER!
DOG!
Benvenuto to Podcast the Rides European Vacation hosted by three guys who are
excited even to take a fake trip. I'm Scott Gardner. Mike Carlson's here as well.
I am here. I'm ready to virtually travel.
Yes.
Which is the best we can do.
Get a breath of digital fresh air. Jason Sheridan, you excited?
Hey Mambo, Mambo Italiano. That's what I say, at least for today's episode.
I guess I'll have to figure out some other country specific thing as we go along.
Yeah, that's what I figured. We'll all learn some fun greetings. We'll let you know where we're going right at the top of all of them.
Because, gang, we're spending the whole month of August in virtual Europe. This is going to be great.
We're getting out of here. As we've said, we've been cooped up. The three of us have been cooped up.
You listening at home have been cooped up. And there's lots of things that are off the table for us to do, including going to Europe.
Americans can't really do that. Rightfully so. It's the most correct, I think, painting there could ever be.
As we're really fucking this thing up. But you know what? They can't put regulations on. It's our imagination.
So we're going to take a vacation in our imagination, all of us together. And I couldn't be more excited to do it.
I think that you should, yeah, maybe if you're a listener and you're at home, maybe get a cocktail.
Maybe listen to this outside, wear a tank top. You know, all the things you do during the summer months during a vacation.
You know, I really want everyone to feel this with us. I want it to be a sensory experience.
It's a virtual reality trip you're taking.
And if today's episode is any indication, start off right off the bat by ignoring any copyright trademark.
Just throw any knowledge you have that out the window.
Yes, we're also taking a vacation from copyright laws with today's topic.
Potentially safety regulations, too.
It sure looks like it. It sure looks like it. Videos and photos.
We'll get into where we're going today and where we're kicking it off.
But I want to say a couple things just right off the top about what this month is going to consist of.
And you know, because another thing we're taking a little vacation from is our usual areas on the show.
And I'll tell you this in this month of August, no Disney, no Universal, no Six Flags.
We're not doing any of the usual shit.
And we I think we couldn't be starting more off brandy than than where we're starting today.
Yes, I mean, I look it's a it's a fake Universal Studios.
I'll just say it. That's what we're doing today.
But we're so we're going to get a little of the flavor, but the flavor is off.
It's slightly it tastes weird, but it's not bad.
It just tastes a little weird. It's exactly like a type of food that doesn't really translate in another plate.
Like if you guys have had the experience of having Mexican food in a place that is where Mexican food is not native, that's how this that's how this perk feels.
It feels like they technically followed the recipe of Universal Studios, but just I don't know.
It's not in their DNA. They just it wasn't in them to get it right.
It feels like somebody went maybe to Universal like five, ten years ago and they're like, we need you to design a park.
And they're like, yeah, I think I remember there's dinosaurs.
There's like that arch thing. OK, yeah, yeah.
Let me sketch something out here for you and I'll have it to you tomorrow.
Which is weird. Weird is I think that's what I want out of this series.
And we're certainly getting it today. I'm a little I'm a little worried.
I'm sure it'll all work out. I'm a little worried that this is episode is kind of like if you introduce the concept of Chekhov's gun and you're like, hey, check off.
Check out Chekhov's gun. Bang, bang, bang, bang.
Like you just are immediately show the gun and just immediately start firing it in the air.
This is so weird.
You might be right, but I also would say, you know, this whole series that we're doing this month, the things we're talking about later,
it's going to get weirder. I think it's going to be weirder.
There's other things coming out that some you might be familiar with.
You might not be that are super weird.
Every one of them that we that we've talked about, because we kind of know our itinerary, some of them charmingly.
So it's I don't know, but I think that's this has always been my assumption about European theme parks is that they are weird.
I don't like and you none of them are that famous in a way like like we're pretty big theme park heads.
We haven't found ourselves really ever talking about European parks to much of an extent before.
Yeah, I mean, I don't know if this is maybe just our American bias or the fact that there's such prominent American parks that they've set the standard.
And now we look at these and we go, it's so weird.
And it's just because we're used to something.
I would be interested to hear from people who live in Europe.
Do you think these parks are weird as as we do?
Or do you think our parks are weird?
Maybe you think we're about to talk about today is perfectly normal.
And you've been to Universal Florida and you go, well, this isn't anything like the place we're about to talk about.
Yeah, which I am hiding. I don't know why I'm hiding.
Yeah, I know. Yeah, we could say I think maybe I'm just wanting to talk through anything else about the theme parks.
Anything else about the Europe thing in general, which one thing that we might want to say at the top is that after some discussion and some some reflection and looking inward, we have decided we're not going to do Efteling.
Might be good to get that out of the way.
Right. Because unlike let's just say I think every place that we're talking about this month, none of us have personally been to.
We're breaking Doug Jones rule that watching videos isn't the same as going there.
And I know that. But hey, look, we're not getting to Europe anytime soon.
So we're doing we can't.
I mean, I've scoured a lot of websites.
But anyway, Efteling felt like somebody's got to go.
One of the three of us has to go for us to do it justice.
Yeah, that's yes. That's such a big heavy hitter.
And probably it definitely has a lot of substance, but maybe not enough madness that I think we're all right in the.
Like I had so much fun reading about this park.
I have to say that I think if it had a little more substance, I would have less fun.
I'll go out and say we're not doing to like to Voli Gardens either.
The one that Walt Disney like walked in and inspired him.
We have we made him. Scott, to your credit.
I mean, we talked about a bunch, but Scott, you made a massive list.
So, yeah, yeah. Well, with with some listener help because we threw it out there.
If we were going to go to Europe, where would you want us to go?
A lot of you said Efteling and we're ignoring you. I'm sorry.
But again, you can see also there was so many specifically campaigning and saying you should not go to Efteling.
Because you need to experience it for yourself.
And we bought that argument and we were kind of feeling that anyway.
But yeah, we considered a lot.
And I actually think what you'll find there, I think there's some parks that seem like fine and good and solid.
But, you know, if you listen to this podcast for a while, you know, maybe that's not the best meat on the boat.
We need the most shitty, bizarre, miscolored meat to be on a bone that's falling apart.
That's what we want to eat.
Yes, I guess I agree. Jason, sorry.
It's a good turn of phrase because there is some shitty, discolored meat coming later in this episode.
Absolutely. Yes. Yes. Dear God, the food.
Well, you want to just let's just throw it out.
Let's let's start talking about it.
But although you know, another what's tough about saying where we're going today is like, what is it called?
Really? There's like four names.
Yeah, there's a lot of names.
What do you think it's called?
All right. We're all going to say it at the same time what we think it is and see if we're all on the same page.
OK. OK. One, two, three.
Movieland. Hollywood par.
Movieland.
Kanavel world.
OK. OK. Kanaver.
I think Kanavel world is the whole property, right?
Yes. Right.
And we are all the only thing on it.
They put Italy in the name.
I kind of say that on the website I'm looking at.
OK. I've seen it elsewhere with Italy is in the specific spot.
And they have a water park.
And the movieland, the Hollywood park is what what we're focusing on.
And what you do now, what you just called it.
But what I decided to say out loud was movieland studios.
Yes, I've seen movieland studios somewhere, too.
But I've also seen movieland park.
And then I saw a video where there is a stormtrooper.
People are taking footage with a stormtrooper.
And on his stormtrooper uniform, it says movie studios in the same font that we've come to know from this park.
So that's the most off.
And in general, you know, not to blow our load on this yet, but a stormtrooper character, there is no way they have permission to use.
Absolutely not.
They can't.
There is so left and right.
There's unlicensed music, I'm pretty sure.
Like on rides, there's full rides that are very much based on properties.
There's no way they have because the properties are owned by the biggest entities that we're ignoring for this month.
That is universal.
Yeah, I just to give an example of what we're talking about, there is a ride here that is like sort of like a big humvee sort of like Jeep ride.
If you imagine the vehicles used on the Kilimanjaro safaris in Animal Kingdom, and I watched some vloggers who toured this park.
And when they were on that ride, that ride was clearly playing the song The Call to Adventure, which is the entry music for islands of adventure.
Oh, well, not even taking music from movies, but from theme parks from theme parks.
Right.
So, yeah, just to give you an idea, if you're not looking at the Internet, the park looks like it has a very familiar like arch, I guess you'd call it, that looks exactly like the entrance to Universal Studios.
And yet more plastery and like the shape is weird.
It's like the difference between, you know, they go into it in the Imagineering documentary, how like that Golden Gate Bridge in California Adventure was just not it was just two plastic fake Lego.
And there just wasn't the mat like that's that's how kind of everything in this place.
Oh, yeah, this is like this is it truly like feels like you're having one of those like dreams slash nightmares of like you're in universal, but it's not right.
It doesn't feel correct.
Something's wrong and everything feels like fake and you're not really there.
It's like, yeah, it's it's strange.
Right on. Yeah.
This if I could recommend a video, I mean, you know, I think Mike, as you're saying, if you go to the website, you'll get a vibe.
There's one that that really helped me a good summation statement.
I think if you if you look up a video on YouTube, Movieland Park 2018, it's from the user Parksmania.it.
If you just want a little like fly through, that helps a lot, including just one thing that illuminated for me was that how much the entrance like you said, it's the big universal gate.
And not only that, but it's very much the universal Florida main drag like they didn't go.
You know, other weird foreign theme parks like in China have ripped off Main Street.
But this is like that that drag that ends in the in the New York facade and there's little businesses on the side.
And instead of the Today Show Cafe or whatever, I really like this that there's an ice cream shop in a familiar font and it says ice stone creamery.
I have that too. Which what is what does that mean?
What's an ice stone ice cube, an ice cube that they cut ice cubes and put them in cones for you.
Did you did you look is there a video of it inside the ice stone creamery?
I haven't seen a comprehensive review of ice stone creamery.
No, I can I can look for such though.
I'll look it up because I I wonder if even they have because the cold stone, of course, the big draw,
which we all love about cold stone is that big cold slab where they make your ice cream concoction.
I wonder if they even have that in ice stone creamery.
Like, is it just copying the name or do they also have a different type of cold stone ice stone?
I might guess that they don't even have ice cream there.
Again, ice stone is like a trick.
That's like calling crab crab with a K.
Maybe they just have like flavored ice.
I'm going to text you guys another.
This is a sign from a video I watched of a restaurant that you can find here.
And their advertisement in the window is just a giant poster that says club sandwich.
Cool. One word.
Run to get no space between club and sandwich club sandwich daily fresh.
Yeah, I was watching a video.
I was watching I forget which YouTube video I was watching people eating this sandwich and they were over the moon about it.
They loved it. Really?
I just because I've been in my apartment for so long.
I was like, that looks good.
I would love to. Yeah.
A sandwich in a hundred degree heat in the middle of Italy right now.
I watched an hour long video about this park like this couple who are vloggers.
The you can look them up on YouTube.
A very pleasant couple.
They said they're from northeast England.
I watched the same video.
I thought Tom and Stace.
Did you watch Tom and Stace?
Yes, I also watched Tom and Stace. Yes, I saw them.
I like Tom and Stace and I have to give them credit because so they this park is in a part of Italy called Lake.
Lake Garda Lake Garda Lago di Garda.
This is not this is the second theme park in the big theme park is called Gardaland in Lago di Garda.
Yes, and which seems better.
Yeah, they went to both.
OK, and I have to they they were pretty good at like as soon as they walked at this park.
They're like, well, this is the Universal Studios gates.
So we didn't really read a lot about this park.
So we're going to be surprised.
And Gardaland definitely looks more polished, but this one definitely looks weirder.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I mean, we couldn't stay away from this.
Oh, wait. And we haven't talked about why we landed on this.
And in fact, the entire Europe series, which was a discovery from Mike back in the episode stunt show showdown to would you care to remind us?
What what you found? What brought us here to glorious movie land?
Well, it was a I was I it was a stunt show in my mind.
It was really it was a little show based on the movie Flashdance, which it was a bit unusual in the year whatever.
Twenty I forget which video that maybe twenty sixteen twenty fifteen was what it was from.
And it was just like one single performer loosely mimicking the dance moves from the movie Flashdance with a small crowd.
And that's where I learned what I learned about movie world or movie studio or movie land studios.
The Hollywood the Hollywood Park.
And we started looking at some of the other rides and immediately we were like, oh, this this feels like that we would like to look at this look at more of these.
Yeah, which now knowing more, I think we totally went the right way because that thing in general is a little encapsulation of what it is.
Like also Flashdance.
Well, I guess they just must have struck oddly struck a deal with whoever the distributor is.
Is it MGM or some I don't know where make made Flashdance.
But OK, so they tried to pull a thing out of it, but I don't think so.
I don't think they have the rights to anything.
Oh, yeah. I don't think they've ever used.
At first I was like, oh, interesting. They licensed all this stuff.
And then I was like, wait a minute, there's a ride based on a TV show that they don't use the name of the TV show.
They use the name of the vehicle on the TV show.
Yes. Yeah.
Although even that hat like it does have.
Did you watch any video of that ride?
I sure did.
I.
It's awesome.
I mean, yes. Yeah. And you know what?
This is why this place got a little bit of press because of this ride.
Oddly, I saw an L.A. Times article about it.
It's sort of shockingly so because this does look good.
Oh, what we're talking about is called Kit Super Jet, which is a delight to me.
I'm a big Knight Rider fan, a big Hasselhoff fan.
And this is a world where I don't know if they actually convey this in a video or anything.
I can't tell because I don't speak Italian.
But I think that they may have overlaid the premise that Kit, the alive car voiced by William Daniels in America,
that is, has teleported his presence into a big boat instead,
which is a funny, you know, being that the Simpsons did Nightboat, which is obviously a Knight Rider parody.
So Nightboat is real here and it's called Kit Super Jet.
And the the rides, it's interesting because it's it's like the kind of thing you would do
if you travel to a place like with a lake or where you go near waterfalls.
You know, this is like a touristy, like, you know, exciting boat ride that you would do and like do a little like hour long class for
and then get your life vest and then, you know, and then go see some place of beauty.
It's more akin to like we're going, you know, mild snorkeling in Hawaii or something.
But instead.
Instead, where the ride takes you is the OK.
Listeners, you know, the Waterworld stunt show at Universal, we know with a like a lagoon and some sets and some stands.
And it is basically this boat takes you.
Imagine you're going into the Waterworld arena and just doing donuts in it.
You're not out on the lake on Lake Garda, a legitimately beautiful looking lake that is mere feet away.
You're just doing donuts in the arena for a different attraction, which I guess they just have to not operate at the same time.
It's like it's like your buddy stole a boat and he somehow got it into the Waterworld stunt show.
And you're just going to like just see what you can do in there for a while.
There's not like much of a plan.
You're just going to he's going to like kind of start to scare the shit out of you.
Like, hey, man, you you scared you scared of this.
What we're doing in here. This feels wrong, doesn't it?
And you're like, yeah, it does. Please stop. We're not supposed to be in this stunt show.
And then like, well, wait, the see this.
And then it's just the same thing you already did over here.
Like, well, then you get like more used to it. You're like, this is stupid, but it's not actually that scary.
We've just been going in a circle.
It is so bizarre. This experience is so bizarre.
You, of course, saw that there is an original video.
Yeah, yes. Yes. Music to my eyes.
There is a there is a pre-ride video that I think come if you think you get a tape of it after the fact, which people posted on YouTube before you go.
You get a little like, you know, send off greeting from David Hasselhoff himself, which maybe doesn't sound like a big deal because he's like a shady guy who does weird European stuff all the time.
However, it's a big deal for this park because as far as I can tell, there's no other instance of an actor of any renown appearing in an attraction in movie land world.
Yeah, I didn't see it. I didn't see any other version of this.
It took it took a second to find this. I found saw it in one brief glimpse of it in one video, and then I found a slightly better version of it in another.
He's wearing a Don't Hassle the Hoff shirt.
Yes, which I guess rules out him being Michael Knight, his character from Knight Rider, because I guess he is David Hasselhoff, not which again, maybe you're right again that they never licensed Knight Rider because that's NBC Universal.
Right. So they just reached out to Hasselhoff and gave him six hundred dollars and off they went.
Yeah, you just like somebody came up to him like outside his house and was like, hey, here's here's six hundred dollars.
Would you just say these these words into this camera phone?
And then he's like, yeah, all right, I'll do it.
Let me just finish wrapping up with the other European film crew that I'm filming with right now.
And then let's you know, let me I can only give you 10 minutes because I got five more of these coming later today.
He is he does. Yes, he does intros across Europe, I assume, for most theme park rides.
It's odd. It's the whole thing is odd because it's a boat.
Like, why? Why did this need to be Knight Rider?
Why is this Knight Rider?
Well, because it's a boat that's doing jumps and stunts and spinning around.
It doesn't appear. I think the video I watch, it doesn't look like there are seat belts in the boat, but you do have to put on a life vest.
And on top of all that, the arena definitely does, yes, look like the water world arena.
And the show that goes on in there is simultaneously referred to on their website as US Army Stunt Show.
But when you pull up a video preview, the logo is changed and says John Rambo stunt show.
So I'm a little confused.
So they run shows in here in addition to running a ride through it.
So that's like I'm so confused.
It's as if the Universal Water World show.
It's like, OK, it's water world at three o'clock.
Then we run 20 groups of boats through it and then we do another water world show after.
Maybe I like it now that I'm saying it out loud.
Maybe I actually like this because how cool would it be to ride through water world?
Yeah, it would be actually awesome.
I'm at the atolls. I'm right next to the atolls, baby.
But they have more space water where I've been told the water well backstage doesn't complete a full circle.
Jason, I don't give a shit. I don't give a shit how much space is.
I want to drive a fucking motorboat around the water world set.
I don't care how small it is.
If the water world boat, like if something happens or a piece flies off, it will fly at a six story office building.
Up into a window. Yes.
Yeah, into a window room where I interviewed to be a tour guide.
I think there was a water world show going on during my interview and it really threw me.
If we could take one of those boats, I mean, I don't know how we would transport it.
One of the tiny boats you and I drove drove around in on the Seven Seas Lagoon in Florida.
If you take one of those boats into the water world set, that would fit better.
It would fit better.
Well, all these places are going to be in dire straits when they open again.
So I want these. I want weird like that on top of admission, you pay, you know, an awkward amount.
You pay $18 to put around in a paddle boat at water.
I think they're going to need it. Yes.
More things to do in each ride like in Transformers, like you can eat like you can eat a meal just like sitting on the side of one of the scenes in Transformers.
And that's an extra upcharge.
And when you're done, when you finish the whole meal, Optimus Prime tells you he's proud of you.
You have you have cleaned your plate. Congratulations, Michael.
I couldn't be prouder of you. I love you.
You finished an entire family style meal. Didn't have to throw out one morsel of it.
You have not wasted any food. You are my son. You are one with the earth.
And Michael, you're right. They should have a smaller family size plate for one.
You were right all along. Your opinions are correct.
Yeah, they're running a bad business.
You know, since you bring up ideas to the drum up business for parks worldwide when they start to reopen,
I think they should look to movie land, the Hollywood Park and their policy.
They're posted on a side policy of wait 30 minutes and we give you back the ticket.
So if you wait 30 minutes in line for something, you can come back the next day for free.
Hell, yeah. They have like a like a pizza delivery guarantee. Yes.
Wow. Like 30 minutes or your your next pizza is free.
The only thing is, I did not really see any lines for any of these rides. Maybe a 10 minute line.
For them to make that guarantee, you know, it's almost impossible to wait longer, like 30, anything close to 30 minutes.
Because if they were having lines that were 25 minutes, that's not a guarantee you would want to make because you're just giving away tickets.
So they must be confident that these lines are not longer than five to 10 minutes consistently.
They're probably also confident that no one would want to come back the next day.
You know, or yes, or you're right. All the lines are extremely long sometimes and no one's ever taken them up on this.
This has never been something that's been cashed in.
We'll pay you. We'll pay you twenty dollars to come back. No, it's fine. Don't worry about it.
We're good. We did the boat. We're good.
I have a kind of a broader theory, but you know, with that John Rambo show as a case study, I think, you know, where it became it was started as John Rambo became US Army stunt show.
And there's other examples of things like this that had a theme and now don't have a theme.
And I think maybe that's what's happened to the entire park.
I think they opened very boldly with a ton of IP and they have slowly stepped them down.
And I don't know because there aren't even any Google results for this.
So it's all off the table and never hit the press.
But what I'm imagining in my head is that they just like, yeah, let's just see what we can get away with.
And then as IP owners started bothering them, they just pulled them one at a time.
And some of that theory came from I thought about busting out a very handy tool, the way back machine where you can see what websites used to look like.
And I found I think this is from this park in 2005 or 2006.
Let me throw it up for you guys to see.
Look at this frame.
There's a lot here and a lot that I don't think that I had.
I certainly didn't find because none of this has been in the park in the 2010s.
We talked a little bit about this, I think, on the episode with the stunt shows, because I saw a picture that was not this picture, but it had it clearly a Doc Brown in the picture.
Yes, there is some and they pushed the Doc Brown presence as far as it would go.
But let's just call out things as we see them.
Doc Brown is in this picture and he's standing next to poison Ivy from Batman and Robin.
Very much Uma Thurman.
There's no mistaking that version of poison Ivy.
It's Uma Thurman from Batman and Robin.
With a human face and she is several.
She is one Doc and several stormtroopers away from a joker with a big plastic face whose chin goes down below his armpits.
So you have a plastic joker mixed with real walk around a poison Ivy.
Right. That's not Jack Nicholson joker.
That is like, is that Brian Boland killing joke joker from Jason from the graphic novel?
Yeah, let me look a little closer.
It's similar to that.
That's an artist.
I had like a pencil with like an eraser cap with a joker head.
That's what it is. It's like it's a it's a plastic eraser head joker.
That's how generic of a joker it is.
It is a very generic joker.
Who is who's next to who's grinding on the joker next to him?
He's in a big.
Boa.
Cruella De Vil.
Could be. It's very small.
So it's hard to tell, but she might like she looks like an alive version of Madame, the puppet of Wayland Flowers.
Oh, yeah, like the fancy lady ventriloquist.
Of course, of course.
And then you got a Ghostbuster singular.
But not in a bad, a really bad looking outfit.
Yeah, yeah, that's that's weak.
The stormtrooper outfits are like perfect, but this Ghostbuster looks like he's just got like loose paint clothes, like loose birthday party Ghostbuster.
Yeah, you got a Burton Batman.
You got a Zorro.
Yeah, you got blues brothers, blues brothers.
I sent you guys something in the chat.
I'm not sure if it went through right, but probably an property that we're all excited to see in this park.
You know it, you love it.
It's the Academy Award winning film, The Artist.
What? Wait, I miss this.
Huh?
Standing in front of the poster, two people like dancing, some text in both Italian and English that reads, My heart burns with passion.
What if pirates captured both of us?
What?
Hang on, I haven't gotten this up yet.
Huh?
What if I can't wrap my head around that phrase at all?
What if pirates captured both of us?
I'm just trying to remember, is that one of the cards in the movie?
No fact, no human being has watched The Artist since 2012.
Yeah.
It has not once been in a DVD player.
It's not on any streamers, none of them bought it.
Once those Oscars were done, we were done with this film.
We're out of there.
Yeah, conversely, I found in the movie land Facebook group a number of pictures of not just storm troopers, but Chewbacca, Darth Vader, Kylo Ren.
And I was like, well, surely this is a Halloween event where people can dress up.
And I realized, oh, it appears these were posted in the official Facebook group by the official Facebook group account.
So, yeah, and then, of course, that other character you want to see in a family amusement park, Uma Thurman's, the bride from Quentin Tarantino's Kill Bill.
Hell, yeah.
Two Thurmans.
How many more?
I wonder if there are more Thurmans lurking.
Who else could it be?
The Avenger, you know, the other Avenger, the British Avengers.
Truth About Cats and Dogs, Thurman?
Oh, there isn't.
OK, at least in a poster form, I saw a wall of posters in this park and right big center was a Gattaca poster.
No way.
That's a Thurman.
Whoa, that's a Thurman.
There's a room that's a closet that's just a TV playing Letterman's Oscar monologue.
He said Oprah, Uma, Uma, Oprah.
That's a Thurman.
Oh my God, can you imagine if the late shift characters were in this park?
Oh, man, with that, well, just like paint over that Joker mask they can't use anymore and make it J.
Yeah.
Just paint flesh colors over it instead of white.
Wow.
That would be great.
So, yeah, they're they're they are just spitting in the face of any sort of copyright law.
Oh, and well, you know, the one that I missed also, Mary Poppins and Burt.
And only them, only that.
There's no other Disney.
I mean, maybe a smattering throughout the rest of their history.
But in this photo, I mean, isn't that an odd only them?
You don't go with like Donald Duck or something.
Yeah, I don't.
There's no rhyme or reason why unless they like did a poll or something.
And it's like those characters, Mary Poppins is English.
Maybe there's a European for the British.
The British tourists like that.
Yeah.
Maybe this is like weird off brand Halloween costumes and they can reasonably say if Disney comes and complains,
they can say, no, no, no, that is Parasol, Madam and straw hat Phil.
These are original creations we saved over them.
Yeah, yeah, I see what you're saying that it looks similar.
I do see that.
But this is a totally different you have to hear them talk to they sound different, totally different backstory.
Are you going to say that it is illegal for a woman to carry a parasol?
If so, how many women across this planet will get scorched on a hot bay?
Mm hmm.
Disney, this is unreasonable.
I would love to see their like shady lawyer arguing this with like the Disney lawyers.
Look, I don't know what to tell you.
We can't you can't copyright that jacket that our character that suit jacket that Bert wears and Mary Poppins.
I can wear it.
You can assume me.
You can't sue me.
The width on the stripes is much different than the width on this Bert, was it?
I'm sorry, I'm not familiar with the film.
If we stay in the Disney area, maybe the funniest ride to talk about is in the photo that I'm looking at.
And that is a ride called Hollywood Tower.
Yes.
Which I'd stumbled on years before and thought, what is this shady shit?
This is just the most like this.
This is where like I certainly would not be comfortable getting on this ride.
This seems to at risk of snapping in half.
Yeah.
Look, if we if this were in Six Flags, I would say I don't know if I really want to go on Hollywood Tower.
If we were in Europe, I think I would have to do it because we're in Europe and it's funny to go on Hollywood Tower.
A clear ripoff of the Tower of Terror down to stealing the Twilight Zone music and using it on the ride.
Unlicensed Twilight Zone music.
Yeah, unlicensed.
And the letters get, oh, this was an innovation when right before it drops, the letters get like a skew on the big side.
Oh, yes, they kind of tip.
Yeah.
I think when like inspectors come to the park or something, they're like there's a switch and they just turn they're like, turn the Twilight Zone music off.
We don't want them to notice or like they hide the Burt and Mary costumes.
Then they're just like, all right, we have somebody coming to make sure we're not stealing copyright.
Just turn Twilight Zone music off and the costumes in the vault.
Yeah.
And they change the names of everything.
Well, they just I mean, it's it's hard because whether you're in a court or you're a ride safety inspector, you can't really see anything because everyone's just smoking all the time.
And then after you're done doing your work of smoking all the time, you take a two hour lunch and then a three hour nap.
And that's kind of the day.
So like even if they wanted to prosecute copyright violations, like just goes a little slower there.
So how do you not move to Italy?
I you know, that's a great question.
It's like your dream.
It sounds nice.
You get those three weeks off everywhere in your life.
Those are not even more than that, but they will just do a three week vacation for no reason.
You get three weeks off a month.
I think so.
Yeah.
I think that's Italy wide.
You have worked two hours a day.
Yeah, that's a lot of it.
Disney shows up and they're like most likely they're on a vacation.
So right.
They probably some.
So yeah, this thing, this this ride is how do you would you describe it?
It like takes you up in a way that's like just a normal drop ride.
But then it kind of like shoots you out kind of slide like almost like it's like the Superman ride at Six Flags.
Yes.
Where you where you end up on your back.
Yeah.
You start sitting upright, but then it's like a bit of curve.
So when you're let out of the attraction, you're lying on your back and have been for a little while.
Yeah.
And it's the one the vlogger I saw said it was a first generation Intamin drop tower, which is a ride manufacturer we've talked about before.
I feel like Six Flags went on a run where they were putting one of these in every park that you drop and then swing down.
I think they've fallen out of fashion.
I I had not I have not done the Superman at Six Flags because and Geo and Anthony Geo and I were going to do it the night of Fright Fest.
But it was closed, we think we weren't sure if it was closed.
I don't know if we mentioned that.
I think we probably touched on it.
There was just like like almost like a velvet rope in front of the line.
And we were like, it's running.
But maybe it doesn't have people on it.
No one was outside to tell you like, hey, this ride isn't working.
It'll be back up in an hour.
So we were just like we walked like a little bit into the queue.
And then we were like, we don't see we don't see anybody.
I guess it's closed right now.
And then we walked and did something else.
But I would have tried to tell we couldn't tell.
There was no one to let you know.
And there was no sign that said closed.
There was just kind of a loose like there was a loose piece of something.
It would they may as well have just like, you know, put up put a cone in front of the ride.
And like that will keep people away.
You might have gotten on it.
And then they told you it was closed.
Yeah, we would have gotten like halfway up like halfway up the ride and someone be like, oh, hey, hey, hey, hey, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Get calm down.
You guys, what are you doing?
I it's so so shady.
And I mean, I don't know if we should go and get some of the people in a row or something.
It's what are you doing?
I it's so so shady.
And I mean, I don't know if we also properly did it justice.
This is it is just like it's Twilight Zone themed.
It says Hollywood Tower, but it's like if the Tower of Terror had no tower around it, like there's no there's no building part.
It's just scaffolding.
It's like the Malibu boomer.
It's like if they just went the Malibu boomer is the Tower of Terror.
You sign slap it on your view from when you get up to the letters.
I'm looking at a still of what you see, and it's just like pistons and loose wires that you could like unplug the ride if you reached out.
You could you could hit a button and the CD playing the Twilight Zone music would eject and you could take the CD out and take it down with you.
That's probably how you have to change it out.
And then you play at the top.
You can you can steal the CD at the top of the ride.
It's yours.
I saved myself ninety nine cents on iTunes.
And they get really annoyed, obviously, when you figure it out and you do it, because somebody's got to go back up there and put the new CD in.
You got to burn a new CD.
We can't afford that.
I think we have fifty four cents sitting around.
All the music at this park is played off of a CD player from 1998.
It's just all the personal CD players and everyone who works there.
This part of it.
Yeah, you want a job early when the day when it opens up, you have to ride the Hollywood Tower, set your CD player there, plug it in and then hit play like repeat play.
And then the ride goes and then you can have music on the ride.
But if like if like the guy doesn't come in and he doesn't have a CD player, then the ride's not going to have any music.
No sound. Yeah. And if they're skipping, it might just like click click click click click.
Yeah. Yeah.
Before the park even opened, that guy had to fly to American parks, buy the CDs they sell in the gift shops at the exit.
And it's like, OK, we got music.
We got the music for movie land, the Hollywood Park.
Now put our own label on it with duct tape movie land originals.
Great. You know, this this ride itself also, Jason, your defense of it was, well, it's made by this company that we know.
And that's correct. But that's because this ride used to be at the West Edmonton Mall in Canada, which has a theme park that I'd love to talk about.
Or I forget if they still do Galaxy land or fantasy land.
It was called one. Now it's the other.
And that's not the only ride where that's the case, because, again, you know, like stepping it down, you know, situation.
They had a Tomb Raider ride that now is called something generic.
And this is the Tomb Raider ride at Kings Island, Ohio.
It's the literal one that I went on in like 2005 without knowing what it was.
And it scared the shit out of me. It was like way beyond my ride depths.
They just bought that from Ohio, kept to the Tomb Raider theme, but didn't build a building around it again because that was an indoor ride, which is why I didn't know what it was.
So they just took it, flopped it outside.
Eventually somebody complained about Tomb Raider. All right.
So it's, you know, cave lady and there it still sits.
Wow. I am always I would love to see a chart.
This is just maybe we do this one day of like I want to see the different rides that have moved because that seems to happen a lot where like they dismantle a roller coaster or something like a drop like this and then they move it somewhere else.
And I would love to see like the chart of what rides have rides moved like three times and move like four.
Like it's interesting.
Let's move them. What's the what's the most military brat?
Right.
It's in a new city every year.
Yeah, sad. The ride can't make friends with other rides.
Yeah, it's a tough life.
So yeah, this is a very strange ride. There's just so much to get to.
Should we do? We could talk about another ripoff.
I mean, there's a lot. There's a lot.
But maybe we could talk a little about Terminator five D. Did we learn about Terminator five D?
Yes.
Yes, that is that is not there right now.
Not there anymore.
It was for a long time.
This is like if you tried to do T2 3D in your backyard, like if if if an enterprising haunted house owner tried to make Terminator two 3D with all the steps with a video at the beginning, it gets interrupted and there's like a lady talking over it.
Kimberly Duncan ask person and but but in the pre show that I found, it's not cyber.
Well, there is cyberdyne exists within this, but they spell it with an I like eating dining cyberdyne.
And then the video that they play isn't of cyberdyne stuff.
It's of Arnold Schwarzenegger on the set of T2 3D.
And they show that that's what their pre show is.
And he's dubbed over as was Hasselhoff, by the way, they have the American actors and then just told them they never you never hear their actual voice.
So Arnold might be dubbed with like movie land.
My favorite park.
I always visit when I'm when I find myself in Italy.
And I in fact, I hate Universal Studios and I only worked for them for the paycheck.
Like is the footage like public domain footage so that they can show Arnold legally?
It can't it can't be unless there's weird rules because it's another country.
Right. Is there is that the loophole or have they again, have they never gotten away with this?
And just as soon as anybody asks, they go, never mind.
Just put a tarp over it.
And it was never there.
It feels like they're getting away.
It feels like they've gotten away with a lot.
I was trying to find there's no information for some reason.
Journalists have ignored the movie land studios controversy.
I yeah.
And Arnold keeps showing.
Well, first off, yeah, Scott, like you said, it's like they try to do T2 in a backyard, but also where it bought a bunch of scrap metal and tried to recreate the back draft set and then had some very janky versions of like the minion mayhem vehicles.
Like there is so much going on in this and also actors.
There are live actors.
Yes, who drive in on motorcycles very much like T2 3D.
But everyone who's seen it picture T2 3D in your head and picture how far away the motorcycle is.
Now picture that motorcycle driving into your living room.
And that's basically this thing.
Everything is very close.
The stunt shows are very close to the audience.
Both of the parks in Lake Garda.
It is like a simile of European cities where everything is very close together.
And that's a little unnerving with massive rides.
There's a thing like the it was in Paris and Disney where the lights motors action stunt show like a very car oriented show.
But it's it's in like an alley.
Like jammed in a little like alfresco courtyard where cars spin around and get lit on fire.
And there's a clip from the Terminator 2 5D on YouTube.
And there's a scene where I'm looking at the audience and they're getting blasted in the face with fog.
They're just getting nailed like it feels like it would hurt.
It would feel like you were getting pelted with like hail.
It's like it looks so forceful.
It's like any you know it's like it's the universal water thing.
But it's like fog and it's aggressive.
I should send this to you unless maybe you saw this.
Yeah. Well, yes.
Sure. The screen.
Please do. Yeah.
It I another weird thing about this is that I think it was open for a while just as Terminator 2 or some other name.
And it was just a miniature version.
And by the way with like up on the video screen there is video of like they made a janky their own version of the T1 million with their own bad CGI.
Oh yes Mike. Yeah.
Let's see what I got.
This is from 2010.
Oh my God.
No. See that again.
See that again here.
Because zero to 100 full fog penetration in one second.
Jesus.
It's like it's like it's like people have fire fire extinguishers.
They're just shooting it in your face from two feet away.
Well they're just collecting the cigarette smoke from the restaurant next door and blasting the other recycling the cigarette.
They're recycling the cigarette smoke.
I will say one thing I like about that show Arnold the Terminator gets lowered into the molten metal.
He gets lowered into a vat at the end.
Yes. Yes.
That is a cool thing that maybe should have been done in T2 3D.
That's cool to see live.
Yeah. Absolutely.
Then for some reason they redid this and made it.
You didn't think there was enough going on Jason.
They just now they gave everybody little laser guns like Buzz Lightyear.
And now there is no live actors but it's just the robots who come up and you just fire lasers at it.
There's just walls of adults and children all firing lasers at the show.
Is this Android? Is that what it's called now?
Well no that's something different.
I think they I think they redid Terminator to be a shooting gallery.
Yes it was.
Yes it was. It looks like it was first this weird show then they just added guns to the ride.
And that's a different thing than Android which is what you're talking about which is a mix of Terminator and Transformers.
That's a 3D like a Minion Mayhem 3D movie.
Yeah.
But then the robot they have outside on the top of the sign of Android looks like Chappie.
Looks like Chappie for the movie Chappie.
A movie I've never seen but I know the unpleasant fact that the robot gets molested at some point.
Oh my God what?
Yes that happens to Chappie.
Jesus Christ.
That's going to make it a dark day when eventually during quarantine you and we all inevitably make it to.
Ah shit we're out of things.
That's Chappie day.
We all have about five movies left.
I did watch maybe the best thing I've watched so far in quarantine is that I watched the movie Unstoppable about a runaway train.
Denzel Washington?
Denzel Washington and Chris Pine.
Chris Pine yeah yeah.
And the supporting cast is like Kevin Corrigan and Rosario Dawson and this other guy who's in a bunch of stuff.
And I had a great that was just so fun.
I don't know why it was just so chaotic.
The train roars like a monster.
And I don't know everyone just seemed like they were having a it's Tony Scott.
He's made some fun movies.
So check out folks check out Unstoppable a movie I cannot believe is not represented movie land the Hollywood Park.
Send them an email and see if you could maybe give them an idea for just like rebranding one of their trains Unstoppable.
Yeah.
Ciao Bella.
You all love trains in Europe.
I know this for certain.
Which they could maybe get away with is the is the word generic enough.
I think that's partially how they do this.
Well you can't.
What are you going to tell me?
I can't say the word Unstoppable.
Right.
Android 3D.
I can say Android.
It doesn't matter.
You know no one owns that word.
Mm hmm.
There's a similar it's similar to that.
Yeah.
One of the main bullet points when I was researching this place was oh that's weird.
There is an attraction based on you five seven one the you know the submarine film with Matthew McConaughey I guess and John Bon Jovi seemingly.
So that's that's odd still less odd than that the Disney Studios Park in Paris has a it's a back out to where you see a little scene from this Christian Bale movie is it rain of fire.
Do you guys know this thing?
Oh I know.
Yeah.
Yeah I think you're right.
Yeah I just like the shadiest like what can we get our hands on what like what like you know like barely released Robert De Niro film.
From 2012 is up for grabs.
Why didn't they go with K-19 the Widowmaker.
That feels like a bigger.
Yeah there's something like straight to video Hunter at October 2 they could.
There's gotta be.
Yeah there's gotta be.
Sounds right.
But anyway but as I dug into it I'm like this is the one that's most on the line for me where I think it's possible that they made a deal with the filmmakers and studio behind you five seven one and I say that because the font is sort of correct sometimes because not all I saw other ones where it's for sure not the font from a poster I saw in passing 20 years ago.
But I again maybe they're just like you can't own those had a letter and those numbers.
You guys I can't use the numbers five seven one.
Some submarine is not like the Batmobile there's plenty of different kinds of submarines.
Yes no one owns the IP of submarines.
You can't own an ocean.
Get out of here.
Jonathan Moss style director of you five seven one.
We knew his name.
There was no need to go over that.
We all know it.
This ride this is this is this I will say from what I saw seems like better than other experiences and a little bit.
But yet here in Corona virus times and this being Italy which had the virus very hard I'm like maybe this is where the virus started.
This sucks.
This is like you imagine that like just imagine your couch being like.
Having room for 20 people and then that same couch gets put two feet in front of you and then that's all in a big tube and that tube is like tipped over a bunch of times.
That's that's this ride.
It's the most claustrophobic like there's no there'd be no worse place to be in the current world than inside this ride.
And the and the park is open we should say right now we're recording this a couple of weeks before it comes out.
Park is open.
Is this ride open.
This feels like the worst ride to have open right now.
I think it can't be unless they're only letting in one person at a time.
Yeah.
Now according to the movie land whatever the hell it's called movieland website they say unforgettable emotions in total safety.
And that's their sort of brand they're going with right now.
So I would hope they don't open this thing.
Unforgettable emotions in total safety.
Yeah I mean I I tried not to spend all day yesterday just screen grabbing the whole website and going like wow these translations are weird.
But there's just so much the Garthaland website hired a translator much cleaner.
This website was just so excited to tell us about these rides.
They did not do an edit on the descriptions of the ride.
Yeah it's the best.
You know I feel bad.
You can't let's sometimes not these places faults that the bizarre translations but man does it result in the craziest sentences you've ever seen.
You know you don't think there's like I do wonder what the Italian equivalent is of the show titled Total Candy Jacket.
Sorry full candy jacket.
Full candy jacket.
It seems like a play on full metal jacket.
I think you're correct.
We found this in the when we talked about this the first day when Mike brought that thing to our attention which I watched it there you know it's what they do that Christine Aguilera candy man there's not a lot going on.
The only thing I thought was odd and I'll screen share here.
I didn't know Drew Tarver was doing Italian theme park theater.
He's always got a lot of irons in the fire you know.
It's an eye demand.
It's super funny guy.
Yeah I know.
Yeah he's hustling.
That's great.
Or it's an Italian cousin or something.
A long lost Italian cousin.
Yeah.
If true is that if there's a cousin Drew's been looking for.
Here's a clue.
There is.
There's European like pop culture stuff.
Like there's a ride based on the Italian comic book character Diabolic.
Diabolic.
See I always thought it was Diabolic and then I went and found the trailer from the Mario Bava like 60s Diabolic movie and they called them Diabolic.
So interesting.
Hard to tell.
This is like a very popular Italian comics character.
He's kind of a thief.
He was very clearly the basis for a more recent in the last 20 years X-Men character whose name is escaping me right now.
Mike do you know it's off the top of your head.
Phantom X.
Yes Phantom X.
We've talked about Phantom X on the show before.
Yeah and then also walking around the corner of the room and seeing the movie.
Yeah and then also walking around is like a walk around Asterix and Obelix for the French Viking comic book characters.
There's a whole park of them somewhere right there came up in our research.
They still might be unlicensed.
It's hard to say.
I don't know how you would do a very good or a very bad Asterix and Obelix.
The Obelix might be the only one that's official.
That seems like the art.
It seems as licensed as a Six Flags property and the coaster seems fine.
Right.
Like if you only were looking at that coaster and that branding you might go OK right on popular European character.
They did it right.
Just don't look anywhere else in the park.
Right.
I mean I have to say the thing that upset me the most was the off-brand Flintstones.
Like there's some weird Flintstone stuff in this park.
Obelix statues look really sad.
They look like they need to be put out of their misery.
There's a kiddie coaster called Bronto Ring that I just call Long Dino because it's very clearly Dino.
But he's like too long.
You sit in his body.
Like I just don't care for it.
You don't care that he's too long.
You don't like it that he's too long.
You want it more accurate.
Yeah.
It's just it's just too long.
And it seems like it goes slow enough that the couple recording footage on it were having a normal volume conversation while they're going up and down the little hills.
Talking about Texas.
Yeah.
Getting worked in.
Is it too early to talk about the original characters?
No.
I'm not even sure what to who you refer.
Oh you.
Of course I'm talking about movie and the character who I assume is the official mascot of movie land.
Is he the guy with kind of a rectangle head?
He looks he looks a lot.
He seems very like an Olympic mascot.
Yes.
He's got like orange boots, orange gloves.
He's got kind of a singlet on and he has I assume a TV shaped head.
That's what it's like mimicking maybe.
And his name is M.O.V.Y.A.N.
Wait you know what?
I take this back.
His name is actually just movie.
They did not put a space between the word and and movie.
I thought his name was movie and but his name is not movie and it is just movie M.O.V.Y.
They needed to put a space after that.
You thought this guy's name because of their typo that it's it's movie and which you've been like trying to wrap your head around for 24 hours.
Would that have made any less sense real or more?
No it seems totally in the character of this relatedly.
There's been a video on their YouTube channel for four years for Christmas.
A video following around our beloved character's Santa Claus.
Guys check the spelling.
Santa Claus?
He's trying to grow up like Ricky Schroeder.
Sorry it's Santa Claus now.
But movie and though as I will keep.
Movie and is how we have to now refer to him.
It is clearly movie M.O.V.Y.
Here's how here's the two different ways you would read this sentence.
Here's the first one.
Hi this is how I thought.
Hi my name is movie and I am here to help you choose help you to choose the best ticket for you or hi my name is movie and I am here to help you to choose the best ticket for you.
I kind of like the first one better.
Yeah he's movie and we're missing a comma too in the first version.
But I assume there was just missing a comma.
It's a it's possibilities what movie and like movies and what are movie and what.
Movie and club sandwich movie and pack of cigarettes.
When you go out on a date if you're going to see a movie on a date you're going to movie and romance.
We'll see movie and chill.
Hmm.
That was uncomfortable.
The two of you did it so I had to do it.
Hmm.
The prospect of a romantic evening.
I haven't been single since the Netflix and chill with.
I haven't been single in the age of Netflix whatsoever so I've never.
When you were last single you would have to after the movie was done put it in an envelope and put it out at the mailbox for the veil.
We were Aaron and I got together on flickster.
Yes.
Movie and return it in the mail.
So what is movie and tell us what you can surmise about his character.
Well he's mostly here to help you purchase tickets movie and as part of all of like the main like logo on the website.
Yeah.
I think he's in some shows.
I think he's in some of the kids shows.
Oh yeah.
Oh really.
I missed them that it seemed like he was he there's like a one of the.
There's like a walk around version of him.
If you look under shows I feel like he's in a couple of those there.
There is so much content on this website and on YouTube.
It's almost impossible to let's see here.
Sort of headache inducing what with all of the misspellings and the bizarre translations and not being sure what the name of it is.
And again like seems like zero seat belts like there are two attractions.
We haven't really the magma two point one and Pantanjeeya and one is the giant Jeep ride I was talking about earlier like Kilimanjaro safaris and then Pantanjeeya.
It seems like that is a car and it seems like that is partially controlled remotely but also one of your guests are kind of driving it at some points like and it just looks like a modified Jeep Wrangler.
The video Jason that we watched of the two bloggers vloggers and I can't think of what their names are.
Help me out here.
John and Stace.
John and Stace Stace went on the Tollywood Tower ride and she kept over and over saying that she's like they didn't check to make sure I was in OK.
Like she kept saying over and over again that she felt unsafe as the ride was starting because no one had like done that usual double check to make sure you're strapped in.
Yeah.
Also don't breeze past the fact that that ride is called magma two point one.
Yes.
What does that mean?
Is it like a Richter scale measurement?
Because if so that's very small.
I'm not worried about a two point one.
No but is a two point one volcano eruption different than a two point one earthquake?
Well it's kind of like it has a catastrophe canyon kind of scene.
It has an earthquake kind of scene like that's that's what that ride is.
And then the other one is essentially you drive through different manicured areas with dinosaurs that move a little.
So one is clearly like Studio Tour and one is clearly more like Jurassic Park.
It's you know just like a trip into the world of the dinosaurs where you you go and it culminates in seeing a T.
Rex who is hovering over a triceratops about to eat it because it's already injured and which you can tell because of its exposed bone.
It's just like a it's like a truly grisly like if you saw that in a person you'd never forget it.
You'd be scarred.
Aren't there intestines also showing?
And the T.
Rex is chewing on like a red flap of paper that never goes away.
It's like hanging out of his mouth.
There's like entrails loose from this poor dinosaur.
It's what the Verhoeven Disney dinosaur would have been.
They based it on his concept art.
Speaking of safety, maybe that could take us into a ride again another step down.
And this one's recent.
This is since I started doing the research about this because a couple months ago.
OK, so I just checked the website today and this ride is called Panorama Tram.
But a month ago or less, it was called Back to the Backstage and which when I found it was that's just written in a regular font.
But several years back from that, it was written clearly in the Back to the Future font.
And you would go on this ride and the Back to the Future music played.
And there's a video with a doc just like a guy in a wig.
And he's got like next to him the little you know where you're going, where you've been like the console of the DeLorean.
But OK, so we know Back to the Future, the ride, that's where you time travel, you know, because it's a time travel movie.
What do you do in Back to the Backstage?
You ride a very narrow monorail around the backstage of all of the other rides in the park.
And Doc talks about what he thinks the rides might be.
So he's like, you five seven one, huh?
A submarine looks pretty crazy.
I wonder what it'd be like to be on that.
What? I missed this.
What? Why?
Yeah, I I I this is I almost did, too.
I just went down to the wire, finding back the backstage.
What? And then you're like, so but then why is he only talking about just like what the rides are?
And you think that's all it is. But then occasionally he'll direct something to Marty, even though there's no representation of Marty anywhere.
He's talking to us as far as I know.
And then, you know, he'll he'll refer to Biff having caused trouble.
My favorite is when he said when Doc says the line, I am the great doc.
I am the great doc.
Well, and this is also like it's just a slightly elevated monorail that like a lot of Six Flags and like Gardaland had one.
It has one of these Hershey Park has one of these.
Unlike those, this one collapsed a little.
Just a baby little collapse last year.
It's just there's been injuries.
I don't think anyone died.
Yeah, the whole thing just fell.
It toppled over.
Yeah, it's just a little baby collapse.
It's like onto a lawn.
This video you can watch if it's all like this.
There's a little you know, it's a stretch of grass.
If you were going to if your ride was going to fall anywhere is the safest place for it to happen.
So somewhere in fixing that up, they also bailed on the great doc.
And then, you know, like they're playing the music when you come back around and the rides over, you see a DeLorean, something we were just talking about in an episode.
How do you just get a DeLorean and then put a bunch of wires on it and like great and people buy it.
There's people taking pictures in front of this thing.
This is not from the movie.
This DeLorean has no significant this metal and these wires added have nothing to do with Back to the Future.
OK, here's another theory I have that I'm formulating right now because there's a show.
I don't know. You're familiar with the show they do called Choice of a New Generation.
Yeah.
Choice of a New Generation features Marty McFly and the DeLorean pretty heavily.
OK, yeah.
Maybe the properties are almost kind of like a shell game where if you keep moving things around legally, you can kind of skirt around.
So like maybe they catch the universal catches wind that they're using the great doc on a ride and they say, well, let's let's sue them.
Let's get rid of it.
And as soon as that they catch wind that they're going to get sued, let's move it to Choice of New Generation.
Choice of a New Generation.
Maybe there's there's something to that where if you just keep kind of shuffling things around, you can legally kind of skirt these issues.
So like for a while, that outdoor show was Doc Brown, US Army stunt show.
Yeah.
They they claim that all the soldiers you're seeing firing rifles were all the invention of Doc Brown.
Right. He armed all those soldiers.
Isn't that far off from like original Doc, who is like, you know, working with terrorist groups and stealing.
Oh yeah, he was corrupt.
Yeah, yeah.
Just having just rewatched the movie.
I mean, I'm sure there's been plenty of observation on this point, but yeah, boy, just like stealing plutonium from terrorists.
That is so funny to put that in a movie.
That is a crazy choice.
And then the mean, concerned principal who thinks that he should focus on school and not hang out with a.
Yeah, old man.
Staling.
Yeah.
A disgraced inventor.
There's the stories and there is a script that like Doc and Marty sat around smoking weed a lot more and selling bootleg VHS tapes.
That got smoothed out a little.
Yeah, they had a band together.
That's why they met.
But like, yeah, you got to.
They're called penny stocks, man.
We could be rich.
Like you could like though, once Universal threatens to sue over choice of a new generation live show, then Doc and Marty will move to like Android.
It'll be like Doc's Android Marty Marty's Android.
Or yet now.
Yeah, Marty is enlisted with the full candy jacket.
Right.
Yes.
Yeah, it's just it's just shuffling things around.
I want to know in terms of copyright infringement, the horror house, 600 seconds of fear again that that that branding is implying it's a 10 minute long haunted house, which would make it twice as long as like any horror nights house has like the Exorcist and Freddy Krueger and all of these scenes.
No cameras allowed in there also.
No, I am.
But I did.
I found one.
Oh, you did.
I found one walkthrough and it's very dark.
Of course, it's a haunted house.
But also this might take 10 minutes because it appears to be a haunted house that is mostly long empty hallways with maybe eight scare actors.
It's scary because it's dark and empty.
All portraying IP though, right?
It seems like, yeah, there might be one or two generic zombies, but like on the signs, it's like leather face and there was a Freddy Krueger walking around.
There's the bedroom with Linda Blair's character.
Oh my God.
When the inspectors come all the like Doc Brown hides out in that house of horrors.
With this leather face mask on.
Also, they like a lot of time.
This is those long hallways are also the offices where they those are the like internal offices of the park.
So if there's like a meeting at four o'clock, House of Horror has to go on hold for half an hour.
Well, and if inspectors come by, of course, they can always reach out for help to the master thief Diabolic to distract them and fool them.
So the show, I will say just real quick, the choice of a new generation show features Marty McFly and Michael Jackson and the Terminator and Rocky and the Terminator and Rocky.
So the new generation shows characters from that stars from the 1980s.
The choice of a pretty old generation of long ago, yeah, Rocky's that older film.
I don't know. Well, if that's that refers to the choice, not the new generation is choosing that old generation.
We can't control their choice.
No to new stuff.
And we know it's a Pepsi park.
It's a park that serves Pepsi.
So it is the Pepsi generation.
They made their choice, which again, maybe maybe it's not Pepsi.
Maybe it's or they like stole it.
Maybe they wait for Pepsi trucks to fly off the road and tip over.
They go spikes on the road and then the Pepsi truck runs over and then like Doc Brown and Mary Poppins run out and steal all the Pepsi from the back of the truck.
And they bring it into the park.
Get the Pepsi, get a cigarette, get it.
They send out minion costumes, which secretly have tanks inside like a cat for those is and then somebody's got to like, what do you call it, gas like huffing it like siphoning.
They've got a siphon loose Pepsi into a minion suit before it dries under the pavement.
That's the biggest surprise that there's not off brand minions in this.
No, no, no, there is.
There is.
There's like wide minions or five eyes or.
I don't know if they're bold enough to just do the real things.
It's just them.
It's them just poorly made.
I. Yes.
No, no, don't worry.
They covered that too.
Also, like, here's a confusing mashup that there's not just the Knight Rider presence with super jet.
There's also a kids ride called Kit Mini Jet.
And those are little boats that you drive around.
And so their kit, but also they have eyes on the windshield like the cars.
Yeah, they look like cars.
They look like boats that are the Disney Cars.
Yeah. And I don't think there's a Hasselhoff video for that ride.
I don't believe so.
No, you're right. And you know, a three year old doesn't know Hasselhoff yet.
Unfortunately, you don't think in Europe they teach kids at an early age who Mr.
Hasselhoff is?
That's true. Maybe in like Germany and Austria.
And obviously I will teach my son.
That'll be one of the first things.
You know, he's really slacking music videos, dude.
It's so funny.
You're playing his records for him, right?
To to calm him, to calm him.
Oh, yeah, I'm already I'm already playing get in my car.
What's that?
What's that? Do you ever that song?
Jump in my car.
I want to take you home.
Um, is best.
Um, that's I haven't said my son's name.
That's Hasselhoff.
Maybe I'll make his middle name and in the movie.
And so often Gardner.
Um, similarly to there's so there's a little cars kind of ride, but then also a different one.
In what has to be made or inspired, but that leads you to the disturbing name name Cooters rodeo.
Oh, God.
Is that Route 66?
Get on board real cars and drive on Route 66.
Maybe.
But I also saw it as Cooters of on this.
These are different rides.
Yeah, they are different rides.
They are different rides.
Cooder is made or right.
The Cooder like Cooder is a knockoff mater.
I guess I don't know if you see Cooder, though.
That's an original.
That's a movieland original IP, I assume.
One of many.
They have dozens and dozens.
Um, here.
Why don't we close out the park so that we can move on to outside the park because there's a lot.
So excited for outside.
Yeah, I mean, we could just get to it.
Is there anything else?
Hold on.
Yeah.
Fantasmic.
Do you know what I'm talking about?
What?
The one there.
There is a whole child's haunted house that is very Disney inspired because it has like cute little songs and projections.
I'll be honest.
I like Fantasmic.
Maybe it's Fantasmic.
I don't know how to pronounce it.
I missed it.
And he is a little character, a little poorly designed character.
Let me send this picture to you right now.
It's one of my favorite logos from the park.
One of my favorite pictures.
He looks like he's in agony.
Fantasmic looks like he's in pure hell.
He's living in hell.
There's constantly ghosts haunting him.
He's got a child equally as scared behind him with a flashlight.
And let me just.
So, yeah.
So you walk through this little walkthrough attraction and there's like a nice, there's little fun little songs and stuff.
And it's obviously the budget isn't very high, but, you know, they did what they could.
And I bet I would like it as a kid.
Let me show you, send you one picture from the website that I think really sums up the budget on this ride.
Here we go.
You're receiving it now.
It is a picture of a slide.
Slide slide.
Just a slide with like a net under it.
And it's like it looks like somebody put a slide in a warehouse, like a warehouse with like some slightly fun colors in the back.
They could put up colored lights and that's it.
Yeah.
So.
And this is what makes Fantasmic, the green ghost, that scared?
Yeah.
Fantasmic.
Now on the website it says Fantasmic, where a fright makes you happy.
So children discover Fantasmic's house, where even a fright makes you happy.
To you parents, if you don't feel like entering, in the meantime, you can enjoy a good coffee.
What are you waiting for?
Exclamation point, not question mark.
What are you waiting for as a command?
Real tiny f**k.
It's real tiny f**k.
It's wise.
Oh, imagine my delight.
I mean, I'll read one when we get outside, but there's so many of them like this one.
I don't know much about the show Medusa, but in a Greek archaeological site among ancient mysteries, twists and special effects,
you will become the protagonists of an incredible discovery.
Protagonists of a discovery.
The human and divine have never been so close.
What will be the consequences?
And then my favorite is a show.
Again, is that typo?
The show is called Pre-X Story Factor.
And the description of it is a musical game where there are two groups of little singers.
Are you ready to win a talent show battle?
So strange.
Mike, I sent you guys yesterday the picture, the Route 66, the little kid driving ride.
There's just a sign in the background behind this smiling child that just says Doctor Movie.
And I can't even begin to fathom what Doctor Movie is about, but I love it.
I love that.
Is it a soda?
Yeah, it kind of does kind of look like the Dr. Pepper logo.
So why does this kid have a pacifier?
He's like eight years old.
Yes, there's an old child with a pacifier and then a smiling, like perfectly coiffed hair child driving.
I think that pacifier is photoshopped in there because it's like slightly below his lip.
Something's really wrong with this.
Maybe Dr. Movie isn't a soda.
It's like a sweet pacifier.
It's like covered in sugar.
This kid's sucking on a Dr. Movie.
I would like a Dr. Movie right now.
Yeah, that sounds pretty good.
Speaking of great snacks in the park, this is going to require screen share.
This is for, and let me credit the website because it's a pretty specific, this guy's blog, pirouettes.org,
who had a pretty tough time on a roller coaster called Bronto Jet.
And I liked the way I liked his write up of that where he concluded it with Bronto Jet.
You are the fuck boy of the coaster world.
I'm sure what that means, but I like it a lot.
But anyway, look at this crazy snack only at maybe it's not only at the movie land.
Please enjoy a Dakota stick.
What are we looking at?
What is that?
That looks like a corn dog turned upside down, stuck on top of a very large poached egg.
Like a cream puff or something?
Or like just a roll with, you know, seasonings on top, like a slightly like it's a roll with like flakes of thyme.
Like bagel toppings and then like a little like kind of a sloppy little puff of tin foil.
Is this?
It's I mean like like of course any of course a corn dog is a little penise anyway.
But this will put on top of a little like puff.
This is I mean this is the most penise snack I've ever seen.
This is like the shaft on top of one giant testicle.
I'm trying to think if there's anything else that it's more penise than this.
Yeah, I know what you're saying.
You're probably right.
It's probably the top penise treat of all time.
I would I guess I guess if I'm thinking about it, you're probably right.
It looks like he's peeing.
It's peeing a stick.
Yeah, it's passing a stick stone.
It does look like you could teach kids sex ed with this.
You could explain to everyone where the vas deferens is using a Dakota stick and where the Cowper's gland is using a Dakota stick.
This could be a good tool for children, for teens.
But yeah, the tin foil kind of is like where pubic hair would be.
Yeah, it's silver pubic hair, the pubic hair of the future.
The Dakota stick is the first sex ed tool that you can learn and then eat.
Little treat for barren with it.
Yeah.
So I can't look at the Dakota stick anymore.
Also, by the way, I don't know if you saw under that.
There you go.
This they also way back in the day had an Indiana Jones thing.
Oh, yeah, I do.
Indie filming sets in the Indie filming set.
That meant indie independent.
That didn't mean Indiana Jones.
It's an it's a shooting of an indie film.
It looks like he shows up in the Medusa show.
That's it.
So they're shuffling again.
That's what I'm saying.
It's a shell game.
It's a shell game with IP.
It's you can you can stay out of legal problems if you just shuffle everything around.
And then the the Overdrive show is the one where it's like 70s cops on those hard streets of San Francisco.
And they're stopping drug dealers.
And that's the one where it's like you can reach out and slap the cars like you can reach out and high five the stuntman firing a gun.
Or I guess give him a kiss, like kiss on both cheeks.
Like, I don't do the high five in Italy.
You could change the air conditioning settings in the car.
Yeah, take the CD out of the player.
This is the narrowest park.
So thin.
There's not enough space for any of this.
Yeah.
Oh, boy.
So have we have we covered everything in the park?
Because we're folks buckle up because we're with what's coming.
We're not even close to done.
Yeah, no, I've worked up an appetite now that we're out of the park.
Yeah.
So where do you where do you go?
What do you like the part?
The park's closed.
There's surely there isn't a district of shopping and fun and dining and shows for me to you know, there there couldn't be because there isn't nearly enough land around here for there to be such a thing.
Right.
You know what?
I think you're incorrect.
Oh, boy.
Oh, look at that.
Yes, we can cruise right on to Sunset Boulevard.
Folks, you're about to hear a little miniature version of some Sunset Boulevard saga.
It won't require daily episodes because it's not that many things.
But boys, there are a lot to talk about and boys, a lot of it like things in the city walk saga.
Yeah, just a few things we mentioned Rockstar restaurant, Safari pizza.
How about that?
How do you like the sound of that?
How about a medieval times?
Well, you're acting as if I don't have things to say about all of these things.
I know.
I'm just giving I'm letting the whistle.
And don't forget, Mike, one most pertinent to your interest.
Of course, I know exactly what you're about to say.
Yeah, yeah.
Yes.
Anyone want to say the name Margarita's cocktail bar?
That's right.
Margarita's cocktail.
Um, and what's in that logo?
What?
Can you guys see the Margarita's logo?
I can't.
Well, I don't have.
Oh, let me pull it up.
I know what you're talking about, but I just want to make sure we're on the same page here.
Is there a plane in the logo?
There sure is.
Yes.
Wow.
There's a plane also outside of Margarita's cocktail bar.
And it is a plane.
This is a Margarita restaurant with a seafarin plane outside.
Yes, it is not this plane that is outside of the Margaritaville restaurant in City Walk, Orlando.
The Hemisphere dancer, which real quick.
Yes.
In case people out there don't know, was Jimmy Buffett's plane that was shot at by the Jamaican government,
which is an incident that he wrote a song about called Jamaica Mistake.
Jimmy was not on the plane.
Bono was on the plane.
But that was just a big misunderstanding.
It was nothing weird going on.
Sure.
Well, it's a pretty different story with this plane because with this plane, Jimmy.
One day, Jimmy Buffett was not on board this plane and the plane was not shot at by the Jamaican government.
And this incident was not commemorated in a song called Jamaica Mistake Faker.
What about whatever the fake Jamaica Mistake?
Yes, sure.
That would also be a good way to frame the song that does not exist about the plane that has no stories about it.
Jimmy Buffett, I imagine, is very litigious.
I would have to think with a corporate, the IP.
This is one of the most egregious things in this whole property.
Maybe it's just because of my personal connection to the IP I so love.
But the logo is exactly the Margaritaville logo.
Does this upset you? Does this make your face hot?
Do you buff it wrong this way?
We talk about corporations. We make fun of them a lot.
And I feel it's always good to poke fun at them, except for Margaritaville, which is a brand I cherish.
And this just boils my blood to see a company like this just use, just take...
Jimmy Buffett created liking palm trees and margaritas. He created that.
So it sucks that they're just taking what he spent so long building, a brand, and just...
People might not even know. They might see it and they might get confused.
And they're not getting the authentic Margaritaville experience.
Well, no, but they're getting a themed terrace with a unique style.
Well, that's true. Now, would I go there? Of course I would go there, but I would be a little upset the whole time.
You can't take that vibe and put it in a bottle.
And you especially can't do it just like next to the parking lot.
All of these places, again, the narrow space that we have here, all of the places we just mentioned are all jammed together,
just like right next to where cars pull up, where you do the drop-offs.
It's like there's four entire establishments in a space that's like one seventh the size of City Walk.
It seems like you could throw your drink and hit a car pretty easily if you were sitting on the terrace here for this restaurant.
Like that's how close it is to vehicles.
Yeah. With that, I started...
Because this was another thing. When you started talking about this, Mike, you said...
Because you probably just quickly looked at the website and you said, like, yeah, I think there's a Medieval Times there.
And I'm like, oh, interesting. And that put some legitimacy to it in my head.
And then I started looking at the website and like, no, no way. This is not that Medieval Times.
They just chose a similar font. It isn't. And I compared the two logos.
There's no mention of an Italy Medieval Times on the website of the Medieval Times that we know.
It's not it. And then I... And then somewhere they said how many people they conceded at a time.
And I looked it up and it's a third the size of the Buena Park one.
So yet again, sorry to be a broken record, but like you could be eating and your food could get speared by the jousting stick or whatever.
You got to watch out for your corn on the cob because a knight might take it accidentally.
It is like this. I mean, in all seriousness, this is truly like theft.
Yes. Like that one's unforgivable.
That name is the name of a brand. You can't do this.
And like the crowns and all the outfits.
We're getting off to a good... We thought we were just going to have like a nice European trip.
And then we've immediately uncovered a world of crime and nefariousness.
We're having this little like national treasure kind of adventure now.
We have to alert the authorities who I feel like might be out.
Like we're going to end up chased around by knights and androids and the great Doc Brown.
Or, and I agree with what you're saying, but let me put this out.
We oftentimes talk about taking IP legally, obtaining IP that we like that is not being used.
Maybe we follow the movie land playbook. Just use them.
Just start using it.
Just write a script about Marvel McFay and say, fuck it. Let them come after us.
Yeah. And maybe they just like, maybe nobody ever catches people.
I think that's what this thing is. This place is indicating.
What's the worst? Do you have to, you know, have a tense conversation with a lawyer and then you blow smoke in their face and they leave?
The best case scenario is nothing ever happened.
I would like to announce a new podcast that the three of us will be doing called the official Medieval Times podcast.
And to try to stop us.
Yeah. Interviews with the knights who are definitely not us.
We got the real guys.
Right.
Marvel McFay can be like in it or our logo.
And if someone comes after us, we just change his name to like Mitchell McRichardson.
Yeah. Marvel McFay will be in it.
Batman will be in it. Wolverine will be in it.
It doesn't. We have official. We're using them now.
No way. That's that's Eared Man and Scissor Fingers.
We're narrowly avoiding two copyrights with Scissor Fingers.
I would say that and then we'll shuffle Batman into the regular podcast, the ride feed.
So we'll skirt by.
Batman will then be a co-host for a couple episodes.
Yeah. And then we can trade him to a friends show or something.
He'll go hide in action boys for a while.
And then when the coast is clear, he's back where he started on the official Medieval Times podcast coming soon.
Yeah. Man, this is just so funny.
This is inspiring. It's time for us to start doing business like the Italian theme parks do, or at least this one.
I've always wanted to write like an X-Men movie or a Ninja Turtles movie.
And maybe it's time for me just to officially declare I'm going into production on an X-Men movie right now.
And I don't care. I don't own it. Doesn't matter.
I would like to say I'm now officially in pre-production on both an X-Men movie and a Ninja Turtles movie.
Yeah. Damn. You're really doing it.
People should just pay you money already because you have these properties and not ask any more questions.
Jason, would you like to announce going into production on like a Dagwood movie or?
Yeah, it's going to be like a Hope and Crosby kind of like buddy travel adventure movie.
And it stars Dagwood and Mickey Mouse.
And they're friends and they're like stuck in Egypt.
They're like tour group left without them.
They have to get back to Toontown and who else is in there?
Like Bugs Bunny, Asterix and Obelisk.
Wimpy?
Wimpy, the Michelin Man and whatever.
The Nike swoosh. The Nike swoosh is in there.
Whoa, that's cool.
Yeah. And he talks. He's super cool.
He's really slick.
And sometimes the whole gang just drives up and watches Neil Young perform his most famous songs for 15 minutes or, you know,
and you go to Led Zeppelin.
It's all in the up and up.
Yeah. And of course, they all ride in the Ecto one.
Right. Of course. Yeah.
Wow. This sounds like a hit.
This sounds like the spiritual heir to Ready Player One.
It sounds good.
I think so. Yeah.
Well, congratulations on pre-production, Jason.
Oh, thank you.
Congratulations on pre-production on you both on your respective projects.
Yeah, I'm doing a joint biopic of the Rolling Stones.
It's part Rolling Stones biopic in part a new Dick Tracy.
It's a film that is both of these things at one time.
It's going to be tricky math to do because one's in the 40s and one's, you know, all through the 20th century.
But, you know, it'll sort of actually they don't marry.
It's just they just alternate scenes because you get bored with a movie having the same plot.
So, you know, every five minutes it changes.
Yeah. Just quick bites kind of one and the other.
Well, it's very exciting.
And I encourage all the listeners to just go into pre-production on any projects you'd like.
Just start. Get it moving.
Doesn't matter.
This is we've seen the way now at Movie World.
We've seen the way things need to happen.
This this feels like almost a wrap up point, but I can't not talk about Rockstar Rock and Roll restaurant.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
And Safari, a little bit of Safari pizza, too.
I don't know much about Safari pizza. What can you tell me?
Oh, it's a buffet style of the grossest pizzas I've ever seen.
But less gross than the Rockstar food, the Rockstar food.
I mean, I've eaten some garbage in my time.
The Rockstar Rock and Roll restaurant food is the most disgusting food.
I will say Safari pizza looks fun as hell.
I love the look of Safari pizza.
Yeah, it is the wildest place to have dinner.
That's what it says.
It's got some fun like lion and monkey cartoons and it's got, you know, like plastic characters around.
Honestly, this is one of the best themed things from just the look of it.
Yeah, it looks great.
Number one on property.
I think it's maybe the best thing on property.
Wow.
I mean, where else can you get a pizza topped with what appears to be schnitzel and french fries?
God, what is it with the just fried bullshit?
That's everything at this place. Yeah.
Like just weird, like like little fried balls.
And I wouldn't even venture a guess what's inside.
Is it cheese? Is it potato? Is it rice? Is it just is it just bread?
I like I'd be there.
They're like little Easter eggs.
I don't know what's inside these little just breaded nuggets that are everywhere.
I can I can list some of the pizzas if you want.
Yes, please.
Yeah, they're all named after animals.
I'm trying to find a Zambezi, which I don't know what that is.
Tomato sauce. One word mozzarella, ham, mushrooms, artichokes, peppers, olives.
Pretty good.
I will say the pizza looks like they didn't really blend the toppings.
It just looks like they dumped them all in different corners of the pizza.
I said that as a text.
I'm now on God, the Congo River with anchovies on it with really stringy long anchovies.
Here is what Jason was referring to. It's called the Hakuna Patata.
Yes.
Oh, there it is. Oh, tomato sauce, mozzarella, worstal and french fries.
The German french fry pizza. What are you talking about?
You know, we're still my piece. I could be wrong.
That's all I think is that the rock and roll restaurant.
I'm sorry. Good.
I know. I was just going to say I again.
It looks like somebody was carrying a different meal by the pizza and they spilled on the pizza.
And that's when they got the Hakuna Patata.
Look at the Lake Victoria.
It's just pure sauce.
It says tomato sauce, garlic, and then it's just like there's three little like they look like beetles,
little garlic beetles having a little meeting in the middle of the pizza.
But otherwise, they're just they're in a lake of tomato sauce.
The pizza looks like like you let the you like let your son make a pizza like a pizza while you were making a pizza.
And like it doesn't come out right.
But it was pretty good for him. And it doesn't look professionally made.
I also you know, it's weird is the fact that only some of these pizzas are named after animals and pizzas,
by the way, can have ingredients and often do that come from animals,
which makes it so bizarre that you can get a hippo pizza, which comes with tuna fish, crocodile.
That why that has a ham.
But this it's such a like brain collision.
And then like there's pop up ads every two seconds on this thing.
I can't look at it.
I just got a big thing with a giraffe that said, check out the offers.
I can't. It won't let me pick a pizza.
The tropical pizza and like I said, I'm trying to eat less meat and like I've never seen grosser looking meat than on this tropical pizza.
Do you see what I'm saying here?
It looks like ham, ham.
I know Jason's a big ham fan, so I don't want to offend you.
But Jason, it has been a while, though.
Could I trouble you for a certain catchphrase?
Oh, hey, I'm in the house.
Yeah, I can tell.
I haven't bought a while, but I can assure you my father texted me the other day a picture of recently purchased ham and I went, hey, look, I'm in the house.
So does he know the phrase now?
Well, he knows. Yeah, he knows it from us.
Oh, good. Oh, geez.
That's a family thing now.
Yeah, so recent ham purchase.
Ham purchase.
The elephant.
Why the exotic toppings on the elephant pizza are tomato sauce and mozzarella.
It is a cheese pizza.
They call their cheese pizza elephant with no reason and nothing to back it up.
And just a reminder, this park is in Italy, the country of Italy.
I like forgot that we've been on this trash island for an hour and a half or whatever.
This is what drove me out of my mind when I was trapped in the in that bad mall at Disney Parade.
Like I was just in the most beautiful places I've ever been in my life.
Now I'm here, which I think maybe brings us to a question.
Could you guys see yourself going to this place?
Oh, I want to go tomorrow.
I want to see this. Yes. Yes. I want to see this.
Absolutely. I'm going to go to Gardaland.
I would go here. I'm sort of there, except I would need to get out of there.
I couldn't spend a night. Maybe I'd love to go.
But yeah, I need to make sure that's I think a recurring thing,
because I've asked myself this with all the parks that we're going to go to.
And often the answer is yes, except that so many of them seem like, well, you have to take a weird bus for five hours.
Like that's where like how how worth it is it to me to go laugh at a hippo pizza?
Well, when I have the grid, the literal greatest pizza on Earth, like an hour away,
you'd really have to break down exactly the time it would take to get to the place.
If it was some insane thing, perhaps I wouldn't go.
But if it was an hour away, yeah, you can get a good six hours.
I mean, I'm now I'm dying.
I'm kind of dying to go on these rides now and be movie and oh, my God, I would love to.
I would I would slow dance with movie and at this point, I would be so excited to see movie and.
And, you know, we all want to try the new formula with great plates.
The way they advertise rock and roll restaurant from on their website, new formula with great plates.
Let me acquaint you with Rockstar Rock and Roll Restaurant by again going into a little bupities.
Become the star with our jukebox.
Choose the soundtrack of the night with the songs that made the history of music a fully themed venue with all the rock and roll vibes.
And then later on a different thing, become the star of the night.
Taste our 12 eat parade.
Huh? Are you saying hit is eat is it's a eat parade.
OK, all prepared with fresh ingredients and all the taste of rock unlimited iced drinks and watch out for sweets.
Not a warning. You need give Jason.
Yeah, he doesn't need to watch out. Hey, no, I mean, I love that they're too big, disgusting looking restaurants are like half buffets, the buffets with unlimited refills.
And don't worry, the Rockstar restaurant is definitely not a hard rock cafe.
Never mind the giant pillars.
Never mind the design of the building, which sure does look like that old art, rock cafe at University of Orlando.
They've since demolished is it looks exactly like the fanciest hard rock cafes.
And then you go inside and it says like live all serve all or some nonsense on the back.
Like in this is the same layout, the same lettering.
And then and then, of course, you got the guitar outside, which I'm sure you guys saw.
But just like here with me, just look at the quality of the construction of the Rockstar restaurant guitar.
It's just like it's like Christmas lights stapled to a pole.
And then the way the like the letters fall off of the star.
You know what I'm saying?
Like they're like some of it's on the cardboard star they attach.
Some of it isn't.
And this is just one of the ugliest items I've ever seen.
It's like I cut it out of cardboard.
Like it's like I feel like in my mind, I was like, I know what a guitar looks like.
And I cut it out of cardboard and then it's pasted it and like it looks like very cheap.
Like, yeah, I mean, it looks sucks.
It looks shitty.
It looks terrible.
And this, by the way, is the first thing you see when you pull up to the property.
And if you're coming in for a exciting day at movie land, the first thing you see is this like Styrofoam guitar.
Or if you crashed into this with your car, it would like not even it would tip over and not even make a noise.
There just would be like a slight little foam puff.
It might float away, honestly.
The wind might take it into the air like a balloon.
Yeah, it's so light.
So cheap.
Oh, my God.
And then the items at this place, which is a it's a it's an it's an all you can eat restaurant as opposed to and you can watch video of this.
People get like choosing from the like, well, I have like a very dry onion ring or a very dry hush puppy or a dry mystery ball.
One that I'm staring at, it's called Dance Supreme Chicken, where I might as well just screen share that you might be looking at.
I'm looking at it. I'm looking at it.
Sure. We're all looking at we're all salivating at Dance Supreme Chicken.
So it's like very thin.
You want you want a piece of chicken to be as thin as possible.
You want it like just crushed with an iron and then with a fatty.
Yeah. Yeah.
I think it's chicken schnitzel because it's got a lemon wedge on top and I believe.
OK, OK. Jason's got that eye for schnitzel.
I always got that eye for schnitzel.
It's a little weird looking.
It's very odd looking, very dry looking.
And then and then I like this little like Jenga tower of fries.
Why do they stack them up that way?
I really didn't do it for the other dishes.
Yeah. Disco burger or Golden Disco cheeseburger.
You know what else?
My favorite is just called Kiss Kiss Dog, which I don't know if that's a reference to the band kiss or the term kiss kiss bang bang, which is how Europeans would describe like James Bond movies back in the in the day.
Hmm.
Hard to tell.
And then it's like some of it.
I feel like every theme restaurant is this way where like only four of the things have the theme and the theme.
In this case, some of them are rock bands.
So just in descending order of well done, you've got the red hot chili dog.
Great. Good. Got it.
Makes sense. Adds up.
And then right after that, Rolling Stones ribs.
Sort of OK, maybe.
And then that brings you to Jackson Sandwich.
Jackson Sandwich, I think is the best one easily.
Jackson, which Jackson Jackson, they have to hedge their bets because we don't know what Jackson's we contribute at this point.
Marlon or like maybe not even maybe it's maybe it's Randy Jackson, the judge, the American Idol judge.
That's his name, right? Yeah.
Joe Jackson. It's it's stepping out.
It's Joe Jackson. Right.
It's. It reminds me of a lot of how one of my favorite bizarre Michael Jackson clips.
He's being interviewed by Barbara Walters and he's very upset about the paparazzi term Jacko.
And he doesn't want anyone to call him Jacko anymore.
And that leads him to say, I'm not Jacko. I'm Jackson.
I'm Jackson.
Is it like I just calling Michael Jackson only Jackson is just giving me a seizure.
It doesn't make any sense. No. Was that a change when it was that a chain was event like Michael Jackson and they were like, well, we better be careful and let's take the Michael off.
But we don't want to lose the name because it sells so well.
Very upset about these allegations.
We has lost the right to have his full name in a sandwich.
From now on, it is Jackson Sandwich.
People love this very thin lettuce and onion sandwich.
What is that? There's eggs on the sandwich.
It's a shocking. It's been in a panini press.
This food across the board looks awful.
It is really I mean, Rolling Stone ribs, I thought was the worst one.
But as we've I've been looking at it, the weirdness of the very first one that just says ABBA veggie be and be is in quotations.
I don't know why that's unnerving me so much, but I don't care for it.
I think you would have to time a trip.
How about this? I'll go to I'll go to what's this place called?
I forget every time movieland.
Movieland, the Hollywood Park.
I think I've said this before.
I think where my personal kitsch dies is when it comes to food.
I can view ironically, I can have fun ironically.
I can't eat ironically.
I would rather die than eat any.
So I need to if I can bring like a cooler with food from real Italy, I just can't I can't be here during a meal.
That's I can't be done.
Huh. All right. Well, I mean, that's that's fine.
I would argue, though, this food, even eating it ironically, it's not it doesn't even look interesting.
It just looks cheap. Yeah.
Yeah. So I would approve that plan of yours if you're going to bring a cooler with like authentic Italian pasta.
Yeah. There might even be like somebody in the neighborhood, which, by the way, this is this place is like you walk out of rock star rock and roll restaurant.
And within a hundred feet, you're at somebody's house.
So if I could make a deal with whoever that like probably that person could make me a better sandwich than rock star rock and roll restaurant.
Some old like Italian grandmother was like right there and you make a deal with her and she like feeds you probably probably be like the greatest food I've ever had.
Right. Yeah.
So if you're going to this park, just go knock at her house.
Say podcast the ride sent you and then hopefully you don't get like shot.
She doesn't know what that phrase means.
There's only like three guns in all of Italy.
You know, that's right.
I think we're going to get like there's going to be a lot of Italian Italian penetration when this comes out for our podcast.
Italian penetration.
I look kiss kiss bang bang.
This is now the third or fourth time I've said the word penetration on podcast.
The right. Yeah.
Why do you keep going to that?
Someone's concerned about body nets going mask off in quarantine.
This one.
Yes.
My whole persona is a lie.
But face mask on.
Yes.
Thank you.
What if I one eighty?
What if I like horny heel turned?
And it was just a pervert from now on.
Just some episode you come in hot and like welcome to podcast the ride where horny guys fuck with cocks.
Whoa.
Hey, horny heel turn.
Scott Garner and Jason Chardon have left the meeting.
We check back in on the link just out of curiosity.
Four hours later and Mike's just streaming hardcore porn for no one else.
Yeah.
Yes.
And our listeners, we get like a hundred times more listeners.
Yeah.
Podcast way more successful.
All right.
Now, let's that's enough of that.
Let's get to the bottom of this wayfair business.
Again, we tell a hundred times more popular.
Yeah, we're ripping the lid off of the Hollywood pedophile rings.
Everyone look, they're kidnapping the kids and all we can do is try to distract from it by, you know, watching some hot adult porn.
Boy, I guess the ride.
Well, in deference to the new movement that we're all adhering to because we went crazy during quarantine, it's quad cast the right.
We replaced the P with a Q.
Yeah, we're all Q heads.
Yeah, we're all Q.
Yeah.
And it's just the libertine.
It's more relaxed vibe from Europe, too.
Yeah.
It was really the European.
The European vibe drove us into the arms of more already.
We're already getting so much looser just from being around this.
So I feel like, yeah, we may all three of us will have a cigarette next next episode and yeah, let's just keep free sexually.
God, what's next episode?
We got these zoom cameras on.
Let's do it naked.
Yeah.
And not just sitting in the chairs.
That's that's a cop out.
Let's stand naked and listeners just know the next time you hear us, we're standing up naked smoking cigarettes.
We're recording it at five a.m.
That's going to be a whole new podcast.
The ride.
Where the guys would be funny if I came out of this all and I had picked up smoking like long Ellen Ems like weird ones.
I don't think it's impossible.
I don't think so.
Everybody's losing it.
We're the we're going to be the people who went who pretended to go to Europe and came back super pretentious.
Right.
Yeah.
Well, that's what's in progress here so far.
And I think we're off to a great start.
I guess I guess I can say you survived.
I placed one of podcasts, the rides, European vacation.
This is great.
We're off to a great start.
We should get our we should get our passport stamped.
Oh, yeah, of course.
Yeah.
Let's let's get it clunk.
Hey, look, look at that.
It's a fun little design.
It says Italy.
But then what's that shape there?
I think well, isn't that it's a Dakota stick.
Oh, no.
But what better way to remember?
I'm comfortable with the.
Okay.
I like it.
Wow.
Beautiful.
A beautiful Dakota.
I mean, what better way to to emblemize the food of Italy than with the famous treat, the
Dakota stick.
Yeah.
Which which I was Googling as we were recording at the first result I found after typing Google
Dakota stick food.
Italy is that guy's blog.
Oh, really?
Okay.
So there is no other.
The Internet doesn't want it.
The Internet of Italy does not want to own up to the code stick.
The Internet of Italy.
They're trying to keep it secret.
Yeah.
Understandably.
Well, hey, that was a blast.
I think we're off to a fun start, a bizarre start.
I'm glad that we're skewing the usual topics and we're going to keep doing it.
So here's how this is going to work.
Next Friday, we'll be back in the main feed, like always, and we'll go elsewhere on this
great continent.
But there's going to be over on the second gate on a couple of these Wednesdays.
We're going to be doing little if you don't want to follow us on the main excursions,
we're going to be doing little little day trips.
Look, look, look, quick side ventures.
You see, and we got one of those coming up on Wednesday.
I don't want to say where we're going with any of these other than saying that we're
heading to the sea.
So if you want to join us on the sea near the sea, that's that's where we're heading.
If you want to follow our excursion in general, we'll be posting little maps and stuff
and they're fun on the Twitter.
But this is I think we're going to have some fun.
We're all we're going on.
How many people listen to the show?
We're going to thousands of persons tour group together.
And let's let's you know, everyone stay in one place.
Don't get lost as we head to our next adventure.
Mm hmm.
Yeah.
And the show is going to get very loose and very comfortable.
That's just what I'd like to say.
That's a promise.
Loosening up.
We are not we're not afraid of being naked, smoking cigarettes, accidentally singeing
our genitals with those cigarettes.
No, that's fine.
We don't fear a thing.
Bodiness is to be celebrated.
European Michael is the new way.
Yeah, I'm feeling yeah, I'm just feeling good.
You know, just feeling good.
We've all said a lot in the last two months.
Yeah, yeah, I see.
Yeah, I've been saying it often.
Yeah, I feel good.
I'm saying it a lot, but just but like many, many times in a row and also type it in.
Hundreds and hundreds of times, whichever way you need to get it out into your yeah,
into your underwood.
All right.
Oh, you know, and one more thing when we cover entire parks, as we'll be doing, I think
it's easy for stuff to fall through the cracks.
So if we missed anything about any of these parks, please let us know.
The podcast, the right at Gmail dot com, and we'll make sure that we, you know, we
cover anything that we left behind in these places or anything else.
We should go in Europe is already clearly we need to do this again.
And maybe just live here.
This is what the podcast is from now on.
Yeah, no more.
We never go back to Disneyland ever more.
Disney.
Yeah.
So this is episode one of a new podcast.
Hope you're enjoying it.
That is simultaneously about medieval times, sometimes be about porn and otherwise be about
European theme parks.
And we'll be back for more of that next week.
Yeah.
Well, all right.
All right.
What did Chow?
Chow Bella.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, visit www.david.com.
Please visit forever dog podcasts.com and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts,
Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram at forever
dog team and liking our page on Facebook.