Biraz ¡Hola!
Welcome
to the first podcast the ride European vacation second gate day trip side excursion.
That's a PTR EVSG DTSE.
I'm Scott Gardner and look who's along for the ride.
We didn't lose him back in Italy.
Mike Carlson is still here.
I am here.
I'm loving Europe.
I'm living it up.
I'm finding myself.
Yeah, well that's exploring.
I'm exploring.
That's where we last left you.
And yeah, I mean, it's been it's been wilder.
It's been it's been body or I mean, ever since that, I mean, we're looking at you on the
on the zoom and I don't know what's going on below the desk, but you are shirtless though.
I am shirtless.
I am but I have very thick pants on.
I will say that.
Oh, extra thick pants, but no shirt.
Just in case any European insects you aren't aware of where to start trying to eat through
your pants.
Properties, deadly European insects.
Yeah, I don't want them down there.
Yeah, to be suddenly exposed is you're a little you're you're above the waist looser now.
But yeah, but I do invite the European insects to feast on my upper half.
I am excited about that.
It's an open buffet.
Well, that's pretty that's pretty welcome.
That's the opposite of germophobia, I'd have to say.
Hey, how's Europe treating old Jason shared?
Good. I am wearing a large, oversized, old fashioned bathing suit.
It looks like a like a wet suit.
It's got white and blue stripes on it.
And of course, a Greek fisherman's cap to go along with the many of the denizens of
today's destination.
Oh, the denizens of Sweet Haven, you mean?
That's right.
Oh, sweet haven.
God must love you.
I'm so glad we all know the iconic, the very singable songs from 1980s pop.
Other than maybe like Islands of Adventure, Jason, is there a place you'd rather live
than Sweet Haven?
I you know, I maybe not.
I mean, this is all very new to me.
This one I kind of like knew as like an oddly enough fact, but I hadn't really dug
into the tourist, the Malta Tourism Board and the official website until the other
day. And I'm I'm pretty charmed by this place.
Yeah, me too. This seems this seems good.
I'll say right off the bat, we're sort of weighing, well, would we actually go to
these places or not?
And this one, absolutely, because the rest of Malta seems lovely.
And then you add this weird decaying film set to it.
Hell, yes.
Yeah, films that they paint it too, because in the movie it is very brown and now it is
pretty brightly colored.
This is what what I read about it is that it was shabby on purpose from Robert Altman's
direction because the costumes are so bright and cartoony and, you know, like olive oil is
primary color red.
So to make those pop, the town was supposed to be kind of dull, which made me think that's
sort of odd then to have a theme park that was directed to be dull.
But I guess so they have you're saying that they have brightened up the colors of
Sweet Haven.
Yes. And I guess we should say that what we are talking about is officially called
Popeye Village in the tiny little nation of Malta.
Mm hmm.
Which I knew almost nothing about.
I in my head it was part of Italy, but that's not true.
It's a little bit off the coast.
You know, if you look at it on a map, it looks like a little like speck of mud getting
flicked off of the old Italy boot.
Yeah. Yeah.
I had no knowledge of this.
I don't know. Do we completely say this is the set, the remaining set from the movie
Popeye that was made in 1979, came out in 1980?
Yeah. So it's like as if it's as if, you know, think of a famous movie.
They left everything up.
Star Wars, Star Wars.
Standing some sets left in the deserts of Tunisia, I believe.
Is that something like that?
Yeah. So like Luke's home became a theme park destination, essentially.
Yeah. Then think about that.
It didn't. It's probably some sort of destination.
But if it had, it's not quite as lovely as Malta out there in that desert.
Are there other examples of this where they left up a little town?
I want to say that the old west in Back to the Future 3 was left up, but then was
weirdly destroyed in a fire at some point as the real courthouse square at Universal
has been several times.
It's just cursed. It's a cursed layout.
It's a cursed like a town square overhead, I guess.
The big answer to your question would be, I don't know how much it is standing, but
in terms of tourism destinations, the Lord of the Rings stuff in New Zealand.
Oh, big, big tourism.
Spot. OK.
And these are kind of equally beloved properties.
Popular movies just about made the same amount of money with inflation.
Sure. Counting for inflation.
I the Popeye movie.
And again, just to fill in some background for the listeners starring
Robin Williams, very huge at the time.
Robin Williams. 1980.
Shelley Duvall is Robin Williams is Popeye.
Shelley Duvall is olive oil.
Robert Altman has made Nashville Mash the long goodbye.
And then he makes Popeye.
And it is cope.
It is like produced in conjunction.
Walt Disney Pictures and Paramount.
So this is a Robert Evans overseeing this production and co-directed
the backup director of this movie was cocaine.
And you can just just kind of feel it in the pratfalls and some of the
performance choices.
Um, that is correct.
It, you know, I'm no expert on any of these people, but
Robert Altman, I believe, was a pretty big drug user at the time.
Robin Williams were certainly aware of his his use of substances.
The music was done by Harry Nilsson and on most sets, especially
Harry Nilsson, famously, like also gregarious, hard drug, hard drinking
musician, one of my favorites ever.
Now, why would the musician be a problem?
Well, because in this case, they flew him out and he made music
on the set and they did little concerts every night.
They'd watch dailies every night and do concerts every night.
And just everyone got hammered for both of these things.
Um, and I'm forgetting one.
Oh, oh, Robert Evans, who was pretty hardcore
busted for cocaine in the fallout from this, like during the post
production of this movie, which kind of triggered a big collapse
of his career, although he sort of got it back together and was, you know,
a producer and kind of a funny oddity up until his death.
But yeah, it really the cocaine blew up for him not long after this movie.
Yeah, cocaine everywhere.
I am not look, believe it or not, I'm not a big drug user.
Maybe Europe will open that up for me.
But I will say the parties that they seem to have every night seem awesome.
Yeah, man.
I mean, think about the people who are there.
I mean, yeah, I think, you know, Mike and I, I think we both dig Nielsen a lot.
And then there's all these other like his Van Dyke Parks is there, you know,
what, like the Beach Boys collaborator.
This guy, Klaus Vorman was around, who was his drummer, who also did the artwork
for the revolver album cover.
There's like the coolest musicians in the world and Robin Williams.
Free. This is his first movie.
So he's you know, that's prime cool Robin Williams.
All the everyone around is awesome.
A beautiful part of the world.
Yes. Although I think it rained all the time.
It was like super rainy and like the the sea level rose,
which caused them to have to build.
OK. Oh, not as ideal.
But still, there's got to be some rain sounds good living in Los Angeles.
And let's not forget a party animal and Robert Altman,
a regular collaborator, character actor Paul Dooley.
Paul Dooley is hanging out.
He's playing Jay Wellington Wimpy.
And this is a thing I always forget about.
Paul Dooley is the voice of Sarge, the military jeep in the Cars movies.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Wow.
He's one. He's very one of those guys.
He's in the Christopher Guest movies like I think I didn't even realize
that was him because he's younger than a lot of what I've seen him in in Popeye
in his role as just don't don't ever not say the full name, Jason.
Give it to me one more time.
Jay Wellington Wimpy, who, of course, will gladly pay you Tuesday
for a hamburger today.
Your favorite character in fiction.
I you know, it's kind of neck and neck with sluggo.
I would love to take on any either either role.
I've aged out of sweepy.
So don't sell yourself short.
I've admitted that I've come around to that.
But maybe the aging Irishman, the aging technology.
Oh, well, I'd love to play like you tween sweepy.
Yeah, tween sweepy.
Oh, in the sort of Riverdale.
Yes, in our date. Yeah.
Sweet Havens. Sweet Havens.
Serious weekly Popeye reboot in which Jason plays multiple characters.
Why the fuck not?
You just that's everything we're in.
We're in the slop.
We may as well roll around more in it. Oh, yeah.
I mean, yeah, look, it's it's coming.
It's just a matter of do we do it or not? Yeah.
And I say we hey, let me hang out and do coke on the set.
That's all I want to do. I don't need to be part of it.
This is Jason's show and I don't want to get in the way. Oh, sure.
Well, first things first, we got to find a micro nation in Europe.
We have to spend seven months building a town.
Dear God, this is the most complicated thing ever.
Did you guys catch why this is this was shot in Malta?
I didn't see it. Not, but I was wondering.
I think that the deal is that once Robin Williams came on board.
And by the way, this this the idea of making a live action Popeye
I think it first grew out of that Robert Evans lost the rights to produce Annie,
which became the 1982 Carol Burnett Annie.
He didn't get to make that.
So he had a big meeting. It was like, what other comics?
I want to make a comic. I want to fuck them.
Fuck those any people. I'm getting a comic movie out.
Somebody suggested Popeye. What's that?
I was trying to do the voice.
Fuck them. Oh, that's Robert Evans.
Voice is one of my favorites to do.
Pat Oswald does it and Bob Odenkirk does it and Michael McKeon does it.
But it's like one of the most fun, one of those fun voices.
This is you. The guy was scared.
You bet your ass I wasn't.
Like it is is is the did he sound like that before?
Or is that super nasal thing due to the cocaine?
OK, and a dray to probe.
He he is he's a guy who and we cannot have this turn into an
an Evans episode because I'd love to.
But he is a guy, I think, always like he loved the old 40s movie.
So he's always kind of talked like this, I think.
So when you watch it, he's like, I'm Robert Evans.
And he still has a little nails a thing going on because he wasn't so crazy
with the cocaine.
But then when he's narrating his book on tape, the kid stays in the picture.
It is full on like his nose is collapsed.
Like there is like you can't he's not getting anything out through the nose.
It's not exactly like this.
And this is how he's talking.
And you're like, he's not breathing.
There's no air going through his nose when he's talking.
I'm just a pure anecdote machine.
I do this 24 7 and if I stop, I die.
And Jason and I met him like seven years ago.
Yes, we have a.
What? Yeah, we have a photo with him.
I guess he put out a follow up book and we went to they were having a signing
at Roman's this big bookstore in Pasadena.
And at the end, like he he was like signing autographs.
Well, well, well, they said they first of all, we went there.
And my first thought while hearing him speak is, oh my God, this man is about to die.
He's going to die tomorrow, like tomorrow he'll be dead
because he was just like kind of way going and out.
And then all of a sudden he would be like, I talked to I talked to Fred
Zafor a couple of and I told him, Fred, this is a great movie in there with you.
What are you doing?
Wasting your time with the kitchen with your spaghetti.
Like you would go into one of his like anecdotes from the book, which is that
anecdote from the book for real.
And then he would kind of drift off and forget what the question was.
And they told like they told us no photos.
He's already signed the books.
Do not come up after the to him after this.
Yes. How did you then?
Well, everybody well, everyone bum rust.
Everyone bum rust.
Roman's one of the best places to do a book signing.
They're so organized and stuff, but so many people just went around
the other side of the table and stood next to him.
And we were like, we were early in the line and we're like, well,
everyone else did it.
So and I I said one of the weirdest, dumbest things I've ever said,
the most embarrassing things I've ever said to like a famous person that I was meeting.
And I said, Hi, Mr.
Evans, I'm a young actor.
Huh? Why did that come out of my mouth?
I knew he wasn't making movies.
I didn't think he was going to put me in a movie.
That's not some delusion I had.
Yeah, right. I said that.
Yeah, right. Show me some ID.
And I gave him a setup for the best Robert Evans line he ever could have given.
He goes, Well, I'm an old actor.
And I was like, wow, he did it.
He did like a line off of my line.
Oh, the other notable person there in attendance, he's Butler.
Yes, very old man.
But I like a spry young chicken.
He's so energetic.
And he's in that video that they that somebody made of Evans's house, his famous house,
which I'm forgetting the name of it.
It's got like some fancy name.
And it's the house that you ask.
It's like why it's like Wildwood or something.
Yeah, it's not that.
But Jack Nicholson famously had to go and beg the person who bought that house when Evans lost it.
He lost it because he was out of money and he had to like, I don't know,
it gave up the bank, took it, and then somebody bought it.
And Jack Nicholson, because he's such good friends with Evans,
had to go and beg this man to sell the house back to Robert Evans.
And he did. So Nicholson got Robert Evans's house back.
Anyway, it can't be a Robert Evans episode.
I can't. I've got a story that's very similar to that, that I just found that involves
Evans and groveling and using celebrities to grovel.
Or maybe I can head back into it from what we're saying that he.
Oh, he wanted to make a comic movie.
He ends it up on Popeye.
Every it's weird that Robert Altman ended up doing it because they talked to the other directors.
It was all always going to be like great on tour.
Hal Ashby.
Why am I forgetting the other one?
Like the only people it was like the greatest of the greats.
Dustin Hoffman was in consideration for a while.
They want to build a Radner to play Olive Oil.
But her manager, Bernie Brillstein, said under no circumstances should you go to an island
with Robert Evans and Robert Altman.
Good advice.
Even though she didn't she never really got that great of a movie career.
And he even was like, it's good money and it's a good boost.
But for your safety, you should pass on this film.
Probably is our move.
They ended up with Robin Williams, but that caused them to have to shoot
in the winter due to Mork and Mindy's schedule.
So now, you know, this probably would have been shot in New England if the summer was an option.
But now they had to find somewhere where it is sunny during the winter,
which is where they ended up with Malta.
It's possibly that, but also possibly that
both Altman and Evans wanted to get away from the studio and be in a remote place
where probably they couldn't get bothered and where they could do whatever they want,
including lots and lots of cocaine.
There's several crazy stories about getting the cocaine around to the island,
one of which, and just to credit him, I'm pulling a little bit of info
from a medium article by Alex Papadimas, a Grantland writer
who wrote a great thing about if you want to learn more about Popeye Village.
But he he quotes a crew member, David Levy, who recalls smuggling
pharmaceutical contraband through Maltese customs inside
human sized dummies.
They pretended, well, obviously, this film is going to, you know,
it's it's a seaside thing is going to be lots of bodies falling out of ships.
You see, there'll be so many cannonballs going off.
Twenty dummies will net another dummy shipment.
So we need 200 dummies,
200 dummies filled with cocaine,
200 Popeye's full crew, Popeye's whole ship crew.
The question is, did they still insert the cocaine
via the butthole?
Was it still is it still a cavity situation?
I insist on it.
It's a tradition. It wouldn't feel right.
Should the dummies
That's too I'm too excited.
I'm too excited to do the voice.
Should the cocaine go in the butthole?
You bet it should.
Do I wish the dummies still said ouch when you were pulling it out?
You bet I do.
You can't have it all.
But the other story.
Oh, sorry.
You know, I have to import multiple glass water bottles of
Playboy Mansion grotto water to preserve myself.
Since that's since I sleep in a water coffin
filled of the grotto water, you bet your ass I did.
The only thing that works.
My skin will completely decompose otherwise.
So much fun.
Yeah, yeah.
So one more Evans thing similar to this bizarre Nicholson.
I guess, boy, this guy will not only pull in a name,
he'll pull in a name for the most pathetic reasons.
I'm a little confused by this story, but I think what happened is
he packed two big steamer trunks with all of his belongings
and in those belongings, lots and lots of cocaine.
Then his luggage failed to arrive in Malta.
By then, as Jason sort of alluded to, they had to get in real close
with the Maltese government.
And he's, you know, he's he's got a good relationship now with the prime minister.
And in order to get this luggage back and to make sure that some rando
doesn't find it and all the cocaine inside, he goes to the prime minister
and he says, you must conduct an exhaustive search for my bags.
Well, I can't do that.
I can't drop everything and make all my people find your bags.
And he says, but you must, because in the bags
is a letter to you, the prime minister from my dear friend Henry Kissinger.
Oh, and that is he is look, he talks about him in his book so much.
Oh, OK. Oh, so the Kissinger thing is a big it's a big thing.
It's a big thing.
He makes him come to the Godfather premiere.
Yes. And what is my one of my I don't I don't know how to explain.
He calls it Dr Kissinger, Dr Henry Kissinger.
He's seeing with the hard Kissinger kissing her.
Yeah, it's like he's he's in a he's in like a meeting.
Like it's like it's like Robert, I can't come to the Godfather premiere.
He's like, I need you there. I need you there.
I need you there. Will it be the same without you, Dr Kissinger?
You bet it won't.
Um, so then so this worked and like, OK, well, I must receive
these bags with this letter,
conduct the search and it was the luggage was recovered the next day.
Here it is, Dr. Mr. Evans.
He was able to get the cocaine out with anyone noticing.
And then he immediately got on a plane back to the US
so he could go talk to Kissinger and get him to write a letter with the wrong date.
He could pretend there was always a letter in there to the prime minister.
I you know, this kind of fits in good with the
Maltese prime minister story.
I read a profile, I think it was a screenwriter a few years ago,
and he had a deal with Paramount and he went to go look at his office.
You know, he had an office and he was on the lot
and he walked down the hall and he saw an office door that said Robert Evans on it.
And the guy is like producer or executive.
He was working with he was like, hey, does Evans still produce?
Like, that's pretty could we get him on there?
And they're like, oh, no, no, Evans.
Evans is on on like kind of a holding a courtesy contract.
He doesn't produce anymore.
But, you know, the thing about Robert Evans is he can keep a secret.
There's a there's a line item there.
It was apparently a line item or an under the table item of like,
well, we got to keep Evans on staff because he knows too much.
I know where the bodies are buried. Yeah.
Yeah. Will I will I say where they're buried?
You bet I will.
You know, not only OK, so on the island of Malta, all of these crazy characters,
Robert Williams, Aldman, Evans, Nielsen.
I'm going to add one more to the list.
I can't believe I didn't put this together sooner.
So in order for all of this to happen,
everything from the hiring of Altman to the casting of Robin Williams to
we're going to build an entire village in Malta, and it's going to take seven months.
The person who ultimately had to sign off on all this
is the person above Robert Evans, who I think at this time was
the head of production at Paramount.
This was he wasn't his own producer.
He was like doing this as part of Paramount and the CEO of Paramount
at the time, one Mr. Michael Eisner.
So, so therefore,
you know, everything it's this is in the kid stays in the picture
that he brings up, hey, what about that kid from Mork and Mindy?
And Eisner says he's great.
But do you think he can carry a film?
Strangely,
Robert Evans' response is this is after Dustin Hoffman had dropped out.
All right. So Eisner, do you think he can carry a film?
Who can? All I know is he is Popeye, not a Jewish Popeye.
What? What?
Yeah, I don't know.
He was like still there.
That was his way of excusing, like, well, said to lose Hoffman,
but at least it's not a Jewish.
What a weird thing to be hung up on and then put in your book.
He essentially says the same thing about Gilda Radner, too.
Like, well, at least this olive oil won't be kosher.
What? I think he's Jewish, too.
So maybe he considers that part of the hour all messed around.
But still, like, why?
Yeah, I guess you're not that far.
Because I feel like when he talks about the Godfather,
other people of that time talk about the Godfather, like all these
goddamn Italians making a movie, I can't wrap my head around it.
Like, so it's like, what's next?
The Irish making a movie? I don't know.
I tell you, he constantly his jokes about Francis Ford Coppola,
who he did not get along with, is all about him being in the kitchen
making spaghetti.
That's just that's like his go to.
I believe it's that I believe Evans claims that they delivered
like a 90 minute cut of the Godfather that was bad.
And he goes, what happened, Francis?
You've made a great film.
Where is it in the kitchen with your spaghetti?
Could barely see the celluloid.
There was so much spaghetti stuffed all over the film.
And I think Francis Ford Coppola has a much different account.
He is a page of the script soaked in sauce.
Yeah. So in his account, there wasn't perpetual marinara
just pouring out of his beard. Right.
Or is it a little bit?
Why does he why does he make Coppola sound like a garbage pail kid
just covered in spaghetti and marinara?
He yeah.
Spilled everywhere.
Sometimes he'd slip it.
He'd spend 15 minutes just trying to get up and then flopping right back down.
Do you want a hand, Francis?
No, no, no. He'd say he was too proud.
It's crazy. I think Pat and Oswald's
Pat and Oswald talking about the book on tape is like it's Lucifer
dictating his memoirs.
Yeah. With a martini on his belly.
Well, which relatedly, because I did.
I searched in the book for mentions of Eisner.
And the last one in the book is that in the 90s,
he got a call or a memo from Disney
that was specifically at Eisner's request, apparently.
It was to see if he would be interested in voicing Hades in Hercules.
Whoa. I forgot that.
Or wow. Really?
He's come up many times on the show.
If you don't remember, that's the character voiced by our favorite actor
of all time, James Woods.
Well, now, OK.
I guess I shouldn't assume, but I don't know.
We love the guy.
I love him.
I don't follow.
I don't follow actor gossip much nowadays.
I don't know what's going on.
Their personal life is for them.
And I don't I don't look into it.
It's none of my business.
But, you know, James Woods did play it in this very like slick
talking agent kind of way.
So I think maybe in the back, they were sort of thinking
maybe it's sort of a Robert, Robert Evans type.
And why didn't he do it?
Did they realize he'd be bad?
Maybe they thought to be like the villain of the film who has to carry it.
He's not I mean, he was an actor.
He was in the movie The Matador.
Oh, he started as an actor.
Wait, or no, no, the bad.
I may mixing it up.
It's the subtle.
It's the Sun Also Rises.
Yes, the sun. Sorry.
Thanks. The Matador is Frank Sinatra.
Is that right?
Oh, I don't know.
It's a movie that he produced, maybe.
Yeah. But he wanted to be good.
He was an actor to begin with.
And then he saw the producer on set who defended him when he had done a bad job
and that the producer yelled, the kid stays in the picture.
And that's why what Robert Evans wanted to be a producer and not an actor.
Wow. Wow.
Because that's where the power is.
And then cut to him years later, controlling this little city.
But here's what I'm thinking is that, OK, this this set was built.
And then today it is still a themed experience that you can go to.
Doesn't that make this really the first themed experience commissioned by Michael Eisner?
Hmm. Very good point.
Pre dates Disney.
This is like the big this is the demo for what this is him
like starting to put plant flags all over the globe.
This is Eisner territory.
I think you're right. I agree.
Yeah, because I mean, the the construction of this was so intense.
Like we said, it took seven months to build the film set.
They also had to build a breakwater, which is a kind of seawall
to keep the raging winter seas at bay and not in Sweet Haven Harbor.
And they also had to build an access road to get to the town to get to the set.
There wasn't that. They didn't have that.
They didn't have a road.
They had to build an access road.
So, yeah, it seems foolish to demolish it all.
Give it a fresh coat of paint.
Put a couple of bars there, a couple of restaurants and might as well.
Yeah, yeah, there was that was like it was kind of the deal with Malta.
Like, hey, if you if you want to keep this feel free.
One more thing stemming from all this, I think.
So what ended up happening here, as you said, all this crazy.
They have to build road roads now.
They got to build a seawall.
This budget is spiraling out of control.
And even though this film was shot in Malta, partially to get away from Michael Eisner,
he did go visit the set at some point.
And this is in the kid stays in the picture.
I'm showing you guys a photo.
This this has to be Eisner on the set in Malta, right?
That looks like a look at it, isn't it?
Look at his messy hair.
Yeah, look at this.
I love it.
Gun this kind of like more hipster.
Devil may care more a lot more hair.
Not as balding at this point.
His clothes. Yeah, his clothes like are actually kind of cool a little bit
versus maybe later when he just looked like, as I said on the episode with about
the ducks, it seemed like he had a hat that was run over by a car.
A little cooler than that.
Yes, a little cooler than that.
He's still he's still got the wild hair that he always has in different ways
in pictures, which is what we like about him versus an eye.
Looks like a cool young actor.
He would still wear this shirt later.
He would just have a dress shirt, a collared shirt under it
and a collared shirt over top of the multi shirt.
Do we think he's is he is he a little handsome here?
Can Eisner get it?
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
I think he can for sure get it here.
He's got a cool like he's got a like a real bad boy kind of scowl going on here, too.
Yeah, I'm trying to think of an actor he reminds me of.
There's a little bit of a I don't know.
He did.
Is not so much in the fit, but the style.
I feel like Adam Driver would dress like this and be all scruff like that.
Yeah, I dress like this.
He looks like all the the most devil may care
hunks like Adam Driver and Jason Sheridan.
Yeah.
Oh, no, I'm just seeing the text under this picture that the next film,
Shelley Duvall made with Stanley Kubrick's The Shining.
This plot. Oh, that's right.
This poor woman.
I know when I was pulling that for that weird kosher quote,
there's also that he says
I remember it says I lied, telling Eisner that Duvall would be the big screen's
next Lucille Ball.
It was the biggest white lie I ever told.
Wait, why? Why would he?
He's saying Shelley Duvall's bad.
What is this? Yeah.
Why would he say that?
Unless he's covering for himself, having said that and pretending now it's a lie.
That he had no inside info about her.
Right, like he had to sell he had to sell her because he liked her.
Why would he put her in the movie being like her?
And then like once maybe she didn't become as big as Lucille Ball,
he was like, I just just kidding.
I didn't mean it.
She does a good olive oil in the movie, but two hours of olive oil is a lot.
Well, two hours of Popeye is a lot.
All of it. All of it is a lot.
I'm curious about your guys opinion about the movie.
Not to drag out Eisner, let me say one more thing.
What happened was they're spending all this money.
He went to the set and was like, oh, my God, this thing is a disaster.
This is spiraling out of control.
I need to get another studio involved to recoup some of these costs.
Hey, it's a family movie.
Maybe I could go talk to those folks over at Disney.
And that is the first that Michael Eisner ever interacted with Disney
or went on the lot. He went and talked to everyone.
Everyone knows all the beloved CEO characters at this point.
Card Walker, of course, and we determined is this silver fox, right?
We talked. Yeah, I decide that.
Get it. We said, yeah, he can get it as well.
Everybody in this group can get Ron Miller, I think, was very handsome.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
So they agreed and they cofinanced it and it saved the movie.
And then a couple of years later, Ron Miller called Eisner and said,
Hey, would you want to take over as the head of the studio?
And he said, well, I'm pretty happy at Paramount.
I'd want to do more than that.
I'd want to like run everything.
I want to run the theme parks.
And that was what began his tenure.
So Popeye and this place are like a key component
in the tale of the rise of the king.
Wow.
I never thought of it like that to frame his rise, like the rise of the king.
But it's perfect.
Yeah. Yeah. This is this really I mean, this this makes me want to see
like the young Eisner Chronicles. Oh, my God.
As I said, Adam Driver, there's any way to get him on the show.
Maybe it's us producing a full season of television about his life.
Oh, that might get his attention.
If he has to like sign a form saying it's OK.
And then he asks, like, what's the tone of it?
Oh, it's incredibly is like worshipping you.
They're going to hire like a really fuckable actor to play you.
And you're going to go on adventures.
You're going to like surf the seawall in Malta.
You're going to like be putting the set back together yourself,
braving the elements.
I think he'd be on board for that.
I would have to think he'd like, OK, so a very.
You're making me look like the coolest man in the world.
Yeah, I want to make this.
Yeah, this sounds good.
Um, anyway, all this is backstory.
And I'm fine with saying all this because I, you know, as far as I can tell,
there's not that tend to do in this place.
It's mainly more about like the that it exists and the story.
But as we head over head into the village itself,
what do you guys think of this film was fighting the sea
and doing all the coke worth it?
It I, you know, I sort of rewatch it yesterday.
I haven't seen it in a few years, but my opinion on it is like,
it's interesting.
Yeah, it's an interesting.
Yeah. Experiment.
I think I rewatch Jason.
We were talking. Jason loves it, I think.
OK. I I rewatch it.
And I remember like half watching it
a few years ago.
Trying to do to
Marissa Strickland, I were writing a Popeye sketch and we're like,
I wish what to watch that movie.
And we like half watched it and like kind of checked out because it was so weird.
But I watched it last night and paid attention.
And I was kind of surprised how much I liked it.
I mean, there's a lot of character actor weirdos in it.
It takes some very big swings.
Like there's a lot of pratfalls.
I I thought it was interesting that it doesn't get the credit of trying to
recreate the comics and the cartoon in live action in the way that
like, oh, Sin City recreated these panels.
Oh, look at that.
Look at look, it's all the Avengers like in this one drawing.
And it's like, well, Popeye movie did the same shit.
And it was a lot weirder and more interesting and in some ways less successful.
But in other ways, like like when Pluto gets beat up at the end
and he swims away and he's yellow, like coward yellow.
I thought like, that's that's really funny.
Like, that's great.
And like they they make you wait for the spinach.
Like the spinach is the equivalent of like Captain America getting Thor's hammer.
And I was like, wow, this is really something like the ending
of the movie I thought was pretty fun.
There's some very slow moments.
There's a lot of Robert Altman ensemble weirdos in it, which we're happy to see.
I think the one guy is the guy in Charlie and the Chocolate Factory.
Is that right? It's Slugworth.
The tax collector.
Oh, yeah, maybe the same actor. Check.
But yeah, I mean, I think it's fun.
I don't think it cracks the top five Robert Altman movies for me.
Yeah. But it's really
it's really odd, but it's no Nashville or Long Goodbye or Mash or anything.
Yeah, I love Nashville.
Yeah. And I feel like I'm supposed to like it.
And I don't I gave it a shot before this.
And yeah, I really drifted.
I definitely drifted the proper national Popeye.
OK, because now I.
Yeah, I don't.
This is interesting.
Oh, that's the weird thing.
It's like it feels like it's like it's like they're talking to no like,
I don't know. It's like.
It's not there.
It's what's going on on the screen is interesting,
but it's like that doesn't feel like it's being directed at anything.
Feels like that weird naturalistic and film from really far away.
And you don't really know where it's going.
I mean, look, I love Nilsson very much and that the song He Needs Me.
It was reused in Punch, Drunk, Love, I think is is magic.
That is such a delightful song and a delightful performance from Shelly Duvall.
Then on the flip side, here's where the movie really
what I have a really hard time with is everything is food, food, food.
Everything is chow, chow, chow.
I get to that and like, I don't know where to.
I don't know what file to put this in my brain.
Is this so bad? It's good.
Is it is it?
Is it just good?
And I don't understand.
I don't. It's from one of my favorite musicians.
But why is it just everything is food being said over and over?
The other song, it's like he's large and he's large.
There's so much these weird meandering repetitious songs.
And I can only imagine being a child and watching this film at the time.
Like what this is, what Popeye is.
Yeah, yeah.
It feels like it's I mean, it is similar to Dick Tracy, which I watched recently.
But Dick Tracy is still more much more of a movie.
More of a real movie than this.
These are the these are the two these are the auteur
comic films that have that were that themed experiences throughout of.
And I can't really think of more on that list.
I think this movie and then Dick Tracy.
I mean, this is going to be disproved by like Superman and Batman.
But these two movies, Dick Tracy and Popeye not being bigger successes,
I think set back comic movies because I would always read for years
like they can't make an X-Men movie.
It just doesn't look right on the screen.
These characters just won't look right.
And I think that there was like the failure of Popeye and Dick Tracy
and specifically them going for the look of the comics
made people think and be very insecure, which is why X-Men has like black leather.
And there's no way Wolverine can be in a yellow costume
that won't look right on film.
I remember reading this like a lot.
Oh, sure, sure, sure.
Well, because some of it didn't work out well at all.
I mean, they they started filming the movie without his big muscle arms.
Yes, they didn't arrive in time.
So that's why he's in a trench coat for a long time.
And then even then, they like it definitely looked bizarre.
Today, however, you know, the arms are have their final resting place
at a pretty cool spot, not not a planet Hollywood,
but rather at the Comedy and Magic Club in Hermosa Beach,
the club that Leno would test his monologue that for many years and post
the tonight show, like when he didn't even have to be doing it anymore.
Let me just show you guys a photo of not just the arms,
but also our friend Ryan Perez happily sitting under the
this important piece of film prosthetic history.
Wow. So, yeah, you have I've never been to the club.
You saw Mr. Leno one night. I know I did.
The whole Moonbeam City writing staff all went together.
And boy, the moment he came out, like seeing him in person,
I think Tommy Blatch said it was like Frankenstein walking in there.
Whoa. I've never seen Frankenstein in person.
And you're just like staring at his proportions for like, wow, that really is.
His head really is like that.
Wow. But going to the Animal Actors Show.
Well, a real live Leno.
Was he still doing it there before pandemic?
Is he still doing it now during pandemic?
Oh, no.
Well, he or his or did Leno get invited to Chappelle's comedy camp?
You guys seen Chappelle's comedy camp?
I know all about Chappelle's comedy camp.
Yes. Yeah.
It's a weird assortment.
Like, you know, yeah, there is Silverman's there.
Louie is there and Jaleel White is there.
Oh, I miss Jaleel. I miss Jaleel.
Jaleel's saying, I mean, I'm psyched on that.
If you're going to have a comedy camp, you do watch Family Matters
and go like he is a truly gifted physical comedian.
I think it's easy to be snarky about Urkel, but he is.
So is Jaleel there testing out new
pratfalls and roller skate hijinks and Chappelle's giving him notes?
I would love to hear how mad he is at Ben Schwartz for getting the Sonic voice.
Oh, that's right.
He was Sonic on both cartoons from the early 90s and a good Sonic.
So why wasn't there a Peter Cullen type campaign that it must be Jaleel?
Good question. I don't know.
But that Jaleel is my Sonic.
Yeah. Yeah. No offense.
I respect for your Sonic. Yeah.
Where were we? The film?
I mean, it looks crazy, which is very,
you know, makes you want to go to this place.
You definitely are like, you can't believe it's real.
It's one of the most ambitious sets ever constructed.
And it's crazy that it's still real.
This is this is bonkers. Yeah. Big swings.
I mean, it's crazy to think that the same guy made this and like
I watched California split not too long ago, which is just
Elliot Gould and George Segal, drunk gamblers,
just kind of going from one big win to the next.
And it is weird that they use the same sort of like he always had a ton of mics
going, so you catch snippets of audio like like Jane was like,
you can hear olive oil in the boxing sequence.
You can hear her voice in the middle of the crowd.
And it's like, oh, yeah, that's weird,
because he's probably using the same setup from all those other movies.
Yeah. A bunch of overlapping.
People talking much like a Zoom podcast record.
You could think of it as being, you know, annoying or fraught with errors,
or you could think that what us and everyone is doing right now is Altman.
Yeah, I like that. Good. Yeah.
Yeah. Give us some credit.
We're always if you hear us talking over each other saying, no, no, no, you go.
It's it's always a tribute to Altman.
Sorry, am I frozen? You guys go.
No, no, no, Mike, you go.
No, no, you're Robert Evans impression.
No, no, no, no, you wait.
No, are you am I?
Yeah. Well, the kids days of the picture.
Am I frozen? You bet I am.
Government vouchers.
So sorry. Are we there?
We said we said all the peripheral stuff.
Can we talk about the about the place?
Popeye Village, the place?
Yes, please. Yeah.
Um, I OK.
Let's see. The set consisted of 19 wooden buildings.
It they had to bring in eight tons of nails.
That's important to know eight tons of nails.
I mean, the whole I guess the article I read said
made a point of saying no indigenous timber on Malta.
So they do import everything from Holland and shingles from Canada.
And there were no roads, as you said.
This is so complicated and it leads you to a place that, you know,
it looks a little cruddy on purpose.
That being said, oh, my God, the views of the sea
in this place and the cliff walls, I mean, because part of this,
but it seems like this place is a mix of being a go into Popeye World and hey,
there's a big trampoline down there or going out in a going out in a bikini.
Like it's like part just regular euro beach and then part.
And, you know, basically see the set of an art film.
Yeah, it's I was thinking, should it be called like Malta Popeye Sea?
As a name for its theme park.
Good punch up. Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Popeye Sea.
I think that's good.
And then, yeah, it's just like, you know, you can go on the beach
or you can walk through a set.
Well, there's a dance.
A lot of dancing. You're right. I'm sorry.
A lot of dancing.
And maybe I can throw to this this clip, Jason, your zoom background right now
is from the video that all I'll play a second of here.
This this really gives you the vibe pretty well.
Imagine listeners that we are now showing you Popeye and olive oil
as they looked in the film, except that they are not Robin Williams
and Shelley DeVille, but rather two random Italians.
Here we go.
And then the shots of nice sights and boats over the with the trolls song.
Waterfalls.
It's messing around.
Let's see, let's see some other dancing here.
You get a dancing Pluto in there.
Pluto, who is just wearing a double XL.
Let's describe the Pluto that we're looking at.
They spent all the money on the Popeye outfit, a little money on olive oil.
And then Pluto is just wearing like a double XL polo shirt and like a pillow.
A pillow shoved in. Yes. Yeah.
The cheapest
fat costume you could ever.
Yeah, the most filthy beard.
It's it's pretty delightful and not a costume you expect to see dancing
to Timberlake.
And then later,
I mean, we could just talk about the freeze frames this year.
Is, you know, they're kind of waving their arms back and forth.
The Pluto and olive oil.
And there's a bunch of like bikini folks and kids,
peach chairs, three, like sloppy flash mob
and like some inflatable stuff bouncing around.
My favorite is when it cuts wide and then there's a bunch of people
doing the Macarena.
Well, and the blink, if you miss a character dancing,
there is a dancing poop deck pappy in a couple of shots.
There is. Yes.
The Ray Walston old man, the father character played by
a 20 year old, who is this poop deck pappy?
This is the life I would love to go here.
No question about it.
Why would I love to be in this flash mob? Yeah.
Oh, and there's one costume character early on.
There's like a bear.
Like there's there's just an unidentified like
bear. Yes, that's correct.
And I have some info about this.
You say bear.
Aaron said dog somehow inscrutably.
Everyone is wrong. It is a rabbit, which makes no sense.
It's just isn't right. It's not I'm looking at it.
It's not it's not a rabbit.
And I know this because they do a big Easter thing every year.
This is strangely as Easter is big in Tokyo Disney.
So also is it big at all the Popeye's?
And this year they had to shut it down, obviously due to COVID-19,
which led to this an old wistful post of the bunny and this strange caption.
Hashtag happy Easter, hashtag everyone from our very own Ricky,
the hashtag bunny, a very different hashtag Easter.
No, ashtag egg hunts and no hashtag rabbit hopping.
Ricky is hashtag celebrating hashtag alone this year.
There's so there's so many more hashtags I'm getting tired of.
Oh, wait, let me let me say the full sentence.
Ricky is celebrating alone this year, but that is what's best.
Hashtag social distancing, hashtag space, safe, hashtag stay home.
We will hashtag hop hashtag next year.
Hashtag do not worry. Hashtag longing for summer.
The masterpiece of a hashtag post.
Who does social media for Popeye Village?
I don't. I'm a genius.
The altman of social media.
Wow. Ricky. Yeah.
So that's Ricky the bunny, not Ricky the rabbit.
Ricky the bunny who's not in Popeye, as far as we know.
No, I haven't heard of that one.
Not in the extended universe.
Ricky, good news, they rolled the stone back from the cave
and it was empty so you can hang out in there for a little while.
It's cool.
The unforgiving Maltese son will dance alone in this hashtag.
Now, does the extended Popeye verse perhaps feature,
I don't know, a dabbing Santa
with some with some elves
who seem to be getting interested in something else during this dance performance.
They're checking out.
There's one of the articles I read about visiting this place said,
just everyone seems stoned.
Like, it's just all these like half committed teenagers who, you know,
they like leave and do more drugs and all have sex with each other.
If they've kept the Altman spirit alive.
Scott, what if I ever tell you that's actually not Santa, it's baby New Year.
Well, you think it much like the bar that you thought that was a dog.
It's a bunny. No, that's baby New Year.
Is that based on something or is that just?
I don't know.
It can't be right.
Everything's topsy turvy here and it played Malta pop, I see.
That could have been right.
So as we if that video conveys it,
this is it's a healthy mix of like it seems like
so there's 19 buildings, at least what's in them.
It's a lot of it is like museums about the film or when Robin Williams passed away.
There's a little like exhibit paying homage to him.
You can go see you can go pay homage to Altman and Evans and Williams,
and then you can go dab and Macarena
with most your clothes off.
Not a ton to do, as you were saying.
It doesn't seem like it.
That's why I'm not too concerned about all the time spent at the beginning,
because I'm looking at the.
Like what there is like the Explorer
section, just as I as I jump around,
you know, like here's here's parts of the of the attractions.
Anchor Square, this platform is re closed for refurbishment at the moment.
Anchorage rest closed at the moment, waiting to be refurbished.
The Santa's Toy Town, that's only open half the year.
Olive Oil's house. So cool.
Olive House is being refurbished and being refurbished.
But wait, what if you go during a specific time of the year?
You know, maybe that being maybe Halloween,
maybe they really do it up for Halloween with the with the outfits.
You know, describe.
So what are we seeing here?
Popeye and Olive Oil.
And is that also blue dough?
I yeah, dress like the strangers.
Basically, they have like olive oil has like bad zombie makeup on her
exact same outfit that she wears all the time.
And she looks drunk.
And Popeye has some sort of massive, you know,
and she looks drunk and Popeye has some sort of mask on and a cape,
but his normal outfit on.
It's a sailor hat, but a Jason mask and a vampire cape.
Yeah, I'm going to go ahead and call that a Dracula cape.
He have her. I would say that.
Pluto looks like he's wearing a lab coat.
The yeah, like buttoned wrong,
like the third button is attached to the second hole.
Yeah, it's kind of stumbling over and he's just in like cargo.
His bottom half looks like Kevin Smith.
The shorts and shoes, the jorts.
And they have here, as you see on the package for the Halloween,
they have Popeye's special trick or treats, the dark haunted house,
meet the monsters that lie in the dark Halloween dance
and crafts balloon modeling and face painting.
Moon modeling, I don't know.
Like you invent a shape of a balloon.
To have, I guess,
design your own balloon.
What about square? Oh, it popped.
Didn't work out, kid.
I also have a poll because I, by the way, I spent one night
just going backwards through their Facebook photos,
which I encourage the listener to do and find your own treasures,
which there are many of.
I'm about to show you something truly disturbing.
I'll just hear I'll just get your reaction without explaining it.
Here is this.
Yeah.
What this is is for Halloween.
Olive oil is in costume as Bluto.
So olive oil is wearing a plastic Bluto mask.
And that might not sound like the most terrifying thing you've ever seen.
But I assure you, as we stare at it, it is deeply, deeply unsettling.
There's something about just the plastic.
I mean, it's like a weird
cute doll with fake rouge and this like ghostly.
I mean, it's a mask you would wear to rob a bank or to kill somebody.
It's kind of this is sort of deep in the Divo world
as a character, I think, called Bougie Boy is like a like
disgusting, creepy like man baby.
It kind of looks like the scary Divo man baby.
I do not like this.
This is I hesitate to show anything right that I find frightening on the show
because I've learned my lesson from Chucko to try to keep my fears in my pocket
less they less they come back over and over again.
And it's a good point.
I'll have to.
Well, I'm sure this will never come back again.
No, this Freudian nightmare will never come back.
No way this grotesque felt unibrowed
olive oil will.
Yeah. You know, somehow like get involved with Randy Gerber, some crap.
No way. There's no chance.
And like make me dress as pan.
I will reveal here that a friend of mine bought me some taramana tequila.
Rock tequila for helping him find a toy.
Oh, that's cool.
Uh huh.
Uh, I haven't tried it yet.
I haven't tried it yet. I'm a little I don't want to.
I don't want to cheat on Randy and George, but I'm going to have to
because it's sitting in my kitchen.
Do you like Casamigos?
Do you think the tequila is good? Never had it after all.
Fuck this shit.
After all this crap, if Scott fucking crap, well, they bet you should.
So, you know, when in the company of people with a million dollar briefcase,
I should throw any them in their tequila, but I haven't had it.
We're striving.
We're strivers.
You know, every time I think about buying it as a bit, I go fifty five dollars.
We're on the grind.
God knows how much the single serving bottle I saw in the Vegas
like hotel gift shop was. I considered it.
But, oh boy, they'll take you for a ride.
That's got to be a four hundred dollar trip or something.
Oh, my God.
For all this, I never said I tasted it.
I know about that.
It's about the lifestyle.
Two guys hitting the road.
Do they look cool on those motorcycles?
You bet they do.
Their casa is our casa.
Let's sound by that and put it on a soundboard for later.
Yeah, no more soundboards.
I bet you're wondering, are there packages for teens at Popeye Village?
I am. Of course, there are.
Party with a difference.
A thrilling birthday or confirmation party for the young teens.
Exclamation point.
Confirmation?
Like the religious, like the Catholic?
Have it at Popeye Village.
Are you choosing a third name beyond your middle name that's a saint's name?
Do it at Popeye.
Do you want to be named after Saint Popeye?
Saint Popeye.
Jason's confirmation name is.
The Asian name is J.
Wellington Wimpy.
J. Wellington Wimpy.
Jason, can you say a middle name?
I don't know your middle name.
Michael.
Oh, Jason Michael J.
Wellington Wimpy shirt.
Yes, that's right.
Back to this copy.
Have a blast with your family and friends during our team building activities and become
a movie star during our animation show.
Take two filming when you and your guests will star in a movie on actual film set.
That singular film set and see themselves on the big screen.
An actual film set, yes.
So have the birthday party you will never forget.
Only at Popeye Village Malta includes food, boat ride, team building, take two show with
free DVD for the birthday girl boy.
Are there now we I think we looked on YouTube for this place a little bit, but is there any?
I don't think anybody posted their team building.
You know, let me Google.
Movie DVD.
Take two filming.
Well, because this is a thing they offer on the web.
They're like you can shoot like you can.
And they in the montage of the music videos, so the promotional music videos, which they
have a second one on their YouTube page, it's like flying drone footage.
There are shots of like Popeye holding a camera and they're like they shoot stuff
throughout the village.
And I think they cut it together at the end of the day and try to sell it to you.
Like one of those classic.
It's included in the teen package.
Oh, OK.
So yeah, so that's included.
The boat ride is free, though, on the map.
It's like get on the boat ride free at least every 15 minutes.
Oh, I saw a thing on the website that said this place with free glass of wine.
Wow.
Free postcard, free glass of wine.
Yeah.
And and of course, let's not forget.
Let me see if I can do this screen share.
I just set up the screen share on mine.
Can you guys see this?
Of course.
Yes.
Oh, yes.
Weddings.
Weddings at Popeye Village.
And it's a little olive oil of Popeye getting married.
It's great.
It's their silhouettes in gold.
And it looks like olive oil is wearing a veil that's curly queuing out in a splendid fashion.
Wow.
Who wouldn't want to?
Who wouldn't?
Yeah, God, you can get.
I mean, these are cool photos.
A picture of like a bride and a bridesmaids and then like a big illuminated love sign.
Like a very modern looking love sign.
Yeah, they're very cheap hipstery.
And then but then and then that's in front of a framed photo from the film of olive oil and
sweet pea sweet pea looking at it.
No olive oil looking out of a pipe and sweet peas and a little.
Oh, yes.
She's trapped in the pipe for much of the third act.
You go in here.
We don't want to choreograph you.
Man, it's it's wonderful.
I actually I have some wedding photos as well because I was starting to feel like.
I mean, Jason, we know your love of this world.
We know your love, Jay Wellington.
This seems like this place is calling out to be the place where you get married.
I agree.
I mean, I look everyone loves a destination wedding.
It's very convenient and considerate for your friends and loved ones.
And if we and we can all assuming we're invited, I hope so.
But if we, you know, as long as we contact the prime minister early and say that we're
bringing in a letter from Henry Kissinger to him, then we can bring all the cocaine we want.
Yeah, I think we can tell we can talk to whoever that prime minister is and we can
tell them we do a very popular podcast.
And I think this thing is on the house.
Just to get tourism up.
If you go to the Popeye Village website right now, they started taking the OK.
These are labeled as red and blue like vouchers.
And what this is, is the Maltese government has given.
I'm assuming I believe Maltese is the correct term.
The government of Malta has given vouchers to its citizens to use a tourism destinations
to drive up business.
So essentially like Disney dollars to use on food and entertainment.
And they're taken at Popeye Village.
Cool.
Which doesn't seem very expensive to begin with, but I don't know the economic situation
of this tiny little nation.
Declare it now.
As soon as quarantine is over, we're going out there.
Jason's getting married.
OK, well, I can't make that keep that promise.
Live podcast recorded right before the wedding.
Yep.
Some during.
It's a write off.
We'll do all these parks too.
And also.
All right, now record it in the cinema, which is just a 30 inch TV at a dark room showing
like making up behind the scenes footage and clips from the movie.
Do you think we can talk to them and let you get in the wimpy outfit and do some of these dances
with the other other cast?
I think I just go real.
I think I just bring my own wimpy outfit.
It probably looks nicer than theirs.
They might not have one.
I haven't seen a photo of one.
I think he's going to bring his own little bowler hat.
Yeah, I mean, I was also thinking this is the place for your wedding because when I
saw this photo, this is like a this is a rose in a little little mason jar in front of a big
wooden sign that says wimpy and I'd gladly pay you Tuesday for hamburger today and he's in
front of a big stack of burgers.
His eyes are half open.
It's kind of a half asleep wimpy.
Jason, is this the most romantic photo you've ever seen?
Well, since second only to the wimpy's at Islands of Adventure when they started including
like a milkshake with your combo order.
That's the honeymoon.
Yeah.
It's a destination multi-pop eye wedding.
Only to Lagoon though.
This is starting to look like an Indiana Jones movie where the plate like crisscrosses the
arrow on the map.
Yeah.
Anywhere wimpy is featured, we have to go to.
The one remaining wimpy's hamburgers chain restaurant that's still standing.
Oh yeah, where is that?
I don't I'm sure there's still was that big in Britain?
I forget where that was.
Oh, the full wimpy trip.
Just here while I'm still screen sharing yours like.
Right and groom kissing in front of like a recreation of the boxing scene with a guy
in a striped old tiny boxing uniform and olive oil going, oh, and then this is this is what
sealed the deal.
If you get married there, your guests can dine on heart shaped hamburgers.
Wow.
We're looking at a big tray of raw meat shaped into raw patties shaped like hearts.
Possibly a heart shaped steak tartare.
Yeah, that is more popular in Europe.
Oh, maybe.
Yeah, yeah, it looks a little odd.
But then look at this.
You got a bun with the heart burned into it.
One thing I'll say about this place, I think all the food, all the food that I've seen
looks good.
I mean, we just got done with movieland Italy, where it was a bunch of like indiscernible
fried horse shit.
Maybe maybe literally.
And then this is these are some good looking burgers and all that.
I think they serve a lot of like good fresh pasta and nice wine.
And there's somewhere you can go.
There's a oh, yeah, tipsy and son's winery.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
With a chalkboard sign that where somebody's drawn a jaunty Popeye saying I am what I am
and I am drunk.
Jason, I'm gonna have a great time at your wedding.
This is great.
How close to this can you live?
How close is the nearest like house?
You can live on the right.
Right.
But like how is it like 10 feet from Popeye Village?
Do we know?
That's what they might be.
They might be leasing.
I don't know.
They might want to fill some of those refurbished spaces.
If you do the refurbished, if you're willing to flip the house while you're there, if
you'll if you'll restore this, the room that you live in to be a fully 1980 quality sweet
peas nursery, then you can live there for just like 100 euro a month.
That's a good deal.
I mean, I, you know, look, I'm not looking to get out of America necessarily, but you
know, it's always something to have in the back of your mind, maybe.
I think about, you know, maybe around November, I might be thinking about moving.
Sure, possible.
It's possible.
No particular reason.
It's the chill.
It's just chilly, you know.
Then seasonably.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It sounds like it's going to be better in Malta.
It'll be better in Malta.
Yeah.
OK, there's still three Wimpy's burgers.
I don't maybe this is a smaller chain.
There's one, two in Tennessee, one in Missouri.
I don't know if this is the original Wimpy's.
It says original Wimpy's, but you know, anyone can just slap that.
Does it have him on it as a logo?
Not not on the home page.
Hmm.
Now they're trying to like, you know, hipify it.
So it's like it's called like WB now.
Like they just do the initial of Wimpy's burgers or like the W.
And Wimpy is hot now.
It's like a hot guy.
Keto Wimpy.
What have we not discussed that you can do here?
I saw some article that said there's like a restaurant where you can play cornhole in the
middle. You throw toilet paper rolls into fake toilets.
There's wooden boxes that say game toilet roll toss, and that's just in the middle of a restaurant.
Man, this is a dream.
Yeah, I'm dying to toilet toss.
I'm loving the vacation, guys.
We're sort of finding all these wonderful places to live.
Potentially, we'll move to Malta.
Jason, can I was wedding there?
But then maybe you end up moving to Missouri to be near the one of the last operating W's.
Yeah, there's a well and then Wimpy is a different.
I knew that Wimpy is a British fast food franchise.
I there's there's all sorts of Wimpy food out there.
There was one in the in the Woodfield Mall, right?
That came up, I think, in our Woodfield Mall.
Wandering.
Yeah.
Walking Wimpy's footsteps.
That's the trip.
All Dooley's home, the Paul, the room that was Paul Dooley was born in.
There was a newer Popeye movie, right?
It didn't happen.
It was the it's a revered design.
Was it Jenny Tartakovsky?
They released like a trailer and it didn't.
Right. They never made that?
Yeah, I don't know what happened.
Some studio hijinks, but whichever.
Like everyone was really excited about and I do.
I liked the look of it.
Yeah, I'm seeing it now.
Yeah, it does look cool.
He's the guy.
He's the creator of Dexter's Laboratory and Zanray Jack and Primal.
It's on now.
Yeah, I don't know.
I don't know what happened.
Yeah, look cool.
Disappointing.
It didn't happen.
Well, as we learn from a movie world or whatever the hell it's called,
maybe we just go into production now on Popeye.
We just say we're doing it.
Oh, well, wait.
Now I'm seeing maybe look at this headline.
This is after up our alley.
Popeye movie gets new life as Jenny Tartakovsky teams up with King Features.
Our favorite thing we say all the time for some reason.
King Features Syndicate comes up a lot.
I think it's coming up on Friday this week.
Can someone break down why I like saying King Features Syndicate so much?
I don't really.
I love saying it.
It's just so functional and like the idea that it's the whole gang.
It's the you know, because you could say the Disney gang, like the big five.
And here's the you know, the are all the Marvel heroes.
And here's the King Features Syndicate.
Pals like crown like the Disney.
The Disney Pals were like the Crown Alliance Group, like something very dry.
That's I guess what that's the fun of it.
King Features Syndicate, the Crown Alliance Group, United Entertainment Holdings National,
Mickey Minnie Goofy Crown Alliance Group, Crown Alliance Group land.
Yeah, I guess that's what's fun.
I think we got it.
I think that yeah, but we're still the Mealy Mouthed.
Yeah, we're still going into production on Popeye.
Jason's writing it right now.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, producing.
Yeah, I mean, I'll switch over.
I'm going to get I'm going to knock a draft out of Young Eyes and Chronicles.
I'm still I'm pretty deep into I'm scripting season two of Late Shift,
the full series, and then I'll like let me know.
I'll pop into the room on the on Popeye or made or Sweet Haven as we were calling it.
Yeah.
When do we yeah, when do we parlay the podcast into a production house that takes way too much,
too many projects?
And then you get like annoyed every time you see that like podcast the right is producing this
and you're like they don't have time for that.
Give it to somebody that you know doesn't have a show.
That's where we're headed maybe with this podcast.
You mean like a certain voice of a snowman who's attached to approximately 45 projects
in any given day?
He has the perfect amount of projects.
He's the perfect amount of time to do them.
And I thank him for reuniting these casts.
See, for being a soldier in the reunion battle.
Everyone's going crazy to see the phantom meet Mandrake the Magician yet again.
All your favorites.
What are the wait are those who are they?
Those are more that are those King feet.
The Phantom is the purple in the purple.
Oh, Billy.
Oh, I see that.
Phantom.
I see Mandrake Mandrake was another like comic strip or pulp character.
They're like Prince Valiant.
These are all like the adventure serial.
Mark trail, you know, Mary Worth.
We are also got a production on all of you got to have a.
Oh, you know, you got to have a it's just called worth.
You know, that's the title.
Yeah, it's called a word trail.
Trail worth.
Yeah, and they're both 21.
Yeah, and they're hot as shit.
They're hot as shit.
Mark trail is hot.
Is it weird that I'm kind of in the Mary Worth?
I'm in the Mary Worth.
Florence Pugh, Timothy Chalamet.
Oh, God.
Boom, boom.
Done.
Hit.
Let's print it.
Done.
Let's get a Broadway World.
So yeah, Broadway Broadway World will be announcing it.
These projects will all be coming to view boo.
They'll all be streaming soon.
So be on the lookout from podcast, the ride features syndicate.
Yes, that's the name.
I'm gasoline.
Alley is back.
Walt and skeezics played by real life couple Affleck day.
Armus, you got it's a hit, you know.
And if anyone harasses us and says you don't have the rights to these properties,
we'll say, can I interest you in a personal letter from Henry Kissinger?
That's a threat.
Yeah, that's a scary thing to get.
My notes are running low.
What have we missed?
Does anyone have any parting words for Puppet Village?
Malta for Malta?
I hope I'll see you soon.
Yes, mainly that I'm dying to go.
I can't wait to go.
Yeah, this is I mean, so we've only done two though, looking ahead at the other place.
Is this the one to be thrown right now is like the place we'd most want to
visit from the European vacation?
I think so.
I think this one is so unusual.
I really think I love how much the Popeye characters are here.
You can get your picture with them.
You can dance with them.
And if the trend continues where they dance to modern music, like in the marketing material,
eventually they will be dancing to the new hit song from Cardi B and Meg the Stallion.
So that's getting very exciting.
The one that Congress guy is mad about?
Yes, and it'll be very interesting to see if they do the unedited version
or the more upsetting clean version.
I will say I am so comfortable with the name of the song now.
I wouldn't have been before this Europe thing started, but now
I'm still not going to say the full name of it, but I'm so comfortable with it.
Wait, I don't know it.
You got to say it.
Say the name.
Is it true that you don't know it, Scott?
I don't know this.
I've seen the thumbnail, but I haven't.
I don't know the name of the song.
Jason, you know the name of the song?
Oh, yeah.
I know both versions.
Jason's mic is cutting out.
I think Mike's got to say it.
If I say the name of this, it will be the dirtiest thing anyone ever said on podcast arrived.
Whoa.
I truly have not seen the name.
I'm not even pretending.
I don't know.
You're going to have to say it.
I feel like you're behind the paywall.
Mike, call your shot.
Do you want to say the official name of the song or you don't want to say the clean edit?
The clean edit version is WAP.
And?
Oh, come on.
No.
Well, Mike, say the name of the song and I'll tell you the radio edit name.
Oh, it's different.
Maybe I don't know the radio edit name.
Oh, okay.
And maybe the song is called Wet Ass Pussy.
That was that harsh to say.
Well, I'm just saying it's the dirtiest thing I've ever said on the show.
But you're right.
I'm in Europe, baby.
You're tossing out.
You're saying Wet Ass Pussy all day and night.
It's going to be your new when I say Mike Carlson is here.
You'll say, yes, Wet Ass Pussy, everyone.
Scott loves saying it.
I'm really reveling in it now.
Yes.
It's a fun song title.
But Jason, the radio.
What is the radio edit?
So you can't say Wet Ass Pussy on the radio.
What you can say is wet and gushy.
Oh, really?
Yeah, that is a lot more.
That's worth.
Yeah.
Huh.
Well, you'll soon see all your favorite Popeye friends dancing to both versions.
All right, guys.
Now the other one.
Let's run.
The show is just them going through all three versions.
I'm hesitant to do an impression of any of the characters.
Is blue.
No, he's just like, yeah, all right.
Now we did when as pussy.
Let's do wet and gushy guys.
Does anyone want to take a stab at a Popeye impression and embarrassed themselves?
Because I don't have one, but I haven't.
I don't think I've tried.
You don't want to try Jason.
I mean, how do you start it?
What's the key?
That's exactly like Donald.
We're back at it again.
Yeah, it's Donald.
I think we got to try it, though.
It's like Dave Coolie.
Right.
That's it.
Me ship.
You've never been so welcome at a party before.
All right, let's go back to Robert Evans.
We should.
Well, olive oil.
Well, wait, in fact, before we get out of here, we got to we got to stamp the passport.
Look, clunk and and wouldn't you know, it's in the shape of it.
I think that the passport stamp is Robert Evans rendered in Popeye style.
And there's a quote bubble and he's saying, am I what I am?
You bet I am.
Great.
Wow.
I'm spelled with a Y, of course, spelled like.
Yeah.
Gonna be tough to beat that, honestly, as far as stamps are concerned.
It's a beauty.
It looks great.
Certainly, I don't have to go make this.
It exists already.
Yeah, it's there in front of you showing it to us.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
There it is.
Wow, it's and thank you, invisible hand that is stamping our passports.
I don't know what entity this is that has given us these stamps, but
thanks for taking us around on this fake trip.
Yeah, thank you.
Making sure it's all on the up and up because we don't want trouble like
Evans and his trunks full of Coke.
Right.
His body's full of Coke.
It occurs to me looking at again at your zoom background, Jason, that
blue does big fake belly might be the perfect thing to smuggle cocaine in.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, no one will open that up.
It's just a blue belly.
Don't worry about it.
Yeah, it looks so realistic.
No one would even know.
I've never seen such a well crafted gut.
Airlines would the airport, they would just wave you right through that normal belly.
Got it.
And Pluto belly coming through nothing inside.
Another one.
All right.
Again.
This is going to be a good movie.
Well, folks, you survived podcast, the ride European vacation, second gate day trip site
excursion.
This is a blast.
We got one more of these coming up later in the month between two of the main feed episodes.
We'll be doing something fun in here.
But as for now, the journey continues this Friday on the main show, the free show.
And we'll be do we do we give any good hints we can say about that place?
Question.
If you like brightening robot smiles, you want a smile that's maybe more terrifying than the
the Pluto olive oil xenomorph we're looking at.
If people know, they'll know.
Like there are some real Europe parkheads, I think somebody's going to know.
Somebody's going to know about.
Yeah.
You know what?
Please guess on Twitter.
If you think you know where we're going based on what I said, I said a scary robot smile.
Yeah.
If that's enough, there's another might be a lot in there because that
that I don't know.
There's probably a lot of scary looking robots spread out through Europe.
I think that yeah, I think that narrows it down to all theme parks in Europe.
This has kind of been the uniting thread between all of these.
Well, but anyway, yes, thanks for joining us.
If you didn't see it on Twitter, we've got a podcast to ride European vacation
shirt available.
A new logo from my wife, Mary Gardner.
That thing's fun.
And otherwise, yeah, keep following the journey.
Fun stuff in just a couple of days.
Are you going to have fun?
You bet you are.
All right.
Bye folks.
Goodbye.