Welcome to Podcast The believe it or not podcast.
I'm Mike Carlson joining me as always Scott Gardner.
But in which order though? I guess we'll find out.
That's the big thing. You gotta wait till the end to find out which one I'm talking about.
I mean, it's yeah, you feel like there should be a twist. There's not a twist. It's the obvious one.
Jason Sheridan. The scary ones. Yes, sure. Yeah, the scary ones.
I mean, I think it's a good thing that we're talking about.
Jason Sheridan also here. Yeah, I had the same question because I think I had stuffed animals of both of the protagonists, I guess, of this attraction.
Well, the protagonists are different than the gremlins.
Like, we'll talk about that, obviously. We'll talk about that.
Well, and there's some in a way there's a there's live action protagonists too,
because there's a the rides introduced by someone who then doesn't factor in in any other way.
But she is your way in. There's a lot going on. There's so much going on in this ride.
I'm so excited for talking about it. There's a lot going on.
And this is a little bit of a side trip because we've been doing, you know, European parks.
But we're going to focus hyper focus on this one ride today, which I'm very excited about.
And we've been we've been hopping around current 2020 Europe.
But this is a trip into the past because this ride disappeared in 2004, I believe, if my stats are correct.
So this is both a travel to Europe and a travel back in time.
Yes. So let's get right to it. Let's bring our guest in here.
She's a writer whose credits include DC Superhero Girls and Thundercats Roar.
But more importantly, she's a Gremlins expert scholar. What would you say? It's Joan Ford.
I'd say, yeah, I don't know if I can qualify myself as a scholar.
I don't know. There's like a like you can get a Ph.D. in like Gremlinomics or whatever.
But I do. Yeah, as close as I am, I am an expert.
And right off the bat, I have to ask, are we do we are you saving?
Are you saving like talk about the Australian version of this ride and the end?
Are we going to talk about the Australian version?
Are we hyper focusing on the German version?
I think we need to mention it at least. OK, yes.
We're primarily interested in the German one, which for my money is the weirder of the two.
Agreed. Agreed. They're both weird combos.
They both make both make no sense.
And listeners might be so confused at this point of what is going on and what is it and what it's called.
Which I feel is probably the mindset you were like people were in when they were entering this ride in from 1990 till 2004.
Right. I'd have to think so.
And I but you know, isn't isn't it a little cool that you like,
especially if you didn't like look up at the marquee of the ride that you were going on and then it just started,
you might genuinely be faked out by it in a very Gremlin spirit.
This film, at least at least part two that has these these meta moments and fourth wall breaks.
It is in a way a ride that has that maybe in bigger ways than other rides have.
Yeah, I agree. I mean, I think both Gremlins movies to some degree,
are kind of like bait and switches where like the first one is like the first half is like a kind of like Norman Rockwell
ask like Christmas movie with some weird elements turned in before it goes into full like like horror cartoon.
And then like the second one is just like kind of like picking up that spirit and like going insane with that.
But yeah, it is like if you write as a couple.
This right as a couple. And I think Jason, you kind of mentioned this right now has like a couple bait and switches like up top,
like from where you like like the first thing you see to what it like turns into.
I don't know. We'll get into it. But yeah, it's a it's it throws you.
This is the I agree. This is a good ride to go in with no information.
And that's probably pretty enjoyable. Well, let's first confirm the name because this is one of the most poorly documented.
Like there's stuff out here about this ride, but like every post contradicts every other post like
there's a lot of weird fan sites.
I'm voting for just calling the episode The Gremlins and Alf Ride or The Alf and Gremlins Ride.
So you're listener, you're looking at the title already because we got to let people know, you know, one of the big stars of the show.
But technically what we are talking about is called it has a title that has no indication of the Alf presence,
which is Gremlins invasion. Yes. Yes. OK.
Meanwhile, the other one and just basic facts.
This ride was at Warner Brothers Movie World Germany, which is now called Movie Park Germany,
which is not movie land Italy, which we kicked off the series with and as many alternate names as well.
We are dense in the weeds of name confusion. Yeah.
And I might be I mean, like you said, the like facts about this ride are very obscure, like obscured by time.
Am I right? That it's the original ride. The original version of this ride was in Australia.
And then it and then it moved to the Gold Coast movie land.
And then it moved to like a year or two later. It was it opened in Austria in Germany with a same ride, but with a different with a very different protagonist.
Correct. And if someone else wants to do the honors of the bizarre other name, because that's true, that's like one of the worst titles of a ride.
I mean, you can go ahead. Yeah, it's very confusing. Very. Yeah.
I mean, we complain about our Disney's our mission breakouts and our like apostrophes and our colons and our dot dot dots.
But this is right, like that the Australian one is called Warner Brothers Classics and Great Gremlins Adventure.
And and although you're really burying the lead there, Warner Brothers Classic sounds like nothing.
That just sounds like a brand of a videotape. And like you're going to shove into the second half of the title that the exciting chaos get gremlins are part of it.
And then and and the and the costar, the protagonist or whatever you are, I guess you're the protagonist of the ride, but you're like you're like your host, you know, co-writer.
Yeah, your host is is none other than the ghost with the most Beetlejuice.
Beetlejuice, it's very weird.
And I will say this is exciting in the in the sense that like we like mashups of characters.
But yes, Beetlejuice is in the movies.
There was no like I think it's great, but also weird.
Well, also, I mean, I just take issue with the idea of like Beetlejuice like teaming up with you instead of the gremlins,
because it really seems like Beetlejuice would be like much more like into the gremlins into their maybe be like, you know, like I want to party with these guys, not like, oh, like I, I will help you escape the gremlins.
He'd be buzzed with them. They'd like, you know, they're they're all very creative, like he'd, you know, like throw on crazy costumes with them and stuff.
I don't know. They're all agents of chaos.
Yeah, yeah, I can't like, you know, maybe that's what like breaks them up at the end.
You know, they like I feel like agents of chaos usually will end up bouncing off of each other at some point.
But like you feel like it's, you know, at least at first they would be collaborating, you know, coming up with like they're like fun movie riffs they could work on together.
Yeah, I wonder what I guess I wonder what the thought process is.
And I wonder if by the time they got to Germany, they were like, Beetlejuice doesn't work.
We need like a more of an uptight character, like a real straight laced character to really be like your way in to be your conduit.
Conduit is humans.
But we need a star.
And in Germany, this guy is.
Yeah, I'm assuming you have an hour on that part of the Alps international popularity.
Not an hour, but some.
I there's certainly some stuff I'm delighted to talk about here.
You know, let me let me save it, though, because I want to I want to be able to hear him first.
I think when we get into the meat of the ride, we'll talk about it.
The strange thing is that, OK, I mean, we can sort of talk about both rides because they're essentially the same in both settings.
You are taking some tour ostensibly of a behind the scenes facility at a Warner Brothers studio, because these are both Warner Brothers, like, you know, universal theme parks devoted to Warner Brothers properties.
So both involve that you've been invited on this little tour and then the Gremlins interrupt a video.
And now you're sent on this madcap adventure with them.
If I'm correct, neither the Beetlejuice or the Al version.
Oh, wait, while is in the video, the Beatles, the Beatles version, isn't he just suddenly in the ride?
Like, he's. Yeah, I don't I don't believe there is a pre show that indicates Beetlejuice's presence anywhere in this universe.
We're in Beetlejuice is just he's uninvoluntarily heard that you've you're under attack by the Gremlins and he like, like, I guess Beetlejuice does.
He shows up to save the day.
Yeah, it's it's a I would be jarring, I guess.
But maybe that's really what they were going for.
Alpha's you know, you slowly introduce yourself in the pre show on the other part of the ride.
So, yeah, he's weaved in there.
I guess I do like the idea.
Wouldn't we love if in, you know, we tried to do Rise of the Resistance without knowing a lot.
And there were genuine surprises.
You don't know how you're going to get out of this room.
You don't know what's the escape here.
And if part of that was a Beetlejuice showing up like Beetlejuice, you know, shows up instead of Kylo Ren at the ends.
I would have gone nuts. I would have loved it.
It's genuinely thrilling.
Drop Dead Fred is somehow piloting your exit vehicle.
A character who's not from space, who doesn't exist in the same century.
Yeah, I mean, that would be incredible.
So I do I can appreciate both approaches because, you know, sometimes some viewers of things and some people go on rides, they probably need their handheld a little more than some like a big, bold surprise.
Yeah.
So, you know, if if you were a parkour in the mid 90s, good try, you try both.
See which one is your flavor.
Try to bring in friends to like and surprise that even if you know the spoilers, try to just have them on and see if it takes them by surprise.
Australia and Germany.
Really? Yeah.
I wish it like comes down to like, who's your guys at Alpha Beetlejuice?
You know, who are you?
I would say me personally, I'm much more of an elf.
I guess we should pull everybody.
Yeah.
Well, I'm going to say I mean, generally, like I'm more of a Beetlejuice, but for this specific ride, like I'm definitely an elf, like elf, I think was is the better conduit for this ride.
Jason, what are you thinking?
I think, yes.
Yeah, for sure.
You know, I think I have a lot of very vague memories of Alf and a lot more specific ones of Beetlejuice, vague memories of Alf, much in the same way I had vague memories of the two Gremlins movies, which I've watched over the last couple of days and I forgot they're awesome.
Like they're great.
Well, I'm asking though, you personally, are you more of a Beetlejuice or an Alf type, you think?
I think I would need to watch some Alf to get a better bearing.
Wow, you don't even want to commit.
You don't want to commit.
What do you think?
Who someone clearly has a better grasp?
I think you're Alf all the way.
Okay.
Yeah.
How are we classified?
Like, what is it to be?
Like, I have a very firm understanding of what it is to be like a Beetlejuice.
Also, I didn't realize that's how we were defined.
I don't know if I'm a Beetlejuice.
I'm just in terms of preference.
I think I go Beetlejuice.
I don't know if I consider myself a Beetlejuice.
But how do we define an Alf?
Who is your quintessential Alf?
I think Alf is very dry.
He's very low key.
He's sardonic.
He's got sort of a cynical take about the world, but he's also optimistic.
And that's sort of hidden a little bit more.
That is actually pretty good.
That's a pretty fair description of me.
So maybe I am an Alf.
And he likes big sandwiches.
I mean, you don't like cats as the ingredient, but he'll eat a big, long set.
You'd put like a more traditional meat in there.
But besides that, similar food taste.
That's true.
Yeah. The eating cat stuff.
The eating cat adds a layer of complication to Alf.
Much in the way that Gizmo is very cute, but is de facto responsible for the chaos of these movies.
Yeah.
Yes. Also, I mean, yeah, I mean, Beetlejuice is all problem.
I mean, yes, they're all problematic figures.
Beetlejuice is problematic.
We all have to like, yeah.
So Scott, are you an Alf or a Beetlejuice?
Do you feel like?
Hmm. Maybe.
Maybe more of an Alf.
Again, I've been eating a lot of sandwiches during quarantine.
I'm judging that is the primary criteria.
A lot of Hawaiian shirts, too.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Just chilling in the house.
Just chilling in the house with a Hawaiian shirt and no pants.
Just like, just Alf in it.
So maybe we change the change in the tagline of the podcast to a podcast about theme parks hosted by three Alfs.
Because now we can't say Childish Men anymore, of course.
Well, we could just open the next episode with that.
And then it's a test of how many listeners have followed us to the second gate and know what we're talking about.
Or, yeah, or how many more?
Well, many more, I think, if we start saying that, too, on the main feed.
I guess let's take this real quick.
Let's take this opportunity.
I just watched Gremlins 1 and 2 for the first time in my life in the last 48 hours.
Really?
Wow.
I am not joking when I say the fear of it as a kid had kept me away from Gremlins my whole life.
And last night I watched 1 and I watched 2 this morning.
And I like 1, but 2 was obviously I love 2.
2 is like, yeah, 2 is like kind of a masterpiece.
I love 1, but 2 is just like, you know, the only movie like it.
Once you start getting other types of Gremlin, once you start getting Bat Gremlin and Spider Gremlin and Brain Gremlin, Sexy Lady Gremlin, the limiter is off, man.
You're just going like 60 miles an hour then.
Robert Picardo steps out of the limo at the start of 2 and I was like, oh, good.
Yes.
You're just like, yeah.
And then the slam dunk was when Gizmo starts dancing out of the cage in front of Christopher Lee and the two twin scientists.
And I'm like, oh, yeah, this is, oh, I get it.
That is so delightful and like comped in there in a way that's clearly a little dated, but not in a distractingly fuzzy green screen.
It's an unwatchable effect.
Like I like that it goes to suddenly clearly a comped Gizmo.
I don't know. And then such a such a charming dance.
He really shines in it in general.
All his Rambo moments.
Yes.
To a song they had to retrofit his dancing to that song.
I forget what the name of the song is in the movie, but originally he was dance.
I believe originally they shot it to him dancing to a Billy Idol song and then like somewhere along the line down the line, Billy Idol was like, no, I don't I don't want this in there.
So they had to like they had to like re edit his dancing to fit this like fifties song that they picked.
Wow.
Yeah.
Crazy.
It's there because there is some modern music in it, but that choice specifically, I don't know.
That's it feels better that it's like an older rock and roll song.
Yeah, that seems like more like what Gizmo would actually be into.
I also it as a it though most of the movie is in an atrium.
It's in a very oh yeah yeah yeah.
He's early 90s atrium.
It's very mall esque.
So it's my vibe big time.
I would love to if I could if I somehow had some bizarre option to spend the rest of quarantine in that set.
I would so happily do it the rest of my life.
Clamp center.
Yes.
Yet another film with a Trump stand in.
It's weird that we were raised on all of these Trump villain films that would have like planted the seeds for us as five to ten year olds and now like he is the villain of our adulthoods.
It feels very simulation.
It's very simulationy.
Yeah.
I had a very odd experience because I watched this like two nights ago and then yesterday in the day I watched that John Carpenter movie in the mouth of madness where it's like Sam Neill's trying to track down a Stephen King like character whose books are
drive people crazy and the actor who plays clamp it runs an insane asylum in the John Carpenter movie and I like sat up like so quick in my chair was like clamp it's it's him and the guy who creates poison ivy in Batman and Robin.
Yeah.
Isn't he and isn't he in smallville isn't he like Lex Luthor senior.
Yes.
He is Lex Luthor's father.
I can't pull the name.
Yeah.
He's like he is like one of those actors that like I've like saw gremlins to so many times the kid before I ever saw him anything else that I can only like seen him as like anything else is like feels weird and wrong.
It would be like if Jay Leno was playing a character in a movie.
Yes.
There'll be no way like that.
And honestly another Trump analog like see like seeing like Biff like years later in Thomas Wilson years later and like freaks and geeks it was like, but this guy and this guy's Biff what's like this doesn't make sense.
Yeah, they got that sitcom sort of locked into this role forever.
Yeah.
Mike I think I had a sense I did not see either of these films till recently either gremlins the first one I think I thought I had seen it and slowly realized that I had not seen it while I was in a 40x screening which was a blast.
That is probably my best 40x experience.
You get hit by a snowball that was one of the water effects.
Yeah, it's cool that you there's like a benign one it's not action and you getting hit by you know with bullets or something scary.
It's it's kind of nice.
It's a little missed.
I did.
I did that last I did that last last winter that went to the 40x gremlins.
It was like a blast.
It was so nice to see it like I don't know I'll pretty much go see it whenever it's playing anywhere.
But it's like getting to see it new under those circumstances was so much fun.
It's a really good job.
I thought I was really well programmed.
I might be at that point now.
Maybe I just go to gremlins revivals when they happen.
Yeah.
Oh my gosh.
The I mean like the scene where you the gremlins are in the movie theater and you're kind of like rocking along with them is like the best like just like the best most aversive use of 40x like I think I've ever experienced.
Well, that's cool.
Dancing.
The so I guess I'm curious then.
Then, John, if we were all we were all Freddy cats about it.
I was just afraid of like the just the gremlins.
The poster was enough to keep me away for a long time.
That scared that hand with the cigar and gizmo hiding in the drawer.
But this was a staple of your childhood.
You were not scared away by what is your your gremlin story?
Honestly, I was like I remember like when I was really little when it was like for like when I was first aware of it.
I remember being like I was like really like I think I had the same reaction.
I was like very terrified of it.
And then I never really wanted to watch it.
And then I I was kind of like forced to watch it at like a friend's sleepover.
And it was really scary.
But it was also like just a lot of fun.
And I think there was something about it being like the first movie that I was like genuinely like scared of seeing that like I kind of like like always able to like kind of like overcome that and watch it and have a lot of fun and enjoy it.
That kind of like cemented it for me as like kind of like instrumental to my like falling in love with like what I like about horror movies and why I like being scared going to movies.
So I feel like there's a lot of that like as much as I like like like just like the movies themselves.
I think it's still like kind of like a milestone as a like this was kind of like a threshold movie for me when I was very young.
And yeah.
So yeah, I was just like being forced to conquer that was like a like really awesome was like what ingrained it is an important movie for me.
Yeah, that makes sense.
I don't know that I have such a milestone moment, but it is literally in the last decade when I start watching these types of movies that as a kid there was a mental block because I think I thought they were just like snuff films.
I think I assumed that like the gremlins were just murdering humans and it was just like grotesque and it was treated very seriously like some sort of like murder procedural.
I think that's in my head what it was.
And then when you watch it, you're like, oh, this is kitschy and campy and yeah, like, and like, especially because like there's so much like out like about the first one there was so much outcry about like the like kitchen scene was like a big deal that was like it was like scandalous.
People are like kids are going to like kids are going to do that to their cats like there's a for those who know there's a scene where like the mom explodes a gremlin in the microwave.
I mean, there was controversy about people being like someone's going to do that to their kids going to do that to their cat.
And like, I think there was this like, even though, yeah, like you said, it's very like campy and goofy and pretty silly as far as horror movies go.
There was just so I there was so much like controversy around it that it did feel like a very like taboo almost like yeah like snuff movie at the time.
Yeah, I think it was just literally the design of the gremlins and I just going to like movies because we all went we're all old enough to blockbuster as children and you would see as Scott said the poster or the box.
And it's just like your mind would run wild with what you thought because obviously I wasn't young enough to even I don't think be aware of what controversy was happening at the time.
But yeah, it's just murder after murder. No story.
Just the story says gremlins to the no bad.
And then it's just claws who put in putting somebody into a meat grinder.
Just like 400 kills.
Yeah, like Freddy Krueger, all of it.
Jason, Freddy Krueger.
I thought there was like no Freddy Krueger, who's just this insane caricature.
I was like, oh, there must this must be humorless.
There must be nothing silly about this.
Yeah, and it's all that all and I'm slowly making my way watching all this stuff that I just knew was bad for me as a kid.
Did you know then how silly it was?
Like, were you surprised that it involves all the gremlins singing New York, New York and being on talk shows and stuff?
I have a couple years ago, someone finally and I somebody finally explained to me that the second one is like kind of a parody or a satire or whatever the first one.
So I knew that the second one was even though it's got a lower IMDB score that I think and correct me if I'm wrong, Joan, that the hard cores think too is better and it's more insane and silly and weird.
Yes, I think like in general, like, like I really love both of them.
But I think in general, the heart of the like the the main like line of thinking is that like that like gremlins is the first gremlins is like great is like great.
It's like a fun like Little Monster. It's a fun little monster movie and gremlins to is like considered to be like like genius by a big group of like people like there are like reassessments written on it on its 20th and 30th anniversary about how like it's this like like like rare gem of like the Hollywood like blockbuster of Hollywood blockbusters that was actually like really like like smart and like kind of like, you know, I don't know.
I don't know. It just yeah. So I would say yes, the subversive. That's the word I was looking for smart and subversive. And it it you know, it's just like a rare it's like something really rare to see in a like in like what was essentially like a giant summer movie at the time it came out.
Yeah, I feel like too. It's like they took it's as if I watched one and they were like, well, what do you like in one and we're going to multiply it by 50. And I was like, well, I really like when the gremlins are in the bar. That's great. Yeah. Like I want a little more of that. And like, oh, character actor slash country music singer who wrote the no no song Hoyt Axon is in the first movie. All right. More fun like weird actors like that, please. Yeah. All over the place.
Get that towns guy, get him to New York City for some indistinct reason. Yeah, like just like no like let's like characters who died in the first one who gives a shit there like the will explain it away by just like they were mildly hurt. And now they're in their visiting.
They're visiting like it's even just insane that the Futtermans are visiting like like like like what do you're like old like who's ever had their like old neighbors come visit them in the in the city they currently live. But whatever. Mr.
Feeney following you somewhere. Mr. Building. Why is your principal on vacation? I don't know because they need to be there for comedy. Yeah, but I do agree. Like I do agree. Like what totally agree with you saying Mike, I think like it makes the it kind of like does not make the mistake that I think a lot.
Of movie sequels make that are like, OK, like we, you know, it's like we have to restart at like ground at like ground zero, like like the way you like any given like Jurassic Park sequel is like, well, we got to do the same kind of like basic trajectory of like first, the dinosaurs are like like inspiring and then they're scary.
It's like, no, it's just like like we kind of got to like a hunt. We got to like 110 in the first one with the craziness and we're going to start there in the second. This is one of my biggest pet peeves about things.
It's like even like a movie I like, like Ghostbusters 2, they have to restart. We're like the Ghostbusters are not being taken seriously anymore, despite the fact there was a giant ghost outbreak a few years ago and they're still like, no, these lousy Ghostbusters have to get out of here.
They're frauds. And it's like there was a marshmallow man stomping his way down the city.
We have to see B and Malcolm as a like sad, thought to be crazy man on the subway.
We have to deal with shit for 35 minutes before there's a dinosaur as opposed to a dinosaur in.
I mean, there's a little cold open, but like as opposed to just pure dinosaurs for the first 20 minutes.
Yeah, it says like, yeah, and like Gremlins 2 just kicks off with like it's like bugs and Daffy like talking to you in a war in the start of the cart at the like pre cartoon.
It's like it's just like it's like kind of bug nuts from the beginning.
Yeah, and it's also something I've talked about.
So I had nauseam on the show, which is the original George Lucas idea for Indiana Jones.
Every movie is a different genre because why not like why not plug in the characters and see them in a variety of tones and plenty scenarios like it's just much more fun.
Like if there was a third Gremlins movie, which I know Gremlins I've heard is grown only grown in popularity and multiplied much like the Gremlins themselves.
If you want a third one, I feel like it's got to be something even more insane that we don't even know.
I'm not thinking of right now.
Yeah. And I mean, they are.
You know, they're doing the HBO Max.
Yeah, right.
Right.
Yes, the cartoon.
It's like a prequel.
And it'll be really interesting.
I'm really interested to see, like, how do you translate that like tone to a series?
And like, what's it like?
Like, are they resetting?
I wonder if it's going to be more in the tone of like the first movie, the second movie.
But it is really hard to imagine, like it working, like going back, like, you know, trying to reset that tone of the first movie.
Yeah. I mean, I hope I would.
I would if it's off the top of my head, I'm like, well, let's see the Gremlins like partying through the different era, like different eras, different centuries.
The Dark Ages.
And like, let's see that.
That sounds great.
Unfortunately, the direction they're going in is BoJack Horseman.
So Gizmo is depressed.
He's drunk and he's horny, but his dick don't work.
So, you know.
Oh, no.
Showrunner Jason Sheridan.
Give them the kids what they want.
Sorry.
The kids, you know, it's got to look like one of two possible cartoons and some characters got to do depression.
That's true.
That is two types of cartoon eyeballs.
And if a new cartoon comes out that isn't one of the two types of eyeballs, audiences eyeballs themselves will explode.
That's right.
What are the Rick and Morty eyeballs and what's the second?
I would say like kind of sort of like pseudo family guy.
Well, do you know our family guy eyeballs and Bob's Burgers eyeballs, different eyeballs?
I think those are different eyeballs, but I think it is somewhere between like Rick and Morty and Bob's Burgers might be it.
Yeah, I think those merged.
I think Bob's and Rick and Morty became one set of eyeballs and rip off family guys is set number two.
Yeah.
Well, let's know your lazily designed cartoon eyeballs.
Let's let's put a guide up on the Twitter so everyone knows what kind of eyeballs.
Is this people size?
How perfectly round they are.
I think we could talk about the movies forever.
And boy, I mean, yeah, I'm with you on Masterpiece.
And I just also have like just the craftsmanship.
I mean, it's the movie itself, I think, is so wonderful.
If you take a step back and go like, is this the peak of puppeteering and physical effects in a movie?
Yeah.
Many there are and that you aren't aware of the size issues.
Our friend Andrew Grissom made me aware that for a lot of that movie, the gizmo is a is giant.
You're looking at like they built the head really big so that they could do the subtlety of that, which is extreme.
I think that's my Joan.
I have this ongoing fear of things that should be small, but that are giant in a in a small room.
Does that explain the fear correctly, guys?
Yeah, it sounds like it's like you're afraid of like a giant bullet in Mario.
Yes, because we know it is small.
And then when you see it extremely big, it just freaks me out.
So I get a little of that weirdness seeing the gizmo.
However, I like gizmo so much that I can get over some of the.
Yeah.
But the first time I saw that, I actually I have like the 1984 Cinefax from that,
like the original and seeing like that, seeing that image of like, oh,
because like in these shots, because his head was actually like person sized is like very, very disjarring.
And when the first one too.
OK, I didn't know if that was a.
Yeah, I know they made like I don't have it.
But yeah, on the first one, they made like all the close ups, a lot of the close ups of gizmos are just like a big like
animatronic head that like they just did close ups on.
Oh, wow. So so strange.
Yeah, so just so technologically advanced.
Amazing to look at. But I guess I guess what I'm curious is, you know, we've we're all clearly so excited about the spirit of these movies.
And the only theme park attractions that came out of this franchise are these.
And we can talk about what they what the ride is.
And that can help us determine. But do we think that they got the spirit correct?
Yeah, yeah, yes, I think.
I mean, it's it's mayhem. It's unpredictable.
There's weird movie turns and fourth wall breaking.
Yeah. It's the way they got the spirit was just repeating, repeating some set pieces.
Yeah. Or in some cases, like literally just like using footage from the gremlins to.
Oh, yes, you do just get a big stint of that, of the projection stuff.
Yes. Joan, did we make you aware of this ride or were you aware in a in a in a
perversely fascinated way as a gremlins fan?
I was I was definitely I was aware of this.
I remember hearing about this, like, I don't know, remember how long, but I've been aware of this for a while.
But definitely like not until after it had gone, it had all shut down.
So I think the first like time I read about it, I was like, oh, he is like probably some like slash
film article that was like the extent gremlins ride you never knew existed.
But I've known about I've definitely known about it.
Yeah, I'm trying to remember when I think it was a couple of years ago.
And maybe it was even because we were doing the podcast that I was like, oh, OK, this
there's a lot of weird stuff I am not aware of even.
Could we just quickly talk about Elf?
Certainly. OK, I love.
Yeah. Oh, well, for the show, he's in the show.
The show is like fine, but I love Elf.
Yeah, I'll have to show it's not a masterpiece by any means, but I love Elf.
I like those like those Oscar movies where it's like, oh, this movie sucks.
This one performance is incredible.
I think that's right. I think I think you go, you know, this elf is going to work again
in a better project.
So you like him like cameoing on something or appearing in, say,
cartoon all stars to the rescue.
We still haven't done it yet.
We got to get there. Yeah.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
I love Elf in the promo from was it on NBC, I think, right?
Or was it ABC? I forget.
I think NBC, NBC.
There's an NBC promo with like all the stars of the network and Elf and Bob Hope
are sitting at a piano and Elf like puts his head on Bob Hope's show.
Like that's probably much better than the whole series of Elf.
It's just that moment.
But his recent cameo on the Amy
Polar Animates that come Duncanville.
Great. Fantastic.
That was Elf. Was it was it voice of Elf?
Paul Fusco.
So here's what I guess. Here's what I know about Alf.
He Paul Fusco like retains the rights to to Alf.
So he can he can do whatever he wants.
So I know the creators of Duncanville approached him for a cameo and he said yes.
Wow. OK.
So we could we could ask and see if Alf would do the show.
Yes, yes. Wow.
Just as Elf.
Yeah, yeah. Just Elf on to discuss whatever he wants.
I mean, if you could get out, if you needed to, I would totally understand
if you got out and needed to record this episode without me.
I would totally understand.
I would say, go to this point on.
All right. So it worked. We got it.
And now, yeah, we're talking about my right.
Don't even acknowledge that I laugh.
Just like Alf pops it.
It's now a surprise.
Alf appearance like the right itself.
Yes. Yeah.
But I don't want the elf doesn't want to talk about this ride.
He wants to talk about like, I love the living seas.
What have they done to Epcot?
Yeah. Well, yeah, I wonder if Paul Fusco like is this
I wonder how much because obviously it's not the ride.
It's not Paul Fusco doing the voice of German Alf.
I wonder how much it's like, I wonder like what
how much say Paul Fusco had in the ride knowing that he kind of like had control.
I don't know how to like control over.
That's interesting because if you say he retains some ownership over it,
it does feel like this is just like from the archives we own, Alf put Alf in.
Like, why would we want to make a separate deal for Alf?
Like they would have found a different character if it was like a big headache.
That's yeah, maybe it's like maybe he like got the right.
Maybe it was like NBC Universe or whatever, whoever had like
like momentary rights to him, but he got he got them back like mid 90s,
which would explain why Alf was able to do the ABC movie in 1996.
Right, which is the finale of the finale,
because the actual ending of the actual official series,
which honestly is kind of recent that I think that I've even been aware of this
is just Alf getting abducted by the feds,
getting hunted like an X-Files episode, I believe.
Yeah, I that's the end.
The last shot of like the official series, I think, is like like FBI agents
like storming the Tanner's house.
Yeah. And they're like all like freaks.
Scott, have you seen this?
No, I haven't seen the very end.
Oh, my God. This is I'm surprised.
This is this is right up your alley.
It is like Project Alf either.
Maybe I'm not an elf guy.
I like the idea of all this, but I've never I've never put in the time.
They intended to come back, I think, for another season.
So they left the season off on a cliffhanger where Alf literally
in a very scary thing, especially, I assume, for kids,
Alf gets taken into custody by the government.
And the family's just like sitting there freaked out.
And that's the end of the whole show forever.
You know, I was more of what was the other puppet sitcom with the dinosaurs?
No, no. Well, I love dinosaurs.
That's no there was a filthy one on Bob with Bob.
Bob Bobcat's voice.
Are you talking about as like a like dirty bunny rabbit?
Am I Matt? Oh, that's are you talking about?
Was that happily Greg the bunny?
Not Greg the bunny.
No, that happily ever.
It was a happily ever after happily ever after with Nicky Cox.
Yeah. And Kevin Conway, which was like, yes, it was.
That was like just married with children.
But Al Bundy also had like a like a like a bunny rabbit friend
that he would visit that he would visit in a basement.
Yeah. And I was too young for married with children.
But when I was like 10 or 11 and unhappily ever after was on, I was like,
oh, yeah, this is this is good.
This is this is like bad kid stuff.
You got a fine ass Nicky Cox says eye candy.
And then you got your fun puppet Sunday nights were a little
before the Simpsons were on Sunday.
Sunday nights was a little more the Wild Wild West for television.
I feel like Jason.
Congratulations on that on your Barstool Sports podcast,
where you watch every episode of Unhappily Ever After.
I think it's going to be big.
It is very Barstool Sports.
Yeah. I just thinking it's perfect.
Jason and Dave Portnoy host
Unhappily Ever Podcast.
I only know Barstool Sports through like comedy references.
I don't I've never actually looked into what it is.
I know what you mean. I've never.
Yeah, like I've never organically just been part
doing Barstool Sports.
Yeah, if Barstool Sports is just something Brad
and Brad Evans and Nick Sorelli made up, I would be I would be like, yeah,
that's I know I feel like they invented it.
What an empire.
What a man they created.
It's a sign up on their part.
Yeah, they like created it and then made like a career out of like blam
proving it. What a great comment.
I mean, money from the people who like it and then you get the cred
to make fun of it. Yeah.
OK, congratulations to Nick and Brad on the Stephen Stills, Billy Porter sketch.
That was incredible.
That I don't know.
We all still haven't seen that from now on.
You haven't seen it.
What's going on? Oh, you got to see it.
It's a it's a it's a what's I can never think of the song
Oh, children. What's that sound?
What's that song? The Crosby, Sills and Nash song.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, this is something happening here.
There's a very Tim and Eric music video made by Billy Porter
and Stephen Stills for the Democratic National Convention.
Oh, no, they really got the very.
You have to. Oh, my God.
We have to see it right after very happily not watching any of the DNC.
So why there there has not been a potent combination like that
since Alf met the gremlins.
Yeah. Well, you want to you want to go on the ride here?
Yes, please.
This one is so might just require the step through what the hell's going on.
And by the way, you know, you brought up a report.
So Project Alf 1996, oddly, the same year that this ride was put in in Germany.
Alf, the series ended in 1990.
Gremlins to the new batch 1990 as well.
So we're we're deep into this is a ride six years after
we've last seen the properties, except for Project Alf,
which is obviously made Alf, you know, more relevant than ever.
But so you go into just kind of a very,
you know, studio lot facility and you're walking through an office building.
It's just like very it's it's, you know, the kind of place where you go
see the screening on a lot or like the scoring stage for a film score.
And you're ushered into a little private screening room.
And the lights go down and the film starts and the film, of course,
stars Sandra Bullock.
Of course. OK.
Yes. If you weren't aware, it of course would follow that Sandra Bullock shows up.
Sandra Bullock films just for this, I believe.
And in German, dubbed in German,
like one of my favorite fascinations, the Armageddon attraction in France
that exists only in a version where Michael Clarke Duncan is dubbed over.
Similar to the Hasselhoff thing that we saw at the start of all this, too.
I don't have a good like catch all for what it is when you film a cameo
for something and then the language your your voice is never heard.
There's no chance of it because where it's going to be playing.
Yeah. Yeah. So why are you even talking?
Maybe they didn't. Maybe he just mouthed words.
Let's fill in something later. It's cheaper. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You don't have to pay them for the voiceover fee.
So Sandra Bullock, Sandra Bullock is here
to play a montage of some of the movie world's greatest bloopers.
Got it done on board.
And can you? Yeah, that's all I want to do.
Take my time out of my day for this. Thank you.
I had a theme park.
Just a mellow screening of bloopers.
And OK, so you mean like
some of my favorite films that I've seen in theaters lately, like Batman Returns?
Yes, sure. Yes. One clip from Batman Returns.
The entire rest of it, very old black and white films
where, you know, none of us got to see this in person.
So I'm going off of, you know, filmed on a handy cam pretty like.
There's no good ride through of this that you can watch.
But that being said, just with the black and white nature,
I don't I can't tell what the bloopers are.
No, it's hard.
It's hard to tell what happens in the corner of the frame and the shadows.
So I'm not sure what went wrong, if anything.
And it's also like it's movies that people I think were hits in there.
But it's like, I don't know that people are going to be in Germany
are going to be like, oh, look, it's a blooper from like
Paint Your Wagon or The Gold Diggers of 1933.
Did you recognize them, Jason?
I couldn't really recognize.
I was trying.
I would probably recognize the like Footlight Parade bloopers. But
one of the dancers fell off the cake or whatever. Yeah, there is.
And I go ahead, John.
Is there a doc?
So I was to say, is there a doc Hollywood in there?
I thought I thought there was like one other like in color.
And it's like Michael J.
Fox getting like dragged away by a pig.
And I think that's right.
What else would that be?
And I thought it was Michael J.
Fox asked me sort of it's a dark footage.
And I've never seen Doc Hollywood, so I couldn't tell.
Isn't Dennis the Menace Walter Mathau in there, too, real briefly?
Oh, or am I thinking of the other one?
On you guys, I don't.
Walter Mathau for sure is in one unless I was watching the other one
and I got confused.
The Australia. Oh, Mathau was exclusive to Australia, perhaps.
But I don't think I think he was in there briefly, too.
I think it was Dennis the Menace Mathau.
I think that sounds right.
There's a Humphrey Bogart at some point.
He flips over in a chair.
I don't know from what film or why.
But so I think if you're in the Australian one,
it's pretty cut and dry like you're watching this.
And then the gremlins start messing with the film.
And as Joan said, it's the same footage from to
this wonderful part of to, oh, my God, where they get into the projector booth
and they make bunny ears and Lincoln's face and all that.
In the German version, things get a lot more convoluted.
And now I don't speak German despite having had to learn
some when I lived kind of close to this theme park, honestly.
So I don't know what they say.
The only word I recognize is elf.
And it seems like it's just kind of a ladies and gentlemen elf.
And then you're taken to the set and it's sort of it's like a pan
across the set where we're not in diegetically in the world of Alf.
We are looking at crew members and such.
And then we go into sort of a little scene.
So so I'm confused.
First of all, so why the bloopers then?
Like, are we going to see a blooper of Alf?
But then that's not really what happens.
Yes, it also.
Yeah, I mean, it's it's already a little jarring that they go from like these.
Here are your favorite movie bloopers to, I don't know, unless like
Project Alf played in cinemas in Germany.
It's like this is not a movie.
This is definitely not a movie.
Yeah, it's like, yeah, we're taking it now.
We're like behind the scenes with Alf. Yes.
And then you just watch a film, which I just wanted to play this brief
sound bite of if I could share the screen.
OK, so here now, as we said, this is not Paul Fusco,
but rather the a German voice of Alf.
Turn up.
Oh, excellent.
Tight, tight, tight.
Come on, pussy, pussy, pussy, pussy.
Come pussy, pussy, pussy, pussy.
That's that's a lot of fun.
Yeah. Oh, yeah. Agreed.
Somebody should, by the way,
for a follow up to Cardi B and Megan the Stallion,
they should sample that for.
Yeah. WAP2.
I think it's waiting to be a hook.
Yeah, that's that would be a good hook.
Come pussy, pussy.
And here's the thing, maybe we have to make it.
I don't know.
Oh, damn it.
I don't work plus the garage.
Maybe start showing on some beats.
Yeah. Anyway, yes.
All right. So Alf lays down some come pussy, pussy.
And at this point,
Jason is why I wanted to delay my German material, please,
just to get a taste of that guy.
He is no Paul Fusco, the famous in America voice of Alf.
But he this guy is famous in his own right.
This is Tommy Piper.
And an article that I was reading pointed out that Tommy Piper
you know, Germany loved Alf for some reason,
and they specifically loved Tommy Piper as Alf.
And in Germany, Tommy Piper recorded two albums as Alf,
which spawned four top 10 singles.
Holy shit.
Yeah, much better than Alf's try
charting much higher than Alf in the States, who only had those
burger, those Burger King records.
Oh, yeah. Oh, wow.
Sounds familiar.
And you got to come back for us to do this.
We got to do these.
We got to do these all for. Yeah.
They were they were like they weren't even like records.
They were like these like square, like thin pieces of plastic
that could play one song.
McDonald's quick hit, whatever that played like in sync.
I'm loving it.
A flexi disc, right? Flexi.
Yes, that's it. Yes. I think that's right.
Yeah, I was just in this. I will go right back to this.
I was just made aware that Webster had a hit in Japan.
What? Yeah. Do you not know?
Do you not know this, Scott?
No, I don't miss. Oh, my God.
I was just somebody.
One of my friends was like, hey, did you know Webster had a hit in Japan?
And I went, oh, my God.
No way. When he was on the show,
Manuel Lewis had a like chop charting single.
What's the gist of it?
I think it's about maybe partying, I think.
Good for him.
It's good. Very city pop.
Well, oh, really? OK.
I mean, while you do that,
let me just screen show one more time so you guys can see the cover of this one.
This is a compilation album called Alph's Summer Hit Parade,
which has he I think there is an Alph song called Alice Paradiso.
And there is some original Tommy Piper material on here.
But otherwise, it's just like fine young cannibals.
She drives me crazy.
And cool and getting celebration.
It's the it's 28 Internet.
So now top hits and only one of the 28 is Alph.
Did you wait? Is it not even it's not even Alph covering?
She drives me crazy. It's just she drives me crazy.
Fine young cannibals, just the regular one.
But it's it's it's this is like if Alph curated his favorite.
OK, this is like you got Alph summer like play like Alph summer playlist.
Like this would be a Spotify thing.
Like between seasons, if they were making Alph now, you'd get like Alph
summer playlists. Right.
For some summer hits.
Chilling on with these cool tunes.
Barack Obama took the idea of doing a summer playlist from Alph from Al.
Yeah. Now, that's what I call music.
Oh, a lot of money to Alph summer hits parade.
Nobody had thought of putting this together until I'm high.
Yeah. Yeah. Compiling music.
All outside. Webster's song is called City Connection.
Emanuel Lewis, City Connection.
And it is credit to Emanuel Lewis.
The YouTube clip I initially saw said Webster, but it is Emanuel Lewis.
City Connection.
And it is very good title. Wow.
No, it's it's a cool song.
I would like this city connection if that was a if that was a song,
if it was a place that you could go, if that was a bar I can hang in.
That's just a good phrase.
Like like an early 90s, like kind of like like, you know, cop thriller.
Like the city connection seems. Yeah.
Some boring Jason Patrick kind of movie.
Yeah, yeah.
So what one more clip, just to give you a taste of the Alph music.
I wanted to hear him talk before I shared the clip of the song.
This is Alph's biggest hit.
Hello, Alph, Aries to Rhonda.
Is anyone does anyone know Rhonda offhand?
Is anyone an Alph fan enough to know Rhonda?
Rhonda was his girlfriend back on Melamac.
You go. Wow. Geez.
You had it.
I didn't know about Rhonda till this.
And we're looking at Rhonda right now.
Rhonda sings the first part via pre-recorded looped remixed material.
And then you will see Tommy Piper, the German Alph. Here we go.
So just to loop the listeners in,
Tommy Piper is singing next to just an endlessly floating pink.
Like it's what the Superman two villains get trapped in.
It never stops rotating and Rhonda is trapped inside of it.
Well, Tommy Piper sings and Tommy is.
I mean, I've been in my head calling him German Randy Newman.
Yeah, that's very accurate.
Yeah, that's it. Yes.
Also, they they Germany had a Rhonda puppet.
We did it like that.
We didn't have like Rhonda in puppet form, I think.
She was only like a concept.
I think she showed up in the animated show, but like that's
I didn't realize how like deeply into Al of Germany was.
It was maybe not a puppet Rhonda until Germany.
Germany. Yeah, they were like, we need to fill this part of the lore.
This is whatever this this German hits show
top music or whatever needs to we need to see Rhonda.
This is we got to do a whole we have to all do a whole thing here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, if I mean, if only I don't know if he's still around,
but if Tommy Piper, if Tommy Piper himself could do the official
come buzzy buzzy, is there still time?
And it's August.
Can we still get this in as song of the summer?
Our come buzzy buzzy with Tommy Piper.
I think we can. Yeah.
I mean, everything is everything is delayed at the moment.
So I think we can just say it's still summer whenever.
Oh, like taxes, like taxes happen three months later.
So some of the summer entries can still come in, you know, by October.
We're not going to age.
Just don't even count the birthday this year.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. No, it doesn't.
Doesn't count. Our bodies will be nice to us, right?
They won't add wrinkles.
They'll cut us a break.
Trees won't grow rings.
Yeah, nothing stressful.
Nothing stressful will make us
older. So that's wow.
That's Alves love affair with Germany, which seemingly fueled them,
you know, putting this in like, you know, the Gremlins aren't going to be enough.
We have to marry them with Germany's favorite son, Alf.
And all. Hey, wait, all of that was a distraction from what happens
in the scene.
So we're just watching a regular scene of Alf.
There's a there's a buzzy and he goes after it.
And I the only word I understood was Essen, which is eat.
So clearly he's trying to eat the cat and he reaches into the sink
to go for this cat and finds not a cat, but in fact a Gremlin.
And then out from drawers burst Gremlins and cabinets and microwaves.
And this just feels like the movie.
This is like getting a little theme park exclusive Gremlin sequel.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I actually think there's like there's some like the music
and the audio and some of the audio is like lifted directly.
It's definitely new puppeteering, but like a lot of the audio,
I think, is almost lifted directly from the kitchen attack scene in Gremlins, too.
Oh, that's why.
So it's completely the vibe because they're just using the sounds.
Well, well, yeah, definitely.
It's definitely the same track.
That's amazing.
So they so that's a logistics thing that they had to do.
And they had to make new Gremlin puppets just for this.
And also, as I said, Alf has been off the air for six years.
So they had to make a new Alf set just to do this.
Wow. And it's it's very close to like what the Alf Kitchen set is.
Yeah, yeah.
They had to get it out of the Smithsonian.
I was going to say, was it in maybe like the Smithsonian or the Germans?
That's exactly what I was about to say.
Was it in the German Smithsonian already?
And then they just filmed it there.
Yeah, we have the cheer set.
They have the Alf Kitchen Smithsonian guys in.
Yeah, yeah.
That's right.
I yeah, we need a deep dive into it.
Like was Hasselhoff more?
Was he bigger in Germany or was Alf bigger?
Yeah. And did they hate each other?
Right. If Alf saw Hasselhoff anywhere, would they get in a fight?
Was there like a bitch?
Was there like a Lee Roth Hagar tour they tried to go on and then they couldn't
get along because he didn't want to Alf, he didn't want Alf to close.
And then he better war.
Yeah, for.
Yeah, they were going to switch back and forth.
But four shows in, they killed it.
You know what I neglected to say?
David Hasselhoff's stirring Berlin Wall,
crumbling anthem, looking for freedom is on Alf's summer hit parade.
So really, maybe that indicates that like
West and East Germany, that they came to a historic truce.
I hope that's the case.
I hope we don't find something ugly between the two of them.
The drunk footage of Alf.
The claw in it.
Don't even don't even look at me, David.
Don't even look at me.
I don't have the problem. You have the problem.
So, yeah, you got a little exclusive Alf movie with mixed up with the Grimms,
which is what I kind of we wanted from the Beetlejuice version.
If it was like Beetlejuice just going nuts and then he like he's
met his match with the gremlins in a little scene.
Sure, you think that would have gone a long way.
That would have been fun.
So it's easier to get else than to get Michael Keaton.
For some reason, Michael Keaton didn't want to suit up again
for clear for not much money.
What a quitter.
I think they could have gotten
they could have gotten like whoever was playing Beetlejuice at Universal Florida.
They could have gotten something like that.
Because Beetlejuice is an animatronic in it, right?
Yes. So, yeah, we haven't talked about it.
It seems like he's an animatronic several times.
It seems like if they had and if they could get Sandra Bullock for like the opening,
I guess they didn't.
Australia didn't have Sandra Bullock.
Sandra Bullock was exclusive to Germany.
Don't think so, because this was put in in 96, which was post speed.
So she's at her height.
But the other one was 91 where we didn't we hadn't really met Sandra yet.
So, right. I guess that's what's going on again.
Now that we know we're adding the plot, the Gremlins have interrupted the Alf show.
Why the bloopers?
Why did any of that happen?
Yeah, why wasn't it just like you're seeing Alf and like we're seeing an episode of Alf
and like it's playing out normally the same jokes and then he goes into the kitchen
and then it's Gremlins terror.
Like that would make a lot more sense.
Like, hey, we're going to show you a new episode of Alf.
Remember Alf, the top character in Germany?
We're going to see an episode.
That would be the good that would be an easy conduit.
And you still get a fake out.
You still get the fun fake out.
I mean, I can kind of understand like you're getting into the vibe of like,
it's like, oh, we're seeing some bloopers.
There's this blooper and that like, oh, like Michael J.
Fox got pulled away by a pig and now like, but the ultimate blooper is Gremlins
attack your set. But like, it's still like like,
it's like I can understand the the like the thought,
but it doesn't quite like play out.
Here's my punch up to what I just said.
It's Alf hosts the history of the movies.
Alf is in his house. He's going, he says, well, here we're going to look at it.
You know, it doesn't always go right on.
He doesn't always go right on set.
And then we see a few bloopers and then he cuts back to Alf.
He's in the kitchen and then the Gremlins explode.
So now we've already set up.
It's about the magic of filmmaking.
Alf is there and now the Gremlins are a surprise.
So so basically your punch up is eliminate Sandra Bullock.
Just give it all to 100 percent gone.
Bullock gone. Michael J. Fox gone. Mathau gone.
Unfortunately, yeah, he had to kick her out.
But you know, yeah, she offers nothing to the story.
Yeah, I feel no remorse about this. Yeah. Yeah.
Not that I don't. I mean, yeah.
And you know, I want to I want an Alf Sandra Bullock team up someday.
But this wasn't the place or time.
Doesn't seem that crazy that in some bizarre post
Deadpool that somehow the hottest property would become the
or I should say post Detective Pikachu, really, that somehow
there's a really cutting edge Alf Sandra Bullock film.
And it is the it saves the movie industry.
It played in three years and puts people back in the AMC seats.
Like what? Yeah, that's it brings people back to theater.
The the just like on fire combination of Sandra Bullock and Alf.
That'd be great. I mean, I think we all actually like that idea.
Yeah. Oh, genuinely. Yes.
I'm looking at smiles. This is all very sincere. Yeah.
Oh, take some time.
It's just it's just here.
Take a deep breath and imagine it.
And then it's such a man.
Let's all select the split screen option on Max.
And we're all pulling up final draft to take a crack at it.
What are all splitting up scenes?
Yes. Oh, wait.
The gremlins are in our computer.
They're messing with her final draft files. Get out of here.
Well, now that you know, that is something that that gives me the
they could have done a parody of theme park rides
going like theme, the setup of theme park rides being X thing goes wrong.
As it stands, it's just movie studio.
History goes wrong.
Escape through fake movie studio.
But if they were like, it's the movie studio, right?
Or like, well, the I think I know you're saying it.
I think it's probably a good idea.
I think the whole focus, much like Universal Studios for this park
with when it was rethought, was we're going to show everyone how to make movies.
So I think they were like, everything has to sort of correspond to this
park narrative in the same way that Universal early on was very focused on
making movies.
And it's another one of those weird
where the the the German one was kind of copying the branding of the Australian one.
But the German one was never a movie studio,
whereas Australia was and maybe still is.
I know that strangely the 2002 Scooby
Doo, either that one or the sequel or both were shot.
Now I have an there's an attraction at the park based on Scooby Doo, but
they were also shot right there.
I I believe the Australian, literally the Australian Scooby Doo.
It's like they shot it in the studio, like right next to the the Australian
the Australian park.
And I believe that's the ride that to this day.
Occupies the space that was Gremlins is I think it's called like Scooby
Doo's like spooky coaster or whatever.
And it's still very steeped in the 2002 Scooby Doo movie, where
like I think like you still like the coaster faces off against like monster
Scrappy Doo. Oh, great.
Wow. I love that.
I forgot that's what happens in those movies.
The German replacement is along the lines of this ride.
The German replacement is much funnier.
I don't remember what it is in the wider cultural spectrum.
Oh, it's a Van Helsing.
He's right. Yeah.
Have you ever seen the the intro video for that ride is great.
No, no. Mm hmm.
It's it's like it's like a news.
It's like a German newscaster being like, oh, yeah, I saw that.
It's like vampires are going to attack Germany in a couple of months.
Like if that our only hope is Van Helsing.
But I just I felt like imminent.
It's like a couple of months in a couple of months, vampires might attack.
Where's Van Helsing?
There's a lack of urgency in that setup.
Yeah. Oh, it's cool.
They're preparing early, though, unlike the coronavirus preparation and
snuffing it out.
Yeah. I mean, you'd rather they get to it three months ahead of time.
It is efficient, famously efficient Germans.
Very efficient.
But like, you know, I like Plan A.
Yes, like Van Helsing. Great.
But like, like if you have this much time, we work it on some back
work on some backup.
I guess. Yeah. Yeah.
I have a couple. Yeah.
Like it's like we're, you know, we're developing several vaccines right now
for covid. So I have multiple vampire hunters.
Abraham Lincoln, Abraham Lincoln,
Al.
And a vampire hunter.
Yeah, I'm now a proponent of Al's being.
Let's just just copy and paste our plus up for any ride in the future
to be more out.
Mm hmm. I mean, that's a good I mean, we should say what ride would be better
with Alph on it and is the answer all of them.
I can't think of one where it would
bother me like I'm trying to think of rides that I love.
Star tours.
If suddenly like star tours, what are you doing?
That'd be great.
I'm the greatest. He was alien.
It makes so much sense.
Is any ride too sacred for Alph?
Alph and the country bear Jamboree would kill.
It would be awesome.
Oh, yeah.
Alph is Alph is your skipper for the 10 times better than the regular skippers.
Yeah. No offense to them.
They're great. It's just Alph would be the best.
Those leopards are making me hungry.
Wow. This is great.
They should just have a whole year where Alph's on every ride at Disneyland.
Oh, yeah. Well, you know, suspense for the Sandra Bullock movie.
Yeah.
Alph should really when when Halloween Horror Nights come back,
like Alph hosting a terror tram would be amazing.
Oh, yeah. That's that is legitimately very good.
Yeah. I, I, Alph, even Alph just popping up in the mazes.
Like you could have a connecting narrative where Alph's just is in all the mazes
in little spots.
Yeah. The character.
Which I mean, all together this year is Alph.
Yeah, there's no bad idea here.
And there's like, I love the idea of there being like a wider narrative to all.
Like, you know, if you go to the mazes in the right order,
there's a wider Alph narrative that you get.
This is great. Talk to John Murty.
Let's email him the head of Horror Nights.
Yeah, we know how to save it next year.
There's going to be trepidation about people going back.
But we've got just the thing.
And Jason has interviewed the man in person.
I have met him. Yes.
Look, John, there's this Sandy Bullock Alph movie coming
and you're going to want to be on the look.
Every studio is co-producing this.
So you're going to be want to be on the ground floor.
Capitalizing on come pussy pussy, the hottest song of summer 2020.
It's going to be Al fever and everyone's going to want a piece.
So Alph mayhem happens.
Then some footage is repeated from government's to government's too.
But I'm not complaining because I like that a lot.
Then if you guys watched both the Australian version and the German version,
there's a big difference here.
So the the Grimmons are in the projection booth and in the Australian one,
it's like, oh, my God, everyone, gremlins here.
Hurry, you got to come in here.
We got to escape in the German one.
The lights come on and everyone quietly exits the room.
A door silently opens and everyone just gets up and walks through it.
I hear people sigh.
Is there an announcement to walk through the door or they just go,
oh, the door's open, let's go.
Probably. We know what this meant.
We're efficient. We know what to do.
It felt like it felt like when Gio and I were at Six Flags on the Justice League
ride and doors would just open and you go, I think we're supposed to go in that door
because there's no one here to tell us that.
And it felt yeah.
So it was like, I wonder if somebody was on this, maybe another side of the room.
And you couldn't see and they were like, just like they did like an aggressive point like.
There, everyone's like, OK, all right, we'll go.
Mark's through the door.
You walk through a room that has just a bunch of posters on the wall,
like really quick, you see a flash of a Tom Petty and the Heartbreakers poster.
I'm not sure why.
It's just a bunch of random posters.
But then really, really cool.
You don't even have to wait for the ride.
There is a gremlin swinging on a light fixture.
And when you get up close to it, the light bulb that's actually on
and powered is in his hand. Really cool.
Very cool. Yeah.
So it does feel like that's the spirit.
Immediately they got the spirit.
You want to see. Yeah, you want to feel like because if I was a kid,
that would scare the shit out of me immediately.
I would be like, oh, God, here we go.
Walk forward. I'd be kind of like, does it?
It's like the alien on great movie ride.
Come to the ceiling. I have to go under this.
This is too much, too much for me.
Yeah. So cool.
Do that classic like haunted house
move of like staying really close behind somebody else.
Oh, I know it well. So if there's a scare, they take it.
And then you can like run and then like and then hurry them along.
Yeah, I still employ this tactic to this day.
Yeah. It's a good tactic.
The Valencia teens shielded me last year at Frightfest from all the scares.
I would I would be hiding behind the teens in Valencia.
It's a good strategy.
Yeah. But now with social distancing, you're going to have to wait.
But the least distant you are is ever is hiding behind teens to get through.
That's a good question.
Well, I still feel comfortable hiding behind the Valencia teens.
I don't. Well, at least anything that's good that might scare you,
you know, will be six feet away for a while.
Hopefully. Yeah. Yeah.
The next year's mazes alpha will have to be six feet away
in the mazes when he's tying it all together.
Many, many. Yeah.
So now you're at least in the video we're watching.
There's a cut. Now you're in the ride vehicle and you're and suddenly Gizmo.
Here we go. I don't know where. Yes.
Yeah. He got in the ride up until this point.
Yeah. So Gizmo's here and Alf is in a cool chair,
a rotating chair with a little joystick.
And they're hanging together.
I guess Gizmo reasons he is fluffy like me.
So I should cling to Alf for safety.
Although Gizmo resembles a cat much more than the other gremlins.
So watch out Gizmo. Yes. Yes.
This is this is great.
Alf in the big chair is this chair is sticking out to me as well
when I'm watching this video for whatever reason.
This is I like the rest of the ride.
I like what what follows.
But this is really the image.
This is when I think whenever I first saw an article about it,
which might have been Peter at Slashfilm, who I think listens to the show, the
that that just like what it's mind boggling seeing those two next.
And a cool chair is the best.
One of the best chairs in a ride, I think.
I think so. Yeah.
Can we think of a better chair?
Mm hmm.
Are there thrones or thrones in rides, I assume?
Yeah. The fact that we can't think of one immediately means this one
is this one of the chair final four by default.
I guess like I would think like there's like the pirate
it doesn't the pirate king have a throne in Pirates of the Caribbean.
The first part that that.
Yeah, but it's not like that's it.
Like that's a fine chair, but it doesn't like stick out.
It doesn't even like it took me a minute to think about it.
Whatever the chair. Yeah.
Is it I think it's the same chair that Captain Jack Sparrow
is sitting in at the end of the ride.
Yeah. Going back up the lift hill.
Yeah. So I guess that's in contention.
Again, solution to it, should we be arriving at a point
where Johnny Depp should not be in that attraction?
All elf, all of them are.
Oh, perfect. Oh, God.
I read pirate elf.
That'd be great. Elf with an eyepatch.
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
That's a plus.
I just as long as we're like eliminating like problematic people
and things from from theme parks, let's just give all of of Hogwarts to.
So wait, how about how about we just say elf created Harry Potter?
So you reimagine it as if it's from the mind of elf.
Yeah, I like but like I want all of like all the rides to be redone with like
no matter how right Mackey and Harry Potter.
Yeah, but perfect.
Yeah. So you just change all the human characters
to or the wizard characters to elf Malmacians.
Escape from Gringotts is now Rhonda's revenge.
Fantastic.
I think this would get the industry moving again, I think.
There's probably a warehouse of old elf masks in America or in Germany
that we can just you don't even have to spend a lot of money to upgrade these.
You put the masks.
Jason, that's smart thinking.
Do it cheaply. That's good.
You know, do it.
We got to have you got to reopen with some new attractions when you reopen.
OK, so it's just it's Jack Sparrow, but with an elf mask
and then like some brown baseball gloves to quickly simulate out of the sands.
Yeah, there's no yeah, we should specify all the elf plus ups.
There's no money to do them.
So they have to be an elf mask found in a warehouse in Germany that already exists.
And then some brown like winter gloves
or some like burlap burlap or leather gloves.
An elf has a human proportion.
Alf is six foot one.
He's like a weird, weird Halloween, like cheap Halloween store
costume version of it.
Yeah, just like Alf.
Yeah, it's like what I would like.
Six, three, six, three, elf.
That weirds me out to a big elf.
Oh, you'll get the writing light, the lighting right.
And you'll be it'll be great.
You'll ever know.
The Imagineers will figure that out.
How to yeah. Yeah.
So I think at this point is where this is where it's all been.
I think we can say this is one of the strangest rides that we've ever talked about.
And it gets extra strange when you start heading through this facility,
which is sort of a film vault.
And then the first room, I just when you see the all caps, German word
film archive, which is, you know, spell like our archive is spelled without an E
and it's all one word.
This is just this is where it feels like an art film of a ride.
Now it's just so abstract and strange and sometimes spare for a little bit.
They you're going through a room that's so dark that the guy filming it
is to turn the night vision on. Yeah.
Yeah, I think also maybe they were they kind of like this idea
because they were like, well, it's a warehouse, so it doesn't have to look
that good.
It doesn't have to have so much production value to it.
There's just the.
Yeah, we got we got low ceilings and it makes sense.
So it does feel yeah, there might have been some.
Yeah, because you would obviously want the ride to take place in that.
What did you call an atrium?
What did you do from the movie?
So, yes. Yeah, yeah.
The clamp tower.
But yeah, they're not going to build that.
This is, you know, actually, when you bring up the stuff from the movie,
I realized something, maybe why Beetlejuice and Alf
and anyone, you know, go ahead and call me a heretic about this.
But it seems like of all the things that we could say that we love about
the Gremlins movies, it does not feel like the main actor
really sticks with anybody.
I don't want to just trash this guy.
Human character that Gallagher and Gallagher.
Yeah.
Um, well, like he's fine.
It's just not, you know, like he didn't become some big films.
It's not exactly like a charismatic Michael J.
Fox at the center of the movie.
And in a way, is that why we got to bring in Beetlejuice and Alf?
Because we can't like nobody's going to get excited that Zach.
Yeah, Billy's here.
Yeah. Am I wrong?
Do people love Billy and I'm I'm?
No, he's fine.
I'm not saying he's fine. Yeah.
Phoebe Cates was the star.
I didn't realize her whole career is that like
people were nervous about her doing gremlins because she had done so many
like scandalous roles, which look pretty tame in our current
like the current culture.
Those Phoebe Cates like scandalous roles.
Well, yeah, she takes off her top once.
And that's so appalling.
Well, yeah.
And there were some some other movie like that, too.
And she did a lot of magazines.
Like she was a big star.
And I think it was one of them, either Dante or Spielberg went to bat
for her to get her in gremlins.
And I like her in this.
I think she I wish they gave in the movies.
I think they should have given her more stuff to do.
Yeah. Well, the second movie especially kind of turns into an ensemble movie.
Yeah, that's really like, yeah, got so many different characters.
Like you see, there's certain characters that are like have like three scenes.
I feel like. Yeah, yeah.
Kind of them among.
So I guess, yeah, it wouldn't really make sense to anchor it in these folks.
Yeah.
And animatronics of them might not work so great.
They might not be identifiable because there's at some point
like a human security guard in this ride.
And it's very much of the quality of like the E.T.
police officers.
It's not exactly fully articulated.
Yeah.
Mannequins that have slight movement.
A glorified mannequin. Yes.
Yeah.
So, yeah, that's interesting.
Like, I guess, yeah, you would want like some that.
Yeah, was we were saying someone to explain it.
And it's not like.
Yeah, there's such a strong character that everyone immediately goes,
oh, I know who that is.
It would be nice to see the the count, the
L. Lewis.
Yeah, that's you could do that.
That's like broad enough to do as an animatronic.
Can I ask a question?
Why didn't they just get Al Lewis?
I love that. That actor is great.
They talk about that.
I saw Joe Dante interviews where they he has been posed that question.
And he said he just thought it'd be more interesting if a real
more esteemed actor did it.
Fair.
I mean, Al Lewis is a maniac.
And I think it would be interesting also to see him in this movie.
Just like, yeah, like just play it be like as Al Lewis.
Yes. Yeah.
I mean, you could have worn out anything, really,
because obviously he has very grandpa Munster outfit and hair in this.
But Al Lewis is another, I assume, future second gate episode waiting to happen.
Oh, yeah.
Because he had a restaurant called Grandpa's that he did not own,
but he would just sit there all day
and like greet people, essentially.
I'm game. I'll do that one.
Yeah. He could have been in this just as well as Alf.
So anyway, now you end up.
So now you're in the film vaults.
You're watching a vault get destroyed.
It's a little bit more comical than the massive universal fire,
which destroyed the masters of many of our favorite artists
and millions of hours of historic music, a modern burning of Alexandria,
if you will, that happened on universal property.
And they lied about anyway, it's more it's more fun to see the gremlins
tearing apart, you know, what the the Maltese Falcon or something.
I mean, that is fun.
I mean, it would yes, it would be.
It would have been more fun if whenever that was 10 years ago,
if it was like gremlins have invaded Universal Studios
and they ripping up Jimmy Buffett's masters.
You know, you would enjoy that too of the most important masters.
Well, yeah, you said like our most important artists.
So I just I went to one of the, you know, the top recording artists.
There were layers in there were instruments we didn't even know
were layered into the 16 track mix of.
Yeah, did you?
There's three different kinds of steel drums he uses on
License to Chill, the album License to Chill.
So he built his own.
He engineered his own last room, burnt them because he wasn't happy.
Do you know how much reverb was on the steel drums on the album?
Last Mango in Paris?
I don't think you do. And you'll be able to.
It's gone forever. We won't know.
We won't have that like Giles Martin, George Martin's clip
where they're in the studio raising the levels to hear exactly the lost parts
of these great songs.
We won't find the part in the notes where Jimmy said,
Ed, this is fine and went on vacation.
Put it out.
Next two months off.
Sounds good to me.
And then there's the car speeding away.
Or I guess the plane or the boat speeding away.
Have fun mixing by.
Uh, OK, so, uh, let's see.
We're in the film vault.
What scenes stick out to be?
I mean, this is again, it's not the most the best documented thing.
We sort of go through like an editing facility.
Are there moments that jump out to people?
I think there isn't there like an editor who's like tied up or something.
Yeah, you see a lot of like you kind of go by the different rooms
and then there's the editing room, which looks like an editing room
in from 1960 or something.
And there's just so much tape everywhere spun around.
And that's that's pretty fun.
Yeah, yeah, it's very like reminiscent of like the the Gremlins
messing with the reels at the movie theater and Gremlins in the first Gremlins.
Yeah, yeah, it's all.
You get some real core Gremlins action in this, right?
And that I think the it's like what they want.
What the Gremlins do is they immediately absorb what a human job is,
kind of get the fundamentals of it and do it.
But in a in an edgy way, an edgy destroy.
Yeah. And like they like get enough of the thing to be like,
I know how to turn this into like a bit like I can make it like I can do
like the funny bit version of whatever this is.
And Gremlins do they're pretty quickly on the phone saying, bye, sell.
And like they're like trying to edit the movie and kind of pulling it off.
But in a chaos way.
Yeah, I like that scene.
I like, oh, I got to get to the end of the ride already.
The one that sticks out to me is the end where the Gremlin
goes down the box and the lights go down because I just I'm having my little kid
brain of like, oh, no, but it is a very memorable scene.
And everything else bleeds together a little bit for me.
It doesn't have these big like tentpole moments like some other rides.
Do I feel like? Yeah.
Well, though, though. Oh, sorry. Go ahead.
Well, I was just going to say they lean a lot on the Gremlins
getting into the costume department.
Yeah. And then they get it like there's a marching band.
There's I think it's a scene from Robin Hood.
Prince of the OK.
Yeah, there's a Robin Hood.
The Robin Hood jousting like Robin Hood.
Is it Little John that he that he is jousting?
Is there there's like a Gremlin Robin Hood and Gremlin Little John.
Yeah. With the Bo staffs on the law.
Yeah. Yeah, that is good.
I was I mean, this is very similar to great movie ride in the sense
that you're in a very similar vehicle and you're going through little show scenes.
But great movie ride, I think, is was as helped by the fact
that you would stop for a second and you get everything to play out.
And this one, you kind of just growl through it.
So maybe stuff like that would pop a little bit better
if they were like kind of more like this is this scene.
And now this is this scene.
It's kind of it's a pretty basic ride mechanism.
And I feel like the only maybe that's the genuine plus up is, I think,
if this if the ride could suddenly spin around by surprise
in a cartoon spin sort of way or, you know, not that it's going to have a drop
or anything, but or some, you know, weird jolts.
I think any little effect like that would bump this over into
a shockingly great ride.
Because that's what I was going to say.
If there's like I like we've said, like this,
I think this ride really captures the spirit of like Gremlin's mayhem really well.
I think the only thing that would do so even better and take it
even like a more like Gremlin meta level is if it was like the Gremlins
were also like fucking with the ride.
Yes. Yeah. Oh, big time.
You want the ride vehicle.
I don't know if I'm sure Tony Baxter or somebody has said something like this.
You do want the ride vehicle and what it does to sort of
be the spirit of whatever the property is or whatever the idea behind the ride is.
So it's like it's just going very slowly like it's a normal tram.
It does defeat the purpose.
You don't get the like crazy manic energy.
Yeah. You saw it would be great if you saw a Gremlin
with wires that were sparking.
And clearly that is your your ride mechanism.
Or yeah, I was just or I was even even like in the Jurassic Park ride
where you're it looks like you're supposed to be going one way.
But like the like the dinosaurs fuck with it and then you go the other way.
Like that would be a fun mechanic where like, oh, this is the escape.
Like no, but no, no, no.
Like Gremlin's flip the switch and now you're going like deeper in.
That would be great.
Or the Gremlin is like controlling the like it's like on Rise of the Resistance.
There's a droid controlling your vehicle.
A Gremlin pops up from front of the ground and he's controlling the vehicle.
Yes. Something like that.
Or even like a tram full of Gremlins dressed like tourists.
Like they are. Yeah, that's yes.
That needs to happen.
Oh, Gremlin tour guide would be so great.
Yeah, yeah.
I was going to say, I'd love it if like you could like you got like in
like there were like maybe like I think all of the core Gremlins
to Gremlins should like have their own like you either get like a Lenny,
a Daffy or a George
tram and it like yeah, like it even affects the way that the the the tram moves,
depending on which Gremlin is navigating with like mumbly like
as you can see on the left.
Yeah.
What's your turn of vehicle?
What's the smart Gremlins name who's voiced by Tony Randall,
the great Tony Randall from the odd couple?
That is just brain.
OK, I'm I would love to get brain Gremlins car to be the best tour.
That'd be the most important.
Yeah, he should be narrating this.
He should be like, yeah, yes.
Yeah, no, the guide or some sort of centerpiece of this.
Honestly, he's so good.
He's he could have he needed the money at the time, I believe,
like around the time that like 82 year old Tony Randall
like was actually having a having a kid.
I think it might be years.
I think it actually might be like five years before or something.
He had kids.
He had kids so late.
He had like in his mid 70s and he dies five years later.
It's insane. Yeah.
Real wild. Anyway, yeah, you should.
He should have done it.
I think this is all you know.
I don't even mean to like criticize this ride that much or say
it's not the ultimate Gremlins experience.
I'm almost just more excited about these plus ups and wish
they could be done because I think they did get part of the way there.
Like when you round a corner and see a room with, you know,
over a dozen gremlins, which happens a couple of times, it's it's legit.
And they pull it off great.
You just wish they could.
I wish you could go back in time and just give this ride,
you know, tens of millions more of more dollars.
I've got from now we've said a lot of different
we've thrown a lot of different ideas out.
Oh, and you mentioned 40 X early.
I feel like maybe the ultimate gremlins would be essentially a Tiki room
for the X gremlins show.
A 360 gremlin show.
The seats move.
The whole thing can rotate gremlins popping out.
You get to have all the fun with all the different characters.
And it's a lot more like they're putting on a show for you like the birds are.
Also, like attached to a like in park bar like like that.
We were like, yeah, like where they're like gremlins on a seat next to you.
Like, yeah, this would be yes, that would be a huge hit.
I don't know.
Warner Brothers is in a weird spot with theme parks still to this day.
It feels like with some of these parks, they were like flirting
a little bit more with getting like more involved, but then they've pulled back
and then they sold six flags.
I don't know if it's even possible.
It's because it seems like I mean, I've done a lot of letters like they have.
There's the Warner's Park in Dubai, right?
Yeah. Yes. Yes.
But that that means almost entirely on like Looney Tunes,
DC and Scooby Doo, it feels like. Right.
And even though I think that's not I think that's there's some cool stuff there.
It doesn't feel like the biggest budget for everything.
Yeah. So it's still like when will Warner Brothers
other than obviously Harry Potter get a major budget for a lot of it?
So like we don't have a definitive Batman ride, which is insane.
Yeah, there's great coasters.
But the idea that it's like so easy, like we want a good Batman ride.
And it's like never going to happen.
It's almost I would say behind the perennial issues with Tomorrowland.
It's it's all I might call it the number two most persisting
may never get solved.
Big theme park problem that all of these properties
that would make great attractions never get to imagineering level
or universal level, you know, fully done versions.
Like just a man.
Put the put the Gremlins thing we just described or any of our Gremlins ideas
with the bar, a full Gotham City, an amazing ticket.
Just make five of these things and it'll be so popular.
Like it's such a slam dunk with how much people like all these Warner Brothers
properties that if they just put the money into it, it would be so popular.
Like a real Looney Tunes ride, like a ticket.
Everyone is in it. Like, right.
I don't. Yeah, right.
And you take a Looney Tunes, you take a Batman.
Also, you take a Gremlins.
But we did the thing to make this happen.
We have to change the structure of corporate America.
This is a huge different things have to own different things.
HBO Max world.
Now that the restructuring.
Yeah. I mean, why not?
I mean, like, I mean, that makes it like, right.
A game of a game like Game of Thrones ride makes total sense.
They have so many things.
They have so many properties that are like have stood the test of time
that would really lend themselves to rides.
And they just can't get their shit together.
And now, especially I want to get a babe taking this.
Babe, picking the city walk through kids, kids.
It's a kids area is the big big in the city area. Yeah. Yes. Yes.
The cartoons you have were the DC Superhero Girls, ThunderCats.
Those are great rides. Oh, yeah. Yeah.
They agreed. They especially like thunder.
I like any generation of thundercats would make a fantastic ride.
Like you're in the fun, like in the thunder tank.
I'll go like going through thunder, thunder, thunder.
Yeah. Yeah.
Multiple generations now of different thunder.
ThunderCats cartoon.
And we also been denied.
You know, we got this version of Gremlins as early 90s Gremlins,
but we've been denied weird time capsule rides from Warner Brothers as well.
I mean, we have stuff that's Batman Forever influenced
at the roller coasters at the various parks.
But we should have a stuck in time
Batman Forever Dark Ride that opened in 1996.
Absolutely.
Yeah, we've been deprived of that.
That's something we were owed and we did not get and we never will get.
But yeah, like those.
Yeah, I want that like those weird curiosity attractions that are like,
like, I don't know the kids know what like have any idea of what our world is.
But it's that makes it all the more fascinating. Yes.
Yeah, we need a kiss from a rose playing on a loop, annoying
people working at the gift shop for decades upon decades. Yeah.
Like, yeah, the like attendees like still in like
like a now very faded like Riddler question marks band.
Yes, this is this has been denied.
We've been denied.
We're we've we really missed out.
And it's upsetting to me to think about all we could have had
a roller coaster based on the George Clooney vehicle, the American.
Yes. I'm just looking at my HBO Max Q now.
HBO Max, surprisingly deep library, surprisingly good.
Yeah, yeah, there's good.
Very good. Can't use it on my TV yet because I got a Roku, but pretty good.
Good on the laptop. You know, what are you going to do?
I've been going through all the Miyazaki movie.
Oh, yeah. I don't know what they actually have the rights to.
But oh, my gosh, like, and they like riding the cat riding the the cat bus.
Oh, my God.
Chiki, all good. All perfect rides.
That's incredible.
Aren't they opening up a world?
They are. They're opening in Japan, in Japan, a Ghibli park.
I did not know that.
That's amazing. I don't know if it's full like rides,
but I think it's a very themed immersive world.
Well, but I thought you had much of the status on that.
And, you know, you've got to have
if not an attraction, then at least a walk around Bazinga.
Oh, oh, well, yeah, that's his name, right?
His name was Bazinga.
He is Bazinga.
Oh, look, Bazinga.
Mommy, it's Bazinga.
A whole land starring Bazinga based on the location of the show Pasadena.
Young Bazinga.
It's all your favorites. Yeah.
And then it started then when it's Halloween,
it's like Bazinga dresses up like the Flash.
Of course, of course, of course.
And then the Flash dresses up like Bazinga.
Yeah. Oh, that's nice little time.
Very fun. Masks on top of all of them.
Well, so to close out, unless we have other.
I was going to say the ride ends with like Alf electrocuting all the gremlins.
Yes. Yeah, he saves the day.
It's the solution from gremlins to the new batch.
And great sequence of all the so many gremlins with firehoses
shooting them over the ride vehicles. That's really cool.
Again, the video isn't great.
I wish I could see this in full fidelity or, of course, in person.
But that seems like a legit amazing scene. Yeah.
Well, and it's missing because at the very end, you pull up next to a big red car
that Alf is driving.
And in pictures, I found Gizmo is standing on the hood, which, of course,
that's what you want to see.
But the video, it looks like Gizmo has been removed or was like not put in yet.
They finally got him. They killed him in the right.
That's see. That was the implication.
I was like, did Gizmo live?
Where is he?
They're good. They're good.
It was that it had multiple endings.
You can see the good ending where Gizmo lives and the bad ending where Gizmo dies.
Oh, no. Like Radiator Springs.
Yeah. Australia Beetlejuice in a police car.
Mm hmm. Yes.
Alf is in a fire truck.
Fire truck. Is that what it is?
It's not just a red car. It's a fire truck.
Yeah. I thought it was just like Archie's jalopy.
I thought it was a big red jalopy.
It's not look.
You know what a fire truck looks like in your mind, but it's
Alf has got like a sleeker version of that that he drives around here.
So, yeah, I mean, that's great.
I would have loved if the ride was like 10 minutes long
and you really got a bunch of different Alf Gizmo things
and they were trying to fix whatever is going wrong.
They were following you through the ride.
You should have seen what that when those two put their heads together,
what happens, it's mainly that they are standing next to each other, which
for me, as I said, is plenty.
That that visual is my favorite thing about this attraction.
But yeah, I don't know.
You want to see Gizmo dance or do his Rambo business?
I wouldn't I wouldn't have my like, you know, I feel like Gizmo is in both movies
is given a little bit of a hero's moment at the end.
You know, whether it's the Rambo moment from Gremlins 2
or him driving that little pink convertible from Gremlins 1.
I wouldn't mind if like a little more of a maybe we got it.
It was just lost in translation the video, but I would not have minded a like
little Gremlins, a little, you know, Gizmo hero moment.
Yes, for sure.
That feels like a real missed opportunity.
Be up other Gremlins.
I mean, I guess he's kind of like is a little afraid of him.
He keeps his distance.
But, you know, like Shondu in Sinbad ride in Disney
see if he's like bopping one of them on the head or, you know, is blind,
blinding them or bonking them.
I don't know. Something fun.
Bonking or blinding either way.
Good with all of that easily.
One of the cutest, at least cutest IP animatronics that the.
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
Yeah. They pull it off really well.
It does. It does look good.
You know, well, since we're talking about, you know, the the Gremlins
and theme parks, I kind of have made this connection my head
and I keep thinking about it.
And I'm sure I'm not the first person to say this, but
are the minions just Gremlins, but they're all cute like Gizmo?
Hmm. Interesting.
Because the minions kind of do Gremlin stuff, I guess they're less
and they're a little insidious.
But like, yeah, do we like do people like the minions?
Because for the same reason, they like the Gremlins.
They might have I see.
I see, you know, they sharing some of the same like energy.
But I would say the big difference is I feel like the minions are like
very like needy and like like codependent.
And like Gremlins are just like, you know, they are like agents of chaos
who are, you know, bound by like bound to like no no person
or even like each other.
They don't even like the great like a one Gremlin will throw acid
in another Gremlin's face like they don't even they barely even care about each other.
Yeah, they're a leaderless collective that can instantly
devolve into antagonists.
Yes, yes.
But there are unless I guess.
Sorry, John, go ahead.
Oh, unless you have like brain Gremlin to kind of kind of like straddles
both worlds of like, you know, he can be a leader, but also knows
like how to like, you know, tap into that Gremlin vibe.
Yeah, there's no Tony Randall minion.
And that's the biggest difference.
So it's really hurt the franchise over the years.
They really should. They try.
They should. I was going to compile Tony's voice from Odd Couple
and then add it into one of the movies. Yeah, sure.
They tried it in Despicable Me 3.
They tried to like have a leader like Minion, but I'm I we all
I can't remember that minions name, so it didn't really work out great. Right.
I was thinking last week because we talked about a
potato mascot for a while named Mr.
Tato, and I was thinking he kind of looked like a king minion.
Well, yeah, yeah, yeah.
He's kind of a guy.
Taller. Yeah, the taller taller minion.
Yeah, they should have put him in the movie.
Well, yeah, I don't know.
Anything we miss closing thoughts?
We obviously wish there could be some other Gremlins attraction,
but we're damned by the corporate malfeasance that stops it from happening.
But we I don't know.
I mean, I think this is this is so much fun.
I'm so glad it exists.
And I think it does. Yeah.
For a lot of the spirit.
Yeah, I agree. Absolutely.
I think, yeah, we wish there would be another.
I mean, maybe the full Gremlins resurgence,
maybe they'll license it out to some some park again.
So we'll see. Maybe.
Who knows if the cartoons have hit and then there's another movie, maybe.
Yeah. Fingers crossed.
Or, you know,
do we give this over?
Is it just like I mean, Gremlins could be taking over the Harry Potter.
Could be taking over Hogwarts.
Yeah, you could just be.
Maybe there's some version like that where you could be watching video of J.K.
Rowling and then the Gremlin Saul pounce on her.
And because, yeah, if we know any like Gremlins are like,
and Gremlins are very gender fluid, like if they even have a like,
which is even assume they have a gender to begin with.
So, yeah, I think, yeah, they would definitely, you know, yeah,
they attack target number one.
Sir, is an enemy.
Yeah, they definitely are.
She is. J.K. Rowling, I'm going to say, is as a Gremlins expert,
I can say J.K. Rowling is definitely an enemy of the Gremlins.
Like specifically, like every human is to some extent,
unlike special ones, but like they would like target her specifically.
Yeah, I think so.
Amen. The official ruling.
I agree. And on that note, Joan Ford, you survived podcast, The Ride, The Second Gate.
Thank you for being here. This was a blast.
Thank you so much for having me.
So far, let's exit through the gift shop.
Is there anything you would like to plug?
Oh, sure. You can just follow me on Twitch at
or at twitch.tv slash Joan Haley Ford.
And that's all my handles, Joan Haley Ford on Instagram and Twitter.
And you can see my stuff on Cartoon Network every now and then,
whether it's on Thundercats or DC Superhero Girls
and a show called Yabba Dabba Dinosaur is coming to HBO Max.
So look out for all that.
There you go. Great HBO Max family, just like just like Gremlins and Gremlins too.
Talk also on one episode of a Quibi show.
So get Quibi just for that. Oh, yes.
Hell, yeah. Do the free trial and then undo it.
If Quibi comes out with a big, cool e-ticket theme park before HBO Max
and Warner Brothers, I'm going to be very upset.
Me too. Yeah, it's possible.
About Quibi. I'm in this dangerous game.
I take it back. I'd be I'd be I'd be thrilled if they did it.
I'd be so excited.
Oh, no, they spent 10 billion on that.
Yeah. Coronavirus took so much from us,
including whatever Quibi had planned for Comic Con.
Oh, no. Activations. Activations.
Taking it. You get your picture taken with with Anna Kendrick's dummy.
The dummy. Yeah.
They wanted it.
So, hey, wait, as for us.
Oh, we got to get the passport stamped, clunk.
And unless you guys see it differently than I do, I think.
No, you know, I think it's exactly how you see it.
I think, you know what it is.
I think that it is
Alf clearly ready to have the song of the summer
because he's got Cardi B's whap hair.
Oh, yeah. I think that's right.
That's exactly what I see.
That's a that's a wonderful official stamp for the nation of Germany to put out.
And we're heading to our last destination, which may not be far.
There's the there's the hint there.
So one more of these little things to go and podcast the rides.
European vacation that'll be on the main feed in a couple of days.
So go check that out and follow our progress and whatever on Twitter,
on Facebook and on Instagram.
Closing words, fellas.
Hum.
Just more elf, I guess.
And more gremlins, but more. Yeah.
More elf.
Be like Germany theme park world and give us more elf.
Make the whole world a project elf. All right.
It's very interesting to talk to you in a couple of days.