FOREVER!
DOG!
Welcome in to the final podcast the ride European vacation a podcast hosted by three alfs
I'm alf number one Scott Gardner joined by alf number two Mike Carlson
Hello, I am alf number two Mike Carlson and numbers love three days ago. Oh, no, sorry
Say what you want to say alf. I don't know. I was gonna ramble, you know, and then I was deciding that I really I should have said
Hey, it's alf number two or something. Which I should have I guess we all should have had the impressions in the pocket
Yeah, Jason. It's up to you what you want to do alf number three. Oh, hey, it's alf number three
Sounds good to me. I just did that to follow up on something that we said we were gonna do
In an episode over on the second gate if you haven't been following the the side episodes
This is the the side excursions
We did a really fun episode came out a couple days ago about the alf and gremlins ride
Did that with Joan Ford and that was a lot of fun. I guess we determined that
We are all more like alf and we are like gremlins. Yeah
Yeah, that was what we we are all more alf. Yeah, we feel we relate more to alf than the gremlins
We're not as crazy as the gremlins are but we're very low-key like alf is and sardonic. I would say
casual like sandwiches and
Hawaiian shirts
I mean, it's truly it's not even that much of a joke
No, not really accurate. It's not even if you okay, please go check out the episode
But if you're looking for a great runner around that point, I can't promise you that
I just wanted to make good on something we said we would do. I appreciate that
But yeah, I'd say it's barely a joke. Let's be honest. No, no, we're just you want to hear further
Elaboration of why we're more like alf and also to hear about a crazy ride
That thing is nuts. I'm glad we got to talk about it. But today we stay in the Western
Germany
Area, we just go a little bit south down to a very delightful place called Fantasia land
I would have my knee-jerk would have been to say Fantasia land, but I found a
fantastic
1891 video that takes you around the park that's hosted by a frightening orange monkey
I don't know if you guys met this right I did and is this an original character to that video or is there a
Fantasia land original character like I
Mean there are original characters and I I definitely definitely kept stumbling upon them. I didn't see him in any other
Context but he was oddly upgraded to being the host of this video
Really kind of a shoddy puppeteering job for being your host
I got a lot of my content out of this video and I recommend it
we'll post a link somewhere, but
Yes from that video. I found a song that taught me that it is not Fantasia land, but rather fun
Taz your land fontaz your land
Yeah, I really liked the song and I like the place a lot
You
How do you guys any overall before we get into it thoughts on Fantasia land?
Is it is it possible for reality itself to be oversaturated like reality to be HDR because this
This park is so there's so much detail
In what I have seen of this park in such a compact space, too
It's it's overwhelming
Like this this this park strikes me as like
It is weird. It is weird like some of the earlier ones we did but it is very full of substance
Like it feels very good
Yeah, yes, it feels it feels like just from looking at the website now the website
I think is probably the best website of any of the parks
We've examined through this European trip as far as making you go. This is a real place. This looks like it's a real
Destination but I will say the website even hides the mystery in the magic. I
Would say yeah, that's kind of true
We were talking about things that we discovered along the way that they did not put front and center as here's big things in this
Park almost as if they were trying to shove them into the basement like they were embarrassed of them and they should not be
Yeah, so I don't know what their rationale was for doing that
But when you look at the website always looks like pleasant and there's some roller coasters
But then you start going through the YouTube videos and you go. Oh they have this is some weird robot shit
This is they have it they really do I
I don't think that this is so much the case in
2020 but I think that there was a sweet spot in this park
Maybe in the early 90s, maybe if you went, you know in the right Venn diagram of a lot of these rides
I think you could have gone there in like 1992 and seen over 500 robots. I really think that is accurate
Which might be I think certainly there have been Disney parks with less robots than that
So you you really got to give him credit? Yes
And there's still there are still some robots. So am I totally wrong? Oh, no, they're definitely
There's an insane amount
In like 90s point in time, yeah, I think there was like tons of like pirates level
There's so many I know trying and shows as well
But my overall thought about this place
I think it's a it's a great place to be ending the European trip because I if I had to take a guess
Before we really looked into any of these places if we're gonna do a month full of Europe episodes. I thought we would find some
surprisingly charming
Parks full of oddities that reflect the European culture and spirit and I also thought we would find lots of weird shady
rip-offs of American rides and I and with Italy it was mostly the latter category
And then you know a lot of odd charm
I think in Popeye Village and Chessington and Pato and I think Fantasia land is the perfect blend of all of it
It's it's everything I thought we would find in Europe. Yeah, that's definitely some rip-offs here
Yeah, and still yeah, it's expensive rip-offs, but newer rip-offs as well in the last ten years
I found yeah, they're still in the in the rip-off game
Definitely though also some rides that I think predated
Rides we have in America
and and I also like
We'll view this on a case-by-case basis, and I don't want to put my views on to you guys
But I think whereas the movie but Park Italy
I think the
Fake Universal
Feeling it just it almost like made me a little mad in its
Exploitation it's just the brazenness of the rip-off and I I still like it
I would like to go there, but there's it doesn't feel as I don't know
It doesn't feel as exploitative the ripping off here. It just feels like I don't know we like these rides
It feels like if your dad and your uncle tried to build a pirates or a haunted mansion for you
Yeah, with with every bit of sweet intention that you could imagine
This is like you know when the Beatles do sergeant peppers
And then the Rolling Stones do that album where they're like wizards on the cover
And it's clear that they're like oh we want to do something weird, too
But you know they're talented as well
How could you be upset with
Another talented group of people doing a weird thing clearly influenced by the other set
Yes, yeah, you know they're hopping on a trend you know the basis, but but it's not just I
Think they might admit it they might admit we were inspired by this whereas the the modus operandi
In that Italy Park seemed like what are you talking about Universal Studios never heard of it?
Yeah, there's a different vibe, and there's a different. There's a craft at least to this
From like when I mean like King Kong is in fun Taz or was in Fantasia land
Still is still is yeah, I am cloudy on what's still there in places
I think I mostly know but I might get one wrong as we go okay. They have a map on their website, which is not
unlike the German stereotype the
Some of the stuff on the website is not very efficient like it's very detailed
There's a lot of layers to it
But yeah a lot of it is hidden and probably by this maybe by design to keep some mystery although even the Wikipedia
Page is not very thorough like it leaves out some big
attractions
Which they've yeah, they've had this this place feels a little more to me like a Disneyland or a Magic Kingdom where there's tons of
Little oddities everywhere it feels like a park of I could be wrong
Like 30 attractions where if you look to the website they kind of only feature the top five
Yeah, yes, I'm wondering. I mean we really again. We should really do our research
We should try to talk to PR. You know we should say what's your philosophy here behind this, but we don't do that yet
We're still a small operation, but I am so I am interested if that's part of the mission like let the wonder be
Experienced when you get here
Don't give it all away for free
Sure sure
well
Basics what do we know?
This this park was opened in 1967
There's two people were behind it one of them. I don't have the name handy
but another one was Richard Schmidt who was apparently a
prolific producer of puppet shows on German television, and I think his idea was very
In the spirit of what Disneyland was gonna be before it it evolved and grew
Where he wanted to house his puppet collection somewhere?
Yeah, and then also have some carnival rides or merry-go-round or something and you know a nice little afternoon place
For for European and German families, and it grew a lot
I think especially in the 80s it seems like this place had a boom which obviously increases its appeal to me
I think there feels like an inherent 80s-ness to it. You can really tell that's that's where it's it grew big time and came
Of it, so it was yeah, so he started it basically just as a puppet puppet storage area
puppet garage
Does don't is Jeff Dunham have a puppet garage oh
Man like J with cars obviously
I mean hit that theme park also if anybody has enough IP to
make a theme park out of I feel like if he
Took over the parking lot of the Venetian or wherever the hell he does Vegas shows
Oh my god did a little shady mini is this it's clearly a tradition. We know Richard Schmidt did it and
Sid Marty Croft did it for several months in Atlanta. Yeah, where's if if Dunham?
Like weird independent puppeteers have to try to do weird shady theme parks. Yes, don't um yeah up we have ideas
We'll help you out with this Dunham fader. You know oh, yeah
Terry's got a massive the chunk of is it treasure island or mirage
He has a giant theater. He has the Terry fader theater. It's the Terry fader theater
Yeah, yeah, so where's fader land?
Where's fader land and why is it people even know who Terry fader is offhand?
He's like one of the more generic looking
people who you would see
gigantic posters have in Las Vegas there are about
Thirty to fifty I feel like maybe this is a little high but thirty to fifty
Names that you would go to Vegas and go oh these are the biggest stars in the world
Because you see their posters so often and they all probably make
Twenty million dollars or more a year
They're all probably very rich Terry fader on that list
My newest my newest favorite is tape face. Oh
Tape face yeah the Australian
Prevords artist yes tape faces all everywhere
Yes
He said Harris heard of tape face. You call yourself a Vegas enthusiast
You don't know who tape face is I am shocked that I've missed to this. He's a Harris guy
New Zealand it's like a
Kind of silent comedy show or like he doesn't talk but he puts tape on his face and stuff
Never seen him. He might be he might be fantastic
I don't know I'm excited to see him whenever we're allowed to go back
Well, I guess we can go back now, but I don't think tape face is running shows not a lot running right now
Yeah, that was an early quarreled activity for me because I had been in Vegas not too long before
but when everything first locked down I was like
Hmm who who was sent best wishes to everyone has tape face yes tape face has said everyone stay safe
Well when you said activity I thought you were were you putting a bunch of tape on your face
Yeah, I was trying to putting tape on my face
I was making like alcohol slushies with a teaspoon of alcohol in them
Do you I do you think with the right
Positioning of tape on your face could that supplant a mask? Oh, that's good question if it's the right kind of tape
I do think that would probably be pretty effective. It also might be a
Effective at blocking any air coming in that might actually be the situation that the conservatives pretend
Is happening with a mask where it's restricting your airflow?
There's no way you're gonna pass out because you're being deprived of oxygen
Tape face actually would have that problem. He would have that problem
Yeah, the conservatives got an early peek at the Batman trailer where the Riddler is to keep the guys face up
This is what they're doing to us. It's like they're kidnapping us. Yeah, put tape on our face. We're all forced tape faces
We're all at the mercy of Dan Oh's the left are all Dan Oh's Dan Oh's world data
My
Last thought before we go right back to Germany is that what if tape face and bucket head teamed up?
Oh, could you imagine kid you could you imagine and his bucket?
Let's say is the bucket a good mask is the KFC bucket if you pulled it all the way down over your head?
Because he has a mask as well and a bucket
But maybe that's also effective
He has a witty as a mask too. Yeah, he has kind of like a weird Halloween
Blank like I forget what you call those. Yeah, Jabbawocke kind of yeah, Jabbawocke masks
I think hmm. I'd say maybe that more than the bucket
I'm concerned about the bottom of the bucket like it's the same thing as bandanas
I write we aren't covering that chin area, right?
So it's what's it's actually weird when you add it up how many masks there are in Vegas entertainer world. So who who needs
Extra masks the least is it the Jabbawocke's?
One of these guys maybe Terry fader has a routine where that's very disturbing. I think where they like
Force a person to be a living
Marionette
Like they'll get like dad from the audience and then like make him be a lady and
I
Feel like that's maybe a fully enveloping
Mask situation. So if Terry fader turns you into a lady puppet, then you don't need an extra mask. Okay
That's good to know
All right back to back to
fantaisie land, I
Also, just want to say this is in
An area that I'm very fond of because I lived here. I studied abroad in this neck of the woods
It's kind of between
Cologne and Bonn in
Germany, I lived in Dusseldorf. I studied abroad
There and my girlfriend at the time lived in Bonn and Cologne was a major city right in the middle so I did this
North South trip many many times. I really loved it around there loved living there for a while and
The only thing now is that I'm baffled why I did not ever learn about
Fantasia land why did nobody tell me it was as I've said the least theme parkie and therefore most regrettable
Time of my life, but I had plenty of opportunity to go to Fantasia land
I died I lived that I had so many days for you. I don't know why I didn't do it and I'm upset
You didn't even know was there
No idea. No Wow
Yeah, that's we all look life is full of regrets
And some of them will take to our deathbed and will never be able to make up for them
so
Maybe this is just one of them and you'll have to just learn to live with it
I mean I could still go to Fantasia land today, but I think there are rides that I missed that are closed
forever
I mean, I think that might have been my opportunity to go on Galaxy or on
I think race for Atlantis was still open and now I'll never be I I was in Vegas and the Star Trek thing was
Still going and I didn't do it soon
It's a tragedy because I love Star Trek and the whole thing looks all it looked awesome
I could have drank a quarks bar and I will regret it for the for as long as I live
Did every did everybody bail on theme parks in your college years? Is this consistent between the three of us? Well?
You know my quote-unquote study abroad was I did a semester in Los Angeles
So I went to theme parks a lot
To the point where my peers I think were concerned
How many times I went to Disneyland and Universal so that was interning issue on the universal lot
So could pretty much get in free, but it got in the that was the time of like by a day get the year for free
So like I was only there for three months
But I could go whatever I wanted and I I lived down the street like I lived around the corner from universal
So is this where you get your love of California Adventure 1.0?
Probably yeah, I mean I that was like I did right before I
went back east and
We did I remember like just being baffled by it because we did it in like before lunch
We had done most of the attractions before noon
So like you're in you're freshly in Los Angeles and Anaheim
You're young and the world is ahead of you and anything is possible
You didn't know what?
Horror show Los Angeles would eventually turn out to be
And you're you're seeing the the the Sun when you come into Disney's California Adventure
You're like this is the greatest place I've ever been
You know I there was there was a lot of like MGM like
Photocopied signage essentially in the Hollywood part that was very comforting to me
Wow
Yeah, I understand our show assessment is a little odd to me that was do you mean just like this year?
Or did you consider it a horror show being in Los Angeles? Yeah. Yeah. No, I look I
Make a bit of fun. It was it hasn't been that bad. There's a lot of good stuff about it. Yeah
I love Los Angeles amazing city
But it certainly takes a couple of years to get used to and there's some real weirdness like every now
And I'm very good. I can spot it immediately where it's like someone it's like, uh, someone's yelling at a car
It's like up. There's a horse running down the street. No one around like these those little moments of Los Angeles weirdness
Know what you're talking about. What are you seeing a horse running a horse running down the street alone?
Yeah, yes
Well, I saw someone okay in the this is Burbank actually that I guess weirdness of Los Angeles County
I was cutting by the equestrian area in Burbank and
someone had clearly just gotten a runaway horse under control and
Then as I was driving down the street
I saw a German Shepherd walking in the lane in front of me and I'd like
Had I was like fought like trying to get this
Protect this dog and like a bunch of other people were to just a day in LA, you know
Was dr. Doolittle in town?
I think what had happened is someone's course got out of control and then their dog ran away
So they had to get them back one after the other which did happen, right?
But this doesn't seem like any way to encapsulate your
The experience of Los Angeles in general. This seems like one thing that happened
Okay, how about the other time where I got off the subway and Hollywood and a man in a trench coat?
But no shirt on lunged at me and yelled. I can't be alone anymore
Jesus
Yeah
What do you think happened I think he just wanted a friend but it wasn't gonna be me
The next guy probably
Yeah
I'm glad he didn't show up after the horse and the dog
You again
He was riding on the horse
So anyways, yeah, I'm upset I missed upset I missed Fonthaziland
and
I don't know. I mean, I'm not sure where to get into it. I mean
I it really is just
There's there's an odd amount of attractions that just have a lot of
interesting odd culture to him
I mean like what one that might bear talking about right at the beginning
Good solid attractions is Taron this this roller coaster that went in in 2016
This came up on the show before because I threw it in as kind of a
Could this possibly make it into the fake rock?
Final four because I think the rock work is pretty strong on it
It didn't make it into the into the competition to 16, but if you google it, it looks
fantastic
This I feel is a ride that is absolutely
This I feel is a ride that is absolutely Disney and universal quality
It's a multi-launch roller coaster the fastest and longest multi-launch coaster at least when it opens that that might be Hagrid's now
But I mean this this ride seems legitimately fantastic
Yeah, it seems like I don't know if it seems like yeah
like a mix of like Hagrid's and Big Thunder or something like that where it's like it's not a
It's like not a ton of
Like I guess theming other than just like the mountains or the whatever you'd call these yeah, would they would they what are these things?
Are they?
My just rocks
Still it's an old Norse village is what it is. So is it is it kind of?
He has a cliff walls or
They aren't man-made right? I don't think so
I mean, I'm sure people are yelling if they know what this is. Yeah cliff walls might be right
Let's say cliff walls. I like that son of that
Yeah, but it's very much like
It's very much like you kind of puts it's enough stuff to make you feel like you're in a different spot
In addition to obviously what is a very cool thrill element with multi launches
Yeah, yeah, they have a lot of pretty sizable coasters here from like the big
coaster manufacturer B&M and they come a
Welcome I don't know how to say it Intamin
And they all seem to have very nice sets like yeah really puts to shame the American like
Yeah, put the steel pylons up and put a bunch of gravel underneath like just really make some of our American coasters
Look like shit. This is what yeah
This is what like a six flags either doesn't understand or doesn't give a shit about and it's probably the latter. It's like
Looking at this I don't think this costs as much as cars land costs or something like that
I'm sure it's a little more expensive than a regular coaster because you're putting up different little pieces of rock and stuff
But it makes so much difference
It's so different gives you a vibe and it makes you able to
Separate this from other coasters in your head
you know, this is the one with the rocks and the the rooftop and the the Norse theme and and it's
Yeah, a little a little more of it a little transformative experience
Yeah, and it makes like it makes it probably like 25 to 50 percent better of an experience
Like it is interesting like see a six flags is just like yeah, you're gonna get to see Valencia
When you get to the top, that's what you're gonna see
You're gonna see the see your car sometimes like make sure it hasn't been broken into you're gonna see your car plugged into a service
trailer
charging
Like mine was regular extension cord just an orange Home Depot extension cord
I'll see teens trying to steal the hubcaps off the car and you'll be able to shout at them, which is fun
Hey, hey, don't you the white car specifically, please don't
They look up
Give you the finger keep doing what they're doing. We talked a little bit of from Alton Towers the Wicker Man coaster
And it's another one where like obviously that's a big impressive thing
But it's not like it's some crazy ass robot
it's just like this big cool looking structure that gives it a vibe and it would be really nice if
Six-flags and other parks were just to like just put a little dressing a little set dressing. It goes a long way
Yeah, and just a theme just to let you know a little like hint of
This is kind of a ride where you go into the Old West or into Medieval times or whatever it like
Yeah, like the like the Riddler's Revenge coaster. It's like I like that coaster
I did it but like give us some of that Gotham that Batman forever
Architecture where like think like a big statue is holding the observatory up like this is your second
I think of the way no, it's I'm making Batman forever content
and I mean this I think is just your particular hang up is I
Love Batman forever. I meant forever land. I love Batman forever so much
And that this is one of those movies were like if if people were like would you are you interested in watching new movies?
Or would you just like to watch Batman forever all the time? I would say oh Batman forever. I think
Like I like if I had to choose never seeing Batman forever again or new movies
I might go Batman forever, and I'm very excited at the idea that there's a three-hour cut of Batman forever
That was just talked about that sitting, you know, yes, there's a there's possibly a full Schumacher
Three-hour cut of Batman forever that puts back in this deleted scenes where there's a giant practical bat that's haunting Val Kilmer
It's a much darker movie apparently that then those scenes are on YouTube. Oh
Okay, but yes this this this Taron released the Schumacher cut
Yeah, maybe that three-hour cut finally get some Leonard Cohen songs in there so we know
To take this seriously
Mm-hmm, I don't hear a sad song. I don't know whether this is a film or not
I mean kiss from a rose seal is
Seal is my Leonard Cohen
Taron
Also as Jason as you said really like all the legit all the best coaster makers have done something in
Phantasialand and this this one's by Intamin who later several years later built the Hagrid's coaster
And it's similar in a lot of ways it does
It's not the same level of you stop and do a little scene
There's no robots or anything, but it it feels a lot like
Hagrid's in that there's like there's kind of a downbeat and then you super speed up
They just do a little bit with lighting and fog and that kind of thing
But they I don't know this feels to me like
If you like the vibe of Hagrid's and you want more of it and maybe a more intense one because this one goes 72
Miles an hour I'd really like to go on this ride
But this would be more than pushing the amount of launch that I can be a queen of what is yeah
What is the speed of Hagrid's do you know offhand?
I don't know if I have that down
Like sounds like I think 55. Yeah, if rock and roller coaster is
That that's the fastest that I've done and that gets up to 57
So this would be intense, but it seems fun as hell it seems really really great
Yeah, and it looks like that like smooth fun crazy like as long as stuff is smooth. I can go pretty fast. I think
I'm with you. Yeah. Yeah, I can't be I can't be shaken. I can't be feeling individual nails
Other awesome coasters there's something called black Mamba
Which I've seen described as the best inverted coaster in the world
It has 10 near misses there are 10 parts of the ride where if you're staring straight ahead
You feel like you're gonna slam into a wall or something and presumably you do not
Yeah, that sounds cool to his black Mamba the one that lifts you up into a building
So cuz maybe I'm not sure a couple of these go through buildings or tunnels and
Aesthetically like it's not like there's show scenes in it
But it does add like an interesting like oh, it's dark and then the next turn is a total surprise
But I feel like I kept seeing and passing that some of the designs of these coasters
The buildings or the walls act as sound dampeners because there are residences very close to this park
Yeah, extremely. It's in the town of Brule, which is pretty
Suburban like it I think this park was like a big boon to that city. Yeah, it seems very sleepy
Around there and yeah odd that there would be lots of coasters right next to homes
I think that really impacted
the ride
mystery castle
Which also seems like I guess in keeping with the rides
We've been talking about it seems like it's it's the bones of a ride, you know, very well
It's a drop tower, but in order to dampen screams, they do it inside
So it's and they and it's not all tower. It's not all riders around the same tower
They're like you're up against the wall. There's four walls and you know four separate, you know drops on either on all the sides
With a little bit of effects like there's lightning up at the top and you know
Kind of some music and some plottiness and the tower itself looks really scary from the outside
It looks like a prison or something
This seems great. It's like it's a ride that you know, but with 20% more effort in theming. It seems really cool
Yeah, almost the setup to dr. Doom's fearfall of like a pod my experiments, you know
Uh-huh, but we just yeah with a lot of inside neon or fake Tesla coil kind of thing and it a little bit goes a long way
That's the lesson for this park and for theming in general a little bit goes a long way
You don't have to go nuts, but I'm glad for times when they do
I guess in terms of
if we start transitioning from hey, that's a good amount of theming to
potentially confusing
theming
I one of the big headlines about fontazi land is a ride called Colorado Adventure
I'm feeling this is their direction you were going yeah
Colorado Adventure is a
Mine train type coaster. It's like Big Thunder. It's it's steel. So you're in a train and it's a madcap train adventure with some
Fake rocks. That's good
We understand what this is
but
After it opened and up until 2013
This ride was called Colorado Adventure the Michael Jackson thrill ride
Yes, I mean is this let me ask you this Scott. Is this why we're doing this park
It helps it really helps I mean hard for me to stay away from something
Something is that contains the Michael Jackson thrill ride that when when I first just saw the first two layers of the website and
And was on the second thing I looked at was Colorado Adventure I
Immediately was like is this all this park has because the website is such a smokescreen
Like like wait are we doing this because we're gonna talk about Colorado Adventure for half an hour
Nothing, but Colorado Adventure. I mean the thing is there's not a ton to talk about there is it with it
And I was because I was disappointed. I feel like I might have heard about this years ago
Oh really they named a ride after Michael. Okay, so then does he do the the pre-show video?
Or is it set to a Michael Jackson song?
No, none of this the theming is that it says the word Michael Jackson on the outside
And then otherwise is an old west thing. It's not even like there's stars or
Glitter like would be on his glove. It has absolutely nothing to do with Michael Jackson. Did you investigate?
I mean, I mean I know there's footage of him on the ride
Is this something where he just was on the ride one day and said I want I want it
I want to be on this ride. No, he was there
Didn't he oh did they not change the name at some point?
Do I have this wrong? Did it open as the Michael Jackson? I think well now I think it's they've dropped that but I
Think that was the opening. Yeah, that was the opening in the marketing for years
Yeah, and and by
It's a curious marketing strategy because you look at the sign and it's very not very far
I'm just imagine, you know
kind of rustic wooden sign for your roller coaster as this Colorado venture and then
Just kind of pasted on letters the Michael Jackson thrill ride the M looks bad
The M kind of looks like an N so it's a little crooked and it looks like Nikol Jackson
to me this feels like
They heard he was coming and threw it up really quickly to make him happy
Dirty get like get old Gus up there to
Bang some letters onto that sign. There are so many different like legends and confirmed stories of
like meetings Michael Jackson took like in the 90s and probably early 2000s like
Michael Jackson was gonna buy Marvel Comics. He had a meeting with Stan Lee and I just read Michael Jackson met with Laura Shuler Donner
To try to be professor X in the X-Men movie
Yes
That's in the big singer article. I think yes, that's true. Yes
So I wonder if this is just a weird meeting he had that actually
Like bore fruit like it was just like yeah
Whatever you want, I guess because it seems like most of these meetings are people leave confused exactly what Michael is looking for
Hey like anytime you read it's like yeah, he he was he thought that he could just
Like star in the men in black to movie was that right?
Like did he think he was gonna have a much bigger part
Did he think like agent M was gonna be the the climax of the film?
I think it was like is he gonna have his like name on the poster
Will he be in sequels like it just seems like any meeting he had people just left confused
And is this the one meeting where he was like, yeah, I want to have a ride and it's a choo-choo train and they were like
Okay, and then like that was done
Like this was the only weird meeting he had that worked and some really severe
Efficient German guy just said just put his name on the sign, right? It doesn't need to be more than that, right?
You're overthinking it. You got her to get it up in the next hour
He didn't develop it
Yeah, the footage of him riding it is very confusing because he has the hat he is like the
The moonwalker hat and then everyone else in the car
The train has clearly been given cowboy hats which they're waving like you do when you're like
Riding a horse or on a bucking bronco, you know that sort of thing
But he it looks like he just has his like the hat you associate with him and he's wearing it going up the lift hill
And then he takes it off and he holds it for a while
And then he tries to put it back on as the coasters picking up speed
He realized he has to hold it and it's just a lot of him taking the hat on it off
And then everyone else never tries to put their hat on they're like these are props and we're waving it is very confusing
Mm-hmm. Yes, did he not have object permanence? Does he did he not understand how things worked?
Well, I think we know for sure
Know how things know how things work. I think that is a hundred percent confirmed. Sure. Yes. Well, he thought he could you know
show his baby to a
Bunch of people outside his hotel without the baby tumbling seven stories to its death. Yes
He so he might not know hats fine
My question though is once they took his name off of it
Why didn't they replace it with another famous German celebrity like David Hasselhoff or elf?
Oh, yeah, yeah, this ride is just yet thrown to the gutter
Unbranded it's just some ordinary ride now who cares?
I don't know
Is there even a way is Foss Bender?
German I forget where he's from. I like that pronunciation is everyone just call some fast Bender, but you're right
If it is if he is it's obviously people don't say Foss. I don't think I've actually heard fast
But it's probably my correct pronunciation. Yeah, but it's all these American fast fast banner
That's how I say I'm assuming it's like Fantasia land
If he ever wanted to just brand this place entirely
Foss Bender land false false badder just rethemed everything after his films
Get all Prometheus. Oh, yeah
I
Yeah, I don't know
Yeah, this ride is now there's no owner
That's the thing I saw it one justification that people said this ride had been adopted by Michael Jackson
I don't like the sound of that
No, I can't say I do
The dream of anything being adopted by Michael Jackson, yeah
There's a
There's got to be a good story
About this coming together that we I don't know if maybe it's impossible to find maybe there's like one old man who worked for the company
That's like
85 and we have to like journey to Germany to meet him to learn what happened
But there's got to be some interesting weird story behind this somebody has it. Yeah, it's it's not public
It just makes no sense. They and they
Stopped calling it that in 2013 which implies that this was not a cancellation
This is not like they recently stripped it of the Michael Jackson's name. Did they just think like oh wait, he died
He's not coming back. Let's just we can take this confusing thing off now, can't we?
It's very possible. Yeah
But this isn't the only
celebrity tie-in to this park because
some friends of
Michael Jackson are also very associated with it
Who also have you know a lot of a lot of flair and sparkles and I refer of course to Siegfried and Roy
big Siegfried and Roy
presence over the years at this park
in 1987
For the 20th anniversary Siegfried and Roy started a tiger breeding program at Fontasia land
They basically recreated their setup at the Mirage like it like those the same
tiger
Territory same tiger tank. I don't know the phrase
Probably tiger tank. I prefer a tiger tank in your tank, you know
But yeah, they I don't know the super interesting to be around a lot around this time
There's no one more suited to be in a park called Fantasia land than Siegfried and Roy
Yeah, yeah big time and
Over the course of discovering that I found an odd little
rabbit hole
And I can't believe this rabbit hole in particular keeps going
So I was on a website that was in German
So I didn't understand the bulk of it, but there would be it was the timeline of the history of
Fantasia land and there was you know big keywords
Here's what we did this year, you know, just Millennium for 2000
And I kind of gave me the gist of what happened when and for when this happened in 1987
The timeline said in big golden letters
Sar modi
You guys know the word. Whoa, Sar modi
Audience if you didn't follow us over to the second gate
We did an episode where we watched every episode of the terrible series father of the pride the
Dreamworks animated series based on Siegfried and Roy and that had a character named
Sar modi played by Karl Reiner
RIP Roy Horn RIP
Also, we didn't do that episode very long ago and both Roy Horn and the voice of Sar modi Karl Reiner have sadly passed away
So
Yeah, Sar modi
Related to Fantasia land and I jumped out of my chair like oh no this word
Because also if you didn't hear that episode Sar modi is an incredibly unpleasant character all of the many
Homophobic moments in the series come out of Sar modi's mouth
So I was a little unnerved to see Sar modi's name again and I thought well did they breed a
Tiger here named Sar modi. What's the deal?
Why am I seeing this word again?
And then I found something that I can't believe the three of us didn't find in our previous father of the pride research
Do you guys know that Sar modi is an acronym? No, what?
Do you know what it can now just picture it in your mind?
And you guess what it what it might stand for at least what part of it might stand for?
Siegfried and Roy
Yep, you got it master
Masters of the
Impossible that's it
Modi means
Siegfried and Roy masters of the impossible whoa this you guys was their magic word
We don't know about Siegfried and Roy to have realized that they didn't say abracadabra. They said Sar modi. Oh my god
We look like such fools
We just left that hand there's one listener
This has been gnawing at them and they were hoping that the day would come where we would be shamed and that has happened
All of a sudden as if magic Sar modi we have been shamed. Oh my god
I mean we I I have not felt so embarrassed doing this that we don't know that much about Siegfried and Roy a topic
We should be experts on
Yeah, yeah, all three of us missed it and not only that that's not the only way that Sar modi has reared its head
In Siegfried and Roy world, it's not even the last time Sar modi has come up in an animated way
Oh my god guys turn your attention to
the shared screen on zoom
Where I'm horrified to say that there was another
Siegfried and Roy animated series this I was cold
Okay, okay, you did find this before her
No, I just it's all coming back to me from childhood
No, I didn't talk I don't think I've talked about this on the show
But go ahead. Yeah
This show is called the full thing. What's our modi means Siegfried and Roy masters of the impossible. Here's a little scene
The dust demons are swept from the hearth and the kindlings been set a place the mages sit by the fire
and recall a once magic world called
Sar modi a place of fairy queens and wishing wells of unicorns dragons potions and spells
so Sar modi is also
the magical kingdom that they
Protect and by the way in this series Siegfried and Roy are jacked
They all have they're like they seem like they're six foot seven and have very broad shoulders
They all look they both look essentially like
Batman the animated series like the proportions of that Bruce Wayne slash Batman that cartoon way better
Yeah, yes. Yes, only four episodes well way less successful oddly
Siegfried and Roy animated series, but there's two one sir Modi is their magical land and in the other one sir Modi is a
old cranky tiger who hates gay tigers
Yeah, I think the first one's better. I think the first series is better. Yeah. Wow, I gotta see that
What is the if you had to put a percentage on your individual desires to watch?
Every episode of this Siegfried and Roy animated show. What would your percentage be?
Rewatch in my case because I think I watched every episode I
I think that show was one of the ones so in like the the golden era of Saturday
I don't know if it's a golden era might be the Bronze Age
but like Saturday morning cartoons when we were kids were like Fox and the WB and even like
ABC NBC CBS we're starting to get in the game
They would usually start around 8 a.m. 9 a.m
But then there would be weird syndicated ones that like 7 a.m. And I think that's where it got
Dropped it felt kind of European that felt yeah
I would do like not me or it was a joint production with England or France or something
Well, there was and there was a lot of fantasy kind of whether there was a Pirates one. There was a Sinbad one
the Sinbad the sailor
And and I think because you know those are in the public domain. You just do whatever you want with pirates
It's in bad, you know, right, right
Well, what how much does anybody want to watch all the episodes of this?
Yeah, we did I would I would do this I would do it because it's everybody's over 50% I'm at like
4% I think you said four episodes and it feels like it's right in the sweet spot of when we were kids which makes me more
attracted to it
Like it's just a ripoff of an action show from the early 90s
Sure. Sure. So I'm I don't know. Oh
Well, I would watch one for sure and then I my percentage could change
Yeah, they would judge it judge it off of the pilot. Sure
It'd be less punishing either way. Yes, thanks to me. Yeah the other one
so
Anyway, yeah Siegfried and Roy they were there. They were in the park a lot seemingly
along with a guy named Hino I
Guess if you're if you're German or
If you grew up in Germany, I'm sure you know who Hino is I did I didn't previously
he's like a he's a blonde dude with perennial sunglasses and I
Don't know like the most one of the most successful German musicians of all time. All I know is when I looked up
Fantasia land on Getty editorial it see I think he was there once a month
I think I know had an apartment at Fantasia land. Was he the that perfume guy that was always an Epcot Center
You know wait, what's that again? What's that guy's name? Oh, right?
Yeah, I got a look at people are yelling right now because he's always there
The your way, I mean gear net gear Ness. Thank you, Jason
The Norwegian fragrance man. Yeah. Yeah, he's like always he's like signing once a day
He's like number one there Mickey Thomas is in Epcot probably the second most out of the year from
Starship
Do they all get their own episodes then I guess
I think people would be very excited about the gear Weiss episode if you're a weird world showcase
Person I think for sure
I
And one thing maybe this maybe I can kick it over to Jason with this. I do know that
while Roy was still relatively with it that they
They went I believe to the premiere of this big dinner show that is a a tentpole
Event that's a must-see at Fantasia land and we were arguing about the pronunciation
Now I don't remember the name at all. Would you like to give it a go?
I think I saw it read as
This is a dinner show, right
Fantasima
fan yeah
Fantasium fun to I would guess fantastic. Oh, but it's spelled F a n t
like not F a
pH a
NT like it
It's it's got the F. It doesn't have the pH
And it looks very
Weird it looks like the entertainment before an eyes wide shut sort of situation
like I
Don't know here. Let me screen share. I mean
if you have seen like the
If you have seen the guys can you see these guys these guys in blue
with the hands
Yeah, they look like in in pitch perfect to the bad guys the German bad guys from that
and then there's like like
Like computer guys like heisty guys have with goggles and stuff
These are just some of the seeds that you can see online
It looks like 15 different cults have gathered to each perform their own musical number
Like it's a there's a variety of different weird little numbers that are all creepy in their own way
Yeah, I don't understand how you get from one to the other those images you just showed
Seem like two completely different shows. I'd be very curious how they bridge it and some of it looks like
Thunder from Down Under some of it is just like jacked guys
Like mm-hmm dancing for you. It's it's interesting. It's a real variety show
I'll say from the look of it. You get a lot of different types. Yeah, you get your like
weird auto erotic asphyxiation Starlight Express
You get your hunks you get your like ribbon dancers you get your acrobats and you get a
Supposedly a decent dinner as well. It's a dinner show. Yeah
I
Was looking at so I'm showing the guy like two photos from this show
But there's like six more photos that again look very much like they're from totally different shows all in a row on this website
and
The other thing that that feels very like the European kind of weirdness
The other thing that's kind of weird on the website kind of related to this is some of the verbiage
Like did you guys come across celebrate?
Which is like the word celebrate but it's spelled CEL EBR colon
EAT
Celebrate and the location known as
Musartium the word museum with the word art shoved in the middle
There's so bad I can't believe they aren't going into Orange County
In a couple years or it's a late period Prince album
Use artium
Yeah, that sounds like it it's a it's 46 minutes of jazz art and oh well he doesn't sing once
artificial age
Which was a pretty good album honestly you late period no that's on the better end. Yeah. Yeah, he got out of the
The nose dive I think but it was rough around
97 or so third eye girl album not as good though
Hmm, but artificial age pretty good
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Can I read some reviews real quick please the show yeah? Yeah? Yeah?
So I mean I think this is actually a pretty popular show and then look just for the sake of comedy
I found some bad reviews because isn't this fun
I'm not trying to say it's a bad show
I'm just let's this I was amused by the way this person wrote so I translated this
It says this person's talking about going to the show approximately an hour before the show the actual auditorium which exudes the charm of an
Unrenovated train station and which also smells like that in some places of nicotine and urine to be precise
opens
With and then this is just a great
Translation with a little less with a little less luck you come across a kind of bouncer who asks for the table number and
Does not use any manners
Most bouncers should be friendlier
We had booked the second most expensive price category by telephone because the most expensive was already booked
Our table was at the maximum distance from the stage ie at the opposite end of the station hall as is typical for a train
Station it drew which I assume smelled like pike soup, and it smelled either of smoke or toilet
Pike soup me I don't know I don't know that's just
Yeah, that might be a but I like maybe it's like a
Because what's a pike is that like like a dock? I'm thinking of like see yeah, they're a pike place right?
Yeah, I know is it like
ground up
coffee beans ground up into a soup
Yeah, I I hope pike soup is real
I should really you know just google it and let's see if it's a translation or if it's just
Oddly the ultimate phrase in Germany pike soup is real
It's a real soup
Pike oh, it's like an edible soup. Oh, yeah, wait a day pike soup doesn't look too bad
Yeah, maybe pike soup is good, so it's either it either smells like pike soup smoke or toilet
This reminds me I didn't get the chance to bring this up on the Chesington episode
But I found a review of the hotels at Chesington is very complimentary
But it kept mentioning the detail that it's like came down here on a trip with my niece
And it just kept saying trip with my niece a lot and I was like that is I
Don't think I ever went on a trip with an aunt or uncle
Do you think that's actually what was happening or that person was like with a young girlfriend and they were trying to deflect?
That was like a smoke screen. Yeah
That's also
Yeah, it seems
Something seemed up. He was 55. He's dating a 23 year old. He's like it's my niece. This is my niece
It's my niece nothing weird
Just a 50 year old uncle and a 20 year old niece. That's right
Those ages are possible that's something that's sometimes the age separation and that's the case here with me and my niece
Did I mention my fun trip with my niece? Yeah, my niece
It's Europe he's going to the park announcing that to everybody
He's like yeah, we'll have the pasta. I'll have a pasta and then my niece over here. What will you have nice nice?
Would you explain your order to the waiter?
How many in your party? Well, let me see. It's me and my niece. So that'd be two
I guess that'd be two one two, right? Yeah, yeah, yeah, be two two is my niece who will be checking into the hotel
Yes, yes, my niece and I will be checking into the hotel. Isn't that right? Is that hey?
Let me just make sure my niece hears me. Hey niece
niece
See what she is she waved when she heard she responded she heard she waved and responded. So yes, a hundred percent nice
So just a separate beds separate beds one uncle one niece
You never sleep in the bed with your niece it's the uncle niece
Yeah, I got the uncle nice package at the hotel just wanted to make sure holiday. It's a short break a short break
short break for an uncle and a niece
I
Can I can I talk about some other shows
Run across and this is what I'm talking about that. I think these are I think a lot of these are gone now
but there was a time where I
think you could have seen hundreds and hundreds of of animatronics and
you know, maybe we'll start heading into the truly rip off the zone of
Phantasialand because they have a lot of things that are
Pretty country bear s pretty
Enchantique room s guess I videos where it is a bunch of flowers descending from the ceiling or like a
animatronic character on a swing
And I when all these were open at once. I mean, this is peak animatronic maybe
anywhere in the world
I'm just gonna flip through some for you guys
This was these guys were open maybe they were going maybe in the 70s. This is pretty old-school
The this is a family of there's a family monkey band there. They're called deep deep
My what I want to say climb bin ski and I say climb because maybe is it climb because they're
Monkeys and monkeys climb. Oh, that's a get wrong though. I'm not sure but yeah, we got a monkey banner like homemade instruments
It was banjo and accordion. I mean, this is really country bear s. Oh, yeah
If you keep going down, there's this other one. I think the name of this is La Scala
I could be wrong though, but here's some like
Showgirl gophers there's tons of animals in this show, but a lot of them are
Gophers and gophers with full
human female
proportions often very scantily clad kind of like it's this is in this case, they look very
You know Brazilian dancer, I guess big headdresses and kind of sparkly bras
You got kind of a Miss Piggy, but way taller in an elegant gown
Here you've got out there. He looks like another character, of course
The king yes, this is the king. We've talked about the it was he a rocker fire
Cast away somewhere in Chuck E. Cheese world. There is a an Elvis dog
Is this a dog he there's he like a mountain lion? What is he this character looks like a lion?
Yeah, I think
But anyway, these are these were all in the park at the same time and then let me show you one more of these
Sexy gophers. I don't I don't feel great about this one. This is very
Can-can like Mulan Rouge
Hey Velco
Here's what okay, so obviously we know now I'm completely comfortable with any kind of sexuality now
It's no you were at the end of the series
You've made the full transformation fully comfortable with every anything. We're almost anything
I will say though. Let me let me approach this from where I would have been a month ago
This half gopher half lady has like realistic skin
Yeah, very smooth. She's wearing furry like a bikini and she has a female human female body
with no fur
realistic skin
very like in a real like cabaret like kind of sexy pose and if I had
Hostile eggs you can't see in this current view
I know that she is wearing bottoms, but you can't see them in this in this view that I'm showing
And if I hadn't gone through all this character development, I would think this is creepy as hell
But but in but currently
I love it. I love that this sexy lady gopher is out there doing her thing
Celebrating herself and her body. I'm so comfortable with this now, but a month ago
I would say whoever built this has some issues
Would you?
So would you hit this?
Look
Would I if you're asking would I make love to this half gopher half woman?
Let me I'd really need to break this down from an exercise is this an actual just gopher or is this truly half woman half gopher?
You know what I'm saying like I think that might actually play into it because if it's like a
Woman with a little gopher then that's that seems perhaps ethical
But if it's just a gopher that's like sexy, I don't think I don't think that's him
I don't think that's ethical at all
Well, she's singing which is something that people can't do or perhaps already people can do I had a reverse people could certainly sing
Gophers typically cannot so her having the will to sing
Implies that she is more human and has more of a human brain because of like it's just like a lady who went to a dr
Moreau island and got a gopher face
Then I'm like, yeah, let's go. Let's hit the town like you'll you'll take a nice break
You'll take a short break with a niece with her, you know
This is just my gopher niece
my niece
This is just my niece who's a gopher lady
Very common a lot of people have nieces on people have nieces who are half gopher
Yeah, so I think I think we would have to fully understand what's going on here
But if it's a doctor island of dr. Moreau situation that I think I'm on board
So
you would need some kind of
What's the the 23 and me with like you need?
Ancestry DNA sort of thing to find out what percentage gopher is it some percentage?
It's at least five if this sexy gopher would swab her cheek and send it away
Then I could understand exactly what's going on here if she was for instance just a
Lady gopher a real gopher that was maybe like came in contact with some sort of wizard and the wizard changed the gopher just into
This giant lady version then it's no way
Absolutely not that is just a gopher that was enchanted by a wizard and I will not take this gopher on a date
That is if it was a wizard involvement. No way
I am this you're implying a scenario where
This gopher woman is I mean, I don't know this for sure
But it seems like this is gonna take a while to do all this stuff
It seems like she's willing to wait for you
Well, he's into you and she whatever it takes if this all plays out over three months if it means
Making sweet love to newly
Liberated the European Mike and it's worth it. Look I I appreciate her way
Waiting for me and I think she'll actually
Respects that I want to take the time to figure out what's going on here
so
This were all a monologue, you know boys to men kind of you know, like this would you you're laying out all the steps
girl
Let's I want to make love but first it's got to be right. Let me just get a swab girl
Let me get a swab of that girl. Let me see how much gopher you are
What's the percentage was there a mad scientist that worked on a lady and made her have a gopher face if that's the case
Then I'm in but I have to know for sure girl
I've been dreaming about you ever since I saw you sitting on a carousel horse in that German
Cabaret show. Oh, but here's the thing if a wizard was involved. I'm out no offense
We can have our fantasies, but we can't make them reality
if a wizard involved
Girl, you just took a DNA test turns out it's a hundred percent gopher. So that deal is off
100% that gopher
Go scurry away to your hole
You don't belong up here above the soil it was nice to meet you though. Well, I will always have the fantasy though
Here have some kibbles
Put some caterpillars in your hole for you. Have a nice day long. It's just about feeding caterpillars to a gopher
the
These strangest slow jam ever recorded
So you can see that there used to be able to
Yeah years ago. Um, do you guys have any?
any favorites
Legacy attractions stumbled across Oh legacy. Oh, okay
Well from any time well any just want Ozzy land favorites the one thing immediately that I'm
Excited about is mouse or shock a lot. Yeah
yeah
which is we I made reference to this, you know, this is a
Ripoff of the ride vehicle from Toy Story Midway Mania
It's the exact same
double-sided the way the
The little podiums whatever you want to call it the little front part and the little the weapon lower down on dia
There's a little ball and a pole on the back of it and you shoot at a 3d screen and instead of it
Just being these weird little cannons on Toy Story. It's like
What do you call these things the the frosting question?
They stress
Pastry bags full which I as a child I always was very fascinated and by these pastry bags
I would imagine Jason you as well
Mm-hmm. You can make them folks
You can make them real easy at home if you got ziploc bags
You just cut one of the corners off you got your own homemade pastry bag right there. Have you done it? I
Had to do it for like yeah with some school projects, I think
Hmm I did it cuz it was also a way to like do it he said or like decorative like
Paints and stuff the same idea. Yeah
So you kept it around at home you just you fill it up with frosting once a month and oh after school snack, too
You know those AP classes you need that sugar boost
This will this ride and I don't know I don't know if this is accurate reminded me of like Mouse Hunt the Nathan Lane movie
Yeah, they're like just because it's about mice but something about the sort of surreal
Aesthetic of it as well cuz like you the 3d
Film element is that you're shooting at like mice that are trying to eat sweets and
You fight them by squirting more chocolate at them, right?
Which seems like questionable like you would only enticing them to stay they want that chocolate
So the logic of this side they seem to just
From the events of the ride they seem to just fight back like it like Jason prepping for an AP test
It only makes them stronger, right?
The graphics not as good as Toy Story Midway mania. No
But there's a style to it and I don't hate I don't hate it. I don't think it looks horrible
It's fun
There's a very fun little pre-show with a CGI kind of eggy man with a curly q mustache
and then he transitions into live-action and
He's got a big fake Santa belly
So when he sits in the vehicle and tries to pull the thing down in front of him
He has a little bit of trouble has a little trouble squeezing in there. There's a lot of whim Z
There's like the office. There's the office section, which is fun
with like a
tired owner of the I
Guess is that what he is? Do you know I'm talking about?
Wait, what is is?
Is this a
Kitchen or a restaurant that's being taken over by these mice and is he the owner of that?
I think I think I don't know the specific
I think that's what's happening because he's in like an office and it's very like cluttered and he's very like he's you know
He's stressed out because of all the mice
And he's showing you how to work the
Frosting whatever I can already forgot the name of what is it frosting a street bag a street a street bag. Thank you
Yes, he's showing you to work your pastry bag
So I think yeah, this is great. This is I think great original yes
It's cheaper certainly than Midway mania, but it's it's definitely its own thing
They they figured out and
Though you might call it a ripoff
It would the ride vehicles were built by the same company as Midway mania
It's a Dutch company called ETF ride systems, so they
Betrayed Disney they went behind their backs and gave them the same
Vehicle they also were behind the mechanics of the actual ride vehicles not the creative but the vehicles
For one of the best rides in podcast thread history nights and white satin. Oh, right
Yeah, what a history for ETF ride system
It's interesting though like that Disney didn't have an exclusivity with this because I think that happens a lot and that happened with
Universal and the Harry Potter ride with the Kuka arm where they have that ride system
Exclusively for like ten years there's probably different terms of the agreement
So it is interesting maybe this was sort of developed even before Midway mania
And they kind of bought it off the shelf in a way
But it would seem that Disney would want to own something like this for a while
Because you wouldn't think that like week if we had a theme park or if you know Jeff Dunham or Terry fader wanted to do
Their own version they could have done it immediately in
2011 which is when I think this ride opened
2011 right right yeah, yeah, so pretty far after Ratatouille the movie Ratatouille
It's also about rodents in a restaurant
Mm-hmm. I mean it's not so far away from a to in 2011
Well so this is this kind of has the I was thinking how a lot of the rides here have little equations
and this is kind of
Midway mania plus Ratatouille, and there's a number of other ones that are similar where it is
This plus this I don't know if you want to throw in a multiplied by or divided by
Yeah, I don't know how complicated these equations are but there's
That's that's the formula. I feel like I love a lot of fontazza land rights
Yes a good example, I think of
The x plus y ride formula is a ride that is not there anymore
called silver mine and
This is basically
Maybe you have to do percentages here. Maybe this is like one fifth
Knott's Berry farm. What's the mine one?
To Timber Mountain alaco no or a timber mountain to my log, right? Yeah, not the not the flume
What's the other one? Oh?
Calico mine ride
Okay, all right
Okay, so it's part that because it's like miserable claustrophobic
You're seeing animatronics in really small spaces
And you feel like you could reach out and slap them or if you stuck your hand out
It would get dragged by the rock wall behind you and eventually just come clean off
But then it takes this turn that you don't expect at all because it's called mine
It's silver mine and then so then four fifths of the way through you leave the mine you go upstairs
And you crawl up to a an area that you'd have to call pirates of the Caribbean plus Mexico
It's really weird it just completely is the vibe of pirates and you're in a little Mexican town
And it's got
Something I want to codify. I think you know we like fake rocks, and I want to say I think we also like cloth fire
Let's just does it's not a lot of examples of it, but probably one of them and this ride is one of them as well
Yes, it's on is it in a spaceship Earth as well
I think there might be some cloth fire. I don't recall a fan
I want to say maybe it's a small world and little in miniature
That's right. Yeah, interesting. Let's say this here now. We podcast red likes cloth fire
I bet there's more cloth fire than we think
Yeah, I think if you had it now that we've put a name on it, and we're on the hunt for it
I think we'll start seeing it more at a new innovation is
Steam fire
We use fire like on Big Thunder Mountain. Oh you project on to steam
Yeah, turn the steam into fire exactly and then they already have sort of had that effect on the Indiana Jones in Japan
When you go that blows the ring yeah, yeah, so so steam fire as well of a big were big fans of I think
Also a fan of steam fire. Yeah, yeah, we I guess you could call it all
Fake fire, but you do need to delineate between the two and maybe there might be multiple multiple types
Well, we'll figure it out multiple types. Yeah, yeah
Anyway, this ride is crazy. People should watch ride throughs of it. It's just like I
It's so much of the vibe of pirates almost impressive that you could take you could capture the
Elements of what pirates is despite moving it over to a different theme in this case a little Mexican village because it's debauchery
It's you know it is it's things on fire
It's antics with the animals that are too close to houses as a woman chasing a donkey out with a broom
There is even in this ride literally a dirty foot pirate you go under a bridge and there is a guy
With a bottle up there swinging around and you pass right under his foot. They do it all it's really the difference is it's like
Mashing up versus like ripoff. It's like a girl talk
version of a mashup where it's like
Yeah, the all the elements kind of work I can see where they rip and this is exactly the same thing as this thing
But they've now recontextualized it and I can't be mad. This is kind of cool
And they did it there at least it feels at least a half the budget like maybe not more than that and they're jankier
Animatronics for sure they do less. We're not even close to Jack Sparrow territory, but I don't know
I give I found this thing charming. Yeah, I
Like all of the things I kind of find like they like it may made it work with the budget and
I'm not mad at the ripoff. I can't be mad at the ripoff. Are we Jason you feel the same way?
I don't know why it doesn't almost doesn't make sense that we were like
For Universal Studios, but I kind of love that they just stole all this Disney stuff
Yeah, well and honestly, it's enough of a trend that I thought you were setting up a
Transition to a different ride to the ride
Geist Geister, Iksha. Yeah
Well, Rickshaw
Yes, because the the literal translation is ghost
Yes, cuz the the literal translation is ghostly Rickshaw
Uh-huh, and this is very haunted mansion to the point of it appears to be doom buggy capsules a
Ghost follows you home
But the big big difference is that it appears to be as if Germans interpreted Chinese ghost stories
Yeah, yes, because it's in the Chinatown section of the park. That's got the ride you were
Discussing is in the Mexico section of the park
The lands of course Mexico Chinatown mystery fantasy Berlin and deep in Africa
Wow, you know the lands in this park is every theme park in Europe a nations of the world
I feel like so many of them. This is what they do
Yeah, it certainly seems that way. I I don't know why they felt the need to add deep in Africa that feels very
Collodio
But yeah from the format of all the other ones, you know, what are you?
Also just naming two sections. It's like this is mystery and this is fantasy. Those are the lands gave up
But yeah, the ghost ghostly Rickshaw I
Is incredibly again another ride that's incredibly detailed like has similar elements from the haunted man. There's a big party scene
Yeah, but again, it's it's
Like Chinese ghosts and culture and architecture and
Masks and it's and then they follow you home. Of course, they follow you home at the end. They have that set piece it is
Just from the look of it and part of it is because it's not the most expensive ride, but it is scary as shit
It is so creepy
All of these things all of these little like a lot of the robots are like little which honestly makes it I think worse
It almost like a storture view of reality and you're like little creepy guys. Yes, and
It's like the skeleton. It's like a little skeletons and you're like, oh
Like I there's a on their website. Is this one still open?
I want to say it's still open because I feel like I saw something on there. Okay. Yeah
They their official literature calls it Europe's longest underground ghost train
Which seems like an attack on something else like is there a specific thing in Portugal or Finland?
That's in their sights making some claim. That's like 500 feet shorter
And they're like we're gonna stick to that ghost train. You are the second longest underground ghost train
I mean, it's kind of it's not really a you're in the Omnimov or a haunted mansion vehicle. Not really a train
Yeah, wouldn't say
Say
Might be like a European term instead of like haunted house. Maybe ghost train
Mmm, I kept coming across that but maybe so the phrase train
Yeah, both of these rides. We just talked about are really long. There's so many rooms
There's so many animatronics. This is what I'm saying. I feel like this place has been
hidden from us in terms of
pure robot
Coverage I would love to know the official number. I feel like you'd have to actually check with someone who knew I'm not gonna watch
All the videos and do it count
That's that sounds hard
But I like it's crazy that I give them that's a lot of what we're after
I think is robots as opposed to screens and oh my god so many
Yeah, I was shocked as I outside of
Yeah, I'm trying to think I don't think any other I mean it's more robots and universal
Yeah, and for like all you like any you know any era of universal it feels like
It's a little more limited in another attraction. That's not there anymore
Called one thousand and one knocks
like nights and
I
Mean the equation here, maybe let me just instead. Let me let me break it down like okay
this is a ride where you
climb on a
suspended ship like Peter Pan
Where you're where the track is up above you?
But it starts in a fake rock cave like the Matterhorn
And then you leave the cave and you spend a full minute outside
Looking over other rides in a very storybook land
Fashion but that whole time you're slowly approaching the mouth of a dragon
And then you go inside the dragon where you're in a different scary type of cave
It's more like mr. Toad hell where it's red scary caves
And then you end up looking at a bunch of miniatures that are like the size of the Sleeping Beauty dioramas
but the
Miniatures are
Telling stories of Arabian Nights kind of stuff it has a vibe a lot like the Sinbad ride
In Disney see that's like five things all in one which is enough to make it completely its own
Original thing this is a really cool ride. I think or was
Yeah, it's like when you see those videos with Quentin Tarantino's references in his movies, and there's
50 other movies and you go he's stealing a lot, but he's
Taking them all and made a different thing out of him. I guess I'm in a blender. Yes exactly right
I yeah, this this thing's cool as hell. I don't know I I just think they
They took things to new levels
I
Don't know just just charm by this place
Yeah, now some stuff is just there is one thing that is an exact photocopy
In the sense that it ran at a lot of other parks and oddly enough
This is not buried on the website this does get a decent
Link on the attractions page. I'm talking about Pirates 4d
Pirates 4d is a 4d movie
Starring the great Leslie Nielsen and Monty Python's Eric Idol
Theme park legend Eric Idol also theme park legend Eric Idol, yeah and
So I looked a little into the make so this was produced by Bush Entertainment Corporation the
Entertainment wing of the anheuser-bush company back in the 90s
Who of course at the time ran bush gardens and SeaWorld at the moment?
I believe just bush gardens, but they produced this string of
4d movies that would just play almost on a circuit of
It would play at bush gardens and SeaWorld places, and then they'd license it to other places movies like haunts of the old country and
something I am very interested in
Not least of which because of the people involved RL. Stein's haunted lighthouse a
40 movie starring Christopher Lloyd
Huh?
Rick written and those are in Christopher Lloyd Leah Thompson and Michael McKeon whoa
so I
That one we might have to dig into a little more. Yeah, we haven't done any of these lesser more overlooked
theme park 3d
Yeah, cuz every now and then people do I believe I saw either Pirates 4d at bush gardens Williamsburg
But I'm pretty sure I saw haunts of the old country
But they would just like they they spent a chunk of money to make these movies with like
You know big stars in them. I believe pirates 4d also played the Wisconsin Dells Michael mm-hmm
I believe Eric Idle wrote Pirates 4d I
Think that's possible. I believe I read that I could be
RL. Stein's haunted lighthouse was directed by Joe Dante
Yeah, that's that we just covered
Were you building to that fact? I'm sorry if I jumped on it well
I another one interesting to me the writer of haunted lighthouse is Sam Ham the writer of Tim Burton's Batman
Crazy
Run of Batman comics that introduced the harrick character of Henry Ducard
Batman's mentor that I believe let Liam Neeson plays for some of Batman begins well you yeah
He's not really it's a fake out. He's not really a fake out
Yeah, I'll go as they say even though I always thought it was racial ghoul because of the animated series, but that's another podcast
Yeah, that's another podcast. Yeah, so so there's some interesting stuff in the Bush Entertainment Corporation
Pipeline we got a that's a full we got to do all of them. Yeah
And pirate the yeah, go ahead. Go ahead
Well I was gonna say the other thing about Pirates 4d the plot is one of the grimace things I've ever heard
Yes, do tell so
Leslie Nielsen is the captain of a pirate ship and right at the beginning
He says ah I have not returned to pirate island in five years and as they arrive on pirate island
They start falling into like comical
You know slapsticky traps, and it is revealed the previous crew of this ship was left to
die on pirate Island and the survivor was a child who has laid all of these traps to get his
Revenge and in the end ends up becoming the new captain of the ship
Captain Davey
It's a child's revenge. It's a home alone pirates
Yeah, because they wanted a lot of antics. I mean it's a lot of like cannonball shot at the screen
door hitting people
Flying Leslie Nielsen flinging a door open and hitting someone in the head sure sure but if home alone at an extremely dark
backstory
like if the if the
You know sloppy bandits. What are they the wet band?
Sloppy band is good too
What else are they called?
Yeah, what are they aren't they the the feathery bandits the guitar to bandits?
Why am I having a problem people are this is another one are yelling wet bandits in which one?
They're the first one the wet bandits
Sticky sticky sticky band. Yeah, all right. I got it. I did the yelling for the odds. Yeah
Huh pirates for D. I mean yeah this when you look at this wiki this was open in bizarre
Locations across the world across different theme park brands from SeaWorld the bush gardens to the Luxor
And now it seems like it is only open in
Fantasia land on Tosy land now the exclusive home of this
proud work of Eric Idle I
assume I
Watched most of this Jason. Did you watch most of it? I watched the whole yeah
Like 15 minutes as my I mean I will say Eric Idle theme park legend, but is he attached to the most unpleasant
Theme park things that exist I
Liked it as a kid yeah, I
It's not it's not no
It's it's not that bad
And it doesn't think it looks like they spent some money on it like that's that's the thing it seems like
The theme park Wars of the 90s it does seem like
Bush garden SeaWorld was like trying to compete a little with these 4d movies, but also
There's a brief period of time where Dave and Buster's had 4d theaters
And they would probably just shove them in there if they paid for the licensing you know
I guess it's just because Eric poor Eric has an association with figment
That's yeah
The audience which I like but is also you you might you wouldn't be wrong to call parts of it unpleasant at least
Yeah, then as a kid I was scared of it and then but I do people do like that
So I really shouldn't tar and feather a title here
Oh certainly yeah, I'm flipping through his filmography also, and I'm reminded that he is a recurring character
Throughout the film that this series is titled after national lampoon's European vacation
As I recall his part is funny. He's a guy riding a bike. Oh, yeah, yeah by
Chevy that being said just I just want to give a quick
His anti shout-outs to that film we titled it after I don't know if you guys agree
I think that is such an unpleasant movie
Like the eating nightmare at the beginning and the fashion montage or that song new looks
You've been down a street for am I crazy I like I had a discussion with our friend Ryan Perez who called that a rotten film
Am I crazy that bear I haven't you're you know that I'm saying seen it in years, but I that feeling is correct
I think seeing when I was younger. I definitely like felt it was very unpleasant
There's stuff I obviously the Eric Otto stuff is a funny runner because he's like very polite every time he gets hit
Yeah, that's all that's all funny. I like his and like the game show John Aston game show
Traffic, so we've talked about John Aston this week too because he was that's right
Still alive teaching teaching theater
Him on I'd love the parking enough. I mean whatever
There's no reason not to have Eric Idle and John Aston both on but the only reason is a lack of ability to get a hold of
Yeah, it's the biggest obstacle
anyway, not to dwell on that if I'm wrong, please yell at me and
Cancel me but not permanently
You can cancel me for a day
What else weird stuff oh oh in that neck of the woods, you know the movies that slid in and out
So I don't think they have it anymore
But for a while this is one of the other theme parks that has a very Epcot esque gold geodesic dome
It's like half of a spaceship Earth essentially
Which I always like seeing those anywhere, and I was never sure what was inside them the monk the monkey hosted video
That I watched
Has a funny moment where it it shows you the dome and it says and in here you can see
Cine 2000 and then it cuts to Cine 2000 and it's imagine if you were in the if you're in LA the
Arclet the Cinerama dome and you were standing on the floor of the Cinerama dome
Just watching a video of the POV of a roller coaster and everybody goes ah
It's just the weirdest lowest rent like a
Simulator, but it's a simulator where you just stand. I think you get dizzy so fast. This seems like the laziest thing
Let's just play a video of a roller coaster instead of building one
But then they put in something that I think has a little more value an attraction called race for Atlantis
Which I think we could just touch on and maybe deal with later
Because race for Atlantis is the same movie that played in an IMAX theater in Caesar's Palace in the mall
shops at Caesar
If you've been to that mall you know that there is a show where a bunch of statues come to life
And that's called called fall of Atlantis, but that's just part of the story the rest of the story was told through this
simulator attraction which
I saw a poster for that said
The IMAX 3d ride that makes every other thrill ride obsolete
Very bold claim
Very especially when this thing itself is obsolete
It has not been at Caesar's for a long time it made it at Fantasia land from 94 to 2016
And now I think this dome is gone entirely
I think we should loop back around to this one because the I think aesthetically it's very interesting from what I watched
I it's a it's a very it feels like Flight of Passage meets Star Wars prequels
It's a very like odd fantasy design scheme
And I'm also intrigued because it has a villain named
Gastelius
And I would I would like to know more about Gastelius, but we could do that as part of some Vegas block
Oh, yeah, it was here, too, and still open in France. I believe so it's still still hanging on but yeah race for Atlantis
I'd love to
Dig into more yeah, that sounds great
I'd like to talk about while we're talking the magic of the movies
I mean the website invites us to rediscover some old classics on an attraction called Hollywood tour. Yeah
I mean this is the star of the show
I think this is this might be the fiesta resistance of this this park look does it have some maybe some of the best
Rollercoasters in the world. Yes sure that of course how many parts can you say that about?
But Hollywood tour seems like something special well, and I would describe this equation as
Great movie ride
Plus universal tram tour plus Pirates of the Caribbean again
Even though we already have pirate rip-offs. Maybe we have a pirate's rip-off and we pirates 4d
This one is yet another
Pirate sea ride, but it's weird they splinter everything off
So the the town and the drunkenness and the fires and the revelry is moved over to silver mine
This right now just uses the caves
Essentially it starts in the caves
They're more well, it's and it's also a mix of the rainbow caverns which is now attributed at the start of Big Thunder
It's all of that at the same time because it's the Pirates caves
But they're now like rainbow much like that scene at the end the hill lift on Big Thunder
Absolutely and
And a lot of these elements also show up in a different ride in this park called Chiapas
Which is an incredibly steep log flume that ends in like an Aztec temple where it appears a
Party is happening
It's like yeah, that ride looks great
Yeah, yeah, it's it's like a
Guy I saw it on their site as a Mexican archaeological site
So I think you're you know, they're digging for artifacts or something
But then there are a bunch of statues or busts that all light up with lighting effects and music and that's a ride that like
It has a backward section and then flips around to go
Front-facing again like the Norway ride
steepest log flume in the world in the world
Yeah, it's got kind of that double bounce like the Dudley do right ride that right that looks just
Legitimately
Fantastic as does River Quest just to give that a shout. This looks like a
pretty unique
Rapids ride where you know, most rapids rides are sort of rustic or it's you know
It through it's through the forests or you know
Cedar kind of area this is like you're in some scary tower and there's a big cyclone on the top of a building and there's
An elevator that delivers you to a drop like again just super unique
These water rides seem really awesome
Yeah, I didn't want to take away don't want to take away from from Hollywood tour Hollywood tour. Yeah, which has a
also
What I would describe is a plus up from pirates where clearly the drop is based on pirates and you go into a cavern right after
But as you're barreling down the drop you're heading towards a wall of water
And it moves out of the way at the very last second before you land
Like if they put that in today in our pirates you'd say that's great. That's a huge improvement
Yeah, that is and even if they like I guess I mean there are different colors in the rocks
I was gonna say if they made the little more colorful rocks, you wouldn't be mad either. I don't think
Yeah, you can light that up. That'd be cool
Yeah, that is a that is a neat little trick. It's much better than the now gone
But they do tell tales with seeing
You know
Blackbeard or Davy Joe it would switch every now and then yeah, it's usually Davy Jones
But then they threw Blackbeard on for like the fourth movie, which we just watched and
It's really like you got Ian McShane and like you're not gonna use him that much. Okay. All right movie
Hmm, very strange. I don't think I think there's things about the refresh that I like fine
But that's not one of that always felt very
Plotty it felt like let me let's just like stamp some exposition
You mean the the barber the addition of the miss and do tells it. Yeah, it sucks
It's like we have to like re-explain and
It's like that's God. That's like of all the things to take out. I think that's the thing to take out
Oh, yeah, and the new thing they put in is a nice little fun
thing
Great illusion, I was probably done pretty cheaply but still pretty effective and does a little
Narrative kind of explanation sort of of what is going on in the ride
Yeah, which I actually helps easy in the world. Yeah
Yeah, super cool, but pirates I think might still rank behind Hollywood tour as the best
cavern born boat ride cuz
Unlike all right, so you're in caverns and you know, do you go see some skeletons and some ships and stuff?
No, you see a lot of nothing for a while and then you see a 1950s film crew making a movie
It's so weird it's why are we in caves for this?
Yeah, yeah is I don't know is the cave is supposed to be a set. Oh
I mean I think at some point you you go on to a set like the big one with the big thing that like
Stuck out to me and I forget if it's a first or second scene you see but you come around the corner
There was a helicopter going up and down then there's a cowboy shooting a gun then over to the left
There is like a film crew and then you straight ahead. There is a giant spider
So it's a cowboy shooting a gun at a giant spider
I have no idea what the helicopter is doing did John Peters have something to do with this ride is my question
It's the scariest
Villain a giant spider scariest bad guy
In the scariest killer in the animal kingdom. Mmm. Yeah, there's cowboys
Talking about Kevin Smith has a story about John Peters the producer trying to get a giant spider into a Superman movie and eventually
He got a giant spider into Wild Wild West
Which was yeah robot spider and if you want to hear that story take 25 minutes and have the words
Fuck and flick a bunch more. That's right
What else say speaking of directors right at the top of it you see a really miserable
Dead looking Alfred Hitchcock. Is that what that's supposed to be? I had that written so yeah
Um, I don't know he's a
And there's no other IP per se it's not like this is then a great movie ride where you see Marilyn Monroe and
Cary Grant I think the only sort of recognizable one is Hitchcock who seems like he's at the moment of dying
Like you were at frame one of a heart attack
Well, that's the most exciting frame. I think it's about to start
You don't know what's happening
His eyes lit up. Here we go
I will say with all of these rides
I'm sure when if you go on them, I think if we were to go on all of them in person
We would notice the junkier elements more because some like there's a fully exposed industrial ceiling a lot in this ride and a lot
Of other rides when the boat is like turning a corner. There's just like some loose dirty pipes and clearly like like water damaged
walls
That are pretty visible pipes
The pipes in the walls for the sad man from the end of the sad man. We got some
We got some for proud design choice
Yeah
You you see it. There's a Tarzan section much like the great movie ride as
then
Then you see a boat and then as you pass around the corner you see rising over it the the great ape King Kong
King Kong is also in this so it's the King Kong and this kind of a jaws
At the beginning. Yes. Yeah, there's a quick shark there. There's um
my favorite thing a a
Alligator pulling a water skiing monkey
That's pretty fun. That's in the that's in the Tarzan section here. I'll show you I just really
Really enjoyed this
He's pulling the monkey
There's another month the monkey above has a like a carrot on a stick or something that's making the Gators swim around
That's that rules. That's great. Yeah
That for I love that Frankenstein. There's Frankenstein's Frankenstein's monster on the on the
trip it's a slab
which honestly is like one of the all like very
worried about
Not getting that Universal epic universe
Horror land now because they're probably gonna build that park in Orlando or it's gonna take a while
So maybe this is the best representation of Frankenstein we have because the rumor was it was gonna be Frankenstein's castle in a crazy
E ticket maybe kook arm
That's also a roller coaster ride with all the monsters and you'd finally get some insane
Classic Universal monster thing but until then we'll have to just go to Germany to experience Frankenstein
Well for a while the title was held by Frankenstein playing a keytar or whatever in the Beetlejuice
Graveyard review right but yes
Not for that's not a ride. So I guess if we're talking ride depictions of Frankenstein, right? It'd be this movie
Are we okay? Is it?
Are we touring an underground movie? So are we touring the movie mines? Is that what it is?
Or is this like a magic cave where all your movie dreams come to light
What what is it? Hmm? I think from what I understand is this park has very limited space
So they have built the longer dark rides underground underneath other attractions. Oh, yeah, this is under another ride
That's right. Yeah, there's a basement literally a flooded now
I
Cannot find a justification for why the generic Wizard of Oz scene
Appears to imply that Alice's house in Kansas is in the woods
And all of our friends are at the house too
It's just kind of a lot of elements of Wizard of Oz just thrown together
the video is a little hard to parse but
Is there I feel like I only saw Glinda and not a door
There's a scarecrow and a Glinda Dorothy on the porch like on the side
Yeah, yeah, I'm looking through the YouTube right here. I think there is a side of the porch
You see her kind of when you first come in but it's not she's not like pointed
There's if you were the main show scene is looking head-on at the building and she's not looking out that way
She's on the porch looking off
This is not Dorothy. This is Dana Dana American farm girl
Anyone could wear a dress like that. What are you referring to straw man?
They are sapphire
Dana
Mr. Ape the gorilla teeth the shark all of your Hollywood favorites
This is the one thing where it's like, all right, you know, not at the license for any of this crap. Okay, that's fine
You got one you got one. You're a
senior swinger
That's not Tarzan
King Kong had the fake King Kong has some very funny eyebrows
You know
I don't recall his eyebrows. Oh, okay. Hold on. Yeah one second. I want to make sure you see his eyebrows
I want to know that they're funny
Yeah, they're fine waiting to laugh
Yo, you'll laugh I put you on the spot. I'm sorry. I don't want to miss out on these eyebrows. You see
Yeah, it's bogged on from breaking bad
Yeah
They're like two feet tall by these proportions and also like his pecs are very strange
Well, he's like you look like yeah, he looks like he love his like pectoral
He looks like he fell asleep on the beach wearing a bikini top. Yes left some tan marks
Yeah, I guess and that also implies that if when King Kong tans that it changes the
Darkness of his hair. Well, I think maybe the hair looks like it's like a bad die
Situation oh that's revealing what's underneath?
Yeah, he looks like maybe he's like either gray or balding or something and he did like a really bad like shoe polish job
On the top of his head
It is receding. You're absolutely right
So maybe he let himself go on the top but he wears a hat and on his pecs, but he wears a bikini top
So right mad at these sailors or whatever because they interrupted him without clothes on
You know my secret I'm balding there's yeah, there's a line
I don't know exactly what he looked like when the park opens
But you know, look we all age
We're all the same Lee fingers too. It's very like it's very big footy fingers
He's yeah, he looks like he looks like he also could be just like some sort of old-time Catskill comedian maybe
Like he's like still doing shows. He could be in Vegas. He could be like opening for Rich Little in Vegas
These Peter Gallagher what he is. That's true
What if we fused in April Peter Gallagher
And give it where would give it a werewolf fingers
Oh
Look at this. This is one of my other thing. I've decided I like in theme park world green cities
I love my dark ride green cities. Give me give me a cloth fire and green cities. Yeah
Man, this is a good ride and it seems like I feel like this is on the chopping block like there
You like you said they hit it on the website
It's like buried all the way you have to keep scrolling and scrolling and scrolling to find out if it's even there
It's like they're embarrassed of it. They shoved it in a basement and they should not be there should be front and center in the ads
I mean if I were to go to this place
This is the first thing I would go there first thing because I'd be worried it'd be broken by the end of the day
They should have a big picture of King Kong's weird eyebrows on the main page
To like entice you because like if you looked at it you'd be like always a nice park seems like it's got some cool
Coasters some nice food
But I don't know if there's any like character to it and then you'd see like a big janky
King Kong robot head and you go something for everyone here
Yeah, yeah, I mean this is that I feels like the best
Thing at the park to me the only thing I'd like to name check really really quick
All these rides are kind of in the dark so you can't there's not a lot to say about them
But I really like that there was
There is a roller coaster that has shifted hands a couple times and it started in the 80s as Space Center
Where it was very space mountain II so I like the vibe of that Space Center became temple of the Nighthawk and today is
crazy bats
Those are three best ride names have ever heard and it's all the same right that's great. Yeah, can I quick name check feng shui place?
What's that no I didn't fan this is a type of ride that I only we've talked about a lot. It's a madhouse
Mm-hmm. Yes, it's a it's like it's a site
I'm reading from Wikipedia
It's an up designed to be an optical and physical illusion
Consisting of several rows of seats attached to a swaying gondola with a rotating drum
So it's sort of making it seem like
Crazy stuff is happening as it's rotating
It creates the impression that the rider is turning upside down where the room is actually moving around them
So feng shui place is something I thought was interesting because to me it feels a lot like
Scott your favorite ride had not or experienced mystery lodge. Oh, hey, yeah, it's very much like
Yes, it's like people like there's obviously actors
They recorded at a certain point they fight and there's a whole narrative going on and in in a madhouse
Which I mean the name madhouse is a great
Name what else is a matter there examples of man?
Absolutely are more examples
The American ones there Merlin's mystical mansion at Clark's Trading Post in Lincoln, New Hampshire
What are you talking about? I'm not sure if some of these are still there
Denny's great escape at Six Flags New England in 1999
Who they had that a something like that a great adventure to where the room goes upside down
You were like seated and you think you were upside down, but it's the room has gone upside down
Yeah, and this is something I've been to this place, but it was not there Noah's incredible adventure at Noah's Ark water park in Wisconsin Dells
We got to hit that one. We definitely got to hit that one. There's so yeah, I mean my friend. Yeah, we're gonna do that
There's so much Tommy Bartlett you guys
I have no idea Tommy Bartlett is so interesting
Tommy Barlow all I'll say is Tommy Bartlett's robot world
And it's now it's changed the name of it, but it was literally like you'd walk through
Tommy Bartlett had thrown together some like tin cans with googly eyes
and
Yeah, here you go. Oh, and that's your happiest memory. Oh my god. I love it
Wow, yeah, okay
That's a great one. Let's build that up his name haunts me Tommy Bartlett Poseidon Fury
Was gonna be at islands of adventure and it was gonna be a madhouse. I believe that's what I'm reading here
Unfamiliar with this genre in general. I'd like to know more about mad house mad houses
so
Yeah, yeah, I think there's a fun house here, too
I forgot what it was called, but like there's so many rides through with the and there's so many still here and
Here and the other thing that we haven't talked about they have like a lot of like
Some Disney parks they have two hotels built into the park
the hotel Mataba and Hotel Ling Bao and they were scheduled for a whole new land for 2020 which is
I don't I'm sure has been delayed
Called Rookberg that was gonna have this Charles Lindberg Hotel Charles Lindbergh
This capsule hotel Wow, whoa, which smaller is he?
It's it's all steampunky and then they were gonna have this fly coaster, which is an act
I don't know what it's an acronym for but it's a flight coaster like
Tatsu where you're lying down. It's a first launching flight coaster
man eats with a hotel built into it and oh my god this with a
And the like coaster would go by like the patio the upstairs like
Roofdeck or something now would I have maybe not named it after the aviator who flew to Germany to get a medal for?
Hermann Goring. Yeah, I might have gone with Amelia Earhart, but that's just me. What are you gonna do?
Well, you're not we're not in charge of anything yet until we get it employed by Dunham or failure
Sure
Fader land till we all come up with fader land
We'll get some advice we'll get some counsel from John Binkowski of Hard Rock Park before too
Oh, yeah, he gives us a crash course and how to open up open a park that makes it at least six months
Yeah, did they start building that Jason? Do you know it's yeah, it's pretty far along
Wow, it seems like from the pictures I saw we have but I don't know they have an opening date yet
The reality is I feel like anything that's with the exception probably of a splash mountain redo
Which is obviously not started
Anything that is already like 25 to 50 percent done will probably get in theme parks
But almost everything else is canceled for the next few years. That's I would guess what's gonna happen. I
Think so. I think that's accurate Nintendo land though construction out here for us still moving along though
Yeah, we're very lucky and they were like they were gonna open secret life of pets like the week of yes
we were you know, it's a funny moment was that
We I keep like a document of episodes that are coming up and like well around this week
We'll do secret life of pets there on here. We'll do Marvel the pandemic starting and need deleting those from the
Won't be needing those at the who about a Europe trip that could be different that's something else we could do
Good we could still talk about the pictures of Josh tomorrow
Installing the Quinjet at the top of the Avengers campus, which I'm sure we all saw
Well, my favorite thing of like the Quinjet has been placed at Avengers campus
Except the fact they're all standing in dirt pathways. It's like you have not you have not paved the walkways yet. So
Let me know when cement arrives. Yeah, let me know when the water is hooked up
All right, I think we're I think we're heading to the end here I've totally forgot one more thing though
Oh my god in in the world of ripoffs
They have a at least I don't know if they do anymore. They had a just full-on Star Tours ripoff called galaxy. Oh, yeah
Yeah, yeah
Which let me screen share that it was so down to the elements of the ripoff
Look at this host. Look at this flight attendant Wow. That's just exactly
Original Star Tours, it's the same weird flippy hair the ward actually actually oddly looks more similar to the current the
Allison Janney voiced robot who they have now
But they did add a new element which was it which is you know, it's not Chewbacca
Obviously who you know, it's it's not Ewoks bumbling in the in the ride vehicle in the safety video. It's this guy
Who looks like kind of a green Michelin man
Yeah, like they took a sumo wrestling novelty suit and threw a coat of green paint on it
You watch his antics. I love this guy
Angry family who has to like we're forced to sit next to this guy who by the way, let me check my notes
Oh, yes, he is Alex from Galex
Alex from Galex love Alex from Galex
Yeah, big puffy arms. This girl is so pissed off to be next to Alex from Galex
As much tension as if you were being taken along on a false niece trip
Yeah, anyway so much crazy IP Alex from Galex it goes on and on so many robots this place is absolutely insane and
I think I mean I've seen look there's there's been some criticism of us
Look, we're not gonna be able to get to everything. We haven't been to these places. I already regret that we haven't talked about
The McDonald's was a Chessington the McDonald's. Yeah the McDonald's non-standard McDonald's
We missed the non-standard McDonald's in Chessington and a medieval
McDonald's. Yeah. Yeah, any other big regrets that we've become aware
I mean Flynn, please let us know please. Shoot us a tweet or an email if we miss something big we can collect all these things
Things we missed or maybe we'll go to Europe again and talk about them. I saw that we'd and I think there was a criticism
It was valid
Somebody said we did not devote enough time to the family
Somebody said we did not devote enough time to the fifth dimension and Zappa manic and I completely agree
I feel like we hit that pretty good. I think we need 20 to 30 more minutes at least
I I spaced on that like the writer of that ride was Douglas Adams of the hitchhikers guide to the galaxy
Like yeah, this big stuff
But we you know what we want to get to these places, you know, we want to also leave some room
For when we go in now experience, obviously we won't get to experience Zappa manic, but you know, maybe Zappa manic is his own
Patreon spin spin him off somehow. Well, I mean maybe that brings me to sort of a
overall question
for you guys
Some of these things in the burn the past you got to take them off the table
But of the places that we have discussed here on the main feed or the second gate
You know Alf and gremlins we can't do but that that leaves five five places that currently exist if you could only go
To one of the five
Which one would you choose?
Okay, I want to work through my my I want to show my work here a little bit
I think Chessington if they still had professor burp and
Zappa-matic that's high up on the list. The problem is they're gone
That one suffers a little more from the really cool things are in the past as charming as that park seems and that right below
Ride, but yeah, maybe with it and the dumpy and the dumpy, you know movie land movie world
It's fun
Yeah, I love to be there. I love to be there right now eating that
club sandwich
That they were advertising I'd love that but the Dakota stick. Oh my god
I'd love to get one of those Dakota sticks in my mouth
And then learn a little bit more about the male anatomy
Show us how illustrate how comfortable you are with your sexuality using a Dakota. Yes, I will
So but that's you know
What so it comes comes on to Malta Village it comes down to this place. What's the is there one more?
Am I forgetting the Tato Park? Oh, of course Tato Park Tato Park is great, but it's not like
What I want from Tato Park is probably a
One-on-one interaction with mr. Tato for a few hours. That's really what I want
I I we spent so much of the episode talking about him. Mr. Tato and we like the ride. They seem nice
They seem cute, but it's not like I want to be best friends with him. I want to go walking around
Telling women that their underwear is showing with him
I want to help him on his quest to
Stop indecency modest up this world. Yeah modest up this world
So I the right the place itself doesn't do so much for me
So it comes down to Popeye Village or this place. I'm between these two as well. So
You know, I
Think I gotta give it to I think for me
Fantasia land seems like so rich and so full of substance like and the other thing
I mean, I don't know the euro exchange rate seemed pretty reasonable for like
The the quality that of the bills, you know, and yes, and and it also feels like they're adding stuff to Fantasia land
Like you just showed like it feels like it's trying to stay somewhat relevant
and I would argue of course getting rid of some of the other robot rides that are crazy bad move, but
This thing you showed me this hotel looks insane. It's got a good mix of old
Crazy stuck-in-time robot rides a new mix of cool coasters. It looks very nice
I think it's this is a slam dunk. I would love to go to Malta Village, but I think it's a slam dunk
This is this is the winner. Are we all saying Fantasia land? I think so Wow
Your land on your land you are the winner
I don't think we knew there was gonna be a competition but you're the winner of the European vacation
I agree as well and just to say I loved living in this area so much
And when one other thing I'm the drinker of the show the beer in this area. Oh my god
That's that was my favorite thing. I got to live there before I was 21
In America, but I went to Europe and could drink at 20 and pay one euro and get like the best beer I've ever had
Wow, the cheap be it said they'll give you this massive thing for a single euro
So
if the if the
Beer is anywhere close because I because I have to take eating into account too and the food at a lot of these places
Seems a little miserable admittedly. I mean, I'm not sure about food at a fun time
You land but seems like some you know, big old bratwurst and stuff
But if the oh, oh Jason which is tied with rope a sandwich with rope
That looks delicious honestly. Yeah, I like that. Yeah, actually we watched a video
Erin and I watched a video where there's a big
French Briesian section where they're making fresh crepes Alex delicious. Did you see did you see this?
Ruttmors Tavern desire for honest cuisine. Oh
My god, I had made up my despite made up my mind before Ruttmors Tavern
This is absolutely the quality of the Harry Potter restaurants. Oh my god
These are unreal
Bratwurst. Yeah, those jams look so great. This is like solid lunch man. Then like what?
Yeah, my god
Yeah, this
also if you I there's a
It might be the case on this menu, too
I saw a rooftop bar called the dragon bar in the China area
And the drink assortment went on and on and on it went there were so many
Varieties so many types of whiskey and vodka and beer, of course
You know and to get to be close to this area. I like so much clone and Dusseldorf
I would absolutely I this one legitimately that after talking about this. I think I do want to actually go to
To Western Germany and check out funtazi land. So yes, congrats you win
I also just want to point the menu you were just showing Mike contain the phrase pork knuckle
That was a staple of the Sheridan house growing up I assumed well sure, you know
Your mama just a wrap all of your your actual knuckles in pork go on
You're gonna go go have some lunch. You say you get smacked by some pork knuckle
It's feeling pretty ramy. He's full of pork
Yeah, too much pork knuckle too excited. Well, then that means that you survived to podcast the rides European vacation
What a blast one more stamp of the passport could clunk and what we have here
it looks to me like a
DNA test from the gopher woman and
Wouldn't you know it? There's a big green check mark. It says more
Woman than gopher so Mike you are a go
Hmm. What person does a percentage does it say a percentage? Is it 51% woman?
It's
72 percent human woman pretty good. Honestly pretty good. So yeah
I think you got to go for it and after this journey you've been on of of sexual liberation you learned what sex is
You still want to participate in mr. Tato's plan to modest up Ireland, but you've I think you've made incredible progress
Thank you. Yes. I feel different. I feel better as I said before I feel good and better
Which is what we're all saying during this time of quarantining and pandemic
We say it's so much you almost get tired of saying you get tired saying I feel better and you get tired of saying I now
Feel willing to have sex with a gopher woman. Mm-hmm
I mean this is look this is a time Marissa Strickland is going to marry a potato chip or a potato
and I'm at least going to have
Sexual Congress with a gopher faced woman with a moon one Rouge
Top-hatted gopher woman. Oh, we made
Yeah, a lot has happened. Yeah, it's been a special time. It's been a special month and thank you all for listening and
Let me just say
You're gonna want to remember this time. You know, you're gonna want to hold on to August 2020 and all of our growth
For as long as possible and that is why you've noticed these
Stamps that we've been getting and these are not just for us
They are also for you if you go to our tea public
We are now offering a sticker set of all of the passport stamps. It's a little they're less passport stamp and more
Trunks now, would you call them Jason?
like I call them like steamer trunk stickers you used to stick you see all the
Trunks back in the day at stickers from traveling around the world on them
Show all of the places that you've been just like Robert Evans used
When he was carting around a bunch of cocaine and a non-existent letter from Henry Kissinger
So we're tributing these great trunks in this great era in this great series
And you can go find all of those on our tea public as a set just to recap
You'll get the logo for the series made by Aaron Gardner my lovely wife
the Dakota stick from Italy
Robert Altman as Popeye from Malta
Jason the height miser from the UK
Mr. Tato's wedding proposal from Ireland elf Cardi B style from Germany
and of course the positive DNA test that allows my
Entry into a relationship with this gopher woman. Mm-hmm. I mean, I wouldn't want these stickers
These priceless heirlooms
Hey, we got you. We got you some souvenirs souvenirs that you have to pick
For
Just like souvenirs real souvenirs. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, just usually people come back from Europe and don't you don't then charge you for the souvenirs?
Hey, but look, you know, that's the only way we're gonna get it
We can't just mail out a bunch of stickers to every listener to the show
We'd love to but we can't so check that out on T public as well as we got merchandise of the
Of the logo of a small world style and a little boat that Aaron did
This has been so much fun
Please email us or tweet or DM get us the info about things that we missed in this series that you would like to hear about
Also, please let us know where we should go next. Do we do a Europe tour? Do we go?
Do we go to Asia? Do we break that off as China and Japan?
Do we stay close and go to Canada? We I think we've completely missed Canadian parks. There's so many possibilities
Yes, yeah sky is the limit
Yeah, and the sky is the limit now that we don't even have to visit so we just maybe you know if
quarantine lasts for another decade
Mm-hmm. We can go anywhere. I
Really? Hope we are not playing that clip what you just said in a decade
Boy, remember when we said that it seems like just a joke. Mm-hmm. Yeah, I hope not. I hope not
I I really hope that
But I hope that we were hopefully I I feel the three of us like we got to I I feel like metaphorically
We got out of where we live and I hope the listeners did to
Imaginary vacation I I had a great time and hopefully we can go to these places for real
Especially fun. Tazza land congrats on winning
Boy, a lot of fun. That was a but
any closing thoughts
No, I think we've said it all I'm I'm I'm I'm tired but a good tired
Yeah, yeah, we might need a vacation from our vacation
We might we might not be doing an episode for Labor Day, but we'll bring out a fun episode from the archives
But otherwise, thank you for taking this journey with us and
Mike
You're free to go share your love
Well, look, I'll keep you everyone posted about that
I definitely that'll be something you'll hear a lot about
This will come up a lot. Yeah
All right. Thanks for listening everybody. It was a fun vacation. We'll see you back in America
Good bye. Bye
This has been a forever dog production
executive produced by Mike Carlson Jason Sheridan Scott Gardner Brett Boehm
Joe Cilio and Alex Ramsey for more original podcasts, please visit forever dog
podcasts calm and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts
Spotify or wherever you get your podcast keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
At forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook