Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, The Second Gate,
an episode firmly planted behind The Second Gate.
It is, we gotta keep it safe here.
I'm Scott Gardner, joined by Jason Sheridan.
Hi, yeah, this one sucks, that's our show.
Thank you so much for listening.
Oh boy, oh no, if anyone was just diving in,
just to do a quick check.
You revealed it all right there, all the cards.
I've been sitting on that joke for three weeks.
Very well, is there-
I almost forgot as I quickly hit record,
because I was always not prepared.
Well, is there any more subtlety
to the opinions of Mike Carlson?
Of course there are, I wouldn't reveal now.
I'm a magician doesn't give away the trick right away.
So I'm gonna have to slowly eke out my opinions.
You're gonna wonder, am I trolling, am I not trolling?
This is my nature, this is the fun of the podcast.
So we'll get into it.
I'll just say this, I like the building.
I enjoy the building.
Which doesn't preclude you
from saying you like other things later.
You're just saying one thing that you like, okay.
Now, I just may have done the first part of a magic trick,
the first third of a magic trick.
Mine might be a distraction.
Oh, interesting.
For the actual reveal.
Mystique for this episode.
A lot of mind games afoot as we discuss
race through New York, and we are doing it
via a Zoom to New York.
To the guest brave enough to volunteer to cover this topic,
please welcome PTR legend, Griffin Newman.
Every time, every time that hair is on the back of my neck,
stand up.
The feels good.
It's like being called, it's like being a knight.
It's like being a sir.
Absolutely.
I need to start demanding that everyone call me
a PTR legend in introductions,
regardless of what podcast I'm on.
Any other show, any other project.
And also just the fact that I know I made it in,
but for the grace of God.
I made it in on a technicality
because Mike accidentally hit a slide
with a video that I had made prematurely.
Yep, that's right.
The world summoning you to the universe
demanded that you be one,
corrected our error not making you one already.
Right, just because to relitigate,
you said something like the next person
that we're about to show you is a PTR legend.
And then you accidentally showed a picture of me.
So then just, all right, sure.
Yeah, why not?
He's in.
Yeah, yeah, okay.
We all decided on the stage by going,
oh yeah, I guess.
Look, I'll say this.
We were always planning on doing this episode in person.
I was vaguely scheduling another trip to LA
the beginning of March.
Ready to go.
Yeah.
It was in the immediate purview.
I don't like doing podcasts over Zoom,
but I will say it does feel now that we're here
a little nice to be able to have me report
on Race Through New York while in New York.
Yeah, I think that was meant to be.
Yeah, I think it would feel pretty inauthentic
if there was no part,
if there wasn't a quarter of this podcast
recorded in New York City.
Because I feel like for so long,
this ride has been dining out on its authenticity, right?
When people talk about this ride,
they talk about versimilitude, you know?
And I feel like it's time to really start
to call that shit into question.
I'm ready to do a full expose.
What Race Through New York gets wrong about New York?
Oh, it does?
Something, what do you mean?
A couple of things in this ride are not accurate.
Now during that-
Where's the pizza?
Where's the halal guys?
You know, where's the real New York?
Construction workers, hey, what are you doing here
with the Knight Rider?
You were making that-
You were making that impassioned monologue
and then changed your background conspicuously
in a sort of distracting move for us
to what seems like a accurate image to me.
It's the New York skyline with the Statue of Liberty.
That's one of the things I know about New York
is that the statue is there.
And then Jimmy is gliding over the city
in his iconic vehicle, the Tonight Rider.
Huh.
I don't know where to,
I don't know whether to pick off the Tonight Rider already
or do we need to go in an orderly fashion here?
I mean, why, oh boy.
Should we talk about our,
one of our many ordeals was attempting to see this
when we were in Orlando.
Do you guys remember the details of this?
Oh, of course, yes, I remember the details.
I have been in this building twice, that's what I'll say.
Okay.
The first time was when Lindsay and I went
right after it opened and we saw the show
and we'll get to what we thought about it eventually.
But the second, you're talking about the second time
when we were on our trip last October.
Yeah, cause I was in your boat, Mike.
I saw it in 2017.
I did do the whole experience.
Right.
We did not do the whole experience in October.
Well, that's a spoiled story.
Here's how it played out.
The, so we're,
the park is closing pretty early.
It was a jam packed day in Universal Orlando.
It was October.
So that's Halloween Horror Nights.
So it was an oddly early closing time at 6 p.m.
So we're jamming a lot in and there was a time for me to see
cause I haven't been there in a really long time.
Just to be clear for Halloween Horror Nights now,
there's a Jimmy haunted maze
where you're just rustling hair of different dictators,
right?
Every room is just him fluffing Mussolini.
Oh yeah, Mussolini, Bolsonaro, like all the hits.
Taking that haunted house trope of the,
with the spaghetti being witches hair,
it's taking it to the next next logical step.
So we're jamming through the universal day,
but it's closing very soon.
And there's a lot of other stuff that we want to do.
And you guys were wanting to get to the Hulk.
At some point we lost Lindsay.
I don't remember why we lost Lindsay.
I think she wanted a coffee.
Oh sure.
Yes.
And one we've done.
She's like, I've done the Jimmy Fallon ride.
And hopefully her wanting coffee is not as controversial
as when she wanted cereal
and I wanted to watch her eat cereal
and not go on living with the lamb.
Hopefully this doesn't open up all other
food based problem for us.
I think if Jimmy Fallon was a 30 year old ride
and you stated that opinion now,
you would be in major trouble.
Sure, sure, sure.
Just because it's a time, I think the nostalgia factor
that people would like want your ass
for dissing Jimmy Fallon ride.
People might be nostalgic for this though,
or if you were 12 when it came out.
I don't want to get off side note here.
I watched the video to get ready for the episode
and I was like, you know what?
I've been inside a long time.
This would be pretty great right now
to go on the Jimmy Fallon ride.
Certainly.
But this feels like one of those attractions
that purists in particular dislike, right?
And I think mainly pure,
I'm not sure that the typical universal guest
dislikes this attraction.
I think it might be mainly a nerd audience
that is not so fond of it.
Right, but I think anyone listening to a theme park podcast
is unlikely to be a defender of Race Through New York
with Jimmy Fallon.
Are we starting, are we wading into the water?
I mean, Jason just cannonballed in already.
So I think we're fine.
I think we're okay here.
We're doing it on the second gate
because I think we don't really like the ride.
There's a reason this is behind a paywall.
Where it's safe, where nobody could ever use any of this
to career disadvantage for any of us.
It's fine.
But I think, I mean, this is probably,
is this the ride that stinks the most of corporate synergy?
Yes.
Just to begin, I think it's incredibly short sighted.
There's a reason a lot of shows,
rides aren't based on TV shows.
This comes up a lot
because they kind of like leave the public consciousness
pretty quickly.
Like movies stick around a lot longer.
This is the main thing I want to talk about with this ride.
I find that angle of it
significantly more interesting than the ride itself.
The sort of decision-making behind the ride
is stunning to me.
We're in like a Comcast branded building essentially.
Yeah.
It's literally very corporate.
Here, let me, before we keep diving,
let me continue the story of what happened to us.
So we lost Lindsay, we lost Erin, my wife,
because she at the time was pregnant.
And she had sat around while we went on the Mummy
and on Hagrid's and on Gringotts
and was not enthusiastic about the idea of this.
So she was like, I need to go on a fucking ride.
I'm going on E.T. to see all peace out.
And I like, well, that's a little short-sighted.
She's going to want to at least see the pre-show
and everything.
I guess.
Well, do what you got to do.
So we go in the building.
We do endure it.
We'll talk about all the things,
the lobby, the history of the Tonight Show,
and then the show that you watch.
But the main thing that I knew
and that made me confident that we could get on it
and I'd be back out,
maybe even had time to do something else,
was that they made a big deal out of the virtual queue
in this attraction.
And we've done Millennium Falcon Smugglers Run.
We know about virtual queues.
You don't have to stand in this line.
You get a color card and they call your color at some point.
And in the meantime,
you're hanging out in a cool NBC lounge.
Like you're waiting for a taping of the show.
You're in very good background.
Right?
This is like a Conan staring contest.
You're throwing things behind you.
I got a lot of them prepped.
There's a little bit of a Trump ruffle happening behind you.
So it's a virtual queue.
So this will be fine.
We're just, they're gonna just run through
a couple of colors.
And in the meantime,
we can enjoy some performances from the Ragtime Gals,
the barbershop quartet that are characters from the show
who do a little pre-show for you.
So we go in, we're watching the Ragtime Gals.
I think we're waiting for blue probably.
And then they perform Ice Ice Baby and Baby Got Back
and in a barbershop quartet fashion.
And we're like, okay.
And then your color is red.
Okay, probably the next one.
10 more minutes pass.
Your color is purple.
Still not.
And you feel like just the way it's set up,
you feel trapped essentially
because you overshot the entrance to the ride.
It was packed.
Like it was packed in there.
And I think the other thing was Mike and I had done it
before and the virtual queue had worked fine for us.
Like on separate trips, we're like, oh yeah,
there's probably one color they call before you.
And then you just wait.
I think also I insisted we get up front at the stage.
You did insist.
We were uncomfortably close to the Ragtime Gals,
which again is a group of singers.
It is a confusing setup because it's supposed to be
like barbershop quartet, but there is five of them
and a couple do play instruments while they sing.
I'm biting my tongue.
There's so much I wanna say about all these elements,
but I understand this is just table setting.
And like almost theme park performance,
like overwork underpaid of course, but doing their best.
I'm happy that they thought of a construct
to employ some singers and stuff.
I think that's good.
Just to fast forward, it's red.
It's purple, it's green.
We are nowhere close to blue.
The clock is ticking away.
I know that now my pregnant wife wasn't gonna go on a ride
in hours is in line for my favorite ride in the universe,
which I maybe will never get to go on again.
I say, fuck it, I can't do it anymore.
You guys are dying to get to the Hulk.
We run out of the place, we leave.
We do not go on this ride.
I have never been on this ride.
And in the meantime, there's a half hour left.
I text Erin, I can't do it anymore.
Where are you?
I'm in front of Botanicus.
She's literally waiting in the line in front of a robot,
a robot who helps bring us together.
When I took her, before we dated,
I took her to see the rotting corpse of LA Botanicus.
And she's there, we're carrying our child.
What am I doing wasting time with Jimmy Fallon?
I sprint across the park and then get in barely in time,
give her a big hug, pay homage to our pal Botanicus,
get a front row seat on the ride where E.T. at the very end,
because we're in the front row says goodbye, Erin, Scott.
And then Erin says, our name's clearly right after goodbye.
You know, they don't talk a lot about magic in Universal.
You know, Disney's where the magic is.
This was a magical Universal moment.
And I got to have it because I did not finish going on
race through New York.
You left out the part where E.T. goes,
Erin, you are with child?
What?
His name.
I think we all in that afternoon had our own E.T.
under the sliding like temple door to get the hat moments.
Because you did that, Mike, I believe you had to get
in a taxi to get to an NXT taping.
Right.
Yes, I went to see wrestling and I hopped in a Lyft
and like made it to full sail, which is about 45 minutes
away from Universal Orlando.
And I could take my time a little longer,
because yeah, I just wanted to get back and ride the whole
like in the, like as it was dark.
Well, the clock was ticking for me because I wanted to
ride the whole and then go to
the speed where they had like a death eater.
They had like wandering, like there was creepy lights
and there was like ghoulies like everywhere.
And so and as since I waited a little longer,
I saw even more barricade, like they're putting out
barricades like the purges about to break out because also
the purges about to break out for horror nights.
And that was when I had the high point probably
of this experience, there was one last parade
and everyone was standing around waiting for the parade
and going through the crowd, bothering people
was hashtag the panda.
And I was the one person happy to see,
I was like, hashtag, hashtag.
I'm like flagging them down.
I got a selfie, which we'll post.
And yeah, I was the one person in a crowd of people
like psych to see hashtag.
It is, you should mention your background on zoom right now.
Yeah, it is.
As generally a pretty good natured happy man,
but this is the happiest I've ever seen you look.
You look just serene.
You've never seen a happy person
until you've seen Jason Sheridan sucking the light,
like the life from Orlando and just radiating pure joy.
Well, we said that day,
the most, the happiest I've ever seen you for sure.
Cause I was more relaxed, I think than everyone else
because I had just checked into Cabana Bay.
So it didn't matter.
Like I could just walk anytime I was like done.
If I was too tired, I wanted to keep going.
Like I could just walk back to my hotel,
that Florida energy though.
Florida moisture gets in Jason's lungs
and it just gives him life.
For the first time in your life, you were level.
And then you saw a hashtag and hashtag brought you to Valhalla.
Oh, absolutely.
Maybe if you felt like hashtag picked you up
and threw you to the moon.
Yeah.
Well, and not to get ahead of ourselves,
but this is the thing I want to bring up.
I mean, who wouldn't have that reaction?
We all know and love the character, hashtag the Panda.
Yeah, of course.
Those are two facts.
Everyone knows him and everyone loves him.
Like Karnak was to Johnny Carson,
hashtag the Panda is to Jimmy Fallon.
We all, a staple of the show,
essentially the second host in a lot of ways.
Yes.
Yeah, I agree.
Can we start to dig into how fucked this ride is?
Yes, yes, yes, please.
Just to get us all on the same page,
have you been on this ride, Griff?
I have.
So the last time I went to Orlando was,
it was either October, November, 2017.
So this might've been the most recent ride to have opened
at either of the parks I went to.
I'm trying to think if there's anything I went on at Disney
that would have been newer than this.
Cause this, at this point was only six months old.
Right.
Things like the virtual queue,
I remember being pretty impressed by,
even though I definitely waited in that area
for longer than I should have.
I was like, this feels forward thinking.
The fact that I'm not standing in a line,
there are couches, we can sit,
we can play really, really mediocre cell phone games,
blown up to large tablet size.
Oh, is that what's on there?
I don't think I know what's on there.
Yeah, they're like, it's like, you know,
Frogger, but you're Jimmy trying to cross the street
or whatever the fuck.
It's like, yes, it's like mobile games
on like a sort of like pizzeria table arcade version
of Pac-Man, where it's like the screen is the table.
If you haven't been on this ride, you're in like the,
you enter a lobby that's a recreation
of 30 Rockefeller Center.
Knock this out quickly.
Cause I have so much to say about the lobby.
I don't want to breeze past the lobby.
I want to be positive and say,
I do really like the lobby.
Cause I am a sucker for like the history of television
and stuff.
I think when I initially heard this ride was happening,
that this was replacing Twister, I was like,
oh, I bet there'll be some tonight show stuff in there.
Maybe it'll get it a little closer to the old universal
about like, here's how TVs and movies are made.
And that is kind of true in the slimmest sense
because they also like, with the way it worked out for us,
I think we spent about a minute in that lobby.
And the lobby I think is the best part of this building.
I spent a fair amount of time there.
I went with my buddy, Scott Kraterman,
who is a PTR listener.
Hello, Scott.
And he is a hardcore Parks guy.
He goes several times a year.
His family has Disney timeshare.
He's currently on the edge of his seat,
waiting to see how quickly it's going to reopen
and how early he can be in the first batch of attendees,
both parks.
Well, no, but he's not a big universal fan.
And so I've gone to Orlando with Scott
and other friends, Sophie Fader, Lisa Malagari twice now.
And he always goes like, universal is just a day.
We're just going to do it really quickly.
It's not as good.
And most of the time we're there.
I hope he doesn't mind me saying this.
He just goes like, it's not the same.
It doesn't have the magic.
There's not the same level of detail.
There's not the same level of craft.
And I feel like Scott and I share a lot of opinions
on Jimmy Fallon in general.
We were talking a lot about how insane this ride was
before it opened.
And then we go there right after it opens.
I think this was the second time Scott had been
in Universal Orlando in the six months since it had opened.
And he was like, Griffin, we're not doing it.
And I was like, we have to.
So I kind of bent our one universal day
around forcing everyone to go on this ride
because I was so perversely obsessed with it.
But I did go on it.
I had a lot of time in the waiting area.
I rode the shit out of it.
I had to sit with a lot of people who were very mad at me
for having them go through it.
So that's my-
The worst Deep Park feeling, like when you've corralled,
feeling Mike knows maybe better than anybody.
Right.
And I had to sort of say to them,
do you not understand that's the point?
Do you not understand that's why I wanted us all
to go on this?
And they said, I don't care. It's hot.
My feet are tired.
Yes. Yeah.
That does make ironic encounters are tougher
when the weather sucks and you're exhausted.
Yes. That was, we had a couple of things in my,
well, one, this was probably the hottest day or the cold.
I think this was the coldest day of the week we were there
or the five days we were there.
So that was like, I just remember it being like very chilly
when I came out of this.
And then the other thing was I think Griffin,
we had already said like, well,
we'll have to have you on for Jimmy Fallon
behind the paywall.
So we're like, well, we should go do it together.
And yet it didn't happen.
Well, too much barbershop.
I thought if there had only been 10 minutes of barbershop,
I would have done it.
I will say, and correct me if I'm wrong.
We tried, that's actually the story you told us,
the second attempt.
We tried it earlier.
Oh, I forgot.
We tried it earlier in the day and they were just like,
we're not taking any more people right now.
Oh yeah. We just got denied at the door.
Like it was a taping that sold out.
Yeah. And it wasn't even, they were like,
we were shut down.
They were just like, we're not taking people.
It was like unclear.
And we're like, well, are you gonna be taking people soon?
And they're like, we were not sure.
And we're like, okay.
How is this more efficient?
How is this possibly more efficient
than just standing in a line?
Well, this is the thing.
For me, it felt like, oh, even though I'm waiting,
perhaps the same amount of time,
this feels futuristic because I'm not on a line.
There's some sort of organization.
There are things to do.
There's a performance happening, the ragtime gals.
Like this is what Q should be like.
But then, since then, things like Galaxy's Edge have opened,
which by all accounts are more organized.
I have not gotten to go on them.
This is still the most futuristic ride
I have probably gotten to go on as of this moment.
The Millennium Falcon Q is,
I would even argue, maybe too fast.
I feel like I never have quite enough time
to walk around the little lobby
or whatever you'd call it on the Millennium Falcon.
But they are very much-
Yeah, I could go for one more group every time.
Yeah, and that's what tricked me.
I think I just thought that lobby with the show
is going to be Millennium Falcon.
And it was not that.
And that's not their fault.
Because maybe there should be a balance.
It does feel like, I think if we wanna say something nice,
the pre-ride elements of this ride
are better than the ride itself.
Yeah.
In reality, if you were waiting 10 to 15 minutes
in that area, you would go, this is pretty effective.
Yes. Sure, yeah.
And it's a very nice room.
All of it is.
The lobby, as we said, the outside is nice.
I think everybody likes that it makes sense
in the New York area as opposed to Twister,
which never related to anything.
And if you were like- Another faint compliment.
You have to give this ride.
That it makes sense geographically within the park.
It is about New York and it's in a New York part.
If you were like a nerdy kid, like I think like all of us,
and like kind of fetishized 30 Rock,
because you watch Saturday Night Live,
and then you kind of get to go in the building
that sort of looks like it.
I do think it's pushing some buttons in your brain of like,
oh, this looks, this is right.
This feels right.
And if you've been there,
and I've been there once or twice.
I would have been that kid big time for sure.
Cause I was, yeah, I toured 30 Rock when I was 13.
And like you had to drag me out of every room.
I was so excited to be, yeah, you're like,
we should not discount.
There are those people who this is probably
their favorite thing for that reason.
Now I want to say this, if I can just split this hair.
I was a huge SNL kid,
big sort of history of entertainment kid.
I remember doing the 30 Rock tour probably when I was 10
and just loving it, being in hog heaven.
I do live in New York, born and raised,
have lived there my entire life.
So if you just tell me off the bat,
the ride is a race through New York,
I immediately go, doesn't sound that exciting to me.
Even if this ride is going to do things
that I can't do in my daily life,
every other ride I've ever gone on is promising a place
that is physically impossible to go to, right?
If only through the level of stylization
or the time period or the elements going on around it.
This feels like the most grounded ride
in terms of what they're promising you in the name,
let's say.
It obviously goes some wilder places.
And then you add onto that,
30 Rock is a very impressive building.
It's a beautiful looking building.
It has all this history within it.
At this point in my life,
and I'm very aware this is a humble brag,
at this point in my life,
walking through a very detailed recreation
of the lobby and waiting areas of 30 Rock
just makes me feel like I'm going in for an audition.
There's something about this ride
that triggers anxiety for me.
I was gonna ask this exactly,
if it like stressed you out to be in that building.
Absolutely, and it is absolutely a point of privilege
on my end,
but 30 Rock has become increasingly mundane
over the years for me,
only because of the amount of horrible pilots
I have had to audition for
that rejected me out of hand in that building.
So there's some kind of bad Pavlovian response.
As much as I appreciate,
I think it is a pretty perfect replica.
I will say like walking through it,
it looks pretty identical.
And even the cheats around the size of it
are pretty seamlessly done.
The floor, it's a very good floor.
Let me give that big praise.
Great floor. Great floor.
But when I'm in that waiting area,
I do have the feeling of like,
fuck, did I forget to print out my sides?
I do have that little.
See, you're just gonna get that.
That's a New York LA divide
because all our casting offices out here
are in unmarked strip malls
or very marked buildings next to salad restaurants
that don't take cash for some reason.
I'll say this though,
like the rare times I have been in LA
and gotten to do an audition like on a studio lot.
That still feels pretty cool.
Yeah, it's still some magical.
Yeah.
Sure.
But my experience, I took the 30 Rock Tour,
I think it was a little old,
I was like 13 or 14 and I thought it was great.
I really liked it.
I got a Conan shirt at the gift shop that I still have.
And in the gift shop, you got to do,
there was a green screen,
like you got to do a Conan desk bit.
You got to do the desk.
The desk goes through 30 Rock.
Oh, the driving the desk, yeah.
Driving the desk.
Driving the, like that was it.
That's one of my big things with this ride is like,
wait, that green screen thing,
which was just like, do you wanna buy a VHS of that now?
Like that was more fun.
This ride, like, just stay in 30 Rock.
Just take us through the history of television.
I mean, maybe the licensing would be insane on that.
Wait, you want it to be about the history of television?
The building or the-
I agree with Jason.
It leaves, you get out of the historic,
interesting building so quickly.
Like you get out of 30 Rock so quickly.
Jason, my thought, if, let me tell you,
if this is what you're talking about, let me know.
Because my thought, and I don't wanna get to the full,
my thought is I wanna see all the Tonight Show hosts
in this ride.
Well, you know the kids,
want more Jack Parr.
They love Parr.
They love Steve Allen.
That's what I, I mean, there was some stuff
I was legitimately excited about in this lobby.
One, the Karnak hat.
The Karnak hat is there.
That's great.
Mike and I used to do this very stupid bit
that I tried to get into like variety shows at UCB
that no one was ever interested in
called Baskin-Robbins Karnak,
where I put a Baskin-Robbins bag on my head
and the things in the punch lines
are just different Baskin-Robbins flavors.
Doesn't make a lick of sense.
But so I was very excited to see the real Karnak hat.
I was also thrilled that they were playing Jay Leno clips
on a big CRT TV.
That I think is so funny.
Well, and we have to talk about the best part of this area,
which is the Conan closet.
The Conan closet.
I'll give Aaron credit for dubbing it that.
All four of us must've had the same thought
walking into the building,
which is how are they gonna handle Conan?
Yeah, which they, you know, and to be fair,
he gets as much space as Steve Allen or Jack Parr, I believe.
It's not like a, especially diminutive.
It's not like Leno has this big shelf
and then you have to go through a doggy door to see Conan.
Or it's like shorter.
They do honor it.
They do give him some space.
But it is so, seeing 2009 to 2010 on top of that
is so heartbreaking.
Knowing that 2010 was only a month also.
Right.
And then also looking at the,
there's the Leno part of it,
where it's like, his thing is huge.
And then it says, whatever, it says like 1991 to 2009.
And then it says like, comma, 2011 to 2016.
Who's the president with the non-consecutive terms?
It's that.
Or like one of these Billy Martin with the Yankees,
like with all the stops and starts of what years he did.
I'm looking at it now.
The Leno thing is huge.
The Leno is the size of like eight Conan's
and it says J Leno parentheses, 1992 to 2009,
ampersand 2010 to 2014.
Like even if the Conan closet still exists,
it does feel like that is messaging.
Look, there was one little bump in the road,
but we wish we could say 1992 to 2014.
You can't not, like, I think they do present him
with as much class as they can,
but it still just feels, yeah, that like,
it was some asterisk, it was some mistake,
which is so weird,
because I think any history that makes it his fault
is stupid.
But I think they try their best, but I did see,
now I don't remember the source of this.
I don't know if this is official universal literature,
but if it is, shame on them.
Listen to this, that in this lobby,
quote, it's an area that pays tribute to Steve Allen,
Jack Parr, Johnny Carson, J Leno, even Conan O'Brien.
Wow. Even.
No, damn that even.
That is such a mean word.
But no, but that's perfect.
It does feel like the way they treat Conan O'Brien
in this waiting area is, it's with the energy of,
see, we did it.
Are you happy?
It's an impression.
We could have dissed him.
We didn't even have to do this.
We didn't have to put him in there.
We didn't even have to do it.
It's very, that's spot on.
That's the energy.
You wouldn't- We took gold lettering.
We'd have nice flits.
So gold, we put his name in gold.
What more do you want?
You wouldn't think he was with the network for 20 years.
So long and incredibly long time.
And then there's that sort of photo mural
where it's like the five or six of them in a row,
like Steve Allen, Parr, Carson, Leno, Conan, and then Jimmy.
And that mural doesn't have the years on it.
So it just makes it look like it's just,
here's the lineage, here's how it gets passed.
And that one almost feels not intentionally
more insulting to Conan's legacy
because they're acting like there was
a proper respectable handoff from Jay to Conan
and then from Conan to Jimmy.
Right. They just did him so dirty.
I know. And they still are doing him dirty
with that even word, God.
I know. Yeah, jeez.
I wish that mural had two Js.
I wish it was just Conan sandwiched
between two different Js.
Jay too.
I wish there was some exhibit somewhere
that tributed all the hosts of the Jay Leno show.
So many, so many.
I wish. All the grits.
And then we could see the car from the green car challenge.
Yes.
My favorite, there's a lot of pictures of Jay
and they're all stuff,
I think we've seen some of these promo images.
The most interesting one though
is they picked a picture of Jay brushing a tiger.
Can't see that with the background,
but he's just brushing a tiger.
And it's like, was that one of his famous bits?
He loved those animals, Jay.
Do you remember how he had two characters?
One was used video effects to make his,
the top of his head very big,
like he had a big smart brain.
And then the other character made the bottom
of his head very big.
So his chin was even bigger and he was a bodybuilder.
That's what I, like early Leno had two characters.
One was a big head, one was a big chin.
Let me talk about range.
Wow.
You guys have any of those like favorite Leno bits
rattling around in your brain?
Cause I remember one like,
oh, he did, it was a, it was a sigh parody.
It was a open denim style.
Open, open denim style.
It's not M, I don't know what the, what the hell the word was.
It was open cause he wears the first button or two.
Oh, for him it was open.
It was open denim style.
Yeah.
And they, and they, even though he, that's not like,
they don't have to put his head on like a,
basically they comp his head onto just a dancer's body.
Even though that dance is not that hard to do,
you could just do, but he like,
so was too lazy to do the dance.
So it's a weird head comp bit.
Coming from Jay Leno also sounds like a threat.
Like I swear to God, if you don't start behaving,
I'm going to open denim style and reveal more of my clammy
chest flesh to you.
Stuck under this famously unbreathable Canadian tuxedo.
I wish when he came back, he did the show in the denim.
Oh, me too.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah. That would have been great.
I do like that Jay Leno's garage, he's in the denim.
And I think the one thing I wish was in this lobby
was the get back to where you once belong commercial.
When he returned.
Yeah.
Yes. They made a night where he's driving back
to the tonight show in a cool car.
Get back to where you once belong.
He belonged there.
Yeah.
It's like, you, you listen to,
I don't know if you guys heard Jay Leno's WTF,
but a true like sociopathic level of deflection
where he just kept on being like, I like Conan.
I got nothing against Conan.
You know, if there's a job, they offer you a job.
What are you going to do?
Don't take the job.
That doesn't help the other guy keep the job.
You know, either I took it or I didn't take it.
It didn't matter either way that we're going to find it.
Like all this sort of like deflection, but he, he,
he's so big on the, like, look, I wasn't happy.
You know, I wanted Conan to succeed, but I was number one.
I mean, maybe they shouldn't have fired me, you know,
all this sort of stuff.
And then the arrogance of that commercial in which he's just
sort of coolly looking at the camera and nodding and smiling
as get back to where you once belonged plays.
It does speak to this like sort of sense of like,
I am the king and finally my reign has been acknowledged.
Like where is the way there's,
I want to see that secret Leno.
I want to see the one video that reveals the dark side
where there are some tape of a phone call
where he does what you know is there.
Just like shut him down.
And this is what's crazy about Leno.
And I feel like we have to talk about this as we're going to
dig more and more into Jimmy of what I'm sure is now on
track to become a seven hour episode with all the things we
promised. We need to find a me if we need a lunch break,
you know, do we got to do it?
Like in terms of interpersonal behavior,
you never hear any bad stories about Jay Leno.
You never hear any bad stories about Jay Leno.
You hear the stories about him,
like out Foxing Letterman and Conan for the job,
but he's one of those guys where it's just like so nice to
fans, so nice to his entire crew, pays them bonuses,
negotiates for them to get higher salaries.
He was like the first guy I think during the,
the whatchamacallit, the writer's strike,
who was like, I'm paying my entire staff out of pocket.
Like he does a lot of shit that's really commendable.
And I feel like he raises a lot of money for charity.
He does a lot of charity events.
Like there's all this weird shit about him.
Like famously the fact that he's apparently never touched
a single dime of his tonight show money
and lives entirely off of touring money.
He has no children and no one knows what he's saving
that money for.
Presumably to build an arc, you know,
for when like the world collapses two weeks from now
and he can sail safely.
A Studebaker shaped Elysium.
Right.
With two of every car.
Two of every car, yeah.
But he is one of those guys who are like,
everyone who's had personal experience with him
tends to say like, look, I'm not a fan of him,
but I have to say he's a pretty nice, decent guy.
Yeah.
Does the, have I said on the show that I, two things.
One, I met him as a child.
Wow.
Because I, there was a family friend
who worked in the music department
and I got to go around and take a tour and we met him.
And I had with me in the hopes that that might've happened,
my autograph book from my recent trip to Disney world.
So, and he's flipping through it
and it's all character signatures.
And he says like, yeah, look at this.
That's me right next to Tigger.
Which was me as a child.
Oh my God.
What a crazy moment.
Talking about Disney stuff.
And then also, boy, we talk about all this video of stuff
that Jason is in.
And this isn't a big deal
cause you can't see my face in it.
But as a nine year old,
I was in a Leno Tonight Show bit
from that same connection.
Yeah.
What?
Really?
But you wouldn't, it's not,
I don't want to build it up too much because I'll,
when we post it on Twitter, I'll have to just circle it
so that you know, that's how you know it's me.
Because it is a Halloween sketch.
I'm a trick or treater.
And I, you got to pick your own costume.
And I chose, I was even like, he'll appreciate this
because he likes politics.
Maybe he'll even comment on it in the bit.
And I wore a mask of Richard Nixon.
So I am, and I'm in a little suit.
So I'm a little Richard Nixon in a 1994 or three,
I forget, Leno bit.
And they didn't tell us what the bit was going to be
in any way because we didn't really have anything to do.
And there was never time to rehearse it or run it.
So it was just that we're trick or treaters at a door.
We walk out and he starts giving us candy.
And then you hear from the side of the stage,
stop the insanity.
And you know that phrase,
that's the phrase of the famous workout health person,
Susan Powder, right?
Remember Susan Powder?
Yes.
Who was like a short haired lady who said,
stop the insanity.
And she gave us health food bars instead of candy.
And that was the sketch.
And I didn't get a candy bar in the sketch.
And you could see me gesture to Susan Powder,
do I get one?
And I did not.
Wow.
So I look for that on Twitter soon.
Oh my God, that's a big,
you're downplaying it, but that sounds pretty great.
It's pretty, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I am pretty, that's,
I revealed my other favorite tape in my family collection.
My dad on the news being upset about gas prices.
And now there's, this will have exhausted my VHS collection.
Wow.
That's pretty big.
So look for that soon.
Anyway, that's my Leno interaction.
But as to bring it back to your point,
to me, a little child who really liked Jay Leno,
he was very, very nice and sweet to me.
And I just want to underline this one thing.
As I feel like has become more and more publicly known
in the last couple months and even years,
most talk show hosts have reputations behind the scenes,
very, very different from their public facing personas.
I am not sub tweeting any one person.
I'm saying it seems to be a profession wide characteristic.
You're not sub tweeting any one woman,
any one daytime host.
You're not sub tweeting, there's no one in particular.
It certainly applies there, okay?
It certainly applies there.
But also like Letterman,
who was known for being like kind of a crank,
was then known to be even more cranky and unpersonable,
you know, with his staff,
unless he was being too personal with his staff.
Conan is known as being a very intense guy, you know?
Like Matt Letterman was-
Very nice, very nice good guy, I will certainly say that.
But like, you know, an opinionated, like,
he's easy because he has opinions
because he cares and he wants comedy to be good.
And that's the only place that ever-
Right, right.
A great guy, awesome guy.
But it is, I think he himself would admit,
like he plays a much goofier version of himself
in front of the cameras and off camera.
He is very serious and sort of focused
and intense about the job.
That's why I think the remote,
the travel shows are so good
and the podcast is so good because he's like,
more the real him.
He's like weirder, judgier, crankier and funnier.
Totally.
Now all of this to say,
I have never heard anything about Jimmy Fallon
that is explicitly cancelable.
So I don't want people to think
that I am talking around some knowledge I have,
but it is pretty widely known
that Jimmy Fallon is pretty fundamentally different
from quote unquote Jimmy Fallon of The Tonight Show.
Is that fair to say?
You see, you might know more than us,
but say maybe as a part of being a New York person
and know New York comedy people more.
I mean, I know a lot of people who have worked on that show.
We both, we've all had multiple guests on our podcast
who either- Yes, now we have.
Or later went on to work with him.
From the time we announced,
maybe we should do a Fallon episode.
They've hired three of our friends,
who I think are having a pretty okay time.
They don't fucking work in New York,
so they haven't met him.
So I got nothing from about Jimmy from them.
But because we're gonna talk about,
we must talk about Jimmy Fallon as a talk show host
and his quality in that area
in order to talk about that ride.
Let me make it clear.
He hires some of the funniest people in the business.
He hires really, really good people.
His writers rooms have been pretty consistently incredible
since he started.
The 80 Miles who's in the ride,
I think we all love from Wet Hot and various other things.
I mean, yeah, he's made us laugh a ton.
Arguably the second lead of the ride, all over the ride.
True, multiple characters, yeah.
Yeah, kind of not doing those characters
by the time the ride came out,
kind of like stepping away, I believe, from the show.
Yes.
2018 or 2017 or so.
One of the many things that underlines
why this ride was a bad idea
is the lack of permanence to a late night talk show.
Yes.
Yeah.
That's the whole thing feels like locked in whenever,
was it 2016 or 15?
I don't remember when it opened.
It opens in 17.
It opens early. Oh, 17.
April 17.
So it opens like six months after the hair ruffle.
And.
Oh, I didn't realize that.
Jesus Christ.
So the tide's turning a little.
That's what's important.
I think it's really important
to frame this ride around that.
Yeah, yeah.
Because that's viewed as the,
it's the inverse of the Leno Hugh Grant.
The Tonigras always have these important moments
that seal the deal or unseal the deal.
And he was the king of nice and everybody loves it.
And then in Trump world, he ruffles Trump's hair.
And ever since then, people view him as like,
not being a hard ass on politics
and that's not really his comfort zone.
It's just all been weird.
And then I feel like during quarantine,
he's the show we like again,
because he's just having fun
and we just want to be cheered up.
But then Black Lives Matter and everything.
And now he once again is like,
not really equipped to handle the moment.
It's like so back and forth.
I mean, we'll get into this an hour five of the episode.
There's a lot to unpack here.
Jason, you seem like you're burning up to make some point.
Well, I was gonna say like,
in the scheme of our history,
of podcast, the ride history,
we started recording a few months after this ride started.
But in the larger scheme of theme park history,
this ride opens and on the West Coast,
kind of within the same one, two month range,
Guardians of the Galaxy opens, which is great.
And I think we were,
I was immediately impressed by probably the,
maybe one of the best screens in a ride.
Yeah.
Maybe the best screen.
Maybe the best.
And replacing a more beloved attraction.
So had a hurdle to overcome Guardians, I mean.
And then on the East Coast,
like this is what Universal rolled out in 2017.
What did Disney roll out in Orlando in 2017?
Pandora, the world of avatars.
Yes.
Wow. Very good context.
Great context.
But also Mission Breakout
is a really interesting comparison point
because the thing that impressed me most with that ride,
which I went on finally for the first time about a year ago,
is that it is funny.
That it is consistently funny.
That it has actual jokes that succeed on a thrill ride.
Like being on Guardians and hearing people laugh
in between screams,
I was like, I did not think this was possible.
That you could engage a ride audience this way
and be able to make them laugh
in the middle of a thrill ride.
Whereas if nothing else,
race through New York should be funny, right?
That should be their pitch.
Is this is gonna be the funniest ride ever.
I mean, that in theory is the competitive advantage
you would get basing a ride,
not around an animated family film,
not around an action adventure film franchise,
but around a personality based late night comedy show.
In theory, the competitive advantage would be jokes, right?
Yeah, you would, yes.
You would think, and what ends up happening, I think,
is that anything that's like a line that would be funny
is said in the same manner that I think
of the Patton Oswalt joke about when he does like ADR
or adds jokes to animated movies,
where he just writes jokes that happen off screen
that are thrown away.
Like just lines that come out,
you can barely hear them and you're not sure
and they don't land at all.
Jammed into less than a second.
Really quick and alts.
The ride is so cacophonous.
And Universal is known for like screams
where you can get like there's laughs to release the tension.
That is the thing that like in books about Universal,
they talk about J-Pops, which are these,
the feeling of like you're scared and then everyone laughs.
Everyone shares a collective laugh
because you release the tension.
Named after Jay Stein, one of the early Universal,
the head of Universal at the time, I think,
when the first, when the Florida park opened.
But like that-
But yes, that was conventionally a strength of theirs.
Yeah, that's a different thing though.
You need it to be really intense
and then you scare them with like a spray of water and stuff.
I'm pretty sure there's a spray of water in this ride.
I can't remember.
I watched the ride through like five times
and I just had to write it, the sequence down
because it just was not sticking in my memory.
It's really confusing.
We, I showed a ride through to Erin
since she didn't get to go on it.
And she just kind of stared at it.
And like, I couldn't tell you one thing that happens.
It's just such a weird, it's all moving so quickly,
which could seem like in conceiving it,
they might feel like, and then you're over here
and then you're over here and then you're over here.
And that's a good thing.
But I think it just adds up into,
I don't really know what that was.
It was just too much with no like beats and pauses.
It's a lot of characters showing up,
saying their catchphrase and then like,
they're kind of blurry because it's moving so fast
and then they're off screen.
And that sort of doesn't really work
with like more fleeting late night comedy character.
Like as you said, it's kind of like constantly changing
or forgotten about.
It's not the same as like Arnold Schwarzenegger
showing up as the Terminator and saying, I'll be back.
Well, like a building blows up
and the whole audience drops, you know?
Or even if they had, sorry, I keep jumping.
Even if they had, imagine if there was a ride
of Saturday Night Live in like recurring character prime
in 1993 and there's a ride where you meet Wayne's world
and Hans and Franz and Church Lady and everybody.
Like they would sort of, you kind of register
who each of them were.
Because I've seen all of these people five times or so.
Late night characters, you just don't know as much.
And then these characters,
I don't think they use a lot of them a lot.
There's a moment that I think kind of encapsulates
what doesn't work for me about this, right?
When he whizzes by a guy and he says, tight pants,
tight as not land.
And then you just keep moving.
And I know what tight pants was.
I know that's a bit he did with Will Ferrell,
but when did he do it?
And do they still do it?
And did that really land?
Does the audience know what tight pants is?
So just to be tossing off all the,
it's like you're watching a time capsule
of a late night show during one particular week years ago.
And then it's all nonsense.
Like if it was shows just like,
hey, look, it's a senior strawberry.
Okay, gotta go.
But wait, who's senior strawberry?
That's, do they do that anymore?
Yeah, you don't.
Just reads as nonsense.
You don't get it.
You would think it would get a beat
to show the audience the magic of tight pants.
Get teachers who are tight pants is.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, the Snapchat snake, look out.
This is the infinity war of Jimmy Fallon characters.
We wanna actually at least get a little moments
and appreciate them more than just kind of waving at them
and going by.
Can we zoom out for a second?
Of course.
I have some bigger points I wanna get to,
but I feel like we need to lay a little runway
to get to them.
I feel like this ride is very much the byproduct
of a thing you guys have talked about a lot on your show,
which is universal sort of like,
we need to look at everything in our portfolio
and take acts, make the most,
like use every part of the buffalo,
in some way incorporate our access
to everything that is valuable.
So I feel like this born stunt show
that's about to open whenever anything is able
to open again.
Oh, it's open.
It's open now?
Yeah, it's open.
It officially opened earlier this week,
end of June as we record this.
That is insane.
Yes.
That is absolutely insane.
There's no better place though to catch the virus
than in a brand new theme park attraction.
No, they can give you some chems
to neutralize the effect of the virus.
I assume the born stunt show is mostly about
the born legacy, right?
The Jeremy Renner film,
it's all about him injecting himself with chems.
Yes, the longest worst one.
That's right.
I'm hearing it's great by the way.
Yeah, the show is supposed to be amazing.
We are hearing a lot of good things
and podcast ride will cover it in seven years.
A really long time.
Absolutely sure it is great,
but it's also one of those things where when I feel like,
I feel like when it got announced,
everyone said, is anyone asking for that?
And even in the days that it was circling as a rumor,
like when Matt Rogers said on your show,
like I have it on good authority,
everyone was like, is there any demand for that?
Well, Jason was the one who was excited.
I am the one.
I love those movies.
The only way I could have been more excited
is if they said, it's gonna be a now you see me stunt show.
Which honestly-
Which I'll say, makes a little more sense
because there's a franchise based around performance
and stunts and live audience interaction.
Huge popular internationally.
Then now you see me movies.
They get a lot of international tourists.
Yes.
Wow, I get to see Arthur Tressler today.
It's my favorite pal from the movies, Arthur Tressler.
Arthur Tressler.
Henry Reeves.
I just, I feel like there's something
that sort of binds together the Fallon ride,
the Bourne stunt show and the secret life of Pets ride,
which is just universal,
not looking at anything other than recent numbers
and being like, if we have something that's popping,
it is a waste to not be putting it in the parks
without that much thought of how long
that demand is gonna last
or whether or not it's a good fit for a theme park.
Where even though like, who knows?
Maybe the Bourne stunt show will end up
being the next water world
and will take on a life of its own
and will become valuable in a way
that grows way past the movies.
But I do think, hmm, that's a franchise
that does not have a lot of iconography,
that is mostly known for its central performance
by a humongous movie star.
And it's very, very specific filmmaking sensibility
from Paul Greengrass,
which you're not gonna be able to replicate
in a live stunt show.
It is terse, it is sort of like spare,
it's stripped down,
it's very like muscular kind of filmmaking.
It's not something that translates that much
in my mind's eye to a stunt show.
And I am fully ready to believe
that the stunt show works on its own.
But it has the same kind of timing
of the Secret Life of Pets ride opening
right after the second movie greatly underperforms
because now you have a Bourne stunt show
where Universal, when they talk about it,
they say, look, it's a billion dollar franchise.
And apparently that was the initiative.
They said, if anything has made a billion dollars for us
and it's not in the parks, we need to reassess that.
We need to find some way to put it in for us.
And so Bourne, they go, that's a billion franchise.
But you're discounting the fact
that the last most recent Bourne movie
was the lowest grossing Bourne movie,
I believe even lower grossing than the Jeremy Renner one,
the one where Matt Damon returned was another dip.
And then they did a Bourne TV show
and that also got canceled within one season.
And then you time that out to the Jimmy Fallon ride
which comes out six months after he ruffles Trump's hair.
And it just kind of shows like there is a sort of
protectiveness and long-term thinking
to most installations in a theme park,
be they a full ride, be they a live show,
be they even putting a costumed character in there
where there really seems to be some forward thinking of like,
how long is this gonna stay in people's good graces?
And when it evaporates, is the thing still gonna have value
on its own even if this particular brand
dwindles a little bit?
Yes, I mean, that's completely true.
I think that Universal, to give them a little credit,
has been building faster.
I think a lot of times, except for Guardians,
Disney takes a long time to make something,
like Star Wars Land took forever
and they threw out plans.
And I guess the good thing about Universal,
it does seem like they're willing to pull the trigger
on something, but perhaps it's not all gonna be Nintendo Land,
which I assume is something that will,
Nintendo is gonna be popular for the rest of our lives.
I can't imagine a scenario where that's not gonna be fun
to see Mario, but-
And I think-
It's part and parcel with the too many screens complain
about Universal, because you have to think
that part of that is giving themselves the back door,
the modularity, how easy it is for them to re-theme things,
that it's just about filming with the actual actors.
Really, I love it.
For whatever is popular that year.
That's where this ride slots in in my memory.
And I do have to correct myself by the way,
the term is J-Bangs, not J-Pops.
Oh boy. Anyway,
what I was starting to say, this ride slots in with me,
I think there is a run of Universal rides,
of screen-based rides that are not going to age well.
And I lump this in with this,
Fast and Furious, just out the gate people,
were not big on.
I don't think Simpsons is gonna age well,
and Transformers either.
Like the screen looks worse and worse on Transformers
as the years go on.
And I wanna say I am not anti like big screen,
because I love Despicable Me, Minion Mayhem.
I think it's delightful.
I think it's got a heartwarming message.
It's nice.
It's a nice ride.
Love it.
Because I am always the one who's like,
well, what do we do now?
Well, we go on Minion Mayhem.
I think it's fun.
That said, I think part of the thing,
Universal's baggage that they have to deal with,
is that from the start of the Orlando park,
I mean, at the time they were owned by MCA,
and then they were owned by Seagrams,
and then they were owned by Vivendi,
and then they were owned by GE,
and then Comcast.
Like it's just a string of ownerships.
And I think that probably contributes to some of like
the confusing decisions.
Certainly the tourism downturn after 9-11
affected a lot of projects.
And this one is especially odd.
I think you are right in there,
just going through the portfolio and see what they have.
But if you go-
Well, it's like the Today Show Cafe.
It's like, people love the Today Show,
look at these ratings, why wouldn't we make a cafe?
And it's like, because people watching the Today Show
does not equate to them wanting to eat an omelet there.
It's not a walk that people are making.
It's Mr. Show coupon the movie.
Everybody used the coupon, why aren't they seeing the movie?
Right, and the Fallon ride is a perfect example
of that for me, where it's like,
look, he's not my guy, but I know people like him.
I know there are people who love that show.
I don't know what the overlap is between the people
who love that show and love theme parks.
And even if you get to that overlap in the Venn diagram,
I don't know the people who are begging them
to combine those two things.
Sure, yeah.
I think there's a big,
I might not have the right words here.
There's a difference between things being popular
and money makers and entering the hearts of the public
or entering, like what's the word,
public consciousness or, I don't know,
which I think is what Disney is so concerned with.
Like what they need, they're not gonna put a ride in,
usually, unless they really feel like people have fallen
in love with these characters in this world
and they'll wait a long time to make sure
that they feel like that's happened significantly enough.
I feel like Minions and Guardians are two examples
of rides that got done pretty quickly
that were correct calls.
I think in both of those cases,
those were fundamentally correct calls
and these things seem to have firmly entrenched themselves
in pop culture.
Who knows how people are gonna feel 20 years from now,
but Groot feels like a fairly safe investment.
The Minions themselves feel like a fairly safe investment.
They didn't need to wait for six of those movies.
They didn't need to wait for the 20th anniversary
to make sure it was still sticking around.
It feels like those things were properly judged.
And even something like Avatar,
I am very much with Mike and being an Avatar defender.
I know people like to say it's insane
they invested this much money in this movie
that everyone's already forgotten.
You haven't forgotten it.
You keep on bringing it up.
If you had forgotten it,
you wouldn't keep on trying to make the point
that people have forgotten it.
But it is one of those things where the world of Pandora
works on its own.
Like it is an impressive theme park attraction.
People who have never seen the movie
can enjoy everything that happens there.
The banality of even if it is an important building
in show business history,
and even if New York City is a very glamorous city,
or at least portions of it are pre-pandemic,
it still feels like we're finally now our state of the art,
our team at Universal,
they're putting the greatest minds, the greatest resources,
millions and millions and millions of dollars
into recreating a building in Midtown Manhattan,
where you're going to be able to experience
being in the audience of a TV show taping.
And as Jason says, the way to do this feels
a little bit more like the way they use Jimmy Fallon
on the studio tour,
where it's like Fallon just wants to be America's best friend.
He wants to be the guy who's like the happy fun time guy,
who's impossible to dislike
and is just excited about everything.
And that persona can map pretty easily onto him doing
a handful of videos on the studio tour,
where he's walking you through the magic of movies
and how things are made different.
And now he's a Western guy, and now he's a sailor or whatever.
And I like the tour videos,
having worked there and suffered through
the Whoopi Goldberg material,
the Jimmy Fallon overlay I think is a vast improvement.
And I also just feel like that's using Fallon
to some greater end and also sort of weaponizing
what he's good at.
They don't re-theme it as the Jimmy Fallon tour.
It's the studio tour featuring Jimmy Fallon,
whereas this ride is the Jimmy Fallon ride.
It may be called Race Through New York,
starring Jimmy Fallon, but the entire thing
is built around his persona, him as a brand,
and by extension, the brand of his show,
which I think we've all been sort of talking around.
The show does not have much of an identity at all
removed from whoever his guest is at that moment.
I feel like when I,
cause I wanna make it clear,
I'm not like trying to imply that Jimmy Fallon
is a serial killer who has bodies stashed in his basement.
I don't feel like there's some reckoning coming
for Jimmy Fallon, but everyone I know
who's worked on that show has sort of said like,
yeah, he's not like this super happy, fun, loving,
like super amenable guy that is very much a persona.
That is the show he wants to do.
It is like he is like a children's TV show host.
He wants to be friendly.
He wants to be positive and enthusiastic about everything.
But in real life, he's like, oh, that's so bad.
He wants it all.
He's like Garfield in real life.
When he was starting doing the show,
his first show, the Conan show,
I was like, oh, it's like Regis does impressions.
Yes.
Wait, you mean on late night
when he took over the previous, the 1230?
Which I liked, I liked the 1230 show more.
I agree, that's what I said too at the time.
I was like, well, it's not being like as subversive
or weird maybe as Conan,
but it's kind of a straight ahead variety show.
That's very poppy and full of music and genre parody.
I might say that I specifically liked the show.
And obviously late night with Conan
was more my comedy sensibility, but I like,
they did something different.
They went a different direction
and are getting a whole new audience and updating it.
And I think they did it successfully.
My immediate takeaway was like,
I still don't think I would have picked Jimmy Fallon
to host this.
I'm not a huge fan of him as a host,
but this show is well produced.
Like on a basic level, you're like,
it's cool that the roots are the musical backing band.
Yeah, they're great.
And incorporate them into the show and the set is cool
and it has a good vibe.
And he hired good writers and A.D. Miles.
The thing had a kind of cool sense of style to it.
But I feel like more so than you look at Letterman
or you look at Conan in particular,
and I just, every time I engage
with any element of this ride,
I think about Conan because it feels like this ride
is Fallon wishing his show had the type of reputation
and relationship that Conan did.
Where Conan had like proprietary bits.
He had characters, he had runners that lasted for years
that are still popular today.
You know, he had members of the writing staff
who he could incorporate,
who they could like make into merchandise.
So like you're entering this crazy cartoon world
with Triumph and the Masturbating Bear
and these bizarre thin characters like FedEx Pope.
And it's, yeah, you have a set,
I know what Late Night with Conan is.
It's this world of dumb, colorful characters.
And when I enter it, it's a vibe.
It's a universe I'm entering.
It's a vibe.
It feels like there's a cohesive universe there.
And as Jason said, they used to fucking sell a $30 VHS
that was you pretending to drive his desk for five minutes.
And people lined up to do it.
Like that was part of the show.
That they would pretend that the desk had wheels
and he could drive it around New York City
and into funny environments.
It is very bizarre that this ride essentially tries
to do the same thing despite that never having been part
of either Late Night show that Jimmy Fallon has hosted.
And there's something, I'm sorry, I keep cutting you off.
There's something about that you're driving,
it's silly that you're driving a desk around.
That's funny.
And then you cut to the humorless tonight writer,
which is just like, it's cool is what it is.
It's the coolest shit in the world.
What were you gonna say, Jason?
Well, I was gonna say like the other, like jaywalking.
That was another bit like that.
I feel like they would do like on studio tours
or like they'd have a little jaywalking thing
in the gift shops at NBC locations.
I think, you know, that the thing that not to immediate,
like here's how to improve the ride,
but yeah, people go to New York.
So that's like not like this crazy thing.
People have been to New York City.
And anyway, it abandons that premise so quickly.
It heightens so quickly out of that.
But you know what a lot of people do not experience
in their lifetime that could be fun to simulate?
Being a guest on the Tonight Show.
Yes, just make the ride should have just been,
you are a guest of the Tonight Show.
You stand behind the curtain and then you get Murray.
You get to meet Murray.
Right, right, you're like, should this ride
just be a fucking kiosk where it's just a green screen space
where you get to act it out?
Should it be Jimmy Fallon tours you
through the history of television?
Should it be just a New York based ride
that happens to star Jimmy Fallon?
But instead, and I feel like I don't know
how much of this is true.
Fallon says that at the moment he got the job
hosting the late night, not even Tonight Show,
that he was like, man, Universal, such a big company.
Like I wanna be such a big company, man.
Like I wanna take advantage of all these different things
that Universal has.
And he went and pitched to them a ride
and they were like, you've been on air a week.
We're not gonna do a ride around you.
You don't do rides around TV shows.
You don't do them around real people.
Like all the things we're talking about
about how much a brand has to prove itself
before it can become a ride.
And then something changed within those six years
and they were like, screw it, we're doing your ride.
And it feels like the ride that got made
is very much a ride that Jimmy Fallon would have pitched.
Like this feels like the thing I could imagine him pitching
like within the first six months of him hosting late night
to a bunch of Universal creative executives
and not a bunch of Universal creative executives
being given the assignment,
how do we use Jimmy Fallon in a ride?
It's interesting.
I could see it in the broad strokes him pitching it,
but I don't know because one of my things about this ride
is that Universal just takes everything they've ever done
in a 3D movie or a screen ride
and makes a worse version of it for this.
Oh yeah.
There's one beat in this ride
that makes me legitimately angry of like,
no, you can't do that.
You cannot just copy a beat from a ride you opened
like nine years ago.
You cannot just copy it exactly.
Doesn't that just feel like desperation?
Like them trying to throw anything exciting into this ride?
It feels like that,
but it also feels like a homework assignment that's due.
It feels like we have a month to do this.
What do we know we can do?
Okay, something attaches to a vehicle.
They fly through the city like on Transformers.
There's a roller coaster at the end
that goes down like Simpsons.
I don't know, okay.
Throw a character in the middle.
You're right.
It's very Universal bag of tricks.
And I think maybe that's the more disappointing aspect
than like, it doesn't feel like a lot of original
Fallon specific inventions.
It feels like he threw them a premise
and then they kind of did their Universal things.
And we end up with, it's not the best of either world.
Because what even would the Fallon specific inventions be?
Like it feels like he's saying,
let's make a ride out of my show,
but the show he's presenting here is very different
than the show he has.
I'm not being literal minded about like,
the Tonight Show never happens on the moon.
I'm saying like, his show does not have a lot of characters.
And this is a ride designed with the confidence of,
we have so many recurring characters
that audiences will be excited to see again.
And that's just fundamentally not what the show is.
The show is, as you said, primarily at this point,
a variety show.
It is closer to a game show
than it is to a traditional comedy based,
late night talk show.
And it is so much based around
whatever celebrity has on with him
and doing a segment that plays to their strengths.
You know?
If their impressions are letting them play a character
or letting them play beer pong or whatever.
There's very little stuff that's proprietary in house
to a Jimmy Fallon late night show
that makes sense to avoid of whoever is on the couch
that night.
Well, I can imagine yours like Tony Baxter
or something talking about Indiana Jones.
Like what would a person want from Indiana Jones?
Well, you want the boulder.
You want some sort of temple.
It's like, these are the experiences you would crave.
And it's like, it's partly because I don't watch
the Tonight Show that much,
but it's like, there's not a lot
other than being a guest on the show
that you could imagine.
With Conan, which of course I know the universe better,
I could imagine where part of it's a janky desk thing
where you're driving it.
Part of it's the staring contest.
Part of it's in the year 2000.
There were both.
The thing fucking writes itself.
Frankenstein could waste 15 seconds of your time
leading you down the back hallways
in a high speed pursuit.
Oh, what a delight.
A really boring 15 seconds.
That's great.
And you could see the staring contest.
You put the camera on the audience
with people in the audience
and then play it against a video
and that'll get a laugh just like the rebel spy.
He built out a universe.
We all know.
Yes, maybe this is for white men of the exact age
to value the peak of Conan O'Brien more than anyone.
Older, not even just millennials, like older millennials.
Precisely the audience.
Aging millennials.
Yes.
That's a new tagline for our show.
Oh, aging millennials.
Sure, sure, sure.
Aging millennials.
All right, we saw that.
Poorly aging millennials.
I mean, look, we are the four guys
who are like most equipped to blue sky
all the cool things that could happen
on a 1998 Conan ride,
including someone who used to work for Conan.
But still the point is there are possibilities there.
And then you look at this ride and it's like,
I remember them promoting it with like
all your favorite recurring characters are gonna be there.
And I was like, I don't watch this show that regularly,
but I'm pretty confident
there aren't popular recurring characters.
And then you get on the ride
and it's Jimmy Fallon appearing nine different times.
Three of them are characters created just for this ride.
Wouldn't it be funny if he's also
the train conductor or whatever.
But then also it's like a couple of AD Miles,
which is already out of date by the time this ride opens
or shortly thereafter he leaves the show.
So he's never appearing as these characters ever again.
He's not gonna be in 2020 reminding people
who Gary the dad of EU is.
Right, right, Gary's not a thing.
No one is like invested in Gary the dad of EU.
And EU mostly exists as an excuse to have whoever's
the guest that night also put on a wig and braces
and do a very reductive impression of an 11 year old girl.
EU on her own doesn't really mean anything.
Let's go ahead Mike.
Who would be better in like the Disney MGM studios
where you bring up some people from the audience
and put the braces on them.
Absolutely.
That would go over huge and you'd go,
well I can't argue with this seeing mom in braces.
Oh, seeing dad, seeing dad with a wig in braces
makes the audience lose their minds.
So should this show be some kind of thing where like,
it's not that we're not at a tonight show taping,
but we're like, it should be like what Nickelodeon studios
did we're at the lab, we're testing some new Jimmy Fallon
bits and games.
Why don't you do a screen test as EU?
Why we're gonna try out one of these games
because he does very double there kind of,
and then he's in it through videos saying,
hey, great job with that one.
Now your next assignment and it's like,
probably the characters still factor in.
It's all the same stuff, but not,
maybe not making it a ride.
It should be like that.
Or it should be like the American Idol experience
or any of these fucking things that they usually do
with TV.
With some characters.
Or not characters.
Some actors get some cameos in there.
When they replaced earthquake with disaster,
who hosts it now?
Christopher Walken hosts it as a Kooky director.
There's a big, huge movie star cameo at the end
that you don't see coming.
Like get some celebrities in.
How is Timberlake not in the ride?
It's amazing they didn't.
How is Timberlake, yeah, that's crazy.
I mean, I'll say like, at least for Bourne,
it checks some boxes.
Like it's been around for a while.
That first movie was like.
All right, defending Bourne.
That's not what we're doing here.
No, no, no.
But like compared to, like yeah,
this came out so quickly after he started hosting the show.
Bourne has been around since 2003.
It's based on worldwide bestselling books.
They play on cable every hour of the day.
What else do you like?
What else?
I like the close up action.
Great early little role from Clive Owen.
Excellent sound design.
Oscar nominated every time.
But there's stuff where it's like, okay,
I can kind of wrap my head around this.
Do I think when the rumors were starting
that something would replace Transformers
and one of the rumors was Star Trek,
is that a more beloved brand?
Yes, absolutely.
But yeah, I can't.
How there's just so much.
Okay, let's talk about why they did end up on this premise.
Because the universal story is when they were viewing it,
when they were looking at the show
and how do we turn this into a ride?
What he does is he does all of these games.
Now the games are not races,
but I feel like the races are things that,
I think at some point he has had some kind of relay race
through the hallways.
And the executives must have seen that and gone,
okay, so Jimmy likes to play these games.
What is there a way that we could pit the audience
against him in a big game?
So there's at least, that's the logic.
It might be faulty logic,
but that is why we got to where we are.
But also, am I wrong in that almost every game
I've ever seen Jimmy Fallon play,
it feels like he's throwing to make the celebrity
look good.
Like that is his brand of his show.
Like very often when they do these things,
it is like he,
the main function of the Jimmy Fallon Tonight Show now
is to give celebrities an opportunity to showcase
a slightly hidden talent and look really personable.
So are you saying that the impressions
on the wheel of impressions aren't random?
And that they're designed around singing voices
that the singers can already do?
Have pre-prepared and when they go,
oh God, I don't even know what this would sound like.
How do I do Mariah Carey singing Jingle Bells?
Well, I don't know, let me think.
I find that really interesting in juxtaposition
with how fucking competitive Jimmy Fallon is on this ride.
Like that is one of the things that blew my mind
going on it for the first time.
Considering how much of his reputation is,
I'm a nice guy, I support everybody.
Look at me, I'm just a fan of everything.
We're just having fun at games, it's light.
That his defense of the Trump thing was like,
look, I don't like to go hard.
I don't go hard on anybody, right?
And then this ride is like, you fucking pathetic worms.
I'm gonna cuck you so hard with my dust.
I'm gonna race you around New York.
He's got, not only is he equipped with a futuristic car,
what are we equipped with?
How are we doing the race?
We have nothing, we're in a box.
And he's got, he can spit tubes out.
He can activate hyper tube.
We have no resources at our disposal.
We don't even know our way around the city.
We don't know our way, it's his hallways.
He has every advantage and it's a miracle
that we win quite frankly.
And he's apparently done this like every night
before taping, which makes him look like a shitty,
like unprofessional host that they go like places, places.
And he's like, two minutes left time for a quick race.
And then just puts his entire audience's life at risk.
Maybe rehearse the bits, look at your notes.
Read what a brilliant, like remember,
refresh your memory about the movies that you've watched
to talk to the guests about.
But I feel like he's got such a weird Bugs Bunny persona
in this ride, which is not who he is on the show
where he keeps on like turning back over his shoulders
and like making snide quips about how much he's beating us
and throwing like pizza at us and shit.
Like it feels like he's got this real competitive
ain't I a stinker?
Like the audience is Elmer Fudd and he's having fun
getting the better of us thing.
Dart's spreading the news, I'm winning the race.
It's a fundamental misunderstanding of the persona
that Jimmy Fallon has spent years trying to cultivate.
It is closer to Conan's.
Absolutely.
Another reason why this ride would work better with Conan.
Like it feels like he's doing the exact ride
that Conan would do.
Like there were so many Conan bits of like Amy Poehler
or Brian Stack or someone just playing a scumbag
in the audience.
And Conan would just be disgusted at them
and be disgusted by the people around you.
I'm really, I'm starting to think about now
like part of this might be that like talk shows
are kind of like empty glasses.
Like you fill them with water, you fill them with liquid.
Whatever liquid you put in there fills it.
And a big part of that is musical guest, celebrity guests
of which there are none in this ride.
But you know where there are a ton of characters
and celebrities, Universal Studios Florida.
And you could have done Jimmy Fallon race
through Universal Studios.
And he could have impersonated people
or actors from the other rides could have shown up.
Like you get the rock to do a little thing.
There are ways to translate the function of talk shows
into a ride.
There's way, yeah, to make it a little self aware.
There's all this talk about like the queue
at the Guardians of the Galaxy coaster in Epcot
is gonna have a lot of nods to the history of Epcot.
Like they could have like beaten them
to the punch on that one.
And there are ways to make Jimmy Fallon
the central character of a ride.
But it feels weird for them to like,
it's like they made every wrong decision.
Okay, people want an experiential interactive
tonight show based attraction.
Okay, so what are they gonna stand on a,
front of a green screen?
Are they gonna get to act like they're a guest?
No, it's a ride.
It's a ride, it's based exclusively off the show.
But the stuff that's proprietary material to the show
that doesn't involve the celebrity guests
and the musical acts that are the things
that actually go viral from the show.
And it's based around Jimmy Fallon's persona,
but not really the persona he does on the show
because that wouldn't translate to a ride.
So it's him adapting like another kind of character
as himself, but also playing seven other characters.
That's Scott, as you said,
if this had been a 90s SNL ride
and you imagine like, oh, going on it now,
or even if it was an SNL ride from 10 years ago, right?
And the idea of like, oh, it's so topical,
how quickly would it get dated?
That would date less than hashtag the panda,
who for all I know has not made an appearance
on the show in the last three years.
I don't think so, and I missed it at the time.
I knew what tight pants was and I knew what you was.
Until this ride opened,
I had never seen hashtag the panda in my life.
Same here.
And when Chase was on your show,
he said like, that was a bit that was created
to fuck with one of the writers in the room.
The bit was the costume was hot
and we made him do shit while wearing the costume.
And he got really tired.
Like it's such an inside bit
that doesn't seem to have permeated culture at large
in a way that something like Triumph did,
but it just feels like Universal looking at and going like,
is there any character within the Fallon universe
who is like visually striking,
could make a walk around character
and is not a real comedy writer or performers face.
And he's the one.
And so they up him to being the walk around character,
the center of all the merchandise,
the antagonist of the ride kind of,
because they just need something that fills that visual role.
He's in the spot where Maggie is in the Simpsons ride,
the dinosaur in Back to the Future.
He's like, he plays as the main villain, but why?
Is he mad?
Why does he throw you?
I'm mad.
That is the moment where I'm like,
you have to be kidding me.
Like this is the exact motion.
It's not even like the dinosaur.
Yeah, I get it's kind of close to that,
but it is exactly Maggie in the Simpsons.
It's the same shot you get close to his mouth.
Yeah.
And it's, oh, I was just like, I can't believe that.
Like it's not like,
it's like if they had done a Conan ride and like Shooverine,
Wolverine character that was just a writer
who put shoes on his hands.
Andrew Weinberg.
And did their hair.
Yes, Andrew Weinberg did his hair like Wolverine.
Like that is like, if this was a Shooverine scene.
But then usually if you made a joke out of,
if you'd made it a little more clear
that hashtag the panda is nothing
in the way the Conan nothing characters
always knew they were nothing.
But I think it's hard to play irony in theme park world.
So we'd any sense of like,
hashtag the panda is lazily named dumb thing.
And it's just an excuse to make a guy dance.
That's all lost here.
Now it's just a kid is supposed to hug hashtag the panda.
And the only one who's ever done it is Jason Sheridan.
And part of the premise of hashtag the panda
is that the costume is shitty.
That it's like a shitty costume you would get
from a shitty costume rental place.
It is not an impressive walk around character.
Jason, I understand that he brought you more joy
than you've ever felt in your life.
I mean, I would have diminished that experience,
but it is insane how much they put on hashtag the panda
because it does feel like an alternate scenario
in which Shooverine was the most successful character
that Conan had ever done.
And I don't mean that Shooverine had broken out
in the way the triumph did.
I mean, that was the most any character
had ever broken out.
If only for justice for Shooverine,
he should have gotten it.
For justice for Shooverine.
He should come back at the Largo.
Oh yeah, yeah, very much.
This is why I don't wanna let everyone
who was involved in this off the hook,
but this is why it feels like everyone was under
such a strict rules.
Like, all right, it has to be a ride
that lasts for two, whatever.
How long is this?
Two and 15?
What is it?
Short, right?
It feels like four and a half hours, but yeah.
It might not be that short, but it feels short.
It has to be short.
It has to be a screen.
We can't have actors doing anything.
That's the cheapest way.
Put people in a theater, load them out.
It's gotta have, all right, it's gotta be exciting.
People like exciting.
Well, what can we do?
All right, all the same tricks in a 3D movie
that make things exciting.
Like, it feels like, and then they just cast
based on this.
They're like, all right, it's gotta be something
that moves people.
All right, we need a big thing at the end.
The Panda, I guess.
It feels like it was an afterthought.
It feels like the property was an afterthought.
And that the executives had watched the show that week
and they were like, I got this meeting at the end of the week.
What am I gonna put in here?
Oh, like they did, like I watched it on Wednesday
and there was this Panda.
That's a thing you do, right?
Let's do the intellectual exercise of putting Leno
on this exact ride.
Yes.
And like, you're gonna have to cast who's at the top
of the, one of Judge Edo is at the top of the building.
Well, maybe that can be the- The Dancing Edo's.
Or that's the, the Dancing Edo's maybe are in the subway.
They're performing, you throw money into the, yeah,
I think so.
I think it's the, the aforementioned bodybuilder character.
We all remember maybe he's up,
because he's strong, climbed up to the top of the building.
This is by the way, the ride you're describing
is race through Burbank with Jay Leno.
Right. Oh, wow.
Yeah, you're right.
Which would make a lot of sense because he loves his cars.
It actually- I was gonna say,
that problem is it's a cleaner walk with Jay
because at least he's a vehicle aficionado.
Yes, that's true. You're right.
Then you follow him, you whiz into the Bob's big boy,
and then that gets right in your face and you almost,
and you bump into the statue.
Oh, it's better than-
And it causes some chain reaction.
It's even better than Conan's, honestly.
Yeah, this is the one.
You have places with a Jay's garage ride tomorrow
and it would work.
It would work better than race through New York.
I mean, it just feels like every time there's a new character
or a new reference or a new visual,
that I guess is something from the Tonight Show circa
fall 2006, it feels like the ride is trying to gabbo me.
It feels like every 15 seconds, there's a new gabbo
where it's like, you know this, you love this.
This is what you like about this show.
This is important and it's iconic
and it deserves to belong in a theme park
for an infinite amount of years.
In terms of Tonight Show characters being iconic,
I might argue that the closest that they get it
is the Ragtime Gals.
The Ragtime Gals were on the show a bunch
and it is a celebrity vehicle, but it's still like,
you know, there's costumes there that are reproducible.
It is a way to get a bunch of theme park performers in.
It was not my favorite thing to watch,
but I wish these people well.
I hope you have fun harmonizing and everything.
Again, you sort of lose the irony in their performance
because the joke is we're doing in some cases
sort of profane hip hop songs, but in this cheesy manner.
But with the theme park filter, it just is cheesy.
And like a theme park would just do
a barbershop ice ice baby.
That's not, there's nothing weird going on there
and it's being executed in a not weird way.
So the Ragtime Gals are weird,
but it is a little bit of an iconic thing from the show.
Absolutely, but let's say two things.
One, it is iconic, but only because they're co-opting
barbershop quartet iconography.
Like that works for you just as well if you,
as if you had never seen an episode of The Tonight Show
in your entire life and you just go,
oh, I know what a barbershop quartet looks and sounds like.
Sure, sure. And as you said,
you're using the surface elements.
Obviously in the video elements of the ride itself,
you have the real four or five writers
who were part of the Ragtime Gals at the time,
like Tom Shalhou and whoever,
but removed from the ironic context
that made them a comedy bit to begin with.
Hashtag the panda is the same thing.
Like the only reason hashtag is funny is the bit of,
you know there's a real performer in that suit
and he's getting sweaty and tired.
And then in this ride, it turns it into,
oh my God, look, and he's 600 feet tall.
How did that happen?
Yeah, the context is lost.
It's all gone.
I just wanted to say about the Ragtime Gals
and I actually wanted to play a clip here
just to give them some credit and a bit from the show.
I just, and they are such an important part of this.
They're in the ride.
They are the pre-show.
So I just pulled a random Ragtime Gals performance
just to help the audience acquaint with them a little bit.
So as I said, this was a good sketch
to plug celebrities into.
So what you're gonna see,
they always reveal the celebrity in the back of the line.
They all line up and then like, oh, that's who it is.
It's a guest on the show.
I didn't think he'd be doing a bit.
Do you guys see the Ragtime Gals here?
Yes, I do.
Okay, so here's just a random one
just to show kind of how they weave
different celebrities into the bit.
Ta-da-la-la-la, ta-da-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la.
I'm not the guy that you get off.
My look, guys, it's that guy from House of Cards.
I know what the girl that need, New York to Haiti.
I'll let it run a little.
This is a Jason Derulo song.
I think it's gonna be hard to leave.
I've been around the world, don't speak the language,
but your body don't need explaining.
All you need to understand is when you talk dirty to me.
Ta-da-la-la, ta-da-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la.
So just to clarify, they're doing a Jason Derulo song,
and there's a line about,
basically, just to clarify, it is a song about,
in this case, Kevin Spacey having sex
on international airplanes.
Just wanted to lay that out there.
Yes, I didn't even think about that.
International.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
But your booty don't need explaining.
Oh my God.
That's a fun bit.
Just wanted to share that with you guys.
But even at other times.
Now it's Spacey Oddities 2.
You're like, right, okay, first of all,
every element of the Fallon attraction,
both pre-show and ride itself,
is stripping the ragtime gals of their bit,
of their irony, right?
But also, that the bit is also dependent
on having a surprise celebrity fifth person.
Like, you're removing that from the equation as well.
And I feel like that's such a huge,
not to keep on circling back to this point,
but it's such a huge difference between Conan and Fallon,
where it's like, for Conan, the characters and the bits
and the sense of world building that show had
was what happened in between celebrity appearances.
Like, there were things that were entirely owned
by the show, because by and large,
you wouldn't see Harrison Ford
interacting with Preparation H. Raymond.
Whereas every bit Fallon has is pretty much predicated on,
and you won't believe who's participating this time.
Whether it's a pain-
Well, you're maybe describing a bigger problem
with pop culture and culture in general.
This is why it's a three hour episode.
This is why the Fallon ride is so monumental in my eyes,
in terms of like, this is just such a culmination moment
of so many different things gone wrong in culture,
all coming to a head.
This is the death of American culture.
Kind of.
You made a good point a couple times
that it's difficult to do irony in theme parks,
in a way, like you can do it in comedy on television,
certainly in film.
But if you work with the context
that theme parks have available,
there are ways to make stuff work.
Like, oh, what are the ragtime girls like?
Oh, they're like barbershop quartets?
Oh, you mean like the dapper dance
who just wander Main Street singing?
Couldn't you just put these guys outside of the building
as if it was kind of poking fun at the dapper dance?
Cause they're singing like Jason Derulo
and they're singing like Lizzo songs.
You could do that easily
because that is what Universal figured out early on.
Yeah, irony is difficult, but you can be a little cutting.
They could do the hashtag, the panda bit,
where he's giant and he's on the Empire State Building
and it's like Maggie, maybe tossing a line,
go like, wait, isn't this just the same thing
for the Simpsons ride?
I think the audience would eat that up.
But that's what makes this even more inexplicable
is everything you're saying,
they kind of did right with the Simpsons ride.
I'm a Simpsons ride defender.
I still wish it was back to the future.
That's a top five of all time ride for me.
But I think the Simpsons ride works
and I think the main reason it works is,
A, you have a TV show that's been on for over 30 years
is has by just sort of a bullheaded refusal to end,
become timeless.
And so the characters have like transcended
to this sort of level of they can represent everything
or they can represent nothing.
Like they're malleable enough
that the show isn't too au courant to base a ride around.
It can be whatever the fuck it wants to be,
but there's a sensibility comedically that you can use
as a prism through which to parody rides and theme parks,
which I think it does well.
Like that's the success of that ride
is less about the specific characters
and more about the iconography
and the sense of humor applied to a ride in the abstract.
Maybe nothing else can really do a parody
of a theme park ride in the way the Simpsons ride
I think successfully is.
I think it'd be overkill to do too many more.
This is an anti ride.
But it also helps that in the universe of the Simpsons,
they have gone to theme parks before.
And the ride is pretending that you are going
to another theme park within the Simpsons universe.
Whereas this ride is just saying like,
step into New York, you are on the corner
of 52nd and fifth, please enter 30 rock.
This is normal New York.
And then once the curtains pull open,
Jimmy Fallon reveals that he has the world's most advanced
race car slash aeroplane slash spaceship.
And also the entire audience seating section
is its own vehicle.
Let's go to the moon.
Yeah.
It's a lot.
And you get none of this in the pre-show.
It's just thrown at you,
which I guess I wouldn't necessarily like an over
explaining pre-show, but truly you watch the ride.
Like, wait a minute.
So how are we moving and why space and why we can go
under water and it is a little too much to stay.
If you.
Fantastico happens until the ride happens,
all the pre-show stuff, all the warnings, everything is,
this is going to be a very normal taping
of the Jimmy Fallon show.
If it's a Joe roadie ride,
there's like two pre-shows that explain how the tonight
rider works.
Yes.
Exactly what the jet propulsion is like and exactly how
fast it can go and what it's raced before.
Why it exists, why it even exists in this universe.
There is no place setting it.
All the place setting is just, you know,
how a TV show taping works.
Please turn off your cell phones.
Here's the roots curtains up.
Jimmy's already in the tonight rider and he is like,
Oh, I guess we have four minutes.
Let's go on a race to the stars.
I think the first reference to the tonight rider,
when he says I'm going to go get the tonight rider and you've
had no previous acclamation to the Jimmy Fallon as a space
car.
We oftentimes, I think, talk about stuff where we go,
it's too much explanation, too much explanation on newer
rides. There's no reason.
And I think guardians, which I love and avatar flight of
passage, which I also love, have a little too much like
explanation.
Rocket raccoon could really tell you a lot less about what's
going on in your hands, scanning and all of that.
But this one, this needs a couple sentences.
It needs a little bit.
I mean, it's got great lines like a space train.
I've heard about this ride.
Jesus Christ.
Like gracefully does take the space train.
It goes space train.
I've heard about this ride.
Yeah. When the announcer in space, who is also his announcer,
announces about that, there is a space train.
But I feel like most rides, as you talk about extensively on
this show, especially most modern rides tend to base
around this is what we're telling you, the audience,
you're about to witness.
But the entire premise of the ride is that something's going
to go wrong and you're going to end up on a very unique
journey that was not planned at all.
You know?
And this is not that it is like we're preparing you to watch
a regular taping of The Tonight Show and then the curtains open.
Jimmy Fallon rides out in a vehicle and goes, fuck you.
Let's race like as if this is just his pre show ritual.
Yeah, every that he does every day.
What if there was what if the pre show involved
that you do a little backstage tour?
I'm going to show you how a TV show works.
Here's the costumes first and all kind of crazy stuff in here and makeup.
They make me look handsome.
And then over here is the laboratory where we and then like
there's a, you know, instead of just some friendly costume person,
now he has like a mad scientist or a tech guy working for him.
Like it's the first it's a Muppet showy sort of like,
wait, why is that at a TV show?
And like some allusion to I have told the audience that I'm going to do a race.
But what they don't know is that I'm going to cheat because I have the high
tech tonight writer with me.
You just you don't get the no tracks are laid for any of this.
Yeah. I took call back to your first appearance, Griffin.
It should be more like Muppet Vision 3D.
It should be walking. Yeah, that's a great idea.
Scott is like, yeah, you're walking around backstage at the night show.
And there's all these crazy like Dr.
Bunsen, honey do kind of like nonsense.
Yeah, it's crazy to work here.
It's so thoroughly not in the DNA of Fallon's show.
Like Conan could do that and you would go, of course, this makes perfect sense.
The way like Conan always talks about how whenever they would do
the sort of backstage bits in the hallways of 30 Rock, he always wanted
to feel like old timey Hollywood, where there's like a guy in a Roman centurion
outfit and there's a camel or horse, right?
A camel. Right. Like any of that shit.
He cultivated that atmosphere of like this show is crazy.
Everything's going on behind the scenes. These characters are real.
They invade my studio. I interact with them.
They stress me out, which Fallon does not really do.
And I think part of that is
Fallon wants to play the characters like if anyone's doing a character bit
on a Fallon show, it's almost always Fallon.
And if it's not Fallon, it's because it's a sketch that requires
more than one character.
And Fallon is still playing the primary one.
Fallon has to be one of the ragtime gals.
Fallon has to be the girl, which also makes building a ride around it difficult
because there isn't a universe for him to interact with.
Jimmy Fallon has no relationship with these characters
because he is them or he is one of them.
Hashtag the Panda is the only one he has a dynamic with.
And the dynamic is torturing him.
Which this speaks to my again over and over.
I keep saying this. Why?
It feels like if there's not enough time, like it feels like they maybe had Jimmy
for 30 minutes to shoot this. Yes.
Like if he loves playing characters, why isn't Neil Young in this?
Why isn't why aren't the big hits from his characters in this
as opposed to a blurry out of focus?
Him shooting like saying lines from nowhere.
But he does take time to play his famous character, Travis Bickle.
Right. Because there's a part if the audience doesn't know this,
there's a part where he pulls up to a taxi cab and then it is the ultimate taxi driver.
And they have a little exchange, which is just a weird
of all the movies to tribute in a theme park like the darkest.
It's like all Cartoon New York and then the darkest New York film.
It feels like Jimmy is playing Martin Scorsese in the back seat.
Like you see up that window
coked out of his mind.
Yeah. But you ask why he isn't doing these things instead.
And it's like, I think there is such an extreme state of denial
where he and everyone involved in this ride don't want to put it all on his shoulders.
But it feels like everyone involved in the making of this ride
wants to convince themselves that this show does function this way,
that it has enough popular characters that you can fill a ride with.
So the idea of having to establish a new tonight show labs down the hall.
I'm sure they would say, well, but that's not part of the show.
Why would we use that? We don't want to add new things.
And it's like, but motherfucker, the shit you have doesn't fit on a ride.
And also you're having to invent the Knight Rider
because there's no reason for this to be happening.
And it's all the more bizarre when he already hosts the backlot tour,
when there already like is a ride in which Jimmy Fallon interacts ostensibly,
you know, not in a very high tech way, but speaks to the people, the ride goers
in California and comments on all the different places
they're going to in history and whatever.
And this just invents this whole new mythology.
To then create a ride that acts like all of these other elements fit into a ride.
I don't want to just dictate the conversation, but I do think I wouldn't mind
just focusing on the tonight writer for a period of time.
Let's do an hour. Let's do a quick.
It's own or just it's own.
And then we're breaking off the night writer into its own episode.
So it's it's like a hover car.
It has it has like those.
It's very Mario Kart, which apparently he is a big Mario Kart fan.
We heard the little inside dirt that he plays pre show pre
taping Mario Kart games with people and is very competitive at this.
So maybe this whole thing was made.
They must have pitched it to him often.
It succeeded based off of his Mario Kart love.
But once again, very, very bizarre that for a guy who is so deliberate
about building his public image that on the show, his persona is.
I always let the celebrity win backstage.
His persona is you have to let me win Mario Kart.
And the ride is I need to fucking beat you.
Like even though the audience barely ekes out a winning at the end,
the ride is competitive in a way that it sounds like real Jimmy Fallon is.
But on camera, Jimmy Fallon tries not to be right.
Real psych. This is a very revealing ride.
I I was looking.
I mean, there's not a ton of insight with newer rides.
There's never a ton of insight into the process.
Sure. But it does feel like he has, as you were saying,
if he truly pitched things, he does have some influence on this.
He kept on talking about how badly he wanted this ride to happen,
how he kept on pitching it to them, that he thought like,
I even think the New York premise was his.
I mean, how much of that is like, you know, PR spin.
But it really feels like this dude
spent eight years biding time until Universal finally decided
that he was valuable enough to build a ride around.
It's tough because today's show Cafe, if that didn't open,
I wouldn't question that fact more. You know what I mean?
The idea that they're opening up other things in the NBC
Comcast Universal Family makes me a little suspicious
that this was always something that was so in the forefront of his mind.
But who knows?
But I think also he.
Go ahead. Defend the Tonight Show, the Today Show Cafe.
Here we go.
Here comes the stand.
Sound design is excellent in there.
Hear the L.
Roker voice very clearly.
Getting out of it, that's a problem.
So the Today Show Cafe
replaced nothing.
It was just bakery.
It was just Hollywood bakery.
So I kind of get why they made like, well, you painted orange,
you put the logo on it and and they're trying to like
up their food game a little.
So maybe we can test this out because it's mostly getting people
getting something quick when they're walking in the park or walking out of the park.
So I I kind of get that.
I do kind of get that.
I'm not putting it down.
I'm just saying that I'm calling it to question
maybe that it was such an aggressive part of Jimmy's part to get the ride
when they both opened Today Show Cafe and this Tonight Show ride
at very similar time frames.
That's all I'm saying.
Yeah, I'm saying it feels like a very purposeful idea from the company
to start branding things in the theme park like.
Yeah, Tonight Today Show tonight.
OK, I guess. Yeah.
But but also like the Tonight Show and the Today Show
are both these like evergreen brands that have lasted for decades.
Right. Different hosts and all of that.
And the Today Show Cafe, which I have not had the pleasure of going to myself,
seems to be much more a tribute to the larger idea of the Today Show
and the entire history of it in the sense that it was not a restaurant
that could be foiled by Matt Lauer news coming out.
You know, like they didn't have to cancel the doing this at all
because of Matt Lauer. Right. Right.
In a way that like this is another thing for me,
and I don't want to imply that I'm sitting on any knowledge because I'm not.
But I'm starting to know what I'm truly not.
You know, I've heard things about Fallon that are just like, huh,
that's interesting.
But I've never heard anything that is like cancelable in the least.
But it is very interesting that this ride opens in like 2017.
Spring and fall 2017 is when the first
Harvey Weinstein stories start getting published.
And then where are you going with this?
This one's like I'm not saying in a conspiratorial way,
but I feel like it is important to think about the fact that this ride was created
at the last window where studios felt like
if someone's big enough, they can never be taken down.
And I want to be clear, I'm not saying this about Fallon.
I don't think he has these skeletons in his closet,
but it just feels like a year later, a company would be like,
we cannot invest this much money into one person,
and especially not a character played by one person, but that person as themself.
Because people's public standing is pretty, you know, it's
everyone's on a razor's edge these days.
You know, you can tell the company is like at any moment
we could have to distance ourselves from anybody.
Do you think maybe, though, they have it in the computer
where they can easily just replace his head with the new Tonight Show host?
They have a Jack Parr. Yeah, it goes to the ghost.
Or they yes, in the interim, when they're figuring out who the new Tonight
Show host would be, they just throw Jack Parr's head on there.
And Jack Parr, like they have a sound to like do all the lines.
Mike, I would completely believe that if this were just a generic race
through New York and not a race that features so many Fallon characters.
Like, that's the thing I always come back to, is they built a ride
that is in no way modular without having to scrap the entire thing.
Like they can't even go, fuck it, let's make it a different thing at 30 Rock
without having to change everything about the ride itself.
But not maybe not the theater and not the lobby.
And it's not like totally a stardo.
That might have been a purposeful design in the same way that now
it's the DreamWorks theater that shows Kung Fu Panda
and the outside isn't themed anymore so they can slide things in and out.
Right. But in the sense that like you couldn't just reshoot this
with a new person filling the Fallon role and keep everything else around it.
You would have to scrap all the video.
You know, well, you'd have to get rid of the characters.
I mean, you could put Steve Allen's famous characters in place
of the Panda, or you could put Johnny's famous characters like.
We're going back. We're going all the way back to Steve Allen.
That's going to be the plan.
Let's do it. Be legends.
You could you could make this an SNL ride, right?
You if you imagine they still kept all the digital elements, right?
You could make this an SNL ride where Lauren Michaels is in his, you know,
SNL low rider or whatever it's called.
And he's racing Saturday Night Live writer. Right. Right.
And all the different characters pop up.
And those would be modular enough that if someone became more or less popular,
you could remove them or add them, you know.
But this just feels like so built around things that are are gabbling,
you know, are just like, yeah, sure.
Being yelled at us, we like.
But I would argue like since since this is so similar to other rides,
like for Transformers, Transformers does a scene where they pick you up,
drag you along, flying behind them in a city street.
This looks so much worse than the Transformers ride.
Yeah, it's clearly a much cheaper version.
So I wonder if part of it was like, we're not going to spend too much money
making this as high level as Transformers.
Are you are you disappointed in a ride that lets you go to the marquee
of the Times Square Hard Rock Cafe?
You get to stare at the Hard Rock Cafe logo in a ride.
I am I do like that.
I just wish we spent another couple seconds being able to enjoy the majestic sign.
I will say and Griffin will appreciate this.
It's a bummer that you can see that toys, Toys R Us Times Square.
Yeah. Oh, and it's gone.
It's gone. Yeah.
It was a great fun store.
My favorite place in the world.
It had all it was fun.
The giant dinosaur wonka.
Yeah, you know that that Times Square Toys R Us had a better ride
than the ride you're on when he zooms past it.
Was there a ride in there?
There was a Ferris wheel.
There was a full size wheel.
Was it four stories or three? Yeah, four stories.
My God.
Truly so fun.
So great. So fun.
Wow. And then Mitt Romney's company ruined it.
Each car in the Ferris reel was was differently themed.
Like there was like an E.T. car, Nickelodeon car and a cabbage patch.
And like you get to hang out with your friends.
It was so good.
But in this ride, you get the Tonight Rider,
which I just I my other thought I wanted to get out about the tonight.
Is it a is it an Air Force One situation
where just once you're installed, you have access to the Tonight Rider
where they're proto tonight riders?
Did Steve Allen have like a, you know, more janky or jalopy version?
Was this a Leno program to begin with because he's such a vehicle guy?
And now now all the hosts get did
Conan get it and then have to turn in the keys immediately.
When was Conan's Tonight Rider?
It's just that 1995 sedan he tried to sell.
Which was in the parking lot at Warner Brothers.
And I worry that that like really.
Yeah, the parking lot where the Ellen audience part just had
his Conan's old car covered.
Yeah. Wow.
The send they have.
Not only does like Conan steering the desk through New York
work as as a cleaner entry point for a ride,
even just the short tonight show tenure of Conan O'Brien
has the Bugatti Veyron mouse like as a better vehicle.
Oh, yeah. They invented a great comedy vehicle. Right.
But but you write you.
I mean, God, the Tonight Rider, the more strings you pull at,
the more questions you ask, you know, because you know,
I feel like when people complain about how much the world sucks,
they always do that hacky thing of like, oh, you know, the future.
We were promised with all this shit like flying cars that never came to be.
And this ride presupposes that flying cars do exist.
The technology is hush hush and only Jimmy Fallon has access to it.
Waited until this race, until we were in his home to tell us,
I have this thing and you can't use it.
You're here to go on a ride.
And instead, I'm going to go on the ride and you're going to watch me.
You're going to get dragged along behind.
Yeah. Is that what's happening also?
How are we moving?
I don't know. Unclear. It's very unclear.
The whole right. Yeah. The whole theater.
It's there's no unless I missed it.
There's like a throwaway line that I missed it where he's like,
also, you're in a tonight rider, too.
But I don't think so.
The audience is one big tonight rider. Yeah. There's no explanation.
I scrubbed back and it really is.
The opening is curtains open.
Higgins goes, ah, Jimmy Fallon.
And then Fallon swerves out in the tonight rider and goes, hey, let's race.
Like, it's that fast. Yeah.
Right. And tonight rider obviously is a play on night rider,
which is not the name of that car.
And it's not the style of that car.
It's not the style that car doesn't talk to him because that's.
And people said there were articles that were like, it's the you know,
and in a nod to NBC history.
But there's nothing else that's a nod to NBC history in the ride.
Once again, I know we're repeating the same points here,
but in the same way that the the studio tour is like a ride through
universal pictures history, this ride could have been
Jimmy Fallon rides through NBC history
and you see different elements from iconic NBC shows over the decades.
He is driving kit, you know, you be time travels.
He goes so that you can go into night rider.
I don't know what else is what else is exciting for me?
You know, the Munsters, you drive alongside the Munster mobile.
Dracula. Oh, that's right.
Yeah, I do. I feel bad.
I dropped that. I didn't get the name.
People would be more excited if this ride, for example,
went through the offices of Dunder Mifflin.
Then they are going to the moon with Jimmy Fallon.
A regular person is would love would love that.
If they were regular, they'd love it.
Are you regular?
These would eat that up.
I'm not sure what I'm implying there.
I have a person like me who watched the office for a little while
and then kind of stopped.
Yeah, yeah. Not to what after Jim and Pam got together. Yeah. Yeah.
If you really step back and start, as you say, Griffin, pull at the strings.
This whole building is insane.
This is a facsimile of a New York skyscraper
named after an insanely wealthy oil magnet.
Is that what the Rockefellers were known for? Or just money?
They just made money. They just made the money.
They were they were in the money business.
I think they were in the money business. Yeah.
A building filled with Diego Rivera murals
that the Rockefeller was always fighting with him about.
And that then became the home of a major player
in the history of radio and then television that was then owned
by any number of like the the implications of building
a facsimile of this.
It's truly insane.
And then what's inside of it is even crazier. Right.
But also like a building where like a bunch of HR people and like accountants
work like there is a lot of glamour to 30 Rock.
But there's something just about being in a park where you're like,
oh, my God, there's the Jurassic Park and there's Hogwarts Castle.
And there's an actual building I could walk by if I go to New York City.
You know, there's a there's a Panera in the basement. Right.
I mean, that's the thing.
There's so much about it that's just a little too banal for a theme park,
even if it is a very nice looking historic building.
Yeah. Right.
So then does it make up?
Does it is do they make up for any of these points by going to
the more outlandish places because it is regular New York stuff
until you then the Tonight Rider begins to fly.
And then you go to the Statue of Liberty and then into space
and then into a tube.
Does this fix anything you're talking about?
Because it's all it's it's outlandish. It's bigger.
Hmm. But there's no grounding like this is this really is like
improv scenes I've coached where it's like, this is too much.
Like I know rides, you only have three minutes.
You got to get a lot of stuff in a ride and have like make people feel a bunch
of stuff and get excited.
But it's just like, whoa, this goes zero to 60 too quickly.
Yeah, I think that's the problem.
As Jason said, is just like everything that's happening is so insane.
Like I'm just watching the video here in a little window.
Curtains open. Fallon's there.
Let's race already. You're racing with him.
No explanation of the fact that you apparently are a vehicle
that you share with everyone else.
Then you're steering down the hallways.
And I'm starting to settle into this ride and going, OK,
I guess this ride is going to go through all of 30 Rock.
But then pretty quickly, he drives through a wall out into the street.
So now you're in New York City.
Now you're driving around from like Rockefeller Center down to Times Square.
And then it takes so little time for him to start flying.
Yeah, like every time you think you almost get what the ride's going to be,
I guess maybe it's like it's it's a theme park version
of seeing the sights of New York City.
Then it just ups it to something crazy where you're so distracted by weight.
This car can fly that when that part happened, I was like,
they fly now.
They fly now.
Tonight, writers fly now.
We just watch.
I swear, we just watched they fly now last night.
You watched the movie again.
No, no, I zoomed through it to the parts that I like.
OK, good.
I was going to say, why are you?
Why are you torturing yourself?
Yeah, but that's like there are so many rides or attractions, let me say,
like Ellen's and energy adventure, right, where it's based around a person.
But it's like that person is plugged into some larger idea.
So there could be a thing that's like it's race through New York with Jimmy Fallon.
And it's just about seeing the sights of New York City.
Or there could be a ride that's like journey into space with Jimmy Fallon.
And the exact premise is Jimmy Fallon
has been given the first opportunity to pilot a spaceship.
It's the first commercial spaceship.
And you're all going to join him in space.
And then you can do your fucking Jimmy Fallon on the moon ride, whatever.
You just need to do that basic amount of world building.
But this is just the guy who hosts the show
likes to casually go underwater and to the moon
every time before he tapes a talk show.
It feels like we were talking about this a little earlier.
OK, so 2016 is when Kong opens
and then 2017 is Fallon, 2018 Fast and Furious.
It feels like they're all sort of and I think this is probably
the least successful, the Fallon one, but they're all in the same CGI
world of stuff happens and you don't even know what's going on.
And the Fast and Furious is very guilty of 3D nonsense with no explanation.
I also wonder if part of it was just that, like the time was the thinking there
at Universal as well, where it was like, just throw a bunch of shit at everybody.
Like, don't worry so hard about anything, because I don't remember.
I think Kong is the most successful one, both on the tour and Skull Island.
But people are still fine.
You want to see that giant monkey head.
Ultimately, you want to see a full body monkey, of course.
But I wonder if it's also the philosophy of the company
at the time of just like just things blow up.
People will feel movement and they won't ask questions.
Don't worry about it.
And their messaging for The Secret Life of Pets ride was so deliberate in the like,
look, it's not a screen ride. We built stuff.
Look, we're listening.
Like, you're right that this was a period where they just went
crazy overboard with the same bag of tricks over and over again.
If you even extend it to like you go, it's it's Transformers,
Simpsons, this Fast and Furious Supercharged Kong.
It's a lot of the same sort of shit sprays smells.
And it's the it's getting worse to Simpsons.
I like Transformers. I like.
And then it starts just going off the cliff.
Like it doesn't. Yes. Approve on those ideas.
Well, Kong and Fast and Furious harken back to the very early days
of Universal Orlando, where it started on the studio tour and then was transported.
However, a lot of those early studio tour
originally like the stuff that was originally on the studio tour
became Universal Orlando attractions.
They really had to do a lot of work to like here is a unique Jaws experience.
Here's a unique confrontation experience.
And they kind of really they did like one thing at each Fast and Furious.
There's a lot of cars.
There's a lot of like computer rooms
where people are like hacking stuff.
There's stuff that kind of reminds me of the movies.
Kong Skull Island. OK.
The queue looks a little nice, but there's a big Kong right at the end.
So like they kind I feel like they kind of know we have to do something,
but we couldn't spend all this money and make a totally unique attraction.
You know, this isn't a Kong episode and this isn't a Fast and Furious
Supercharged episode. I just want to say I
I frequent the Hollywood Universal far more than the Orlando Universal.
Almost every time I'm in L.A. I go to Universal usually by myself.
I find it a very fun and relaxing thing to do since it's such a manageable park.
I have done the tour almost every time I've gone.
I've done the Fast and Furious and the Kong parts of the tour many times now.
I like both of them a lot on the tour.
I think they work super well on the tour.
And in both cases, when I heard they were going to bring them to Orlando,
I got excited about the idea of them running with the little morsel you get
and being able to blow it up into a full ride.
I think Kong just barely pulls it off.
I wish they had done more, but I think the theming is good.
I like the fact that it's sort of like an old universal like, hey,
I'm your tour guide. Let's take you through here.
Oh, no, this isn't good.
And the robot at the end worth the price of admission.
I have not gotten to go on the Orlando Fast and Furious yet.
That is my favorite film franchise.
It really bums me out that they didn't really give a shit
because that is not enough to sustain an entire ride.
If you told me we're going to use what happens on the tour as the kernel
of a thing, we can expand until like a proper seven minute attraction.
I would be thrilled.
But it just seems like it's right.
Minimum effort. You're going to be upset.
That's what I've heard. That's what I heard.
So I I went back to Universal on the very last day before we flew out of Orlando.
And that was the last thing I did before I went to the airport.
And I was so I guess I got a bite to eat.
But like I I was like, guys, I'll you don't have to wait.
We don't have to wait. We can do Fast and the Furious.
I'll I'll be the bearer of bad news on that one.
Because I have notes for that.
I realize we never got around to doing it.
So we could do that in the future.
Yeah, well, definitely I can walk through it because there's some bunker.
There's some stuff in there that's like, oh, oh, that's what we're doing.
OK, like it's just yeah, it really doesn't translate because yeah, it's
I'd say 95 percent the studio tour.
And you think Fast and the Furious, I want to be in a souped up car.
That's the problem. I want to go fast. Right.
Nice try, asshole. You're not getting that.
You accepted on the studio tour because you've been watching.
You've been experiencing a very slow paced stroll through like
Wisteria Lane for 45 minutes.
Like it works in juxtaposition to what you've been experiencing
and understanding the ride vehicle you're on.
But then when I heard, oh, they're going to bring it to Orlando,
I was like, OK, but just run with it.
Please go a lot further than this.
And that sounds like it's just the same bullshit.
How are you how is there a Fast and Furious ride
where you are not in a car?
I know it's such madness.
And like if there was if if we found out that the Super Mario
Kart ride was you are in a bus and you look at cars,
mad people would burn the building down.
And a universal franchise that has made billions of dollars
that is going on 20 full years of major theatrical releases.
Like there's so much to pull from.
It clearly is something that isn't like a fad for them to commit
so much less to that.
Like that that is less effort than this.
It is crazy that they put less effort in the Fast and Furious ride
that they did in the Jimmy Fallon ride.
Is it is it worse, Jason?
What do you what's your call having been on it?
I think.
I think this is this is worse
as a ride, as an attraction.
I think Fast and Furious with the source material
might be more disappointing.
Yeah, because, yeah, that is you know, let's that is Universal's Avengers.
Right. And it's still going and it's going to keep going like forever.
And right.
Why wouldn't you just I mean, I guess the Mario Kart technology
wasn't ready yet and wasn't cheap and duplicatable.
But there are so many things.
Yes, there should be a Gringotts Fast and Furious with the roller
coaster cars that look like the rock and roller coaster cars. Yes.
You should get in a roller coaster that looks like a car.
You can put some screens to make it feel like you're going way faster
in certain places, but then actually give people like a thrill.
It also just feels like that the opening of Rock and Roller Coaster
should be the starting point of any Fast and Furious ride.
100 percent have a Fast and Furious ride that doesn't start with you
throttling and like hitting the nose and then suddenly going super fast,
even if it's screen based.
That's how the thing should fucking start.
Yes, it's not with like watching a very still party
where people are dancing in like a oddly corralled together way,
a way that's very distressing and COVID-19 era to watch.
Once again, stand close stand right next to each other.
Really jam together works on a tram tour.
Well, what you've previously been seeing is someone putting 40
percent effort into playing Norman Bates like that.
And it's and it's what you were saying about this.
This ride is not a classic universal and then things go awry.
The tour is that's completely the tour.
We're going to go into a sound stage, but something crazy happened
in the sound stage. And what's this building? Oh, my God.
We went in there and there was a car race and Vin Diesel and stuff.
And I'll say this. Yeah. Bare minimum.
It kind of it kind of does that because of like the setup of the tram tour.
Things are going wrong.
Things are coming out of the water, whatever.
Like the Fast and Furious at least has.
Once again, haven't been on Orlando, but within the studio tour
has the sort of building to explain why you're there,
why they need to escape, you know, like I feel like they fazed this out.
But when I first went on the Fast and Furious tram tour,
I call it the Fast and Furious tram tour, even though it's only the last
three minutes of it.
They certainly promoted it that way.
Yes, yeah, sure.
They do that thing or they used to do the thing where they would have
Dom's car at different locations.
Yeah. And the tour guide would go like, huh, that car doesn't belong here.
What's going on here?
And then they'd play over the PA like, be on the lookout for some fast racers.
Like, there's a bit of that.
Oh, I didn't know they did that. That's kind of cool.
I feel like they've scaled it back a little bit, but there was that sense of like,
you understand why this is happening to you.
You understand why you're getting caught up in this.
You understand why they need to get out of there so quickly.
The Fallon ride just does none of that.
None of that. The stakes are I want to beat you.
That's it. And we have no way to control.
He's completely in control.
And it's an accident whether we win or lose.
So there's no way for me to impact the bearing of the I kind of like to.
I do want to make sure we like step through everything.
You just explain things concisely.
What happens after that? We end up like
we're in Times Square. We meet Trev's pickle.
We go into the do we go into the subway?
Yes. After that, here you go.
Right. You go like 30 Rock Hallways to Rockefeller Center.
You drive down to Times Square.
You're in the heart of New York City.
And then he steers down into the subway.
Of course, goes by the ragtime gals, gets on the tracks.
You feel like maybe now it's going to be a fun Jimmy Fallon subway ride.
But no, he drives in the wrong direction.
The train is coming towards us.
It pushes us back essentially to where we started.
Then he goes above ground again and he passes by some construction workers.
Hey, what are you doing?
What is this New York City?
And also drives by Jimmy's Pizzeria, a place that does not exist.
A Jimmy Fallon based pizza chain.
It seems like he's maybe just in a different exit of Times Square.
And then he goes into space.
Then he starts riding through the skies.
When you meet you, you run into you, who we've established in the pre show,
likes puppies. Yes.
You is like,
is it the broadest performance ever given that anyone on camera?
Yes. So like the most hyperactive.
Well, you know, I'd have to like watch every tape of all that
and 90s Nickelodeon to be sure.
But I think this might be the broadest performance ever given.
I know a sketch like thing.
It's a comedy subject that I think is on its way of like, oh, teen girls.
Yeah. And I think like now most people doing comedy are like,
well, that's kind of diminishing to a large segment of young people is like,
oh, young women.
Disgusting. Like that's not what's funny there.
You're just being cruel.
You're being it's a trope that was already super creaky.
It was such well-worn territory.
And now in the last four years, people have been like,
it's actually kind of fucked up that it's a subject of ridicule to begin with.
Like it went from being unoriginal to now being borderline offensive.
Yeah, it's like, well, young women like young men have interests
and inner lives and intelligence and emotions like.
Yeah, it's like Jimmy doing a fucking impression of a 10 year old boy.
Let's act like that's any better.
You did that on SNL a number of times.
And it was funny.
This is the lesson learned by Sebastian Maniscalco at the VMAs
when his whole monologue to an audience of 12 year old girls was,
and we don't want to have our safe spaces.
OK, none of that PC.
And everyone just stared at him like, why are you like,
what are you scolding us about here?
Yeah, that may have that.
And then like, I can't artists doing the most high budget
Lizzo just doing costume changes within songs like
and just dancers and crazy like sets and yeah.
But doesn't that relationship, the relationship between Sebastian Maniscalco
trying to control an audience
who are there for the exact opposite of what he's good at?
He's good at yelling about ma's zucchini.
They are there to see singing and dancing and not hear about ma zucchini.
The Sunday sauce, it's got to cook all day.
It's got so much meat in it.
A complete mismatch of performer tradition and built in audience, right?
Compared to people like Lizzo at the top of their game,
exactly who the audience wants to see using the night to the best of their ability.
Isn't that kind of the relationship between the Jimmy Fallon ride
and most other rides at Universal?
Or you just look at it and you're like, what are you doing here?
This is you have your own spaces where you work.
This is not it.
This could be a ride where we go somewhere that we couldn't go.
If I want to see a taping of the show, I'll go to New York and see a taping of the show.
But I truly think that would make Jimmy Fallon feel like his show wasn't valuable enough.
That's what it always comes down to for me.
Like when you talk through the logic cycles of how this ride could have been better,
any of those things necessitate taking Jimmy Fallon
and applying him to something entirely different or bigger than himself.
Hmm. Wow. Wow. That's very.
Sedy stuff is powerful stuff.
Psychology is the reason why the it's a weird ride.
Right. But if it's through television history, if it's more about sightseeing
through New York, if it's any of those things, it becomes less about him and his show.
It becomes more about him merely being the host for some fun ride.
You're going to go on. Can Tom Shales do a book or can Bill Carter do a book
on the making of this ride?
Because I would love to know
exactly what the genesis of it is.
What you're saying makes a lot of sense.
And I wonder if it's true.
I wonder if anyone actually has documented the process by which this went through.
It's all conjecture on my part, but I've watched this thing so many times.
I am saying what you're saying makes some sense.
I'm so obsessed with this ride.
I watch the ride through video as if it were the Zapruder film.
I study it obsessively.
I've done this for years.
It's one of the reasons I asked you guys to please, please do this episode
behind a paywall.
I've made other people watch it because I need other people to get infected
with the virus that is this ride.
And I just really try to figure out all the decisions that lead to this
where almost every choice it makes, it feels like is the worst one.
It's funny because Jimmy has taped it universal.
They build this day.
I think they build a stage looking out on the water at City.
Well, like they they shoot outside today.
That's not true. But they I think they did it inside.
But did they do it? OK.
I don't think he did an outdoor. I am pretty sure.
But he he gets I think he gets that the parks are fun.
Yeah, like he'll shoot.
I did a bit where it's like him and someone else ride the rock and rollercoaster.
Him and someone him and a guest ride rides with Kevin Hart.
I feel like it's like his most viewed video ever.
Yeah. Yeah.
So I think he does get that.
And I think like if they had just I don't know if they just divorced it
from the Tonight Show a little more.
Wait, maybe this is a good segue for me to talk about my favorite thing
that really ties it to the Tonight Show and to the legacy.
I have one more little clip.
I mentioned this when we talked about it the first time.
But this is one of my favorite things about the culture of this ride.
Is this moment where this universal executive is taking him around
and showing him the exhibit down in the bottom of the, you know, the lobby.
And, you know, with the little here's the Conan booth in the Leno booth.
And then he lights up at a very particular booth.
I've thought this is my version of this career films this clip.
Oh, Steve Allen.
He started the long day. Steve, we have arrived.
We have a ride.
Look what you made.
We have a ride at a amusement park, Universal Studios.
He would love this.
And then they just hang on him, looking wistfully at this tribute to Steve.
It's like he's mourning the death of Steve Allen.
He's even though this is a beautiful moment that we have at Tonight Show
Ride, it isn't entirely happy because of, of course, Steve Allen.
Couldn't be here.
We have a we have a ride, Steve.
In years, he died.
Steve, Steve, I know you died 20 years ago, but Steve, why can you be here?
He would have been 130.
They, why can you be 130 beer?
God, he would he would love this.
I know. I know that Steve Allen hated hippies and rock music
and thought they were destroying society.
I know that Steve Allen made Elvis perform in front of a literal hound dog
to humiliate him because that's how much he hated rock music.
But you would love this theme park rides.
He devoted the last like 15 years of his life to being part of the parents
television council to get obscene content, take it off of the air.
Steve, I know you were part of the parents television council.
And I know that right before you died, you wrote a book called
vulgarians at the gate about how Tupac is destroying the mental health of young
people, but still we have a ride, Steve.
Steve. Oh, my God.
We are the friends, Steve.
We have a ride. This isn't about me, Steve.
It's about us.
You did this. You did it.
This ride belongs to you as much as it does to me.
If you were to go on it, it would be exactly what you had in your head.
Steve Allen, who famously was always begging,
begging the Rockefellers to front him money to create attractions
at the World's Fair, he was.
He lived this life.
It was all he wanted.
He said, got an idea. That's a night rider. Right.
Can we build a rolling wooden roller coaster at Rye Playland
that goes through all the best bits from my tonight show?
And no one would ever let him do it.
It's a little it's a merry go round and it shows you all the best bits,
like the one where I read rock lyrics.
And that's the joke, because the rock lyrics are funny and bad.
The kids love it.
We did it, Steve.
We did it. Your team.
Jimmy does not know that Mr.
Steve Allen had a theme park presence before this, though.
What? What?
Had his hands at Disney's MGM Studios.
Wow. Yeah.
The cement. I don't know if they're still there, but he did have that.
Steve, they have your hand, Steve.
I checked Steve Allen theme parks before this, and I just found that
and then pictures of him and his kids at Disneyland in 1957.
So I did confirm the second most watched
video on the tonight shows YouTube page of all time
is Jimmy Fallon and Kevin Hart ride a roller coaster at Universal Orlando.
Wow. Six years ago.
I mean, before this open years before this open.
So the synergy was happening then.
One hundred and eleven million people watched that.
And then Jimmy said, I think I have a good pitch for a ride.
It's me cucking a bunch of people because their vehicle isn't as good as mine,
because it doesn't have underwater or space capabilities.
Or I don't want to miss this one.
It doesn't have hyper tube.
It can't you can't activate hyper tube from me, which,
if you haven't been on the ride, is how, you know, you can just fly up to space.
And that is safe.
And Jimmy can just float through space without a helmet.
But the one thing that you can't do is fall from the moon
off of a not completed theme park attraction.
You need a roller coaster to get back from the room, not from the moon,
not to the moon.
And then so if you're just falling, you're going to eat shit and die.
You need a hyper tube.
So that's why that's nightwriter can spit plastic out that forms a tube
that hardens as soon as you land on its front grill.
It produces a tube, which it can then ride through to safety.
But for miles and miles into space, this is like the longest
you just ran through.
I mean, breezed through so many humongous sci fi concepts that we must discuss.
One man, they could all be their own film.
Everything I just said, absolutely.
The tonight rider has no covering.
It is it is by all intents and purposes, an open air vehicle.
Right.
Convertible.
It's a go car.
It's supposed to be like a go car.
Yeah, it's a hover go car.
It looks like a Mario Kart ride.
It does.
It looks like a little card from Mario Kart, but he goes both underwater
and into space.
I think neither atmosphere does any sort of helmet presents itself.
Right.
There's never any covering.
It never turns into a bubble.
He's just safe and let's water.
The reason he goes into water, he's he's flying through the skies of New York City.
He's getting close to that old lady herself, the statue of liberty.
And then we tilt down to see that there is a checkpoint in the water
because this race seemingly happens enough that there are checkpoints
littered across New York City.
You know, there's a starting line in the hallways of 30 Rock,
but then there's another checkpoint somewhere on the streets, which he flies past.
And then this one is like a video game, like it's like electric, lit up
the word checkpoint three in a circle that he like dives through like a tunnel.
And there hasn't been that yet.
This is the first time it's happened.
It's very reminiscent of Echo the dolphin.
Absolutely.
Because I've been through every other checkpoint has been a banner
and now it's like a ring.
But the type of ring that only exists as a video game
can seat to help you win some sort of race that goes into multiple environments,
but does not actually represent a physical, tangible thing in that character's world.
It's like just a guideline for you, the player.
So he dives through that underwater, through the wreckage of various ships.
And of course, those famous New York City sharks
would come jumping at you.
That's why the Sully landing was so scary.
You know, those sharks were circling.
Fins to the left, fins to the right.
Amen, brother.
Jimmy Jimmy Buffett also was on the Jimmy Fallon at Universal
during that week.
Yeah. Wow.
Isn't it the shirt you bought, Jason, that he was wearing?
Oh, yes. I bought once very late at night.
I bought a Margaritaville shirt from the Margaritaville web store.
Full price, $40 shipping.
But that's the one he was wearing.
Jimmy was wearing. I was so excited.
And I was like, oh, it's the Lakers color shirt he was wearing on the Tonight Show.
Great shirt. Iconic.
Well, so, you know, the way you admire like a particular share outfit
or a Liberace outfit, each each Jimmy Buffett outfit is a unique flower.
Well, Bob Mackie designed that one, right?
His outfit for the Tonight Show in Orlando.
That was a Bob Mackie.
I believe so. Yeah. He hand laid each litter. Yes.
I'm just scrubbing through this again.
It's like he he when he goes underwater,
you're very close to the Statue of Liberty.
Then he goes underwater for a while, does a few rounds, it feels like.
Avoid several sharks and then pops up and no real distance has been traversed.
He is now just slightly closer to the Statue of Liberty,
even though it seems like he's been driving around in circles
and going like nautical miles and shit.
And then I was just going to say it does feel like a knockoff,
like when you play Mario Kart, but then you play like Sonic Racing All Stars
and you're like, this isn't the same.
This doesn't even too much of a compliment.
It feels like like Garfield racer.
Yes. Thank you. That's much better.
Yes. It feels like I don't know.
Garfield doesn't really belong in a racing game, but it was a cheap license.
Right. We knew what the track was.
Then when he gets out of the water, he's closer to the Statue of Liberty.
He flies up her side and you see that the Statue of Liberty is now wearing a sash
because she is now the fourth checkpoint.
And he dings her torch.
He hits it.
And that is that is the indication of the checkpoint has to keep her humble.
It does feel like he like Jimmy Fallon in a video game is a cleaner premise.
Like, like all of a sudden we're in the Jimmy Fallon six.
Jimmy Fallon 64.
Yeah, right. The pre show is hey, look, great news.
You just got hired to be a writer at the Sniteshaw.
Now, unfortunately, we have to warn you before every taping.
Jimmy challenges his writers to a Mario Kart game and you have to lose.
OK, are you ready? Buckle in.
Like that would be a better, cleaner walk for this ride.
Yeah, but no, but then he goes from Statue of Liberty.
I forgot this. He goes from Statue.
I'm just rewatching this video over and over again.
He goes from Statue of Liberty to Empire State Building,
which feels kind of backwards because we've worked so hard to get out of New
York City, right, to get underwater, to get into into the skies.
But then he circles back around into Manhattan, Midtown Manhattan again,
goes up the side of the Empire State Building, where now
hashtag the panda is 60 feet tall, which he calls out that there's no explanation.
Finally, a meta type joke, but there's nothing else like that in the ride.
Right. And then you crash land in the Bowery ballroom and hop on stage with Prince.
The next move is Hyperdrive Up to the Moon,
which has Race Through New York starring Jimmy Fatten, etched onto its side
permanently, which I should like because it's kind of a spiritual heir to that.
In the Back to the Future ride, you crash into TVs that say back to the future,
despite that logo having no meaning to Doc Brown.
Yes. No, that is good. I like that.
But I do like that.
Do I only like that because it's what I grew up with?
Would I like this moon thing if I grew up with it?
But for how much the narrative crux of this ride ends up being, oh, no,
we are going to die trying to get back to Earth.
The journey from Empire State Building to the moon is maybe one second.
With no sort of talk about how we got there.
Then you're just on the moon. The roots are playing on the moon.
In helmets. They need helmets, right?
Aren't they? Yeah. Yeah.
Jimmy is wearing full spacesuits, suits, full helmets.
Jimmy, of course, takes the moment to write a thank you note.
Our favorite funniest thing.
It makes me which now this another bizarre thing.
And I don't think the joke that he I don't think this thank you note joke is bad,
but it is thank you notes is their version of a refillable joke bag thing.
We do it every week and we will do this for decades and decades.
And, you know, the way these bits are done on shows,
you take 150 of them and you get them down to 10.
Here they have committed to one that will play forever.
So if you laugh at it the first time,
you will certainly not laugh at it the second time, much less third, fourth, sixth.
And the and the joke is, excuse me, as I as I paraphrase here, something like.
Thank you, Moon Dust, for making dirt feel special.
It's for turning regular dirt into moon dust.
Thank you, Moon. Thank you, the moon.
Jesus Christ. Again, I don't mind it.
I don't mind the like odd way of saying the moon.
I think he delivers those jokes well.
I like the way he kind of like does that big pause before he starts writing the joke.
Yeah, I kind of like that.
That weird repetitive rhythm.
Thank you, the moon for turning regular dirt into moon dust.
And then he blows and blows.
He met this is one of the stranger tableaus in it to me is Jimmy Fallon blow
blowing dust at you and then kind of like sweetly staring at you,
kind of like seducing you with his eyes as he floats through space in a full suit,
full suit and tie without a helmet.
One of the stranger images, I think, in theme park history.
So now, right, which also raises the question,
how is he staying in the Tonight Rider at all?
Like, it feels like gravity or the lack thereof is trying to pull him
floating into space, but he seemingly gets to choose on and off
when he's sitting normally behind the wheel of a car.
It's kind of godlike, basically.
I mean, Jimmy is kind of godlike.
We have to acknowledge it.
It's like when you're playing like superheroes as a kid and it's like,
what's your power, Johnny?
It's like I'm all powers.
I can I can I can do all powers.
The way Leno was dethronable, I think maybe he maybe maybe Leno had god powers
and he passed them on to he did not pass them on to Conan and he did pass them on to Fallon.
The immortality that he'll never go away.
You can't get him out of the throne.
The fictional character of Jimmy Fallon in the ride
race through New York, starring Jimmy Fallon, does have big infinity plus one
energy, as as you're saying, Jason, that everything is like, no, you're infinity.
I'm infinity plus one.
I can do it even a little bit better than you.
And I can choose to change the rules of my reality at any moment to my whims.
He is no rules.
There's no rules.
Jimmy's got in this.
Jimmy's got. Oh, cool.
Oh, I'm God.
I did it. I'm God.
Oh, my God. I'm God.
Oh, God. I'm God.
Thank you, Megagod, for making me God.
If Jimmy does a funny cover of your song, that's like you've made it.
That's like, you know, Johnny waving you over, waving you over to the couch.
The dream, you know, the dream.
Can I maybe are we done?
We can go back to anything, but I want to bring up an idea real quick here
that maybe the four of us are dead wrong.
Oh, OK. Oh, yes.
I'm interested. Yes.
So I was looking at friend of the show, Lentestas Company Touring Plans.
And I think we should do this for more rides.
Touring Plans does audience reaction.
They get ratings from audience to see if people like rides and shows.
And I was just doing a couple.
I just looked at a couple and Fast and the Furious does have lower
ratings than this Jimmy Fallon ride.
I will say Jimmy Fallon is neck and neck with the E.T.
ride. What audience satisfaction.
In fact, Jimmy Fallon is a half star above when it comes to teens.
Well, allow me to say I will say this.
Teens are more likely to know who Jimmy Fallon is than they are.
E.T. There just isn't a new E.T. thing.
So if it's just awareness, that makes sense to me.
They love E.T. from the commercial, but they don't know maybe where other
places you can find E.T. would be.
Obviously, love the commercial.
So let's let's connect to other dots here.
Jimmy Fallon and we were sort of talking around this, his success, the
popularity of his show represents a sort of larger cultural tide turn in
comedy towards everything's fun, positive vibes, sort of prom king humor,
but also that's so much of Fallon is about like, you know, this thing.
We're referencing things, you know, that so many of his bits are like
reunions or restagings of things, or it's what if this person saying that
other song, you know, like, it's a lot of that comedy by association stuff
where you have to imagine if you are a big Jimmy Fallon fan, I guess you
would find this ride funny.
Maybe, but I think I think the definition of funny is I think you'd
find it fun.
I I've this is a too big of a theory to get into, but I think people have
changed. I think people now describe things as funny that don't make them
laugh. I think if you think it was fun, that was fun.
I think the definition of funny is maybe if it makes you smile, that means
funny. But that's kind of my point is like, is it testing better with young
people than ET because they like they're on a ride that they kind of
know like they feel special because they get it.
Do they know Jimmy Fallon?
Do they think about the Tonight Show as an entity or do they know him just
from clips going viral on YouTube?
I think they know him from clips and I think the exact things that this
ride is referencing are the things that don't get turned into clips on YouTube.
Yeah.
Hmm.
Hmm. Does any I was going to ask this.
What's the percentage of the audience, particularly the teen audience who
could do who goes into that ride every day who could tell you who Higgins is?
Great question.
Does Higgins register in any way to people from other countries to teen?
Is there because he there's a huge poster of them.
We're going a lot of real estate to Higgins.
Just one percent of the audience in this ride know Higgins.
Maybe we can team up with Len and the Touring Plants team to poll people about
specific things like do you know who Higgins is?
Do you know who hashtag the panda is?
And we can do very hyper specific podcasts, the ride specific polling that
will help for our purposes.
Yeah.
Like, do you do?
Do you do you like Jack Parr better or do you like Steve Allen better?
You know, this is what maybe if we just tack on they're already surveying people
as they come off rides.
Now we can we can.
So we're going to engage in our very first survey.
This is an interesting new development of the show.
I think I think I don't want to speak for Len already.
I mean, but I think maybe he would be interested in us getting some hyper
specific questions on these.
I do specific.
Yeah, I will admit like we probably have pretty we're not necessarily the target
audience for this.
I think if you work in comedy for a little while, you start to you start to get a
little weird in your taste.
Yeah.
The funniest thing to me recently has just been repeating Jack Parr and Steve
Allen's names a countless number of times.
Yeah, so I get I get that I would not necessarily be the target audience.
But in terms of the rule, the rules of theme park, I think this this violates a
lot of the rules.
Yes, like successful park endeavors.
I will say seniors gave this ride four stars and gave ET four stars.
Jesus Christ.
They're both very clean.
You mean older people, not high school seniors, right?
Not high school seniors.
Right.
OK.
How did freshmen rate it?
They said it sucks.
The big one.
What do they know?
Because seniors rock and freshmen drool.
Yeah.
Seniors.
But seniors gave Fast and Furious two and a half stars.
A little body.
So seniors are not just giving out four stars left and right.
I don't get this.
I mean, I do agree with what Jason's saying that like perhaps no one is is less in the
wheelhouse for this ride than a comedy fan, because this ride is very much like comedy
adjacent.
It's very much as you said, Scott, like, oh, you think it's funny because it made you smile
a little bit.
But I even feel like most people who I guess, you know, love Fallon, watch Fallon clips on
YouTube all the time, I would question how often they're actually laughing at them or
if they're just sort of thinking like, this is charming.
I like seeing this person do this thing because in so many ways what his show has succeeded
at is closer to something like the match game, you know, or Hollywood Squares.
The kinds of things I think the success of the games on his show has helped lead to that
there's all these primetime game shows.
Absolutely right.
He's he's in a lot of ways more of a game show host than he is a talk show host.
I do think it's interesting.
I've seen a little bit of his quarantine stuff, which I know he's had this like big boost
in popularity again because of filming at home and having his wife and his kids involved.
Everyone thinks his kids are so cute and whatever.
But we're in the ride too.
There's a little cameo.
And I'm going to send a little photo to the chat for you guys just so you can see.
Give me a second here as I prep this.
Sure.
But I watched a little bit of it because I've been curious to see like how different people
are handling this different entertainers adjusting to quarantine and stuff.
And I found him a lot more engaging and charming now than I have in years because it feels like
now that he doesn't have as many gimmicks he can rely on, he can't play games with people.
He actually has to like sit down and have an extended conversation with someone over
Zoom because there's nothing else to do.
I'm starting to feel like I'm actually seeing him as a real person for the first time in a while.
Like he's got a very different energy in those interviews.
And even just the fact that he's like not shaving and he's not wearing a suit, he doesn't seem
like overly excitable.
Like he's like actually asking questions and listening to their answers and things like that.
I think he's adjusted better to quarantine world than a lot of talk shows.
I would almost argue that someone like Colbert, who is a lot better at sort of like the
performing and the comedy of everything, has had a slightly trickier time adjusting to the lack of
a studio audience because he's maybe trying to do a lot of the same energy just without a crowd.
Whereas Falonet feels like has totally reset here.
It's a new show.
Yeah.
I just sent you guys how Deadline looks right now.
The entirety of Deadline's home page is bought out by For Your Consideration, Jimmy Fallon ads,
which are now just for fronting his daughters.
So it says vote for Jimmy Fallon and Jimmy Fallon is crossed out with a red crayon and it says Winnie
plus Franny.
And then the Tonight Show logo is written in crayon.
It's like they're trying to sell his daughters as the star of the show over him now, which just
speaks to the idea that it's crazy to invest tens of millions of dollars into a ride based around
a show where public perception can change it that radically at any moment.
This list is a ride literally of a different show.
It is forcibly due to the coronavirus.
It is a he is not doing the show and already hadn't been doing Gary and you for a long time.
It's a weird.
This is now like a time travel ride to 2017.
This ride was like created pre Trump.
It was made while A.D.
Miles was still the main creative voice in the show behind the scenes.
You know, like everything about it has shifted.
Mm hmm.
Which makes it a little interesting, I guess.
It's thinking of it as a period piece somehow in three years.
This ride has become a very antiquated throwback.
Yeah.
An archive. I think I mean, that picture you sent is charming and I do.
I am in favor of like.
I understand that people want like positive positive stuff, light stuff like.
Yeah, I totally understand.
We television has always had that.
I am in favor of it.
I like a little of that, too.
I do think the reunions, the remember this like that, I think, is very realistic.
And I think it's maybe in a larger view, it's like, oh, this kind of seems like the death of culture.
Like we've given up on creating new entities and we're just.
Oh, you know, we're just swimming in the backwater of when we had money to make good movies
and allowed people the creative liberties to make good movies.
But also one of those things.
But it's like the 70s again, where they're like, remember the good times of happy days in the 50s?
It's like that wasn't what the 50s was like.
But it's also Jimmy doing these reunions and these tributes to things where you're like,
I don't think that actually times out properly.
Like you're you're doing reunions for your target audience and the things that they grew up with.
And Jimmy is pretending that he loved things that came 15 years after he was the right age to enjoy them.
Right.
Oh, like 90s full house sort of.
Yeah, there's stuff like that where I'm just like, or even now I feel like they are tiptoeing into like early 2000s stuff.
And it just speaks to this persona of Jimmy just being like the guy who's like a fan of everything.
He just like loves everything.
Like everything's great.
Like it's just like really positive.
This is like so awesome.
You know, the cast of The Squid and the Whale altogether in one room.
Whoa, the District Nine gang is back.
I remember like in the first couple of years before he went to Tonight Show and he was still on late night
when he would do like a special episode that was getting all the living Monty Python members together again.
Or there was one where they had Dick Cavett on and they like recreated the Dick Cavett set.
And it was so bizarre because you could tell that he really cared.
Like these are people who actually were influential and important to him starting out in comedy.
And he's a big fan and he has real questions to ask.
And clearly this episode is a labor of love and the audience just doesn't give a shit.
Like you can see that like he's like, like, Dick, you'd like created everything.
Like you changed the game for all of us.
Like I'm rocking in your footsteps and everything.
And the audience just has no idea who Dick Cavett is.
And I feel very quickly after that, it's like the show is now trying to reunite the cast of Full House or say by the bell, you know,
like doing that as like an event that stretches over months and acting like I care so much personally.
Me, Jimmy Fallon, I care about the idea of getting Mario Lopez to wear his weird half cutoff shirt again.
You know, to that point, it's kind of what you have to give yourself over to to be the host of the Tonight Show.
I have one more clip I want to show.
There's another thing I've thought about a lot since it happened.
And this is from before the ride.
This is when he when he did a week of shows in Orlando, as we referenced.
And he so there's a kind of an extended thing, him like, you know, checking out, you know, Diagon Alley and all this stuff.
And then finally, it's time for him to tape the show.
So we end up with this moment. You guys seeing this kind of yellow frame here?
Yeah. Yeah. OK. So this I mean, it'll play more.
It doesn't really work as audio, but just just so you guys can see this moment, I think,
taught me what it takes to be a crowd pleaser, to be the host of the Tonight Show and see if you catch what I'm saying.
But when I show you this.
So this is a clip of he's running down a red carpet to the big universal gates
and he is high fiving all of the universal characters who, by the way,
this clip also exemplifies to me the universal experience of, you know,
there's the Disney gang and, you know, goofy kind of fits alongside the genie or whatever, even though they're from different eras.
And in this, Jimmy is high fiving a lineup that includes the Simpsons and Sight Shabab and Thing One, the man in the yellow hat,
a lot of rabbits from Hop. Yeah.
He knows characters from Hop. So it's so much Hop. A lot of Hop.
You catch him noticeably missing Shrek's hand.
Shaggy and Scooby, Egyptian Beetle Bailey.
I love it. I'm loving this.
I mean, this is universal right here as well. This is universal.
Here comes Beetlejuice. There's like, I think, Groucho Marx at the end of the line.
Those chickens are also from Hop.
So much Hop. Yeah. I mean, I think no clip exemplifies the vibe of universal better than this.
But also, just to go back to this frame where he's kind of he's smiling and high fiving.
And I just thought, like, this is why.
OK, Leno won. He beat Letterman because he would go shake the hands of the affiliates.
That's what being the host of the night show is. Letterman is like a snarky guy.
Conan's a judgy snarky guy.
Leno shook hands and Fallon high fives the cat in the hat with a huge grin on his face.
And that's why it's that's why these guys are doing these jobs.
And it doesn't stay, you know, then Letterman and Conan went and did their own thing,
which I guess could not be the tonight show.
This odd, like, cursed idol that people end up with.
It's also like, look, that's that's a lane.
It's hard to do. You know, I certainly caught that.
I certainly couldn't.
I understand it takes skill and it takes effort and whatever to be America's best friend.
Like, that's a full time job, both in terms of the energy it takes and the sort of management of your own personal brand
and the control over every tendril of it and being equally positive about everything you see.
I get that. But it also feels like.
He he and and for a long time, he used to be a big gripe of mine of just like this feels like the end of sort of specific comedy viewpoints.
Right. When when the show was doing so well, when not only did Conan fail on the tonight show,
but Jay came back and then Jimmy took over Jay and it was succeeding.
It was like, I guess I don't know.
Is this just what people want now?
Do they just want a guy who seems like their friend who is like completely unwilling to take any stance on anything?
Even beyond like Jay Leno going after OJ Simpson, you're like that feels like it would be too aggressive for Jimmy Fallon.
You know, and he was forced to change in Trump world and for the hair ruffle.
So he does the hair ruffle.
And it's the opposite of what Jay did, which is like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, hete.
And what Jay did, which is like, Jay was so softball.
He was so friendly to celebrities.
He let Hugh Grant rehabilitate his image.
Letterman was a little too like toothy.
And so Jay got him back by shaking the audience hands and being everyone's best friend.
And instead, it was this like cultural collapse moment where Fallon ruffles Trump's hair and then everyone decides we don't want frivolous bullshit.
We need people to like take this seriously.
And suddenly Colbert just grabs the ring from him and has not let go.
And Colbert has just become more and more political.
And he just has been running circles around Fallon in the ratings.
I also think that coincides with this idea of just like, why is it only a certain type of affable white man in a suit who gets to ascend to this type of position?
Why is only this kind of like personality lists, you know, sort of like I'm everyone's friends.
I'm a standard, inoffensively handsome man who gets to do this sort of job.
Like all this stuff is like starting to come to a head and be reexamined right around the time that they're reopening this ride or they're opening this ride rather.
Yeah. And now we have it.
As we said, it is a it's a like time capsule of already a bygone era.
What happens? Does he keep being the host?
Does he? What happens to this ride if he is not the host?
Or do things just just trump out of there?
And now we want and the virus ends or this lockdown ends and now we want to be silly fun again.
It's it's it's hard to know.
I think whatever 2020 is going to have.
What a statement. 2020 is going to have a lot of impact on a lot of things.
But I am interested in this specific area.
Like, what will we be ready for fun again?
Or do we have to mire in a bunch of fucking post corona misery comedy, non comedy?
It also just feels like the idea of having like the late night talk show as the thing that everyone can come to as this sort of like great cultural meeting place is kind of out the window, not just because there are so many more talk shows now,
but because there are also so many other types of content in general and you have generations who are never going to think about the idea of sitting down and watching a full hour plus of one person hosting a late night talk show, you know,
because they want their content in quick bites.
But here's that's what it boils down to.
They want one of two things.
They either want the one funny thing that Ariana Grande did on Fallon last night cut down to three minutes or they want to watch seven hours of Ninja.
You know, like they will watch like that for them is closer to a talk show is like watching YouTubers do like extended live streams and make appearances on each other shows like that's exciting to them or they want to see short form stuff.
But I think the idea of like an entire talk show that is still holding on to these sort of like classical tropes of like you have the opening and the monologue and then there's a little sketch and then there are two guests and then there's a little like interactive thing and then there's a musical act of whatever.
I think they would just be like, I don't need all of this.
I'm only going to watch the parts that I want to watch and only if there's someone I like on it.
I'm not going to tune in every day.
Something Conan knows really well and I think Conan's like deconstruction while keeping the core but we're also going to do the podcast and it's going to be clips and I think he gets he knows that like and for an hour a night you watch your old pal.
It's just kind of not there.
I think Colbert is also wisely going like I need to do what Daily Show was doing during the Bush era like I need to be the show where like all the angry liberals can unwind and have a laugh and it's the reason why he's retained an audience better than Fallon because the types of people who would want to watch a show that's just like we're all friends we're having fun we're playing games are maybe getting distracted by entirely different types of entertainment.
Whereas Colbert is doing the show for people who still want to be watching a nightly talk show like he is still doing the show for the targeted audience who likes that format and speaking to their concerns and their anger and there have been those two big New York Times pieces on Fallon in the last couple of years.
One was the Itzkoff one that was like done a couple months after the Trump thing that was him like the first sort of like ding in his armor trying to come back from that and explain it and he just keeps on saying like I just don't want to make a challenging show like my goal is like people have tough lives and I want to do a show where they can have fun at the end of the day and I question whether there is a large enough portion of the viewing public who views watching that entire show as the right type of entertainment.
So that's the type of way to unwind you know if they're individual segments much like James Corden where there are little bits and pieces that travel wildly across the internet that people love but that like the talk show is starting to become more and more of a niche thing for comedy nerds again and then if you're not doing that you're a delivery system for viral clips for later.
So do we think that then that that Millennials are below or teens you know in 2020 do they still want to take a race through New York where they get to smell pizza and avoid a shark.
I have data that says they do apparently and learning to one man.
Maybe the way they think of Jimmy Fallon like they don't even really think of him as oh host of the Tonight Show that show whose format I know very well.
They think of him as just like he's a guy who shows up and does stuff he like hosts a bunch of things. He's just like very positive and excitable. Why wouldn't he take me on a race through New York.
Teens don't know the history the rich history of this institution that this is what the lobby is for this what the lobby is for Steve Allen.
Yeah, we did. It's all right Steve Steve. They don't remember you Steve. I'm trying to let them know.
I'm telling your story Steve Steve. I'll never let your legend die Steve. Is there a video of broker in the Today Show Cafe being like this is for you Matt.
They do say.
Oh no.
I'll help them develop the menu. OK.
Well we'll do it. We will do a longer episode about the Today Show Cafe. Actually one more question. Do the do you think that the host of the Today Show have a today writer.
Boy, no. These are the kinds of questions I want this ride to answer. You know if they're going to open up the world in this way I want them to really dig into it.
Get into logic. I'm glad we got into it. But I feel like we should have this up for all of our personal health. We've transcended several meal breaks. Did we do we know. Did we get the record. Did we win. Did we win.
Did we win our zoom to New York. The record.
The record I believe was I don't know if you count Hard Rock Park because we broke it into two after the fact. Yeah. If we keep this as one is the longest single episode is Dogpatch USA with Chris Cantwell.
I want to say that we broke it but the listener might be looking at a number that says otherwise. What was the dog patch episode. Like 245. I think at this point we're at three hours. Yeah. Yeah. I think it's close to three hours.
So we'll see. I don't know because we took we did take breaks. Yeah. That's why I'm not completely sure. But I just want to it's a it's a ride about a competition and I feel like we all need to collectively win the competition.
Break the record. If we didn't if I put this all together and we didn't we will come back and do as many minutes as it takes to get over the record. Great. Great. Yeah.
To nudge us over so that we barely like the audience barely snuff out Jimmy in his tonight writer leaving him looking the fool with his suit partially on fire.
I well I hope I hope that we did it. I hope I hope we did it and thanks for helping us do it. Griffin Newman you survived podcast ride. Oh my god. What a discussion.
I think my least favorite ride of all time. I've been on it's a favor. Do we have choices for that. Gentlemen my knee jerk is journey into imagination new version. But do you have a knee jerk. What's the worst mission space.
Mission space Jason it might be this this might just be a little too cynical. I would spend all day in in 30 rocket on this ride then go in that little mission space capsule and look at that low like low quality screen mission space rocks.
Just scramble my brain King. Yeah. Mission space can step on me. I felt like I was going to die going on the one and it's I mean that's it's crushing my chest. It's an acquired taste. It's an acquired taste. But what can I say I'm a simp for mission space.
Do you have anything to plug. Let's exit through the 30. Oh wait what's that Mike. Jason would let mission space make love to his wife.
To to use a word we've used before to cook. Yes. I was saying I was saying it in the more romantic term. That's our that's your version of seats to. Yes. Let's exit through the 30 rock gift shop full of toy t-shirts with our buddies the tight pants and you. But also is there anything that we can buy in that gift shop that you would like to plug. Oh sure.
How soon is this episode coming out. Do you know yet. It might be delayed a tiny bit. It might end up like 1st of August. One blank check my podcast blank check the Griffin David coast with the film critic David Sims. We're going through Robert Zemeckis will be starting Robert Zemeckis right around this point. A couple movies that have resulted in rides. That's right. Wait what else. OK. This makes me sure there's forest gum pleading to the restaurant chain which is not a. Yeah.
Roger. That's right. Yeah. It's actually weird. There was never a Polar Express ride but I guess that falls into Warner Brothers weird history with the parks. There is some weird Polar Express for the X. Yeah. Thing which I don't know if that counts as a in the 3D movie series that we've been doing. Is that worth talking about. Could we will we decide no but then do it anyway and then take three hours on it.
Probably yes. Yes. If you want it if you want to if your lizard ship does not want to deal with Polar Express 4D and you want to cover it over here at an equivalent time let us know. I would love nothing more. And I have been doing this show called the George Lucas talk show. My friend Connor Ratliff is one of the finest people in the world plays George Lucas and I play Wado the toy Darien from Phantom Menace and the
We used to do is a live stage show at the UCB in New York City and now it's become weekly twitch shows on planet scum dot live. So tune to those. Those are every Sunday.
I think the first toy that I bought for my son was a Wado from from Orlando. Yes. Yeah. I love those the hand stitched looking toys at Galaxy's Edge. I think those aredirect.
Those are top notch. I thought I was finally going to get to go to Galaxy's Edge and so many friends of mine have gone there have taken a photo of the Wado for me and said do you want me to get one for you. And I said no I will be going there soon enough. I want to have the experience of buying one for myself. And now who knows when I'll ever get that chance.
Torture torture or terrible. It makes this time is making us like all pent up and full of rage and we take it out on things like this ride based on a talk show.
Absolutely. It's very helpful to do so. I hope you listeners enjoyed it. Stay tuned to the second gate. Lots more stuff coming. You already do all the things if you're here.
Although if you're new and came to listen to this episode there's always fun stuff at the second gate and then be sure to follow us on Facebook and Twitter and Instagram. Anything else Mike Jason.
No I'm good. I think that's it.
Well all right we did it and I do well you know what I do I want to say is just like this one's for Steve. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah Steve. All right Steve. Steve we did a podcast about your ride Steve. Steve Steve Steve.
We have a podcast. We did a podcast Steve. Bye everybody. Bye.