FOREVER!
DOG!
May the road rise to meet you, may the wind be at your back.
Here on Podcast the Rides European Vacation.
I'm Jason Chariton, here as always with Michael Carlson.
Oh, hello there, right?
Faith and Bogor, yes, that's correct.
Okay, great. I'm here.
And Scott Caradner, of course.
Oh, I have to say, uh, uh, one love, one life, uh, elevation tour now.
That's, Bono counts as Irish, right?
Sure. Like they say at Ben against Slantja.
Uh...
Are you gonna do the voice the whole episode?
I'm not gonna do the voice the whole episode.
I'm already well past the end point of the voice.
You know what I should have said?
I should have been like, oh, my name is Chief O'Hara.
Because that's all I know about that, is that he was the, uh, side, what was he?
He was the cop in Gotham on the 60s Batman show.
On 60s Batman, yeah.
He was always in full dress blues.
That's right. And he and Commissioner Gordon were incompetent.
Yes.
They couldn't get anything done.
And they were just at the mercy of Batman.
Yes.
Uh...
The only Irish representation in film or TV you were aware of for some time.
Up until right now, I think.
Until today, until the place we're going in, and the character, which I imagine will be a lot of the source of the episode.
Look, I'll be honest. It's crazy that the theme park exists.
Uh, that's fine.
I don't almost give a shit now that I've found this certain character that we're all gonna talk about today.
I'm completely with you, yes.
But before that character, our guest character for today.
Yes.
Uh, Jason, you wanna do the accent?
Yeah, Jason. Do the voice. Do the accent.
Yeah, yeah.
You gotta give everyone.
Well, she's a bonny lass, all right.
It's Marissa Strickland, one of our first guests, finally returning home to podcast the ride.
Hoi hoi hoi hoi hoi!
And there it is, the national motto of the country.
It's hoi hoi hoi.
Hoi hoi hoi.
Of my ancestral homeland.
Hi, guys.
I'm thrilled to be here. This is a true delight.
Yeah, thanks for doing this.
Thanks for being interested in this park and this certain character that we're about to get to.
Ah, delightful.
Jason, do you have a whole plan here or should we just, should we say it?
Do we reveal what we're doing and why, if there's a why?
Well, I think the only thing, cause Marissa, I asked you to be on this episode,
cause when Scott, you told us about this park, I was like, we should have Marissa on for this one.
And you guys said, oh, has she been there?
And I went, no, this character just has the most Marissa energy I have ever encountered.
Well, it's a European spokes character, which I believe Marissa introduced me to another character many years ago who I was unaware of, Mafalda.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, Mafalda is my childhood.
Right. If you wanted to speak a little bit about Mafalda before we get to our topic.
Well, she's a Spanish language little girl who's kind of a, you know, the world isn't treating her so well.
She's kind of a Cathy.
But I think she's in fact like Argentine or something.
But, you know, she's known throughout the Spanish world.
And she, you know, she's just kind of like a hrump.
You know, things aren't going well for her.
And that's that's what I read during my childhood.
And she was your favorite character in fiction.
I really liked her. Yeah, she was great.
I also I also was fond of a fairy tale called The Little Lame Prince.
It was a prince that couldn't walk.
My parents made me weird.
Well, sure. You lived in Europe for a little while, right?
I did. Yeah, yeah, yeah. I lived in Spain for almost two years at two different times during my childhood.
OK. Yeah. And then in college, you were in Prague.
Right. Right nearby. I was in Hungary.
So just south. Yeah. In Budapest.
And did you ever encounter the character we're talking?
I know that you weren't in the specific spots, but no, I haven't encountered this character.
I think this character is very delightful.
I would say previous iterations of this character are cuter to me than the current iteration.
OK, that's fair. You guys can you know, I you know, let's just say his name, you know, we all want to say it together.
We all want to say, yeah, sure. That sounds nice. All right. All right.
Three, two, one. Mr. Tato.
We're so excited to talk about Mr. Tato.
And I guess incidentally, Tato Park, the theme park that bears his name and the name of the the chip brand that he endorses, rather crisp brand.
This is a theme park built around the factory of an Irish potato crisp brand.
And I think, you know, I think we were aware of it. I think we knew about it.
I think it was on my little short list, but I wrote down almost nothing about it.
And then we did throw it out to the audience.
Hey, where should we go if we do this European thing?
And this is the most biggest audience influence, I think, on this series.
And I want to give credit to to Sean P. O'Brien, perhaps Irish himself, or at least sounds as such, who said we should go to Tato Park in Ireland for everybody's favorite theme park based on a cheese and onion potato crisp.
And there was a photo of Mr. Tato with it.
And I just, boy, I started staring and I just had a feeling.
Sometimes you just have a nice feeling in your heart.
And I sent it to you guys and we all agreed.
And parks were bumped apart.
Parks were bumped because of this.
Yeah.
Thrown into the end of the shitter, you know, the dustbin of history.
It seems odd at first.
But then you remember we have Hershey Park in America, which has anthropomorphic candy bars running around and they have giant weird googly eyes and they have Santa hats on and they have like ascots at Halloween.
Like, this isn't as strange as it first appears.
So I think it's in the family of stuff already that with the curiosities that we all have in common.
Sorry, really quick.
They have ascots at Halloween.
Well, they have costumes at Halloween.
And in my mind, they have kind of like one of the maybe the Hershey bar itself has like out of a Dracula type kind of ascot and cape situation going on.
Don't quote me on that.
I know the listeners are going to be very upset if there is not a photo of Hershey bar wearing an ascot.
But if there's not, if somebody wouldn't mind mocking one up on Photoshop, I'd appreciate it.
Yeah.
Don't forget to a lot of Bush Gardens have a brewery next to them, or at least the one in Virginia where they brew beer because it's Bush.
So like they brew beer.
Right. So when my family when I was like in middle school and we went to Bush Gardens in Virginia, we took a tour of the brewery and then my parents got free beer at the end of it.
And the monorail that took us there broke down for a while.
So we were just sitting in the cafeteria waiting and it's it's stunk.
This this place is factory tour scenes much more pleasant.
Right. Flavored crisps of the Tato Company, which include cheese and onion, salt and vinegar, smoky bacon, prawn cocktail and the limited edition Tex-Mex.
Why do we what do we think of these?
I don't think we've gotten to try this particular brand.
I don't know if it's available in America.
I'm not sure I like the sound of prawn cocktail, but I could be wrong.
I don't mean that's. Yeah.
What was the name? No, I just don't think it's like to me, prawn cocktail sounds like a flavor that exists in other parts of the world and would be scrumptious.
But maybe isn't for American tastes.
But I don't know. It's possible stuff for American taste.
Prawn itself sounds so unappetizing.
Prawn, I don't it's prawn sounds like it's like alive when you eat it and it's going to latch onto your tongue while you're trying to chew it.
Like, that's what I think of when I think of prawn.
But I'm willing to try it. I'm willing to do.
I think we maybe there was a version of this podcast where we like spent a lot of money and had it imported and we would have all tried it.
And also there's a version where I ordered a thing I just found existed today.
Mr. Tato's autobiography.
Oh, that exists.
We got to postpone. Can we postpone?
We should postpone.
But I think we'll just do it.
And then maybe there'll be an addendum later once I finally figured out.
I was so desperate to find an ebook of Mr. Tato's autobiography.
I put my credit card in a website that I'm very sure is fraudulent.
Like I was like I was like, oh, my God, I found this.
It's an hour to go before the pockets. I need to read some of this at least.
Oh, this site seems to have an ebook of it.
Credit card, credit card error message.
Then I like Google what the website was.
And it's like, oh, yeah, this is a scam.
I am for sure getting my identity stolen because of Mr. Tato and my quest for information about him.
And it was like four thousand dollars to the IRS.
The IRA keeps a few irons in the fire just in case this shit hits the fan in Belfast again, you know, just to get a little, you know, slush fund.
And part of that is stealing credit cards from Tato book purveyors, browsers.
Well, look, if it helps them, I don't mind if they want to take a couple grand from my credit card account.
I can tell you this. Mr. Tato ran for office in 2014.
Oh, I know all. Yes, I know all about it.
You know all about that. I found one seemingly one guy's blog where he was very mad that they, I guess, polls.
Some polls are for political advertising in Ireland and they thought it was very uncouth that they put the like Tato for office posters on them.
Let's describe before there's a couple of other things I like to talk about, obviously.
But let's describe Mr. Tato before we get rolling here.
Marissa, do you have a description? You always very good with descriptors.
Um, OK.
Well, I see yellow.
He's yellow. I think he looks a little lumpy.
You know, there's some lumps and bumps.
He's a potato. He's got a darling little hat like a short little black straw hat is what I'm imagining.
But it could be made of felt or something.
It might be silk. It's possible.
Yes, it's a little like a Heisenberg hat.
It is.
Thank you, Scottish.
It's a pork pie. Yes.
And he so which maybe his real name isn't Mr. Tato.
Maybe he adopted that his real names just like Mcduff or something.
And he adopted this whole persona.
Very possible.
Yeah, he seems to like a bold red and white colors.
Yeah, simple kind of a simple basic.
You call him basic, I think, in his color choices.
Yeah, I like it. It feels like fast food.
I'm enjoying it.
I will say the current Tato seems a little too much CGI for me.
I would prefer a more 2D kind of older animation looking guy.
And we've talked about this before on the show, especially in regards to the Keebler elves.
You know, Ernie Keebler now is CGI and he looks like he's had a lot of work done.
And it's not the Ernie Keebler we grew up with.
You know, I mean, yeah, they say nothing is constant but change.
So I guess we have to live with it.
I mean, we're already going through hell with this whole Mr.
Peanut Baby Nut Nut Jr.
debacle.
Like it's a bad, bad vibe.
I can't keep track of it.
Yeah.
What is the difference between Baby Nut and Nut Jr.?
Oh, Baby Nut is aging up now.
Baby Nut stuck around for a few months, was not well received.
And now I believe he's as of a few days ago, he's Nut Jr.
He's 21.
What?
It seems like they're trying to quickly speed him up to get him back to Mr.
Peanut.
Okay.
Can we delay the episode so I can do more research on Nut Jr.?
Because I do really want to know about him.
We're not ready at all.
We're going to have to put this back in the can.
This is going to come out in three years.
Yeah, this is going to be a whole project.
So, yeah, so I think we all.
You know what's related to this maybe or what might help us here?
First of all, I should say to the audience, it's probably in our show art, I'm sure that it is.
But if you haven't already seen Mr. Tato, I think it's important that you Google him, you know, just so you know what we're talking about for the next, you know, for the 90% of the episode.
So you should be looking at him.
Maybe just like listen to the don't like drive or work out or something while you're listening to this particular episode.
Just like find a photo and stare straight into his eyes.
Just like really give him your attention as I'm doing as we record it.
But maybe a sub link within that is I'll share my screen with you guys.
I found him on a great wiki, which I should we should all pursue more that the ad mascot wiki and they kind of break down the different eras.
And maybe we could all like an out loud Twitter thing.
We could all tag ourselves in what is our preferred Mr. Tato.
And I'm most curious about Marissa's opinions here.
So we have a couple.
We have the current, which is very CGI.
We go back to the 2000s, the 90s and all the way back to the 1960s.
Do we do we what do we think is peak Tato?
I mean, all the 60s Tato is very much like he was a member of the Avengers, the British secret agent group.
He's got like kind of that like he's like kind of posing on a little umbrella.
Same color palette as now, but it's more of a bowler hat.
It's more of like a classic.
Yeah, the hat got smaller.
I think that 60s Tato looks like the ink hat, like the pen had a little bit too much ink in it when they drew it.
The black lines are too bold, a little thick.
Too bold. Sorry.
Sorry.
We're all entitled to our opinion.
I think that, yeah, the 90s and the 2000s Tato very similar.
They're very close together.
Like they except for the color of the hat, essentially, they appear to be the same.
One is yellow.
In one, the hat is yellow, the same yellow of his skin.
Right.
And then, yeah, that other Tato, they're all kind of similar.
I think it's really kind of there's really only three versions as far as what we're looking at here that are very different.
There's not a lot of I was mainly just curious if 60s did it for anybody and it does not.
No, he does it for me.
Mr. Tato from the 60s for sure does it for me.
He can get it.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I do not like that Tato.
Do you like the new Tato better?
My favorite Tato just looking at these is Mr. Tato as he appeared in the 2000s because his hands are jaunty.
That gives me a lot.
That suggests.
I was going to ask if you felt like he something was suspicious was going on with him in the 60s, but because the hidden hand is a tad unnerving.
I mean, what's back there?
It's symbolic.
It's a gun.
Yeah.
No, Mr. Tato is holding a gun behind him in this picture.
Oh, no, he's MI6.
Yes, that's right.
Mr. Tato is MI6 in the 60s.
And I look I like that.
You know, it's a fun romanticized version of spying and you know, the classic James Bond.
I don't know.
I don't know what he was doing in the 60s.
Maybe it doesn't hold up.
Maybe it's problematic now, but I can enjoy the romanticized version of a gentleman spy.
That's also a potato from the 1960s.
He was in the I was going to say he's in it's a 60s.
He's a gentleman spy in Ireland.
What he was doing was not good.
Yet.
Yes, Jason, I said I made a qualification that I'm romanticizing the idea that if the reality of it is, yes, of course he's killed.
He's overthrown governments, but we want to we want the fun.
We want the short.
Sure.
Kiss, kiss, bang, bang.
That's what we want.
The 90s, 90s and 2000s adds the striped pants.
And I think the striped pants, that's that's a pretty good upgrade.
Right.
Yeah, I like them.
Yeah.
So, yeah, I'm saying 60s.
What do you so you, Marissa, you and Jason both 2000s?
I don't know.
The thing is, is like this feels very not me to like something not from the 60s.
I find that very hard to believe that this is my choice right now.
But I think 2000s Tato is for me.
Wow.
That is shocking because if I know anything about you is that your brain, I do think forces you to like something that's 50 years old.
Yeah.
There's something about it that just like that feels more authentic.
Yeah, it feels it feels like where I come from.
Sure.
I wonder if there's a 70s that splits the difference.
I wonder, is there I don't want to say that ad mascots dot fandom dot com isn't doing its job.
I just wonder if there's this whole era is I think where we might be missing here.
Yeah, there was more of it like a disco, a disco Tato.
90s Tato.
I like you know what I like about 90s Tato.
He's holding the bag.
He's holding a bag of crisps as if to say, look, here's my work.
I'm proud of it.
Yeah, I have a question.
I have a question.
There's a big leap from umbrella to crisp bag.
Was Mr. Tato an umbrella mascot in the 60s?
Was he selling Mr. Tato umbrellas?
The potato based umbrella.
He was just a poorly drawn person.
He was never intended to be a potato originally.
Somebody drew far too big of a head.
That's what people look like, right?
They hadn't invented skin tones for crayons yet in the 60s.
So it was just that was the color they would they would paint skin.
Yeah, there is no spectrum.
Yes, it was the closest to what human skin is like.
Yeah.
So, yes, I can see I can see how you would see this character and like base a theme park around it.
I'm not 100 percent on this because I came across in a couple of places.
But supposedly the Tato was they were the ones who figured out how to season crisps like seasoned chips.
But then I saw somewhere else saying there is a second Tato company in Ireland.
Yes.
But I think it is this one.
I think it's Joe Murphy, the founder.
You know, when he was in charge of it, they figured out how to get seasoning on it.
And it was an immediate hit.
And all the American chip people came over and licensed the technology so they could start selling seasoned chips.
Is this Jason, is this one of your heroes, this man for developing this seasoning?
Hero and also like the scourge of my child, the scourge of just putting on weight in my childhood,
because I would just immediately come home from school, put my backpack down and just fill a bowl of potato chips and get to watching Power Rangers, Batman, whatever.
That was going to be my next question. Were you a potato chip kid? And the answer was yes.
Yes, I may have loved them more than some extended family members.
What? What? I was I was a lunch chip kid, but I wasn't I would eat them at home, but I wasn't eating them.
I wasn't into them as much as sweets, but I definitely would have a laser, a Cheetos in my lunch.
We've talked about this before. It was you had you couldn't not have lunch without eating some empty calories with salt.
Yeah, it was part of it. Sure. And that was the problem, Michael, because I had lunch chips and then I had afternoon chips.
Were they different chips with the lunch chips different from the afternoon chips?
You know, we always had at least three or four flavors in the pantry. So lay, lay, very possibly.
Lays hurts. Pennsylvania is sort of the potato basket of the country where you can get lays, hers, but wise like it.
And a lot of them have factories in Pennsylvania. So we had a bounty of chip options.
They were delivered to your door like a milkman.
You got to have a fresh, got to have a fresh in the glass chip bottle by like a man that kind of looked like a potato.
He resembled a potato. Marissa chips in your house growing up.
Honestly, I had the worst house for snacks. I think my parents were influenced by some type of healthy foods, 1970s movement, but then like didn't go all the way to like actually do it.
So like I would have just like rice in the cupboards. You know what I mean?
I think it was I was not a snack house. I feel like I ate a lot of quesadillas though.
I would like just microwave quesadillas, not like a nicely grilled one.
So you would come home and watch TV and just eat a bowl of rice?
No, no, that was just to illustrate that like the pantry in my house was like to me deeply depressing because it was all things that in three steps could become something good, but weren't anywhere close to being something good right now.
So it was not easily accessible snack. Like the snacks weren't readily available. You would have had to put a pot of boiling water on to mix something.
Yeah. And what 10 year old is going to do that?
You had like you had all the ingredients to make chips, but you didn't have chips.
Honestly, they're in my kitchen growing up. There was like a mortal and mortar and pestle or whatever those, you know, I could grind something down.
Can we have chips, mom? And it's like, well, if you make them, if you create them yourself.
Well, get the mortar and pestle out.
Mortar and pestle, you know, the thing you use to make chips.
Mortar and pestle snacks and then like books about what was her name? Morvola?
Morvola.
Mofalda.
Mofalda brand chips. And then it's just like a bag of flour and salt and with like a 20 item list of instructions.
Marissa, from what I know, your family was like really pushing back.
Like I think Jason Scott and I all had a very American of its era upbringing with the exact snacks that were popular with a lot of the same like TV shows.
And I feel like I envy you.
Complete opposite from what I understand.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
Well, I think the hard part about being an only child is you don't know how weird your life is until you encounter other people and they tell you how cool their life is.
So like you would have met like a Jason type and he's like, yeah, I go home every day.
I eat a bag of Lay's and I watch the Power Rangers and you were like, oh my God.
Yeah, I would like heaven. Yeah, I would have been amazed.
Do I have to have another kid? I think you just made me think that was the best argument I've heard so far.
Well, I could I could expand out that argument and say any family is unusual until you you know what I mean? You realize that when you encounter other families.
So Scott, Scott, you want you want both of your kids then to be able to be like, Dad is so into this theme park stuff.
And he's like, he's obsessed with like Steve Lukather demos.
All he talks about is this one guitar player.
I know what he played. I know he played the solo on physical ever this every day.
And didn't you think like every dad knew that and cares about that? Yeah, I thought that.
But apparently that's rare. Oh, God.
These little bastards are going to conspire against me. Yeah.
You know what? Only one. I think only one is the correct way to do it.
Yeah, I'm keeping him solo. I'm going to Brigsby Bear this kid and he's just going to have his own little universe and I hope he never breaks out of it.
I think that's a good idea. So, yeah, I said as far as us chips, we'd have the lays and whatever.
And we had bugles. There's a lot of that in the house.
But, you know, it was and I wasn't crazy for chips.
Scott, were you crazy for chips real quick before we continue?
Yeah, I remember I specifically remember going to the pediatrician's office and getting a pretty bad cholesterol test.
But from the era where I was eating so many Ruffles and what's what is it?
Ruffles cheddar and sour cream. Oh, yeah.
Because then I looked up and they have MSG and I devoured Ruffles cheddar and sour cream.
How old were you?
I remember it. So old enough to 10 or 11.
Yeah, yeah. And it's the same office where I go with with my my new son now.
And I every time I walk in, I'm like that that Ruffles diagnosis.
I think about it every time. Did they diagnose you with Ruffles?
They can tell immediately like what what's rising the cholesterol.
It's the Ruffles. Yeah. Look at his stomach. I noticed like what's this bendy shape?
I see ridges in there. Yeah.
Wow. Well, we all have made it ridged the lining of my stomach.
That's how much I was eating that those might have been the most addictive chip because I eat those for a lot in a short amount of time.
And then they make me I cannot eat them now.
The sight of them makes me I don't know.
I don't also like sour cream and how often do you encounter I guess on nachos or baked potatoes?
But it's just like, hmm, what a delicious combo.
Dairy and dairy. I know I'm not a sour cream eater at all now.
I and you know, I think now I can't be like a little kid in my my chip taste.
I'm an adult. I have to step it up.
We all do, which is why I think we need to address the more adult elevated version of Tato crisps, which is, of course, occasions.
Stumble upon occasions. Yes, I saw occasions.
The classier chip. It's much it's so much classier.
It is for occasions. It was a bad time for occasions.
None of us are having occasions of any kind right now.
Can you describe them? Yeah, because I didn't I didn't look at them.
I should bring I don't have photos in front of me.
If you Google it, it's it's like very you know, it's it's classy font.
It's classy presentation.
Mainly, I just copy and pasted the varieties, which are very mature, you know, like bistro Caribbean chutney.
Oh, I didn't even notice the word mature occasions, mature cheddar cheese and red onion.
That's not not no little kid ruffles here.
Party occasions, party mix for cheese and Mediterranean herbs.
These are some of the longest product names I've ever encountered.
But then and then it's all like presented a little hoity toity.
But then you get to tortilla original cool.
The end is cool. It's the last word.
Yes. Look at this serifed fonts.
This is class. You could hardly tell it's a Tato.
You know that Tato is so small in the corner.
Yeah, they have Mr. Tato in there with a cartoon.
But yes, if you looked at the chip, you'd be like, well, this is a very sophisticated chip.
This is not for children after school.
This is for cocktail parties.
This is for this is for yacht yacht.
This is this is what they would eat on David Geffen's yacht.
You know, this is not something that this must be a five fifty dollars a chip.
That must be how expensive this is.
That's right. And, you know, if you've ever been if you've been to as many Irish wakes as I have,
it's important to have some salty snacks around to soak up the Jameson, you know,
because the bars are open.
No, wait, so you are Irish, Jason, is Irish descent?
Yeah, not not like a few generations back.
Oh, this isn't going to turn into an Elizabeth Warren thing, is it?
No, no.
No, I the I the child of a Sheridan and a Murphy, I can assure you there's some Irish there.
OK, sounds like it.
I am getting to the age of like where I you know, I I would like to travel more internationally.
Of course, can't do that right now.
That's why we're doing this series.
But I always think about that American Express commercial where the guy uses his American Express card
to take his father back, take his family back to Ireland to buy uncomfortable sweaters
and stand on hills and look at old books and go like, yeah, that's where they were.
All right. I like that you would, Elizabeth Warren, that you'd you'd kind of like fudge some details
in order to seem like you're you have closer lineage to Mr. Tate.
Who knows? Maybe we're related.
He's like a third cousin.
I did a DNA test and turns out, yeah, I'm related to him.
It's kind of a little farther away.
It's not a direct first cousin or anything, but for sure.
Yeah, I'm definitely part potato.
There's this I found a couple of things about Tate before we actually get into the theme park.
And I'm going to share a little bit of the story that I found.
I'm going to get into the theme park and I'm going to share the screen here.
Conan O'Brien.
Did you see this clip, Scott?
I did see this clip. Yes.
He went to visit the Tate.
Oh, he went. I don't know.
He's in a store somewhere and he he found the actual pronunciation, I believe.
That's sort of what he's leaning into.
And I found this fun for a second.
We are entering the Irish gift shop now here at the Irish American Heritage Center.
These are potatoes. Look at that.
Yeah. Potatoes.
Just in case you mistakenly pronounce it potato, they correct you.
Not a tato.
Say a tato.
Oh, a tato.
As we go down here, we have the dancing shoes here.
These are the shoes.
That's fun. That's a fun pronunciation.
I do remember seeing this, but I didn't know he doesn't mention Mr. Tato, which is a big mistake.
Obviously, the segment would have been much better.
It perfectly lends itself to that super exaggerated pronunciation, to tato.
And now, Mike, I'm now I'm looking at you clicking through other tabs and you have tabs of things that I have also.
Okay.
Please, I think, go ahead.
I'm so excited for you to share.
I love seeing these tabs here.
Okay, good.
I assumed you would probably have them.
But yeah, let's just get a couple of these more Mr. Tato stuff out of the way before we get to the rides.
You know, this is a theme park podcast.
That's what we say, at least.
Sometimes.
So there was an ad campaign about Mr. Tato looking for love.
And Marissa's face just lit up.
I'm in.
I'll fast forward some of this because basically, it's a couple very romantic.
They're looking into each other's eyes.
And then they hug.
Obviously, they're going to get married.
That's a plan.
And then the camera pans over to Mr. Tato sitting alone at a table and he just exhales sadly.
No!
And he's like a practical Mr. Tato.
And it says Mr. Tato is looking for a Mrs. Tato.
Is he still looking?
Well, there was a whole...
I do think he is still looking.
Okay, because I mean, I like Tato of 20 years ago, so maybe there's still a little bit of that Tato left.
Are you saying you could be Mrs. Tato?
I'm not saying I could be. I'm saying I should be Mrs. Tato.
If only you knew 20 years ago, you could have gotten peak Tato.
I know.
They had a whole promotion where the women would go on the radio and explain why they were a good match for Mr. Tato.
Did you want to do that now? Did you want to make a case to him?
Yeah, I'll make a case. Hopefully Tato hasn't found love.
Hopefully he's been sad.
Hopefully he's been sitting at that table for 20 years with a really weird nose.
That nose, I didn't think it translated.
It's a live action.
I did not like the nose.
Okay, so if I were to appeal to Mr. Tato to become Mrs. Tato, I would say...
I think beauty is more than skin deep, and I can tell that you're beautiful.
I want to explore flavors with you.
And I want to be shielded by your umbrella.
I want to be eaten your crisps.
I want to throw crisps at each other in a satin filled bed, but tastefully dressed.
You know, I could be Mrs. Tato.
Wow.
I'm wearing yellow currently, so I feel like that feels like Kismet.
Could you resist taking a bite out of him?
Only if he allowed me to.
Great answer. Perfect answer.
Well, look, he's obviously going to hear this, so hopefully we get a response.
That was glorious. That was so beautiful.
And if you got with him, you could ask to borrow his hat too.
That'd be a little residual benefit.
Now, I'm just wondering what's under that hat.
You know what I mean? Because you want to know who you're marrying,
and I'm wondering if it's like a pointy little head or like he's got a couple little sprouts up there,
like little eyeballs coming out. You know, what's going on on a potato's head?
It's a ring.
I'm engaged.
It's all happening.
It's wedged into uncooked potatoes, so you really got to rock it back and forth to get it out.
So I have to like dig in like a bad potato?
No, it's still good. So it's hard. It hasn't been boiled yet.
The one method of cooking in Ireland.
I hope we can go to this wedding and then we enter the church and half of it is people and we go sit over there and the other half is all potatoes.
Oh, my God.
Hey, Scott, I think it's rude that you don't think I have potato friends.
I'm really sorry. That's a big judgment.
And vice versa. Of course, Mr. Tato is friends with many humans.
I'd like to count myself among them. So I'll sit on whatever side you guys want.
I won't make you put me in a box.
All retired spies on Mr. Tato's side.
Oh, sure.
I'll get him talking at the reception. I'll get him liquor up.
All those secrets.
So, OK, let's go to this 2015 Mr. Tato commercial.
And look, I, as we've said, I'm going through character development on podcasts to ride.
I'm getting a little body or I'm getting a little more used to a rubalds humor.
It's just like you said, a very offensive.
You said a very offensive song title over on the second gate.
If you got on the second gate, I said the name of Cardi B and Megan, the Stallion's new song.
I will not say it on the front main gate. I'm not. I haven't developed that much as a character.
You got to pay for that.
We got only fans that you want to hear Mike say those words.
If you want to hear me say those words, you have to pay us five dollars.
That's how it works.
But so so when I watch this commercial, you know, I know Europe has, you know, commercials that have a little bit more suggestive stuff.
I was very surprised, though, by this.
Can we see this commercial here? Yeah. OK, here we go.
So there's like a young a young lad, you would say, is that his computer and he sees like a lady in a bathing suit.
And he's about to type, I wish I was the blanket that she's laying on.
And Mr. Tato unplugged the computer and just shakes his head at the kid.
Like, don't post that.
He's like he's suddenly in the room of basically like a bout to masturbate teen or something.
Yeah, Tato shows up out of nowhere to stop him.
Sorry, you want to backtrack to this?
Yeah, so I'll backtrack.
There's like three vignettes in this. It's very fast.
It comes very fast.
And by the way, Mr. Tato in this looks jacked like he has like a very like upper like a bigger upper body is a little more built than normal.
OK, so this shot. This is a really lewd commercial.
I can just tell you one thing, and I'm falling for him even harder.
He's helping people.
I'll explain this scenario because he's a gentleman here.
Yeah. OK, yeah.
How would you describe this?
Well, I would say a lot of women we know we know some leggings are not made for bending over because you see your underwear through it.
And Mr. Tato is spotting the bum of a woman with some floral underwear peeking through her leggings.
And he is alerting her.
But he's being a gentleman about it.
Whispering, doing it discreetly so that the other people at this bus stop don't notice.
So yeah, he really did her a favor here.
And that's a great lesson for all the men out there.
If a woman's underwear is showing, just whisper in their ear at a bus stop.
Let them know.
And of course, they'll thank you and they won't call the police on you.
Yeah. Follow them to a bus stop first.
Notice, then follow.
Right.
Whisper what Mr. Tato said in her ear, which was a cover up.
Jesus can see your sin.
Oh my God.
I don't know about this, Tato.
I assumed it was the same thing that Bill Murray whispered in Scarlett Johansson's ear at the end of Lost in Translation.
All right. So, so OK, that's the end of that.
One more little scene.
Vignette. Yeah, the woman covers it up with a jacket.
And now there's a man who's leaving. He's going to go play sporting.
He's going to go play like football.
And Mr. Tato looks down at him as he's leaving his flat.
Those eyebrows.
And he sees that the man is wearing shorts that are very tight that expose his bulge.
It's a very prominent bulge.
And the man looks down at his own bulge and Mr. Tato has shorts for him or no pants.
Excuse me.
Has pants for him already.
And the man puts the pants on and thanks Mr. Tato for it.
So is he like the indecency police?
What is he doing?
I think he's trying to keep the world as proper as he is.
You know, he's a man of virtue.
Because he believes and he dresses nicely.
He's in a suit and tie.
It's not about he's, you know, he's down with casual clothes, but not at the expense of decency.
You wouldn't see his bulge.
Maybe it's implicit that like you wouldn't want to be seen with a bulge.
Maybe that's what he's trying to prove.
Maybe that's embarrassing.
I don't know.
He's anti-bulge.
He just he wants the bulge in other places because he's a potato.
I imagine potatoes being bulgy and lumpy.
Of course, of course.
It's all over everywhere.
It's not genitals.
It's just lots of different.
Right.
The edible bulges.
At the very least, the underwear was a very sharp Kelly Green.
Very, very like a classic four leaf clover.
So yeah, and then the commercial lens and Mr. Tato is in this like young lad's room with an arm around him as the young lad is like sad and like eating.
The crisps like aggressively.
It's very odd.
And then the tagline comes up and it says more than just the crisp.
And I guess that means like he's also judging you for like indecency.
I guess like you should think of the potatoes when you're eating them like to make sure that you're not putting sex out into the world or the disgusting human body.
No, I'm going to defend my future husband here.
Just by saying we're all complex.
We're all complex.
You know what I mean?
Like you can want to live in a black and white world where like there's good and evil.
There's right and wrong.
But the fact is the world's gray.
Tato's living in a gray world and I love him for it.
OK, well, that's a pretty that's a pretty big defense for him, which I can get behind the philosophy.
Obviously, I, too, at one point would have been like Mr. Tato, where I was offended by a man's bulge coming out of a flat in England.
But I've gone through, again, aggressive character development these last couple podcast episodes, so I'm a little bit more comfortable with it.
Are you willing to just put that that guy's bulge up and leave the screen shared for the rest of the episode?
Scott, I would love to.
I would love to leave the bulge up.
Just look at that close up.
Great.
Where is it?
Yeah, that's very.
Randy, European Mike is really firing off.
I just love that Tato's eyebrows change when he sees the bulge.
They get so sad like they flip and like you can see he's he's really distressed.
Disappointed.
He's sad.
He's upset.
I would like to bring up one more thing about this.
A practical concern from from a person who's done a few commercials in his life as a few of us have.
Can you imagine getting the casting notice and having them like also explain like your bulge will be on display in this commercial?
And then like you'll have to do this.
That's prosthetic.
That's that's a fake.
I don't think that's a fake.
I think that could be real.
We don't know.
Look at those thighs.
They look like Rusev's.
They do look like WWE wrestler or former WWE wrestler Rusev's thighs.
I agree.
Marissa has been a big fan of of his thighs for years.
That is not a joke.
I love when you would have his thighs.
This is coming before.
Oh yeah.
Like seven or eight years ago when she would come and watch wrestling pay-per-views.
She loved Rusev and she specifically would say she likes his thighs because they were very thick.
They're very big.
Yeah.
They look like Thanksgiving turkeys.
Very glazed.
Yes.
He's been he's been on Twitch lately.
He's been playing video games on Twitch and his name is his real name is Miro.
It's a cool name.
So give him a give him a follow on Twitch and check out those thighs.
I'm not trying to objectify people but I guess that is what I'm doing.
You're a fan.
I'm a fan.
Rusev Tato Rusev's thighs and Tato's non genital bulges just as potato we bulges.
There should have been a WrestleMania entrance where Rusev came out and Mr.
Tato appeared and like shook his finger at him and then like gave him like a sweater to cover up his legs.
Like a like a V-neck college style like 1950s sweater.
Yes.
For sure.
So yeah.
So Tato look Tato is a layered character.
He's got a lot of yeah a lot of different things going on.
Right.
He might he might be encouraging body shame.
We just don't know.
I think we actually we do probably know.
That's sort of what's happening.
Yes.
This is completely.
And it's but at least he's he's all over the it's men and women.
He's shaming any anyone for showing their body.
I would like a full 90 minute feature made by the same guy who made Paddington with Mr.
Tato going around shaming people further dress.
I'm yes I'm I'll buy a ticket.
So if you go to Tato Park very strict dress code be aware no shorts no showing of dirty thighs.
Certainly no bulges.
Thick thick thick leggings please.
Like five of them just load them up.
Don't stop at the one pair.
I think that's good.
Yeah that's really I mean those are the two big ones.
I mean Mr. Tato went to the Euros and like what's the Euros.
Yeah I wasn't.
It's a soccer tournament.
Is that right.
I believe so.
Yeah he's got a soccer ball there.
And then it was like will he make it to France.
But that's not as fun as him being alone at a table looking for love.
But you know what.
So there's clearly levels of Tato.
There's there's ones with articulated eyebrows and who can who can you know smile and frown and sadly sigh.
And then you've got you know more of the mascot style.
And that's really the I think Tato is is like an Irish version of the wonderful Japanese mascots.
This is great account Mondo mascots.
I feel like he he fits right in with those guys.
And and then you've got the version of the park which is probably the most limited version.
But but still wonderful.
He's just it's just a great design.
Marissa you're right that not every part of his face works in Ria.
His nose can be odd sometimes.
But I now I'm like low to see this guy in person.
If this could be one of the first things I do when the lockdown is over.
Fly to Ireland.
Go give him a hug and then leave immediately.
That's my plan.
That would be a great thing.
It would.
I want to go to every restaurant in Ireland and just wait and hopefully one day I'll find the one he's sitting at.
That empty that table for one and you can make it a table for two.
I thought I was out of stuff but I have found a quick thing and it's a very small graphic but I will share it.
I found something called the love bus that Mr. Tato is on and it's like a double decker bus that you would see in Europe.
And he's like seductively like posed on and he's wearing his normal outfit.
But it's it's that's a much more suggestive Tato Marissa has been like she's been hit in the head with something.
She's so taken aback.
I mean this is a very suggestive Tato.
This Tato is like a come hither Tato.
It is a come hither Tato for sure.
It's it's and it's kind of again it's like in contrast with the commercial we just watched too where it's like this is this is suggestive.
Yeah.
What is he doing here?
Maybe he only believes he himself could be suggestive.
Yeah.
Oh if he thinks if people are showing off their underpants and bulges that it'll distract from him and then he'll never find his Mrs. Tato.
That's got to be what it is.
Cover up.
I'm putting on a show every day of my life.
The love bus.
We don't know what he sounds like as far in all of this.
Aside from that one sigh does he does he not talk.
Is that the thing is he one of those characters or what's the vibe of the voice.
Jason do you got a voice for him.
I think Jason's voice you did at the start of the show was the voice.
I think I don't I think he doesn't I think he's like a teller.
He doesn't talk.
Yeah I mean like power of him is the not talk.
So some people flap their mouths forever but not Tato.
He does it all his face in his presence.
He saw too much during World War Two or the Troubles and he's just you know very pensive very pensive every now and then he'll open up and it'll be crazy.
He'll come out with something like like your underwear is showing your underwear is showing.
I blew up a fiat once.
Jason could you give us the line your underwear showing in the voice real quick.
Whisper to like a real whisper.
Yeah he Tato only whispers.
I know you have to warm up I get that.
Take your time.
The underwear is showing the armor light is hidden in the flower bed.
I think Jason for Tato should get trending here and we could actually get you this job.
Sure.
Yeah let's go we'll go backwards and read all of the ads so that they have full vocal presence there.
I mean we're definitely going to take that thing that Jason just said and add it into that commercial.
Certainly that shall be done.
That's easy.
We can do that no problem.
So yeah.
Cover that bulge up.
The ladies are mine.
All of them.
Yeah so Tato I mean that's that's all I have for Tato right now before I guess we have to talk about rides.
Well I did.
Before we get to the one thing we haven't talked about and Marissa you brought we both immediately jumped to this when we first talked about this park.
Yeah.
And that is Ireland very much a place associated with potatoes from the famine of the 1800s.
So then to have a potato based theme park is is kind of wild.
It feels that way but maybe it's like you know you got to get over the stigma right.
So you go real hard.
Yeah.
But it is important not to forget about it and that's why I have some famine fun fact during the famine one million people died and one million people emigrated causing a population decrease in Ireland between 20 and 25 percent.
Oh.
That's how about that.
Did you call that a fun fact.
Yeah.
Why was that fun.
That's a famine fun fact.
Just going back to a thing I did I used to do more on the show where I would just drop some knowledge in the middle of stuff.
You know.
Did you.
I don't remember that.
Oh yeah.
The tortilla.
But I know that crap about tortillas.
Okay.
Was that when the before times.
Yeah.
It was in the before times.
Because I have a very fuzzy memory of ever actually seeing all of you in person so I might just have forgotten.
That's true.
Did we ever was the show ever in person.
But I don't bring fun Jason bring the fun facts back.
Yeah.
What we need during the pandemic is famine death statistics.
Oh you mean like how the famine was caused by what is known as late blight a disease of the potato plant caused by water mold.
Oh my God.
Anyway.
Can you.
All right.
I have one more request.
We just keep giving you assignments here.
But can you read one of these facts in what we've determined is the Mr. Tato voice.
And when you get to the word potato in any of them make it me or if you have to pluralize it me's you know.
Like instead of where there were no potatoes there were no me's and you can pick your whatever facts lends itself best to that.
Oh OK.
The the Irish me family the Irish me famine was caused by late blight which is a disease of the me plant caused by water mold.
All right.
We got to do we got to mock that up too I guess.
The me plant.
I think this is I don't want to talk about another type of crisp or chip but this is like Pringles I can't pop just one.
Do we have any more facts you can.
This is delightful.
Yeah.
Do you have any other me facts.
It can be one you already said.
Well I'm out of famine fact but I do have some Irish freedom fun facts if you have any interest in that.
But there's no potato in there.
No we don't care about that.
Find a way to make it come from his you know like if it was a very sad fact and then like you know that's not as fun as eating one of me.
OK.
The drink called in America known as the black and tan is one part stout or porter and one part ale or lager.
Unfortunately it is named after a part of the Royal Irish Constabulary that was used by the British to repress the Irish Republican Army.
They were known for acts of police brutality and were eventually run out of Ireland or killed.
But take your mind off that with limited edition Tex-Mex brand of me's.
That was great great scenes ever performed.
Yeah that was like a monologue.
Yeah.
Boy boy.
Wow.
You got to do one too.
You gave your your marital plea.
I this is this is like like there's a lot of great Irish playwrights.
We're all like doing little little one acts here.
Yes.
Jason did you really only have two famine fun facts.
I had two famine fun facts so I could switch over to the Irish freedom facts.
For example the Good Friday Agreement was signed in spring of 1998 bringing an end to decades of violence colloquially known as the Troubles.
Of course Northern Ireland is still part of the United Kingdom but I believe we will see a united Ireland in my lifetime.
Until then tide yourself over with a delicious bag of prawn cocktail me's.
Wow. This is so this would be such a good ad campaign for them.
Oh sure.
This is such a good idea and I'm sure they'll listen to this.
Michael you me Marissa Scott we've all spent a little time in the ad game we know what that the Madison Avenue or whatever the street is in Derry.
We all know what they want.
Yeah I mean look let's let's let's list the credits OK.
All state insurance for me.
Dunkin Donuts for Jason Dunkin Donuts.
Marissa.
Scott.
I directed some Nissan Juke commercials that were did a lot of body shaming of Mike Mitchell.
Yeah we've all got great credits.
All of great credits.
It's the meanest.
He's talked about it on Dope Boys.
There's I didn't write them but he ended I might have been said yeah sure he could be in them but boy it's so like I it's all like all right.
Then he gets on the scale then he gets on the scale again and then it turns out he never lost any weight it didn't work.
Oh well I assume these exist somewhere.
Can I ask you can I ask you a question if Mr. Potato were to come I mean excuse me Mr. Tato.
Oh my God.
Oh my God I'm sorry.
If Mr. Tato.
He said his first name his first name is Poe.
If if if our friend Tato was to show up in one of those commercials what do you think he would have said to Mike Mitchell or how do you think he would have influenced the character that Mike Mitchell was playing.
Who was a guy really struggling with his weight.
It's like to like to no avail and being made fun of by everyone around him in a cruel script that I did not write.
So let me make that very clear.
Is this a is this for Jason because he's been doing the voice.
I mean you can set the scene and maybe Jason will add the dialogue.
I have I have it I have it here.
He would come into the scene he would come into he would break into Mitch's house.
He would see that Mitch was wearing shorts that were very tight and he would like shake his head at Mitch's bulge.
And then he would say he would say that your bulge is showing so your bulge is showing Mitch.
So Jason go ahead.
Breathy please make it please make it breath.
OK. Yeah.
We've got to wait.
Wait one more thing. Let's reset.
OK.
Mitchie my boy your bulge is showing.
You can't kiss the Blarney Stone with that.
So much better than the ad nightmares that I was that I was a part of.
Wow. We all rewrote them on the.
Yeah.
We just we just all moved our Madison Avenue prowess right now.
Yeah. Yeah.
And we learned that some people kiss the Blarney Stone with their bulges.
That's good.
Well you can't you can't.
Then you get the bad luck.
But it seems like something people want to do and have at least tried previously to be to be forewarning someone.
Yeah.
You want to lose weights cut back on me's very good.
I like that.
I feel like that's the end of the commercial.
We feel satisfied.
Yeah that's good.
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
Even though it's an ad it was an ad for a car we've now commandeered it to be an ad for a potato crisp company.
It's like how McGruff is in like insurance ads now.
It's like he has his own National Crime Prevention Council but now he's appearing in insurance but he's also promoting himself.
He's appearing so you know you can have crossovers is what I'm saying.
Yeah that's very confusing.
Yeah very confusing.
Do we have to talk about this theme park right.
This is some of the latest we've ever gotten to theme park.
This is an hour in content.
It's an hour in.
Well because look the park seems very nice and lovely.
There are some nice cute rides and I have no shit to talk about it.
You know this isn't like the fake Universal Studios that we covered where I have many pages of complaints.
I just this this place seems really nice.
That's that's what I will say.
Yeah.
You guys agree.
I mean there's yeah there's not there's no like unlicensed 80s NBC hour long drama based rides.
There's fun basic rides like they they have a picture of their vortex tunnel which just is like a cool colorful circle which I love.
I mean I can't what could I say other than I'd love to walk down this vortex tunnel.
Yeah me too.
It reminded me of that that part of Universal Studios tram ride right.
Isn't there.
It's been like an avalanche sometimes it's been something else right.
It's in a mummy's tomb and now it is nothing now it's the Fast and the Furious finale.
OK.
It's very it's it's very similar to that old Epcot hallway with the car like it's very circular and there's colors and the greatest.
That's an episode right there.
We should do an episode about the tunnel.
That's probably right.
The Epcot tunnel that's now closed.
What's just sitting there with nothing happening.
That's the idea to replace it is just not opening it ever.
It's insane.
When we were there we saw it and we're like we just can't walk down the tunnel with the colors like it's cruel.
That just seems cruel.
We're talking about the journey into your imagination tunnel now that so much better than the ride.
So this tunnel is far better than the right.
Yes.
So yeah I mean it's got you know it's got a train.
The Tato Park has a train.
Jason were you excited about this.
I was because I watched a couple like vloggers go through this park.
The one this guy theme park worldwide has gone to most of the European parks we've covered and pretty thorough.
The train goes fast like I would say it goes like twice as fast as like the Disney train.
Sweet.
Interesting.
Do you think that's good.
I think you would think that might be bad.
I think you like the slow plot of the Disney.
Slow plotting nature of a train.
Well things are a little they do things differently in Europe.
So you know I could you know change it up switch it up just like you're switching it up with the body.
Yes.
Scott I thought you were setting us up earlier talking about rides for the very adorable looking Nissan driving school at Tito Park.
Oh my old pals at Nissan who paid for Nissan who paid for it.
Paid Mike Mitchell very little to be body shamed on camera.
My old my good friends.
Now I do like this Nissan driving school.
This is adorable.
It's like I just wrote down it's a little town you drive in exclamation point.
It's not like an utopia where you have a set track.
It's like a couple little city blocks like miniature city blocks and kids drive tiny cars around and then go wherever they want.
It's so cute.
Yeah I mean it gives the kids a lot more freedom which is what I desired from those type that type of utopia ride as a child.
Marissa is agreeing with me.
Yeah.
Because because when you're very little you might not even realize the I like the physics of it.
You're still on a little track and you can't go far.
But then once you get to like six years old or seven years old you're like this is kind of bullshit.
You're onto it.
And that's why I always wanted like a power wheels car.
But I would I never received one and it still haunts me to this day.
Do you feel like power wheels were the kind of thing where like you went over to your friend's house and they had one and you'd want to use it because you didn't have one but they were like it's old hat.
We don't.
It's like not even fun.
Oh yeah.
Yeah for sure.
Yeah like we don't even take that out of the garage anymore.
Yeah. And you're just like how can you be sitting on this gold.
Yeah.
Yeah it's like a kid's like I'm driving my parents car at this point.
Yeah no I I'm trying to think I didn't have a close friend that had one.
But yeah anyone any kid that had it I was either like they would just monopolize it and wouldn't let me drive.
And it was never something negotiating wise that my parents took care of because I think that's the way sometimes you have to do that because when we're little like.
Kids get very territorial over their stuff which I get but sometimes the parents have to be like well let's little Michael do this like a guy I was friends with in elementary school who wouldn't let me play Sega Genesis.
I sat and watched him play.
I have a question.
Did your parents come on all your play dates and mediate for you.
No.
My mom came on all my field trips though.
Oh wow.
Well you know you would go to like you know the nature museum or you would go you know to what yeah like the science museum whatever that was.
My mother volunteered and was just looming.
She was a presence anytime we were out of the school and that was unfun you didn't like it.
It just I felt there was a press there's always a pressure when you like your mom is there.
Yeah it's kind of a freedom to go to school.
Yeah.
And if kids are all like daring each other to say dirty words or something and then you feel the shadow.
Yeah I was glancing I'm glancing over my mom's like my mom did the same thing with it Mr. Tato did where she was like mm hmm.
You don't say those words.
But see I liked it.
My mom would also shop at the museum and she would be like oh my gosh I'm going to go to the museum and I'm going to go to the museum and I'm going to go to the museum and I'm going to go to the museum.
I liked it.
My mom would also shop for it a lot too because I was not a kid with expensive taste.
I did not ask for powering power wheels that sort of thing.
I never wanted the really expensive stuff.
But when I went on trips I was a big souvenir guy.
So it's nice if I ran out of the money I brought if I need I was like you know I want one more you know mom this is nice right.
This is pretty good I get that.
So it was nice having you know the community bank around.
So you were you were just you were you were fine with her being there but you were especially happy because she could bankroll any souvenirs you needed.
Yeah I feel like we also like I remember we went to the inner harbor a lot which is like the tourists area of Baltimore.
It's like an aquarium and a science center with like three city walk kind of mally things in between.
So like those trips the parents always liked going on because they would just like let the kids like all right be back in an hour.
We're going to go eat crab cakes and drink wine or drink beer.
All right.
So the Baltimore Inner Harbor debacle coming.
It's 24 part daily series in 2024 Jason's mom's going to be on that one.
And one of the running.
Yeah she'll be she's the sector keeper of that saga.
Oh no.
She's a smart.
Hey well she has to do it.
She I should be able to give you money if you need it during the show.
Oh that's good.
A full daily series where if we start to go towards a dirty word somebody's mother is like.
Hi folks I just want to prepare you that Scott's audio quality is about to dip and it's just because something happened with the recording and I wanted to prepare you for that and didn't want you to be shocked when you heard it because you know you might have dropped your bag of crisps all over your phone or your computer and I didn't want that anyway.
Back to the show.
She does not know she she has listened a bunch now and she does not like it.
Those kinds of words that said when I came down the stairs like when I was visiting for Christmas last year she was wearing a big oversized haunt cast the fright shirt so and there was a bunch of magnets there was a bunch of our logo magnets on the fridge.
So that was very sweet.
That's very nice.
But if we put one out if it's you know if we had a profane one she would be happy podcast the book.
Yeah, in that merchandise by that.
Hey, the inner harbor is owned to a building that when I was there I knew it was like a Barnes and Noble a harder out cafe and ESPN zoned, but many years before was the infamous six flags power plant.
The.
Yes, they crazy designed indoor theme park with no rides just a lot of optical illusions and shows and yeah.
That sounds like an Instagram museum.
Like, just where there's not really anything to do there.
Yeah, yeah, I'm not a big fan of those.
Baltimore, Baltimore power plant. I've had a sticky note on a laptop for like years that has said, we should do Baltimore.
That's that's a good way.
Yeah, that's a long one. Yeah, that's a good today. A lot of technological innovation was tested out there that showed up in other places I feel like.
Sure, but the thing itself was weird and bad, although I kind of a disaster. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Okay. We're all right. All right.
Theme parks, theme parks, current theme park.
Marissa, is there one rider experience when you were looking at the website that you felt like that was like right up your alley.
Yes.
I honestly thought that that big wooden coaster is probably very cool. So I think that that would be like a delight. It looked like very fun classic kind of roller coaster.
And certainly the YouTube vlog that Jason referenced, that guy was over the moon about it.
And what's the name of this?
I looked up so many pronunciations and all of I swear I saw like eight different ones. It's great.
Because it's very Gaelic and yeah, I have seen it as like Coo Coo Lane or I'm only going to try that.
It's probably wrong, but it's one of the ones that Ireland's only wooden roller coaster.
And it is named after an Irish Denny God, like the the Odysseus kind of of Ireland, which I skimmed through some of the facts about that tale.
Spoiler for the end of this Coo Coo Lane didn't live for very long. His legends did not last long. Died young like a like a rock star like a Jim Morrison or a Janis Joplin.
He got into a seemingly got into a fight with a bunch of teenagers, like teenage kids of a guy he killed who cut him open at the chest.
And then all of his intestines fell out of his chest. But he shoved him back in and said, let's let's go. Let's fight more.
So they did fight more and decapitated him. And that was the tale of Coo Coo Lane.
Fighting Irish baby! Fighting Irish!
He put the intestines back in.
Yeah, for like five seconds, seemingly.
Like triumphant, no, I'm fighting on. All right.
This immediate headshot.
Wow. I saw him described as like an Irish Incredible Hulk because he could like change.
He would get very big and muscley and stuff like a tall tale like a Paul Bunyan or a John Henry.
One of his parts of his legend is that he at some point kills a very vicious dog, which basically makes him the first Irish cop.
So there's that. Yeah, he I was not familiar with this character.
Yeah, I wasn't either. It's so complicated Celtic lore. It's so the pronunciations and all the variations and stuff.
But Marissa, of course, grew up with this was one of her favorite childhood.
Yeah, it was actually my first language. So
You were butchering it. Oh my God.
You were you were not allowed to know the story of Blossom, but you were allowed to know the story of Coo Coo Lane.
Yeah. No, I didn't really grow up with these myths, but I was like obsessed with Greek myths as like a kid.
Like I had that big yellow book. I don't know if you guys had that book.
It was a big yellow book. It's another one of these.
I don't know the yellow book. If you saw it, you'd be like, oh, it was like this oversized yellow book.
You know what I mean with like the entire, you know, pantheon of gods.
You know, there was a sun and maybe some blue.
It was.
Dailor is I'm saying this name wrong.
Do you lower? I'm butchering this.
It's a book of Greek myths. I don't know.
I don't know. I don't remember, but like I was obsessed with that book and would like read it and read it and read it like as like a 10 year old.
Would you would you go and like talk to kids and assume they had that yellow book as well and they were very into those gods?
Yes. Yes. Yes.
Equally as embarrassing or unusual.
My mom took me to a lecture and musical presentation on Gullah, which is a Creole language and culture with African influences that developed in the American South as a result of the slave trade.
And as like a six year old, I went to that fell in love with the music, bought a cassette tape, brought a cassette player to school, played that tape at recess.
And didn't understand why nobody else liked this music or knew it.
That's very sad.
I mean, beautiful music. But you're sitting there as sad as Mr. Tato alone in his booth.
Truly. Yeah. But I just think that like you just don't know what other kids are doing until you show up and do something totally different.
Were there any other moments you remember as a kid where you were like coming in and like, I got something that's going to really impress all the other kids?
Or is that the biggest one?
That's like the biggest one because like it was like one of those moments where like we're at the park at recess because we went to recess at this like park across the street.
And I just remember playing it and thinking I was going to be such hot shit.
Like I thought I was going to be so cool.
And then, you know, I realized no one's interested.
And I sit on a park bench alone.
That's that Gullah girl.
That Gullah girl's cool. You talked to her yet?
You think that's what they were saying?
I think it went well. You only asked.
They were intimidated. Yeah.
That's something my mom always said to me. It wasn't that kids weren't talking to me. It's that they were intimidated.
They probably are just afraid to talk to you because you seem so smart and cool.
Or it's like they're jealous of you is a lot. You'd hear that too as a kid.
And then like after a couple of years, you'd be like, I don't think they're jealous of me.
I don't think they're jealous of my weirdness.
They have problems of their own for certain, but I don't think that's right.
Marissa, what you are describing is how I felt as a kid when I would start going on about the backstories of theme park attractions.
Here's how this works.
The dream finder is Figment's friend.
At a certain point, I was just like, this is a private thing for me and for my family.
And yeah, it honestly kind of wasn't until college that I was like other people.
I was like, hey, yeah, this thing. Right. Yeah.
Yeah. You found your tribe. That's right.
I talked about the Beach Boys so much as a nine year old boy.
And I would like wear like a bright orange, like a neon, the brightest hat you've ever seen with their logo.
I would wear it to school and think that was cool to do.
Were you at all?
Anyway, then Jardine was, you know, Jardine was less of a presence for a minute.
And some David Marks came in and said, anyway, want to go out with me?
Okay, so they might be giants used to have a dial-up song that you could call.
And like this is before you could get every song.
So it was a nine hundred. You'd have to pay a little, but you would hear their songs.
And I was just going to ask Scott, were you like maybe this is the wrong timing.
But like when the Beach Boys appeared on Full House, how did you feel?
Well, that, you know, that made them more relevant among seven, eight year olds, which which helped.
Definitely. At least you like people finally had a signifier.
But I might have been a person who was like if if even I started connecting and like,
oh, like so they oh yeah, they did Kokomo.
Yeah, Kokomo is, you know, like you have to go back into the 70s, you know, like, you know,
it's kind of a pop it. But like Sunflower is really where things are at.
And we're very lush, wonderful, smart, smart music.
They're like pushing people away even with the connection.
Trying to trying to make a connection.
No, I don't care. No, go away.
You know, I get the same way as I do.
What is that? Is there a word for that kind of feeling?
Because I've certainly encountered it in myself and seen it in others where like someone's trying to connect
and then you have to showcase your depth of knowledge or that you're not a part of that.
Elitism.
Feature, a superior feeling, superiority, feeling ownership over something.
Cry for help reaching out.
No self sabotage.
Not to nowhere.
Please, I'm so lonely.
All I have are my crisps to go home to.
Boy in the ad resting on his shoulder.
Mr. Tato is the answer.
He can take anyone away from all these symptoms.
They have at Tato Park, they have a 5D cinema.
Did we come across this, which is doesn't have like a specific movie?
It appears it is closed right now due to social distancing.
Yeah, the factory tour, too, is closed.
Yeah. Oh, that's a bummer.
Yeah, you feel like why would you even go?
But it says featuring air gusts, water jets, leg ticklers, flashing lights and bubbles.
Sure to get pulses racing from start to finish, but it doesn't say what it is.
And it looks like it's a 4DX theater and it's got about 25 seats from this photo.
And they're all children and they're all like pretending they're excited about whatever they're seeing.
I really feel like Tato wouldn't approve of something called like leg ticklers or whatever, you know,
but wouldn't love bus Tato like a leg tick.
He has a leg tickler at home for private use.
Definitely. But children are not involved and children should be shielded from that.
Right. That's fair.
He probably has just two of the chairs from the 5D cinema and he puts his lover in it
and he just has like a little remote control that says leg tickler on it.
And he like controls the speed at which the tickles happen.
I mean, I'll know one day.
Hopefully soon.
When you're married under the eyes of the church and God and your family and friends,
let's also say the wedding party for Marissa and Tato.
We got Mafalda's there.
A movement, a bunch of the movements, the rounded.
Yes. Creatures.
Cartoon creatures.
Hot Stuff, the Little Devil from Harvey comics.
Little Devil.
I think a lot of Harvey comics characters would be there.
There were a lot of Harvey comics.
There were two little guys that I like this comic book I read when I lived in Spain called Sipi y Sapa.
And they would be there.
They're like little mischievous twins, one with blonde hair, one with black hair.
Great.
We've ever come across a mythology called Beano land.
I guess it wasn't called Beano land.
What's the thing?
Beano is the thing.
We went to the steam park last week.
This whole Beano world.
That's a weird British thing.
You ever run into Beano?
Are you talking about the pill you take for flatulence?
No, no, no.
That's a very common mix up.
In this case, even though Mr. Tato is a big walking potato, Beano is not a big Beano pill with a face.
Yeah, they're just a series of older characters, like cartoon strip style characters.
I think you would be interested in them because they're very old.
Yeah.
Which is really, that's like number one.
Yeah, it's got to be old.
It's got to be off brand.
Do you know what I mean?
Like it can't look too mainstream for me.
Right.
It can't look like something people would like.
Exactly.
Well, then you're going to love the British version of Dennis the Menace, which is unrelated to our Dennis the Menace, even though they debuted on the very same day.
It's a different guy.
He wears a striped shirt.
He's got an ugly dog.
It's a whole thing.
And you're saying guy.
Is it a man?
It's just a little dude.
He's like it's like Sid from Toy Story, which I have you seen Toy Story.
Is that too mainstream?
I'm sorry.
You were there's a French Toy Story.
Marissa likes a lot better.
It was made in 1975.
Le Petit Jouguet.
I don't know if that's right.
The real Toy Story.
The Red Balloon, the series.
Marissa doing a Quibi version of the Red Balloon.
It's just me with a cassette tape in a park.
Lil Bicycle Thieves.
I think these are good ideas.
Yeah.
Band of Lil' Outsiders.
They still do the dance.
They're just a lot less graceful.
What haven't we done?
Oh, yes.
Like Chessington, Tato Park has a zoo next to it.
And I just wanted to showcase.
I'm going to try to screen share.
I never know how to do this.
But here we go.
OK, I am going to share.
These are the residents of Lemur Woods.
They're Lemurs at Tato Park.
And they look like they want to come out and do a dance.
They look like they want to kick my ass.
And then one other thing that you can see at Tato Park.
Let me try and get back to my notes.
Make these scary Lemurs go away.
I guess we've been looking at them the whole time.
They're your Zoom background too.
Boy, yeah, they're growing into my soul.
They are my Zoom background as well.
Far from what I've been having.
Yeah. Is it because you want to kick our ass, Jason?
No, I don't.
I'm having a great time.
But not as good as a time as I had when I rode the horse ride here at Chessington.
As a child.
You mean Tato?
Oh, yes. Here at Tato.
Excuse me. The pony rail.
The ride is called Pony Rail.
And there is a child that looks very much like.
Not dissimilar from a child me.
Yeah. I think that pony ride is very darling.
It was one of the ones I clocked as like a cute little idea.
That child looks both like a child and a very old man.
Yeah.
The two ends of Jason, I guess.
The two ends of Jason.
Guys, guys, come back.
I got more to tell you.
I haven't even started on Fred and Ethel Mertz.
Now they live downstairs.
They own the building.
And there are friends.
Eventually they move to the country when they sell the building.
Fred became Ricky's manager.
He had no experience.
Well, he managed the building.
I guess it's kind of similar.
I'm the only one in the school who knows this.
The janitor is even walking away.
The ancient janitor hates it too.
Get with the times, kid.
I know what it is.
I just don't care.
Watch it. Watch.
Turn on empty nest.
Watch a new show.
I love them.
Evening shade.
I let's see.
There's a little, there's a Viking ride.
And this is very charming where you, you go, it's, this is fake rocks.
As very recently they have fake rocks at this part,
which makes it a real theme park in our eyes.
You take little Viking ships.
Up into a mountain that has like a big Viking.
Helmet.
That is really cool.
Look. And so they're getting into theme.
That's the toughest part.
It's like,
it's like a big,
I think that,
that's the stupidest thing.
I think with any little theme park.
I think the actual seeming is tough to do,
it's expensive.
They have to get on their feet before they can do it.
And Viking voyage seems like,
a great step in that direction.
Seems like really fun.
Yeah, I thought that one looked really cool.
It reminded me.
And I don't know if it is that similar, but it reminded me of,
there's a ride at Efteling.
And I'm going to butcher the name of it.
It's a very,
kind of a voyage Viking style ride also.
I think you're a merchant.
Technically in that, but you know,
or part of a.
I was going to ask you this.
We specifically are not doing Efteling on this European vacation
month because we feel like we have to actually go to do it proper
homage, but to represent Efteling.
Is there, is there any odd Efteling detail you can,
you know,
you can give us so that we can say that Efteling had a little presence
within this month.
I would say one of the most magical moments of my life.
Was turning around.
To see a majorette.
Being followed by 20 ducks.
And all of them.
Dancing. You know what I mean?
The ducks are like marching along and the majorette is like blowing a
whistle into like a rhythmic beat little song. She has like a,
you know, a bee feeder style hat.
I don't know what majorettes call their hats, but so darling.
And like, they're just going through the streets, like the, you know,
Walkways of Efteling.
Performing and like.
I love ducks.
Like ducks are one of my favorite animals.
So like turning around to see a bunch of.
Choreographed ducks was so magical.
Choreographed ducks. So they all were in.
They were in a line. They knew how to stop and they knew how to start.
They weren't dancing or anything.
Okay.
So the number one thing you can do at Efteling is see a majorette with
ducks.
I mean, it's the highest on my list.
And there's a lot like truly Efteling. I think, you know, whenever you guys.
I think it's my favorite theme park in the world.
So.
It might have to be a star studded episode too, cause it's so.
A lot of past guests have been on other friends have been on and,
and just everyone, if you get people started talking about it,
they'll just go like for hours.
I think one of the things that I like about it,
and I'm not going to go into it is that.
I think very few times in life do you get to be immersed.
In kind of like.
A world that feels very created.
Intentionally and specifically, and by mostly like one point of view.
And a lot of Efteling was created by like one, you know,
a director or whatever. I know you guys probably know the words better than I
do, but like a creative director that.
That implemented so much of it. You know what I mean? So it's,
it's very special in that way.
And I think it's very, very special.
Wow.
That sounds so up our alley.
And also I'm excited to say, I found a video of this.
Look at that. That's it.
That's the Efteling Gansun parade.
I mean, it's, it's insane.
Truly. Yes.
One.
These are like mighty.
I was going to say mighty ducks.
I was organically going to say.
Like a bird, like a Mary Poppins bird with a,
like a big drum contraption. Oh my God.
Wow.
You're right on the money.
It's magic.
Wow.
I had no idea there was that.
So well, we'll have to break it up.
We'll do the full Gansun parade episode.
Yeah.
We didn't, it wasn't a best angle, but I mean, if the ducks are thick,
you know, their seats.
Have to be thick.
Out of this world.
Have to be thick as well.
Now, now you got to, you've got to,
you've got to Mr. Tato behind you.
He doesn't want to see no seats.
That's fair.
They're, they're, they're behind.
Would he be okay with that?
He's okay with the word.
He just doesn't want to see them.
He just doesn't want to say a duck, but even though duck,
even the duck seats are not, unless you're married to those ducks.
Okay. That's fair.
Well, I will respect his wishes in this moment.
I hope one day Mr. Tato gets to see my duck, but
you, you brought some things to the table before we wrap it up.
There, there, there were some things you wanted to accomplish.
I created.
Yeah.
So I created a little quiz for you guys, cause I was like,
you guys are always doing the interviewing.
Maybe you need a little bit of newness in your life.
You know what I mean?
You get to be, Ooh, how can I answer these questions?
So like, I love trivia.
I love game shows.
So I put together a little quiz kind of in the vein of like true or
false. You know what I mean?
You have a 50% choice either way.
And because it's not about Tato park specifically,
but it is about potatoes.
So,
you've got my attention.
The name of this quiz is potato or Jason.
So you're going to have to choose is the fact about a potato or is the
fact about Jason.
All right.
And I'll just go round Robin style.
So it'll go like Mike, Scott, Jason, Mike, Scott, Jason, Jason.
You might have an unfair advantage, but you get to play.
You would think though, you never know.
You never know.
You might not.
You might not know.
Okay.
So Mike, this one is for you.
Go ahead.
Is a potato or Jason 80% water?
Good question.
Uh, I'm going to say,
see it's how specific is this going to be?
That's the question here.
I think it's a potato.
It is a potato.
That's a potato.
Jason is in fact 80% ice cream.
Well, yeah, that's accurate.
Of course.
Yes, of course.
Um, so this one's for you, Scott.
Did a potato or Jason fish for pond eels using little pieces of hot dog as bait?
Well, as much as I'd like to see Mr. Kato do that someday, I'm going to have to say that's Jason.
That is Jason because potatoes know better.
Right.
The pond eels like sharp cheddar cheese instead.
Jason, this one is for you.
The largest one of these weighs in at seven point one pounds.
Is it a potato or is it a Jason?
I'm going to have to go with potato on this one.
That is that is correct.
It is potato.
But interestingly enough, Jason is in fact seven point one pounds potato.
Wow, I didn't know that.
Well, you know, we can take a look.
Yeah, makes sense.
OK, Mike, as a child, did potatoes or Jason relish thumbing through used books down the shore?
See, I think that's Jason.
I'd love to see a potato do the thumbing, but I believe Jason thought that is correct.
It is Jason.
Potatoes cannot read.
Scott, this one is for you.
Did the United Nations dub the year 2008 the year of the potato or the year of the Jason?
Oh, I mean, as much as I want to give credit to whatever Jason was doing at the time, which I think was being a P.A.
on American gladiators, I don't I don't think that would have been enough to get the UN's attention.
So I will say potato.
It is potato.
But Jason declared 2008 the year of relaxing after doing all that laundry.
OK, this is the best thing that's happened on the show.
Jason, this one is for you.
My therapist calls laundry a non-preferred task.
You just like said a Ziggy out loud.
Jason Sheridan is a real life Ziggy.
That's another one that we never gotten to know.
It's a way to help me keep things in perspective and not magnify little problems.
It sounds like you got a good therapist and one that is, I don't know, on your rhythm or whatever.
Long suffering, I believe, is the term he uses.
Sounds great.
OK, Jason, Jason, this one's for you.
Do potatoes or Jason's historically suffer from crippling hat headaches?
I OK. OK. It was me.
Eventually, I just found out I had to drink more water.
I'm kind of a hat guy.
I like my baseball caps now because I am sitting on top.
So you got to do your best.
You are correct. It was Jason.
Good job.
Yes, I hope those pork pies don't give you a potato headache.
Potatoes do know how to buy hats that fit them properly, though.
Mike, this one I have one more for each of you.
This one's for you, Mike.
Were potatoes or Jason first domesticated eight thousand years ago in South America?
Huh? Domesticated is an interesting word I've never heard used for a vegetable or a fruit.
I'm going to say it's a potato, though.
That is correct. It is a potato.
As we all know, Jason is feral.
Would a domestic off the leash, baby?
I mean, a domesticated man would not have the nickname The Carouser.
I want to just give a little context here.
Marissa is digging deep here for some old-school Jason Sheridan lore.
We were calling him The Carouser about 10 years ago.
And when he would get really hyped up about something, I would say like Wolverine, he was going feral.
I mean, the audience has to be eating this up, getting extra Jason lore, getting the Cuckoo Lane myth making one of the great, our modern day myth.
Jason.
This one is for you, Scott.
Will keeping potatoes or Jason's in the dark too long cause them to become poisonous?
I don't. Hmm.
You have any Jason have dark preferences and does good poisonous mean like mentally?
Like will he become a very sharp tongue?
I don't know. I'm going to say it is potatoes.
Keeping Jason in the dark too long will just make him rammy, which is what his mother used to call him when he was too rambunctious.
Now that was that was one that everyone in my family said, like everyone uses this term.
And that was one where like, I'm pretty sure kids would look at me sideways if I said like, oh, he seems a rammy.
I mean, it's crazy. It's great.
That's I didn't I did not remember that one.
That was a very good one.
That was a really obscure one.
That one just always stuck with me because it blew me away.
I think it's it's both adorable and confusing.
Sure.
We've got to pull that into the oh my God.
Like like we might just just file that away because we'll be able to call it Jason is being ramby.
Oh yeah. Oh yeah.
That counterpoint you were wrong.
I think we're in the wrong episode.
That was a big ramby.
If only we had the term.
Okay, Jason, this is the last one.
Okay.
Did a potato or Jason inspire the mascot at Tato Park?
Oh, I think it is going to have to be a delicious potato.
Oh, Jason, it's actually Jason.
That little potato in a hat definitely has a hat headache.
Is that why he's like getting in other people's business?
He's like he's ramby, baby.
He's ramby. He's ramby.
He's wound up.
He's not addressing the actual problem.
He's just projecting so much laundry.
Tato's got so much laundry.
Well, he has the clothes to hand out to those underdressed people.
It's just got laundry hanging out everywhere.
Out of sight, out of mind is what I say.
You should start giving your laundry away like Tato.
That was so delightful.
That was fantastic.
I have thought we should eventually do a full roast of Jason Sheridan,
but I don't think we need to do it now.
I'll come back for it if you do it.
I think.
Tato Park, aka the roast of Jason Sheridan.
And you know, not only that, but it's like if the listener is thinking now,
Marissa has brought more to the table than many, many guests do.
Not only that, we have items in front of us.
We have physical items in front of us.
And keep in mind, listener, that this is still quarantine time,
so physical items are harder to do.
Marissa, you drove around town leaving.
You were a real Santa.
You were a three-stop Santa.
Thank you.
Tell us what's going on here.
So these are gifts for you guys kind of to celebrate this quiz.
I don't know.
I bought them for you guys a year ago and figured I'd give them to you
guys.
I'm not sure I came back on the podcast, so, um,
there's just a little gift. You guys can open them now.
Oh, not only that, but you drew, there's a little, there's a Mr. Tato.
On the don't know that it's recent. I knew what I was doing.
Take a picture before I open it.
Please don't open the recording.
It's a mini Christmas.
Oh, wow.
Did we all do we all get the same thing?
Yeah.
Whoa.
Cool.
Do not disturb from Disneyland Paris.
Yeah.
That's the Hollywood Tower Hotel in Disneyland Paris.
Wow.
Um,
anyone feel confident enough to say the French version and the do not disturb
and then on the other side,
Nippa deranger.
Maybe pretty good French in high school.
This is great because this is obvious.
This is a gift.
This you didn't steal this from because obviously it's Hollywood Tower on it.
You didn't stay.
That's the ride.
That's not the hotel.
I'm not telling.
No, I bought them.
I bought them.
Oh, okay.
Oh my gosh.
Thank you.
This is good.
You put this on your door when you're either sleeping or what I've understood
in the last couple of weeks, making love.
It's a new thing I've learned about.
Are you talking about like a song in a dorm room?
I mean, yes, I was reading about that version of it as well.
But wait, Mike, you had sex for the first time due to this European.
I didn't say that.
I just said I'm learning about it.
I'm just saying,
understanding how it all works now because of the,
the character development I'm having on the saga.
You know that it's a thing that people do.
That's what made you exist on this earth.
Exactly.
I'm figuring you out.
But you're saying that you learned that people put this on before you at a
hotel, you're saying.
Yes, sure.
Oh, I thought you met in your regular life.
I see.
Well, I may use it in my regular life.
Tell the dead.
Deadbolt too, for good measure folks.
You know, better safe than sorry.
Can the dog, can the dog read this?
I know.
Can the dog read this?
I don't know how smart is your dog.
You have average dog intelligence.
All the dogs, no dogs, no English, but all dogs, no French.
That's true.
This is incredible.
And then you bought this a while back,
but that you've given it to us during a European vacation episode.
You've brought, you brought gifts from Europe.
This is so appreciated and so appropriate.
Yeah.
Thank you.
That's, that's just kind of a, you know, amazing coincidence, but yeah,
I just saw them and they were,
it was like right after our Hollywood tower of terror changed.
So,
Oh yeah.
So it was more, it's a, it's a rarity now.
Yeah.
They, they still got it.
Geez.
Well, this is wonderful.
I, I,
is it any, any parting words we want to say here in an episode that was
slightly about a potato theme park?
Anyway,
I got their final,
the last of our things to fit in.
Jason seems to have a iPad out.
He's got facts maybe at the ready.
Just rest in peace, Bobby Sands and God save Jerry Adams.
All right.
Here's, here's maybe like a nice transcendent note to go out on.
When we were on topic in this episode,
we mostly talked about the man, not the partners.
And if that seems like an odd amount of weight to put on a character,
you know, just some silly mascot.
It seems like in Ireland, he's very well regarded.
As I said, you know, they ran him for office and people actually voted for
him.
They did this.
Can we say the end of the, of the,
the campaign of the Mrs. Tato campaign?
I think what happened is somebody said,
They couldn't figure out a satisfying here's, here's what would the end,
the end of this would be.
They just said, he's not ready to settle down yet.
That's good for me.
Yes.
Great news.
You're still in the game.
I got really scared for a second.
Nope. They didn't.
The official company say that is cannon that use, you can still have.
He is a, so he is very beloved.
Not only that, this was a quote that I saw in an article about him on
Prospect magazine.
Okay.
If you want to portray Irishness in pop culture in 2020,
Tato and Mr.
Tato in 2020,
you can still have him.
And then you can still have him.
Yeah.
You're not going to stayGenius,
no.
I think Choi is pretty curious.
That is important because something that is happening.
Almost
so this is a journalist saying that they want to do away with the
data.
Wow.
Hell yes.
This is
coming from us.
I'm just, I'm reading a quote, but I can't help it, but agree.
This.
Yeah.
That seems like something we would say a little bit joking, but this was
the kind of point we would end an episode on, but they kind of, they did it
for it.
This is vetted.
This is a professional writer who see what actually is from there.
I'm guessing that's the entire country of Ireland is really seeing you guys
and me by association as heroes right now.
So I think, you know, congratulations.
We're freeing them of they've, they've been shackled to this, like this
stereotypical imagery for so long.
And then this, this article from 2020, us doing this, it's going to be that
article first.
And then this podcast episode are really the things that just open it up for
Ireland and really be themselves.
And here's what I think.
I think we need to expand Tato.
Let's get Tato out here and let's have an American version of the mascot.
Obviously we're talking about Jason doing Tato's voice, but maybe, maybe that's
sacrilegious cause he's an American.
Let's have Tato Jr.
Much like nut junior is in America.
We're all having, we're having junior fever as far as mascots are concerned.
Jason Sheridan is Tato Jr.
The American version of this character.
And let's bring Tato crisps into America so we can all enjoy this nice snack.
I just speaking of Tato Jr.
I love this idea.
I wanted to bring this up to there's a Japanese potato mascot that I think Tato
would be friends with.
And now to me looks like Tato Jr.
So, cause it feels like baby new year a little bit to me.
If you guys would look up Kalbi potato chips, you'll see a delightful little
mascot that I think Tato would approve of.
Kalbi.
Kalbi up here.
Oh boy.
He's in a sash.
He's in a sash and the same proportion of hat.
And he's, he's like, he's running for office.
He's like a little mayor.
He's running for office.
This is so Jason S.
Great.
Wow.
Kalbi.
You know what?
I don't even shit about Tato anymore.
Kalbi is my new man.
Yeah.
Hey, delete this episode.
You have to go spend money for Kalbi's PDF.
Yeah.
I want to see if Kalbi's autobiography exists.
I will, I don't care what it takes.
I will.
All my credit cards can be stolen.
You'll give money to Ugandan princes in order to read the story of this potato mayor.
Kalbi is my man.
I think it's president vice president situate.
It's just figuring out which is which, you know, Kalbi Tato.
There we go.
How about.
And well, then let me ask if that's the case, I don't want to throw too much of a wrench
into this, but I feel like we have to find at least a cabinet position for the mascot
of Americana and brand mainstay potato corner.
This guy, if we've seen him before, his name is spudster.
So spudster is makes great use of the airbrush tool and Photoshop, as well as the stroke
tool.
I've seen many of them.
He's got inner layers, outer layers.
He looks like a turd.
Let's be honest.
Oh, he does.
He looks like a pellet.
He's nice to spudster.
Yeah, he's like a.
I'm a whole I'm into Kalbi now.
I don't care about any of these other potatoes.
I like spudster.
Spudster is a threat.
I'm into spudster.
I think his name could use some work.
But other than that.
Full first thought.
Yeah.
I think I could stand for him to get a little gra.
Actually, he has a graphic redo because this is very airbrushy.
But if I go down here, you'll see that in some recent art in which he's promoting social
distancing and there are two spudsters who are six feet apart, though also in the middle
of a street.
And while they are practicing social distancing, they also may both get plowed down by a car.
And there are two people behind them that are very close.
No man.
Yeah.
Hang on.
All right.
You know what, Kalbi?
Fucks buster.
This guy's morally in the wrong.
Kalbi's great.
Mr. Tato is great.
Marissa Strickland is great.
You survived.
I guess the ride.
Thanks for being here and bringing so much to the table.
Yeah, thank you.
This is delightful.
It's actually through the gift shop.
Is there anything else you want to say?
I'm going to go to the end of the video.
So would you like to do a giveaway?
Yeah, I would be happy to.
We could do one for you if you want to.
Yeah, yes, we could.
Oh, so on the first one is you can buy something.
I can buy something.
We could do it.
Yeah.
Let's do it.
So where would you like it to go?
The gift shop, is there anything you'd like to plug?
No, but I'd encourage everybody to vote.
Sure,
Yes, indeed.
If there's a Tato campaign specifically.
Right.
You're saying,
Right at Tato.
Right in Tato in November, please.
And right into
Mr.
Tato finds love.
My name Marissa Strickland,
Hopefully I'll fucking become a married Tato one day.
Wait a minute.
Look at this.
We're getting our passport stamped as we have at every step of our European vacation,
kaklunk.
And look at that.
It's Mr.
Tato himself,
his beautiful eyes staring right at you.
And he's holding out a wedding ring.
It's for you.
For you, Marissa.
That's our passport stamp.
What do you say?
I do.
Yay.
With rice being thrown at you from your childhood cabinet.
I'm not there.
I'm hanging out with Kelby.
I'm upset about the wedding.
Kelby would have been better for you, I think.
So anyone tracking continuity in this episode?
Well,
I got a couple of things to say.
I'm going to start off by saying that I am not a married Tato.
I'm married to Mr.
Tato.
And I,
I am married to Mr.
Tato.
And I know the concept of intercourse.
I understand what it is.
Intellectually,
just intellectually.
I'm saying, I'm saying,
I'm discussing.
Kelby's telling you what it's like because he's not approved.
Like Mr.
Tato.
It's not like I'm going to be doing it.
It's like,
I'm not going to be doing it.
I'm going to be doing it.
And he's got a couple of different things to do.
And he's got his brother's VCR.
And he's showing me some stuff.
It's got the two spots for two tapes.
So we can make you a coffee.
Wow.
An episode.
Full of mythology.
And a whole lot of fun.
So.
So,
we're going to have a little bit of a break.
And then we'll get back to you.
As for us, we will continue.
The pockets Reds, European vacation.
We're heading back over.
What's between Ireland and.
Europe.
What's the.
English channel.
Great.
I know.
Smart guy.
And yeah, we're heading back over.
I don't want to give any.
Clues.
I guess.
You know,
I think it's going to be a little bit of a break.
We're going to have a little bit of a break.
So we're going to have a little bit of a break.
Where we will be doing our,
the last of our little day trips.
And I'll say.
What's, what's a good clue.
We're going to deal with some.
Some IP.
That's all that I'll say.
It's a, my, some IP will be discussed.
And then we'll, we'll wrap up the main show on Friday.
It's been.
It's been a lot of fun.
Fun vacation.
And as always check us out on Twitter, Instagram.
Facebook.
And Twitter.
It's a great place.
I think we're going to have a little bit of a break.
We're going to have a little bit of a break.
So we'll read the last two.
Three.
The last three.
Are the last four.
Let's see.
Does Mr.
Tato have a way to say goodbye?
Say goodbye.
Mr.
Or Tato Jr.
Oh.
Here.
I'll just do, I'll just find the whole.
The whole of the rest of the old Irish.
What the old parable.
No, no.
W H.
So does Mr.
Tato.
And Mr.
You shine warm upon your face and rains fall soft upon your fields.
And may we, until we meet again.
May God hold you in the palm of his hand, like he could hold one in the
poem, like he could hold a recommendation.
Yeah.
Of classic salt and vinegar Tato crisps.
Me.
Tato crisps.
Yay.
Beautiful.
Everyone give Mr.
Tato a round of applause at home or wherever you're doing this.
Thanks for listening everybody.
Talk to you next week.
Bye.
Well, before we go, I just want to give a quick shout out and plug to the show Infinity
Train, which is on HBO Max.
It is a very cool cartoon about a weird train.
It's got a bunch of weird, cool cars.
There's adventures.
There's fun.
There's colors and there's sadness, but it's like good sadness, heartstring tugging
sadness.
I mean, this is why we watch TV folks.
You will like it if you like this show and you like all the same nonsense that we like
this show.
One of the writers, of course, is Lindsay Katai, who is a friend of the show.
He's a friend of my heart.
We would appreciate it if you checked it out, stream it on HBO Max, you know, whenever you
have time.
Do it at night, do it in the morning.
It doesn't matter.
See you next week.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a Forever Dog Production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehme, Joe
Cilio and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts,
Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram at Forever
Dog Team and liking our page on Facebook.