Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast contains things that make good boys very uncomfortable.
Danger, injuries, high powered weapons, and most importantly, rude teens.
It's Action Park with Class Action Park director Seth Borges on today's podcast, The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, a theme park podcast that will not be held legally responsible
if listeners die from laughing.
I'm Scott Gardner.
I take no responsibility.
Mike Carlson does not either.
Yeah, I also don't take responsibility for anything that I do in my life.
I'm reckless now.
That's just, that's a thing that happened from the Europe trip, I think.
I didn't mention it, but now I'm mentioning it.
Anyway, Jason Sheridan is here.
I'm here and I guess we should, you know, mention we, like a cruise ship that is docked
in like a country that is constantly changing governments, we are incorporated in the country
from the terminal that no longer exists anymore.
So we cannot be held liable.
That's right.
And while we can't remember the name of it, it is legally listed on a legal document.
It just says the country from the terminal.
And yeah, if there's any legal beef with us, take it up with our holding company there,
Manhattan and Global Obsolvings Inc.
It is a completely legitimate company with a very fancy name.
And, you know, take it up with them.
We do have insurance, but we will not give you any of it.
This is all we, we today are talking about a notorious, the notorious Action Park, which
somehow we, has eluded us for the years we've been doing this podcast and we're finally there.
You know how it's eluded us.
It's because it was so dangerous and it's just we, I think the three of us, as you know,
everyone, are good.
We're too good.
We would have been scared of this.
Oh, we would even be like it would have just like not even we wouldn't have acknowledged
its existence because we would have never gone.
Our my parents, my mother, I wasn't allowed to go to a normal water park.
I don't know why she would have like like duct taped me to a chair to keep me from going.
Yeah, if I sensed that a group trip was forming, like, oh, I think I think there's, you know,
all the boys choir or something I was in is all going to Action Park.
I would have just like, well, do I fake an illness?
What is my do I quit the boy choir before this has to happen?
What is my plan to get out of Action Park?
Nervous, crying into nervous vomiting.
That was that always worked for me.
The Jason Secret.
Well, it's a scary topic for us.
And so we need somebody to lead us through it.
And I think we have just the person in Action Park experts.
He is the co-director and producer of the documentary Class Action Park.
Now streaming on HBO Max.
Seth Porges is with us.
Hello, Seth.
Hey, it's it's awesome to be here.
Yeah. So happy to have you.
Yeah. Yeah.
I don't know.
Are are are you appalled by our point of view, by us,
our good boy is working its way and like that?
How there's I think there's no chance that the three of us would have set foot in that.
I don't want to speak for Jason, maybe, but I think we would have been very scared
of this place if you can't handle a haunt and you can't handle a launch coaster.
The chances of handling an asbestos laden alpine sled
that would leave half of your skin at the top of a ski resort in New Jersey.
It's probably out of the question.
Well, now, while we look to point out, we've made progress in these areas,
as I've just been through.
I am a launch queen and Mike loves haunts and haunts now.
I will say, though, this may be like if this was still around,
this is maybe a decade later where I get there.
Maybe maybe it's like I can feel the progression,
but I still don't think it's right.
It would be right around the corner.
Let's just in case anybody doesn't know this, just real quick,
what we're talking about, this was a very dangerous water park.
That's probably the most probably the most dangerous, most dangerous.
I'm in New Jersey.
I mean, yeah, the very basics of it.
That, yeah, it was in Vernon, New Jersey, many lawsuits, some deaths,
unfortunately, and it's developed this notoriety.
And I feel like especially I don't think that I ever heard of this place
pre 2015 and somewhere around that point, there was a tipping point
where suddenly I'm aware of it. It comes up every once in a while.
I don't know if it was just like everyone was ready to be nostalgic for it.
But suddenly you're seeing articles and videos and I think things
you were involved with said that, you know, mention this place
and all the crazy stories and the loops, the crazy looping slide
that is sort of the emblematic image reading you.
The entrance of the park, like a demented Cinderella's Castle.
The first thing you see when you walk up to the park, the icon of the park,
a giant enclosed tube looping water slide that just instantly
scrambles your brain because it makes no sense.
And when you saw people come go down it, they would come out
facing a different direction.
And that doesn't make any sense because what happens?
How does that happen?
It's very strange to be seen.
You would understand. Yeah.
It really feels like I'm I'm just going to say I'm just I'm sure
this is not an original thought, but it feels like some a five year old
made a roller coaster tycoon park.
The whole park.
Like the whole park like that.
And they didn't put any thought into it.
And like it's like, yes, they're complaining that they're
getting dumped out the side of a of a inner tube or no thought.
But a ton of imagination.
So imagine like going there as a six or seven year old.
And you're used to parks where sort of like the laws of common sense
and physics regulate and dictate what rides you can have there.
And you go to Action Park and all of your wildest fantasies,
like the things you would see in like itchy and scratchy land in the Simpsons
are like suddenly in front of you.
And it's it just it messes with your head.
It like you feel like anything, anything is possible when you walk up there.
And that's like in the air.
And so it's not just these crazy slides, it's this general sense of
possibility and chaos and violence kind of like conspire
to just put people in this mindset where they do things that they would never
in the normal world normally do.
Well, and watching the footage like the period footage
you have in the documentary, like as as someone who like reads
and watches this stuff a lot, everything was just a little off.
Like it's like that's not how water slide like that ski lift
is awfully close to that alpine racing thing.
Like there's just little aesthetic things of like, oh, usually like
raft rides that four people ride in.
There is a series of lifeguards going down and they use hand signals to say,
OK, send another one. This one is clear.
And that just does just didn't happen that next.
Next, next, next, next.
If you want to go down like six buddies at a time and get like clogged up in the tube,
like that would that would just happen.
That's like what life was like there and everything there.
You're right. It's all these slides.
You look at it now and you kind of seen versions of this like Typhoon Lagoon
or a normal water parks.
But what made actually different was it was it was earlier.
It was one of the first three or four water parks in the country.
Modern water parks country.
So you had like Schlitterbahn, you had one wild Disney's River country
and you had action park first four water parks in the country.
And so it's just kind of very early and sort of like the evolutionary tree.
Like nobody knew what a water park was.
So they're trying out all these ideas, many of them not yet perfected.
And so they all kind of had issues.
And now you look at it and it's like, that's that's not right.
That's just like not right.
Yeah, I wrote I recall from learning about Schlitterbahn and Wet n Wild
how and I don't remember which is which, but I know like there was there was a time
where there were parks operating for a long time before they figured out,
oh, here's a softer material to make the slides out of.
Don't just tear people's knees apart.
Obviously, there's a lot of trouble that is specific to action park.
But you're you're that's interesting context you're giving us that it was
it was sort of a wild west of an area in general, the water park.
It was a wild west and all of those parks, like except for Disney's
River Country, clearly, but like Schlitterbahn and Wet n Wild
and Action Park are all run by these kind of really big iconic personalities.
And there's this great like Grantland article about this kind of weird
frenemy relationship between the Schlitterbahn and the one wild guy.
The action park guy was like 10 times like crazier than those guys.
And all these rides coming to action park, we talk about in the movie,
but it was it was literally just like some random employee has an idea
and they build it or the owner has an idea or they build it or they go to like
IAPA, like an industry convention.
And instead of like the big display booze
where like the real legit manufacturers are, they go to like the little tables
in the back where some dude has a doodle and it's like a ball that rolls down a hill.
And they decide to build it, even though no prototypes
have ever been built before.
And so you get all these strange rides
that were just kind of, you know, thrown at a wall and what's going to work.
It's very like old timey Coney Island, the way when you see
we have to do an episode in some way, like actually getting specific about,
you know, like that weird footage you see where it's 20 people in full
thick wardrobe, all like on like a vibrating floor,
like being slammed against walls.
I'd like to know what that is and where it comes from and what the hell happened.
But it feels like for the 1970s, when there are more polished Disney parks,
it feels extremely like there's never been a park of any kind before.
Yeah, it's like they're starting again.
It's like, you know, like this was decades after Disneyland.
Disney World was already there.
And this was in many ways like a direct response to the rise of Orlando
as a theme park destination.
Like the owner was literally saying to himself, like, OK,
Orlando is all the way down there.
We're right next to New York City.
We're right next to Philadelphia.
We're not that far from Boston.
Like half the country is within like a day's drive of here.
Why don't we build Disney World here?
And so they had the ski resort.
And of course, the ski resort in New Jersey has like a three month long season,
like nothing. Right.
And so he wants something to do within the summer.
And so they dreamed of building this four seasons resort.
There would be a ski resort in the winter and action park in the summer.
And in order to build it, they would, you know, it was mostly funded
via like a penny stock scam.
So they would call up like grandma's eating dinner at their table saying,
we're going to build Orlando in New Jersey.
And that's how Action Park was built.
Yeah, I it's funny, the scam stuff is very interesting to me.
Like, it's always interesting to us.
It's like an evergreen topic on this show.
But at the start of this documentary, I thought, you know,
Mulville, the guy behind Action Park, he was going to join the pantheon of like,
you know, John Binkowski kind of miss the hard rock park.
I kind of misguided.
But like I was optimistic or like David Hare, like completely delusional.
But Mulville has a body count.
The other guys don't have like blood.
Literal blood on their hands.
With his claim to fame.
Yeah, this is the second episode where the phrase near decapitation will be uttered,
though. I mean, I think that's worth.
But that was dogma, you would say, before David Hare,
for all the things you could call David Hare for, he didn't put up a wire that almost
killed the dog patch episode.
I was just like, like so tense, like when are they going to get to the capitation?
Like when's the capitation coming?
The answer was two and a half hours in.
Exactly. You know, it's coming.
It's like, when's the trip wire and all that has to come, it has to come.
And it gets to the fireworks factory. Yeah. Yeah.
Exactly. When the fireworks factory coming.
Wait, so you knew about dog patch.
So is this your interest in weird, shady, dangerous parks?
Extends, I guess, beyond just action.
Yeah, I got I got a shady theme.
Do you guys know about Spree Park, by the way?
This is no.
OK, it was this park in Germany, and it was like the only amusement park
in East Germany during the Cold War.
And then after the Cold War, it was purchased by this guy who used it
as a vessel to ship large amounts of cocaine inside ride vehicles.
So he'd be like transporting like carousel horses
and they'd just be like loaded with cocaine.
It's like a totally wild story. Yeah.
Oh, my God.
That's wild.
That's like what Robert Evans was doing on the set of Popeye with mannequins.
Oh, yeah. Is that right?
I believe it was. Yeah. Yeah.
And then like, you know, hiding it in his trunks
and having to falsify a letter from Henry Kissinger.
That's a second date one.
Yeah, there's a second gate episode clear, but there's a park.
I think it's in Germany that's built in a decommissioned nuclear reactor
like the Simpson style, like smoke staff is like the center of the park.
And you're like in rides in the middle of it.
Wild stuff. Do you know anything? Is it cool?
Is it a good place?
I hope it's cool and not very, very hot, honestly.
It's probably much safer. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
So do you do you have I assume the answer is yes.
Do you have like sort of a maybe a Mount Rushmore of these figures
who have started these parks? Because these people are fascinating.
I think it's interesting because Walt's shadow looms large.
And I think everyone in their own head thinks I'm going to be
the Walt Disney of New Jersey or I'm going to be the Walt.
Like, that's always fascinating to me how I think these people are reaching
for that like. Yeah.
Well, well, Jean Mulvihill, the guy who created Action Park,
he was like trying like directly in many ways modeling.
So what I like is he was friends.
He was friends of Trump.
And what I like to basically say is like when Trump decided
he wanted to be like whatever politician, his friend Jean Mulvihill
decide he wanted to be Walt Disney.
So like the thought experiment is like really what would have happened
if Trump had opened an amusement park?
And I think that's like exactly how Action Park played out.
But there's, you know, we talked about in the movie how amusement parks,
theme parks in particular, kind of these like embodiments of these
eccentric auteurs often people have like this vision for the world,
like a petri dish, maybe for how they want the world to work.
They want to create this little lab
and they want to just like throw people into it.
And Walt Disney had this like very specific idea of this,
like fantastical, very safe, tame place.
You have Disneyland and then Jean Mulvihill's vision was like anarchy
and chaos and like Lord of the Flies.
And that's what Action Park was.
Right. And his background seems like it's stock trader, insane pace.
Like no rules.
I mean, you basically detail all this in the movie.
Yeah, it really he he got his vision.
It was realized.
Yeah, he was, you know, he was just kind of, you know, like Jordan Balfour era
Wall Street kind of guy who was breaking all these rules.
And that's kind of like par for the course of that time, that place.
And he gets banned for life by the SEC.
But prior to that, he he had his hands in all sorts of businesses.
And he kind of buys up these ski resorts for cheap
and basically decides he's going to turn Vernon, New Jersey
into this big time resort destination.
And he quickly realizes that this like small town,
you know, if the SEC can't stop him, what's the town of Vernon going to do?
You know, like this attitude of like ask for forgiveness, not permission.
Break every rule in front of you, like these small towns,
even the state of New Jersey, which is so helpless, like the wheels of regulation,
the wheels of government move so slow.
So if he didn't have insurance one season, maybe just like
conveniently forgot to file paperwork by the time the state got around
to realizing it or saying anything, the season would already be over.
And you'd be like, well, what are you going to do?
We can't undo that season.
And as you mentioned before, like for many years of operation,
the park operated with a totally fake insurance company
that the owner created based in the Cayman Islands
with the amazing name of London and World Assurance.
I think I want to like print t-shirts that say that.
Like one of my favorite detail, the insurance company of the Cayman Islands.
I think the name of the word super name.
How does that mean?
It reminds me of King Features Syndicate.
No, yes.
The company that owns all those comic strip characters.
So things fancy if you put a stuffy word like Crown or London in it.
Yeah, I think it was like designed to be a pocket of Lloyds of London, clearly.
So like some clerk in New Jersey is going through.
Papers like that sounds like an insurance company, sort of, right?
Yeah, for sure.
You mentioned Trump, the another character that briefly shows up in the documentary.
And I appreciate you contextualizing New Jersey at the time of like Atlantic City
had only gotten casino gambling legally,
you know, in the early 80s or late 70s or so early 70s, early 70s.
Yeah. And one of the first casinos on the boardwalk was the Playboy Club.
So then Hefner opens the Playboy Club in North Jersey, too, which
it's kind of like North Jersey is always close to New York.
It's always associated with being close to New York.
A few years ago, I think Chris Christie started giving out
casino permits for casinos in North Jersey
while casinos were struggling in South Jersey.
So like there is always shady business going on financially there.
And in the 80s and 90s, you could go to Seaside Heights
or you could go to Wildwood Beach and just bungee jump off a crane.
Like that just and what was under you was maybe a small plot of grass
or just the beach, just the mile long beach.
Very brief story that is not in the movie,
that I don't think anybody really knows.
So the owner of the park, he had one of the first bungee towers
of the sort at Action Park is actually sponsored by Snapple.
It's called like the Snapple bungee tower or something.
But he had partners and was investor in some other bungee towers
along the Jersey Shore.
And one he was on like the outs with one of his business partners or investors.
And so he planned an overnight Carmen
San Diego style heist of this bungee tower.
So he literally in the dead of night steals an entire bungee tower
from the Jersey Shore and then drives off with it.
And the person like doesn't even know until the next morning
the entire bungee tower is gone.
This is all the thing after that.
What do you do about it?
No, he was he this is who this guy was.
So another OK.
So in 1994, towards the end of Action Park's life,
MTV Beach House, Hampton's Beach House, like the grind around the pool,
you know, all that stuff.
The MTV wanted to build like a really stupid, ill advised water slide
that would go from the roof of the beach house into the beach house swimming pool.
And they had like four days to get the beach house ready
from when they took possession of it to when like the show began.
So they're thinking like, who can we get to build this really shady water slide
without permits, without zoning, without permission, with Action Park?
So they call up Action Park and Action Park, the whole team,
like drives from New Jersey to Long Island, to the Hamptons
and constructs this really shady water slide
that went from the roof of the MTV Beach House into the pool.
If you look online at like videos and footage from the 94 Beach House,
you can see this big Action Park sign they put next to the house.
So like the best video is probably the one of Lisa Loeb performing.
You just see this Action Park sign behind her in all of the B shots.
But then the kicker to the story is, you know, the park, Gene,
he had to supposedly like pay the lumber supplier in Long Island
for the wood they were using to build it.
And he just decided he wasn't going to.
He basically was saying like, they're in Long Island.
We're in New Jersey. What are they going to do about it?
And apparently nothing.
That's there's a whole documentary in just yet.
And just how much he just flaunts laws.
Yes. Like I just I am almost I'm just kind of fascinated how that works,
because I think we've talked a little bit about the show, about,
you know, we're following rules and everything.
And the idea I'm assuming that you touch on about five percent
of just the court cases and the lawsuits that he just ignores.
And then like 90 percent of them do kind of go away.
Like it seems like it.
Yeah, nothing. Nothing stuck. Everything went away.
The park when it shut down, it was never because of like legal reasons.
It was bankruptcy.
It was it was never like they suffered virtually no fines.
Their citations, their entire existence.
Here's a great story. OK.
Almost none of this is in the movie just because it's a 90.
It's a tight 90. You got to tell a story. Yeah.
Can't tell exactly. Exactly.
So next to the park, they had they had a parking lot
and connected to the parking lot was like a gate.
And if you walk through that gate to this mom and pop restaurant,
the mom and pop restaurant was closing and McDonald's wanted to take over
the site and build a McDonald's.
Gene didn't want McDonald's to open up because he thought
would eat into all his concession sales.
So what he does is he concocts a scheme.
There's always a scheme.
He sends like one of his kind of attack dog, like lieutenants
to a town council meeting, and he has him say the following.
He says, here's what's going to happen if you allow McDonald's to open.
We're going to shut the gate that allows people to walk from a parking lot
to that restaurant in order to get there.
Oh, the first thing you got to know also is that a major highway
ran through the middle of the park called Route 94.
Says what people are going to have to do is they're going to have to walk on Route
94 on icy roads in ski boots.
They will slip.
They will fall.
They will die.
And the blood will be on your hands if you allow McDonald's to open.
And they did not allow McDonald's to open.
Wow. This I mean, that's crazy.
And my first thought is like not to get too political, you know, but like
this is a Trump's running the government.
It's just like, fuck you.
Don't I don't care.
And then like, are you telling me that action park is are you saying
that action park is America?
I wish you're telling me at least at the moment.
But also, I will say is for the first time, but then I'm thinking
this isn't that dissimilar to what Disneyland did in Anaheim,
where they were going to build a bridge from a new parking structure
that was across from Harbor.
And Disney wanted not not
to have a little area or access point so people could go down
and harbor and go to those businesses.
And Anaheim said, no, they should be able to access those businesses.
And he said, fuck you, we're not building it.
So it's not totally dissimilar.
I think we keep coming across all this odd legality and like shysters
and tricks with these because theme parks are such massive undertakings.
Like, there's no way to get one made without at least a little sprinkling
of shadiness and maybe a giant bucket full of it.
Yeah, you need like a little bit of Robert Moses in you.
I think to like get any of these places built, you just need to like steamroll
over people.
Well, it's messy man, Barnum and not like great showman P.T. Barnum,
like maniac P.T. Barnum, not not singing and dancing Hugh Jackman.
Not to bar them.
No, that's a little like a racist, eluded P.T. Barnum.
So different. But waiting for the sequel with Gene to it's like he
there's a face to all of these stories.
But with, for instance, like Disney and Anaheim, there's not like one hulking
figure that's like, hey, we want to build a parking garage
and you're going to pay for it.
And then we're going to collect all the money and not give it to you.
Like, there's not one guy making a weird demand like that.
It's a corporation, so it doesn't have a face necessarily.
But they they didn't get away with it.
And maybe this is sort of similar to this is like how the DNC
is like is facelessly shady and they don't get away with as much
as when it's just some asshole who like is right, wears it, is proud to wear it.
Yeah, it's me. I don't know. Come at me.
And then nobody does. Right.
Yeah, they're very gene and Trump are very, very similar.
And like, I don't know.
Yeah, we'll see if like none of this will stick to me.
And it kind of didn't. Yeah.
Basically challenging them like what I can imagine, like the Anaheim
tops like going to like an Anaheim council meeting and being like, hey, guys,
here's what's going to happen. Here's the deal.
It's all thing we're going to pick up.
Eiger sends like his Beagle Boys to a town council meeting.
This is when they hire all those like the social clubs that like grow Main Street.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Some heads.
This is what this is their moment.
This is what they've been waiting for.
Time to activate them. Yeah.
They've all been like lying dormant sleeper cells.
And now the Hell's Angels
of that are outsourced to police like, of course,
the famous Horrible incident at Altamont.
Yeah. The Rolling Stones.
It's the Altima of Disney.
They call like, was it like the Waltz Gang or whatever they call it,
like all these groups that are just busting heads, you know, you don't
you don't mess with those guys.
They just call it the California Adventure Food and Wine Festival.
That is.
Yeah, it's wild, but it's yeah, it's interesting.
It just you could you feel it more when there's a maniac doing it
one maniac.
Yeah. What a what a maniac.
I mean, he certainly like holds the piece together and like boy,
hearing is hearing his voice is really you've got a couple little moments
of his voice and it's it's also very Trumpian and that like,
he doesn't like look character.
He doesn't like seem sleazy from his appearance, does it?
Oh, no, extremely.
He looks like a sleazebag.
What does he like sounds like?
And then there's one I wait.
I don't I I only wrote it down so I couldn't do an impression,
but the phrase I wrote down is we got skin, you know, it's a beautiful asset.
Does that sound familiar from your movie?
Yeah. For a very hallucinating.
We got skiing. We got all these nice, beautiful places.
You know, we're valuable asset.
That's what it's. Oh, it's skiing.
I wrote it down like skin and I was like, what does that mean?
I didn't.
Slide skin.
That's what I wanted.
Is he like harvesting the skin of these people?
All right. Skiing. Got it.
In our movie. Yeah.
You can hear it in his voice and something about this place,
I feel like just emanates it that the there's a defunct land about Action
Park and they he Kevin ends it on a clip of like a local news.
And it's just an anchor, the news anchor being so sleazy to the correspondent.
I know the clip.
It's just so gross.
And it's like, did this get in the air?
Yeah. And it just seems to emanate from Action Park.
Yeah, absolutely.
We talk in the movie a little bit about some like the hanky panky
that was going down at that park.
Well, my favorite. So there was you guys ever heard the term?
I never heard this.
I don't know if this is like just an action park thing, but they call it
pool scarfing.
And that's like when you just like raid the bottom of pools
for like jewelry and money and all that kind of stuff like that.
That's how they would make up.
Yeah. These employees are paid like three bucks an hour,
like whatever minimum wage was in the early 80s.
And so in order to augment their pay, they would just like,
first of all, they go post scarfing.
So hunting for gold and money and all that stuff.
But more than that, they were basically trained by their superiors
on how to steal from cubbies when people were on rides.
So that was like part of the job experience.
So theft was a huge problem.
But it was almost all employees stealing from people
while they like put all their stuff in the cubbies while they're on rides.
With a New Jersey Oliver Twist gang
stealing from cubbies.
I can't wait to spend a day in the wave pool.
And I certainly want all my gold jewelry in my pocket as I do.
I wouldn't dream of.
Now, hold on. If you're in a wave pool in New Jersey, those gold.
No one is.
Without common and Scott thinks that there's a guy,
there's a bunch of gold chains at the bottom of a ratio of gold.
The skin. Yeah, the ratio of gold, the skin.
Yeah. A frame under shirt and the gold chain, the communion,
the gold chain you got as a communion gift stays on in the way.
Aspiring Mr. T's everywhere.
They would. OK, so they had this thing, you know, like you go to Disney World
and like people take photos of you by the castle and they try to get you
the photo.
So they would do that at Action Park where they take pictures of like you with
basically these like girls dressed like mermaids.
They were all about just ripping off IP.
So it was like right after a little mermaid came out, they would hire all these
people dressed in like mermaid outfits and you take a photo, take him
and they try to sell you the photo.
But even if you didn't buy the photo, they would still develop the photo
because that's you know, wasn't digital or anything back then.
So all the photos that went unsold, the employees would take the ones
with the most just a visually large guess.
And they put them onto a wall that they labeled the Wailing Wall.
So they just built this monument to it was just such a like that's what this
place was, man. It was just a lot of respect going around.
Sleaziness. I found an article saying how this is just a quote from
This Might Be Sports Illustrated.
When Jean discovered that the force of hitting the water at the bottom of
Surf Hill could tear off bathing suits, he took immediate action by building
a grandstand so spectators could watch this teenage burlesque show.
No, it was Jean's first stop every morning was Surf Hill, I was told.
So he personally would do the rounds and wind up there.
They built an observation that you can sort of see that in like the
headbangers ball clips we use in the movie, which is like a crowd of people
overlooking it with that ride kind of looks a little innocuous.
It's like a big slip and slide on a mountain.
You go down this like Matt, the original design for that ride, original concept
was you're going to jump off of a cliff and that Matt was going to catch you.
And then you just kind of coast the way down.
That was abandoned because they couldn't find anywhere appropriate to build it.
But the employees, everything about this park, like every ride, the employees
would, like the teenage employees would personally plus up in some really
strange and erratic way.
So this one, they would lift up the mat and they would place other mats or trash
cans or just any like large bulbous object they could find under the mat in
order to build a jump.
So the last lane far in the right, it was like eight or 10 lanes of people
racing down this hill.
They would just build up and build up and get more and more air until the guests
eventually broke their neck as it happened.
Like everything at Action Park, it was like the employees found a way to plus
it up, which is weird and creative.
The laws of physics still apply and that just makes the teenage employees furious.
I know the only rules that anyone has to follow at Action Park.
Yeah.
When you're saying all these stories, it's like if somebody was like, well,
hey, tell me like, why did Rome fall?
They would be like, oh, well, there was this water park and they sort of just
pushed everything to everything went too far.
And then like, obviously like it couldn't sustain past that.
Everyone just lost their minds.
You know how like movies are given some weird title in other countries?
That's like sort of vaguely related, but it's a little different.
So I was in like Paris when train wreck came out in a poster called a crazy Amy,
which was terrible and offensive.
Oh, but they always have like some type, like a little bit different.
The four tells, I just imagine they're like other countries.
They really some movie they're going to call it like America Park or something.
You know, like America.
How do we quickly translate what's so crazy?
Like, what's the spirit that this is tapping into?
It's exactly like America.
Oh, my God.
Title, probably the most accurate description.
And they go, oh, yeah, we know exactly what that is.
We don't even need to see it. We know.
Are you telling me action park is a metaphor for America?
Because again, I just don't see it.
I don't see. I don't want to.
I want I want the I want the listeners to view it themselves and decide.
I would never decide for themselves for them.
But if any of our listeners have just started
college and are looking for an essay to write and need a thesis,
this might be a good one.
I I I was just going to say, like, I I get I gotten so nervous
watching this because I was really putting myself and I said at the start
of the show, like I was not allowed to go to
my friend's waterpark birthday when I was 15, 14, 13.
It would happen every year.
And my mom, we would get we would like, oh, we're busy.
I'd have to say, like, we're busy that day.
And I'd be like, because my mom thought this was too dangerous for me to do,
especially with a group of kids and the kid whose birthday was
they were a little crazy. They were a little reckless.
One of the kids had a BB gun.
And I just the whole this whole thing gave me anxiety.
And there's so many stories about like, you know, all fond memories of it.
I I can't I can't see it being possible for me.
Again, quick, quick role play.
I'm OK, I'm you and you're your mom.
Hey, there's going to be there's a change of venue of that birthday party.
This year, this year, they want to do it at Action Park.
Well, what is that?
Oh, that's like this.
I mean, it's a water park, but it's you know, there's like
slide the loops all the way like there's like a full it does.
Like it was upside down.
OK, not going to that.
Tell Brian that it's our anniversary and we're all doing something that day.
But I told him that a month ago and I wouldn't
I wouldn't go watch him show off his BB gun.
OK, well, tell him it's the anniversary of when we first started dating.
That was our marriage anniversary.
This is our dating anniversary.
But I use that when he wanted me to come over and he wanted to show me
May West level sensuality on a black and white VHS.
I tell him we're celebrating
the bicentennial
years later from that.
Tell him we're late to it for 15 years too late.
Tell him you tell him you died.
Tell him that you plan to commit suicide.
I think this this is not not this is accurate to what would happen.
I think oftentimes then I would just be like, well, you call and tell his mom.
And she'd be like, OK.
And she would. Yeah.
Of course, she's going to if she listens to this, she is going to dispute
the story that we know.
Well, the anniversary is absolutely correct.
That part is absolutely 100 percent correct.
And everything else is it's all hypothetical.
We're all we're imagining if you went to Action Park.
Yeah. So what a place to spend an anniversary.
Yeah. But a place to spend an anniversary.
What was your danger tolerance as a child going on rides and water slides?
I loved the thrills.
I did. I really love the thrills.
But it's so weird.
I went to Action Park at like a super young age.
So it's kind of hard when you're six or seven years old
to tell the difference between the artificial danger,
like the imagineered story danger of like Tower of Terror, where, oh, my God,
these ghosts are attacking you and your your elevators crashing
versus like the actual danger of a place like Action Park.
And that's why it's such a mind scramble and like messes with you so much.
Because you go there really young.
You're told these things are dangerous.
But like that thrill isn't, you know, it's an illusion.
And actually, it was like super real.
And I think when you're young, you really can't tell the difference.
So you think like it's just like going on a roller coaster.
And it's within the confines of like a gated amusement park,
which is a place you kind of take for granted is going to be safe.
So all these things in Action Park were effectively like extreme sports
within the perceived safety of an amusement park.
And that's what made it so so strange, I think.
But even then, you know, I went on a bunch of rides there,
but there were ones I wouldn't touch, ones I couldn't touch because,
you know, they like the speedboats.
I think you had to be like 16 or have a good fake ID to ride.
And I think we should talk about the speedboats for a second, too.
Yeah, I don't know.
I don't know about those really.
Yeah.
Was Gene selling fake IDs as a side business?
Oh, somebody had.
OK, there were all the teenagers there had hustle.
So like this park, it wasn't just employed by 16 years old,
which which is like kind of common for regional parks and like fairs and whatnot.
It was managed by them, except for the really, really top people,
like the people who would manage like the entire section of the park
would be 16 or 17 years old.
So they all had hustles. They all had schemes.
There were a lot of like pot plants growing up on the mountain.
The people who would be in charge of kind of like reservations at the hotels
would just like pretend like rooms were booked and then they'd live in those rooms
and throw parties in them.
Like everybody kind of had a hustle.
They would, you know, scarf the bottom of the pool for gold jewelry and stuff,
kick a little up top and then throw parties with the rest of it.
It was a fun place. It's a fun place.
Wow. I am interested to know whatever.
Did everyone basically you talk to have like, well, I was also
stealing like big canisters of soda and I was selling them
to a local restaurant for profit. Yeah.
Well, there was some of the scams were like, OK, so they had daily wristbands
and maybe different colors depending on what day.
So like Monday would be orange, like Tuesday, green kind of thing.
So if you collected and people just like tear off their wristbands
and throw them in the parking lot, you can really easily just collect
all these colored wristbands.
So not even employees, just like local kids would just scour
the parking lot for used wristbands and then sell them to their friends.
It was also really easy to sneak into the back of the park
because it's like kind of a wooded.
It's not like there's no gate around. There's no berm.
You know, it's not like Disneyland or something like that.
There's no berm at Action Park.
So one day this dude escaped from a jail near Vernon
and he was hiding out in one of the condos
that was like a budding, the ski resort in Action Park.
And this, I think, tells you so much about Action Park and this idea
that like rules and laws just don't apply here.
He thought he was he was bored while he was hiding out as a fugitive from the law.
So he decided to sneak into the back of Action Park, thinking that like
the laws of God and man just like don't apply here or something like that.
And he was eventually busted while waiting in line for the Colorado River ride.
I didn't even did he not get to go on anything?
He was just standing around a couple of times.
I got a couple of a bit of you in. Oh, my God.
This is one of the things that I'm sorry.
Go ahead. I always go to say no, no, no.
One of the things I think that Action Park probably had going for it is like,
you know, I think people think of New Jersey
and they think the opening credits of the sopranos like the smokestacks of Newark.
But in the spring and summer, they call it the garden state for a reason.
It's very lush, very green.
And in a lot of the footage that does add some to me, it added like, OK,
that does the woods look kind of nice.
That stream looks kind of nice.
But like, I mean, there are water parks in the northeast that don't have like
the one in my hometown was just two tube slides and a swimming pool.
And on one side was I-95 and was on the other side
was the smaller local highway that merged onto I-95.
So it was practically on a highway island.
And you knew even as a kid, I knew like, I don't want to go there.
But I think if I saw Action Park
from a distance, I would be like, oh, OK, yeah, this looks nice.
Vernon is this incredibly bucolic, gorgeous, very lush area.
It's you know, it's 45 miles from New York City, but really like it was a cow
town, just like farms and whatnot.
And then everything started to change in the 70s when Hugh Hefner built
the Playboy Club and he wanted to basically turn Vernon into the next
Atlantic city. That never happened.
Gambling never actually came up there.
And the Playboy Club slowly kind of fell into various states of disrepair.
In many ways, the Playboy Club might be a metaphor for something.
I'm not sure why.
Man, what could it be?
I don't know. I don't know.
But then Action Park, the same deal.
It was like, we're going to take this area that has this beautiful,
natural surroundings.
What is a day trip from New York City and just kind of exploit that.
So you have this like natural resources and then just like New Jersey
personalities and politics kind of moving in on it is really what made Action
Park what it was.
There really is a facade of this is a nice, cool place to go.
I mean, you're right, Jason, the seeming natural beauty of it.
And then that logo rules that rainbow color.
It's so simple, but pretty instantly iconic.
So you're watching those ads and it's got jingles that are akin
to any theme park jingle we like or the we've got it all at Woodfield.
It's very like it's it fits right along any of the there's nothing in the ads
that tell you this is a shady land.
It's not the what was that like old SNL like super
like the bouncy ball to how the ads like super deep or fun ball.
Super fun ball.
It's not like super fun ball with like 100 disclaimers at the happy fun.
No, it's like happy fun ball.
Yes. Happy fun ball. Yeah.
It's it's not. Yeah. Sing the song.
You know, it's not where it's like come to Action Park
and then like three minutes of fast talking disclaimers,
which is probably what it should have been.
No, but maybe another theme park tour might have like
some entity might have said you got to put a bunch of disclaimers in there.
But the jeans not going to do that.
It would have made it more popular.
I mean, the whole appeal of Action
Mark and why I am fascinated with the topic is that the danger was no secret.
Like it was in the newspapers.
Everybody, everybody knew when you go to the park in real time,
you're hearing people talk about like, oh, yes, some kid got stuck there.
Some kid died there.
You're just like here.
People are calling it to your face like welcome to Accident Park.
Welcome to Traction Park.
Like it's in the air.
And instead of scaring people away, that's what drew them in.
And that's what's so strange and I think amazing about Action Park
was what happens when not only is the danger draw people in,
but then how do people act when they're in this environment
where they know it's dangerous and they know there are no rules.
And that's really like it's not just any one thing.
It's not just this is a dangerous ride.
It's just a dangerous ride.
And people know it's dangerous and they know they can do things
they shouldn't be allowed to do on it is what made Action Park what it was.
To again, bring up a sketch analogy.
It also it reminds me of the Mr.
Show sketch thrill world where it's alternating between.
I wonder if this was Action Park inspired,
where you're alternating between news reports
about all of the calamity and death occurring at thrill worlds
on their new on the Devastator and then and then switching back
and forth between that and ads for the Devastator in the line only grows
as it like it's not a deterrent.
It it feels there's almost like no chance that one of those writers
like isn't from the Tri-State area and when you know, it's like
it's so weird how the kind of cultural on trails of Action Park, like
Judd Apatow tweeted that the screaming that Steve Carell makes
when he gets like waxed in 40 year old version was inspired by the screaming
he would hear when people were having their wounds treated the Alpine slideshed.
It's just like, whoa, wow.
It's like wild and crazy. Yeah.
Like like you have to imagine.
I love the thing that is amazing about Action Park is this thing
that really shaped just like shaped this generation of kids
from the Tri-State area in no small way, like show them how the world works
or doesn't work, like traumatize them, like, you know,
push them to their limits, maybe build their confidence, did all these formative,
better or worse things to millions and millions of kids.
And many of them, like they don't really it doesn't never comes up.
And I think that's why once Action Park kind of enters the cultural melew,
it kind of has these legs because all these people are like, oh, yeah, that
I absolutely went there and that, you know, I here's a scar.
Like I met I met I met Cory Booker, the senator from I met Cory Booker.
And he tweets about Action Park every once in a while.
And I mentioned it to him and he just starts lifting up his pant leg
and showing me his scars from like the Alpine slide.
Like, it's just like millions and millions of people like have these experiences.
And it's just kind of like this hidden trauma in the Tri-State area.
Well, and there's that that ball, the the I forget the man and ball and ball.
Yeah, that they that the metal ball that someone got inside and rolled downhill
and rolled onto the high glass ball, fiberglass, excuse me.
I watched that that 80s romantic comedy a few weeks ago.
Take me home tonight.
And that is a major plot point in that movie, a fiberglass ball
that rolls out of control, that is an act of bravery for someone to get into.
And I would you have gotten in the.
Yeah. Would you have gotten in the man in the ball in the ball, Jason?
I think even I have my limits.
The man in the ball.
Come on, Jason, get in the ball.
The man in the ball in the ball.
You know what?
I don't want to.
That's your cool.
I'm tearing the highway that cuts through the park.
What?
Even just hearing people talk about a 94, like not 95.
The major road you always hear about I-95 going through New Jersey.
And it's like, wait, what?
There's a 94 like that.
That seemed off to me.
That made me uneasy.
Just like, yeah.
So so so about that.
So we're 94 kind of cut the park in half.
He had Waterworld on one side.
That's all the water side in Motorworld on the other.
That's like the speed boats and the racing cars and whatnot.
And in order to get between them, they had this real rickety,
shady monorail type thing.
They'd be like sitting on a bench and would take you over the highway.
And Gather told us a story that didn't end up in the movie when a friend of his
or maybe it was him, I can't recall, was on that thing and it broke down.
It broke down over the road and caught on fire.
And either his friend or somebody had to jump down
like into the middle of the busy highway because their monorail car was on fire
as they're trying to go between Waterworld and Motorworld.
So that's Action Park.
And that wasn't in the movie.
That was not in the movie.
That was on the cutting room floor.
I just give you guys a sense.
I just want to give anybody a sense that they don't know anything about this
or anything about the movie.
That story is not in the movie.
That is not even a significant enough event to make it.
Also, the the Action Park Gladiator Challenge.
You want to talk about IP rip offs.
That was a rip off.
That was not licensed.
Gladiators rip off where guests could just joust
large, jacked up to name Turbo.
They just hire like this was kind of that peak steroid bodybuilder, like,
you know, WWF below and up era.
And Action Park was a huge hangout for like steroid freaks and bodybuilders.
So many of the stories, especially the ones involving fights from the security
guards, involved just like jacked bodybuilders.
And so they hired all these like local jacked up steroidal dudes,
gave them names like Turbo and Nitro.
And then you as a patron at the park could just joust them and fight them.
And they got legal action was pushed against them from the actual
American Gladiators for just like the straight, straight IP rip off of that.
My this is I think is my favorite thing that's there.
And I found this this is from a newspaper at the time promoting it.
The idea is a spinoff of television's American Gladiators.
Though there is no connection with the popular show.
Well, I don't know.
But is it spin off?
There's another blank off word you might use might be a more.
Are you allowed to just do that?
Are we allowed to like spin things out?
Italy, Italy, a movie land.
I guess you could say the park we just did at our European
trip spun a lot of different things off.
They're full of great spin offs.
Yes. Yeah.
And then a couple of paragraphs later,
the Gladiators attraction is run by Michael and Vince Mancuso,
former bodybuilders.
We end up being a former bodybuilder.
Like that's not a like like you can build your body any time.
There's no license that's revoked.
What happened?
Why aren't they bodybuilders anymore?
Straining orders or
any number of bannings?
You can do this just not in New Jersey.
Go, you got to go over the state line if you want to lift the weight.
It feels like you could just like go in in the morning and be like,
hey, I got a couple strong guys.
Can we have guests fight them tonight?
And you'd be like, yeah, Jean would be like, fine.
OK, which part of the park?
Sometimes they would almost you get the feeling like they're almost asking for
for like these big fights and may lays like fights would happen nonstop.
Like the security guards are so to just like every day, just fights everywhere.
You let people stand up in the middle of the Colorado River
ride after the rafts bump into each other and just like have at it.
But one of the biggest fights occurred.
So a brief period, like in the early days of paintball,
action park, got some paintball guns and thought this would be a good attraction.
So they decided to orchestrate.
Now, they had a lot of guests coming in from the city, meaning like New York.
So they decided to orchestrate this year, Queens versus Brooklyn
or Queens versus Bronx paintball match.
So anybody coming in from Queens is on one team.
Anybody coming in from like Bronx or Brooklyn is on number two, another team.
And it was just like minutes before the pistol weapon started and the fights.
And like it just became this like all out like fight, like blood
everywhere kind of thing.
And was this like published, like was this in the paper the next day?
Or is this just sort of a story people told?
It was. Yeah, this kind of stuff happened.
I mean, it got reported. It was widely reported.
You know, we spoke to in the movie, a former Vernon newspaper editor
who was, you know, she she dared report
honestly about the park and kind of suffered the consequences,
which you kind of go into in the in the movie.
Here's another good story about Jean, I think it sort of builds off of one in the movie.
We very briefly have a security guard tell us
that he had heard that Jean kept a Mac 10 machine gun in his desk.
The full story is that he actually broke into Jean's office
in order to look for this gun with the idea that he would like
shoot some cans and play around with it and have a good time with this machine gun.
The idea being that Jean saw the gun had been taken or was missing.
He wouldn't report it because it's an illegal gun.
What can you do about it?
Oh, when he got to the office, the gun was not there.
And I only found out a couple of weeks ago, speaking to another former employee,
why the gun was not there.
That former the other employee basically told me that he had the exact same idea
just before this dude had actually broken into Jean's office,
found the gun, shot up a bunch of cans, like had a good time,
stole a bunch of jeans ammo, and he's pretty sure one of the guards
who broke in with him stole the gun.
And that's why it wasn't there.
So so plenty of people were going after Jean's gun.
And his doors are locked.
Yeah, everybody knew.
And she'd also had a had a panic button in his desk and nobody knew what it went to.
It didn't go to the local police.
Like nobody knew where this panic went to.
Local toughs, his Beagle Boy, jeans, Beagle Boys, former bodybuilders
to the Knights of Columbus Club.
You know what I mean?
I would pay money to know what that panic button went to.
I would. That's like a mystery that I'm going to dedicate a couple of years
to solving, I think.
I'm sure people, psychologists or something have done this.
And I'm fascinated by in general human beings behavior, because there has to be
some cognitive dissonance when you hear like, oh, there was a giant fight
or there was a man firing a machine gun off at Action Park last night.
And then you then you go, oh, I would like to go.
I'd like to go.
Is it because I think in your head, you go like, oh, nothing's going to happen to me.
And like, it's going to be fine.
And I'm fascinated by you could probably apply this to covid.
You can apply this to a range of different topics.
But I am fascinated that this only all these stories made this more popular.
Yes. That's that's crazy to me, because I was
I've never been again, I've never been like that.
But I think now, especially you would hear all these stories
and there would be this could never exist now.
The uproar, the articles like it would be shut down in two seconds.
And I do think more people would be like, oh, my God, that sounds crazy.
There's gladiator unlicensed gladiator fights happening.
I thought the real turbo.
It's not the real.
Oh, yeah.
But I think it's interesting to say that, because I think like,
so you yourself would be like, I just was a death trap.
I'm not going anywhere near that.
So the place became self selective so that like no good boys were going there.
It was only bad boys.
It was a park just like full to the brim of bad boys who were going there.
And then like what happens when you have a park that's nothing but bad boys?
That's actually right.
Well, now it would be bad boys and vlogger like influence, like, you know,
people going to get stuff on camera.
Right.
Oh, yeah. Can I get an incident?
Yes. And the two million views that will follow if I catch one.
Oh, they're just going to go today.
They go there without a mask just for like the clicks on their TikTok or something
like the libs or something.
I don't know. The park is still open and it's actually kind of a cool place now.
Mountain Creek, you know, a lot of the some of the old rides are still there.
But like they're, you know, modified a little like the Colorado River ride.
You have to wear like a lacrosse style face mask
because so many people were smashing their faces against this cave.
That that ride, by the way, super important in the history of fake rock,
I will say, Colorado arrived.
So it was so they were really early to gun night,
which is one of the fake rock materials, basically get like a hose
and you spray this stuff and when it dries it onto like a wireframe
and it becomes rock.
And they were, I think, very likely the very first water park
to use gun night in like any capacity.
And so Gene himself was like super obsessed with this
and would just spray shit building these massive like rides.
And so he was really intimately involved with the construction
of most of these rides.
We talked about in the movie, but oftentimes these rides ideas
to come in and be somewhat tame.
And then he get his hands on them and he'd like plus them up
in his own weird way and make them just kind of truly insane.
So the Colorado River ride was initially going to be something like a lazy river,
like a gentle day with your family on a raft kind of ride.
And he wanted during construction to be plus up into a class
for rapid simulation like the real Colorado River.
And he didn't want any lifeguards on the ride because he said
the real Colorado River doesn't have lifeguards, which I love.
And so that was so these rides that in Roaring Springs,
it was just this massive area.
So that whole area was called is called, I think the whole area
is called Roaring Springs, but they was built in like 1984.
And it was just like this gigantic gun night installation
that kind of trying to create this like old timey mountain rocky
swimming hole feel super important in the history of fake rock.
Because maybe up until that point, water slides were just
industrial looking tubes.
And the idea like what makes Typhoon Lagoon special
or any other wealthy water park is is some environment.
And maybe it was I was I guess with it emulating the real Colorado River,
it is the maybe the first steam just water slide potentially.
Well, or not slide, but whatever it is, water attraction.
Yeah. Other than River Country, which opened, I think 72, the first water parks.
I mean, like what and wild was and most water parks are like a couple of towers
in the middle of a parking lot.
You know, they're they're just like, we're going to build some slides
and you're not really immersed in this environment anyway.
What made Action Park kind of interesting from an environmental perspective
was it was built on the side of a mountain and a wooden mountain of that.
So it felt very natural and very like serene.
But it would also use the slope of the mountain for the for the slides.
So instead of modeling, like maybe we here's what the exact angle of this
right should be for maximum effect and safety.
It would literally be just whatever the slope of the mountain is.
That's what we're going to use.
And that that's how like most of the park was built. Wow.
And it used just the real bodies of water that were there in some cases,
which was a true shock to the system for people to just slash down and hit real
like chillingly cold water, chillingly cold water.
And it was shaded natural water, too.
So those areas and that area, that's where like the Tarzan swing was.
And Cannonball Falls, that was open until like two years ago.
So that's stuff you could still do until pretty recently. Yeah.
Well, it's a safe with no restrictions, essentially.
Yeah. Well, I mean, back then they were just like throwing kids off.
Well, OK, Tarzan swing is not a ride that's like innately dangerous.
Unless you get a lot of people like slip and lose a hold of the handle
and like hit their head against the platform, they're jumping off.
What that would happen all the time.
But like in theory, you're like on a rope and you're swinging into a pool of water.
If you do it safely, you're fine.
The real thing that made Tarzan swing so notorious was just like the atmosphere
because like 100 people from New Jersey are looking at you and just taunting you
and making fun of you and screaming at you.
And so even if you weren't like a big enough kid to go on,
like the speedboats or the looping water slide,
you could still probably go into Tarzan swing
and still get like a taste of what this park was all about.
And I think that's why Tarzan swing is so infamous and kind of lives on so much
in the imagination because everybody could go into Tarzan's way,
not just like the bigger kids.
Yeah. I mean, they had stuff like that at River Country.
But it was a simulation of the old swimmin hole.
You know, there are plenty of lakes and ponds that do have a rope swing,
you know, in the northeast that do have that kind of rope swing
that you can go into a body of water, a varying coldness.
And River Country was like, you know,
non chlorinated famously like fed from the waterways around Disney.
And they had rope swings and everything.
But it's Florida.
It's Orlando. That water is like bathwater.
You know, it's just constantly cooking, you know.
So my this is like in my blood, my my mom actually grew up
on an old timey swimming hole water park.
So that's like so she that was like her upbringing in the Ozarks in Missouri.
She grew up living and working on one of those kind of like swimming hole
with the Tarzan Swing Water slide water park.
And, you know, that's all there was until the late 70s
when like Schlitterbahn Action Park opened and tried to kind of commoditize
these really like naturally occurring organic like places.
That's what it was. Yeah. Yeah.
And I mean, River Country was open.
I think it was 76, like two years before Action Park.
And obviously a much bigger budget, much more imagineered.
But you see the way the slides look and they're pretty small at that point.
And you see like this is what fiberglass like slides.
This is what it looks like.
And it does not look like that at Action Park.
No, no. And they would and it would test things.
I mean, every like they would test things in a way that you knew it was safe
by time, because it was Disney, you know, Disney had decades
of experience making rides and like testing rides.
Action Park's testing process was let's send some dummies down
and hope they're not decapitated.
And if they're not decapitated, we'll wave hundred dollar bills in there
and then send employees down and then we'll work out the kinks that way.
That was how they would test rides.
And if somebody corrected me, though, only the older kids were given $100.
There's more. They've got more bodies.
They're taller. So you give them more money.
What's not clear about that?
Yes.
Can you imagine?
Yeah, that loop, I'm sorry.
What were you saying, Mike?
No, I was going to say if you were saying about the loop,
I was just thinking about being this tall and going on that loop.
And it would just I would come out twisted into a cartoon.
That's like I would be all wrapped up like a present compacted.
It hurt.
Yeah.
I'm trying to remember in the movie, I was just going to say,
was there stuff, was there anything Gene was like, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, too far?
No, he was probably the most the most like to the right of the curve
of anybody at the park, you know, so everybody under him
was like trying to temper his instincts to be like, hey, maybe we shouldn't do this.
And he was the guy was like, oh, we're just going to do it.
It's going to be great.
It's going to be so much fun.
And that was his thing.
And it's such an interesting that's why his character is so interesting
because he he was this, you know, fairly well off like Wall Street outcast
who just like really immersed himself into like playing rollercoaster
tycoon and like coming up with these novel ideas.
It's something it's something strange about that.
So is it literally true that the the loop, because the it's
it's said somewhere in the documentary that the cannonball loop
looks like somebody just did it as a doodle on a napkin and then that was built.
And that was what happened, right?
Like like Gene drew one of the slides loops and then it and then it happened,
which because it just that's what's so striking.
I remember when I first saw it, you know, as some thumbnail to click on,
it seemed fake. It looks like an onion.
Like it's like it looks Photoshop the the actual photo of the slide in reality.
It looks like it's in scratchy land.
It looks like something like The end of Simpsons or like life is hell.
Back in the day, it was Gene himself who drew basically a circle and a cocktail
napkin. And the only thing that comes to mind, it's like in the Hudson
Cripple proxy, it's like a circle napkin.
It's like, you know, for kids, what else would go wrong?
That's probably the most upsetting thing in the documentary is the phrase
teeth pad in the loop.
Second, the only other competition might be pond filled with gasoline and snakes.
Yeah. And dead fish, too.
And dead fish.
But they had to put a pad in the loop to cushion people.
But then people kept coming out with cuts and abrasions.
And then they looked at the pad.
It was it was covered with loose teeth.
Yes. And there is like a Lovecraftian monster.
So you go through it and the teeth would just like eat into you,
which is nightmare fuel. Just terrifying.
It's the worst place in the world.
The top of that loop is the literal worst spot you can be.
Scientists have studied it for years trying to understand this little spot.
It didn't exist until 1978.
And being an employee there, like the stuff you would have to do.
So the Alpine slide, which it's widely thought to be like a concrete
or cement track, but it's actually mostly made of asbestos,
was just like a loose track built into the side of a mountain.
And you take this cart and you go to the top on a ski lift.
And as we talk about in the movie, it was a pretty regular practice
for people to knock their carts off their ski lift and attempt
to hit people below them as like a sick game of target practice.
Because why not?
But you make it to the top and you'd be greeted with like warning signs
and photos showing you wounds and like gory bloody bodies,
like saying, like, keep your hands inside the track.
Like this is serious.
Well, in the movie, we show like a quick shot of a newspaper article
about this girl who got her finger cut off because she,
I guess, didn't keep her hands inside the inside the track.
The girl who lost her finger wrote me after the movie came out
thrilled because she's like, nobody believes me that I lost this on a ride.
I can't find any documentation.
And she sent me a video of her fingerless hand, just like like she told me.
She got a nine thousand dollar payout for that.
But she was she was like super excited to have her missing finger
or make a cameo in the movie. Very strange.
The Alpine slide to put them to Twitter afterwards, by the way,
if you guys want to the video of the finger video.
Yeah, she said I could share it if you guys want the bigger
if the audience demands it.
Yeah, if the audience, we're going to blur it.
I think we're going to blur it and put a bar on it.
We're too scared.
Yeah, I want to mention Action Point,
the Johnny Knoxville movie inspired by Action Park.
So they kind of replicated the Alpine slide in that movie.
And first off, Johnny Knoxville said
making that movie was the most injured he ever got.
And the Alpine's the story goes that like on the Alpine slide, he flew off it,
landed on his face, went to the hospital.
They checked him out, gave him the OK to go home.
He went home, blew his nose and his left eye popped out of his head.
So even the recreation of the Alpine slide was
was like dropping people.
The worst damage ever done to Johnny Knoxville.
Yeah, a man who gets damaged every point of Johnny Knoxville.
Oh, my. He got messed up making that movie like really.
He's and then I saw some article where he detailed some of that and said,
like, and it wasn't worth it because the movie didn't do good.
It didn't do.
But I think I didn't get hurt at all.
One thing that's odd to me in general about the places
where people got injured and in fact killed,
you know, Action Park did not invent the Alpine slide.
Like there's an Alpine slide in Big Bear that I've done a couple times.
And I'm I'm a pussy and I did it.
And so if that tells you like and I had fun,
I wasn't you could tell how if you just throttled it the whole time
and were a little, you know, play it a little fast and loose
with it could be dangerous.
And I was trying to break a lot.
But like it in and of itself isn't this crazy idea.
It's just like the way they did it and the negligent way, which similar to
I was just going to say the same thing about wave pools.
It's funny. Wave pools in the world.
But there's only one that kept like drowning people.
Yeah. So compared to this,
you you probably at some point in your life have had an automobile.
That automobile in itself is not dangerous.
But if you remove the brakes, got drunk and tried to smash into the person
ahead of you, it would be a very dangerous.
Yeah. And that's kind of what the Action Park Alpine slide.
That's a very good way to break it down. Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, I don't you also explain how it's you had to like know all the curves.
You had to like know it as if you'd done a hundred runs before you could.
I just imagine it's even cool runnings where he's like in the bathtub,
memorizing and studying like all the twists and curves he's got to do.
It literally is the the there are three tracks.
And one of them was the expert track, they called it.
And that was like that was extreme.
That was the one where people just constantly flown off of that.
Like you have to be crazy to go on that thing.
And that was one where if you went at full speed, you were going to fly off.
You just were going to fly off.
And this gets really dicey because part of the duties of the employees
was when it rained, I think it was super dangerous when it rained.
So it was your job.
If you're an employee, they didn't want to wait toward like the dry naturally.
That's like downtime.
You know, so if you're an employee, it'd be your job to dry it off
by taking an Alpine slide cart down the wet Alpine slide with towels
dragging behind it, sopping up rain.
And you weren't supposed to break while you were doing this,
because for some reason or another, the act of breaking was like super
dangerous on the wet surface.
So you had to go down it without using a break with towels behind you.
And I spoke to somebody who was doing this when the person behind them,
their thing got messed up or they know what it was, was they couldn't resist
the urge to break because every fiber of your body is telling you to break
when you do that. So they break.
A person behind them ran over them, just like over them on the Alpine slide.
These are sending like four kids at a time down with towels.
Sopping up a wet Alpine slide.
So she's Seth, when you go on like the Matterhorn at Disneyland,
do you just like yawn or you just like as you went to this place
as a child, like it reset your whole danger level?
I mean, yeah, you know, yeah, yeah.
Right. Like Matterhorn.
Come on, guys. Yeti is not even real.
You know, right.
Like there would have been a real like like there would have been a real animal
at Action Park that was stuck inside of the ride that would claw you.
Dude, that would be
one of you guys is from Jerry. Jason, you're from Jersey.
Yeah. Oh, I yeah.
From outside of Philadelphia, but spent a lot of time in Jersey. Yeah.
Do you know about that?
Like drive through Safari attraction built around this time in Jersey
that they like had lions and stuff, but they abandoned it.
And then like the lions and like tigers took over this place.
Do you know about this thing?
It's hard to say if I know about it, because I think there's more than one.
I mean, Six Flags.
I did the great adventure.
My family would do the you drive your minivan through the Safari
and don't put the windows down and also take the antenna off
because the monkeys might take it if you don't. Yeah.
I was like a Jersey thing. Drive through.
So that's like a big Jersey thing.
And in recent years, they had a big like, you know, Six Flags.
They had an official driver off road vehicle that would take you through this park
in times of covid.
They reopened it for like, and, you know, the park's not open yet,
but you can drive through the Safari again.
So I don't know what safety measures they've taken, but,
you know, it might be it might be on the rise again
as drive through entertainment catches on.
Yeah. In early days of Action Park,
when they were still figuring out what it was going to be,
the Alpine side was the first ride they had before was like any water
size about they had like a roller skating rink.
And I think they actually had a petting zoo and they had like lions and stuff.
So they were they were definitely like they weren't going to put a robot yeti
and they were like everything was going to be real there.
Everything was going to be.
Gene was looking for a real yeti.
He went out on an expedition.
He was going to find the Jersey Devil.
The Jersey Devil was going to be the the main draw.
Gene would have gone around Disneyland and been like gone to Mr.
Toad and been like, remove this track, let him drive the real car
through the ride. What the fuck is this?
Like and then there's every ride.
I assume he would have built pitchforks.
People can reach up and grab them.
Ram them into the other vehicle.
I actually go into hell.
Yeah, let's summon up some demons in here for real.
Let's get a look at a crooked priest.
I got to say I got a guy. I got a guy.
Got a Ouija board over here, guys. Let's do this.
Yeah, let's.
It's not the mission. So turn it up to 400 degrees.
Get it up and up and down.
Action Park is the real life version of the Jurassic Park line
about like if the Pirates of the Caribbean breaks down, the pirates
don't eat the tourists like if the ice breaks down, you will.
You will get destroyed.
There's like no chance Michael Crichton didn't go to action park, right?
Like Westworld and Jurassic Park, like like half of the Michael Crichton
cannon is theme parks that go raw.
Like he went to action park, right?
Huh? That's I mean, yeah, like he was.
Yeah, he was probably born in what, the 40s or 50s?
He would have been a little older, maybe.
This was all born from this timeline.
Might not be right because Westworld is maybe up.
But I like to imagine that it was his entire body work was born from
doing the Tarzan swing and a bunch of Jersey meatheads yelling,
you fucking pussy.
And he splashed hard and everybody booed him and made fun of him.
And he's like, I'll show you.
I'll become one of the great authors of the century.
Thirty eight year old man doing the Tarzan swing.
Getting yelled at.
The first scene is biopic is him wiping out a Tarzan swing
and it's just trying to get us come up.
And the thing nobody talks about about action park,
this is going to be kind of gross, is so OK.
It became like super popular super quickly.
They started running TV ads and then they got up to 15000 people on a busy day,
like a million people a year.
And it was this regional park and they didn't have enough bathrooms.
So there was like a multi-year period in which they just didn't have
the infrastructure to deal with all of the waste.
And so people were just like shitting everywhere.
So I had a former employee tell me they were like, clean out the grottoes
and the caves and everywhere you look, they just be like shit like everywhere.
And that was like a big job for all the teenagers.
But they like like hosing down the Alpine slide.
It really disgusting.
Eventually, they added more bathrooms.
That's good. Eventually.
The food. It's like a roller coaster tycoon when you don't have enough bathrooms.
It's like weird things start to happen. It's just like that.
Right.
Yeah. He sits on the coaster.
Like it doesn't all the footage you have of a guy manning a grill or manning.
It looks disgusting.
Like I love eating garbage, but the food cooking footage is so unpleasant.
And it's crazy that like,
you know, the I always how do you pronounce his name again?
The head of the hill, the hill, the hill
that he like, like Silvio or Polly Walnuts was obsessed
with community festival like that was another odd layer of him is that like he
loved throw it the German festival, Polish festival, Irish festival
and putting on the later hose and putting on the later hose.
And like that was such a weird detail about this guy.
Yeah, actually, it was kind of
historically significant some of the things he did in that regard.
They opened up one of the first microbreweries in the country and they'll
claim they kind of kick started the microbrewery, whatever.
But he went to Germany and he had an entire brewery dismantled and shipped
to New Jersey, including the Brewmaster.
They would claim that everything but the water came from Germany.
And according to the book put out just a couple of months ago by the owner's son,
the Brewmaster they brought in had previously been Hitler's personal Brewmaster.
That too.
I think if this part couldn't be any more cursed,
it's just they should have just leaned into like it's a crazy extreme place.
And yeah, Hitler's Brewmaster.
And you think that's a that's a clever name.
And they'll say, no, it isn't.
It's descriptive.
It is true.
Like, yeah, how old is Hitler's Brewmaster?
He was like an old dude when he came in.
Everybody was like, he was like the old guy by that point.
He's got to make some like that.
Those beers can't like the pod.
They can't like sting and bubble too much because it'll like nip at that stash.
It's he probably had to go a little mellower.
That's fair.
I've used this joke, I think, on the show before, but it's like Emperor.
I assume is Hitler's Brewmaster was like
Emperor Palpatine, an exegol and the last Star Wars movie, the crane kind of like
just keeping him alive because he needs to brew more beer and making beer with
lightning. That scene.
Yes, that scene that had to have been somebody who like just rode Forbidden
Journey and was like, that's what that's what moves the Emperor like a cuckoo arm,
whatever it's called. Like, you know, that's it.
Right.
Yes.
So JJ Abrams was interested in the cuckoo arm technology and he was like, we're
going to put a arm attached to the cuckoo arm.
Totally cuckoo arm, isn't it?
Well, I think we're like the corner of the DVD box of Prometheus.
I saw like a Giger drawing just out of the corner of the eye.
And it's like, oh, that's yeah, that's good.
That's cool.
You're based on my vague memory of this.
Based on the thing, the DVD box.
What rights would you have, guys, would you guys have gone on, like actually got
any of them? That's what I was thinking about the whole time.
I the Tarzan swing I might do
now as a kid, I would have freaked out because I was freaked out of that high
dive as a kid.
I could barely go off the regular diving board.
Yeah, I could not dive at all
as a kid.
Now I might do it.
Alpine slide, the easy, whatever the safest version I might have tried, but that's
still I don't know. Yeah, I mean, yeah, I mean, that one's dangerous.
I like the idea of the Colorado River and maybe today I would do whatever version
of it there is, but back then it seems kind of deceptively.
I really like that aspect.
You can choose your own adventure, that there's different paths.
I think like that is a water slide or water attraction asset is cool.
And that would make me want.
But I also feel like it might just like
I might just slam my head on those innovative fake rocks.
Yeah, yeah, you don't really get to choose like physics chooses for you.
Typically, the Tarzan one, I think.
Now, you know, look, is a needy ass performer.
I think I would enjoy being on the stage of the Tarzan swing.
I would enjoy the audience.
I would do something impressive, but I would I would maybe enjoy yelling at people.
And maybe I wouldn't even go off.
Maybe I just go up there and taunt everybody and then get them to all boo me
because I also like wrestling so much.
I would feel like I would.
That's a good deal.
You would have been the heel turn.
Yeah, the Tarzan swing.
You would have had your persona like, oh, it's that guy again.
I just stands there and holds up the line.
Right.
And making fun of people out there.
And then I got like ready to go.
I pretend I'm going to do it.
And then I turn around and then everyone booze me and I relish.
I then when you go to the Gladiator experience,
everybody is excited that turbo gets the whoop you because it's like, oh, they got
that that wimp from earlier. I get my.
Yeah, I remember him.
He held up the line.
I don't think I would.
You know, it seems maybe safe ish.
It correct you.
You might know more than me, Seth.
But for the person playing more than the employee, the battle tanks sort of seem
like I would love to do that.
But that was is there a way that I'm forgetting that it would hurt me?
No.
Well, unless the OK, sometimes the greats
that like would close that would keep the balls from hitting you in the face.
Wouldn't close and be able to get pelted in the face.
We did a drive in screening of the movie
in Brooklyn like a couple of weeks ago right before it opened before it was
released and we had a dude bring us a bunch of vintage action park ride vehicles,
including a battle tank.
So I got to like get inside of one.
And that was like I could feel the ghost, man.
That was that was it for me.
That was it.
Getting inside that tank. Pretty cool.
I was like, I'm home.
We talk a lot about owning pieces of the park.
Would you want to own one of the battle tanks and display it proudly?
Oh, there's like a weird kind of underground collector.
You know, it's not it's not like the,
you know, the Disneyland collector scene like at the Van Eden Gallery or anything.
But there's people who collect old action park ride vehicles because something
strange happened that when the park shut down,
I'm going to get my timeline and my story mixed up here.
So like, don't scream at me.
But this one dude like bought up all of the Motor World ride vehicles.
So the speedboats, the Lola cars, which were the racing cars, the tanks.
And they sat in this like storage container in Vernon for like 20 years or so
until I want to say 2015, he just sold them all at once.
So just a couple of years ago,
all these collectors started getting their hands on all of these rides.
So I've been in touch with like a half
dozen people who have battle tanks, so speedboats, Lola cars.
And so we had a couple come to the screening.
It was amazing. Just wild stuff.
Do these fetch a lot of money on an aftermarket?
I assume they fetch a lot of money.
But is it how how crazy does it get?
Do you know?
I think it's I think it's closer to what the value of that would be as like a 40
year old speedboat than like as a nostalgia item.
You know, I don't think I think it's like a couple of thousand bucks.
But I think you can get them to work is what's cool.
You know, like Disney, you're buying like a space mountain car.
You can't actually ride that if you're
buying like an action park battle tank and you get a fixed up, you can actually
ride that. I think that's what makes it cool.
Now I'm afraid I'm going to see one of those coming down my street.
Firing at people who voted for whoever they didn't vote for.
With like on fire tennis balls.
It's just Leno.
Oh, in our area. Yeah, yeah.
He's got an airplane hanger full of all the action
park ride vehicles, I'm sure.
Oh, my God.
I remember the East Coast equivalent of Jay Leno is just collects this stuff.
Yeah. We speaking of vehicles.
Super speed boats.
I have the Wikipedia in front of me.
The super speed boats were set up in a small pond known by Park staff
to be heavily infested with snakes.
Yes. Yeah. Yes.
Well, it's true. Good.
Nobody died on that ride, at least.
So no one died.
But that's a big moment in the documentary where the woman,
the woman who was a lifeguard talks about how one speedboat did not slow down,
went on top of the other speedboat.
And that's where the reference she was very concerned that these
person underneath was going to be decapitated.
And imagine you just got a little cut, a little.
Well, the propeller, the motor was cutting into their neck
and she was worried the hair, like whatever mullet this guy had,
because, you know, the era was going to get pulled up into this thing
and get like scalped or something.
But that that ride was was nuts.
And that position we talked about briefly in the movie,
but working being a lifeguard on that ride was the worst job.
That was like you're being punished.
Nobody likes you.
You're not connected.
You're like not part of the cool kid clique.
You're the lifeguard on the speedboats, because if you had to pull somebody out,
you're diving into a pond just like full of snakes and oil, just like snakes and oil.
All right. So do we know what was
do we know what has like changed like in the local government
now there that would prevent snakes and oil being in a pond
that people would have to go in?
I honestly feel like there's no law in the books against that.
So, you know, I feel like I don't think there's a law about that.
So you could probably get away with that.
By the way, so it's snakes and oil is what evil Ringo Starr wishes.
Snakes and oil, everyone.
It's oil.
Oil. They got a man from the snake, oil salesman.
I don't know. There's something.
Oh, yeah, not to say, oh, it's no, it's not.
You misheard me. It's not snake oil in the water.
It's snake and oil.
Snake, oil sales.
The oil is not from the guy who filled this.
Yeah, we filled the pond up with the wrong stuff, guys. Sorry.
That was the big like revelation for me in the documentary,
because I think I first heard about it on the best show.
You're in Tom Sharpling talk about Traction Park and the looping
waterslide and and all the stories about that.
But I it didn't dawn on me that like, oh, the town,
not only like it wasn't that they ignored it, like they they full on
like tolerated it and it brought a bunch of money into the town.
Yes. Yes.
Imagine like this parks been open, not just the park, but the ski resort
prior to that have been open for 15 whatever years more than that
and just dominates the local economy.
You know, it's the biggest employer in town.
All the foot traffic, kind of a million people a year just like shopping
at your stores, like paying your tolls, whatever it's going to be.
What do you do if that shuts down?
Like, what do you do?
And it's like it's like the, you know, the factory leaving town
is what it'd be like.
So that resulted in, I think, a very high level of risk tolerance,
we'll say, from the town for what the park had to offer.
It's so funny that it wasn't just like, well, we like having a park here.
Just take the snakes and oil out of the water.
Like, just make a few changes.
Why not?
You think the very I don't think it's a kind of park where without.
OK, so now it's open under a different name and they got rid of most of the rides.
But at its peak, it was the they claimed it was the largest water park in the world.
And more than 75 rides and attractions.
That's like a lot of stuff.
And the vast majority of them were, I think, what Ralph Nader
would have called like unsafe at any speed.
Like, there's no fixing that.
There's no way to like, we'll just pay attention and this will be safe.
Like there's something like innately flawed with the design or the concept of it
that was going to get people hurt.
You couldn't just be like, we're going to pay a little bit more attention now.
It was messy. Right.
Like have more than half the rides were like unfixable.
It would be like, well, we can't plus up the ride
where we just hand you a bag of rocks and you sink to the bottom of a 30 foot pool.
We're plusing up this ride by not killing it.
Like it was a really it was a wild place after the park was shut down in 96.
And the purchase in 98 by Intra West, which owns like Whistler Mountain.
They mostly bought it for the ski resort.
They kept the Alpine slide open for one year.
And they forced you to wear a helmet and sign a waiver.
And I think that that only lasted one year in that form.
I think they realized like either.
Yeah, this is too much.
Or that defeats the whole spirit of the Alpine slide.
Maybe I don't know.
It's also so crazy that, OK, so the first death occurs in 1980, 1981,
the first of six all told, and then it's not closed till 96.
And that has nothing to do with it.
They just ran out of money. Nothing.
Yeah. And if you ask like, yeah.
And I think the death count, which is, you know, single digits,
I don't really think that was justice to how incredibly dangerous the park was.
I think it's the injuries and like there should have been many, many more deaths.
There just should have been on any given day.
The Alpine slide alone would injure hundreds of people a day.
One ride, one day, triple digit injuries every single day, day in and day out.
And I think that to me is a lot more astonishing than than the number of deaths.
I think it's crazy in with the horrible things in our world with Covid-19
and with in mass shootings and stuff that people find comfort in.
Oh, well, there was only this many deaths.
Don't worry. There were injuries or they didn't die.
You know, that's still horrible.
Like people are scarred, scarred physically, mentally.
But you kind of gloss over injuries in general.
Yeah, we don't want to minimize that.
And, you know, I think that was that was like sort of the purpose of our movie was,
you know, Action Park has become this like urban legend and to some degree a joke
because it's so surreal and absurd that it exists.
I like the only response your body can make after reading about Action
Park is to laugh because it kind of short circuits your brain a little
like the mere existence of it.
And one of the big purposes, the goals of our movie was to kind of go beyond
that a little and figure out like what was the actual cost here?
What was the toll?
What stories are being kind of like swept under the rug in service
of this myth and service of this legend?
And as you saw in the movie, we spoke to the family of a kid
who was killed there, who kind of walked us through the beat
by beats of like what happened to them after their son died, like what went wrong
and then how the park responded to it?
That's kind of horrifying.
Like, it's very scary. Yeah.
Yeah. That's not to put a damper on the funnies.
Well, that's what's weird is what you have to do.
And like, like, so was that tough in the documentary to
make that turn and have that balance?
I mean, it became the whole purpose of the movie was this really sudden turn
that we want to do. And it kind of think a lot of people by surprise.
And it's something I think people, you don't really see that much in movies, I'll say.
But it was it was kind of whiplashy by design
as, you know, as sort of response to the legend and myth that actually
also because like not to like over explain my own movie.
But I mean, say you are at Action Park and you're having like the best time
of your life and actually work with a place capable of giving you immense
thrills, immense joy, immense happiness, immense memories, immense all these good
things. The distance between that experience
and and getting seriously injured or even dying is like one second.
Like there is no foreshadowing.
There's no there's no telegraphing it. It just like happens suddenly.
And that was sort of the idea there was like, this is the most fun
you've had until the minute it's not is what Action Park was.
Yeah, right. Yeah, there was no because I yeah, if you were there,
the people that were there were probably not like us and not like like
nervous all time. They were like having fun and then something goes horribly,
horribly wrong.
And we're incredibly desensitized to it.
You know, unless you're actually seeing somebody get killed, you're you're very
likely going to see people get injured while you're at the park.
It just happens constantly.
Like when you take the Alpine slide ski lift up, the chances are really good.
You'd see somebody wipe out as you're going up, just like see somebody wipe out.
That would happen. And yeah, so that's what I was saying earlier.
I'm fascinated by human behavior like that.
And I think you can apply it to like Covid and masks and you can apply it to.
Are you telling me that Action Park is a metaphor for Covid?
Is that what you're telling me?
I first look, I don't I don't I don't make conclusions.
The listeners of our podcast do that. I don't tell them what to do.
Are you telling me that? Tell me what a metaphor is.
Just keep hearing this word.
This literary device. It's very fancy.
It's like a simile. It's very similar to a simile.
Are you telling me that a place, a place where the where the forces of fun
and freedom in air quotes are up against common sense and safety
is a metaphor for anything we're all experiencing today?
Is that what you're telling me?
I might be walking down the road, but I wouldn't tell you anything.
I'm walking down that road for sure.
But it is interesting because I think we all in general in our lives
have to do a lot of this ignoring stuff.
You can't have all this stuff in your head.
You'll be like this is just general, like whether it's, you know,
the chance of you, I don't know, getting in a car accident or something like this.
You just have to put all this stuff out of your mind.
But to see constant accidents and you're like, huh, OK,
I'm going to go on that ride now.
Choose to go to a hot spot, essentially of accidents and injury potential. Yeah.
That's like that's like a supercharged version of what I'm saying,
where you just have to sort of put out the fact that like something bad
is going to happen to all of us at some time.
But we just got to go on with life.
That's what's so interesting about Action Park is for people who aren't from the area,
this seems like this crazy, absurd, how could this possibly have existed thing
that people grew up there? It was so normal.
It was just so, so, so normal.
And that is what's so weird to me about it is I and I think
the whole city of New Jersey, I think, like is super into this movie
because it gives them this like validation, like, see how tough we are.
This is what we grew up with.
But it wasn't just that.
I mean, New Jersey was a weird New Jersey.
It was a weird place.
And even if you weren't from New Jersey, like just growing up in the 80s,
people were doing stupid stuff and like getting hurt and running around.
And today, everything about that seems so foreign and so absurd
because we have like cell phones now and kids aren't like nobody's outside.
Period now. But and just how normal this all was.
And it wasn't just like the injuries and what not at Action Park.
Working at Action Park, you're in this small cow town.
Suddenly becomes this major tourist destination.
A million people a year coming in and just the things that happen
when that many people come in and what you're exposed to.
So there's employees is going to get dark.
I'm sorry, guys. But so there's like employees who I spoke to,
like 15, 16 years old.
They're working the front gate.
There was an oil tanker like like upturned,
like an accident, like right outside the gates of the park.
And the cab got trapped underneath the tanker.
And they couldn't use the jaws of life to get the guy out
because it would have sparked and caused an explosion.
So these like teenage employers are watching this guy who just like
knows he's about to die and like how like what that does to you.
And now they laugh about it and they joke about it
because there's like really no other response.
The human body is just like capable of doing when faced with that
while still going on with your life, while still, you know, waking up
in the morning and like going through your life.
Right. Our brains do gymnastics a lot of times, either to just mask
like crazy trauma like that or just, you know, if it's just like
you're normally at a park where people are flying off the slide, you go, huh?
That guy got hurt really bad.
Here I go. And I think it's really.
Yeah, it's important because when we like joke about action park,
get there, put this really well in the movie.
But nobody's joking about it.
Who went there because they think this was good.
They're joking about it because that's the only response
the human brain is like capable of doing when something short circuits it like that.
Like what is like laughter from like an evolutionary perspective?
It's I just miss like narrowly escaping a saber to tiger.
You laugh about that's like what it is.
And I think that bit of like it is such a weird, strange type of laughter
that is sort of not really as common as like, you know,
designed comedy and things that are designed to make you laugh
or that kind of tap into that same instinct are.
But it's there and it's present and it's real.
And I think it's like it's so weird.
And that's what makes action like such an unshakable topic to me
is that it kind of elicits that sort of laughter response.
Well, it seems like a lot of the people in the documentary are
tacitly acknowledging the old adage about like
tragedy plus time is comedy.
Yes.
But then there are plenty of people in the documentary who it's just, well, no,
it's just tragedy plus time is just that it's just more tragedy.
I just keep thinking about the tragedy, you know,
tragedy plus time plus like a little bit of distance.
Like if it wasn't you or somebody super close to you, I think it's what it was.
Yeah. Yeah.
It's a weird place.
Well, the, you know, the Mulvahills have a comment on all this.
The the the son who wrote a book and kind of was
attempted to be front and center when they tried to do the park again.
And he's kind of kept the legend alive.
I think this is also from the Sports Illustrated article.
He says, as for the people who died,
I'm sure Dad has gone and looked for each and every one of them to say he's sorry.
All right. Yeah, sure.
Yeah, OK.
That's that settles that.
He certainly seemed like an apologetic man
in his day to day.
A client to participate.
And he's like, what if he's in heaven trying to sue these people more?
I'm suing you under heaven laws.
The you. Oh, oh.
So this wasn't a movie.
Oh, man, the stories that kind of just filled my inbox after the movie came out.
So we talk in a movie about how if you manage to sue, manage to win,
like Jean just wouldn't pay unless the US marshals literally collected the money.
A lawyer reached out to me who was like a client who had that happened to him.
And how they had to get the US marshals to show up.
But they had this big problem because the US marshals collected.
It literally went from like ticket booth to ticket booth, collecting cash
and put into a duffel bag.
When a duffel bag was the US marshal duffel bag
and they weren't allowed to hand over US marshal property.
So this lawyer had to like go window shopping until he found another duffel bag.
The stuff all this cash into and then take gets to the bank
and like try to deposit like half a million dollars or whatever in cash.
Wow.
Wow. Do you have enough?
You've given us a lot of stuff that's not in the movie.
But now that you're getting all these stories, do you have enough for like a follow up
as far as just a movie full of stories?
I mean, yeah, there's a movie full of stories, but what's the story?
You know, so, yeah, right.
It's at least supplemental material on a DVD or Blu Ray release.
Oh, man. If only we had like DVDs with supplemental material.
I would have had so much fun with this.
There was a lot.
I mean, it just seems like ever.
This is going to sound corny, but like everyone who went had a story.
Everybody who went had a story or like 10.
And like, yeah, right.
And it's so weird, like you look at like the Wikipedia page
and like the stories that kind of become the action park
lore and the actual canon and just like that's just like such a tip of the iceberg.
And most of those come from a couple like Weird New Jersey articles.
That's like patient zero, like ground zero for most of the action park.
Lore was like Weird New Jersey's coverage.
If you look at the citations on the wiki page, it's like 90 percent weird.
New Jersey stuff is like all it is.
And that's just talking to a couple of employees for those articles.
You talk to any employee, they have just as many stories.
And now after the movie came out, I'm like I was invited to these
secret Facebook groups that are all former action park employees.
And it's like a thousand people in them.
And it's just like gold, man. It's gold.
It's wild stuff. Yeah.
I you know, I have I was goofing a little bit on the Valencia
teens who run Six Flags Magic Mountain, but they look like saints and angels,
I think, compared to fairy level precision operating.
I mean, I don't think those Valencia teens next time I see them. Yeah.
And I don't want to bash the teens who work there.
I mean, they they were all put in the tough spot.
Yeah. And yeah, they were just living their lives.
They were coming of age. They were doing their thing.
I don't think anybody can like blame the 15 year old kid
for all the stuff that's going on around them.
It just becomes normal.
They partied, man. Those kids partied, by the way, like like they would regularly
just like show up to work three days in a row with the same shirt on either
sleeping at the park after a party, sleeping in some random condo
because like all the condos that surround the park, different people like access
to them, so they use them as like crash pads or just, you know,
partying all night and then like go to work the next day at like age 16.
Sleeping at the top of the cannonball loop.
And then it just hot boxing the entire loop.
Hot boxing the loop.
Just goes in the bottom of it and just fill it up with smoke.
And they already had to worry about the normal problems.
Jersey teens have to worry about cruising down Highway nine,
working on their cars, learning that they blew up the chicken man in Philly last night.
You know, that's Nebraska, not Jersey, I think.
But no, wait, no.
But that was way too much.
But also the tan and the hair.
I don't know. It was it was a strange place.
And it's really amazing speaking to the place people live there who live this,
who like grew up working there and how fond they all are of this place.
And you kind of some degree, I think it's like a little bit of Stockholm syndrome.
But to some degree, it's I think we all kind of take whatever we went through
and we internalize it and we make, you know, this is this is our childhood.
It's a weird place.
Yeah. Did did do we know did Springsteen or even Southside Johnny go to Action Park?
OK, I am sure that like like everybody did.
Like from this area, it was what you did.
It was what you did.
Like like Fallon mentioned on the show the other day, like I know that
like I know that Kimmel went there.
Everybody who grew up like Springsteen had to have gone there. Right.
Like there's no way older.
He's he's another little older.
So maybe not. But he was I mean, he was he was still like very
he's probably very popular by the time this open.
At least one member of the East Street band went there, I would bet.
At least one member.
We think it was.
It was it was a little I don't think it was a little Stephen.
I don't think was it Weinberg?
It doesn't seem like Max Weinberg seen either.
He Max is probably the most likely. Yeah.
Little Stephen probably broadcast it.
Little Stephen's garage from the reopen renamed cleaned up version.
All right. We're going to do some I'm going to do some research and figure this out.
He's got a built in difficulty, though, which is you don't want to get a bandana
caught in one of these slides.
I was thinking about that.
Like once your bandana gets why you won't wear a mask on rides out,
because like it gets wet, that that cramps your style.
Like how do you how do you go down on a looping water slide in a bandana?
And little Stephen is just full of scarves as well.
So he has the bandana and the scarves.
They're fused to him now.
So he can't exactly take them off.
Maybe that's where they come from, is the scars.
It's very possible.
Yeah. So he's got to stay out of the slides and he's got to stay out of that.
If he gets yanked into a turbine, then he's like
then he stays down there with the snakes and oil.
Yeah. You guys throw me a ride name.
I'll give you a story that nobody's heard.
We missed what's the the one that's spelled weird, the aqua scoot.
I think that's one that hasn't been name checked yet.
OK, there's nothing too crazy about that.
It did. It was kind of a messy ride.
That was OK. Actually, I'll tell you something about that.
That was like warehouse rollers on an angle.
And you take this car, you try to skip across the pond like a stone.
That was actually created by the same guy who made the man in the ball
and the ball, the same the same dude made that one.
That right actually made it the prime time, though.
A lot of people got got like their toes like cotton and stuff.
Nothing. That's like the most team right.
Come on, give me another one. Only your toe.
Oh, man. Wait, what have we not named checks?
And we've talked about a lot of them.
What car I have, kamikaze in front of me.
That's tame, though.
Kamikaze people, people would people would fly off the kamikaze all the time,
because that was a ride that was built like into the natural slope of the mountain.
And the rails on the side of it were like three inches.
So people just hit these like lips and they'd fly off.
And the ride we talked about in the movie, that was like a prototype one
based off of zero gravity planes where you go over like parabolic hills
and get some air time was sort of like the amped up version of the kamikaze.
I think once they realized people were getting air and flying off the kamikaze,
they're like, well, let's just like milk that for what it's worth.
Let's like make that a ride where the goal is to get airtime.
Surf Hill.
Yeah, Sir, feels the one that they hit broke his neck
after they started building up the jump and just like going
in the observation stands, all that stuff.
Mm hmm.
Um, the whiplash falls.
I don't even know what that one is.
I'm just I'm just making them up now.
I'm just trying.
So they had a lot of rides that like don't get much attention.
Like if you look at old park maps, you're like, what was that?
Like they had one called the human maze.
Like, what's the human maze?
Nobody talks about the human maze at Action Park.
Well, that's just what I used to call having a nine to five, the human maze.
I'm just getting lost.
This is my life, man. The human maze.
We're all just trying to navigate the human maze and trying to have some fun
while we do it.
And, you know, I I think I enjoyed myself talking about about this old place.
And I thank you so much for being here.
So the porges, you survived podcast, the ride,
not as harrowing as a day at Action Park, not in the least.
Unless that microphone you have is near some water,
you're some snake oil that could get you.
I think it's a little too dark.
Somebody actually did die from electrocution at Action Park.
Yes. I mean, well, there's a look.
We've been hovering around darkness.
I think the world's worst, like improv guy who like, like, yes,
and somebody died, like just air out of the room.
You could say when it comes to Vernon, there's certainly darkness
on the edge of town.
It's like, hey, everybody has everybody.
Who did anybody get hurt today?
It's just Christ. I'm that guy.
So never invite me to your improv trip, guys.
Well, it is no longer an art form, so that's not happening anymore.
So no, it's just for everyone to continue to live.
Yes. Someone should make a documentary about improv.
Very funny. Oh, that'd be great.
Oh, that'd be the problem of great documentaries.
Anyway, your documentary, I'll do your plugging for you a little bit.
Your documentaries on HBO Max and it's a little bit of a fun one.
HBO Max and it's a lot of fun.
But but is there anything else you would like to plug
or anything else related to the film?
No, guys, it's on HBO Max.
You know, social for me is just like at Seth Porges with a P.
That's simple. Wonderful.
And as for us, we are at podcast the ride on the socials.
We have merch available on T public and for three.
And if you want three bonus episodes every month, subscribe to podcast
the ride, the second gate at Patreon dot com slash podcast the ride.
I mean, as far as parting words,
I can't think of anything better than snakes and oil.
Everyone still oil, oil, oil, oil.
I'm evil Ringo snakes, comma, separate and oil.
That's new. And everything for us.
Evil ring. If anyone has art of people, Ringo, feel free.
I will be signing autographs.
I start everything snakes, comma oil, everything, everything.
Opposite peace sign.
He doesn't do peace sign. He does like this.
He turns them upside down. Inverted.
It did be sign.
He wears rings on his toes and are a big brother.
Don't don't do that on the aqua scoot.
Don't wear toes in the atmosphere.
Is that the thing here?
Everyone else, thanks for listening.
Bye bye. Next night.
Bye.
This has been a forever dog production executive
produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Baum, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts dot com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify
or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter,
Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.