Five, four, three, two, one.
Salud, amigos, and welcome to Podcast The Ride The Second K.
A very special episode.
My name is Mike Carlson.
Joining me as always, Jason Sheridan.
That's right, I'm here too.
Jason is here too.
We, of course, I guess I shouldn't say of course,
but we're missing one of our hosts today.
Mr. Scott Gairner is gone.
He's not here, and you know what happens
when the cat's away, the mice will play.
Yes, so what happened was, you know,
Scott's doing nothing crazy,
but it's his information to share if he wants,
but he's busy.
So he said, well, if you and Jason have something
you'd like to talk about, you know,
we did an episode about Marvel Comics,
about the Marvel Mania restaurant.
Scott and I have done an episode about rock and roll.
We're big rock and roll guys.
So I was thinking, yeah, there's probably something,
and then I was thinking, you know, what is it?
Is it more Marvel?
There's gotta be other Marvel things, you know,
storms, what is it, an accelerator, what do you call it?
The storm force accelerator?
Yeah, storm force accelerator.
We could do an episode about that.
That would be fun.
But we sort of did Marvel Mania,
and maybe it's been, maybe wait a little bit longer
to do more Marvel.
And then I thought, hmm, let's really go for it.
Let's really, you know, do something,
because Scott said something that would be very good
for just you and Jason to do.
He said it, he spelled it out.
He basically told us what to do.
He told us what to do.
Yeah, he told us what to do,
and obviously you've probably read the title of this episode
so you know, and if you're a second gate member,
I mean, we'll fill you in
in case this is your first second gate episode,
because you're probably very confused.
But I assume if you're behind the paywall,
you know what's going on today.
We, of course, today then have decided,
with Scott's blessing,
even though he does not know what we're doing,
he does not know the name of this and why,
he knows why, but he doesn't know what we're doing,
we of course are talking about Casamigos tequila,
the tequila created by George Clooney
and Cindy Crawford's husband, Randy Gerber.
That is what we're talking about today.
I believe the first time we talked about this
was the Downtown Disney ordeal with Nick Mundy,
am I correct here?
I was thinking about that right before we were recording to it
and I believe that is the first time it came up, yes.
And I'm not even quite sure how we got there, you know?
I don't remember how we got there either, yes.
I don't remember, you can hear I'm out of breath
because I've done more prepping for this
than I think I've done for a podcast in a while,
maybe since the Downtown Disney ordeal.
There's a lot of moving parts is what I'm saying.
So yeah, we don't exactly know,
all I know is that I started talking about
Cindy Crawford's husband, Randy Gerber's tequila,
and everyone except for Jason got upset with me.
Yeah, because I knew the story about how
not only did they start this tequila brand,
when they sold it for $700 million with a possible 300 million
depending on sales performance over the next decade.
I knew that when they did that,
George Clooney invited the boys,
there's about 14 of them, the boys.
And he invited his crew to his house, September 20th, 2013.
A date that will live in infamy.
You celebrate that day by getting a briefcase.
I do, yeah.
And then on September 14th,
I returned the briefcase to Joseph A. Bank.
That's fair, yeah.
And inside that briefcase in $20 increments
was a million dollars for all the boys.
And he said, I know, you know, there are people,
some of these boys were living paycheck to paycheck.
We're really struggling.
And he said, you don't have to worry about
your kids' college, you don't have to worry about
paying your mortgage, you're all taken care of.
You know, essentially we're all millionaires now.
And Randy Gerber, he's tequila co-founder,
was like, I don't feel good about taking this money.
And George said, there's one rule.
If you don't take it, no one gets it.
And so Randy had to take it.
And you know what else I just learned today?
September 13th, 2014, George married them all.
Right.
One year later.
Two significant days.
On the same day.
Oh, the same day.
A year apart.
So what's funny about this is that you just told this story
and that story you knew, you had that locked away.
You would never share that with me or anyone maybe.
I do have to correct myself.
It's September 27th.
I just got so excited.
I got so excited.
I remember 2013.
People are already upset because they know all of the facts
and information about this topic.
And they're gonna be very upset if we get anything wrong.
So we have to correct ourselves if we do.
So you had that piece of information in your head.
I didn't know that piece of information.
I never heard that story before.
I just knew a couple of years prior,
I saw giant trucks with pictures of George Clooney
and some guy on a motorcycle.
And I thought it was funny.
I was like, what is this?
This is ridiculous.
And it said Casa Migos Tequila.
And I did a little investigating
and found that it was George Clooney
and Randy Gerber's tequila company.
And I have photos.
I proved this on Twitter a month or two ago.
I have photos a couple of years prior
to doing the podcast even.
Maybe one year prior to starting the podcast
of pictures of me and the truck.
And they're on Twitter.
I forget which thread it was.
I was thinking I was posting them to Scott.
So I have been a big fan of the idea of this
for a long time.
And I think if we really break it down,
I am a big fan of celebrity endorsed drinks,
spirits, restaurants.
We just mentioned not too long ago,
there was a restaurant that had Grandpa
from the Munsters on it in Jersey.
It was called Grandpa's apparently.
And Al Lewis, the actor who played Grandpa
did not own this place.
He would just sort of be the greeter
and he made some deal with the owner.
So I love anything like that.
Jimmy Buffett, of course, my personal hero,
did this better than anybody.
So anytime I see it, I think it delights me
for some reason.
I don't know if it's because it's just insane.
If I'm thinking, how much money do you guys need?
Is that like, that might be part of it?
That's probably part of it.
That's probably part of it too.
And I think there's the implicit,
just the endorsement makes it seem like,
well, and these guys know good stuff.
They wouldn't just slap their name on something.
Well, right, of course.
No one would just slap their name on anything like that.
Yes, there's a pretension to all of this
that I really like where the commercials for Customigos,
which we'll get into, the commercials,
George and Randy are out in the fields with the workers
and they're just breaking bread and drinking tequila.
They're just the regular guys.
They're just all in the same tax bracket.
They're all enjoying the same luxuries of life together.
And these just-
They're all on the same level.
And as I'm sure we'll get to,
another character has opted to do the exact same thing.
Yes, I think I know what you're talking about.
We'll get to that person.
But I think real quick first, what we should do,
and now this came out not long ago,
I think on a main, no, I think it was a Patreon episode,
that I had not tried Customigos tequila.
And that sent Scott into a rage.
He was very upset.
Yeah.
Because I think he thought my love of Customigos
had anything to do with the actual tequila, and it doesn't.
Absolutely not, no.
It has nothing to do with it.
And I pulled a U in that instance and I said,
well, anytime I wanted to get it as a bid, I go,
ooh, $45, I don't need this bit that bad.
Yeah, I famously, I hate spending money on comedy.
I feel like there are such easy ways to beg, borrow, steal
in comedy, especially when we were coming up at UCB.
It almost guarantees, at a sketch comedy theater,
the more money you spend on a character or a sketch,
the harder it's gonna, if it bombs,
it just stinks so much worse if you spend $100.
I hear what you're saying.
To be fair to this, it's like tequila,
you're not gonna throw the tequila out.
You can actually drink it.
That is true.
You could have a nice, oh, we're having a special night.
Let's crack open the Customigos, darling.
Yes, much more justified.
Yeah, because I came across a bottle
at the hotel gift shop in Vegas, and I was like,
should I, and I'm like, God knows how much the pens
in this gift shop cost a lot of money.
You and I did a show at UCB theater many years ago
that did not get a run, we did it once,
and I bought a giant roach costume
that I still have somewhere.
It's a disgusting roach costume,
and it was very expensive.
Not very expensive, but expensive.
I was hoping that I would get to use it more than once,
and now it's just sitting in a Rubbermaid
in the storage area of the garage.
Yeah, that stings a lot more than all of the Bud Light
Platinum's we bought for Bud Light Platinum-based bits,
when that was at the height of its popularity.
Yes, you and I played Franklin and Bash in a bit
in a show at UCB, and we bought a case of 18
Bud Light Platinum bottles, and wheeled it out
in a Rubbermaid on stage, and did we hand,
I handed them out to the people on stage, I think?
Not the audience, we wouldn't do that.
We gave them to the judges, and I have to say,
I've been in the middle of the desert,
no one around for miles, and that was still not as quiet
as that audience reception to seeing Franklin and Bash.
Well, okay, we'll give everyone a little bit of the lore here,
of the friendship lore, and the performance lore.
Yeah, we did a show at UCB, I mean, I still do the show
when shows happen, called The Tournament of Nerds,
which is not unlike other shows.
I've done enough debate shows online, in theaters,
that I'm sure everyone is confused,
but the first one I ever did was something called
Tournament of Nerds, where you would compete as a character,
and you would argue and debate why one character
would beat the other, and I had a lot of success
at that show doing what one might call an ironic character.
One of my biggest victories in life was competing
as the character, is the NBC character, The Cape.
The superhero show from a decade ago, called The Cape,
and I basically just got a lot of mileage out of,
and I think this will surprise the listener,
just naming the other characters on The Cape.
Max Malini and his underground carnival of crime,
I believe that's the characters and the name there.
Ruby was a hypnotist, I believe.
Yeah, so anyway, so we were basically like,
oh man, Franklin and Bash is gonna kill,
and you would get a big laugh when you would come out,
and they announce your character, and you know,
if they said like, NBC's The Cape, we'd all, ha ha,
everyone's laughing, clap, they say,
and representing Franklin and Bash, and it's like crickets,
and then you and I come out on stage,
and it's as if no one heard of Franklin and Bash,
the hottest USA show at the time, Breckenmire,
and what, Paul Mark Gosseler, is that his name?
Mark Paul Gosseler.
I said his name, I'm sorry.
I sound like an old man now.
But yeah, so we've spent, yeah,
liquor comedy bits different, I think,
because at least you can enjoy some of it.
Yeah, for sure.
So yeah, so I revealed not long ago,
I had never had Casamigos, and Scott was like,
yeah, he was very frustrated because I think he thought
at the very least I must have tried this once,
and I hadn't.
But today, for you, the Patreon paywalled listeners,
Jason and I are going to try Casamigos tequila right now.
Yes.
And give you our first review, first sip review.
Jason was nice enough to go get, now he got tiny bottles.
I got the little airplane-sized bottles.
How much were these tiny bottles, if I may ask?
Well, Mike, the universe was there waiting
for us, knowing it was coming,
because they were all on sale when I went.
So one of these was $5, and one of them was $6.
Wow, pretty good.
Yeah, so we've got the Blanco and we've got the Reposado.
Now, I did a little bit of tequila research
because I always wondered what was the difference.
So Blanco is bottled right after fermentation,
or aged at maximum for two months.
Reposado is aged for more than two months,
up to a year maybe.
There is a third variety called Añejo,
which is aged much longer, and that they were sold out of.
And I was not going to a second Bevmo.
So I do-
Sorry, which one were they sold out of again?
The Añejo, I believe it's pronounced.
My high school Spanish is pretty far behind me,
but I'm trying my best.
Yeah, so now the thing with these tequilas, all of them,
because I was like, oh, do I need to get salt and lime?
And the more I researched,
and right on the Cosmica's homepage it says this,
this is a smooth, they wanted a smooth tequila.
Yes, they didn't want to burn.
This is what I found in my research as well.
No burn, that's what George and Randy wanted.
Yes, the salt and lime are used to cover up
the unpleasant taste,
which I guess is kind of similar to cheap whiskey
being covered up by Coca-Cola or ginger ale.
If you would indulge me,
I'll read what Randy even said about creating the tequila.
I wish you would.
Okay, here we go.
He said, Casamigos was created out of our desire
to drink the best tequila.
At the time, George and I were building homes in Mexico,
and as one does when you spend time in Mexico,
we were drinking a lot of tequila.
We would go to different restaurants and bars,
and bartenders would suggest different tequilas,
some really expensive, some not so expensive,
some good, some not so good.
They all had one thing in common, they burned going down.
With that, George turned to me and said,
why don't we just make our own,
one that's perfect for us?
So we did.
That's straight from Randy Gerber's mouth, folks.
That's the origin story of Casamigos.
And they also, a lot in the press,
if you read a lot of their press on their website,
it's a lot of like, we just were doing it for ourselves.
We didn't even intend to start a business.
Yes, they intended to just have a private label
for themselves and family and friends.
And then I'm sure someone swept in and was like,
you can make some real money on this.
Well, I think you're actually giving them a little too much.
My feeling is that story's bullshit.
That's entirely possible, yeah.
Celebrity restaurants, even more so celebrity liquor.
There's so many people where you're like,
Ryan Reynolds had a liquor company?
Yeah, my guess, and look,
I guess this is maybe sort of insulting George and Randy,
no disrespect.
My guess is the actual story is
they were both pulled into a meeting at CAA,
and they go, all right, here's what's selling.
Tequila, celebrity endorsements.
You guys sign on the dotted line here,
and we can make this happen.
And they go, okay.
I mean, I think it might be closer to that.
I don't know if George or Randy wanna come on podcast,
all right, I'd love it.
And I want them to tell me I'm full of shit,
if that's the case.
Yeah.
But that's the lore, that's the legend of Casamigos,
which I choose to believe.
Sometimes the legend is more important to believe
than the actual truth.
And I think we should believe the legend.
So, we have the tequila in front of us,
and I have two little glasses, and it's sipping.
You can sip it, which, because there's no burn.
Yeah, that's good.
I mean, we've done a number of episodes
where we've either imbibed beforehand or during.
I find I get very exhausted and sluggish,
and I feel bad I'm not being entertaining
to our wonderful listeners.
So, there'll be less of that kind of episodes burn,
if you will, and there'll be more just pleasant sipping.
So, I guess let's start with the Blanco.
That's the clear one?
Yeah, that's the clear one.
Because- I'll sip it right here,
and I'm gonna let the listener-
That is the least aged.
I will say now, this episode is coming to you
in binaural audio.
So, you can put on your headphones
and listen to Jason and I drink,
which is one of the greatest sounds you can ever hear
the human mouth make.
Very good, and I've poured some of mine over ice
because I do not particularly enjoy drinking lukewarm.
I mean, I'll drink lukewarm water, you know, if-
All day long.
I have to, I prefer cold beverages.
I do not like lukewarm beverages,
especially lukewarm liquor, so.
Okay, so here we go, here we go, listen up.
It is very smooth.
I will say, and I look, I'm not a huge drinker,
but I will say there's a slight tingle,
but it's nothing crazy.
It is- No.
It's not a burn, because he has a normal tequila.
I would be coughing like crazy right now.
Wow.
Wow, cool, you know what?
Kudos to George and Randy on fulfilling that promise.
Let's see if the other one does the same thing.
Yeah, and that was like the entry,
like Blanco is the, often mixed with something
because it's usually a cheaper one,
but that was pretty pleasant.
So let's try the middle grade.
All right, listen up.
Also pretty good.
Also the same level of, wow, interesting.
I mean, yeah, it's like, obviously,
you know you're drinking alcohol,
but if I were to straight, and these aren't freezing,
if I were to add a regular tequila,
that would have been crazy.
I would be going nuts right now.
I'd be going wild.
Wow, so they did it, so they did it.
They did it, they did a good job, yeah.
So I'm gonna go with the middle grade.
I'm gonna go with the middle grade.
They did it, they did a good job, yeah.
And one of the facts I like is that,
they have sold the company, as we said,
they've sold the company,
but Randy still goes to the office every day.
They're still involved.
Oh, and they're still all over the website.
Like, you know, when they sold to,
do you know how to pronounce the name of this company
they sold to?
I mean-
You do it.
Well, we'll all probably be working for this company.
I was trying to remember this company came up
on the Downtown Disney or Deal,
because one of the themes for me on that
was just how like, oh yeah,
there's only five companies that own everything.
I don't know if it's Dege-Gio or J-Gio.
It's a massive, oh no, De-A-Gio, I think it's-
De-A-Gio?
I'm gonna guess it's De-A-Gio.
This is a massive beverage concern
that owns like Johnny Walker,
black and white Scotch,
Walt Disney, famously loved black and white Scotch.
What else do they own?
They own Bullet, and Seagram Seven Crown, and Crown Royal,
Smirnoff, Captain Morgan,
Bailey's, a liquor-
Whoa, a liquor called Sheridan's.
I do not know about this liquor.
Is it spelled like yours?
Yes, it sure is.
Oh my God, do you have a liquor?
I guess so.
Gosh, and that's gonna step all over a bit later.
They also own Don Coolio,
so they already own a tequila.
How did you not know about Sheridan's?
And it's got a bottle that looks like a dick and balls.
Holy shit.
Do you see this?
Let me see, send it, screen share it.
Holy, whoa, folks, this is an unplanned,
this is the magic of Podcast The Ride, here we go.
Is that not?
Wow, that is,
yeah, that is not an aesthetically pleasing bottle.
So it's a coffee layered liqueur,
and it's got two different sides.
It's almost like the ketchup and mustard in the same pack,
or the peanut butter and jelly in the same bottle,
but it's got two separate things,
and it's got, I assume, vanilla on the top,
and that would be the top of the penis shaft.
And then the bottom, where the scrotum is,
is full of coffee.
The jug's full of coffee layered liqueur.
Yeah, sorry.
And still has a foreskin.
Let's be clear, this bottle is not circumcised.
Okay, so Sheridan's coffee layered liqueur
is a bottle that has a vanilla top coffee cream shaft,
a coffee scrotum, and a coffee foreskin.
This is a shocking and unpleasant discovery.
This is the greatest thing to happen to the podcast
in a long time, I feel.
Maybe since the Downtown Disney ordeal.
I guess everyone's getting a bottle of Sheridan's
for Christmas.
I do-
How do you not know about this?
I don't know.
I guess I just need to Google my name.
I just keep getting, like, anytime I've gotten
a Google alert for my name recently,
it's just been about this guy who runs gyms in England,
who's like, I sure hope I can reopen gyms soon.
But there's no discourse around Sheridan's
coffee layered liqueur.
Oh, wow.
You need to be a spokesman for this.
Yeah, I mean, I wonder if it's good in,
I do like a splash of like Amaretto or Jameson in my coffee.
So when you take off the foreskin, the coffee foreskin,
I wonder, yeah, how does it, how, what does it look,
let me look, let me find it.
Let me look what it looks like without the foreskin
or when it's fully engorged.
I think that foreskin is important though.
I think it comes out.
Oh yeah, you're right.
Look it, I got a picture here.
See it here?
Yeah, twists.
I think they have that cap on,
so you get both simultaneously.
Okay, so the foreskin twists
and then you can get a good blend of the coffee and vanilla.
Wow, it's got a scrotum reservoir.
This is insane.
Why wouldn't it just be the same?
Why wouldn't it be symmetrical?
This is like we're back in Europe for you
except we're in the highlands of Jalisco, Mexico.
I reverted back last week, but now I'm back.
Seeing this penis bottle with your name on it
has got me really excited.
Wow, look, I guess it's obviously, it's more coffee based
because that's, you want more of that in the drink
than you want the cream or the vanilla, whatever it is.
Yeah, but you don't see it like Bailey's
is just a regular bottle, you know?
Right.
God, are there commercials where it's like,
hi, hello, I'm Jason Sheridan.
I created Sheridan's.
I molded the bottle after a certain appendage.
Someone, there is a video of the pouring.
Someone did record the pouring.
Wow, well, we have to figure out
what to do with this information.
Yeah. I don't know.
This is really throwing me for a loop
because I had a whole plan here
and this is actually so exciting.
You know?
But yeah, all right, well, we'll come back.
We'll do the research and come back to this
at a different time.
Well, sir, go back.
The other surprising thing to learn about this beverage,
like massive beverage company,
they also own Guinness and Harp.
Like they own beers, too.
They own so many and I forget.
InBev is one of the other big beverage conglomerates,
but yeah, everyone owns,
everything is owned by something nowadays.
InBev sounds like a Skynet type company.
Yeah.
InBev and the bottles will come to life.
Yeah, so they're owned by that company,
but George and Randy still taste every batch.
Oh.
That's what I read.
That's what they say.
I don't know how that works.
I don't know how big the batch is.
I assume pretty big.
You wouldn't think that they,
that George and Randy took a little swig
of each of these little bottles before we got to them.
And then they put the cap back on and then-
They put the cap back on.
Put the plastic.
Randy Gerber like took his tongue and just like,
licked the outside of the bottle
and then screwed it back on and put it in the Bevmo?
I did see, you know,
I think we went into the Mexico Pavilion real quick
when we were in Epcot last fall.
And I got an avocado margarita to go,
cause I mean, they make really good margaritas there.
And then they do have the Casa Amigos varieties
on the menu,
but not in any mixed drinks
because they're sipping tequila.
So you're not gonna bury it in a mixed drink?
We had the mixed drinks there at Epcot last time,
which I was a little,
it's easier to go to the bar.
If you don't know what we're talking about,
there's a tequila bar in the Mexico Pavilion
and Epcot Center in the World Showcase.
And it's the greatest,
it's still I think my favorite pavilion probably.
I mean, just being able to be like transported
to like a night market in the sky.
There's the restaurant there.
There's of course the Mexico Boat Ride,
Scott's name for it.
There's a lot of like great,
like artisanal toys and neat stuff.
And then there's also, yeah,
there's this little tequila bar,
which is a nice little hole in the wall,
which is what you kind of want.
Like the stuff that we kind of pine for,
I think at these theme parks and stuff,
I'm gonna do a little theme park talk here,
is like things like that,
that feel kind of special,
like Abracadabra over on the boardwalk.
It's like, it's tiny, it's small.
It feels like this is a little thing you found.
And that's the same way that the tequila bar
in the Mexico Pavilion is.
But it's hard to get a seat in there,
because it's so small.
So we only did, they only give you like the mixed drinks
when you're just walking up to the bar
to order and then leave, which is what we were doing.
But yes, I would have loved to sip Casamigos
sitting in there.
Yes, I believe we guzzled that down,
left the building, or like I was in the process
of guzzling it down or eating like,
eating something from a food stand.
And Scott and Eric right shortly thereafter were like,
we're having a baby.
And I was like, oh, oh wow.
Mouthful.
Mouthful of avocado or raclette or something.
Mm-hmm.
That is, yeah, that is like right outside that pavilion
is where we found out.
Yeah.
Last year.
So we will always remember that spot.
Mere yards away from where I saw the Baja Men.
Yeah.
I mean, hundreds of, maybe hundreds of yards,
but not far.
Casamigos, the Baja Men, the miracle of life,
everything happens at Epcot.
The World Showcase,
I've said this probably on the show before,
the World Showcase is the one thing from Disney World
that I would trade a lot from Disneyland for.
I think that's fair.
As an adult, obviously,
to be able to have like a World Showcase,
obviously they were gonna do a version of it with Westcott,
which didn't get built.
But that is the one thing I go, oh man,
I really, I would trade, I would trade big for that.
I think.
Would I trade, let me see, let me think about this.
Would I trade in Credit Coaster?
Okay, what would be the fair trade?
I would trade in Credit Coaster, Sorin,
the whole pier, Toy Story, Midway Mania.
These are all rides I like a lot.
I don't wanna give up Guardians.
So that'll be the only E-ticket there.
They can have the Quinjet.
They can have the newly installed Quinjet
that they finished before they finished Sidewalks.
Yes, I saw that.
Well, it's harder to get a giant jet up there
than it is to pave some sidewalks.
I think I would be okay with the trade-off.
Bye-bye in Credit Coaster, bye-bye Sorin,
bye-bye Midway Mania, bye-bye Raft Ride.
And then the whole pier, if you could put in
at least like 75% of a World Showcase.
Yeah.
There'll still be one or two rides in there too,
but the space is not gonna have it.
It's not gonna be able to be like a giant in Credit Coaster.
I think that's fair.
Maybe I'm crazy.
I mean, you definitely, you gotta give away a lot.
You gotta back the truck up, you know,
cause you're doing it.
It's like when you would trade like five superhero cards,
like five trading cards for one card that like,
I really want this one, you know?
Yeah, you gotta make it so you can't turn the deal down.
Yeah.
You have to make the deal undeniable.
So yeah, I think that's, yeah, with World Showcase.
All right, stop the theme park talk.
Back to celebrity tequila.
So yeah, so we're having this.
I will say as I'm drinking it,
I think the Blanco is better.
Yeah, I'm surprised.
I think it's a little smoother.
To me, it feels like there's less,
it is smoother, the Blanco.
I think some of them as their age
are aged in bourbon barrels,
which I don't really like bourbon anymore.
Like I think that's what I drank.
I drank Jack and Coke a lot when I first started,
like became like 21 and I just didn't,
it was just so sweet.
And now I like, I like like rye or scotch,
but I really haven't drank that much during quarantine.
We were drinking White Claws a lot at the start.
Yeah, I was drinking some White Claws at the start.
I haven't in a while.
I had been drinking like sparkling water and vodka,
but then I realized it was like bubbling my stomach
up too much, I think.
That is a pro, you can give yourself a stomach ache
with too much seltzer, yeah.
Cause like I'm stressed.
It's not so much probably even the alcohol.
It's just that like I go downstairs to like stress drink,
like diet cola or sparkling water.
Like I think there's a,
I'm trying to like nervously do something.
Oh, sure, yeah.
So I kind of stopped, well, I'm at once in a while,
but yeah, rye, I like rye.
I like that bullet rye a lot.
I like that a lot.
I like it on the rocks with a twist of lemon.
So then that's a little tip, a little complicated
cause then you got to keep lemon in the house,
which I do something nice to have lemon in your water,
you know, change it up.
Good antioxidants.
Nice to have lemon in the house, I think.
Not that expensive.
Lemon's not that expensive.
No.
Yeah, so I am finding the Blanco better.
The other one's good too though.
I will say I would actually probably be fine drinking
this Lukewarm as well.
Yeah.
Cause it's getting there.
Do we want to talk about the third man a little bit?
I guess we should.
So I know everyone's thinking,
it's George Clooney or Annie Gerber, case closed.
Well, not so easy, not so fast, okay?
Cause there's a third partner and that person's name is,
is it Michael Meldman?
Yes, it's Michael Meldman.
So I started to look up Michael Meldman
cause I knew there was kind of like a third
less prominent partner.
And the first thing I came across was a Wall Street
journal article with the headline,
real estate party boy.
And I was like, okay, gotta shut this down
cause God knows what sort of sinister craps in this article.
Well, you didn't read it.
I read a lot of it and it's not,
they're not gonna put anything that bad in there.
Now for people that know, for people that watch the show,
Real Housewives, I know there's many versions,
this man was married to Brandy Glanville.
Oh, okay.
So that's a big connection for,
I think a big section of the,
I mean, a lot of people watch that show.
I don't watch, I've seen it.
I know some of the names.
I know people are mad at Denise Richards right now.
I know Lisa Rinna is mad at Denise Richards.
Do you know that?
Is that a familiar thing to you?
I did not know that.
Okay.
I'm not sure exactly why.
I just sort of absorbed this like via people
or if I've CTMC, if I'm like going by and I see TMZ.
So yes, she's not married to this Michael Meldman anymore,
but he is, I'll tell you what, he's a notorious party boy.
And he is somebody who claims to be
one of the best beer pong players in the world.
Oh, he's too old to be claiming that.
He's probably almost 60, I think.
Yeah.
That's not, yeah, that's not,
that's not a game our parents enjoyed.
No, I don't, I feel like at most,
maybe they played quarters.
I am not even sure of the rules of quarters.
Yeah, beer pong, I mean,
I was first introduced to it in college.
It's a gross game, first of all.
I immediately, like at 18, I was like, oh, this is gross.
Oh, everyone just shared.
In case the kids today, I know we have a big,
of course, youthful audience, I assume.
It's a game where you put, I think is it six cups out,
almost like it's their bowling pins,
six red solo cups,
and you fill them with a little bit of beer,
and you throw, basically, there's the same configuration
on each side of a table.
And then you take turns throwing ping pong balls
across the table to try to get them in every beer
so your opponent has to drink each beer.
Yes, and there's two cups of water, rinse cups.
And there's two rinse cups, because we know that really,
so you take the ball out of one of the beers
and you rinse it, and that really cleans it.
That sterilizes it immediately.
It's amazing this game did not cause a pandemic
before the current pandemic, you know?
That's true.
I assume, though, it's helping the current pandemic along.
Now the colleges are open, though.
Oh, yeah, it's helping them open for two weeks and go,
all right, we are immediately going back to online classes.
Everyone has three days to move out of their dorm rooms
before they are charged.
Yeah, I think that if the CDC would do
some more investigating, they would see that ping pong balls
carry COVID-19 very successfully.
One time I was at a place called O'Shea's in Las Vegas,
and they've rebranded O'Shea's, I forget in which hotel,
but it was just on the strip and it was a real shithole.
And they had beer pong in the back by the subway,
by the restaurant, the subway.
I was like, who's doing this here?
That's my favorite trick of the Vegas establishments.
I mean, they're all in a tough spot right now.
I think a lot of them are opened.
I think they opened with a lot of offerings
and have scaled back, similar to the way LA
kind of scaled back.
But even like, I think Caesar's is a pretty nice,
it's not the nicest casino anymore,
but I think it's pretty nice.
I guess it's very big.
That's the big defining thing of Caesar's now.
It's got like six towers.
But the ones, most casinos,
hotel casino resorts have a food court in them
that is just truly like feed your id.
Like here's a Krispy Kreme, here's a like a Sbarro's
and at like the nicer casinos,
it's like pizza by the slice by Buddy Velasco,
the cake boss, you know?
I have a photo of you and a giant cake boss, right?
Or no, no, I have you and Emeril maybe.
I think so because we stayed at the Venetian once
for a bachelor party and they had massive,
like two story murals of like the Bouchon guy.
You and cake boss and you and Emeril,
I think I have a photo of.
I should find those.
I think so.
And then there was a real like acclaimed
Michelin star chef next to them.
But of course everyone went to pictures by the TV people.
Yeah, with Bam, the Bam band.
Bam, yeah.
Yes, in Vegas, Lindsay and I were in Vegas,
when was it, last August?
And we were trying to get something to eat so quickly
and we were like right before a show,
maybe it was before Copperfield.
And it was like, are we gonna go to this
like Philly cheesesteak place
that's in this like mall looking?
And then we're like, ah, this looks like shit.
And then we're like, well, what about this pizza
at the place that's not even Sabaro level?
And then we like got in and we're like,
God, this like, this all sucks.
This is all really bad.
I mean, that's the innovation of putting an Italy in Vegas
is that like, if you're in a pinch,
you just go into Italy and walk right up to anything
and it's delicious.
Like. Oh, Italy.
It's very good.
That's the Park MGM is like the last one to open.
Yeah. Still closed.
I long for that Park MGM cause I went twice.
I was stayed there twice last year
and probably would have stayed there again in May
for when there was another wrestling pay-per-view.
I, we, yeah, we, I had such a great time.
We had such a great time in February when we were there.
And I was like, we're coming back in the spring.
Like.
I like the idea of like gracefully going into my old age,
having like, well, that's the hotel we go to, the Park MGM.
That's the hotel we stay at.
And like, if somebody were to maybe suggest like,
oh, you know, there's a new hotel
they recently fixed up X Hotel.
I would be like, thank you for the suggestion,
but we don't stay there.
We stay at Park MGM.
That's what we do, which is a thing I see in old folks.
So I'm happy that that might be where I'm headed.
Yeah. I feel like my family,
I feel like I've already been doing that
for a good portion of my life.
I feel like my family has primed me for that.
I feel we were a family who did that sort of thing.
I'm a little curious by like the other, there's like Vidara.
Some of the ones that are like,
oh, there's no casino in this hotel.
It's just a nice hotel.
I'm like, oh, that could be a nice change of pace.
Sure.
I mean, you seem to be like,
you're still actually more flexible.
You'll take a suggestion.
I mean, I think, didn't you go to Park MGM?
Cause I said, I stayed there and I liked it.
Well, and we had comps from those Vegas games.
Right.
So, and yes, you recommended that one.
And I think Jane had looked up that one.
It was like, this looks pretty nice.
And it's the most recently redone.
And yeah.
Yeah.
We had a nice time at the pool.
Anyway, it's not a Las Vegas podcast.
It's about celebrity tequila.
That's what we're doing here.
So Michael Meldman, he's a silent third partner.
He is a guy who builds like developments.
And I looked, look, I really struggled too to be like,
oh my God, I'm gonna find such a good tie-in
for theme parks and this topic.
And I go, oh, Michael Meldman, he develops things.
Surely he is involved with a theme park.
I don't think that's the case.
I think he just builds like big housing developments
for rich people and golf courses.
I think that's all he does.
Sure.
And that article is all about like,
oh, he's building another home.
All these fuckers are building like eight homes.
And it's like, oh, he built like a party barn.
And that's not verbatim what it says in the article,
but it's along those lines of like,
well, he likes the party and he bought a barn
that would be able to be converted into a rave space.
And if you wanted to have a host a foam party in the barn,
Michael Meldman would be able to do it.
If you got a little bit of funny money,
you build a man cave and then you build a she shed.
But if you really got money, you build a party barn.
Right.
A party barn, I think is a thing I guess.
I think we should coin that.
We should trademark that.
Cause I don't think that's a thing.
Yeah, I have to agree.
Podcast the Ride, well, we host a podcast about theme parks.
And of course we go on auditions.
We're also the leading purveyor of party barns.
We're in the party barn business.
Sharks, listen, okay.
So this is, you can use this for as a livery stable
or keep your tractor in here when the elements are bad.
But what if you just need to relax?
You can use it for that too.
Are you tired of just having horses in here?
Horses are boring.
Yeah.
Why don't you replace those horses
with industrial sized foam machines?
Why don't you pump out a hundred gallons of foam
per 30 minutes in this party barn?
Let's get it going.
Let's get, look, I mean, we're gonna get to,
I'm teasing a little bit.
We're gonna get to some pitches later,
but let's get some investors in on this as well.
Cause party barn, I don't know why I think Scott Storch
should invest music producer Scott Storch.
I don't know.
Maybe it's just because I was looking at his Instagram
year, hours ago.
You know, you know all these guys.
You're a big Scooter Braun defender.
I'm a big fan of Scooter Braun.
I think that he's got a lot of good ideas.
I am, yes, I am fascinated with the elite world
of celebrity and I guess really if we get to the core
of it, like side celebrities, like Randy Gerber.
Yeah.
Who no one knows who that is when I say it.
Yeah, he's like one of the richest men in America.
He wields insane power.
He, look, he's part of the Gerber group.
We haven't even gotten there yet.
He's part of the Gerber group that he owns
with his brothers, Scott and Ken with two N's.
That is true.
Randy is spelled with an E and not a Y
and Ken is spelled with two N's and not one N.
I, you know, the Gerbers, they do,
they do whatever they want.
They do whatever they want.
Scott is the one who I think, Scott Gerber,
not Scott Gerber, Scott Gerber.
Scott, do you think Scott Gerber maybe is the Scott Gerber
of the Gerber group?
Oh, maybe.
What is the Gerber group?
What is their line?
What is their business?
They do, okay, I have some more information about,
well, I'll say they are in the hotel bar business.
They started by making a bar called The Whiskey,
which I believe was in New York
and I should double check that.
Not The Whiskey at GoGo, but a whiskey in like 1991.
And they've basically made their like life's mission,
putting fancy cocktail bars in hotels.
That's what they do.
That is funny because the prices are already
so inflated at hotel bars.
So then to inflate them further with like muddling,
that's pretty funny.
What's also funny about this to me is that
when you're on vacation or when you're on a business trip
and you're just like, I need a fucking drink
because I'm on vacation or I'm on a business trip,
you'll go to any garbage bar in a hotel.
Like this is the easiest business you could possibly be in.
Yeah.
You and I could design a bar in five minutes right now.
They could plug it into a big hotel
that a lot of people go to and they'd be like,
wow, that bar is really successful.
It's like, well, yeah, no shit.
It's a bar in a hotel.
Yeah, a lot of like lights you can angle towards the liquor
or like you light the liquor from below.
There's a lot of black wood and black metal.
Like just all the tricks, all the crap they did
to like Johnny Rockets at CityWalk where you're like,
oh, this is just a weird lifeless husk now.
Now, yes.
And now I'm not talking about the off the record bar
slash club at the Park MGM in Vegas.
That's a whole different story.
I love that place.
No, that was pretty fun.
A little claustrophobic for my tastes.
Definitely not going to be opening anytime soon.
Did you go to the secret, did you go to the speakeasy room?
Yes, because I had free drinks.
I had free drinks to claim.
And that was the bar that was the least crowded.
Right.
When we were in there, yeah, it was pretty crowded
when we were in there in May and we saw a wrestler in there
who kind of snubbed us, but I won't even get into who that was.
No one that we ever have ever had on the podcast.
So that's a whole different story.
So yeah, but the Gerber group,
they're like the podcast, the ride of Hotel Bars.
So there's three of them.
They're obviously all brothers.
We are not brothers, but it's very similar.
I feel like maybe Scott Gerber is a Scott Gardner.
I feel like, look, and don't take this the wrong way.
I think I'm the Randy Gerber of the group.
Randy seems like the big picture guy.
You're the big picture guy.
And I do think that.
But I look, I think this is a cop.
You're the Ken.
You're the Ken, Ken Gerber.
I'll take it.
Of the group.
And Ken is successful as well.
I believe there's the least information about him online,
but I don't think that's bad.
No.
He's just, yeah, he's just sort of involved, you know,
a little bit more in the shadows.
He's not sort of the front.
So I think that makes a lot of sense.
I think that that lines up perfectly really.
So yeah, that's where, so Randy, by the way,
Randy was a model in the eighties.
Oh.
So that's how he got his start.
I mean, his wife, Sidney Crawford, of course,
probably the most famous supermodel of all time.
There's been some drama with her kids.
I don't think we need to get into it.
There's been a dating Pete Davidson type
of a situation going on.
Uh-oh.
You could read, you can read all about that in the TMZ.
So yeah, but they, but George and Randy still involved
and they're still very excited about Casamigos, I find,
when I'm reading these interviews now,
are all these interviews on the official Casamigos website?
Yes.
Yes, yes.
And that's where I spent most of my time.
And let's be clear, the Casamigos website,
when you first open it,
when you have to do the age check
that you have to do for like liquor websites,
you get a preview of what's coming.
And that's George and Randy drinking in the field
with their workers.
Right.
Just, you know, they're just one of the guys.
I'm sure they're helping out.
And then when you successfully enter that you are over 21,
then you get the full website
and the full picture is revealed.
It becomes video, they're laughing,
they're riding the bike, they're on the motorcycles,
you know, they're having a good time.
They're really haphazardly pouring drinks for people.
Like that's a thing that I get really anxious about
on these celebrity liquor websites
where they're just like, yeah, pour a little,
pour and they're spilling it.
And it's like, guys, it's a premium product.
Let's not waste it, come on.
Well, of course, you know,
you're from the school of John Taffer.
And if you ever watched Bar Rescue,
John Taffer is so concerned with overpouring.
You know, when you do a regular drink,
you're supposed to pour a sort of one shot worth,
one shot's worth of alcohol in.
Yeah, you do a, I think it's a four count.
If you have the skills and you have the right,
you know, lid funnel kind of thing,
you can count to four and then you like do an arm movement
and the air bubble stops the pour.
Right.
So yes, you're from that school
and you just don't wanna see it go to waste.
And also John Taffer of course says that, you know,
if you start overpouring,
people start getting too drunk
and you start to get a situation
where maybe people are acting crazy
and you don't want that in your bar.
That's a real liability.
Then the bar's on the hook if someone gets, you know,
over served or if someone starts a fight in the bar.
And of course he would explain that by screaming it,
which is what we love about John Taffer.
Yes.
Does he, did he probably vote for Trump?
Yeah, sure he did.
But other than that.
Pretty much, and there are sharks on shark town,
any business TV show person, it's just like,
well, if they didn't vote for him,
they're at least heavily benefiting
from Donald Trump's policies.
Yes.
But yes, so overpouring is happening
in those Casamigos ads.
But you know what, let's get to some of the ads.
Did you see these ads?
The commercial? Have you seen these ads?
Like the press, cause this website, wait,
the press section, the House of Friends section,
what are you talking about?
Or like the advertisement section.
I just looked on YouTube for Casamigos.
What is House of Friends is loosely the translation
for Casamigos, of course.
Yes, and well the House of Friends tab gets you to see
pictures of all the events that Casamigos sponsored
and all of the brands friends.
And there's an interesting thing,
but let's stick to the press.
Sure, you're right.
I'm getting too excited about the topic.
You're getting too excited.
Let's go.
So I just grabbed a couple of press clip-ics
that I enjoyed.
One is, do you know about the collaboration
with the Omega watch brand?
Oh, I don't actually.
Thank you. Please enlighten me.
I will. All right.
I'm gonna share this screen with you.
So Omega is a high end watch brand.
And they did a collaboration with Casamigos.
I'm sharing it with you now.
It's a pretty standard,
it's a Seamaster Planet Ocean watch.
It's a pretty standard, like, you know,
are they called chronometer?
It's like a nice looking watch.
You know, it's a nice kind of-
Of course.
Watch that someone on a boat or a pilot might have.
Do you want to take a guess at what this watch,
which by the way, has touches of turquoise,
like the Casamigos brand, the Casamigos bottle.
You can see Omega in turquoise
and some other turquoise touches on the face.
Can you guess what this watch retails at?
I have to imagine it's very expensive.
I keep, yes, okay.
What is your definition for very expensive?
Well, when we're dealing with the elites,
when the world of your Randy's and your George's
and the price point of their tequila already,
which is not maybe necessarily for the common man,
I would say this watch is $750.
Okay, well by price is right rules, you did not go over.
This watch retails for $11,600.
What?
Yeah.
What does it do?
It tells time.
That's it?
It's not even like a spy watch where you could kill a man
with some piano wire inside?
I mean, presumably it's very solidly made.
So you can maybe, with force, it's like a blunt instrument.
Okay, but there's nothing special
other than it's got like the Casamigos logo on it?
That's correct.
It doesn't even have that.
It just has touches of the Casamigos turquoise.
Interesting.
Can you still buy that?
Do you know?
I think you can, there are like resale websites
and secondhand websites.
Someone had a funny thread on Twitter
where they talked about working an event at Oakley stores.
And they were like, I think it was Alex Q. Arbuckle.
And he said, the people who collect Oakley sunglasses
are very particular type of guy.
And vintage Oakley sunglasses go for like $200 to $500.
And that already seems like a lot
to have the sunglasses Tom Cruise wore
at the start of Mission Impossible 2.
The style, not the authentic ones.
I'm sure the authentic ones go for a lot.
I hate to sidetrack.
Did you see the stunt that they're planning
for Mission Impossible 7?
What is it?
Oh, should I spoil it here?
All right, here, let me give everyone
like five seconds here to get out.
Can I spoil it for you?
Yeah, is this the space?
This is not space.
No, they're not going to space.
That's a different movie apparently.
That's a different movie.
He's very interested in going to space.
Elon Musk involved, which means bye-bye Tom.
So Mission Impossible 7.
All right, I'm going to give you everyone,
if you don't want to hear the spoiler,
I'm going to give you five seconds
and then I'm going to start talking.
One, two, three, four, five.
So on the side of a cliff,
there's a giant like evil Knievel ramp.
Apparently Tom Cruise is going to motorcycle
off the ramp and skydive off of it.
There's photos online on Twitter.
That's great.
Yeah, I think he may also have be like attached
to a helicopter, but I'm not sure if that's just for safety
and they'll take that out later
or that's part of it as well.
Ace, he's got to recover from seeing Tenet
in a movie theater first.
If you have not seen the Tom Cruise video
of him seeing Tenet in like England or something,
highly recommended.
He's like, oh, back to the movies.
And then he's like very serious about it
as if he's like making some sort of statement.
Like he's wearing a mask and then somebody goes,
so Tom, did you like the movie?
And he goes, loved it.
Like very sincere.
Nothing he does is insincere.
Anyway, it's interesting.
Tom Cruise does not have a celebrity liquor.
Well, I think Scientology does pride itself
on a little on cleaner living.
So I guess that's right.
That was the woman who plays Veronica's mother on Riverdale.
The story came out about her,
about how she has like helped the FBI
in like actual sex trafficking cases,
like go undercover and stuff.
Wow.
But very like the last,
and she volunteers, she has her own organization,
volunteers her time.
And either the last paragraph
or second to last paragraph said,
now she is a Scientologist and she says,
the rumors about abuse in that organization
are totally unfounded.
Okay.
Well, if she said it.
She said it, you know.
Hey, but you know,
that's what I like about these celebrity liquor companies.
You know, it's very richy, bougie,
pretty harmless, you know, overall
of like what rich people can do with their time and money.
Yes, I agree.
I mean, let me, you know what?
I'm gonna call an audible here
and I'm gonna give you a quiz.
Would that be okay?
It's not Potato or Jason.
Okay, sure.
Don't worry about that.
That's for only for Marissa.
That's fine.
Yeah.
I'm gonna give you a quiz.
Is this a real celebrity liquor?
Okay.
Let me put my feet up like Randy is here.
Oh my God.
See, Randy plays a guitar too.
Can you imagine?
Can you imagine what it sounds like
when Randy Gerber plays an A minor?
Oh, I wonder what song he played for the reporters
and photographer from Los Angeles Confidential Magazine
where he's playing the guitar with his feet up.
Okay, let's get to the quiz.
You know, what's funny about this is that
when you do this, I can't look at my notes.
Oh, okay.
So, okay, great.
Okay, so we'll do a few of these here.
So these are, you have to tell me
if this is a real celebrity liquor
or a fake celebrity liquor, all right?
Okay.
So very simple.
We don't even have one.
You're not playing against anyone,
so it doesn't really matter,
but everyone can play at home.
Okay.
Is it true that Bob Dylan has a celebrity liquor
called Heaven's Door Whiskey?
Is that true or false?
I think that's true.
You are correct.
Bob Dylan does have a liquor called Heaven's Door Whiskey.
Okay.
All right, question number two.
Does Billy Gibbons from ZZ Top
have a liquor called Pura Vida?
I think that one sounds a little too perfect.
I'm gonna say false.
That is true.
Billy Gibbons does have a liquor called Pura Vida,
which I did not write down what kind of liquor it is.
Okay.
Does, question three.
Does Sting, the musician Sting, not the wrestler,
have a brand of champagne called Champagne in a Bottle?
False.
That is correct.
That is not real.
That is made up.
I made that up.
Here, we'll do a couple more here.
Does, question four.
Does Marilyn Manson have his own brand of absinthe
called Mansonth?
That's gotta be true, right?
That is true.
Okay. Yes.
Okay, let's do one more.
Okay, question five.
Does Judge Larry from the Anna Nicole Smith trial
have his own brand of gin called The Verdict Gin?
Now, Judge Larry is still alive.
Judge Wapner is dead.
Is that correct?
Judge Larry, I believe, is still alive.
I honestly did not check.
I'll say that's false.
You are correct.
That is false.
Judge Larry does not have his own liquor.
Now, okay, so the game could go on and on.
I formulated, or I tabulated,
I don't know what you would say,
a list of 40 different celebrity, real celebrity liquors.
Martha Stewart, Chris Noth,
the Mr. Big from Sex and the City has a tequila.
Luke Bryan has a lager,
the Tulane American Golden Lager.
Kenny Chesney has Blue Chair Bay Rum.
George Strait has Codigo Tequila.
Ludacris, of course, has Conjured Cognac.
Robert De Niro, VDK, A, 6100.
And then, of course,
you know what I should have done in the quiz?
I really should have prepared it better.
Billy Bush has a whiskey called Beach Whiskey.
Oh.
Yes, the famous, grab them by the you know what,
Billy Bush.
Has his own brand of whiskey called Beach Whiskey.
So that's fun.
Go and look all of those up.
Of course, I think it'll come out later,
but I mentioned John Bon Jovi's new rosé,
which is called Hampton Water.
Which is very, you know, look,
the more the better, I say.
Post Malone has Maison Number Nine.
Did we know what that is?
I have to look it up.
And you sent me the Snoop Dogg,
Snoop Dogg rolling out his own line of gin.
Right, and he's already been affiliated with other liquors,
but now yes, who knows gin better than Mr. Gin and Juice?
Post Malone's is a rosé as well.
Okay, yeah.
And I believe the fat Jewish, he has a rosé.
Does he really?
Yeah.
Called like, I forget what it's called.
There's a place out in Los Angeles called Howlin' Rays,
which is hot chicken.
And just by happenstance, two friends of mine,
well, I guess a friend of the show, Evan Susser,
we had the Ghost Malone,
which was a special Post Malone created sandwich.
Oh.
Which had a good ghost pepper cheese.
So I have sampled some of his food.
Some of his wares.
Items before, yeah.
I like that sunflower song he did for the Spider-Man movie.
They did a cool video for it.
I don't think I know what you're talking about.
It was a big hit.
Just in the dust, like a sunflower.
There was like a music video
with like comic panels and stuff.
It's good.
Yeah.
I don't know anything about this.
Well, you have to send this to me.
Yeah.
So yeah, so I'm, the more the better.
Of course, The Rock has Tear-A-Mana tequila,
which I have a bottle of.
I have not cracked it open.
But I'm saving that for maybe a special occasion.
Now, The Rock is the other guy
who when you open the Tear-A-Mana website,
it is exactly like the Cosmogor's website.
He is in the field.
He's drinking with the workers.
He's drinking at a picnic table.
He's like really pouring, really heavy pours.
Yes, that's true.
And I think that is a winning strategy.
I have a few more things to say,
and then we'll talk about strategy in a second.
Yeah.
I will say, somebody pointed out to me on our Facebook group
and it was a post by Christopher Arrearilio,
I think is your name.
I apologize if it's not, if I got that wrong,
that in Dumb and Dumber 2,
there is brand product placement
for Cosmogor's in the background.
Ha ha ha.
And I just want to mention that,
like obviously the brand is getting out there.
People are becoming more aware of it.
That was a worldwide smash, I assume, Dumb and Dumber 2.
Yeah, well, not to get too morbid,
but as we learned this week, very sad,
The Rock and his family were fighting coronavirus.
But as you and I were simultaneously working
on this episode, it caught my eye
that he was wearing his TerraMana tequila hoodie.
And there was three picture perfect bottles
of TerraMana tequila in the background,
right in a perfect view of the camera.
Okay, so I like, look, I'm a big wrestling fan.
I was a big wrestling fan when The Rock,
it was The Rock's heyday.
I remember seeing The Rock at the Allstate Arena,
then probably the Rosemont Horizon.
I've never heard any person or group
get the reaction The Rock would get,
like when he would come out.
So I'm just saying I'm a big fan of The Rock.
So I follow him on Instagram now.
And one of the things I like is he posts his cheat meals.
Yeah, he goes nuts with those cheat meals.
Like he really cuts loose.
Yeah, for a while it was sushi.
He would go like, he would literally eat
like 70 pieces of sushi or a hundred pieces of sushi.
And then lately he's been making like giant pancakes
with just the most insane spread of peanut butter on them.
Like just insane amounts.
Like you would think it would be like half the jar
would be on these pancakes.
So I like following that.
Now I've noticed since the tequila,
it's always got, there's always a glass
and a perfectly placed bottle of Terra Mana tequila
in those shots.
So now he's posting like, you know what, I take it back.
It's pancakes, but it's also French toast.
I think that's actually what he's been doing lately.
He's doing this specific French toast.
And you'll always see a bottle of Terra Mana and a glass.
And there's always a little ad there.
He's always hustling.
You gotta respect the hustle.
As Rivers Cuomo said, you can't knock the hustle
in one of his famous songs.
So I have noticed that yes, product placement has crept in
to the formerly pure posts about cheat meals.
A lot of carbs, heavy on the carbs, those cheat meals.
Right. And believe me, I've seen those sushi pictures
and gone and gotten sushi because of it.
Like it gets me hungry for sushi.
So I get what he's doing.
Because like I ended up with a bottle of Terra Mana
and that was just sort of like I willed it into existence.
Yeah. Like that just happened.
That just came about.
So let's, so yeah.
Oh, so let's get through.
Do you have anything else you want to add
about Casa Amigos as a brand as the Gerbers, George Clooney?
You know what I'll say here
that we didn't get to the commercial real quick.
So there's a big famous story.
This is another thing I like about celebrity endorsed
anything is there's a lot of myth-making.
There's a lot of like one story you tell on press junkets.
And the story they love to tell on press junkets
is that George and Randy were out for the night.
They were tying one on and they both came back and George,
you know, or George and Randy both were, you know
three sheets to the wind.
So Randy said that he usually goes to the guest room
not to wake Cindy up when he comes back late like that.
In this instance, George went to the guest room.
So George got into the bed
because he wasn't going to drive home
and it was too far, whatever.
And Cindy came in at 3 a.m.
and she went over and thought Randy was in the bed.
So she got in the bed with George thinking it was Randy.
Now, what a cool, what a crazy situation this was.
They all had a good laugh.
It wasn't Randy, it was George.
I've seen this story written about
in I think at least five pieces of press from this website.
And now what a big, oh, imagine waking up with George Clooney
but it's not so bad to wake up with Cindy Crawford.
Like this is the narrative over and over again.
Isn't this funny?
I will also say side note that all of the press
for any of this stuff is all bought and paid for.
There's not a critical sentence involved
in any writing about anything here.
There's just no one has done any research.
It's just literally they spent a ton of money
on a Forbes article or their publicist did something.
Anyway, I mean, maybe you know,
the tequila we do know is perfect.
So maybe there's no reason to dig or anything.
Maybe there's no reason, yeah.
So, sorry, sorry, to cut you off real quick.
So this story, did you read this story?
If you're going to talk about the story,
I'll allow what you're about to say.
No, no, no, go ahead.
The only other story I found was how their line of mixers
and barware was through William Sonoma.
And it's like, oh, that's where I hit up
for my drink mixers, William Sonoma.
So you see this here, this YouTube link?
Yeah, yeah.
So this is 2013 and you hear the sexy music.
Randy Gerber goes in this commercial.
He opens up the door and Cindy Crawford,
his wife is in bed with George Clooney.
And they don't know, this is crazy.
Can you imagine?
Then they see a big glamour shot of Casamigos, the bottle.
And it says Casamigos tequila.
Now wait, that's not all.
Now George walks in.
He sees his then girlfriend, former WWE wrestler,
Stacey Keebler in bed with Cindy Crawford.
Can you believe this?
And George gives a huh.
And now we see another shot of Casamigos tequila.
But wait, there's more.
There's one more scene.
Here comes Cindy.
And now Randy and George are in the bed together.
Can you believe this?
And there's Stacey Keebler, George's then girlfriend,
former WWE wrestler.
This is crazy.
Jason, can you believe this?
Can you believe this?
This is crazy.
Perfect.
Can you believe this?
Jason, I don't know if you knew this,
Randy and George are boys.
Hi, it's like a perfect improv show.
It's everything you want.
Very crazy.
So there's a couple other commercials.
There's like a more standard, like what you would imagine.
Sorry, I'll share this one more time.
What you would imagine a sort of commercial
for a high-end liquor is.
We owe great times to good friends.
To the glasses that spark conversation.
To the ideas that then pour out.
Hours came from a night like that.
And somehow,
George and Randy are by the bath.
To make our own tequila.
Won't we be proud to pass around?
Yeah, so they're in the fields now talking.
Wasn't meant to leave our house.
But since we made this for friends,
we thought it wouldn't hurt to make a few more.
Oh, they're all laughing.
They're all friends.
Have a glass, amigo.
Our tequila is your tequila.
Our casa is your casa.
Oh my gosh.
That's all you want, right?
I just want to just run, drive through those fields.
Top speed on a motorcycle, no helmet.
Well, I mean, look.
I think we might have an opportunity
to do something like that, you know?
With like friends?
Like friends like say, this guy?
Or these two?
Jason is showing me pictures from the official PR
of Casa Amigos.
There's a picture here of Bono,
Randy Gerber and George Clooney all together.
Oh, is that William H. Mason and Felicity Huffman?
William H. Mason and Felicity Huffman.
And then on the house.
Oh man.
Oh, okay, it's good.
On the house of friends section on the website,
you can see the,
there's Vin Diesel with a drink at the Blood Shop premiere.
Kate Bosworth's birthday party.
Paris Hilton's birthday.
Lauren Conrad's birthday.
Which kind of fulfills my thesis
that the death of culture,
there has been no new celebrities since 2003.
That's possible.
Yeah.
But I mean, Pete Davidson's newer.
That's true.
And Post Malone is on that page.
So I guess you've got a couples.
There's a couple.
You've got a couple.
Not as many.
I agree with the majority of your hypothesis.
Yeah, so you'll find these photos
of completely candid moments.
Just so candid.
William H. Macy, Felicity Huffman
with three different bottles of Casamigos
in front of them on the table as they're cheersing.
That's candid.
There's no way that was set up.
Sure.
The Bono, Bono was holding a bottle
that does not look like it's been opened.
That picture with Bono looks like
they could have Photoshopped that into his hand as well.
It's very possible.
George's head too looks like maybe that was a stand-in.
And they Photoshopped George's face.
Yeah, I don't know if I trust that photo.
This photo looks odd to me.
That photo was from TMZ.
Hmm.
Well, let's get Harvey on the line
and let's see if Harvey can verify that this is authentic.
So yeah, so there's all this.
I mean, look, go to the Casamigos website.
We'll post some of this on Twitter
if you wanna enjoy all of this fun
with these fun celebrities.
Jason, do you have any more from the website
you wanted to talk about?
I think that's pretty much it.
Again, they got a brand partnership with Williams & Nova
where you go to get your glasses or your mixers.
I think that's, but that's kind of the meat of what I had.
Yeah, I just spent a lot of time on that website
watching those fun videos on a loop.
Right, yeah, so you can enjoy this
just like Jason and I did at your own leisure.
Whatever, at your own leisure.
Just enjoy it at your own leisure is what I'm saying.
Yeah.
But here's what I'm thinking.
And we talked about this a little bit.
And full disclosure, my father had a thought,
cause he listens to the show.
And he's heard all the Randy Gerber talk.
I don't think he necessarily knew who Randy was.
But my father said to me,
why doesn't podcast the ride have their own tequila?
And I said, that is a good question.
I love the sound of that.
And I share this idea with you.
Yeah.
And you were just as enthusiastic.
We're very excited about it.
Sure.
We're doing a little brainstorming.
And I think we've come up with what I'll say right now
is a good pitch.
You know, we don't have the full funding yet.
Maybe we need to find our Michael Meldman.
And I'll say this, right now only you and I
are involved in this.
Yeah.
Scott does, Scott Gerber does not know about this.
And we would like to officially extend the possibility
of him being part of our new endeavor,
but he doesn't have to.
I understand if he's busy and he doesn't want
to be part of this, we would love him to be there.
But we're gonna sort of give you a little bit
of a taste right now.
And we're gonna roll out some of the images online
on Twitter to try to get investors,
a Michael Meldman type involved.
And we of course thought the perfect name
for a podcast the ride related to tequila would be
Buenos Chicos Tequila.
Roughly translated, good boy tequila.
Okay.
Good boy tequila.
Think about that.
Think about.
Is that the name?
Is that the name we said?
Did I say a different name?
Possibly.
What was the name?
What was the name we actually agreed on?
Buenos Ninos.
You know, you're right.
I've actually gotten the name wrong already.
When I hurriedly wrote this part of the bit on my notes,
I wrote the wrong thing.
Jason is of course correct.
And look, there's gonna be hiccups in all startups.
So the official name is Buenos Ninos Tequila.
Good boys tequila.
Okay.
And I want to give everyone a little taste
of what maybe an ad campaign for this would look like.
And now before anyone comes out with us,
yes, we checked with someone who's Spanish is better.
The grammatical term is Ninos Buenos.
Ninos should come first.
But for selling liquor, it's probably not best
if the first part of your name is children, you know, or boys.
So we're having a little fun, just like Casamigos
just made a portmanteau.
They mushed up House of Friends.
They mushed up Casa and Amigo.
Right.
We're mushing up words.
That's the fun of Buenos Ninos Tequila.
Yeah.
So here, this is sort of like, imagine in your mind,
you're seeing like, you know, a guave.
You're seeing Jason and I on bikes
and we're going through fields.
And it's a beautiful, like beautiful cinematography,
like, you know, Roger Deakins style cinematography.
Okay. And then you hear this.
Buenos Ninos Tequila.
What does it mean to be a good boy?
Is being a good boy something you learn?
Or is it just something you are?
Is there a wizard in the hospital nursery
that grants special good boy status to newborn babies?
It's hard to say really.
We don't know.
And we probably never will.
But there is one thing that the family
of Buenos Ninos Tequila does know.
Great tasting spirits made from the finest guave
in the most unique recipe.
Our patented bottle of tequila
mixes half of George Clooney
and Randy Gerber's Casa Amigos Tequila
with half of the Rocks Terra Mana Tequila
to create a very special, very unique blend.
It's literally so unique, there's no way to reproduce it.
So here's to those wild nights.
And those slow mornings when yeah,
you might not be perfect, but you'll certainly be good.
Buenos Ninos Tequila.
Invest today.
So that's just a little bit of what
like an ad campaign would be like.
Okay. If I could give you
a little constructive criticism start,
we've been collaborating on this for a few days now.
We've been messaging back and forth.
That Black Keys song was so oppressively loud.
I have no idea what you said.
So. Okay.
Well, you'll have to hear the episode then I guess.
Okay.
Are you gonna be able to lower the levels on the song?
Oh, the levels will be fine, yeah.
Oh, okay, great.
Well, I'll listen back to the episode.
Yeah, believe me, whatever it was, it was very good.
Yeah, because I could tell it was very smooth.
Just like a smooth tequila where you remember
and you cherish the night before, you know?
There's no hangover.
Yeah, and yeah, we're going to, I think,
try to conquer the tequila market here.
Yeah. And I think, yeah,
we're gonna bring our goodness to this avenue, you know?
I think that Podcast Survive for Too Long
has not been able to share our brand of goodness.
And that's what we're gonna be doing here.
And that's what I'm very, very excited about.
Yeah.
And as I said in the commercial,
our special blend of half of Casamigos tequila
and half of Terra Mana tequila is very delicious
when you split them half and half.
It's like a perfect mix.
Oh, it's terrific.
Yeah.
So if, look, if you out there in listener land,
if you know someone who has a distillery,
if you know someone who's into a guave,
if you know a Michael Melman type,
if you know a Randy Gerber type, hit us up
because we want to make this a reality.
Yeah. It's time.
It's time for this to happen.
I mean, yeah, we have shirts.
We, you can have a button.
You can make like a pillow sham.
I don't know what you can do on T-Public,
but I think like, like,
I think the listeners will let us know,
would you be interested in Buenos Ninos tequila?
I think the answer is yes.
And again, let me officially say,
Scott Garner, Jason Sheridan, and Michael Carlson
formally invite you to be an equal one third.
Okay, well, you know what?
Let's, okay, you and I will have a slightly bigger stake
in this because we came up with it.
I'd actually, I don't think this is unfair.
I think that we should have, let's figure this out.
You and I will have 40% of the company each
and Scott will have 20 because he didn't come up with this.
So we formally invite Scott Garner
to have 20% of this new tequila venture.
You think that?
I think that's fair.
I think that's fair, but then if you and I share 40,
don't then we also have 20%?
Excuse me, I misspoke.
You have 40, I have 40, Scott has 20.
Okay.
I think it's only fair because we put so much work
into this pitch.
I think so.
I mean, we've been illegally crossing the border
at Tijuana, getting to the highlands of Jalisco
to visit the Agave fields.
Yes, and we've been breaking bread with the workers as well.
You'll see some of these photos on release day
and you'll be very excited.
And I think you'll get just as excited as we are.
So yeah, that's what we're thinking next.
That's what's next for the podcast.
Right, I know you were all thinking it too.
You were saying, when are they gonna do their own liquor?
And we're here, we're at that point.
We can't really do live shows.
I was really looking forward to going back to Orlando
or somewhere like that this year
and live venues kind of on pause at the moment.
So how can we share our love of good times
with the listeners, besides just the podcast
with a premium tequila?
Right, and I think, yes, as far as premium,
I think we're gonna go for the highest end.
I think a price point of $99.99 a bottle.
That's good, yeah, that's good.
Because people see, you see it's under 100.
It's under 100, so you don't think, oh no, three digits.
It's still two.
And yeah, that's what we're going after.
So if you're excited, just keep letting us know.
Please give us that feedback.
If you wanna even maybe tweet at Randy Gerber
or Michael Meldman and let them know,
maybe they would be involved.
I know Randy, he doesn't wanna get spread too thin.
But he's an entrepreneur,
and if he sees a brand like podcast The Ride,
I think he'd be very excited about it.
Yeah.
So, gosh, I mean, I'm exhausted.
I'm sweating.
It got dark while we were doing this.
Well, it was, I mean, we started happy hour.
We started at six o'clock on Friday night.
So I guess, you know, you've all survived podcast The Ride,
but you have yet to experience Buenos Niño.
Buenos, is it Buenos Niño or Buenos Niños?
Niños, probably, that's plural.
Buenos Niños Tequila.
So prepare for that.
So thank you for listening.
Thank you for enjoying.
And stay thirst, our new catchphrase,
stay thirsty, my friends. Stay thirsty.
It's fine, they can't copyright that, it's generic words.
Generic words.