Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast contains Eating Meals While Robots Watch, Stomach Scrapes,
Wayne's World Land, and one of the hosts reveals the childhood love of shuffleboard?
Which host could it be?
Eliza Skinner joins us to talk Kings Dominion and much, much more on today's podcast, The
Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the theme park podcast where sometimes we are so despondent
about the state of the world, we wish we could hide underground in the land of the dews.
I'm Scott Gardner.
Don't you feel that way, Mike Carlson?
Yeah, I was just saying this to Lindsay last night, that that's exactly where I would like
to go.
There are a couple places in the place we're talking about today that I think you could
hide though.
I won't say the specific one that Jason Sheridan, who's also here, is very excited about.
Yeah, this is a big park for me.
And I don't want to contradict what you said, Scott, but researching vintage Kings Dominion,
maybe the most at peace I have felt during the pandemic.
Except I will say this is the only theme park to give me a semi-permanent physical scar.
Whoa, really?
Yeah, it's like your action park.
Kind of.
Well, not quite.
Yeah, not on that level, though.
It's pretty minor.
I think it's faded at this point.
Okay, so faded, but there.
And I believe that our guest is a big fan and enthusiastic about this place as well.
She is the producer of Earth to Ned on Disney+, and she has an album out called
Regarding My Lovers.
It's Eliza Skinner.
Yay, it's me.
It's me.
I forgot to get even the like, slight amount of memorabilia to set up my...
Wait, yes, you have a hat on that you didn't have when we
began.
Whoa, Kings Dominion.
It says...
My co-Kings Dominion hat.
I have a bun on so I can't really wear a hat.
That's a really like, world brightening aqua color as well.
That's a beautiful shade.
Yeah, it's corduroy.
Like you want your summer wear to be.
Your summer hats.
You want them in a nice corduroy, nice wooly corduroy.
Yeah, that looks...
You have that summer heat up there.
Yeah.
Yeah, in this quarantine, as I have been putting on quarantine weight, I've been replacing
the clothes that fit me with oversized t-shirts from old theme parks.
Why am I having such a problem talking?
Bush Gardens and Kings Dominion.
Jason has just shared his screen with maybe what you're talking about.
This one is shipping to me as we speak.
Because I did that too.
Yeah.
It's a very mom shirt.
It kind of, yeah, I mean it's very 90s.
It is of course a Paramounts Kings Dominions, which was how I knew it.
I predate that.
You predate it.
I'm going for the Hanna-Barbera stuff.
I'm going for anything that looks like the animal that would have been attacking me
in the world of that ride.
So like your Grizzly, your...
This is mostly the Grizzly because everything else is.
The Shockwave, Avalanche, the Rebel Yell, which have they renamed that?
They should rename that.
They have renamed it, yes.
Yeah, it's called Racer 75 now and is still standing.
And they did the rename not even recently, like not even in the last year as part of
everyone should do these kinds of things.
It was several years ago, seemingly completely voluntary and out of nowhere.
So good for them.
Has Billy Idol changed the name of his, the Rebel Yell song?
Do we know?
Yeah, I think it's Defund the Police now.
Oh, okay.
He's pretty progressive.
Wow.
I'm glad he in England is tapped into our issues.
I guess it's their issues too, probably.
Yeah, yeah.
That's great.
So, all right, so you were on Doughboys and you were talking about King's Dominion on
there, which caused a listener on Twitter to set up an arranged marriage between us.
You must have Eliza Skinneron.
Why haven't you had Eliza Skinneron?
And my only answer is because we haven't met.
But if we...
Let's meet quickly and then we could do this.
And we did it.
We've made progress.
So you're welcome, whichever person that was.
Yes.
Yeah, I'm very pleased to be here.
Wonderful.
And now I've not had a chance to listen to that Doughboys, so I don't know your specific...
Oh, it's mostly me shit talking this podcast.
So yeah, you should have listened.
It's just, what do these guys think they know?
What a bunch of doinks.
Yeah.
My biggest fear is of what they think.
It's why I avoid it on the regular.
I turned it off at that part.
I was like, I should circle back around to this, but I don't know if I have time.
Yeah.
I mean, it's kind of a way of getting more podcast bookings.
I just neg other podcasts on each podcast appearance.
And by the way, never not funny.
More like never funny, you know?
Get rid of the not.
Hopefully they'll book me.
That should get them.
Talk to them next week.
Okay.
But so you did grow up with Kings Dominion.
So you're from that area, Virginia.
I don't know where it is.
This park is close to Richmond and kind of close to DC.
Yeah, I'm from Richmond.
So it felt like...
So Kings Dominion was the closest, but it felt to me as a child,
like I was just right between Kings Dominion and Busch Gardens.
And that's pretty much how I classified my place in the world.
Was this like your number one park as when you were a kid, or was it like just low?
It was close.
This a little of both.
I mean, I did Busch Gardens.
Williamsburg seemed like the fancy one because it's themed European.
So like each place you're going to is a different country.
And it's like, ooh, but Kings Dominion
you had more rides for your inch, square inch.
Also, as a little kid, they had a much better kids area.
So they had like a bunch of kids rides and a kids roller coaster that sort of like
could transition you into the world of roller coasters.
The Scooby Doo.
The Scooby Doo, yes.
A big favorite of mine.
Yeah.
Kind of big.
It was like a, it's not exactly a super small kiddie coaster.
No, yeah.
It is a decent sized wooden coaster, but that's what I rode a number of times
to work my way up to the Rebel Yell now Racer 75, which is very large.
Yeah.
No, yeah.
It's not like those kiddie coasters that you see on a boardwalk that'll just be like,
oh, they're going around in a circle, a little up and down.
It's a legit coaster that just got shrunk down.
Slightly and doesn't have any loops, but yeah, I felt like a real grownup
once I was riding the Scooby Doo.
There's not a ton in that genre, like the step up, like the PG 13 of roller coasters.
It's a kind of a, it's kind of a bear area.
It's not as either just kiddie or full tilt, super scary one.
Yeah.
So I feel blessed, honestly.
Big Thunder's a little bit of one.
Yeah, I would agree.
I was maybe the type of kid who Big Thunder was a, was an R or even an NC 17.
Whoa, really?
Then I, yes, I would say that's scandalous.
But then I was a very wimpy kid.
Can I ask what age you were when you went,
do we talked about this before when you went on Big Thunder?
Oh, maybe not until 13.
It wasn't, I guess, well, I guess so maybe you classify it as a PG 13 for that.
Yeah, for comedy's sake, I was hoping you said 17 or 18.
It was last week.
It was recently.
That would have been good.
But I can't remember.
I threw, got scared.
Just waving your arms up, please.
I can't, I can't, no.
Can I be airlifted out, please?
Dear God.
You threw clothes on the track to like trigger the sensors to turn it off.
You only have so many tools at your disposal.
You have to sort of MacGyver it.
Yeah.
I don't have that many things on my person.
Right.
Anyways, so yeah, Scooby Doo was like a kind of bridge the gap.
But there are some pretty like mighty coasters in this place.
How were you, Eliza, on that spectrum?
Are you afraid of these things?
Were you down for any of them?
No, I was very into it.
Very into them.
I mean, when I was before the Scooby Doo, I was terrified of all of them.
But then I got really into them, rode all of them.
Definitely had ones that I preferred.
Did not enjoy the shockwave, which I believe has been replaced because it murdered people.
But that's the mark of a good park to a degree.
Almost every park at some point in time, you try to avoid it,
but it shows that they're taking big swings.
Yeah.
I mean, fewer people than a highway and people are on those all the time.
So yeah, that's true.
It is.
I think we've done this podcast now for a couple of years,
and we'll talk about some dark topics like that once in a while.
But it is funny to just remember that we are building giant steel contraptions
to whip human beings around.
Like the this is very strange.
It's strange enough that we've done this podcast for years,
but think about what human beings have created
and continue to make new, faster, crazier versions of.
Yeah.
And I mean, I think that's the fact that more people aren't gravely injured on them.
That's kind of the amazing thing.
Yeah.
The ratio is pretty good.
It's a point.
Yeah.
And hopefully there isn't some turn where suddenly I guess during COVID,
they just let everything rust over and then they opened everything back up
and never worked again.
Yeah.
Trump Trump deregulated like some sort of code for rust on tracks,
which honestly, like not that far out of the realm of possibility.
Like we're ending the rust,
we're ending the stoppage of rust on roller coasters.
That is I know the supervillainy is such that yeah,
he might be pro roller coaster accident.
I don't know.
Nothing would surprise me anymore.
Yeah.
As long as we're as long as we've taken this turn into comically awful,
it would feel wrong for that not to be included.
Yeah.
Like.
Also, like poisonous cotton candy made out of bees or something.
Yes.
If you're dressed as a clown in a theme park, you also have to carry a knife.
It's just, it's a weight balance thing.
You'll fall.
You need to balance things out with a huge saber.
Mm hmm.
Well, and he made a point of, all right, if they're bees that help the environment that we need,
they should be killed off immediately.
But if they're key, if they're bees that surprise people and attack them,
especially within children's candy, we should breed them far more aggressively.
Yeah.
That's how we get stronger as a country.
Genetically engineered candy apples to have a razor growing inside of them.
From a seed.
From a seed, a razor seed.
Yeah.
And you know why?
Because why you can't stop us from doing it.
That's why.
Because that's America.
Yeah.
Well, these will all come true in a week.
Barrel like towards all of it.
You know, actually, just a quick side trick from King's Dominion,
because you also talked about, wait, it's Busch Gardens Williamsburg, correct?
Yeah.
The only time that that's come up on the show before is that we did an entire episode about
the Fabio goose incident.
Right.
I didn't know that that was there for a long time.
I just found that out kind of recently.
That was there.
We had this confusion when we had Dave Ferguson on about the Sister Park of King's Dominion,
King's Island.
I think he always thought it was there, but in fact, it was Busch Gardens.
So then you were if you didn't know it was there, then this was not a story that like
shook you to your core as a local.
This wasn't like heartbreaking to see.
Not as a local.
I remember hearing about it and being like, that's hilarious.
But I didn't remember that it had happened.
Maybe maybe I was still in a place where I was like, this is the whole world.
Virginia is all there is.
Of course it happened in Virginia.
Where else is it?
You didn't like call any friends to make sure they were OK.
No.
Yeah.
And we didn't have that feature on our phones yet.
So now, obviously, if something happens to Fabio, everybody can just click that thing,
check in and notify your friends you're OK.
We all have the alert.
We're all concerned about Fabio danger.
Anyway, so with that as a sidetrack.
Yeah, King's Dominguez.
So when did you go for the first time?
What are like early memories?
Early memories include going with friends when I was, again, very small in the kiddie park times
and having to have a stack of books in the back seat of my mom's car to read on the way there.
So I wasn't just like so excited to get there that I was like, are we there yet?
Are we there?
Oh my God.
So I would like plan out my OK, you've got a couple of Snoopy
pendiums that you can go through here.
This is you're going to make it.
And then my sister got a job there when I was, I guess I must have been like nine years old,
10 years old.
She was in one of the shows they had.
OK, so one of the big things that King's Dominion did for me was give me a love of
eating near animatronics.
I just like that that stepping into a very air conditioned place with these like clicking
old animatronics, trying to get you like worried about something.
I loved it.
And my sister was speaking our language.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
We all are not in agreement.
Yeah, I have.
I mean, I've also priced old tin and aluminum statues and animatronics from
King's Dominion before.
I'm like, I'm still not there in my career.
Oh, really?
How crazy does it get?
Where did it?
Well, there's just there aren't there aren't a lot out there.
People are holding on to their old singing mushrooms and stuff because that was a big
feature.
They had singing mushrooms.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I have a little singing mushrooms clip.
We'll get to that.
Oh, good.
Because I saw a picture of those and I was, you know, this is a big part for me, but
somehow I remembered quite a bit of it.
Did not remember those singing mushrooms.
I don't know how that escaped my view.
They were right by I believe they like a merry-go-round or bumper car, something that
had like a roof over it.
So it wasn't I think it was a station for the like gondolas, the like sky bucket.
That's what it was.
I remember the roof.
Yeah.
So I mean, I guess they're entertaining if you're standing there waiting to get on the
sky gondola.
But my sister got a job at a show inside of this jungle themed restaurant that had a
bunch of, you know, different animals and explorers like popping out of different parts
of the room being like, well, I'm a snake.
You better get a hamburger.
You know, that kind of stuff.
And the show that she was in on the stage there was a like it was like a review of
fairy tale princesses.
So sometimes she played Cinderella.
Sometimes she played a little red riding hood.
Sometimes she played, you know, Rapunzel, all that stuff inside the jungle themed restaurant,
which made no sense.
Absolutely no sense.
But when you have when you're looking to make shows for a theme park, you're going to be
dealing with a glut of pretty teenage musical theater girls.
So why not write to that?
Why not write together some shows that are like, this is definitely we can pull this off
with the high schoolers in town.
As opposed to some jungle show, like because then you need people to play like, you know,
like old explorers and like the big white hats or that's that's more of a stretch for
a 16 year old girl, probably.
Yeah.
Or animals, you know, some sort of budget jungle book type of thing they could have done.
Sure.
But then your face paint budget goes through the roof.
Yeah.
And your animatronics are doing most of that work for you.
So why double it up?
I did not learn about this jungle animatronic restaurant.
This is very delightful.
Yeah.
There was definitely an explorer that like popped out of a stew pot at one point.
Wow.
It was pretty good.
The Explorers stew pot.
What a weird old trope that I feel like there used to be like 70 movies a year that can add that.
Yeah.
And you know, I mean, obviously there's there are racist connections.
So it has it's good that it's died off.
But I also I feel like Bugs Bunny did a lot to make it stick around.
I feel like Bugs Bunny was just always ending up in somebody's stew pot.
Yeah.
Rabbits do, you know.
Right.
Was that was the stew pot like the really of six, 70 years ago?
Yeah.
It was well, I think actually we referred to it as that's got to hurt.
Which I hate to be hacky, but being cooked in a stew pot, that's got to hurt.
That's the whole point.
Yeah.
Look, when it's true, it's true.
I did your your sister enjoy her her role in this in this show.
Did she do it for a while?
She just did it for one summer and then she went to work at Hershey Park the summer after that.
Wow.
What happened?
Yeah.
She did a 1950s review.
So she was sometimes a nerd, sometimes a cheerleader, you know, sometimes a poodle skirt kind of Bobby Sox.
What was your reaction?
Were you like, this is awesome?
Yeah.
I was like, oh, my God, this means I get to go all the time.
I can go anywhere I want in the park.
I can get in for free.
None of those things were true.
None of them were true.
It was a huge disappointment.
I think I got to go like twice that summer.
And one of the first time I went, I actually won a prize at one of those games where you
have to hit a mallet onto a thing and it makes this little rubber frog flap onto a
lily pad.
And I won, I think it was like a stuffed alligator.
I was very excited about it and gave it to my sister to take home so that I didn't have
to like walk around with it.
They don't let park employees take home prizes.
I didn't get that alligator.
Oh, what?
Like insider trading or something?
Yeah.
Yeah, exactly.
So I was so upset about that for years.
And still, when I see that game, some part of me is like, maybe I get it back.
No, no, the time has passed.
I would be heartbroken.
That would never leave me if I had that happen to me.
That's also some ridiculous like King's Entertainment Company, like red tape.
That doesn't, she didn't, you won it.
She was like holding on to it for you.
But they had no proof of that.
And I don't know, maybe you could get really good at the games if you worked there and
game the system with their bad, cheap prizes.
I mean, it's not like they were giving out watches, you know?
This is not equivalent to McMillions.
This is not a massive.
Although anybody does want to invest in that type of a documentary, I'd be willing to go
along with that.
Yeah.
10 episodes minimum.
Much.
We haven't talked about like games, I think a lot of like prizes from Carnival type games
and even stuff like this where they cheap out, I feel like on plush.
Yeah, there's like sirefomi like crap in.
This was better than a lot of those like a state fair prize.
Definitely.
It's just like a cardboard box inside of it.
Right.
I do remember that this was probably the best stuffed animal that's ever been.
Was perfect and beautiful.
You're like half hour spent with it.
Yeah, yeah, that's what that's what got taken from me.
The best stuffed animal ever.
Was it the Hanna Barbera alligator?
What is his name?
No, it wasn't.
It was just generic.
No, yeah, just generic.
Yeah, it's really now.
I didn't realize we were opening up your like loss of innocence story.
It's OK.
Thank you.
Yeah, I also went camping there one time with Girl Scouts.
Camp there?
Yeah, they had a campground and they had this big Girl Scout thing where just tons of Girl
Scouts went and camped out and I was again so excited that I could not sleep and it rained
horribly so our flooded and I was just like, you guys, can you believe that we're going to
ride the grizzly tomorrow?
This is going to be so great.
And everyone was like that you're making it worse.
This is truly awful what you're doing.
But yeah, it felt like that felt like really being an insider.
At the park.
Did you ever consider also trying to perform there?
I mean, you're a very good improviser, musical improviser.
Did this?
Did you go, I got to get on stage here too?
No, I didn't because at that point, by the time I was a teenager, I wasn't really doing
that kind of performing.
I wasn't really doing musical theater stuff and it seemed like it didn't seem like my
sister had a great time.
It seemed like kind of a grind and I was like, well, I wouldn't want to turn something that
I love into that.
Plus, I didn't know that I had the chops for it.
I don't know.
I mean, interesting.
My sister's been Tony nominated since then.
Oh, I can't say that.
That right.
Wow.
Oh my God.
In hindsight, though, or right now, is there any role in a Disney park or in King that
you would go, you know what, I do this for a couple of weeks.
That seems good.
Yes.
I would definitely play the weird comedic part in any of them.
Like the girl who runs in and is like, what?
A time machine?
Guys, we can't do that.
And then someone else is like, stop it, Carla.
We're doing whatever we need to to go find them.
Hits of the past.
Yeah.
So that one is about collecting all of the greatest songs of all time.
For your time travel.
That would definitely work, right?
Yeah.
It seems that's pretty like what theme park shows are.
Yes.
Like we talked about those Disney Cruise Line musicals.
That's almost exactly what they're like.
Yeah.
Or like the Universal Studios show with all the, or I guess it's Islands of Adventure,
maybe show where it's like different monsters performing in a band.
Coming up on podcast.
Coming soon.
Yes.
Beeljuice's Graveyard Review.
Oh, yeah.
But they have it year round in the one in Florida.
It's not a seasonal thing and it's not so much about it, about the year review.
It's just like, hey, it's me, the bride of Frankenstein.
I think I could probably play guitar.
Oh yeah, because I'm the Wolfman and I can play drums.
And then they do a bunch of songs.
Yes.
They bulldozed it a few years ago to build a very, very poorly received Fast and Furious
slapdash.
That was that?
Oh no.
Oh yeah, we'll get into it.
Yeah, we'll get into it in that episode.
Oh geez.
Well also you have to think that being in a theme park show is the opposite of improvising.
I would say there is no room for improvising typically.
Yeah.
Well if you-
It's like whittled.
Yes, Mike?
I'm just going to say maybe the genie in the California Adventure Disney's Aladdin show
where he's dropping topical references.
I do think he has a little wiggle room.
He does.
To throw some stuff out.
But that's the exception that proves the role.
Like everything else is pretty well coordinated.
How much wiggle room is there with the Jungle Cruise pattern?
That's a good question.
I feel like you could probably get in like a couple sentences here and there.
I've been on different cruises where I go, this is-
I've been on one where it's like exactly what you think it is.
And then I have been on ones where they're throwing stuff in in between the normal script.
I think you can probably get away with it.
You just have to be smart about it.
There was a strange time where they rethemed everything to the 1930s due to the Indiana
Jones ride and they outlawed topical references entirely.
If it's not something from the 30s, you cannot bring it up.
And audiences hated it.
The people working there hated it.
This was a failure across the board and I think they reversed it at some point.
That's awful.
Was it all just like a pre-Nazi kind of jokes?
Seems like something weird is happening in Germany, but look, a hippo.
Like in the end it was mostly about that.
Yeah, it was mostly about pre-Nazi turn over.
Movies in color.
Get this one to the loony bin.
Scott, how much improvising were you doing on the studio tour?
Because Scott was a tour guide at Universal.
Would you, percentage-wise, how often would you go a little off script just for to say
something that might have you saw and wanted to comment on?
I wanted to do it.
I did more than I was supposed to because they threatened that they would secret shop
you and you could get in trouble.
I definitely tried to, but boy, if you were feeling lazy, there was a way to do it the
barest bare minimum humanly possible.
There were certainly ones where it's like, it's too odd to be funny.
But my favorite thing for sure was making up false info, if I could.
Like fun fact?
Yeah, I forget if I said it on the show before, but I made this whole thing.
There was a montage you could show about bloopers and I made up all this stuff about how bloopers
were named after a guy named George Bloop because he was the first actor to make a mistake
on camera because he transitioned from the silent era to the talkie era and he forgot
that he had to say lines out loud.
From then on, they were called bloopers.
That one was so dry and what movie facts are actually like that I would watch faces at that
one like, yeah, interesting.
I think that one traveled.
The first blooper was actually, oh, shit, I forgot.
I have to say things, right?
They were, he was also extremely profane.
Fuck, cock, sorry.
God damn it.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Is this a clean podcast?
No, it is.
It is not, except that there's at various points, guilt about people's parents,
our own parents maybe hearing it and being shocked that we've turned to profanities.
Mine don't because they're still on like burner cell phones.
They wouldn't know how to get a podcast if they had detailed instructions, but other ones do.
Yeah, yeah.
Jason and my mom, Jason's mom, they don't care for the cursing.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
No, you're fine.
You're fine.
Jason and I.
It's on you guys.
Yeah.
My mom sent an email about it saying like, it's not just me who doesn't like it.
Young people don't like it either.
And that was after she listened to a live recording of a sold out show that we had just done.
But were those the people who buy tickets so they can boo every time you curse?
Yeah.
Okay.
There was a little of that and I was wondering what the explanation for it was.
Yeah, that's what young people do.
It's cancel culture.
So the original cancel culture.
Yeah.
Tisking profanity.
It's a culture is mainly about getting people to stop saying crap.
I'm here and I'm a kid.
So sorry.
All right.
We'll be good.
We'll be good from now on.
Well, let's be here.
Let's be good by watching some like some very wholesome entertainment as alluded to
from the singing mushrooms.
And in fact, this is some very like parent approved material because that's exactly
what they're singing about.
And the voice that you'll hear at the beginning is a frog who is introducing some four singing
mushrooms who are multicolored.
Here's a clip.
Wake up, boys.
You're on.
I want a girl just like the girl that's very dear old dad.
She was a girl and we always grew up together.
It's an old barbershop.
I want to like the girl who married your old dad.
It's about wanting a woman who's like the woman.
So that's pretty wholesome, right?
I think he says he kind of grades them on the performance.
When I said I was moving to Los Angeles, this is what my mom dreamt of for me.
It's to be a frog in a top hat with a collar with like a cigar and a cigar.
Yeah, he's like a sleazy promoter.
Like he's going to get the payment run out on those mushrooms.
Yeah, he's a lot more mobile than the mushrooms for sure.
Yeah, he's like that partridge family guy, the dad who no, it wasn't a dad.
Scott, are you talking about Ruben Kincaid, the manager of the family?
There was maybe a point in time I could remember the name Ruben Kincaid.
But I feel like Ruben Kincaid was not crooked.
That's my memory of the partridge family, but I could be wrong.
It would have been a much darker show, right?
Yeah, I mean, that's for the Gritty reboot that's coming.
I don't think he was selling off partridges for other purposes.
Ruben Kincaid.
You sing when I say you sing, seven-year-old.
He was not like Lou Pearlman, I don't think.
Not with them, but maybe with some other families who he felt he could exert some more control over.
Scott, when you work on the young Ruben Kincaid spinoff for Peacock,
you can do whatever.
Kincaid, you can do whatever you want with that IP, okay?
Jesse Plemons, I think.
I think that's right, yeah.
Yeah, complicated depth.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You and you get the choice.
You get to pick which classic rock song is slowed down and whisper sung over the trailer.
Oh, yes.
Kincaid, yeah.
Well, it's got to be come on.
It's got to be like Partridge Fam, like,
Come on, there's a song that we're singing.
It's got to be something like, right?
Come on, get happy.
Yeah.
Piano single.
So ironic to hear come on.
Piano key.
You're sad.
Yeah, one key.
From Scott Gardner.
Very stirring.
Finally, my turn to Dark Showrunner.
But it still involves bell bottoms, so everybody's happy.
That's one form of entertainment.
Another that I'm very fond of that I'll just throw out.
I'm curious if Jason or Eliza ever got to see when Paramount came in.
So this was not a Paramount part, much like Kings Island.
You can check that episode out from a couple years ago.
But Paramount bought this park at some point and started installing Paramount properties.
And I think they really announced their arrival for the first time
in a big way with Paramount on ice.
Did anybody get to see Paramount on ice?
For sure.
Yeah, I brought it.
Yeah, it comes up on the Kings Island because that has the Star Trek ice skating sequence.
Yes, which might.
Did we talk about in the Star Trek one too?
A little bit.
It was a big Star Trek zone.
It was an ice skating thing at Kings Dominion.
Yes.
Yeah.
This is a park that is only open in the summer.
This is not like a year round park.
This is.
Yeah, it's welteringly hot.
Yeah, but like, why bomb there?
They've got a lake right there.
Make it a jet ski show.
That is a good idea.
I don't know if they had such a thing.
They did.
They had a water stunt show for a while.
Water skiing and yeah, just put those people in Star Trek outfits.
Same thing.
That's good.
They had it, I guess.
They had the facilities.
Wait, Jason, what were you saying?
Well, I was going to say, I think part of the appeal of the ice skating theater,
I remember going in there and the appeal of a lot of indoor places at parks located on
the East Coast in the summertime.
Virginia gets very muggy.
Virginia gets super hot and super humid.
So anywhere I feel like my family, yeah, we saw the ice skating show and I just remember
eating at Country Kitchen a lot because it had like food that you could tell was cooked.
Like it was good.
Like it was fried chicken and barbecue and everywhere else.
As a kid, I was very happy to eat pizza for most meals.
But my parents were a little frustrated by that.
That said, I did find a King's Dominion map where it just listed food items and like a
long list of like pizza, funnel cake, ice cream, hot dog.
And it would tell you every place you could get that one item.
And I don't know how that didn't become a theme park map standard.
Like that is a great idea to get a child to stop screaming.
Yeah.
I don't know if this was an era thing or a King's Dominion thing or what, but I do
remember getting popcorn shrimp for the first time at King's Dominion, which seems like
kind of an odd theme park food choice.
And it was from this stand that was like primarily popcorn shrimp.
Like that was, you know, they have those little round ones with the different lines
can come up and they just have buckets of the same kind of food inside.
Yeah.
Is it a popcorn shrimp stand?
I also remember at some point trying popcorn shrimp and it's seeming like exotic and me
thinking that this is adult food.
I bet as soon as an adult, I'll mainly be sitting on popcorn shrimp.
I'll move out of this whole chicken finger era that I'm still in right now.
Having gotten past the chicken nugget stages of my youth and eventually
arrive at popcorn shrimp, a true adult.
I could never never a full like roasted che.
That's for elderly people.
Maybe before I die, it'll be breaded up through my 50s.
I'll be married and have matured to the tender period of my life.
Very sweet.
I will wait just really quick before I move on from the ice show.
My favorite thing about the ice show is that it's a lot of I did like Shazam what some of
the songs were because it's not quite like Disney where you recognize the melodies.
I didn't know maybe other people without Shazamming it would know the theme from
Terms of Endearment.
I didn't know that score.
Oh, wait.
Yes, I think so.
Wait, that's a pretty famous melody.
Yeah.
I mean, if I'm right, I had a music box of it.
That was one of those.
I was a real music box head when I was a kid, too.
So a lot of the hits that way.
How many music box?
Great.
Like at least a dozen.
I started collecting.
I would also as soon as I had two or three of something be like,
I'm a collector of this thing now.
I must complete it.
And so every time I saw a music box on sale, no matter what it was, I would be like, yeah,
here we go.
You'd be surprised by what the musical contents were.
It's not like you bought it because it was Terms of Endearment.
No, no, no.
It would very often not have anything to do with it.
Like the outside and the inside.
Yeah, I was like, oh, great.
A sale Dick Tracy music box.
That will be what my allowance goes to.
For sure.
Do you still have that?
I don't know.
My mom contacting me recently and was like, what are you doing with these music boxes?
Get them out of my house.
So I might still have them.
I should I should find out.
It's a general stress for everybody.
The what do I do with my childhood belongings that the pain you're like, how do I?
It's hard for me to make this a priority to solve it, especially for you guys who
grew up across the country.
I don't like to think about even the stuff I have out here in L.A.
I was a collector, too, Eliza, and still have only partly shaken that habit.
And it's ruining my fucking life.
I have to do something with this stuff.
Yeah.
Yeah, I went through a big action figure phase when I was in high school also.
Every Christmas.
Just give the box away.
Just like, yeah, I wonder what it's like to have a really bad.
Actually, your problem.
I wonder what that could be like.
But we used to like drive around.
We knew which days the shipments were at different toy stores and we would like
drive around and look for specific short stack action figures.
Which figures were they?
Usually they were.
I mean, this is part of why I was into it.
Usually they were the female characters.
The short stacks would be so they would stack them in a box and, you know,
they would have like this size of a stack of Batman and like this many Wonder Woman's.
So the female characters were worth a little bit more.
So it would be like any any popular thing like Batman or
like whatever female characters in the line of that.
Yes, exactly.
Yeah.
Yeah, I think I had some Earthworm Jim stuff even or no, the tick.
I had the Queen Bee from the tick and a lot of different Star Wars things.
Yeah, it was it was weird.
But, you know, when you don't have anything to do when you're a teenager,
you're like, yeah, sure.
I'll spend Tuesday night driving around looking at the toy sections and Rite Aid and Toys R Us
and see if I can dig up something that feels special.
For sure.
I miss doing that during the pandemic.
Yeah, E-Bang and Amazon, isn't the same thing exactly.
OK, so one more thing about this ice show.
It's mostly like kind of love ballads and stuff.
But then there's a funny part with Frank Drebben from Naked Gun,
where which they can make it's like any ice skater with a white wig.
And he's like, he's doing like a parody of a romantic pairs figure skating.
But he keeps like falling over and tripping on stuff and pulling curtains down and like
yanking parts of her clothes off and her wig.
And it's good.
It's really funny.
Brought me a lot of joy.
I was like ready to judge it and dislike it.
But it was just very sincere or good ice physical comedy.
The ice clowning section of the show.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
You got to do it because if it's all if it's too serious to
and or too scary with all that Star Trek stuff and those Klingons.
Sure. Sure. Sure.
I mean, a lot of is it a Simpsons joke of like a theme park show called Hooray for Everything?
Like that is what like theme, especially King's Dominion or Hershey Park,
where they're only booking for like the summer season and they have a small cast.
It is a lot of like ages eight to 80 sort of stuff.
So are you getting a lot of Brill building like classics?
At least back in the 90s, you were getting a lot of standards and like early rock songs.
And then like there might be one like 80s rock song.
And that's the like, oh, that's that's to switch it up a little before we get back to to do Ron Ron.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, we had a budget and we decided we had to decide which songs to spend it on.
So, yeah.
Look, if someone can think of a motorcycle thing,
we got a bunch of handlebars from when we did the leader of the pack song last year.
Oh, we still have my boyfriend's back.
Also, great. Can we build something out from that?
Perfect.
The I'm curious what was going on musically in this show.
Flintstone Follies.
I would love to know what the rest of Flintstone Follies was.
Huck. I mean, this is and it's not just the Flintstone Tuckleberry Hound Yogi Bear.
Who's Jabberjaw?
Jabberjaw Hong Kong, Fui Hong Kong, Fui Hong Kong, Fui.
Yeah, it's everybody.
I mean, the whole you alluded to it at the beginning, Elizabeth,
but Hanna Barbera was was part of this park, at least in the early days.
And I got 35 years.
Hanna Barbera characters were there for 35 years, even after Paramount, they stuck around.
Why is some of us?
I'll be scooby doo and a convert got a Corvette.
Yeah, this is my favorite.
Yeah, I'm like luxury car.
Scooby Doo's posing next to it just like behind a building,
just like a place you'd go sneak off and smoke cigarettes and with a license plate, KD Scoob.
Yeah.
And my favorite photo in Hanna Barbera world is here's the gang, here's Scooby and Barney
Rubble and Fred Flintstone and a really strange flattened Yogi Bear.
Yeah, his head is too small.
That's not the proportions of I mean, he looks like a rock landed on his head and
crushed it down by.
Well, I mean, hanging out with the Flintstones, who knows, right?
You know what you're getting into.
I have I had framed pictures where my parents have had framed pictures.
They might have switched them out of me at different ages, one with
Fred Flintstone and one with quick drama grow.
And I believe the quick drama grow was partly because the friend that I had gone to
Kingsden and in with her brother was working there.
Her teenage brother was working there as quick drama grow.
So I remember talking to a guy in a suit and being like, hey, or no, I think maybe
she wasn't with me.
I just knew it because I remember going up to the some teenager in one of these suits
being like, are you are you Sally's brother?
I know her.
And the guy was like, yes, I can't, but I can't talk.
But stop.
He was doing a lot of shrugging and a lot of like trying to communicate no to me.
That's the theme park celebrity is a weird fleeting like it's the biggest kind of the
most accessible kind of celebrity when you're 12 and yet completely meaningless in the
broader spectrum.
And there was some local celebrity crossover in that there was a I believe Q 94, which was
the big, you know, pop music radio station booth at the bottom of the Eiffel Tower at
Kingston Minion.
So sometimes they would be broadcasting live from Kingston Minion.
And so when you're walking around, you can be like, whoa, that is a radio DJ.
Oh, my gosh.
What is this?
Hollywood?
Come on.
I bet he's he could see me and is probably talking about me eating these warheads outside
staring through the glass.
What are you showing us here, Jason?
OK, so this photo of a bunch of Hanna Barbera characters, you know, the whole gang, this
yogi looks pretty good.
Scooby looks like he has hives on his face.
But he's like, yeah, he has an infection.
He's like, be red.
I just remember as a kid, like this photo was on all the promotional stuff.
And I feel like I stared at this photo like I know this photo better than pictures of
extended family members.
I loved this so much.
And this might be a good time for us to talk about, because I cannot state how big this
park loomed in my mind as a child.
Like I live three hours away.
I checked the drive from my childhood home to Kingston Minion was just over three hours.
So it felt far enough away that was an event when we were going.
But it was close enough.
You could drive to it.
You didn't have to fly to it like Disney World.
Would you stay overnight there?
Yeah, we would stay overnight and usually make it a few day trip of a couple nights
at the and I found this.
I'm so glad I found it.
The best Western King's Quarters Motel just on the other side of the parking lot.
I am so was so excited to learn that not only is it still standing, the pictures from
the last few years show that it has not changed very much for better or worse.
Besides, I think it's a Wyndham now, but they had an arcade, they had shuffleboard.
It probably goes without saying I was a big time shuffleboard kid.
I mean, it does.
And yet I'm glad you said it.
So I was so thrilled to have an arcade and the shuffleboard and you got on a shuttle bus
that would take you right to the entrance of the park.
I believe Eliza, the campground, I think was adjacent to the hotel or was in the
neck of the woods of the hotel.
The King's Dominion was the home to one of my favorite places in the whole wide world.
Yogi's Cave.
Yes.
Let me try and share this picture.
This is what would greet you.
This guy right here, Yogi himself is outside fishing and unfortunately, it seems like all
he ever catches is a boot.
I believe.
Yeah, just up and down with that boot.
Up and down with the boot.
But yeah, Scott and Mike, I sent you a link.
There is a walkthrough video online of Yogi's Cave.
Yeah, if you want to share that.
Or we find out it's 35 minutes long.
I wish it was.
I could do an hour on Yogi's Cave.
Eliza, it's good that you're here or else I would just be telling my memories of this
park and telling them to shut up.
Is there anything particular you'd like?
Are we just going to enjoy this?
I honestly would rather see you playing shuffleboard as a youth.
So it's just like we're walking through Yogi's Cave here and it looks like it's fake rocks,
which we love on the show.
And there's families and there's like hieroglyphics in the cave.
Yeah, how he evolved and there's Yogi footprints.
So you could be like, I'm going to walk exactly on his footprints.
There's gems in the wall.
Did Yogi find gems on the cartoon ever?
Wasn't he just looking to steal someone's lunch?
This is just where he crashes, you know, swear him and his friends.
He could have been rich.
He actually could have been rich.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I mean, it's it also might have gotten ugly.
Those do appear to be uncut gems.
Oh, no.
Probably just as well.
So wait, Yogi then is Sandler in this metaphor?
Well, he's he is the calmer version.
He didn't go down that path.
There are animatronic frogs in this too.
So many animatronics.
You can stop it, Mike, because Yogi is not actually in the cave, really.
He's outside kind of greeting you.
Those frogs move.
There are more frogs.
More frogs.
Boo Boo is conducting them.
Is he?
Catch that.
It's really quick.
Yeah.
Are they all playing?
They're all sharing one big harmonica.
They're all sharing a big harmonica.
This is not actual.
This is like extended Yogi Bear verse because this never appeared in any cartoon.
There was never like his magical cave that was huge.
He was just like a bum that would run around and terrorize the ranger.
Right?
Like there was never anything.
But that's what they did with the E.T.'s ride.
That's true.
Yes, not in the original source material.
I mean, yeah, in a way, I guess that's kind of what you want is to expand the universe.
Show us more.
You show us more.
This is also this.
I watched an interview with the former head of King's Dominion and he described this place
as a tilt house because it's built on a very slight angle.
So you are off kilter the whole time.
You're leaning.
Yeah.
And it's just a walk there.
And I would just go in the this was one of the first rides where I was just go through
the entrance, go through the whole thing out the exit, wave to my family and go right back
into the entrance just again and again.
Why?
I just loved it.
I just loved I loved the music.
I love the waterfalls and the gems.
It was just like it was so great.
Were you a big Yogi Bear fan in addition to this?
I think everyone probably watched the cartoons and had some affection for Yogi and Boo Boo.
But were you particularly big Yogi fan or was it just the actual cave itself that
kept you coming back for more?
I liked I liked all the Hanna Barbera cartoons.
I mean, heavily syndicated when we were all growing up.
So like it was very excited to just go into a character's house, I guess.
And also this is likely an early exposure to like the theme park smells like I was very
cold.
The water smells like I was almost I was about to say with that waterfall part,
I would remember you would get like a little mist from that.
So when it was really, really hot, that was a whole reason to go through that alone.
Just the cooling waterfall mist.
Going into the character's house, I will say now that brought up a memory of
that being like an obsessive thought I had as a kid.
And I didn't have to because we went to Florida, we went to Disney World and they had like Mickey's
Birthday Land, which had a little Mickey's house, but it wasn't Toontown, which I would read about.
And I thought, of course, I'll never go there.
We don't go to California.
So I was like obsessively thinking like you're going to go into Goofy's house.
I love Goofy.
I'd love to go in his house.
I want to see where his bed looks like.
Yeah, Disney cribs.
Yeah.
Yes.
So I get that.
So it was Yogi.
It was like Yogi's crib.
Yeah.
And Boo Boo was there.
There was a couple of generic bears just kind of around too, just so they could kind of pat it out.
But I think I just like the off kilter feeling and the yeah, just seeing some of the Hanna
Barbera characters.
And it's called a tilt house.
That's what he called it.
I'd never heard the term before.
I think like fun house kind of.
We just heard the term madhouse for the first time on the Europe episodes, which is like a whole
when it, what was it described as when like the walls kind of spin and keep where you are stationary.
Yeah.
I'm wondering if tilt house and madhouse.
I like the house genre is something we need to investigate more.
Yeah.
For sure.
So like when you would see yourself walking, when you'd see people inside, when you were outside
and you're getting ready to walk into it, they all looked tilted because they were
tilting to like keep themselves.
Right.
Balanced.
So it had kind of a like, oh, like mess with your equilibrium.
Yeah.
Which was fun.
And that was great.
This is like in camera effects.
Yeah.
And they, I think the very first time I went, I was super like kindergarten young and
would have been, we might've gone once right before Paramount took over
and then Paramount took over.
And that to me, it just, in my mind, it just like upped the game because
I started to know like movies, studio, like I was like, oh, Disney is movies.
Universal is movies.
Paramount is movies too.
So then when you get Hanna Barth characters, yeah, it's legit.
So then I became a weird little kid who didn't want to just
tell all its relatives about Yogi's cave.
He wanted to tell them about the days of thunder simulator attraction.
You might remember days of thunder, the 1990 Tom Cruise, Nicole Kidman.
Wait, that's where that was?
I definitely wrote that.
Oh yeah.
I remember when that was new and it was like a big fucking deal.
And yeah, it was all the radio commercials were like days of thunder.
Yeah.
Yes.
So you were excited about that just as much as you were about Yogi's cave.
Days of thunder and Yogi's cave.
And I really liked the motel, even though we would constantly be switching rooms
because my mom would be like, we asked for non-smoking.
There's ashes.
There's a full ashtray that smells like cigarettes in here.
You're in Virginia.
Yeah.
That's what I...
Well, the funniest one we had, we checked in once and we're like, the floor is...
Has popcorn on it.
What's up?
Did you not want it like that?
Did you not want a popcorn room?
Okay.
Well, specify.
Just in a bag or on a shelf or I don't know what you were expecting.
Yeah.
Virginia, you're going to have smoking sections everywhere.
When I was a kid also, we would have more than once.
Multiple times I had field trips to the Philip Morris plant and you would get to tour and see them.
Yeah.
See them making those.
And then you would get, when you left, every kid would get this big pen
that has all the names of the brands around it.
So it'd be like medicine and hedges.
Marlboro.
So everybody's house had tons of these huge oversized novelty pens with cigarettes.
And apparently, according to my sister,
teenagers would actually be given cigarettes as their leaving gifts.
Great.
Wow.
We should have done this as a topic for today's episode.
That's a themed experience.
Morris plant tour.
Yeah.
You're on a factory floor watching people make cigarettes.
Wow.
Sure.
But you did ride a little, there was a little tram that they would drive you around in.
A cigarette tram.
Wow.
So that means in Virginia, you could go to the Philip Morris factory tour and then go
to Bush Gardens and go to the beer brewery tour.
Yeah.
Wow.
And that would have been on the way too, I believe.
Well, sort of.
Yeah.
Not quite, but you definitely could do that in one day.
Here's your future.
Cigarettes or beer or both.
You choose.
The future is bright.
Or a shot.
Or hang out with some Navy guys.
That is, yeah, that was our full trip.
We would do a couple days at King's Dominion, a couple days at Bush Gardens,
and one begrudging day at Colonial Williamsburg.
Boo.
Which, I was a nerdy kid.
I liked history.
But when you grow up in the original colonies, it is a little, it's like, well, it's everywhere.
It's interesting.
I like this.
But it's not a theme park.
No.
Come on.
You're not going to compete with Yogi's Cave and Days of Thunder.
Get out of here.
Yeah.
I mean, so you see somebody make a candle and that's the highlight of your day.
When in the distance, you can see Bush Gardens.
That would be the thing that would drive me crazy.
Every time I had to go to Colonial Williamsburg for anything, I'd be like, I can literally see the fun.
It's that close.
Why can't we just go do that instead?
My parents made a lot of, my dad's a filmmaker and so my parents made a bunch of films for
the Jamestown York Down Foundation.
When you go to a museum or reenactment place and they're like, this is what it was like.
Here's the story of Jamestown.
My dad made those.
So I had to spend a lot of time there just like hanging out in break rooms,
watching reenactors drink diet cokes in between their shifts.
And I was like, wow, if this couldn't, if I, if any kid thought this couldn't get more boring,
guess what?
It can.
Well, for little Scott, I was a history buff.
I talked a long time ago about how I, there was a video that I saw at the Independence
Hall in Philadelphia and my mom and I liked it so much that we bought it and made my class
watch it and we returned.
And it was like, this is from Scott and Mrs. Gairdner.
And then it's the dullest, most morose, smoky old movie you've ever seen.
So I would have loved that.
What did you like about it?
Um, I don't remember now, um, because now I like it because it's weird and sad and morose.
Why would I have liked it then?
I think it was like, I think ghosts were involved.
I think it's like, well, John Adams walking around these grounds where I used to step
and where I dreamed of democracy.
Paranormal.
That's a fun twist on it.
Yeah, it was probably that ghosts of history appearing to me.
Yeah, I'll send you a link to one of my parents.
When somebody sent it to me recently and was like, Hey, here's this thing where I was an
extra in your parents, um, history movie.
It's it's streaming for free now.
And I was like, well, okay.
Yes.
So it was like period movie.
It wasn't about like, here's what James sounds like now.
It was like, here's a full period.
I think I would have loved this.
The Skinner family output.
Yeah, they made one and then they like had to do an update on it.
And then there was at one point they also reenacted the voyage and my dad made a documentary
about the reenactment of the voyage, which that was more about like, here are some modern
day sailors on an old ship.
What was it like?
But my mom has even seen these things independently and she's a teacher.
She probably she may have shown these things to her students.
Well, my dad's day job was working for the State Department of Education in Virginia,
making educational films.
So they're so probably.
Wow.
Yeah.
Any like crazy ones, but like not doing drugs or not huffing paint or morals.
A lot of those, a lot of things about like, here's the new way that we teach math.
Here's a like, so it would both be like things to show kids and things to show teachers and
things like about what's happening in schools.
I was definitely in one about something about like guidance counselors.
I remember trying to be like a cool kid and being like, what do you even
what's a guidance counselor even for that kind of stuff?
It was your idea of what a like what the cool character is in the theme park show.
I guess you have like, it's like to to really pop and be cool.
You have to have this.
The voice has got to go up an octave.
You need a little attitude.
That's that's that's that's 80s acting, I think.
There's not anywhere close to like organic in the moment.
It's like, hey guys.
Also, there's a lot of crossover between just general child acting and theme park acting.
That's the same style in many ways.
That's the bridging the gap like Scooby.
Yes, it's like it's performing and being confident, but it's not.
You're not exactly doing Noah Baumbach style.
Yeah, the very understated Flintstone Follies.
You know, now that I say that, I'm like, why did I pick him of anyway?
That basically is theme park acting now that I say it.
I want to see a theme park show about a teenager trying to silently process his emotions about his parents divorce.
The squid in the whale starring Bam Bam and Pebbles.
Hey, you're no whale.
He's a shark.
So you guys don't like the sad theme park stories I'm getting.
Oh, I don't know.
What do you what do you got?
I'm curious.
We just did action park where a bunch of a ton of people died.
So we're mired in it right now.
This is maybe sadder than people dying.
And also, this is kid rumors.
I think this actually might have made the news though.
They had a dolphin show right underneath the shockwave, which was the standup coaster.
And those dolphins died.
Those dolphins died because that's not where dolphins are supposed to live.
Underneath the standup coaster.
Well, I mean, similarly, there was that we haven't talked about lion country safari,
a whole like lion drive through lion place that they had.
And lions don't want to have cars by them or know how to deal with it.
So eventually, like they would just start standing up on the cars and go to sleep on them for a while.
So then it became a monorail through a grounded monorail through.
I guess you've done this at some point in time.
Yeah, I did that monorail.
And I think I did it once and just hated it.
And I also I do.
That is one of the things that every now and then I'm like, where was that?
Where geographically for the rest of the park was there suddenly a safari?
I have no idea.
Yeah, I was trying to remember a lot of these parks.
These older parks that I went to as kids.
I I a lot of times I will think back to them.
And then when I find videos of them, it's like, oh, I was nearly right, but it was reversed.
It was on the left side of the Eiffel Tower.
Wasn't on the right side.
Like, for whatever reason, I did remember a lot of the King's Dominion stuff when I found old pictures and videos.
But I whatever for whatever reason, I pictured everything was to the right of the Eiffel Tower.
And it's like, no, that was a smack in the middle.
Some stuff was left, some was behind, some was to the right.
I would guess that's probably that that was the route that you like to take.
Because for me, if I'm if I'm entering and I'm looking at the Eiffel Tower,
I think everything is to the left.
We said the right, right?
But that would be that's because when I first started going there, that's where Hanna Barbera land was.
Yeah.
So that would always be where I had had.
And then you go through that to get to there is a lot of
a lot of mountains and rocks.
Like when you said you liked rocks, there are all of you, I guess.
They had tons of fake rocks at this place.
There were three rides.
They were all inside one mountain, supposedly.
That was the best.
The Haunted River Smurf Mountain for a period of time.
Wow.
And then I forget the third one.
Well, it changed around.
There was Mount Kilimanjaro for a while.
And there was the Time Machine, which I think Mount Kilimanjaro became the Haunted River.
The Time Machine was one of those ones where it spins around and it sticks you against the wall.
Yeah.
And so that one didn't the line didn't move very fast for that one.
And I liked it a lot.
So I remember being in that line a lot.
And you would go from being in the line outside to being in the line inside surrounded by all this fake rock,
which is all absolutely covered by inches and inches of gum.
That was like part of what you did at King's Dominion was stick your gum to the wall by the Time Machine.
And yeah, before the Smurfs were the Smurfs, they were the Doozers.
Oh, yes.
Well, from my opening joke, there was a ride called Land of the Doos, Journey to the Land of the Doos.
That's D-O-O-Z.
And it's so confusing because all right, Smurf Mountain, that's the Land of the Doos.
Is the real Smurfs.
Doozers, is that like Dooser or like Fraggle Rock?
No, it is not.
Oh, they were just weirdo skin people.
They were just these weird little like goblins.
Like you want your little things to be fluffy, I think.
Right.
Yeah, that keeps them up.
This was not that bad.
They were not.
Yeah, like weird little.
I was describing them to my wife as like little Ziggy's.
It's a whole race of Ziggy's.
Yeah, they didn't even have like.
And a little more holbous than Ziggy.
Yeah, because they were all bald too, right?
They were.
Yeah.
Yeah, I think so.
Like pretty hairless for the most part.
And they were like weird hats and it looks like wigs essentially.
But the point of the Doozers is that they are a tribe of creatures who live beneath the surface
of the earth and they make the world work.
So they crank big gears that make the world turn.
They push up plants, which makes them grow.
They die in the Red Sea.
They manufacture water and air.
They clean the Statue of Liberty's feet, which are not actually underground,
which was a surprise to me when I found that out.
Wait, I have a shiny thumbnail of that.
They're like they're putting like nail polish on it.
Do you have that available?
I didn't see that.
Pull that up.
Hang on.
I'm not into, remember, I'm not into foot stuff or anything.
I just wanted to see this picture.
Yeah, why are you so voracious?
You're making me do work to see these feet.
Oh, yeah, I did not see that.
That's weird.
Yeah, wait, the feet.
Well, they stole the feet.
They stole the fireman.
They're foot freaks.
Yeah.
When you're that little, I mean, this is combining several fetishes, I think.
Yeah, there are like a couple of them in the background jerking off on the feet.
So at least there's acceptance.
Yeah, this.
So they're the proletariat is what we're saying.
And forced to live underground in poor conditions and they
don't individually get credit in the way that Professor Back and Forth does.
Well, they run old faithful probably for no money.
Maybe they get tossed a yogi gem every once in a while.
How much can you do with that?
Yeah.
So yeah, when this became the I'd never like the Smurfs.
So when that ride became the Smurf ride, I was like, oh,
so the bad ride became the worst ride.
No, thanks.
Yeah.
Oh, this, by the way, is some sort of design card ride design for one of the things that was
at some point in that mountain.
It was like a journey through.
Atlantis?
Early Earth.
Yeah, supposedly.
That's amazing.
Yeah, you're showing us a real nice framed art, like concept art here.
That's a well, it's a shitty frame and it doesn't.
I put it in there myself.
But yeah, where does that come from?
How did you get your eBay?
So like, it might not be real, but I think it looks cool either way.
So I'm putting that up.
Yes, you have delved into like Kings Dominion Merchant History.
Wow.
Yeah, I'm not wearing my I have a little necklace that has
you remember those spoons that you would get places?
They're like your novelty souvenir spoon.
You know what I'm talking about?
I know what you're talking about.
Yeah.
So on the top of those, the cheap ones, it would just kind of have a little stuck on button
that was like that would say whatever it was.
And they would also sometimes make jewelry out of those stuck on buttons.
I'm taking a long way around here, but it's how I thought of it.
I've got a necklace, a Kings Dominion necklace also that has the Eiffel Tower.
It says Kings Dominion, and it's so teeny tiny that people can't tell what it is.
So they're like, oh, nice necklace.
I'm like, well, it's from a gift shop and it costs three dollars.
And I'm a real freakazoid to be wearing this at a fancy party.
That's cool.
Yeah, I know.
Yes.
No freakazoid here.
Can I get your thoughts on this current eBay item for sale?
It's a little frog.
Oh, I like him.
Magnet frog that you can hang up.
Yeah.
How else?
Kings Dominion.
Are you bidding on that, Jason?
No, I thought about it.
I don't know what I'd do with it.
I guess you're supposed to hang them on a doorknob.
I kind of remember these being like souvenir things.
So you would hang them on a doorknob and then you get a little bit happier all the time.
Anything that can do that.
I mean, so here's my Loch Ness Monster hat since this is a visual podcast now.
What's Loch Ness Monster from?
That's from Busch Gardens.
That's the big coaster at Busch Gardens.
Oh, gotcha.
And I'm trying to see if I have this one other thing I've got to.
Oh, yeah.
It's the wrong Busch Gardens, but it's a Busch Gardens Tampa, Florida.
A big like platter from Tampa.
Yeah.
Tip of the iceberg.
I got a lot of this junk because I'm like, especially now, like,
whatever will make me happy.
And the theme parks of my childhood are what make me happy.
When I was a little kid, I was just so obsessed with theme parks and no one in my family liked them.
So I remember my school lunchbox was a Walt Disney World lunchbox.
And I had never been, but I was just like, this is the dream.
I would collect pamphlets from different theme parks and just like, look through,
like lay them out and look through them.
Be like, someday Hershey Park, super duper looper.
I don't know what you feel like.
Have you made it to all the ones you wish to have made it to or are there ones that have eluded you?
Yeah, I think so, because also once so many of them transitioned to Six Flags,
I was like, not as excited.
I like a standalone place.
I haven't been to Action Park and that does, that's that that eluded me.
But Knott's Berry Farm, that would be that's a fun one.
Also, I like the ones that have characters and shit that aren't attached to anything.
So the fact that Knott's Berry Farm, when I was like really little,
I had a comic book of Knott's Berry Farm that was about the Knott's Berry Bears.
And that was another thing I would sit and read it and be like, man,
sometimes got to visit these bears.
Oh, and you probably didn't make it to Berry Tales because they were they've been going
for a long time. Berry Tales, though, is coming back.
Yes, but in a weird, suspicious of what it is, aren't you?
Well, of course, it's a 3D like CGI Berry Tales ride.
But it's not going to be.
It picks up the story.
Again, it's another I guess this is quite a genre, the factory of like maybe undervalued,
you know, like individual personalities are not encouraged.
There's a lot of like just sad, begotten factories in theme park.
I guess I'm projecting that they're sad, but I don't know those deuces.
Of all the theme park factories I've seen, the deuces seem among the most miserable.
Well, Scott, you mentioned sad factories, but it was a poor city safety ordinance that injured a
young Jason Sheridan. I'm, of course, talking about Nickelodeon Splat City.
I will share a picture with you guys.
So some background, as we said, Paramount took over ownership of these parks at a certain point,
and they started adding more and more stuff.
Your Days of Thunder, your Days of Thunder, your Days of Thunder, your Days of Thunder,
your Wayne's World, your Nickelodeon.
And they added this Nickelodeon play area, which you can all see now.
It's perfectly safe. I don't see what the issue could have been.
Was that at the same time that they had it at the Mall of America?
I wasn't because Mall of America has gone back and forth on Nickelodeon and Snoopy, so I'm not
sure on the timing. But this got added by the Hanna-Barbera stuff and its big water play area.
So somewhere in this maze, it's kind of a little maze you go through and you get blasted with water
from pipes. There was a chain link fence covered in green plastic. If you can picture that sort of
green plant, you would see it like athletic fields and stuff. And I ran by that fence,
not realizing there was a jagged piece of it sticking out. And it kind of like cut me along
the stomach. Not deep. Not deep. It cut like very fine. Like, Mike, you talked, maybe talked in the
past the pro wrestling term blading, where someone hides a razor blade and does a very fine cut.
I essentially bladed across my stomach and it caused not a lot. Okay, it wasn't a lot of blood,
but it was just a continuous stream of blood. And I, first off, I had to get out of the water maze.
So I got blasted with chlorine water a couple times before I could get out. And then I found
my parents are like, oh yeah, that's not good. And we were like cleaning it up and it would not stop
bleeding. So I had to go to first aid and they use that like liquid bandage on it. And it sealed it
up and it did like heal pretty easily. I didn't have to go to the hospital or anything again,
but this was like an inch and a half long, like white scar I had on my stomach for years.
Wow. Really? Yeah. That's like Dr. Grant taking the velociraptor claw at the start of like,
that's where I was basically. Like if an animal was going to kill you, that's where they would
have attacked. Pretty much. Yeah. Was it a warning shot from a lion or anything?
I think I probably started like really detailed, like, okay, so, okay, King's Dominion added an
additional Nickelodeon area in addition to the existing Nickelodeon stuff. There's a busy world
of Richard's scary cafe next to that is a water. So there's a chain link fence. Like I probably gave
them the whole step by step. Yeah. It's near Yogi's cave. Have I told, I have told you about Yogi's
cave. Okay. Got it. Ah, yes. The child date talk. Jason, have you checked, is it, you don't need to
do it here, but have you checked, is it completely gone? The scar? I, I, I think it might be gone.
It's hard to tell because I have a hairy belly now as a man. It's hard to see. Well, what do you want me to call it?
I have a hairy belly. So, but for years I had that like white scar. That was always a reminder of King's
Dominion. And otherwise I don't think we had a lot of like, oh, so and so got sick after this ride.
I don't think we had a lot of like, besides just the general like heat, like, oh, I'm going to go back to
the hotel. Like, I don't remember a lot of like friction at King's Dominion. I lost $20 in a bathroom
there once. Like I left my wallet in there and I think then I got the wallet back, but it was minus $20.
That was, that was pretty, that's the worst as a kid. That was so much money. Yeah. Yeah. I just recently
remembered when I lost $80 when I was 16 and I remember it was like a bigger crisis than like
anything has been in the last five years. Like nothing in having a baby was as stressful as the 16 year old losing
$80 at the time. Yeah. It was so much money and you're so disappointed in yourself and yeah. Oh yeah.
It's what you run through mentally. You idiot, you stupid idiot and you're ugly too. No, you're
going to date you either. You'll never see that money again. I had an even stupider version of that
happen. Like same about age, like 60 or 80 bucks thought I lost it and it turns out I had just wedged
it in the VHS box that I used to constantly tape the Daily Show with Jon Stewart. And so found it
three months later when I went to reuse that tape again. Well, that's just a treat for you then.
It was a happy ending, but I was like, why would I shove money in a VHF that is what the, what was
I thinking? You're mad at yourself now. It was just like all of us. Yeah. These are raw memories. I
just wanted to laugh. You know, I just wanted the money and I just wanted to laugh. To play clips of
hypocrisy, dreaded politician hypocrisy. It can't get worse than this. I said,
the irony. It's a different time. Jason, you brought up something and now I can't, you said the
sweetest words and I can't not go into it now. I figured I teased it because I think it came up just
when we were in conversation about doing this. Oh boy. The sweetest fruit of this paramount takeover.
The outer limits, flight of fear. I'm the most mad I've ever experienced. That I didn't get to experience
a themed Wayne's World area, a Wayne's World roller coaster. Oh my God. The hurler. I'm so delighted
that this existed. And I think what I didn't realize until I watched a commercial with Mike
Myers himself as Wayne is that this was an entire themed area. That there was the restaurant too.
There's the restaurant with the hockey player and the little speaker booths where Wayne does
his hijinks. If you did it in person, you got to tell me what was up with Wayne's World.
I was young enough that I knew Wayne's World from TV commercials, but it didn't really track for me.
I didn't really... That was an adult movie. Yeah, it was an adult movie. I may have seen
Mike Myers because they just showed... So I married an axe murderer on Comedy Central so
much when I was a kid. That's right. Yeah. But yeah, I remember the hurler. I thought it was a funny
name for a roller coaster. It's so good. I love that there was this and that there was a themed
restaurant to go with it. It looked so perfect. There's also apparently something called the
Rock Shop where it was decorated with huge logos of bands of your nine inch nails and your chili
peppers. And then my favorite thing I discovered about it is that there was, for the opening day,
they had from the cast of the film, Tia Carrera and not Mike Myers or Dana Carvey,
but rather impersonators. Here you are looking at a fake Garth and a fake Wayne who looks like
one of the Lawrence brothers. I'm not sure if it is. He really resembles him. And then my
favorite thing is fake Wayne riding the hurler with a visibly annoyed Tia Carrera.
So put off by this guy, which you can only... I mean, I just... The point of Wayne,
Wayne seemed very good natured and sweet, but the way this guy's doing it, even just from the photos,
he seems to be kind of a pest. And just imagine if you're trapped with this guy on a ride and he's
saying, swing over and over. And you have a bar preventing you from leaving.
And she's not playing Cassandra. She's playing Tia herself. She's not part of the cosplay.
Yeah. She's really from the movie. She deserves better than to be palling around with a...
You don't get the feeling from this photo that she knew that there were going to be impersonators
there. What if she... The worst thing would be if she got on the ride, he was facing the other way.
She's like, oh, did they get Mike to come in costume and then he turns? Oh no.
He said it wrong. He said, swing. That's not it.
This impersonator sucks. Yeah. It's... He does... While he might not be
getting the best Wayne attitude across, he is getting the best
King's Dominion goer attitude across. This just looks like every guy who was at King's Dominion
all the time. Oh no. Yeah. Wait, were you there in teen years and wanting to date or avoid dating?
I was there more pre-teen. By the time I was a teenager, I was a punk rap kid. So I
was doing that instead. But when I was 11 and desperately wanted to be a teenager in love,
yes. While there would be teenagers waiting in those zigzaggy lines to go on a ride,
making out or putting each other's hands in each other's pockets or playing with the
fringe on their fringed t-shirts. I was the weird tubby little 10 year old behind them being like,
yeah, look at how in love they are. Someday it'll be me. Yeah. I hope somebody kisses me
in the line for the grizzly someday. And never happened. Guys, never happened.
Because I always wanted to go on the Matterhorn, which had lap seating. And I'd go like, when I can
date, I'll have a girl of my dreams in my lap. And that'll be romantic and not like just strange
for 20 seconds. Was there like, all right, the place in King's Dominion would be? I don't think
there was a place, but definitely just like the general concept of a teenage boy in a sleeveless
Metallica shirt kissing me up against those steel bars that you're waiting for that made the maze to
get onto the ride. Just like there's an eight year old me going like, let's keep the line moving.
Come on, we have rides to ride. I'm bleeding from the stomach.
I believe from the stomach, the action theater is closed. I'm not going to get a chance to ride.
Stan Lee's the seventh portal. You know, I'm not in a good mood. Don't make out against
just anything. Might cut you at the stomach. Yeah. There was also a kid rumor that there was someone
whose job it was, I think this might be what I said on Doughboy, someone whose job it was to go
around at the end of the day every day and hammer the nails back into the grizzly. That was one of
the two wooden coasters. As though if that person wasn't there for their job that day, we're all
going to die. There's just nothing that could be done. It shakes the nails all out of it.
Be like, slept in and didn't go instead of just being there but stoned as usual.
Yeah. There was also an old west stunt show. That was weird. And that was way before it was
Paramount. There was no movie connection at all, but they were still like, we're going to show you
how people pretend to fall off of stuff. You get the like the whole side of the building falls
and you land exactly in the window. Not that good. That would have been too complex.
There was some very odd, the Paramount stuff just got odder and odder over the years. Of course,
the Italian job turbo coaster eventually renamed to the back lot stunt coaster. The one that sticks
out in my mind, we were there the summer it opened. I remember my dad, he rode it himself and I
waited at the exit and I just thought it took forever. Did something happen? It was just like,
oh no, I just didn't have a watch and I didn't know how long 40 minutes was. The Outer Limits
Flight of Fear, an indoor launch coaster, which I could not get anyone to tell me if it went upside
down as a child, I was scared of going upside down. But this ride almost came up on the Mummy
Returns episode because it was the first launch coast, indoor launch coaster that used linear
induction motors, which we admitted we do not know how that works, but was kind of historic.
Yeah, very cool. And Premier Rides, the manufacturer would go on to make the Mummy,
Revenge of the Mummy ride. So yeah, Outer Limits is, isn't that pretty old?
That's a weird theming choice. Yeah. I don't know if I've ever seen an episode of the,
it's like the Twilight Zone. It's like the runner up. Yeah.
There are newer versions of it. I think there was a syndicated,
yes there is, I Google it, a syndicated Canadian version. Okay. Like Hercules and Xena?
Seemed probably. Something like that. Or Tia Carrera's Relic Hunter?
Yes. Oh hey, came back around. Hmm, strange. I don't know, does that, does that like read those
rides? Is that the, taking a Flight of Fear? Is that the kind of thing that would happen on the
Outer Limits? Well, it was like an Area 51 sort of setup. And actually by making it very generic,
when Paramount stopped sponsoring stuff and they had to like just rejigger a lot of rides,
they were just like, ah, just drop the Outer Limits, just called Flight of Fear. Done.
That one's easy. A lot of the, I was kind of, I kind of want to go back, you know, they didn't
open this season because of COVID, but I kind of want to go back because they, Racer 75 is still
there. Flight of Fear is still there. The Scooby Doo is still there. It is called the Woodstock
Express now because it's all Cedar Fair owned now. So I was surprised how much is still
remaining. What do you think Yogi's Cave is? Well, they renamed it to Treasure Cave at some point,
even before they stopped the Hanna-Barbera Association. But I think it is-
I'm not going to say that that doesn't make sense. It does make sense.
Is it the same? Are there still like frogs singing? They just took all their gems out.
But besides that, it's- Those belong to Yogi.
The only treasure item in there. They removed that and then-
It might belong to the ground because I think that God Bulldozed it is.
When was the last time you were in that cave, Jason?
Well, here's what happened was like after we went for a few years, my family joined the Disney
Vacation Club. So as I am a young child going like, we got to go back to King's Dominion.
There's a James Bond ride and Judy Dench is in it and Q's in it. And they're like,
we just joined the- We're not going to a different theme park. We made our choice.
We're going to Disney World. We made our commitment.
But we get to see actor Desmond Llewellyn portraying you in a theme park, mother.
Mother, a few years after that, they'll put in a generic Stanley superhero thing that looks like a
reboot ripoff. I've missed all this. Wait, there was a James- It was in that- So that's where
Days of Thunder was and then they did a James Bond thing for a while. Yeah, they would slot in and out
different 3D movies there. And some of them were just those movies that were on a circuit.
That 3D theater, for a brief time, Dave and Buster's had 3D theaters, which is like-
This theater was a slightly nicer 4DX D-Box sort of experience. So you could go to a Dave
and Buster's and go like, hey, is that the James Bond movie that plays a King's Dominion too?
And they wouldn't know if it was, but you could ask them.
Oh yeah. They'd want me to stop talking about some sort of cave in Virginia.
Yeah. Here's a- I have this fun little thing. When you're talking about mashups of the world
of Hollywood and King's Dominion, this one really surprised me. Here's- I'm going to share the
screen and in fact, not show the first frame because that will reveal the Hollywood talent who was-
Hey, baby.
Well, you saw that. The Hollywood talent hosting this 1986 King's Dominion commercial.
There's just one place where 32.95 gets you a season pass. Good for an entire summer of rides
like Rebel Yell, Whitewater Canyon, even the new Shockwave roller coaster. You actually ride
standing up and for just a few dollars more take in concerts by the biggest names in rock,
country, R&D. All this and more.
Yeah. There you go. William H. Macy, chilling for King's Dominion. And I was just-
I was thinking how with a shot this close of him, I just expect him at the end to
put a gun in his mouth and splutter blood on the wall.
No, but probably get caught in a frog storm of those magnetic frogs that you were considering.
Oh yes.
Oh yeah.
It's raining.
Yeah, it's raining Velcro frogs.
Yes. Yeah, I had a season pass that was one year I only asked for that for my birthday. So I had
to get it, but my parents still wouldn't drive me there. So I just had it. You would go to JC
Penny's to get it certified or something. So yeah, I was very excited to be a season pass holder
one summer.
What was your peak? When was it the best for you? What was the-
Probably when I was like 11. So that would have been like around 90.
Sure. Sure. Right before Paramount. Or wait, are you a punk at that point?
No, I was 11. I was a Girl Scout. So that was when I was camping out there with Girl Scouts.
Had friends that had parents who would drive us there. Had enough money that I could-
I think that was when I had my season pass. So I could pay for food in there and I had my
little season pass. So that was probably about it. But then yeah, a couple of years later,
I was just going to Fugazi shows.
That's right.
Did you reject-
Who probably didn't like Jimmy Buffett play at King's Dominion.
No, but I remember when Richard Marks did and I cut out that ad and had that on my
bulletin board being like, oh man, how do I make this happen with my nine years old amount of money?
How do I get myself to this Richard Marks concert at King's Dominion? What could be better?
It's all the best things at one time.
Did you pull it off? Did you go?
No, absolutely not.
When was the last time you went?
I think, gosh, I don't think I've been since I was a kid. I've definitely driven past it
because you can see the Eiffel Tower from the highway and considered it every single time I've
driven past on tour as doing improv or as a standup being like, hey, you guys want to go
to this theme park that you definitely don't want to go to? No? Okay, never mind.
The pain of being the only one.
It's a hard wall for a lot of people that they're totally unwilling to cross. I think we found a
lot of people on the other side of the wall. That's what this podcast is about.
I did a tour. I was on a show called Totally Biased and then when we got canceled, me and
the two other female correspondents and writers did a standup tour down to Disney World called
The Greatest Tour on Earth. We did standup shows all the way down. We drove past this
on that and I was like, hey, so maybe, I mean, obviously we like theme parks and they were like,
no, we don't have enough time to do this to go to a show. But further down the road,
we did pass south of the border and we did get off. You guys know about that place, right?
Wait. Yeah. What is it? Where is it? Is it in the Carolinas?
Yeah, it's the border between South Carolina and North Carolina. South of that border is this place
called South of the Border that's like very racist at this point. I don't know this at all.
It's just like a lot of those. What is that metal that all those things were made out of like those
mushrooms and everything? Is that tin? Is that aluminum? Whatever it is, just tons of those
statues of different animals wearing sombreros and the main building is shaped like a sombrero
and they have like a reptile attraction and like, I want to say maybe like a massage place
because it's also a place where like it's a place where truckers could stop, you know, when you're
just like a weird themed truck stop that became a place that all the kids in my elementary school
loved and would talk about and have like t-shirts from and I'd never been there before.
You guys should look this place up. It's nutty. It's real nutty. It's one of those things where
you see pictures and you're like, I can't believe this exists. How did this ever exist?
And how is it still existing? They should change this. Like robot, like robot animals? No, just
statues of animals. They're just statues of animals. So you can like take your picture next to them.
So it'd be like, oh, there's a kangaroo in a sombrero. There's a big snail in a sombrero.
Didn't make a lot of sense, but. And a trucker could get a massage there. I believe so. Yeah.
Or you could go like hold some snakes. Fireworks. A few different restaurants. Definitely fireworks.
We bought fireworks. That's why we stopped. Because that's between the truckers and the fireworks.
That's probably the genesis of it. Because suddenly once you get into South Carolina,
you could buy fireworks. So people would go south of the border and stock up on their fireworks.
On the Wikipedia, I like that in the very functional see also area that it says see also
tourist trap ethnic stereotype. Yeah. Yeah. It's wild. This is a, it was our place. Yeah.
Yeah. I don't remember it depicting any sort of cultural stuff. Like at least it wasn't like
it is acting out any kind of historical thing very badly. It was in my memory, just animals and
sombreros. Still not respectful, but bizarre. Wow. Certainly could have been worse. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. And probably was at some point. That's fair. Yeah. I probably saw a toned down version.
Very fair. Almost undoubtedly. So if you could go, would you be, especially after
all of this, this terrible time and being cooped up for so long, is this anyway, is this on your
list of things to, would you go do this as comfort food? Now would you fit this into
traversing of America? I don't know. I don't know that I would, that I would do Kings Domain.
And cause I think I would probably be too sad at how different it is because of how many times
it's changed hands and rethemed. I would probably do Bush gardens again, cause I know that that's
still the old country. It's still just Italy and Scotland and Germany, Oktoberfest, all that.
Yeah. So you can't, we can't go to any of those places right now. So it would be a little more
like visiting my childhood that I think Kings Dominion would, I think Kings Dominion would be
like when you see an X and they're just like completely different and you're like, oh,
Oh, what was, who, who was the person that I was with? It's not you.
Like the volcano, the mountain not being there anymore is like the equivalent of like,
oh, he lost his hair. Yeah, exactly.
Interesting. What do you do for, what's the big draw if you go to Bush gardens? What's like your,
what do you make a beeline for? Oh, Loch Ness Monster. Loch Ness Monster.
All time favorite roller coaster. Best roller coaster. Does a double loop. You get an indoor
section that does a spiral thing. It's the only indoor coaster that I'm not scared of. And it's
not indoors. Most of it's out. It does a little underwater thing. I have a phobia thing. I don't
know, phobia makes it sound fancy, but I get irrationally scared on indoor coasters that
something's going to pierce my eyeball. Something's going to like fly out of somebody's pocket or like
a bobby pin. And it could happen just as easily on a regular roller coaster, but like, I guess I
would see it coming and dodge. It doesn't make a lot of sense. Yeah. That makes sense to me.
Yeah. So, but the Loch Ness Monster is real. And it's a, it's Loch Ness Monster themed. That's great.
That's, I mean, it's pretty close to a dinosaur, but it's got the urban legend aspect thrown in.
It's very much my shit. It may be where a lot of my shit comes from. It may, that might be the origin
story. The ride I used to love there though. I mean, it was never better than this, but never
better than the Loch Ness Monster. But I did really like, even as an adult, cause I did go back to
Busch Gardens more, more recently, the Big Bad Wolf, but it murdered a worker. So they had to take
it away, but that was a great ride. It was like a hanging thing where like, so you're sort of in
almost like a ski basket, like your legs are swinging, but you're seated. Oh, I've seen
pictures of it. So it's one of those ones where you like lie down and it's not a standing up one.
So it gives you like an extra aspect of the swinging back and forth as you're zooming around.
Oh, my family was a big fan of the Roman Rapids, if you remember that, at Busch Gardens. See,
I hate all water rides, but yeah, that was a pretty exciting one. My mom got so wet on it once she
walked off the ride, went into the gift shop, bought an entire new set of clothes and changed
into them. Yeah. I remember that there were lots of clothing gift stores around that ride
specifically. I like when you were wet, cause I wouldn't go on it. So I would sit there and wait
for people. And it was like being at the intersection of all these different t-shirt stores. So I think
it probably wasn't just your mom. Jason, did you then put her wet clothes on? So you had double
wet clothes because you love it so much? Jason loves wet clothes after a ride.
Do you? Yeah, he does. That's not a joke. Oh, I hate it so much. That used to be my
online dating profile thing. It would be like, Hey, I like movies and go to the museum. And I
hate the water rides at theme parks. And it would filter out all the guys who were like,
why you shouldn't, I love them. Or like, what's your problem? Like,
that's not a very nice first line. Yeah. A lot of fellows do that though. And they'll find something
and they think they're asking you a question about it when really they're poking at it. And it's like,
you can't tell the difference. Oh, that's, that's, this is sad for you fella. Cause you don't know
what you're doing, but you're being a dick. This is what the dynamic will be like when we date. It'll be great.
I'll challenge you on stuff all the time. Exactly. Exactly. I'll think we're just having a conversation
and you'll feel constantly attacked and defensive. Really like harmless things you tossed off,
not meaning much by it. Yeah. That's like a prevalence to like just Twitter in general.
Yeah. Yeah. Can I fight you all day about something that you don't remember? Yeah. You
tweeted already. And similarly when you're like, I don't like this. They're like, what did you expect?
It's Twitter. Like, yeah, not this. This isn't clearly by me not liking it and telling you about
that. This is not what I expected. Yeah. Twitter, not as fun as Roman Rapids. And as things dominion,
that we could escape to a little fantasy theme park for a little while though. Now we'll segue
into the part where you maybe say your, your Twitter name. But first I will say Eliza Skinner,
you survived podcast the ride. Thanks for being here. Let's exit through the gift shop. Is there
anything you would like to plug? Yeah. My album, Regarding My Lovers. It's 10 tracks of standup
comedy, five tracks of original songs and Earth to Ned on Disney Plus, which I was a head writer for
and I like it a lot. It's very weird. And there have been discussions on Reddit from Disney fans
saying that there should be a Ned feature at Disney World. So I saw this on a Twitter,
like a theme park, Twitter news place posted this, the idea of this thing, the Monsters Inc. laugh
floor where characters are funny and interact with you. And yes, it may be could stand a refresh and
you've got this new cast of characters. It seems to be really well liked already on Disney Plus.
So that must've been cool to see. Yeah. I mean, except the actual article was like,
I don't know why anyone would want this. This show is garbage, but I found a whole bunch of
people who want it and I'm like, okay, we didn't need the editorializing.
We have a lot of opinions about different theme park news aggregators and maybe even that one.
But yeah, it was probably nice to see a picture of the show on your Twitter feed.
Can I ask Eliza this show, so if the audience doesn't know, this is a show,
Henson show with a very cool puppet, many puppets. You said you liked eating around animatronics.
Did you get to eat around these puppets and feel the same feeling?
I did, but it wasn't the same feeling because they're better than animatronics. Because part
of the thing with the animatronics is the reassuring robotic clicking, you know, like the head can only
go this far and only go that far. It's almost the same feeling that you get, like when you have to
put a baby to sleep and so you drive around the block with them and they're like, so it's a little
bit of motion and excitement, but controlled, very controlled. My puppets, our puppets,
they can do, well, there's a lot they can't do actually. I was going to say they can do anything,
but that's not true. One of them doesn't even have legs, but they can definitely move a lot more.
I did take lunch in the studio when it was cold and quiet by myself frequently.
Just a lifeless mid sitting there.
Yeah.
Claude's everywhere scattered about.
Oh no, the Claude's always wrapped very carefully in their satin and like we had Claude Wranglers who
I would be like, hey, can I see a Claude? They'd be like, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, which one?
Which one? Hold on. I can get one for you. I don't know if we can let you hold it.
I'm like, come on. And then they started trusting me eventually. But I took a lot of pictures of the
different Claude outfits.
Delicate. What do you think it says? A dews?
Yeah. I mean, they were everything. It was weird. We had to book a lot of time with each guest
because partly because the puppeteers have to take a rest every 15 minutes,
because they've got their arms up or they're being smushed into some weird position.
But also partly because sometimes the puppets would break and we would have to send somebody
up with a screwdriver and poke around in Ned's mouth or like swap his head out for one of the
other heads and keep on going. Yeah. So pretty much his name is covenant.
So you can't reach out to people like, hey, can you hang for an hour?
So like, you gotta be ready for some puppet repairs.
Yeah, exactly. Like it might not happen and then you have a short day, but
what kind of sandwiches do you want? Well, we'll have treats for you.
All of our guests were really great because everybody's just excited to hang out with some
puppets. Yeah. You know, wouldn't be.
Talk to them and engage with them. Yeah. Yeah. Well,
yeah, everybody check that out on Disney Plus and other people have been on the show. Nick Weigert,
Jordan Morris, great, great staff you had there. So yeah, congrats on Earth to Ned.
Okay. And as for us, we're at podcast, the ride on social media. We got merch on T public
and for three bonus episodes every month, subscribe to podcast, the ride, the second gate
at patreon.com slash podcast, the ride, anything to go out on.
I'll just say that I have a lot more questions about Jason and shuffleboard, but I will save
them for a later time. That's fine. I'm sure it'll come up again.
All right. More shuffleboard to come. Well, as thanks for being here to thank you all for listening.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson,
Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey. For more original podcasts,
please visit forever dog podcasts.com and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts,
Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts. Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following
us on Twitter and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.