Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast contains mockumentary style humor, fake endings, sexy humitep, and
we finally answered the question, what is Michael's favorite Britney Spears song?
All this and Matt Rogers joins us to talk revenge of the mummy.
Hey, your souls are mine.
This is Podcast the Rye.
Welcome to Podcast the Rye, a theme park podcast hosted by three men who all have a secret fantasy
of being eaten alive by a horde of scarab beetles.
My name is Mike Carlson.
Joining me as always, Jason Sheridan.
Yeah, I would agree with that.
I would agree with that.
Scott Garner, do you also agree with that?
Of course, that's how you want to go.
I mean, it's at least quick if horrifying and but maybe a little weirdly pleasurable.
Yeah, I guess they make it look quick in all the movies and TV, but I do have a suspicion
maybe it's kind of slow.
It's kind of a slow death.
They don't all move at that hyper speed.
Yeah, on the Universal Tram Tour, when Whoopi gets eaten alive by scarab beetles, I think
I feel like it's very quick, but that's just I think for time.
Oh, sorry, go ahead.
I was going to have the fantasy, but I think maybe it's just based on fiction, you know.
I'm glad there's just scarab talk happening in general.
Love scarabs.
Is anyone confident that scarabs exist in real life and that you could exist?
Right?
Or maybe they don't.
I don't know.
Do I ever actually do any research pertaining to the real world when we do this podcast?
I don't.
So that's not what we're doing here.
No way to know.
It did not occur to me to research scarabs.
I was mostly looking at track lengths and budgets to try and get to the bottom of a
long time mystery.
Yeah, it's insane.
The heck happened here?
Yeah, I was just I was just looking up linear induction motors.
I yeah, I gave up on trying to understand that.
Well, look, I think our guest probably wants to talk about linear induction motors as well.
You know him from Los Culturises and his upcoming HBO Max show Hot Dog.
It's Matt Rogers returning.
Hey, what's up, everybody?
I just want to say before we start, I'd like to die peacefully in my sleep.
But the scarab beetles thing is definitely a theatrical way to go.
However, I don't think it's painless the way that they scream when it's happening.
I don't know.
I don't know, you guys.
Yeah, but it might be quick.
What if it's like, ah, you're gone?
Yeah, but here's the thing.
It's like if I if I'm going to have a quick death, it should be quick and painless.
You know what I mean?
Like it happens instantaneously.
Otherwise, what does it matter how quick it happens?
Like you're literally getting eaten alive by beetles.
Like think about what it feels like to be stung even one time.
Imagine that all over your body.
And also it's kind of starts at your feet and then goes in.
The last thing that happens is your eye gets closed up.
But you know what's happening just like physically and like emotionally.
That has to be true terror.
It does.
I don't disagree with what you're saying, but I think part of me also would be kind
of thrilled that I'm going out like Whoopi did on the tour.
So I think maybe just sort of the tribute to Whoopi on the tram tour, I would be like,
oh, this hurts so much, but oh, this is pretty cool.
You'd be amongst legends in the way that you die.
Exactly.
Yeah. So I think maybe that could override the true physical pain.
I don't know. We'll have to find out.
And we got to go out.
It's scared beetles.
Her. I imagine Alan Menken will go that way.
Oh, yeah, probably. Yeah.
So we're going to talk, you know, mummy today, revenge of the mummy.
But, Matt, I don't know if you're aware of this last time.
You've been a while since you were on the show.
Yeah, but there's been a lot of character development on the show since you were here,
which we love to see.
We love it. We love it.
Gross narrative people love to follow.
Yeah. Growth. Human growth.
You deem Scott Gardner a no launch queen.
Yeah, I heard that it kind of became merch.
Yes. It emerged and well, I don't know.
Well, I'll tell you that launch queen sold a lot better than no launch queen.
Nobody wanted to proudly.
It's like, no, who's going to come out as a Scott?
You know what I mean? Like, who's going to come out as like a weakling?
Can I ask you a question?
Have you not done the mummy because of the launches?
Well, that's what we're going to do.
That was the case, you see, when we recorded before.
But just like look at that. You're right.
Nobody wanted to identify as a Scott, least of all Scott.
I didn't like that that label.
And I think I became determined to overcome the label.
So not too long after that,
with the help of a bunch of Chardonnay, I braved the credit coaster.
I got over the launch issue.
Did I end up doing it twice?
I feel like I went. I'm not sure.
Well, the point is, it quickly became one of my favorite rides in the park.
It's one of the ones I'm dreaming of now.
I've watched right throughs of that a ton.
I quickly went from just to completely loving it.
And then we all went to Orlando together in October.
And I'm launching all over the place.
Yes. Yeah. Yeah.
Nice. Only sort of crazily humid.
Yeah, a little bit.
I know. But I'm I'm rocking roller coaster.
I'm Hagrid's.
Hell, I'm well, besides Orlando, there's that, you know, that horse one.
We did it not a bunch of times in a row.
Pony Express, Pony Express.
There you go. Did you get on the Hulk?
Didn't do Hulk.
That is that is the one of the of the launch lineup at that park.
That's what you will be on now that you've started.
You will. I think so. I think so.
And you and of course, all of that building up to Revenge of the Mummy,
which after all that, that launch, not too bad at all.
That's a lot lesser than some of the other launches that I listed.
OK, so I'm actually going to say this.
And, you know, the fans of the podcast might disagree with me,
but I actually think that the launch in Revenge of the Mummy
is a more intense launch than the one with Hulk, because I think that
the way that you pop out of your seat at the top of like the airtime
that you get at the top of the first launch of the Mummy is one of the more
thrilling moments to be found in the entire city of Orlando, to be honest with you.
Like, I think it's one of the most intense things that can happen to you
on a on a ride in the city of Orlando.
I wouldn't disagree.
I think it's heightened, too, by how cold and dark and like windy it is in there.
You don't know what's going to happen.
The thing is, you've seen the Hulk do what it does a million times.
And so, you know, what's in store for you, which is that sort of, I guess,
inversion coming out of the tunnel, whereas you have no idea where it's going
when you shoot through that mouth of Imhotep.
Yeah, true. No, yeah, no idea.
The layout I knew very little about any of it.
I that's that's the really the benefit of some of this launch queen
journey that I've been on is now I get to like have these new rides to me,
which I haven't had completely new rides since I was, you know, so exciting.
I so wish for that.
I feel like it's actually better to not know anything about the mummy
before you do it. Like whenever I bring people to the my favorite thing to do now
is to bring people to that park that I've never been there.
Like I took my friend Suti there and we just put her on the mummy
and just didn't tell her anything about it.
And it's really fun to watch someone experience what it is,
because I actually it is my favorite ride.
Oh, yeah, I don't think it's it's it's strong.
I mean, getting to do it, really not really knowing.
I knew some of that meta stuff and everything.
I mean, that was a blast.
And was I not conditioned a little bit?
I know I wouldn't have had definitely one of the peak new ride experiences
of that trip. Yeah. Yeah.
I was going to say the Hulk also, I think, is so intense
that it almost gives your brain only one experience the whole time.
Like you kind of just gray out immediately and you're just doing it.
The mummy, you're going through the levels, you're experiencing different emotions.
Hulk is just one emotion the whole time.
The thing about the mummy is it truly is the reason why I think it's
the most successful ride in the park.
And it's actually one of my favorite parks is because it genuinely
combines a thrill ride for real with a narrative experience.
And I think that that's not something you can say for Hulk.
Like you're just not you're not removed from the experience
of being on a roller coaster the entire time. Like
and I do feel that the back half of Hulk is pretty weak in terms of design goes.
That's why I'm so excited for the Jurassic coaster, which looks like
which looks like it's going to be incredible in the first half
and then even better in the second half.
I think the way that that is shaping up to be designed is really cool.
And the insider intel that I have,
apparently, when it's all done and themed and like put together,
it's going to be pretty amazing.
Wait, you have you do have info because you predicted on our show.
You always have the role of intelligence.
I said this was going to happen on your show.
Yes. Oh, this ride to the Jurassic one. Did you predict? I did.
I said, wow, I didn't remember that. Oh, my God. You're way ahead.
And now you know, has it been that long ago where I said it was rumored?
Or did I break the Hagrid stuff to you guys?
The born you said born for sure.
Yes, I did. I remember. Yep. Yep.
I'm trying to remember what the specifics about Jurassic were.
So maybe I didn't because it was like a very gray rumor.
Like it wasn't it wasn't like a thing that was definitely going to happen.
But for years, there's been this Jurassic coaster rumored.
And then like probably about a year ago, there started there started to be
markings discovered on the ground and clear small clearings happening
where they were like, something's definitely going on.
And now we see like they're putting what is definitely,
I think, going to be one of the signature rides of the resort.
I mean, it looks unbelievable.
On social media, Raptors are being constantly lowered onto this track.
I mean, I'm sure we're all following these Twitter accounts. Yes.
And large birds of prey have made their home there.
Yeah. The ospreys are like living on top of the top hat. Yeah.
It's it might become a problem.
It will be going forward unless like like once the train once the trains start
going like they'll know not to be there.
But for right now, it's like it's so funny because you'll see updates
that they've made a home on top of the top hat.
And then the next day, they're like, the osprey nest has been removed.
And then it's like the ospreys are back.
The osprey nest has been removed.
The ospreys like, oh, I was going to say the ospreys like me
are concerned about the eye lines when you enter Islands of Adventure,
that the beautiful view of the Jurassic Park visitor center
is now obscured by black track all around it.
See, what do you guys think about that?
I think it kind of hasn't.
I mean, I'm not wild about it.
I think the coaster will be good.
But on the other hand, they haven't really done the boats
that crisscross that lagoon in like, oh, God, 15 years.
Yeah, years. Yeah.
It's also like it's like the visitor center is cool.
And it's cool that it's like framed like that.
But it isn't quite like they just put up a roller coaster
in front of Sleeping Beauty's castle.
Because it's kind of far so far away.
It's not the central icon of the park, and therefore it doesn't ruin
anything aesthetically for me.
For me, it's just like flat out there was nothing in that area.
And now they've put a huge ticket in that area,
which is a great thing for any fans of the parks, especially if you're
like proper roller coaster enthusiasts like I am.
Like for me, it was like devastating when they took down Dillion Dragons.
And I love Hagrid's, but it was missing that big roller coaster to say
I am the same intensity level as Hulk.
And I'm thrilled.
Yeah, yeah, I think it'll be I think it'll be fine.
I might not even have like maybe quite noticed it.
Oh, like, oh, you can't see it.
I wasn't going to be that that big of a loss for me.
Matt, do you know anything about I don't feel free to share.
Feel free to say no.
Do you know what blues roll blues roll in the coaster is?
The famous Raptor Blue.
So I don't know about Rue Rue.
I don't know about Blues specific role in the ride.
I do know some facts about what was going to happen
in the ride before all this covid stuff happened, which I think now
there's a little bit up in the air stuff.
But the ride was supposed to have six Raptor animatronics throughout.
I think what was the idea was there would be two.
And this is going to be, you know, if you're if you are the kind of person
who wants to be a purist and experience these things first, just know that,
A, this is definitely not for sure.
And B, this is going to spoil some stuff. But.
In the first room, the first show scene that you go into,
there was supposed to be two Raptors in there.
And then you launch sort of like the way Chris Pratt
launches with the motorcycle, with the with the Raptors in the movie
Jurassic World into the ride.
Then there's two which we've now seen placed in the actual ride layout itself.
And they are literally there.
It's sort of unclear whether those are audio animatronic or just figures.
I hope they're audio animatronic, but I don't know.
They've definitely been, as we've seen in the ride, we're going to discuss today.
Like they've been known to just put figures of mummies in there that don't move.
And, you know, I don't think they would do that now, but we'll see with budgets.
And then there's supposed to be one or two more
that happen at the end of the ride as like a final scare.
And so so it's again, it's two in the first show scene with the launch,
two during the course of the ride, one at the end.
And apparently there's one in the queue, like one really, really, really
advanced audio animatronic that's in the queue.
That sounds like Blue, doesn't it?
Potentially. But again, I don't know specifically what Blue's role is
or if there is a role for Blue because Blue is at the Raptor encounter.
Like, that's like the big thing with the Raptor encounter is you go meet Blue or whatever.
So I don't know how canonical they're being about this.
Probably not very.
But I don't know about any celebrity cameos.
I don't know about anything like that.
I know.
Clear Dearing's role.
Brice Dallas, it's Clear Dearing.
She definitely went back.
Brice Dallas definitely went back and did stuff for the Jurassic
World ride in Hollywood. And so did Chris Pratt.
I don't know what their role is in this.
I would imagine it's something.
Also, maybe we can get some BD Wong action up in here.
Oh, yeah. He is InGen.
And so this is an InGen themed ride.
I don't know that it's definitely called the Velocicoaster, but it looks like it is.
What's the premise? Are you is it simulating the movement of a Raptor?
What? Like, what are we in the ride?
I don't know if we're a Raptor or we're the motorcycle
that is like the thing that Chris Pratt is riding.
However, I will say it would be a little redundant for them to do a motorcycle thing.
Now they've put the Hargard ride up.
But but I don't know how down they are to do the thing of like
you're a Raptor the way that you were a dragon on Dueling Dragons.
I just don't know if that fits in with the narrative of the park
or that area of the park.
Like we are very much humans experiencing Jurassic World or Jurassic Park
as it stands now.
But I don't know how much they're going to bend
sort of narrative disbelief there.
But I know that we're getting a bunch of animatronics.
I don't know if all six made it with all the stuff that's going on with Covid.
You've seen them, you know, sort of drop the progress on Epic Universe
and everything, but they sure are full steam ahead with the Jurassic Coaster.
So it looks like every dollar they were going to spend on it has been spent so far.
I mean, who thought we would have gotten like an enclosure?
You know, like it's so cool what's happening there.
They're really going all out.
And I think it looks like it's going to be the best ride in the park. Wow.
Easy. We get the scoops with you that you're willing to impart
whatever this internal.
This is like a passion of mine.
Like I I'll follow.
I'm sure everyone that, you know, listens to this is following at bio
reconstruct on Twitter like they are every day.
He's so diligent
about like posting new stuff.
And then I follow like on YouTube, like Midway Mayhem.
And I follow like all these like YouTube's like you could really fall down a wormhole
because some of these people are going to the park every day
and just recording like the progress, which I appreciate.
But, you know, just a way for me to live my inner child
without actually going to the parks. Sure.
Well, yeah, because I met, you know, we could all be going to Universal Orlando.
Technically, how high is anyone's desire to actually do this among us?
Well, not that high.
I think at this point,
I think my fear is less about being in the park.
Maybe if it's really crowded, that would probably stress me out.
But I just don't think I'm ready to sit on a five hour airplane yet.
A five hour flight.
As I've flown cross country a couple of times, it's really safe.
And I they make you feel really good about it.
You know what I would do is I would just spring for like a clear membership
or whatever, just to like make sure you don't have to wait on long lines,
like just pay the extra money if you really want to go somewhere. But.
But the flying of it all wasn't what bothered me.
What bothers me is the Florida of it all.
Well, that's another aspect.
You're right. Very important.
Like you're not dealing with it with the finest.
Sorry.
No, no, no. You haven't gone to Florida, though.
No. OK.
No, you're not thinking of an Orlando trip anytime soon.
No, I'll. Here's what I'll say.
If when when this coaster opens, if Covid is still happening, I will go.
But but I'll be really safe about it.
But I'm like not going to be able to wait on this one.
Like, I really want to ride this.
I've got the same way with Hagrid's, like the second it opened,
I went down there and I did it and I was really happy that I.
Oh, yeah, you did it.
We did it and did a whole episode about it.
Oh, my God. What a what a blast.
It's amazing. It's so good. They did such a great job.
Of course, like, you know, with their with Universal's animatronics,
they're always lacking.
And whenever you go to Disney and then go to Universal, it's always like,
I mean, there's a market difference in like the quality of their animatronics.
But they did what they did.
And I'm really happy they use practical sets and effects.
And it was a real thrill ride and they were super ambitious with it.
And I think it was fucking great. Yeah. Yeah.
But the thing I might have sat out if you had not called me out as a no launch
I might have missed what I called the best ride in Orlando.
Had I not made some done some internal work.
It might take that spot for me for the mummy. Yeah.
Oh, it was really was mummy.
And now maybe Hagrid's for me. Yes.
Because because Hagrid delivers on the same thing I was talking about
with the mummy, which is it's a real thrill ride that has narrative elements,
which is what I think these things should be.
And it takes up a lot of space and it makes sense.
You know, you sort of like need launches to make this possible
because you have to like it's pretty hard to start a ride
and then it just goes and goes and goes.
Like you need slowdowns and stops and pacing to really tell a story
and give you a full narrative experience.
Agreed. Yeah.
But before we go to mummy, I will just ask Matt, do you have any?
I mean, everything's canceled potentially.
Yeah. You have any epic universe scoop?
I do. I do.
Probably not much more than you guys know, but I know that the lands,
the plan lands were obviously in the Super Nintendo world.
And then there was a classic monsters area, which I was really excited about.
I've been waiting for them to do this for so long.
I've been waiting for them to commit to how good they are at at at horror
and bring that Halloween Horror Nights energy all year round with a land.
And I think that what they had planned was really cool.
It was do you know about this?
The Kuka arm thing.
Yes, it was similar to the Forbidden Journey style,
but it was actually going to be on an actual roller coaster track.
Yeah, I saw that it was going to be with all the classic monsters.
And then their idea for an expansion was they were going to do
the creature of the Black Lagoon, which is like a Jaws type thing.
Whoa. So that was going to that was going to come in the years to come,
which we probably won't see until like, you know, 2030 now. Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, the Universal Monster stuff feels like money in the bank.
Like, it feels like it's it's it's such a and there's going to be a huge
amphitheater there, like whether we're going to do some type of show.
But it's so obvious to me that that's what they're missing
because they're so good at it and it's such a part of the Universal's history
and brand. So that there was obviously
another Harry Potter expansion.
It was going to be more focused on
a fantastic beast, which for me sucks, but that's what they were doing.
And then there was a how to train your dragon land,
which was going to be more of the kids stuff because,
you know, Nintendo is going to be obviously it's for kids,
but it's more for everyone.
And there actually are some legit rides there.
There's going to be not only the Mario Kart ride,
but also the Donkey Kong roller coaster. Oh, yeah. Yeah.
And then there was a huge dueling launch coaster
that was themed to space, which was like just in the hub of the park.
It wasn't themed to any particular land. Yeah.
Oh, yeah. You have to look at the concept art because it's all.
Oh, it's all there.
The curvy building, like off to the one side. Yeah.
It's it's somehow themed to space.
And there's a restaurant that's themed to space.
But basically the central hub of the epic universe was basically
going to be themed to elements.
So you're getting water, fire, earth and then air.
And they were I think they were connecting space with that somehow.
But there's like a fire barbecue restaurant
that we're going to do between classic monsters and Super Nintendo World.
There was like a very cool, like waterfront,
more fine dining restaurant that was like water themed.
And there was going to be smaller attractions throughout that central hub,
because the way that they're going to end up doing it again,
this was all pre-COVID, this was all announced.
But it's basically going to be you enter each land with the wristband that you have.
It's like you can just walk to the park and do whatever somehow.
I don't know how they were going to do this.
But it wasn't like you walk into islands of adventure and you're in the park now.
It's like you have to enter each land.
And then, of course, there was that huge hotel that they were building,
which is like their major resort. Right.
But they were really trying something different with it.
I think there's going to be almost entirely virtual queues
because that's the way that they want to go after the success with it
that they feel they've had.
But, yeah, I was really excited. Yeah.
Yeah. I mean, the telecom, them being owned by a telecom
is maybe the only saving grace that it won't take another 20 years for them to do it.
You know, they have the money.
I think it's just that they want to just hold a second to wait
to see just exactly what's happening.
I think that, you know, come November, we're going to be seeing
like what the next four years are going to look like.
And I think that that's that's actually huge.
So are you saying that Epic Universe is that the Biden's election
causes Epic Universe and Trump's election?
But that's actually exactly what I'm saying.
And this is Intel that I have is that if you vote for Biden, Epic Universe
will happen and if you vote for Trump, it won't.
So if that's keeping you undecided on the count,
if that's going to get you undecided off the couch, then I'm happy to say it here.
Every that's me. I was leaning Trump.
And but now we're all in very accurate, especially all the Florida voters.
I just insulted apologies.
But if the Epic Universe comes, I think they're willing to vote for Biden.
I hope so. I hope that.
But, you know, they're they're like almost done with the one in Hollywood.
Like they they've constructed the entire
Mario Kart ride building, and they're pretty much like hard at work
at the rest of the framing of the steel framing of the rest of the land.
But I think that, you know, just around the corner here at Universal Studios,
Hollywood, we have a pretty decently finished Mario Kart ride.
So I think we will at least get to do that within the next two years.
I have also heard that with the park being closed, they are finally
getting around to fixing the last scenes of the Jurassic World ride.
Like, you know, that's putting in 100 percent done.
Yeah. All the full like the full kit and caboodle that they kind of like rush through.
What were your thoughts on the Jurassic World revamp when you did it?
We we basically I'll speak for myself.
There's some cool stuff, but there's it's like miss.
It's like missing. It feels missing pieces.
There's long stretches where nothing kind of happens.
I like the tank thing fine.
But is it better than the glory and majesty of Jurassic Park from the old ride?
I don't think it is.
I I'm surprised how much I liked it.
And some of it replaces you're right, that goes away,
but it replaces just some perfunctory here's where we turn around.
So I think that part is a plus up.
But then after that, yeah, it feels like there are less dinosaurs,
which is in no scenario a good thing.
And there and like supposedly from hopefully the redo fixes it,
because I do kind of like this weird like habitat they have going now at the top of the lift hill.
But it's like the B mode supposedly, where it's just like what is the
what's that crazy dinosaurs name? I don't remember the indominus.
Dominus Rex. Is that right?
I think it is.
The big bad villain dinosaur in the eye.
Indominus Rex. OK, yeah.
I loved I loved the new scene.
I will say like the they really modernized it to Jurassic World.
I felt like when you come over and there's like the park map
and you go around and then, of course, it is screens,
which sucks. And I feel like we need to lay off the screens, which we've we've said.
But for me, it's like at least there was.
Like I liked that we specifically visited a scene from the movie,
which is with that huge underwater dinosaur and the water effect I thought was cool.
And anything that gets that fucking brontosaurus or whatever
that had been there out of here, that because the thing barely works and moves.
I thought it was so lame.
Slowly falling over.
The skin was so, so bad.
And I'm now realizing I've said the F curse a couple of times.
And I know we have a parent that listens that doesn't like that.
So I've been a refrain. I don't.
I think at this point, a lot of them listen.
And sorry, sorry, folks.
At least we're working, you know, mine.
That's the benefit of parents who still have burner cell phones is
they'll never listen to you say fuck on a podcast.
Well, I'll be cognizant of it either way.
But yes, I was really happy they got that fucking brontosaurus out.
Fuck, yeah.
I never I never thought about this part.
I don't think I know the brontosaurus well enough.
I didn't know it needed to be shot out of its misery.
It was really bad.
It was it was like so if that's going to be the way you set the tone for the ride,
then it's a huge failure because like now it's like the one in Orlando,
the Jurassic Park River Adventure.
I have to do it at night because you can't see the fucking steel
framing around it, which is so shitty.
And you also you notice less that it's like
so such a warm piece of mechanics like.
And then, of course, it is like, but my inner child wants
at least try to pretend that it's real.
And I don't want to have to be on a pound and a half of edibles
for that to be real.
I mean, anyway, but yeah.
Well, that's the real thrill ride taking a pound
to have of edibles to the state of Florida.
Bingo.
I think it's I do think that Jurassic World is like one
extra little dinosaur show scene and then a really cool finale away
from being like like, yeah, in my mind, which I think we might get.
I mean, the thing is that I think is a real bummer is that they really seem
to do nothing with the scene that they've turned into the Indominus Rex cage
when you first enter the Rapture Containment Area.
Like what they've done with that is like they've made no choices.
Like now I see they've added like that sphere that the boys travel in in the movie.
They've added like a broken sphere to that section, like the gyrosphere.
But there's no story happening there.
You just know, I guess you that's when you find out that something's gone wrong,
but there should be something happening.
There should be dinosaurs there.
We're middle.
Not sure. And you get a wall blood.
You get some nice wall blood, if that does anything for you.
Which it doesn't know so much.
I'd rather see a robot.
Yes. Or you see the blood getting splashed or may are produced in the moment.
The leaked photos of the original concept was the two dinosaur heads,
like budding heads almost at the end of it, as opposed to one just kind of like
like like a peeping Tom in the bushes overlooking at the T-Rex.
Yeah, I think we will get something closer to the concept art.
But when I was there, which was during Halloween Horror Nights,
actually, like it wasn't even the Indominus Rex's head.
They covered it up.
So it was literally just the T-Rex doing what it always has done.
And I was like disappointed.
But for me, it's just like if you're working to get the finished product
in the place where it needs to be, whatever, I'll come back.
I have a season pass to that place.
Sure.
I will say I'll transition to the topic.
I was thinking about, OK, there's two versions of this mummy ride,
one in Hollywood, one in Florida.
We know the Florida one's better, but I almost feel bad.
And I'm so hurting for going to these theme parks that I feel bad that I
have such a negative feeling toward the mummy out here.
And I feel like once it's back open, I will never forsake it again.
I will. I want to go on this bad version.
The Chili's two version of the mummy ride.
So bad. I get what you're saying, but I know I cannot second that.
I yeah, that doesn't I.
I just enough feelings. Don't worry.
But if you this is one of my theme park grievances, like I when the mummy
ride opened in Florida, I was so into it.
And Matt, I'm so happy to hear your enthusiasm for this ride,
because I was going like, am I looking at this through rose colored glasses?
And then when we wrote it last fall, I was like, oh no, this is still great.
This is still so fun, especially in 2004.
It was like such a leap ahead.
And it's aged so well. It holds up. Yeah.
And I think shows like what could have if the ownership of the park
had stabilized a little sooner, like, oh, if the mummy had been the
the early adopter, the standard, like the screen in that
is pretty small, like pretty minor.
That still looks good.
That looks better than like Transformers and Fast and Furious,
like that little one little screen like. But the rest is practical.
Yeah, I mean, Fast and Furious, we don't talk about.
I know, but we haven't gotten there yet.
It's literally such an embarrassment.
It's a bummer. I was the only one who read it.
And I have I've just been sitting on the notes of like just bumping everyone out.
Yeah, we don't want to do this sad, gray episode.
But that will be it's it's so long and so bad.
And it's just there's really very little good about it.
But anyway, I am a Transformers stan and protector.
Like, I think it's pretty fucking great.
I guess. But but but with the mummy, it's like.
And first of all, like something I want to say is this is the first ride,
the first major e-ticket theme park ride that I was like.
Fully following the progress of online, even as a kid,
I think I was in my early teens, yeah, 2004, so I was
probably 12, 13 when they announced this.
And I remember them describing it as a psychological thrill ride,
like they had never done before, like they were using all these terms.
I was really interested in it was like, we're going to play with all your senses
and it's going to be a high speed roller coaster.
And I remember thinking this will be really cool if they can pull this off.
And the fact that they even came close to what they were describing
is pretty unbelievable.
And like you said in 2004, when this opened, like there wasn't shit like this.
There just wasn't. So, you know, I think that.
If there's one thing that maybe doesn't hold up about it,
it's the fact that it's like the Brendan Fraser mummy.
Like, you know what I mean?
Like that, like property, I don't think is something that's like evergreen.
But the ride itself is evergreen and it was so ambitious from the beginning.
And it was it's fun to ride every single time.
Yeah. Would you give any points to that?
Probably not the L.A. one.
I learned a little about the Singapore one, which seems like sort of a blend.
It's missing elements from Florida, but it does not have the
we're making a movie or the Brendan Fraser of it all did that.
Do you think?
Are those other versions superior at all because they're lacking the little
we're making a film with Brendan?
You know, I don't think the story fully tracks on the Orlando one.
Like, I think that it's a little confusing to go from we're on a set
to all of a sudden we're in the in the world.
Like, I just think they could have, like you said, like,
I think we could have committed to being in the world from the top.
It's like meta in a way that I don't think it needs to be.
But ultimately, if you're able to follow the narrative through the cue,
then it does make sense.
But who's doing that?
You know what I mean?
Like it's your move.
And now it doesn't really drop huge lines at all.
And so you're moving right to the end.
I always have the express pass.
So it's like you're moving, you're breezing through the queue
to the point where you skip all of that
narrative stuff with Brendan's character and like the is the P.A.
that then dies during the ride.
It's like you don't know who that is.
So when you're just going right through and you're already in the
ancient Egypt section, like you miss all of that.
Whereas I do think if I'm going to give one prop to the Hollywood version,
it's just we're in the world of the mummy.
You know what I mean?
Like this is what it's not too complicated.
It's easily accessible.
You don't need and you don't need it to be.
I went on in 2019 not not knowing any of that.
I knew there was like that beat in the middle where the way you think the ride
started, but I didn't know the story or Reggie.
I had no idea about Reggie Reggie, the assistant production assistant
or the assistant.
Very important.
But I did the single rider.
I think we all might have.
So I literally had no idea what was happening when there was a red hat on a mummy.
I truly just literally didn't even see that.
I think that is an issue.
They need to represent that somehow, even in the single rider.
It's not how that's supposed to be.
So under all that, like mummy bondage stuff that he's got on
is like an actual human animatronic.
But the effect of like when emo tap blows the smoke
or like sucks the life out of him, like him going back to mummification,
like that was like too much.
And also that emo tap animatronic barely works.
So much about that ride is like
just working in like a beta function.
Oh, really? Wait, I don't know any of it was.
So they wrapped it up as a way to get around that they didn't make a perfect Reggie.
Like, no, it was just the effect of the mummification happening
was too precarious.
It was just like not working.
Wow. I think this is true.
I'm almost positive this is true, but it's not like a supposed to be a mummy
animatronic, it's supposed to be a Reggie animatronic that then
gets like turned into that.
Yeah, it just was this technology just wasn't there yet for it to look good
and run like every 30 seconds.
Yeah. And in the Hollywood version, a mummy was supposed to jump on the car.
Oh, really? Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
And then they had to cut.
They had to cut. So it was like a hydraulic thing.
It was like the mummy was going to hop onto the car and then pull back.
I forget it's like in the beginning of the ride.
It's like so short that who even knows what that means.
But they had so many plans for what they were going to do that they ended up landing.
They reached for the moon and landed on a star.
Let's just say that.
I mean, yeah, they got pretty close.
Yeah. There's so many impressive things, especially for what this is 2004.
Yeah. Like crazy stuff that you wouldn't expect because like 2004 was a long time ago.
Like Rise of the Resistance is 16 years later and they're maybe in Rise of the Resistance era.
They could if they built this new in 2020, maybe they'd get everything right.
Yeah. Right.
The Singapore one built in 2010 cost half as much as the Hollywood and Florida ones.
And it doesn't have like the fake out.
See, it has a scene.
It doesn't have the fake out loading scene, but it has an extra emotional effect.
Imhotep there and the Book of the Living, which I guess it was their version is much clearer story wise.
And it's as long as the Florida one.
And somehow it costs half as much.
I don't know how they did that.
But the queue and building look incredibly detailed.
I think probably because they made it so long after the original rides.
There's a lot about like a lot of the money that they spend goes to like sets that they have to originally create.
So that's why you see like a lot of carbon copies.
Like that's why Transformers is the same, exactly the same in so many different Universal parks.
And the same thing is going to be true with Mario Kart.
Like they're going to be and Harry Potter for what it's worth.
The entire land is just like copy pasted because it's so much cheaper.
So maybe that went into how much cheaper the Singapore mummy is, because they could essentially just recreate a lot of it without without it being exactly the same.
Maybe. How do we even get into that?
I mean, we've sort of said it, but the basic idea of the Florida one is that you are on the set of not the mummy returns, but a different mummy sequel.
Revenge of the Mummy.
You are not on the set of the mummy tomb of the dragon emperor, the third in the Steven Subbers Mummy series.
And the tone of the videos is very much like Christopher Guest Light, maybe like that vibe of like we're just having a little jokey, some quirky characters.
Yes, like a mockumentary.
Yeah, yeah, which I probably took a long time to shoot.
And now it's like people are just walking right by it.
Like you really booked Brendan Rager for this.
Like fucking what's her name?
A Rachel Weiss was like, I'm not doing that.
She's not present.
I get nothing from this.
It's like in the movies, the mummy movies are like kind of light.
I don't know, were they thinking like these videos would balance out the dark because the ride is very dark, a very scary ride.
The queue is really dark, too.
You can't see shit.
Yeah. Yeah. So were they thinking like, oh, we'll do this whimsical, this fun little light pre-show to balance.
Like, it is curious to me why they would go completely that tone of like, we're just goofing around.
Well, you have to remember, they're obsessed with how things are made.
So maybe they maybe they felt this was like a subversion on that.
Like it's around that area of the park where at the time they did have like, you know, earthquake, which then became disaster.
Right. It out. So there is like there's something to be said about them potentially making a comment on the way their other attractions work.
So it's like, see behind the scenes, props from the movie, et cetera.
And then there's a twist, you know, because this this ride at the time was really them saying we're changing the way we do things.
And that's where I think it gets like a little heady is they were commenting on the type of universal ride that they've always done.
Right. This is maybe that is this the last big ride they made where they had to sort of put in like,
how the movies are made, perhaps.
It seems like they really lost that after this.
Right. But and this and again, this wasn't even that.
I think it was like truly a transition out of that.
Right. Because now it's like there's none of that in the park anymore.
Because Simpsons opens a couple of years after this, like four years later.
And that really isn't how the Simpsons are made or anything.
No, it's just we're in the world of the Simpsons, which is what it should be.
I mean, I think that's great.
Harry Potter is just like, welcome to the Wizarding World, which I think is what it should be.
And I think, you know, that's what Islands of Adventure does so well is it's like we're transporting you into worlds,
whereas Universal Studios used to be ride the movies and there was like a BTS element to it, which they've really left behind,
I think, so they can capitalize on just getting into the IP.
And the most successful of the early rides, I think, easily was Back to the Future, which never had any behind the scenes component.
Like they should have learned then.
Jaws as well. Jaws as well.
I mean, like it was just this was your encounter with Jaws and Back to the Future was Back to the Future was so fun
because you really felt like you were going you were doing that, you know, like back in the day, Back to the Future.
That was like, I mean, truly chef's kiss.
And, you know, Terminator for the same reason, like I really enjoyed that when I first when it first came out years ago,
I was like, this felt like a really specific only Universal could do it.
This this very perfectly fits with the IP.
Would any listener be upset if we just we've done a lot of these attractions?
Can we just do Terminator and Back to the Future again?
Because we just and make no new observations or new twists.
I just want to talk about them.
I keep thinking about like, I know there's stuff in my notes we never got to on like,
who cares? They're just saying all the same shit.
I mean, yeah.
For sure. I remake.
How many times has Doughboy's gone to Burger King at this point?
Let's be real.
Uh, yeah, fuck you, Doughboy's spoons fired.
No, but I mean, you know, they got we got it, Jason.
You hate Doughboy.
Hey, all right.
You're going to always just pretended to like them.
We know the last of the three of us to do the show, we get the extra.
But you guys haven't done the mummy yet.
Well, no, we have not done this right now.
God, I can't believe it took you guys this long to do the mummy.
You guys have been doing this podcast for so long.
Oh, there's there's giant ones we haven't got.
There's glaringly obvious ones we haven't done.
What an honor to be the person that's the mummy.
Oh, we've and I've had it.
We've had it like earmarked for you.
I was like, well, we got to have Matt back on for the mummy.
And we talked about it a bunch.
Because what did we do the first time?
Twister ride it out.
Twister. Wow.
Yeah. Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Now, wait a minute.
Did you just say disaster, but say disaster, right?
It because I was like, I love it.
Oh, I messed up. I messed up.
What was the disaster subtitle?
Disaster, a major exclamation point.
I'm a picture starring you.
So stupid. I like.
But since you mentioned Terminator and we talked about jaws,
I think mummy might be the last of Universal's
chip on its shoulder of like we're not Disney.
We're a little more cutting.
We're a little edgier because like the yeah, the ride itself gets very dark.
But those few lines are pretty sarcastic.
The Q video is pretty sarcastic.
A little mean, like everyone kind of like dumps on Reggie a lot.
I think they're they're not killing people in pre shows and rides anymore.
You know what I mean?
Like I used to watch Kimberly Duncan get choked out by the Terminator.
And they they they they like literally to death.
And like they've pulled off that.
I remember the one time I went back, like in later years when Terminator was
like happening, the Terminator came up out of the stage and Kimberly Duncan just goes,
I'm going to get security and walks off.
And I'm like, oh, enough people complained about watching a woman get killed,
get killed six times a day.
Yeah. Yeah. Interesting.
But but like with this ride, it's like, you know, Reggie dies.
He dies. Yeah, he eats really painfully.
There is one very funny shot because some of the YouTube
ride throughs got capture some of the pre show videos.
And there's one very funny shot where he's just like crouched on the ground,
wiping up a spill with paper towels.
And as someone who did a fair amount of work when I was younger,
that I found very relatable and very funny because he was so shitty and uncomfortable.
They used to really be unconcerned about like optics on that stuff.
They were just like, we're universal and we're setting ourselves apart.
And all these rides are rated PG 13.
The rides used to literally have ratings.
I remember that like it was like like in the park map, it'd be like Terminator 2
is PG 13, which I was kind of movies.
You know? Yeah.
But and obviously like
Halloween Horror Nights was like a rated R experience because that's like so brutal
and like so violent, so insane.
All of that. Yeah.
So it's just like that's their that's their version of that.
But it does seem like.
They are only interested in pushing the envelope in that regard now with humor.
Ish. Yeah, right.
Like I couldn't I'll say this, like I think I might have even said this
on the podcast last time, but when I went to Halloween Horror Nights
a few years ago, I saw that Bill and Ted show and it was right before the election.
It was so.
Dark and it was it was so rough to be there in Florida.
Like I listen to you then.
What was shared for Trump a lot and like someone playing Trump
and there was someone playing Hillary and like whenever Hillary come out,
it was just like honestly, I should have known what was going to happen
because it was just groans and booze and like at her very image,
which I'm sure would happen now, like they have like a Biden or a Kamala.
I shudder to think what the reaction would be.
But shockingly, like Biden comes out and they shoot.
Yeah. Voice of reason.
Yeah, I mean, like it was all rather right.
But I just I have such a fear of what the actual mentality is.
Literally there and saw it.
And then the election was weeks later.
And obviously it went the way it went.
But I think like if they're willing to do that,
then again, it was Halloween Horror Nights, like at least there is like
they have the spirit of that in them, like they'll they'll go for it.
But we haven't seen it in actual rides, probably because they're
like always going to be there and they have to commit to the murder of someone.
Whereas like in a seasonal show, it's like, yeah, we can kind of make a joke here
and there. We might not ordinarily do.
Pull it. Pretend it never happened.
You didn't see. Also, there's a there's a murder of a woman in Revenge of the Mummy,
too, like that ride operator gets gutted and her blood splashes on you.
Yeah, that's true.
Wait, is there literally? Yes.
It's a water effect.
Or I don't remember that.
I always thought it was the broken glass.
I always thought it was simulating with glass breaking.
To me, it's like woman dies.
You get splashed like that to me feels like the the insinuation
is supposed to be that it's blood.
Hmm. Could it be glass and blood?
It could be both. OK.
Is it? I have a thing about
both of those specific iterations of Imhotep.
Is it weird that I find Imhotep cute?
Like the way he the way he moves, he's just like a little weird.
Like the way his arm catches Reggie, he's just so like little.
And what does it remind me of?
I like I don't know, like if you if you take a villain and like shrink him down,
it's the opposite of my big stuff problem.
He just seems like he's like he's only like four foot five.
Is his movements are so like he has little and jerky.
Imhotep has girl boss diva energy.
I mean, basically, Imhotep just put his hand up in Reggie's face
and sucked his soul out.
And it was not even a thing, honey.
Yes, that's how it feels.
You you you he says your souls are mine.
Death is only the beginning.
Girl, he is turning iconic lines in the ride.
Talk dirty to me, Dad.
Like it's so just erotic.
The with the power that that has.
We have no choice but to stand.
Oh, we have no we had no choice.
Join me and
riches, savor riches for all eternity.
Yeah. Or refuse and savor a more bitter treasure.
Saver. Yeah, there's a power, doesn't he?
Oh, yeah, hon.
I mean, like we're talking about.
And then what does he say?
When you when you fall back after the scarab beetles, he's like.
Nothing, not even the magic I can save you now.
I was like, oh, yes.
Damn. I'm about to get taken care absolutely of.
And then they shoot you shoot through his mouth.
It's very sexual, the ride.
Yeah. Yeah.
Serve me and savor.
Yeah, these are all very these are they're sexual verbs, aren't they?
Scott, when you say cute, were you just being like a little bit
like you were bearing a lead that you also were kind of getting a little
worked up by this guy? It was less.
No, I think it was less.
I was thinking cute more like a pet, like he just seems like, you know,
the energy of a big dog, but he's little and he tries to act tough.
That's that's what I was thinking.
But I assume you weren't you weren't aspect.
You you weren't erotically interested.
God, not then, but after your description, that that changes everything.
I got a lot of things to do.
Launch Queen.
Arnold, this not taking the queen part out.
That's staying.
No, it's just the no left. That's all.
No, he is.
You know, he's an underrated character.
I feel like just in general, like we all talk about the
obviously IP characters, you know, you're Vin Diesel on what's what's Dom, you know.
But this is a character that's not so famous that deserves a lot more attention,
you know, like Rex Star Tours or any of the other like in theme park characters.
Well, yeah, Mike, you're you're talking to us from a shelf
full of park stars, you know, the little, you know, characters,
dolls of characters are only in Disney parks.
There's no such thing at Universal.
They're they're much lighter on the merch and worshiping characters.
Not I mean, emo types in the movies, too.
But yeah, there should absolutely be the the toy of Rex or the Rex.
This is I'm holding up smart one part.
Sorry, he's very cute.
But there should be an emo tap.
Cute little vinyl figure you can get.
That's with my proportions thing, me calling him cute.
It'd be the most adorable, like two inch tall little guy.
And they could sell a sexy one and just kind of a cute one as well.
Like they could do a full one where he has full like male anatomy.
And then they could do one where he's like a little short stout vinyl.
Or he's like just gotten the pecs off of one of the bodies that he's,
you know, stolen parts from.
I have watched the Brendan Frasier
mommy the other night, I sort of understand they have.
I mean, I'm a toy collector.
I have, you know, I have these cute vinyl nations,
but I also have what's called hot toys and they are about their one sixth scale.
They're a little expensive.
And I have an Adam West that is fully like a man.
He's a fully little man.
They call it a hot toy.
That's the brand. It's called Hot Toys.
That's not a joke. Whoa.
Just the brand.
And they make a lot of, you know, one sixth scale toys
that are realistic proportions.
And they're very cool, very dynamic.
And I feel like let's get one of these with a emo tap.
He was on your shelf.
Who's on your Park Stars shelf who you'd like to see a little more fleshed out,
like a lot done, a little more hot toy style.
Well, certainly I would like a full Mark Twain toy.
Buff Mark Twain.
That's really good.
Let's see here.
I also think that.
A wall, a famous performer, Wally Bogue.
Oh, the star.
Golden Horseshoe.
Wow. You do collect toys.
Yeah. Oh, my God.
This isn't even the half of it.
I bet. So, yeah, there's other.
I mean, maybe a full hunk.
Mr. Potato Head doll.
Yeah. Carved up.
You sort of like, yeah, like, you know, slice those sides up a little bit.
Crunch him in. And yeah, he's looking good.
Totally. But one last one.
Adventurers Club.
Oh, yes. The general, the general or the major.
A lot of possibilities here.
A lot of possibilities for merch.
Yeah. But give us our our Universal Park Stars for sure.
Why don't they have a brand like that?
They do. We all do.
But they buy them.
Well, I bought I got my dad.
The they had a John Hammond one.
I got him that when we were down in Florida.
It was so hard to find.
I sold it one and I had to keep going back to stores
because the stock was so inconsistent.
But it's mostly like that was the main good one.
The rest was like Woody Woodpecker and then a faceless creature
with like a film strip for a face that just said universal.
Who is that? It was not a strippy.
I've never heard a strippy before.
It was like nothing.
But yeah, they should definitely make an emotive vinyl guy.
I mean, I am of the mind that Universal should make a another Brendan Frazier.
They should just do another one.
You're a big fan, I think, Jason, these movies.
I think especially like you were born.
Yes, I think it's they're the perfect like Saturday afternoon on TNT movies.
And I also think that we're due for a Frazier songs.
Like I think Brendan Frazier needs to have his Birdman or the unexpected
virtue of ignorance like where is Brendan Frazier's big prestige movie?
You know, I forget he was in crash.
Oh, yeah. OK.
Sure.
That would be the best picture.
And what we all agree it was the best picture.
I mean, of course, really, move questionably the country forward.
You know, had a lot to say.
The problems we're having now are just because everybody forgot about crash.
Everyone get a watch and certainly wouldn't make things way worse.
I've never I literally don't know what's contained in the movie crash.
A bad movie. It's a mess.
I've heard bad, irresponsibly written movie and won the Oscar.
Scientologist.
My favorite. That's best.
Yes, for sure. It beat broke back mountain.
Oh, yeah.
And that was like a shock at the time, I think.
Very much so.
Yeah, that was like because one was a very good movie and one was bad.
Yeah, I remember this.
So it really it sent shockwaves through the industry,
but not really because the industry is homophobic.
Sure. Yeah.
So hold on. Where was I?
I just have pictures of him a tap up here now.
Oh, wow.
Talking about his his sex appeal slash cuteness. Right. Yeah.
Yeah, it is.
I almost like forget because he's obviously not featured enough in Hollywood.
So I sort of forget him.
He's he's he's featured, but it's just not in like the animatronic is
so good in Florida.
And his presence is kind of he does he does he drop from the ceiling?
I'm actually confused now.
No, that's Hollywood.
Yeah. But I'm saying what what is he featured?
He's his head is featured.
But you go through his mouth in the lunch and also he's in the beginning
of the ride and, you know, like, I guess his like
visage is like present throughout the rollercoaster parts and like
you know, I guess you're sort of teased at the end, like he's not really dead.
Right. Yeah.
Haunts Brendan Fraser when he gets his cup of coffee.
What do we think of that part?
What's there in his opinion about the the Brendan Fraser coffee gig?
I mean, again, if you didn't know that he was wanting coffee
in the pre show, that means nothing to you.
And so like it's got to literally mean nothing to I'm going to go ahead and say
95 percent of the people that ride it on any given day.
It's very much a piece of the Men in Black, the fake world's fair
bookends of the ride, which you really miss if you do.
They didn't really think about the express pass as much back then
when designing stuff that there would be separate lines.
So there you could go to Men in Black, totally skip the setup
and just go right into the headquarters.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
It's kind of an odd ending.
And I guess with that, we should say you survive.
I guess I ride. That's the end of wrong.
Prepare to forfeit your afternoon.
Our one is only the beginning.
I it's the best.
It's the fake out ending of the ride in 2004.
It's good now. In 2004, it was mind blowing.
And I mean, we also have to say like, that's the part with the roof
on fire, which is like the ceiling rather.
That's amazing. I mean, like that holds up so much.
It's so impressive. It's so hot.
Like and I miss them doing fire effects, obviously.
I don't think it probably for environmental reasons.
They're not doing it all the time.
But that to me is such a strength of the ride.
And it makes me so reminiscent of the days of Jaws when that tanker would explode.
That's all universal.
There were so many in both Hollywood and Orlando, so many opportunities
to feel uncomfortably hot, to be real close to real flame.
A lot of gas smells.
I associate universal with the smell of real gas.
They've replaced.
I think I think theme park.
They've replaced maybe real fire with what we I think deemed steam fire.
Yeah. And the last one.
We like steam fire. We decided that.
And I think I'm assuming, you know, safer, cheaper.
So that's probably the way the future.
But yes, there is something because like
nothing freaks your body out like a flame.
Right. Yeah.
It puts you in a sense of real danger.
It's like, like whenever I'm riding Spider-Man and they decide
not to do that effect with the fire when the Green Goblin throws the ball.
I'm always like bummed because I know what it's like to be doing that
and then have that fire happen.
It's so unbelievably impressive. Right.
And and urgent.
Yeah. And they do the same thing on Transformers, right?
It's the same exact.
He shoots a missile.
Yeah. So. Yeah.
And Disney doesn't. Yeah.
Disney's Disney's track record with fire.
There's the fire on Indiana Jones, but they don't really.
Yeah. You're not close to the flame shooting up on Indiana Jones.
Fantastic. Canyon. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Which hasn't been there for years.
I mean, like even like Rise of the Resistance.
Like I just felt like something was missing with Rise of the Resistance
when I did it. I was really so blown away by this.
Like, I think it's so amazing what they were able to do.
But there was a sense of danger that was missing for me.
I think I said that I felt like the ride vehicle
like Indiana Jones, the ride vehicle shakes a lot and gives you that sense
of I'm in danger the whole time.
And it's such a smooth ride.
It was so time. Yeah.
And there's only a couple of scenes where you feel like, oh, crap.
Like when you're when those guns are going, you're like a little bit like,
am I going to crash into the gun?
But other than that, you're not maybe experiencing
like no. Yeah.
I respect what they were able to do with it.
But I think like like those blasters firing off, like I wasn't scared.
Like I just I felt like maybe this is because I'm 30.
But, you know, I and I'm not doing this as a 12 year old.
But I just felt like I think it is primarily exactly what you're saying.
The motion of the vehicle did not make me feel like there was enough chaos.
Yeah, I don't know.
Yeah, because I think that was a big when they were doing it.
And Jones trying to figure out how the vehicle would like
make you feel like you were really going through the thing
and you were really going to like tip over at any moment.
And I think that might have been yeah, that might have benefited from it.
Yeah, a little a little.
A little goes a long way, probably.
Obviously, it's like a cool ride vehicle and like it works.
I did the Pooh's Honey Hut in Japan, which is the same ride.
And that's a much that's a more of a property, maybe for a nice, smooth ride.
I would agree. Yeah.
So we like that.
What do we think of ride vehicles here?
I mean, we haven't talked about that a ton besides the launch.
It is a cool I like that it's this little like stout
roller coaster car and you feel because it's not a big long train.
You feel like you're able to really whip around corners.
And I like the bluntness of the mummy vehicle.
Yeah, I read a really interesting thing.
I never knew about this.
There was there's a theme park insider article from 2004
right before the Hollywood one opened and the ride vehicles
weigh themselves at the loading station so that it can like compensate
for the weight of the vehicle throughout the ride.
So like they joke like if it's a car full of like
football players versus a car full of children, like the ride can
counterbalance that.
And I never really knew that they used to do that with Dillion Dragons
so that they could meet exactly at the same time.
Oh, yeah. During the lift till they would get weighed.
And that's why one car would stop and one would
keep going to catch up to a certain place so that they they would know like once they.
Started going, they would meet up at the places where you're supposed to have near misses,
but that's a thing that they're able to do. Yeah.
These smart vehicles.
It's it's crazy seeing a roll.
I mean, I guess I'm trying to think how many seats is Hulk have on one car?
Is it the same as this?
I think four row, eight rows, 32.
I don't know if for whatever reason, the vehicle seems like very impressive
to be a crazy fast roller coaster and just be on like it looks like it's just on
this piece of metal and there's so many seats on it.
This is four rows of four seats. So it's 16. Yeah. Yeah.
I will say and this is mostly a Hollywood situation.
And I talked a little bit about it on the Six Flags episode.
This ride vehicle, especially when I did it a couple of times in Florida,
because I'm kind of tall and because of the way the seat goes up,
it oftentimes can crush my genitals.
And I really have to make a conscious effort getting into it
to adjust myself to not feel like my penis is going inside my body.
I don't have penile issues on this.
But what I do think is like the way the seats are, there's you sit super upright
and it's a very hard back like it's not like a cushy back for your head.
So the scene where you go into the scarab beetle section
and then you roll backwards when you pull up to the scarab beetles,
it stops so short, so hard. Yeah.
And it really hard.
And it does the same thing in the fake unload.
It stops really hard.
And you you hit you.
You really have to be careful there to not hit the back of your head.
And so that's the one thing I do say to people that I'm doing the ride with
for the first time. I'm like, hey, for this part, just like lean forward a little bit,
you know, because because because if your head's back, you're going to go.
Oh, yeah. It's nice.
There are, yeah, little things like that that I think I'm OK on it now.
But I remember the first time I went on it and it was I think that had the head
thing, too, and how hard the chair is.
I think I did all the I had all the mistakes happen to me
the first couple of times on it.
Well, can I say what happened to win Hollywood to me?
And really, I think why I misjudged the whole franchise,
I think for a long time, I didn't know how much better Florida was.
And I was highly anticipating this in 2004.
And I think I just got thrown by seeing one article that hyped it up too much.
There was some art might have been L.A. Times or something that said,
this is Universal's answer to the Indiana Jones adventure,
or maybe even that they were going to top it.
So I'm getting on that that universe, that Hollywood mummy with that expectation.
I'm about to go on something that is better potentially than the Indiana
Jones adventure. And as we know, not even close.
It's not even close to the Florida mummy itself.
So I've kind of always scored and and at the time I was a no lunch queen.
So all of that factored into me just not going on this ride in Hollywood
for many, many years.
It's crazy to think about because the Hollywood version opened
like a month after the Orlando one, which I don't think I ever really knew.
They cost the same amount of money.
One is much shorter.
I would say very compromised.
The same summer, the compromised Tower of Terror opens a California adventure.
So that was just the summer of abridged rides in Southern California.
I love loser West Coast cousins.
I when I first came out here and I think I had just been at Universal Orlando
and then a month or so later was at Universal Hollywood and rode the mummy.
And I was like, what the fuck was that?
Like I was so confused because I will grant that it's simpler story wise.
But I don't think they ever did a good job
communicating the story in the queue or the story,
especially the ending was always so janky.
And then I read so abrupt. It's it just ends. It just ends.
And then I read this.
I found this article from 16 years ago and they had a fully fleshed out back story.
It made so much more sense to me.
And I'm like, how did you get how did you mess this up?
Like, I don't I it's just a mind boggling.
Just to like play devil's advocate on the ending of the Hollywood version,
because the first time I did it, it did just end.
And I'm so used to the Hollywood, the Florida version, which
so commits to completing its narrative.
Yeah, as we've discussed.
But the thing about it is like there is something about the fact that it just ends
on like Imhotep's laugh and like the eclipse.
Like that makes that is like an eerie ending.
You know what I mean?
It's like you almost believe that you've been a part of like
the re-release of him into the world.
So that to me, I think works for me if I take a second to justify it.
But I mean, flat out, it does just end.
And then all of a sudden, you're in the load station and it feels like,
well, did that just happen?
But I do think that thematically and narratively, it does keep its integrity.
Well, because it's like the eclipse is bringing him back.
It's giving him the power.
And then the eclipse ends and then he like disappear like the
he loses his power is is what I saw.
And so like that kind of makes sense.
But like I just I don't I don't think they did a great job setting it up.
And a few years ago, they did tweak it a little.
But it's like, well, that didn't really add anything.
It was a real lateral move.
And I thought the eclipse killed him.
I thought that's always happening.
I didn't take it as that or maybe it did.
I don't know. It's been a it's been a bit.
None of us know.
I mean, that's not a good sign.
What does an eclipse do to him?
I've also done the one in Florida, I think, upwards of like
probably over 50 times.
And I've done the one in Hollywood like three or four.
Yeah. Is it do you like actively avoid it?
Have you been in that park and gone now?
It's not only recently living in Los Angeles.
So it's like I've only been a couple of times.
And then I'd only done it like once or twice before that,
like on vacations and stuff.
So I think it's not that I avoid it.
In fact, that's actually my favorite part because I love them.
And I do enjoy the Hollywood Mummy.
I can accept that it's not the Florida one.
Like, it's not bad.
I think it might even be the best thing down there
because because Jurassic World, I haven't been able to see.
And like, it's completely fleshed out state yet.
But that is my favorite section.
And especially when Mario Kart is done, that area is going to be
it's going to be all about the lower lot.
Yeah, yeah.
The area is gentrified with the existence of Mario Kart.
Yeah, I basically yeah, like I I really what I was saying earlier was
I've been not able to go and I was not going to Mummy.
I would skip Mummy now.
And, you know, we take for granted things in our lives.
And now during quarantine, I think I was saying let this be a lesson.
Always go on Mummy.
It's a privilege, even though it's the airport version of the Orlando version.
I always feel like that, though, like I always do every ride
because I never know when it's going to be the last time.
Like, yeah, always will go on ET when I'm there,
because you never know when it's going to be the last time.
Like it could be any day, for example, with Jaws.
Like, I didn't know the time that I did it was the last time I had ever done it.
And I almost had the instinct to go to go down there and do it one more time,
because that was truly the end of an era.
But I always make sure that I have logged hours on these things
in case they're going to go away.
Like, I always do Poseidon's Fury because I feel like its days are numbered.
Yeah.
I just always want to like have it fresh in my memory.
And, you know, the the one that we talked about this last time I was on, but Twister,
you know, I would do it every single time I was there
because I just knew they couldn't rely on that movie in the long term,
because it wasn't like it's not one that you remember forever.
Like Jaws or Back to the Future or, you know, whatever.
But I genuinely miss Waterworld,
which they're dying on the hill of every single day.
It seems to work.
I don't know. I don't think it's a full water world area somewhere.
Yeah, it's huge.
It's strange.
I think they thought about doing a new movie based off the success of the stunt show.
Oh, is that right?
No, they have. I know I'm I'm asking.
You're proposing. They should. Yeah.
You know what I think that if they would have success
with like a Waterworld Netflix movie, I think that's a perfect.
Yeah. Yeah.
Boot forward on streaming, I think would be really good for that
franchise, because I think people just ultimately didn't want to pay
to go see that movie in theaters.
But now if you could just sit on your couch and watch that, I think people would.
And probably decrease the urine drinking element,
maybe give a little less percentage of that of the running time to urine drinking.
Yeah. Lean on the action adventure of it all, unless on the survivalist aspect.
I think you'd have something good.
And also, like you could bring back the cost of your character as like a,
you know, like a mentor for someone or.
And you know that it's not like.
But that is also a depressing topic.
Like our world is covered in water because of climate stuff.
That might hurt it. Yeah.
People don't want to let's go into a world of water for a while.
That's a reboot of Postman instead.
I do keep saying I do it all post man means
really not mean, but I keep seeing people posting about the post man
and the like the fear of the state, the post office. Yeah.
Oh, right. Right. Of course.
I didn't realize Tom Petty.
I think we've talked about it before. Tom Petty is in the post, man.
Oh, right. OK. Yeah.
So I don't know.
I just like that.
That's just a good thing.
Like about it.
You know, what's another thing I realized
factoring into my dislike of the Hollywood version that is something
that the Florida one doesn't have on its back is that the Hollywood one
is the one that evicted our beloved ET.
That's like a stink. It doesn't have to have anywhere else.
And so you're going to do a lesser version of a really truncated thrill ride
where there used to be a kind of significantly long dark ride.
It just didn't seem like a an improvement to me.
I just always felt hurt by the ET eviction.
Well, of course.
And it was ET.
Forgive me. Was the ET was did the building outside look the same?
Like it was just the soundstage.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. But barely themed. Yes. OK.
Because I think like if they really went the extra mile with the exterior of Mummy,
maybe you could have been like, well, at least it like it's it's visually better
now than it was before.
It looked just sort of like a boring soundstage, but they didn't do that.
So it just looks like you're going into a soundstage.
They just painted it beige is all they did.
Or orange ish.
I don't know what the color is.
And I'm sure, look, all this stuff, all this stuff is what the universal
creative people wanted. I'm sure they wanted a theme.
And it's just a money situation.
I always I don't know why I feel like there's universal creative people
listening, going, we tried. Shut up.
It's also like space. There's no space down there.
And that's ultimately why the ride is not great or not.
Not what we're used to in Florida, because it's just they didn't have the space.
Like, and also remember, it's like ET can be a long dark ride
because you can move slowly like in a high speed thrill ride.
You got to move through this building and there's just not the room.
So that is something that you run into when you are going to say, let's
you know, shoot for the moon here with only so much room.
Right. Whereas, you know, like that's why you can fit something like Transformers
or just two levels and it can feel so big.
Like when you because when you compare like what Transformers feels like
to what the mummy is and what Jurassic World feels like to what the mummy is.
Well, I'm nervous about Mario Kart for this reason for that.
Like, is that going to be enough space down there?
I'm not, because that the building that they
the thing is, they had to fill an existing space with the ET becoming mummy
with Mario Kart, they created a gigantic sound stage,
which also uses two levels.
So it's not going to be a concern.
I think that's going to be this.
It's the exact same size.
Basically, the ride is not the land.
I think the land is going to be smaller than the one in Japan.
But the ride is small.
Well, the land is the land is not going to have Yoshi. Right.
It's not going to have like the Yoshi Omnimover type. Right. Right.
So you've been seeing those going to be the one ride in Hollywood.
Have you been seeing those like what people can see over the fences in Japan?
The Yoshi's and the coins and the plants. Oh, my God.
It looks cool. It looks really cool.
I'm excited to see it when when it's totally done with the Donkey Kong of it all.
Yeah. Yeah. But, you know, the Yoshi ride, it doesn't look like it's for me.
But I think for the people that it'll be for, aka kids,
I think it'll be really fun.
The Mario Kart ride.
I'm really excited to see what it's going to be, because they're talking a huge game
like about this one, too, almost reminding me of the way they talked about the mummy
before it opened.
Like they're saying it's going to be like unlike anything they've seen,
like the state of the art, like now new gold standard of theme park attractions.
And so I guess I would say like they talked about that with mummy.
They talked about that with Harry Potter.
The Forbidden Journey, anyway.
And then they're talking about that again now with Mario Kart.
And I feel like they were right the first two times.
So, yeah, yeah.
I think it's the main thing we all have to look forward to in our lives
is the Mario Kart.
This is like for me, it's the Jurassic Coaster.
But yeah, the Mario Kart thing is for sure.
Yeah.
The one other thing about the Hollywood ride that kind of set it apart
when you would exit the Hollywood ride, there was a long hallway
with statues of mummies.
And for I don't know how long they did this,
but it happened to be multiple times.
One of those mummies was a guy
and he would jump down off his pedestal or like move around.
Like it was a scare actor who would like swipe at you.
And people always fell for it.
Really?
That's I mean, I love when they do shit like that.
It's fun.
Yeah, I appreciate it.
Now, at the time, I didn't know it was coming and it scared the hell out of me.
At the time when it was intended to be scary, it did scare you.
It worked.
Therefore, it was not a pleasant emotion.
I'm impressed, but I am glad it is God.
Tony Baxter said that there was a period of time
where they did that on Haunted Mansion.
There was like a one actor in the hallway or something,
and he would just jump out in front of the car.
I wonder if they still do that at Skull Island.
That was a big in the marketing for for Kong Skull Island
is that there were going to be scare actors roaming the queue.
Yeah.
And there were the last time I last time I did the main queue anyway, there was.
Like I said, I'm always getting the express because I don't
now that I've seen the things once, I don't need to see them again and again
in terms of the queue experience.
But there's a lot of cool stuff in the in the Kong Skull Island queue.
And one of them was a very scary live actor.
Yeah.
Thanks.
I think I missed that when I I think I did the pass.
Yeah, he would like poke out of holes like that were in the queue.
Like it was like he would just go, you know, it's just like a scary,
like problematic native.
Yeah, sure. Yeah.
That's I will say I would have been scared.
But Matt, when you were last here, I was not doing fright fests and horror nights.
But now I'm into haunts.
So that's happened, too.
So I think I like the idea of that.
But I think you got you.
Boys are growing up.
That is what is happening.
Really are. Tell us we're good.
Tell us we've done good.
You're doing so good.
You're doing such a great jobs.
And I'm so proud of you guys.
This is what I needed.
And yeah, but Jason, have you bucked up and gotten over anything like that?
I think I've had some breakthroughs in therapy, but other than that,
I think my theme park going hasn't really changed that much.
Great. OK, well, at least emotionally, things are on the up.
You know, I'm trying my best.
Oh, good.
What are we what are we missed here?
We're talking.
Yeah, we were talking about
Rise of the Resistance.
Scott Trowbridge was the lead on this ride as well,
in addition to being the lead on Rise of the Resistance.
Genius.
Whole.
Giles's Edge.
I stand.
The only thing about Galaxy's Edge is I think that Laniam Falcon is a fucking flop.
But but Rise of the Resistance, he did an amazing job.
Yeah, it was.
I think it was hard for me to say or hear phrases like that at the time.
And now just as the months go on, I don't it.
You have to.
It's a flop. It's OK.
It's I don't know if I can even say it.
It's still so I can't I almost can't accept it.
Something I was looking forward to so much is a flop.
Maybe I was a little relieved to hear you say it.
It was a really ambitious idea,
but it was not.
Executed well.
We need new levels, we need new places.
I don't want to do no more of these crates.
I don't want to crash.
All of that.
It also should just be, you know what?
Just give people the Star Wars.
You know what I mean?
Like we don't know this character.
Like we don't really have a lot of time to get to know him.
The jobs for a lot of people in that cockpit.
The jobs are really stupid.
Like if you happen to be in the last row and you're like, what, the engineer?
Like it's so lame.
I think Gunner is worse than engineer, though, because Gunner is just like,
what am I even doing here?
And I have to work very hard.
It's hard to see.
You know what I mean?
Like it's just like visually not appealing.
The worlds don't seem super different from each other.
At the end, something I really hate is when you you stop the ride and he says,
it appears there's something you've brought back with you on the ship.
And then it's nothing.
And you don't even see anything.
Nothing happens.
It's just like blue balls the entire time.
There's nothing in the queue.
It's not interesting to look at.
It's there's no characters that we enjoy or appreciate.
And for that to be the lead of the entire land that was launching the land,
it was really, really, really whack.
And then thank God the rise of the resistance kind of capitalized on all the promise
because it really tied the land together in every way which it needed
because the Millennium Force, sorry, Millennium Falcon Ride was.
I yes, I feel like, though, I do feel like it may be not impossible
to at least take it up a letter grade.
I do think you could probably make some tweaks
and it won't be perfect, but it will maybe be a more consistent experience
because because and we don't need to get off.
I think we've said this before.
Like Star Tours has moments that you remember.
There's drama.
There's like there's something happening.
There's a compelling reason for you to be there.
You're in a giant monster's mouth and you remember it getting off the ride.
That was crazy. The tongue hit the windshield.
There's like comedy and like Star Wars is a wacky kids adventure movie.
Let's not forget what Star Wars is, which is their sci fi action
adventure soap operas for kids. So.
Why are we taking ourselves so fucking seriously with this Millennium Falcon Ride?
Like it just feels like not fun.
Yeah, yeah, it might be a lot of the Rex appeal for me is that Rex is a pure
comedy character and it's not ponderous like
some of the elements of Star Wars I vibe with less.
But it's also like.
The scoring of it all, what to compare to what?
You know what I mean? Like, I don't know what this what this score means.
They never tell you what's a good score.
Absolutely. What did I do correctly?
You know what I mean? Like what was it that got me this point score that did it?
And it's like you'd have to do it a bunch of times, like I guess.
It's like the men in black of it all.
Yeah, but I get the men in black of it all because you've told me how to shoot
these aliens. I know what I'm doing. I'm killing aliens.
I know what happens at the end because you get like Galaxy, the vendor, cosmic,
whatever, blah, blah, blah. Yeah.
On this, it's like they put a number in front of you in a weird font
and then you leave.
And like, there's the one cool touch of like the Millennium Falcon is obviously
beat up and like technically failing as you leave.
But other than that, it's like this was really garbage, like
because I don't understand what's happening.
Men in black simple hit the red button.
Rip-torn screams that you hit the red button like you could simplify
the Millennium Falcon down to everyone hits a button once
and then everyone gets it is satisfying to touch the buttons.
Yeah. You have to dumb it down for me.
I think kind of smart 30 year old who's invested in theme parks and this IP.
What the fuck is anyone else getting from it?
You know what I mean? I'm just like, who is leaving that park saying,
a highlight for me in Disneyland was Millennium Falcon.
I don't think any as a six year old flying, like doing the actual flying
and getting to go work.
I guess, I guess.
I think that's the probably the best thing you can do in it.
I mean, I spent a lot of time on BATU last year
and I rode this single rider with so many families
and the confusion.
Yeah. Every time Grandma was.
I was always next to Grandma in the engineer's seat
and she did not know what was going on.
Oh, and it's like, I think they had a lot.
They had a meeting early on.
They were like, well, everybody's going to be fighting to do something in the cockpit.
False. Not true.
That is not going to happen.
Also, like what what does happen is like your experiences
are dictated by what everyone else does.
And it's like if you're in there with like another family of three,
if you're like in a three and you get with another three, it's like
that's like conflict.
Yeah. And I wanted I want to deal with conflict with people
that are like at Walt Disney World's Hollywood Studios.
Like, I really don't.
You're like at a Thanksgiving dinner of people you don't know who are
just having a real rough year.
The ball dropped completely, completely.
Boy, boy. Yeah, I was.
There were kids I was trying to gun effectively,
and there were kids who just driving the Falcon into the dirt.
Yeah, because again, like they have no incentive to not.
Yeah. Anyway.
Boy, I think they can fix.
I think it can be fixed slightly.
I like America, right?
So that's a different story.
I hate these video game rides.
Like unless it's really clear, like Midway Mania or
like Men in Black, I don't like I'm not super psyched
about this Spider-Man thing that's going to happen in California.
I'm worried. Yeah.
I don't I don't know why is why is it not just a ride?
I don't understand.
I don't care.
I don't need to be actively involved in it with a gun in my hands.
Like, in fact, I reject it.
Just put me give me take me on the journey.
Well, we've said or I've said, I think I'm a little worried about the new
the new version of you are the thing that's apparently coming to Avengers
because it's like you train, you suit up.
And I'm like, I as a kid, I wanted to be Iron Man,
I wanted to be Iron Man, but I don't want to be me as a superhero.
Why are you making me do work?
Yeah, I don't.
I've heard somebody claims that it's going to be cool.
You're going to lose somebody. Who is that?
Oh, we have inside. We have some insiders.
Got our people to, you know.
OK, so what are they saying?
They said that it's going to be very cool how the web
when you do your little Spider-Man motion, that it's going to be very cool
and it works really well when you're shooting webs at whatever the nanobots
or whatever they are.
OK, but I also think like do this for 30 seconds and go,
oh, I'm a little tired.
Yeah, anybody with carpal tunnel.
I get so exhausted on Midway Mania, I get my wrist.
Oh, yeah.
Rounds.
It's like that thing when like the web part of your thumb
and your your pointer finger start like stinging, you know that?
Yeah, yes.
I it's and I like me when we may allow, but I am by the end
when you're doing the thing where you're supposed to when they're flying off
the little mine cart section, I am dead.
My my arm is dead.
Yeah. And in between the scenes, I get so like,
OK, got to stretch, got to limber up.
Wait, you do do like hand yoga here.
Speaking of that area of the park, like when I when I went at truly six
in the morning to do Rise of the Resistance, because I was one of those people
that did, I'm sure you guys were as well.
Like, yeah, early, early as crack of dawn by myself.
I was I literally was in group 10.
I was like, I went on right away, but I had enough time to go do the slinky dog,
which also gets a crazy line and it wasn't one of my fast pass elections.
I liked it. Oh, yeah.
Yes. Yeah. It's really fun.
It's such a lot. It is so charming.
It's so, you know, it's not like it's thrilling, but like it's fun.
There's so much scenery to go through that second launch.
I mean, like, it's really cute.
I love the spinning rings.
Like, I like that slinky dog. You can hear him talk.
Yeah, it felt like like, again, like a really good, well executed idea.
And I'm not surprised that it's so popular.
So relaxing to be on, like maybe the one of the smoothest roller coasters ever.
Yeah, definitely. Like in the same way, Big Thunder is like I could see it being
like a scared nine year old who's tall enough will go on it and love it.
And it'll be the first coaster.
So it's like really the age range is high.
Yeah, it feels classic. Yeah. Yeah.
Or or a, you know,
34 year old was still one of his first launch coasters ever,
as it was at the time.
I got brave enough to do slinky dog. Can you believe it?
I mean, we got to get you on the Jurassic coaster when it opens, though.
That sounds great. And I don't have to be afraid of these.
I used to when this podcast started, I was like, well, we'd talk about a ride.
And I'd say, but that's off limits to me because I cannot launch.
And I got over. Take off your shackles.
You got to be brave enough to do this.
I mean, this Jurassic coaster, I think it's going to be really good.
Sounds fantastic. Yeah.
Yeah. Possibly.
Do you do you think it could take the title from Hagrid's
as Hagrid's took you think?
I think it will. I think it will. Wow.
Yeah, I don't think I'm giving it no thought.
It's been like a sleeper to me.
I haven't been looking at the updates like you guys.
And so I'm amazed to hear it's like what's great about Hagrid's is it's like,
yes, it has seven launches, but it's a family coaster.
This is like an adult coaster, which is themed to an adult popcorn movie,
which I which I, you know, like the threat of dinosaurs ripping you to pieces.
Like, of course, kids can enjoy it and like it, but I like it.
I like that they, you know, matched a type of ride to a type of film.
And I feel like that is universal.
You know what I mean? Like that is something that Disney would never do.
Like Disney is never going to make you feel like,
um, you know, a dinosaur is going to kill you.
And in fact, when they did do that, they backed off of it and made that ride so much more tame.
Like, but but I was really respecting them for Countdown to Extinction because it was so chaotic
and so rough and so dark and so scary that when they backed off of it, I was like, this is why.
And when they backed off Alien Encounter, you know what I mean?
Like, just like they they they they've like really.
And maybe they're going to go back to it now that they have, like, you know,
the IP that they have in there, like so into that.
But I don't know. I just felt like they were
a little lame, a little lame when Universal wasn't.
And so I think that, like, I mean, the fact that we're getting a launch into a top hat,
like that's great to me.
And that inversion that's right out of the top hat, it's like a like a it's like a serious airtime,
like a corkscrew or whatever.
It looks really, really, really, really, really, really.
Since you brought that can't tend to extinction, can I just get your eyes on something?
I'm going to screen share here.
Do you think that baby Aladar is cute?
I think that's so cute.
Yes. I'll never win.
I'll never win.
Nothing invested in this bit.
This is a fight has been going on.
We've been fighting about this.
I think it's so cute.
Like, if I saw it in my apartment, I'd probably be like, I'd kill it.
But I do think that it's so cute.
Now that I know what it is.
Understandable.
Scott, I do appreciate you, you bringing up something cute.
Of course, Imhotep the mummy.
Yeah, I appreciate you.
I don't know why. I think he's cute in the window shatterer, too.
I like that he's like miniature.
I think it's the fact that he's like a little he's a he's like a miniature pony.
I think that's that's exactly how I feel about him.
Can I give you a little a little piece of information about the animatronic?
Yes. Universal claims Imhotep is the most sophisticated animatronic robot ever
developed. This is obviously at the time for a theme park capable of lifting
two thousand five hundred pounds.
His arms are hollowed out stainless steel that can be programmed
to perform motions four times faster than any other theme park robot.
Wow. And that are six times cuter.
Which is why it's literally frozen in time, not working,
because they probably bit off way more they could chew.
It doesn't matter that it can do any of those things.
It doesn't work.
So it's like that's the only thing about it is I do wish they could like
go back in there and refurb the audio animatronics.
But I actually think they'll.
This is controversial, but I think that they'll re theme
and do a new attraction before they do that.
That's what I was going to ask.
Do you think would you be upset about this or would you feel like
I it's had its time and I trust Universal to bring us something better?
I think it has less than 10 years.
Well, yeah, yeah.
I could see them, you know,
I think it could use a little fresh coat paint, a facelift.
But I do think it's it's pretty popular.
And I don't quite know.
I mean, Fast and the Furious, a Fast and the Furious ride done like this,
I think would have been a big hit.
I think that they just they just fucked up with Fast and the Furious.
And it was because they were trying to save money.
But because they already had the Hollywood
well, the footage sets and yeah.
Yeah. And I think that they were they got such a bad response to that,
which is I think what actually was the idea behind Hagrid's
is they were like, we need something big that's practical.
That is going to, you know, really give
classic energy, because when the Tonight Show
ride happened and the Fast and the Furious ride happened
and they happened so close together, it was just like,
what are we doing this for?
Like you you carbon copied Transformers from Spider-Man.
That system already.
And you're now doing this with King Kong and Fast and the Furious.
And you're you're doing a Tonight Show IP.
Like there's something wrong.
There's just something off.
And it didn't feel like the same park anymore.
And there's also so much Harry Potter that it kind of felt like.
And their IPs are getting old, like they still had Terminator at the time,
which was an older IP, and they had like, you know, Shrek,
which is like something that I think over time,
people are caring less and less about.
So they were really in like a tough spot, I think just in terms of IP.
So I think that I would agree with you that the ride will stay there
as long as they don't create new IP or find a way to make existing IP fresh.
And that's going to be an improvement on the ride.
But they do seem like they want to do this thing of every single year
something gets new put in the park. Yeah.
Which they've been pretty good about doing.
And I think that the thing about ET is they've got a problem with Spielberg
because he says don't take it down.
They have like a relationship with him where he where he doesn't want that ride
taken down.
And I also think it does give you the classic universal movie energy,
whereas like, you know, the Simpsons doesn't.
Men in Black, that movie's aging,
but it moves it moves crowds.
And then like, what else do you have?
I mean, they're not going to they're not going to take the Fast and Furious ride
out, even if it's bad, while that franchise is still going.
The Mummy franchise is not still going. Yeah.
You know, tonight show ride, like as shitty as it is, it feeds the tonight show brand.
So they'll keep that.
Born Identity is new.
Shrek, that 3D space is is is going to be a 3D show for whatever.
It'll probably be like Kung Fu Panda, whatever is doing well.
And then you have Despicable Me, which is like, you know,
you can't do much with that space besides that.
So it's like, what else is there in the park really to replace?
Which they said they were committed to doing.
So this is not something I want to happen,
but it's something that I think we need to get used to the idea of.
What do they have? It's like
Peacock Saved by the Bell reboot.
Can that become a coaster?
Well, yeah, I mean, they do have other Nintendo stuff.
Right. Which will become its own little mini lands.
And I've also heard a rumor that they might have to dump
Nintendo land in one of the existing parks.
Yeah, because there's a contract.
So they like that like Barney and Fievel, like Yank Barney and five.
Well, that was the original plan. Yeah.
So that might still happen.
You're no that could be my dead body in.
Woody Woodpecker's Barnstormer.
What's the no, that's goofy.
That area is so large, like I'm never back there
because I'm never going to see Barney.
But like that entire the entire Curious George area
and the Barney like stage is huge.
Like I went back that back there for Halloween Horror Nights.
And I was like, there's like a whole maze back there and the Barney thing
and the Curious George and Fievel's playground.
And I'm like, oh, there's a ton of space here.
So it made sense that that was going to be
Super Nintendo land.
But then when they were moving Super Nintendo land to the new park,
that was ultimately going to be a Pokemon thing. Right.
So you guys know about the rumors that that was going to be Pokemon.
Super Nintendo land was going to be in the new park
and that they were going to phase out Poseidon's Fury
and the Lost Continent area to be a Zelda thing.
Yeah. Oh, interesting.
But now I don't think so.
Yeah, I think that's all.
But I think, yeah, they think they just have to have some sort of Nintendo
presence in Orlando by a certain day.
But obviously, that time frame is all different.
But I don't know. Yeah, because of money, will they like cram
some Nintendo things somewhere and not do a full themed like Zelda land,
which is my prediction is that what will happen is.
By the by the early next year,
it'll be announced that Epic Universe is not happening
or it's postponed indefinitely, and they're going to do
Nintendo land in universal in Universal Studios.
And I think they might try to find a way to repurpose something
that they were going to do in the new park with Harry Potter,
a fantastic beast or whatever.
I think they'll try to do something in the Fear Factor area, maybe. Right.
Oh, yeah. Oh, that's got to be.
Yeah, that was one of the most unpleasant theme park live shows
I have ever seen.
Is that relevant, though, because the host of Fear Factor
is the biggest figure in all of media?
Well, now, when you go to see that Fear Factor show, just a guy
sits on the stage and tells you about DMT and like
mixed martial arts and all of that.
Move to Texas, bro.
I'm out of here. Texas.
And he also he actually the big finale of the show is he says a lot of transphobics.
Yeah. Yeah.
And the Florida crowd, they go wild, wild.
Not the people listening to this who are good.
And we know that. So just to say that.
Yeah. But if you're saying transphobic slurs, you're not good.
Oh, no. Then you're then you're not.
These are just all right. These are different people.
I'm just going to keep I'm just going to keep spinning holes if I don't
stop talking at some point in time.
Do we make it our way at the end, Jason?
Well, I have a very odd that this has not come up yet.
But since the you know, the setup of the Florida ride is that there's a,
you know, the there's a curse, the curse.
Everyone's worried about the curse.
They're all wearing Magi medallions.
And then, of course, poor Reggie learns the curse is real.
Do you guys know the story?
I read about this years ago.
I could not find the original article, but I found out the facts about it.
Do you know the story about Stephen Summers cursed house he bought?
What director of the mummy, Stephen Summers, the director, cursed house?
Yes. Now bear with me.
There's a bit of a leak.
So in 2007, he, Stephen Summers and his family bought a house
in Malibu for 10 million dollars.
The previous occupants of this house were the newly
read's Britney Spears and Kevin Federline.
Mr. Popo's Al himself, Kevin.
Oh, yeah, of course. Wow.
They put a lot of money into fixing up this house
and put it on the market, asking for he paid 10 million initially.
They were trying they were asking for it for 15.95 million
because they had put so much work into it.
It sat on the market for three years and eventually sold for 11.45 million.
And simultaneously with that, Stephen Summers career
as a director was really slowing down.
He did the G.I. Joe movie and then the adaptation of the Stephen
Coons books, Odd Thomas.
And that was kind of the last we've heard of Stephen Summers.
So I remember coming across this years ago and the writer chronicling
the foibles of this house was like, this house might be cursed.
Britney Spears and Kevin Federline, Stephen Summers,
like, it's not good energy at this house.
Wait, he's blaming the house on the career falling apart.
Like that, just like if you're superstitious, like I wouldn't buy this house.
There's no way you're a white man in Hollywood who fails.
It can't possibly be you.
It's got to be. It's got to be your home that's cursed.
It's got to be your eleven point ninety five million dollar home.
There's not even a ghost story.
No, it's just a very weird connection between Kevin Federline
and Stephen Summers and his directed career kind of slowing down.
But his career was bright.
She had the whole world ahead of him.
And then this house, this cursed house, cursed house.
The curse was real.
Well, Britney Spears, like in the early 2000s, her career also kind of getting weird.
So like the poor woman was through the ringer.
Her plan. She was saying this house is fine.
All right. Let's just let me as the gay here just get on record by saying
she actually hit her creative peak in the early aughts.
OK, because the Blackout album was a piece of art.
And never forget in the zone and also never forget that she
revitalized what it meant to be a pop star in Vegas. OK.
People before her were like, it's the sunset of my career.
I'm going to Vegas.
Britney Spears said, I'm Britney Spears.
I'm like 35. I'm going to Vegas.
And now you see all the girls in the peaks of their careers going to Vegas.
I'm not saying the work is bad.
You know, I'm not saying the words are good.
When does Perfume come out?
Oh, bitch, that's been out.
No, I know. But when is that? When is it?
When did it come out? When does when did it come out?
That was on Britney Jean, which was like 2000.
Third. So that's even later.
Perfume is even later.
I'm such a big fan of I know Sia wrote it.
Yes, I really respect you for knowing Perfume.
I think Perfume is one of the best pop songs. I'm not even kidding.
And she famously sounds a thousand years old on it.
She sounds like she sounds in Motep's age.
It's like the track Perfume is like Jolene.
Like it's like the same like the feeling.
Yeah, it's like you feel the say you feel the emotion
very strongly in both those songs.
And you do it as you can.
Can anyone? I don't know the song well enough.
I could do it myself, but so I wait for
a call and I try to act natural.
Have you been thinking about her?
About me?
Work, bitch, for all eternity.
There's your title of that.
Yeah, there it is.
Awesome. Well, I think I think on that note,
on the note that the curse is real of the house, at least.
Matt Rogers survived.
Podcasts the ride.
There is no escape, but we'll try to get out through the gift shop.
Is there anything you would like to put?
Oh, I just put my podcast, Last Culture East,
that's where I sometimes I'm allowed to talk about things like this,
although when I do, it's it gets real insular.
So but you can listen to that.
I co-host it with my best friend, Bowen Yang.
Is he is he anti theme park or is it just you know, very pro, very pro.
It's just that once I get going, I can take up a lot of space with that stuff.
So I have to check myself.
And then I have plenty of space here, plenty of expansion pads.
So I want to go at the end of the month in September.
I have a show coming out on HBO Max that I'm hosting called Hot Dog,
which you mentioned before, which is a dog grooming competition show.
So I'm really excited about that.
Wow. Wow. And I have my show on Quibi called Game Show.
Wonderful. It's great. Yeah.
And as for us, you can check us out on Facebook, Twitter and Instagram.
And there's three bonus episodes every month at Patreon dot com slash podcast.
The ride that's the second gate, not canceled like Epic Universe.
Mm hmm. Not on what?
Yes. Yeah.
And I think I speak for all of us when I say we would have enjoyed this podcast
a lot more if we'd all gotten our cups of coffee.
This has been a forever dog production executive
produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts dot com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify
or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter
and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.