Welcome to podcast the ride the second gate where today we set sail on one of the most ill-advised
ventures in theme park history pseudo theme park history. I'm scott gertner mike carlson how do you feel about this one?
I feel sort of sad that it didn't make it because in concept everything that I've
Seen online at least in concept. This seems cool. It seems like it could have been cool
But it was a disaster and why and why not try to I know it seems like an odd fit of brand and
Thing to do but like why should disney be to get the full cruise pie? It doesn't make sense. There's so much
Wonderful ip that universal has and uh jason charidan. Are you disappointed you didn't get to try this? Um,
Yeah, I guess um
Yeah, I don't know. I just uh
Sorry, I don't use I just feel a little what confused a little weird about
What's wrong? What's going on? What's what are what's happening to you right now? Uh
Well, you know, you guys know I I like doing the research for the show. I love digging digging down
We know that yeah. Yeah, that's one of your things one of your trademarks. Yeah. Yeah a little research boy and I
but um
You know, I found I found some like speculation of like when will universal try to tackle the cruise market, but I
I really didn't find a lot else about this
and I
I don't know. What do you I? I it's not like it was the deepest dive. I don't think I've
I know all about the shrek deck. I know all about hitch cocks the adults only lounge
Like why why was this so crazy? Um, he splat ets wet and wild the children's kiddie pool with the giant et
I yeah. Yeah. No, yeah, I I came across some of that. I don't I maybe i'm just feeling weird
Maybe we should have pushed this recording. I've just been kind of
Like I feel like weird stuff is going on. Like I like first off. I don't even know how we got
This zoom. I usually mike sends out the zoom email, but I just got texted a zoom link and like
Well, I was wait wait from wait a minute. I just that happened to me like yeah
It had no source. Like I assumed it was from mike, but then there was just it was just blank
It I don't know where the yeah, I thought that was a weird tip
Yeah, we showed up and it was you and I in the room and then mike and so
I just chalked it up to technical difficulties. But then I was I've been kind of rearranging like trying to
Purge and rearrange my room and stuff and like I came across the coffee coin you remember
Where like two years from city walk? This is the city walking. Yeah, the city wall coffee
We're about two years out from the city walk saga. And um, oh, yeah, we'll wait. Yeah. Yeah, we yeah
We were doing this. Yeah, well like two years ago right now. Yeah, and and I
It it felt like it was calling to me
And I feel like if I looked at it at the corner of my eye it it looked like it was glowing like pulsate like
what so are you uh, how much how much has the the pot smoking increased during I know it's like
It's that you've enjoyed it during the eat it. These people don't usually hallucinate. Jason, what are you smoking and can I have some of it?
You know, I that's
That's fair. I mean it's certainly helping with the the quarantine but but yeah, not not significantly that it would
It would be that bad. But I you know, I kind of I unwrapped the coin because it it was still
Had some painter's tape on it from the live show. Um, and I I gave it a wash. I gave I cleaned it just to see
Because I realized like yeah, it was really grimy, you know, you got to give it a clean coins. I yeah and I
I never noticed this before there was an inscription on the coin
An inscription, I mean, I guess I never got a good look at it, but there's wait
There's like something on it that you didn't see before. Yeah, and it was like, you know, I was like, I'm not sure
It's like something on it that you didn't see before. Yeah, and it it said when two years have come and gone
extra sectors lie beyond
What what what right boys
It's time what did you guys hear that?
Yes, i'm back
What are you talking about?
We got a surprise
Poppin that's like it started it got it was distorting and glitching out and then suddenly oh my god the sector keeper
That's right boys. I'm back. Yes. Yes. I'm back because there's a missing sector boys
This isn't about universal cruises. I sent the link out
Boys, you said this is a magic zoom link
Yes via my cricket wireless prepaid phone. I I only had three texts left this month
Boys, wow, this is sector 20 hit the music
When your town has let you down
When your port has fallen short
When you're too worn out to run
And need some ribs or a cinnabon
Cinnabon you need a place a place for rock a place for roll
A place where oakland raiders merch is sold a sublime hot topic and billabong
A place where you can purchase a candy thong
So let's go take a walk
Let's all go to city walk
Tonight podcast the ride presents the city walk saga sector 20 an addendum to our daily
19-part extremely necessary series do multiple closures and a pandemic hinder city walks ability to deliver its wonderful magic
Well, keep listening to find out
Whoa
Whoa, you are kid. All right. This is a big turn. I this is unprecedented
You obviously in podcast the right history. We've been asked to bail on the topic and a second
Theme song has been added when we're just now
This has ended up being a surprise the city walk saga is back. Oh my god, scott
Let me let me do the honors here. Welcome to podcast the ride the city walk saga sector 20
Yeah
I'm, so out of I didn't even think to do that. My name is mike carlson
And scott garner is very flustered. Boy. Yeah, I forget the protocols about all this. It's been so long
It was nice to hear that
Yeah, it was nice. It was a simpler time
Jason, sorry. I scrambled your brain
I you know if it's for the sake of quality
Podcasting i'm all for it, but i'm just happy i'm not being driven mad
Geez I shouldn't have I shouldn't have blamed it on the demon weed
Um that you were being called to and the sector keeper is back with us. How you been? It's been a while
I'm good. Yeah good to be back excited to talk about
the city uh city walk and
Uh, you know
Just a you know a place no matter what it never changes
Uh always feels good
It's like home
Yeah, yeah, well that's sort of true. I mean like
I I guess it's funny that this can there must have been
Something in the air because I don't it's all it's almost like like in a way
we knew that this was coming and that we were going to be called to do this because
strangely a couple days ago
The three of us gathered for the first time anywhere in six months
And we actually went up to city walk
All together we were finally we the three of us finally reconvened up. We went to city walk. Yeah. Yeah, it was crazy
It was crazy
so
Reconvened
Uh, yeah, because we haven't seen each other for a
A while and it's kind of weird to be at city walk. You haven't seen each other
summer break
schools out missing friends
Oh
Well, certainly the latter
He definitely the yeah. Yeah. Yeah, we we have a no does he I don't know. Yeah, we haven't recorded since
march
so yeah, there's
Do you know what?
There's something happening in the world right now sector keeper that is preventing a lot of people
from gathering
Let me think
Um, yeah, take your time in their houses watching the tokyo olympics
No, no, that's not it no, that's that'd be nice I wish yeah. No, that's yeah, I
i'm stumped
Um, I I don't know how to tell you you're a it's this is tough for anyone to hear let alone a child
Um, there is a we're in the midst of a global pandemic. There's a disease that is
Is all over the world? It's not even just just los angeles everywhere on earth is currently
Stuck under the shadow of this very bad disease and we have been for the majority of the year
Oh
Oh, wow, I I missed all of this I was uh
I was on a cricket wireless corporate retreat and we weren't allowed to have phones
What what you were even though it's a phone company
Yeah, that was kind of part of the theme it was about unplugging
so they took our they took our phones and we
Uh, we stayed in cabins and solving
For six months for six months, you know, we just kind of did retreat activities
about how um
It's better to have
Snacks in the break room than to have a union that kind of stuff
Oh, yeah learned about the family tree of the cricket wireless goo goo people
Yes. Oh, yeah, he showed up goo. We love goo
He did you know that the goo from cricket wireless is married to the mucinex mom?
Oh, that's like the voice of mickey marrying the voice of minnie. That's so cute
Yeah, that is that's nice. I hope they party with flubber sometimes
Flubber is their dog. I think
He can't talk it's like plow that's a pet
so you've got so sector keeper you
Famously in the last in the downtown disney ordeal you were looking for severance from cricket wireless
This sounds like you were looking for a
You famously in the last in the downtown disney ordeal you were looking for severance from cricket wireless. This sounds like you were hired back in a corporate setting
yeah, um, so
We I tried to take them to court and there was a settlement
Um, I don't understand a lot of it, but they let me sign the papers with a cool pen and i'm back
Wow, so are you just back in the retail uh sector to speak or yeah, I work the floor
Okay, so you have your old job back essentially. I got my old job back. I get paid a little less
I get to park a little closer
um
and uh
The work week includes saturdays
Includes saturdays. So the severance package was just resettling to
Essentially do the same thing but for less money
Mm-hmm
And a six month corporate retreat
Which sounds fun? I mean I wouldn't mind
Yeah, go into a cabin for a while. You might have had more fun than we've all been having lately
but one cool thing is they use some of my paycheck to put into a
Low interest savings account so that I can maybe afford surgery one day
Oh, well, well, that's nice how does does that work everyone pulls their money into a savings account? Yeah, it's like a swear jar
So so the first what is it like the first couple people get their surgeries if they need them
Yeah, it's whoever gets hurt first gets healed first
Oh, wow, uh, shouldn't you get preference here back?
Yeah
Can it like bring you back to life because you still exist in this sort of limbo ghost state?
I don't know if there's a surgery to make you a full human again. Oh, um, no pre-existing conditions
Don't count and my death would count as a pre-existing
condition
Oh shit, that's too bad. You know, maybe one thing to talk about
Right off the gate because there were a lot of odd changes that we encountered when we went up there
But the the place that put you into this condition
to begin with the city walk fountain
Uh is now inaccessible due to the disease
There's now like a red rope
Surrounding all sides of it. So it's only to look at and no kids can ever play in it again
Hmm
Only took global pandemic to realize unsafe
Yeah, I yeah, I guess I guess story didn't
Resonate. Yeah, that's true. If they had just
If there had been any attention called to your story whenever that happened the mid-90s
then maybe
A lot of kids could have been saved a long time ago
Yeah, your story sector keeper. I'm surprised it has not been co-opted by some sort of political movement and used in a
vast
Right-wing conspiracy to be honest with you
hmm
Well, that's something for the movies
Well, if only it stayed in the movies
Boys unfortunately robert kennedy jr is just everyone, you know, everyone's trying to save the truth. It's better
We don't tell you about this. Uh
Yeah, yeah, I would love for you to not hear about anything that's been happening in the last couple years the the boys boys
There's a lot to cover. There's a reason i'm here
Oh, yeah. Yeah, please get to it boys. So sector 20 is jam-packed and loaded with lots of food and fun
sector 20 is
on tojitos
havayanas
nbc nbc sports and brew
abracrombie kid
And tillies
Anything else anything you want to wish us
Good luck boys there
And remember
If you complete this you'll give me strength
Yeah, that's that's the stuff isn't this nice to hear I felt so
Unstructured during this entire pandemic like it's hard to set boundaries of when you work and when you don't like I've that I feel
My life just feels tidier having this assignment to do
Oh good. Good. Well, there's a lot to cover and i'm sure you boys have a lot to say
Um, we do um, and and it was it was a lot of fun to go up there
Um, and and we will talk everything that you just listed is new
At citywalk since we did this
Two years ago. Um, so that's that's good news for you that we can tell you that there's a lot of new fun stuff to do
shops and restaurants
Um, I do feel like we have to let you know
I forgot to mention
If you don't complete this i'm in grave danger
Wait how what?
Grave danger and I would have guessed I guess per usual in grave danger
That's why i'm back, but i'm back for a limited time. You see
The corporate retreat has not fully ended boys. I need you to complete sector 20 to give me strength to leave solvang
Yeah, you should that's where you're coming from that's where you're like astral zooming from
Yeah, i'm astral projecting from solvang not to over complicate it but yes, uh, uh
Lots on the line. Okay. Good luck
Oh, boy, I mean he should I I didn't want to say anything but like he does look like he's been mostly
eating able skeevers the puffy pancakes because
He's looking a little puffy right now as if he spent six months at solvang just eating pancakes
Yeah, jason, would you switch places with him? Uh
Out of the current I mean i'd consider it
All right
So if we don't just actor keeper if we don't do it if we don't complete our mission
And jason will drive up to solvang and dress like you and switch places now. Wait a minute. I thought that was a hypothetical question
No, no, you'll trade lives. Oh, that's fair. That's fair. My my boss is shaking his head. He says that's fair
Your boss is watching you podcast right now
Yes
Okay, very intrusive. Yeah
He just wants a body there. He just wants a head count
Yes, he wants yes
Jason's photo is on the wall of every avar skeever
Restaurant here in solvang. I like to support local small businesses
Is it like his headshot like at a dry cleaner?
Uh, yes, it's like a headshot at a dry cleaner also
It's almost like a competitive type photo where you were uh, you
You ate the biggest avar skeever and got it for free
Okay, well because what happens is if you do one of the places challenge
Then the then you can get the other challenges for free like they they you know, I have a system
Clearly yeah, you swept it
But boys boys boys, we must focus. We must focus
Please get in a separate challenge
All right. Okay. We got a lot to cover
There's different stages of clothes much like states phased reopening city walk has different stages of clothes
Yeah, what I was getting at surger keeper is that for there's five new things to do?
Uh, and that's good. That's progress but um
Uh, there there have also been some losses. I am sorry to report that there have been
Honestly a vast degree of fallen brothers
Fallen brothers
Yes, I saw some of raider store
Open. Oh, thank god. No raider images raider images open and thriving in the middle of the week
wide open
Mid pandemic raiders fans crowding store raiders crowds crowding store as raiders
Raiders organization moves to las vegas. Mm-hmm
Yeah, that's the city move when things are going wrong
Some things when things are going wrong. Some things are still right
Hey, we're all in this together, you know
I will say it's still there
Margaritaville is not open but the raider store is
Now, what do we think about this was one confusing thing about our trip is margaritaville closed
I don't think it's closed for good because it's not gutted but like is it ever open?
It wasn't we do it a wednesday afternoon. Yeah, I don't know if it's ever open. I'm not sure
Um, let's let's go through the things closed down permanently
Okay
Let's give the sector keeper space to breathe here because this is going to be tough
This is going to be like hearing a laundry list of relatives that have passed away. Okay, most recent ludo bird gone
uh
Let's see, what else hard rock cafe gone becoming toothsome chocolate
And savory treat import whatever the place that smells upsetting in florida because they're cooking savory food and chocolate
simultaneously in the same facility
um now
There is I would sort of say there's a new
Dog that's debuting a spokes dog for the toothsome chocolate. Have we seen this? Uh, yes those boston dynamic
Robot dogs that will eventually hunt us down
Yes, uh
Jacques is the robot man that was there already, uh and
Dr. Toothsome is the female like steampunk woman and then latte is their dog and that character is new
So I just wanted to mention latte
Uh latte debuted right around the time, uh universal florida laid off a significant number of employees
But latte is working. They fired a thousand humans and hired one robot dog named latte
So anyway, go ahead city walk hollywood though, so hard rock's gone. There's still one on hollywood boulevard sublime
uh gone like
2016 perfectly preserved in amber the billboards for swell water bottles and patty wax candles still
Loom above the empty store front
Uh something from our theme song is gone. It's gone unless again to reopen this does this is it?
About a sublime hot topic and if so, the hot topic is still there and it is still sublime
Yes, i'll never say what my intention was never say these accursed homonyms
Uh potentially still relevant how let the moon gone move to hollywood boulevard
Oh go ahead what oh
That's correct, oh he howled himself i'm not sure that that hollywood boulevard one has opened though. I didn't see it on their website
Yeah, I don't know. That's that's yeah, they announced the plan. I don't think i'm
I was gonna say i'm sure it's not open, but it's possible. It's been open for six months
I I will look in a second. I believe I got a grand opening email and I believe it might have come
Right before a week before so everything shut down. Oh that might be it
I I was looking at the the locations on their website and it's a lot of
Cities, but then right in the middle of it howl at sea
so speed visiting at the topic we didn't get to there there was a
Uh, you can go to a howl at the moon on the norwegian escape
the cruise ship
um, which I
Wait, but then it's within a different it's how at the moon, but it's inside
Headliners a separate club entity within norwegian cruises
Uh, i'm confused as always very fitting irony. That is on a ship called escape
The main instinct one feels as they enter the doors of howl at the moon
uh
Uh
Now I
Now and I think this is very important. There's been some real big developments up at city food. Now city food is the second floor area
What yes
Um, are you okay city food city food is food court. Yeah, that's the food court
uh
Keep keep going
Oh, right, we still can't do it. We're still not allowed to go to the food court. All right
That's that's fine. I won't complain. We got places to go. Uh if things are talking about yeah, we have plenty of food to talk about
We have to talk about mbc's take on cheesy fries
Well, hang on you might be getting lax up there with your solving easygoing attitude, maybe we're the ones who have to reinforce
Uh the way we step through this and when we are not through with jason's tears of what has closed and to what degree
Please jason the floor is yours. Sorry. Mr. Scott
I guess i'm the the rule setter now
Uh, I think that's everything that's closed permanently. There is a yeah, no, no, but there's more there's more levels
Oh, yeah, so the next level right right, right. What was closed when we were up there and possibly might be closed forever
uh
And we can all chip in on this because I have I mean the big one that we saw was like samba the brazilian steakhouse
kind of
An inconvenient setup in current, uh times not open when we were up there
Yeah, I don't want to go to a buffet at this point like a just where meat is being tossed around the room
essentially
Mm-hmm
Uh samba. Yeah right by the margaritaville, which is closed again. These both could be closed forever. It is possible
Yeah, carl strauss looked wasn't open when we were there had no outside tables was unclear what the status of carl strauss was
Yeah, i've i've heard word from you know, the rumor mill that
Universal is trying to
Own everything that exists at city walk. So I do wonder if universal is using some backdoor machinations
To try to force certain things out of there so they can put in their own toothsome chocolate type things
With their own intellectual property and their own robot dogs
Yeah
Do you think they made the disease? Is this part of their plan? Well, you know, some people are saying
Some people are saying this a lot of i'm not saying they're saying it. Yeah, but a lot of people are saying it
That bathroom by the hot topic
I was gonna say something that would be made for a movie
Straight from the movies that's true
Yeah, I know but you you might not know the degree to which the actual world is getting scary
Like those scare the pg-13 movies you would watch before you died things are starting to feel like that a lot
hmm
Who else is close who else is close popcornopolis when we were there clothes zen zone I fly
the movie theater
Zen, so we can't go into a tube. We can't put people in and out of a tube where you fly we can't like
Uh have like a literal aerosol trap that you fly around in during this pandemic
Uh, yeah, they they I you know, there are some uh devices they have in the zen zone though that I feel like might be healing
You know, there's those
oxygen machines
Maybe they can put the vaccine in the zen zone oxygen machine and and get it in that way
Well, I want to show you guys, uh, um, you're set up with a screen share capability sector keeper, right?
Uh, I believe so. Yes, I would have to
Uh, uh, all right. Wonderful. So yes, brian's my boss
Um, uh, all right then brian can take a look at this too, uh, here's i'm just going to show you guys the uh,
This is what we found on the door of the zen zone or the water coffins
uh
Here is a number of
notices
About uh covid-19
regulations, let me just count the pieces of paper one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen
There are 17
Laminated pieces of paper on the door along with a padlock
so city walks, uh
Doing as good as ever I went and like looked at some of the handwriting to see like some of what I don't know if this is
What they have to do for the city's sake it just looks like they're trying to do something
I don't know if this is what they have to do for the city's sake it clearly didn't help them reopen the place
I'm, not sure the purpose of any of it, but I took one
Photo of some of the handwriting mike's upset outside. He can't he's very sore. I know I look like i'm sexually sexually posing
Very coy. Yes. Yeah, it looks like scandalous mask. We don't know what face you're making under there. Mike looks like pinup girl
Yeah, I really do. I thought I was selling a back injury a body 40s, baby, huh? I'm looking good
Um, so here's uh some of the copy like somebody handwritten wrote, you know how the
How does all the covet regulations apply to the zen zone and then listen to this our aqua massage have?
Zero contact it is self-directed from a machine with no human touch
Customers remains fully clothed
Just so surreal that these things that we experienced two years ago all have to one by one
Discuss with the city and the public the city of us the county of les angeles public health
Bureau whether they can do this
Reopen or not
This feels like there was an inspector like an inspector coming to city walk to like discuss with them if they could open or not
And the person never came and they're like, well, I print it all out. Just write just explain to them
We'll just stick it on the wall if they come by and then they'll just like put a big yes
They'll like leave a note that says yes open
And it never happened didn't happen. I'm not great at spelling tests, but customer was misspelled
There's a number of yeah, there's some pluralization issues
on this thing
um
You know, i'm just glad that you know, I think we we get into the weeds on these these daily podcast series and that's not daily
We're just doing this one and it's it was all two years ago
But I just know that the audience would expect us to read
Some of the bullet points on appendix r from the les angeles department of public health
And we are doing it. So, um, yeah for all your appendix r updates follow podcast
Can we should we find appendix should we find this document online somewhere and give it?
Post it on twitter and you can all out in the audience add your own reasons why zen zone is safe
You know, it'll be a fun contest
We'll have explain why the water coffins are okay during a pandemic like a coloring contest and whoever wins
gets uh
Their bullet point is law
Yeah, exactly
Yes, we'll look for we'll see if we can find this document
Full appendix are coming to twitter. Um, so yeah things things really exist in this strange, uh limbo
Um, you'll be happy here searcher keeper, you know, what's not open, you know, it has a ton of pieces of paper on the wall
sparkies
Sparkies ain't running right now
That's right boo him I don't hell
He might be he might have been sent to hell for poor health regulations he's bad
Yeah
He's a bad boy. It's very possible
Um, he yeah, he he purposefully coughed on a lot of people sparky. Uh,
Went to trader joe's and tried to film viral videos without masks
he
Went and coughed everywhere without a mask and then he got his propeller hat going which helped spread the virus faster
all around the market
And then the biggest insult the video didn't even go viral. So he didn't he didn't get what he wanted at all
I mean we better in case it was we better uh talk about some of these specific I knew going through his mistake
more, um
Popcorn opolis closed nectar bath treats closed when we were there. Um
um
et and frankenstein garages seemed
Impenetrable, I mean you might have been able to get it
Yeah, we were
Yeah, there was a lot to prevent us
I think et is where because I was very obsessed with trying to see the nintendo land progress, but
It was too hard. I think et would have been the only place you could have maybe gotten a glimpse
Yeah
um
You want to talk a little about um, just how it felt to to be up there because as I said
This was this is the first time we all have hung out since march
It was pretty crazy and I think we all felt it that despite all of the the oddity
um
And you know all the fears of right now that
Being in a place that we know so well that we've spent so much time in it was
Very comforting. I think we all were a little touched to emerge into the the center atrium
Yeah, so
We went yeah, we went we parked in the parking garage
We went to this little area where they were doing your temperature check, which is of course theater
It's just theater for people because you know, you can take tylenol and get rid of a temperature
Anyway, they do a temperature check. They have the hand sanitizer there
Don't forget one step of this though. You just you just glazed past the parking and this is notable
That how surreal was it to park at city walk for free? Yes
Yes with the parking attendant, uh in the little uh security shack
Being even more checked out than usual like when I pulled up
He did like this with his hand and I was like does that mean keep going or stop?
And then he handed me like a parking ticket
But I I saw no cars plenty of cars in the garage
I saw no cars on the streets driving up there
Mm-hmm. It was uh, yeah
Wow
I got I got a receipt as well. I definitely felt like I was getting away with something
And did you feel guilty did you like oh, sorry? No, no go sector keeper. I was gonna say
Actually free parking or did you have to?
Go into amc and do some strange exchange rate
Uh shockingly
For just pure free you but whether you bought anything or not
I think a couple of us bought a thing or two, but even if we hadn't yeah you it's finally is genuinely free up there
You're talking about when you uh pay for parking and then
Unless you use the app you have to go into the amc and they give you like a dirty 10 dollar bill
To redeem part of your parking the filthiest around
Uh, no, yeah, we didn't have to do that amc of course was not open
still had the onward posters and posters for
Minions coming soon. Well tenant. Yeah
Tenants up there. I'm very i'm very happy with a very obscure thing that I shot up there that I won't even mention
We'll put it on the social media. No one will understand what the reference is. I didn't get it
But now that I it's been explained to me. It's uh delightful. Yeah, so we'll put that up
but do you mike do you feel like
Does that take away some of the city walk thrill for you in a way that you didn't get to do?
An outsmarting of the system that you don't get to play that that mental game
of trying to park where I can
Yes, I can outsmart them all that's kind of what it is. Uh
There was a lot of other stuff going on in my mind that day
So it was not so high on my list
I think sometimes i'd have to I have to really like be in the pandemic city walk a few times to see
Where the system's weaknesses are there has to be something I can do
But I was just scoping it out this first time and i'm sure there's got to be a way
And I want a spoiler alert. I got a some sort of food to go
There might be some sort of discount I can figure out there can be some sort of twitter alert for a coupon perhaps
Uh, i'm i'm just at the start of my journey as far as pandemic city walk deals are concerned
Adjusting to the new normal the new the new normal way to try to get value out of this one
theme park adjacent shopping complex. Yes
Absolutely thrilling stuff
Well, someone got drool over the last six months
He used to be polite and like would pretend like he was sick or so
He was like he was getting sick and now he's just he's just goofing on me
That's fine he's grown that's character development that's you know, it's growth it's growth
Yeah, well if you didn't find that exciting let me talk about how uh, the the there is though the
Parking rates have changed and in some cases gone down by 45
There is one thing about the parking experience that has maintained it is still incredibly confusing
We all parked in different places
We didn't understand where we did and why we all had to follow a series of signs that took you into narrow corridors
The kind of thing you don't want to be in during a pandemic
Uh, it was as confusing as ever and but again normalcy. I kind of like that
Yeah, and they had
They had social distanced the cars
with with cones in between each space
which
What are we doing here folks?
Like there's some basic information about what's actually a concern and I don't think the cars are going to catch covid from each other
Uh, which is what I think that was signaling to me that they thought perhaps a car
Would get covid from another car and then infect a family cars get sick
Well, well in a certain universe like mater
Oh, so you've seen cars sector keeper you've seen the movie cars we have movie nights at the compound at the cricket wireless compound
Oh, wow, so you like you like mater
Mm-hmm mater's funny
Yeah, yeah
Calling it the compound is a little unsettling it starts that's where it starts to feel like sort of a um, you know a nixie
Situation you don't all like dress identically. Do you brian has a lot of good ideas?
Brian has good ideas and we'll get well every
Well every afternoon we get together and play kickball and listen to his ideas
Oh, that's his brand ever like just like loudly discussed
His iq test. Does he like say what his iq is a strange amount of times?
Yeah every day
Every day, huh? That's how we know you don't find that
Alarming or a little like uh, if somebody was really that smart they wouldn't have to
Say it no, he's like bill nye
Okay, brian from cricket wireless is like bill nye
Um, okay
I just I guess just be on the lookout that if you if it goes beyond ideas to way make the business better
And heads into I don't know like ways to ascend to higher
Planes or achieve better and I want to say a bad word in front of you
But orgasms if it gets into like that just be on the lookout for some for shady language from brian. Yeah, okay
I will
I'll tell you this. I I felt like I needed bill nye to figure out how to get out of that dang parking garage
They made walking through it as confusing as driving through it now with this uh security
Uh screening stuff. Well, they don't do security screening. No, no still no metal detectors to get into city
Yeah, orlando has the metal detectors, but universal does not holly in hollywood does not have them yet, right?
Um, they have yes the temperature check they have also and I really should have written down exactly what it was. They have the
virhovan
Cheery voice telling you to wear a mask and social distance at city walk
Oh, it's the classic universal voice. It was kind of nice to hear the voice again, even though it's saying scary things
Yeah that uh, there's like a line and like people in masks and then the classic universal voice
Telling you not to get sick
Uh, so I'll be honest I was a little stressed there that was stressful
but then when we emerged so we emerge out and if you if I had to
To bet a thousand dollars. I would have bet that we were coming out right by the movie theater
We were not coming out by the movie theater. We were coming out
by the the uh
NBC bar and grill or whatever and the the bamboo cage
Ceiling area of city walk and let's be clear that NBC grill is not it's completed
But it's empty and the tvs are all on outside
But and inside and inside but I don't yeah think it's officially open even though it has a decent sized outdoor dining
area
Yes
Um, so we can't really tell you much about the nbc sports grill and brew unfortunately, so keeper. Hope that's okay
Yeah, we know it's a good idea. We just don't know you can't even tell me if they have lester holt ribs
Well, i'm hoping
Yeah, we're hoping uh, maybe maybe don't know yet maybe you'll have to go back boys
Huh, I don't I hope that it gets that creative with the uh, you know blacklist burgers and uh,
What's uh, zoe's incredible?
uh pizza zoe's
That's good that's good
I will say, uh if for nothing else we have to go back to meet latte
So we'll at least get back there to meet latte
Do you think we're getting a latte or they just shipping that latte or they overnighting that latte to the hollywood one?
You're saying maybe they won't have separate lattes
Hmm
I don't know. It depends how how much longer we're in lockdown. That's true. But then latte could be a spreader
What if somebody gave latte?
Covid in florida and then it's shipped here and then it spreads it here
And then latte gives it to a car in the parking garage and all the other cars get it
They all their hoods pop up. They're all coughing
And then they give it to uh one of jay's cars in the big dog garage and then it's over all of burbank
My family they're all sick
I lost every last one of them
All 300
And the motorcycles too. I knew it was a problem when the motorcycles got it
the sweet innocent motorcycles
300 sounds low, doesn't it? Yeah, he probably has more cars than cars. Yeah
Uh, so we emerge we emerged in the bamboo cage ceiling area
And I think I said and I was feeling I go i'm a little emotional
Yeah
But uh, I haven't I really we have really not been out much late at all. We're very very uh locked down here
Uh, and it was like a mixture of being outside
And in a place I have a lot of fondness for
So it wasn't like bawling or anything, but I was like, huh? I'm a little touched
I'm a little i'm a little moved
I could tell it was affecting you guys in another way because both it seems like both of you guys like forgot how to walk
You're both well, like straining yours like mike you walked up like a half set of stairs and we're like, oh god
Never walk anymore. Well, I was oh, okay. You explain yourself. I'll explain myself
Well, I think cycle psychologically I get very i've only been into a couple stories. I would we're crazy about keeping inside so
I was in a best buy for like eight minutes and like I start to like I feel physical problems
Like I have a mental block of being around people a lot in this situation
Even if I kind of intellectually know
That this is probably fine. So I think it's something that you did it. I'm glad you you did this
Yeah, and also it's affecting the fact that i've mentioned this on the show before
Somebody once referred to my walk as the walk of a fancy horse
so I think that
Whatever anxiety I was feeling
And it was it was low anxiety wasn't like crazy or anything. But whatever I was feeling was certainly affecting my gait
It was certainly affecting the the manner in which I moved
Mike's trot looks weird
Mike's trot looks weird. He should have brought a salt lick along for comfort
Yeah, yeah, so that was that was I think probably any any strange energy. I was giving off
Well, and I just got I got a cramp so I have been
uh when when
The first few months of lockdown I was making sure to like walk like take a long walk every day
and then
Uh half the state of california caught on fire
So trying to do a walk hurt both my eyes and my chest
So I really had not been walking very much the air quality slowly clearing up
Um, I might still kind of bothering my eyes. But um
Uh, yeah, so if I don't like stretch I forgot to like stretch in the morning
So I got a cramp like and we we took a sit upstairs in the totally empty seating area
You gotta limber up. Uh, yeah city walk you gotta
I was very worried worried about you. I'll be honest. I was like I looked over and I was like what?
Well, yeah, we were coming up a slight incline and I was like my my leg was cramping up. So
But had an ice it for a few minutes and then I felt fine. So
Uh, I forgot that yeah, you're right
It has been harder to walk because of air quality and and I have I have something that circumvents all this as I said
Which is that i'm putting on daily dance parties, uh for a baby. Um
Uh sector keeper. I don't know if you know this. I have a kid now that happened since
Since I talked to you last. Yeah. Yeah
thanks, um, there is uh, i'm sorry to say that I have another child in my life and it's a little
More I have to defer to him over you i'm glad when you if you ever need it, let me know
No, no, of course, of course no, so good boy has good boy
Hey, that's that's how I felt about it
And the only thing that I do feel guilty about is that you know, I know you remember how we met all your cousins and
They sent us on all these different adventures that we got to do. Yeah
The expeditions are just I mean they're already tough because of lockdown and now with the extra time being apparent
I'm just like i'm not sure how many of your cousins i'm gonna get to
Hang with in the near future. It's just very imposing to do these
30 day series or whatever. Well, we met one of them not long ago. Yeah, he did. Oh, right. He was a jerk
Hey, we met the american dream keeper from new jersey. I don't know how well you know him. He was an absolute ass
Yeah, he was mean to us. Yeah. Yeah, I know i'm okay from um
From like christmas and stuff, you know when you get together. Um,
Oh, that's a bummer. I'm sorry to hear that. Uh, uh, hey, but scott. I know you're saying you're maybe a little low on time
Remember spirits live forever. So we'll we'll always have time for you. Well, you'll get to it
Well, that's nice
All right, so we'll do we'll get to we'll get through that full list when i'm like by the time i'm like
Yeah, yeah
74. Yeah. Yeah, and none of it's behind the paywall
And in the meantime since scott can't care for you, uh, sector keeper, whatever whenever you get out of the compound just move on with jason
Yeah, sure. Yeah, i'd love that. Yeah. Yeah
We just gotta make sure to do some some stretching and walk it with me because I clearly my body will just fall apart
Oh like visiting my grandpa
Yeah
Basically, yeah. Yeah
I'm, assuming uh grandparents also have allergy attacks in their eyes as well. Like I've been experiencing for about a week. So
And get tummy aches from drinking seltzer
That was me. Yeah, that was that was both
We both we both done that before. Yeah, we agreed on that boy. That was my favorite part of the kusamigos
Imagine me listening to that and like I can't respond to this right now kusamigos episode
I I was so amped up for it. I don't remember most of it
Hey, that was one of the yeah mike and I working on our marketing plan, you know
We met up to take pictures on uh los angeles city bikes
Oh, that's right. Yeah, you guys met up. Yeah. Yeah, but the three and after our big fight we hadn't convened
We had a person and we got to do it here
You know what would help you jason, uh, I think with future uh walks and posture and not sprangling if you say fruits and vegetables
I don't want to hear it again. No, that's a lost cause
Um, no, i'm i'm talking about you need some better
footwear
Uh big new big headline new we really buried the lead that the flip-flop shop is gone
and instead it's replaced by
Hawaii enos, hava
Anas, havaianas, uh, it is not havalinas the wild boar found in parts of the world
But have I not just full of boars when you open the door?
Um, yeah, it's the flip-flop shop has been replaced by a different store that sells flip-flops
wow, it's
It's a bit of a lateral move you might say
Not that that's bad extremely. Yeah
no, brian says there's no bad ideas
Oh, but see he's conditioning you i think brian might have some really bad ideas
What so havaianas did you get to go inside did you try on flip-flops
I I did I looked around a little bit. I asked them some questions. They said they were from brazil
I said cool. They asked if I wanted to try anything on I was like absolutely not i'm not gonna go
Like I don't think i'd be doing that anyway for foot cleaning
You don't want to try a barefoot shoe on during pandemic
During pandemic it didn't sound good to me. No despite how nice the person in there
Was made me feel awkward and then I left uh right away. So, uh, that's that's my report about
Havaianas shit. Yeah, there was three it said three customers could go in at a time scott was the only customer in
jason and I looked through the window as if there was some sort of uh
A bunch of chocolate being made or something. Yes, and I later learned that uh
Havaianas embodies brazil's fun and vibrant and spontaneous way of life and at
200 million sold a year. It's the most popular flip-flop brand in the world both of those
according to the havaianas
Twitter and website and that sort of thing
Yeah
uh, I was looking online because you know
We we of course talked about the sock market in the city walk
So I was looking online to see if there were any maybe like dirty flip-flops
With like a dirty message on them or an aggressive message
So you were looking for dirty mike carlson google's dirty flip-flop. That's not a foot fetish thing
That is just I was looking for for comedy
Like the sock that said carpe the fuck out of this dm
Mm-hmm famously, uh, but there's nothing like that. It's all there's a couple, uh, you know
stranger things and star wars flip-flops, but mostly
I mean the most outrageous thing is there's a skull
There's a skull on some flip-flops, I think
Wow
That's about the extent of how how crazy the brand is
Well, I guess that's that yeah, so
Hey since you you mentioned the sock market
There's exciting developments since we were there. We were there on a wednesday friday afternoon
There was an update on the city walk on the universal studios hollywood twitter account city walk update
Wetzel's pretzels and la sock market have reopened both are open friday through sunday only noon to eight p.m
so
A return to normal, huh?
Yeah
For the weekend, yeah
Yeah, because wetzel's was closed where I have a picture of you despairing outside of it. Well, jason was happy. I was happy
I was happy. Oh because that you made the what defeated your stomach, uh before the
indoor skydiving the beast has been felled during the week. Yes. Yes, senator giebert
If sock market strong economy us economy good
I guess that's fair
Well, I mean the fed has been pumping the sock market full of
Liquidity actually during this last six to nine months
Uh, so some people would say that just because the sock market is strong. It doesn't necessarily reflect to the actual economy, especially right now
So I just say and there's been a little bit of a pullback lately, uh on the stock on the stock market
so people are a little bit, uh
Worried people are still cautious as far as the stock market goes and not maybe not willing to carpe the fuck out of this dm
That's what steve munchen and larry kudlow said, uh last week at least
They were they were really waiting for the the minions
Sequel socks and the wonder woman 84 socks and like all the stuff that's been pushed the black widow socks. Um,
Yeah, they're thinking that the stim if they're if they have to pass another stimulus for all of us before maybe there's more
More faith in the sock market. Hmm
Yeah, so
We figured it out. We figured it out. Yeah. Um, the what have we not
What's in that list that we haven't done to make sure we cover?
Anteheato's
Oh anteheato's. I can't tell if you did finish talking about nbc's
I
I think we did
There's just not a lot we can say it's the former tony romas
Um, and they did almost nothing to it except put on a tv that plays
For no one. Mm-hmm
Anteheato's I have been
Anteheato's a few times now before pandemic. Have you guys been I forget I did in florida
Not not here. I really like uh, I have not been
But you I went I went before horror nights last year
I went we were we saw some movie. I forget what movie and we saw we ate there before i'm i'm i'm into it
I like it a lot. All three of us agreed. We're not really like
ready to eat at a table with other people outside of our bubbles yet even outside so we
we uh, yeah, we did not eat at anahito's or the
Bubba gump or outside, uh bubblegump annex where the hat stands hat stands are currently inactive. No hat stands
Right now. Well, take it from someone who's died a good call
Yeah, hopefully no no ghost boys join you uh as much as you might like having some new friends
Yeah, my friend
Menchies was open was it? Yeah, I oh, okay minchi bad boy
Yeah, I guess menchies menchies is one of the people that's been around for a long time
I don't know if you guys know menchies
Minchi bad boy. Yeah, I guess menchies menchies is one of the people that early on was saying
We must keep the economy open. So
That's just I guess
Yeah menchies point of view I guess
You got to use gloves. I think I think that was a big change at menchies
You have to use gloves to because you because menchies you have to and we've talked about this before
I don't really care as much for scooping my own toppings on frozen yogurt
But this new change is not that they do it for you. It's that you just put on like disposable gloves
That seemed that seemed to be the vibe or you have to bring your own winter gloves into a menchie
They've got to be padded yeah
Leather gloves leather vortex at least bring a byo g. Yeah, that's right
Bring your own gloves tcby is now byo g
airtight and jason
Jason did not have his frozen yogurt gloves with I did not have the frozen
gloves
um
Uh, no, so we didn't end up eating anything up there. But you know what we did what we felt we had to do
Was support the local businesses of city walk and we bought some masks and not just any masks
but masks with the classic neon
Universal studios logo and we got some photos that will post of the three of us looking very happy and normal
all wearing
matching
cool retro masks. It's almost better. We have a new way to express ourselves. It's cool. It's cool
We cool. We we put them on we oh, they were sealed in bags
We opened up those bags put them right on and boy. Did they smell like industrial grade shit?
They stink to high heaven
Three just three boys and stinky masks. Well, surely these are not just repurposed novelty panties
We said as we put them on our faces
You think they're
like vending machine
Is this the debut of the word panties on podcast the ride no, I don't
We might just call it edible underwear, maybe I was gonna say I think that's the body word panties well, we're behind the paywall. Yeah
But it just felt like very thin like like joke gag gag material like it didn't feel like joke gag joke gag
Well it was like a Halloween costume
Yeah like a Halloween costume
We were wearing a sliced up Dracula's cape
Yes
But we were tricked into buying because it had a 90s thing on it
It fit fine. I mean it was fine. It's probably fine
I it was the first time I encountered small medium and large masks. Like I think we all just bought mediums
Yeah, I don't know my mask size. Yeah the hell yeah
Um, you gotta get sized you got you guys haven't gotten sized at a tailor for your mask
No
I'll be unfitted. Okay, my luxury mask. I went to Joseph a bank and got sized for my mask
That's weird, I thought everyone did that
You're gonna like the way you mask I guarantee it
Um, you bought uh, all the retro stuff is out at the studio store scott. You bought the mug you bought the coffee mug
I bought a mug. That was nice. Yeah, it's nice to see all the basic stuff in the studio store. Nice to see the retro
logos
um
Yeah, um just just nice to be there and be spending you know, I've
I've really missed giving my money to this place. I didn't give any money to abercrombie kids
Um, that's a new place sector keeper. You were excited about that because that's a kid's thing
abercrombie kids
Sort of like
off-puttingly
uh breathy
I feel
I guess you I guess that's just childlike joy, but abercrombie abercrombie
Is for the cool kid
Oh wow, so so the kids you know are all no I forget what is your age? What is your age at this point?
What?
I'm just forgetting because you're working so you're not like an eight-year-old kid. Are you i'm well, I i'm timeless. I'm i'm
I'm as old as I was when I passed don't oh don't drum that up michael
Oh, i'm sorry. Okay. I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. I didn't mean to do that. I didn't
Reopening wounds. Yeah, that's my fault. Um
Isn't it just like universal that if you're wearing abercrombie, you're one of the cool kids
That is universal and that's probably why universal chose to uh open it up there
Yeah, yeah
So basically there's a new there's a new door that says abercrombie kids so you can enter a different way
That's a kid section. I went up to the door you guys encouraged me to you have a kid you get in there
I started opening the door and I was like, I don't need to know what's in
Abercrombie kids I could see through the it's all I don't know. It's all like khaki pants, but little that's the end of that
Well, and we can get yeah. Yeah. Sorry. Go ahead
Oh, I was gonna say we're all this made because there was a new store called production central that replaced the old skate shop
Uh that used to be next to like hot topic around that area and that was closed when we were up there
It appeared to have the identical material for the identical product for sale. It's the studio store half a block down
But with a really bad logo a terrible font that they did add that yeah
um
What haven't we
Tilly's
Oh, man, well everyone buckle up for the 30 minutes of tilly's talk
Um, it's a small tilly's which mike and jason have go
It's like tilly's but it's small. It used to be angel. It's now tilly's
It's small angel is now tilly's. No, it's now tilly's
You know what? I'm sorry. Maybe i'm getting these tillies
Angel is tilly's that's a big adjustment for you to make I know
Hmm you're trying you're trying to square it
Is not angel
No, not the other way
Yeah, why even so much problem with so much of a problem with this
Tillie's is cool. Yeah
Angel is now tilly's
Hmm, he's you weren't brian isn't putting stuff in your water. Is he?
Brian no brian's no, he's just in his recliner behind me
He's writing in his journal
He's fully clothed, right? Yeah. Oh, yeah. Yeah
Can I ask is brian does brian like um purified rain water and grain alcohol?
Whoa, yeah, wait, whoa, you know brian
Yeah, yeah sure
Okay, huh?
Let's probably move on
I just think you should get out. I think I think you should get out of there and we should you guys are gonna
Help me get out of here. Yeah. Well if and again if we don't do it jason will come and help
Yeah, well if and again if we don't do it jason will come and replace you. Yeah
Get to hang out with brian and drink rain water all day as long as you can walk around and you can get some exercise
Jason there's a lot of land
I you know, I like that
Sounds good
Clear air up there when it's not on fire and brian will make you walk because brian monitors everyone's weight. Oh, that's true
Um
So a back to away from the ranch back to the compound back to city walk. Um, this is uh,
I I went a little above and beyond this wasn't on the list, but I did want to address something odd
That I found about city walks past
Somehow during the saga. There's a thing that completely
Eluded us and i'll explain how I got to it
Uh, um, I was uh, I mentioned a thing a long time ago on the show called shangri-la plaza this weird
failed pilot that actually starred alison mac aka
pimp mac of the nixxiom organization
uh
And uh, there was I don't know it was this weird like kooky pilot about a strip mall. Uh, I I did an interview about it
Uh, uh that a listener, uh wrote and for la magazine you can look that up
But I was looking up like who because there's a really distinct like vibe to this
Uh to this show in this place and I looked it up and it's a guy who was a production designer of uh,
Pee-wee's playhouse. So it's got that vibe and i'm like what else did this guy build because he's got a cool artistic sense
And I saw something that he built that i'd never heard of that was at city walk called the panasonic pavilion
And i'm going to show you guys a picture of the panasonic pavilion. This place is crazy. Um, check that out
Oh
It's a it's like a carnival. It's like a merry-go-round
thing
Um with a lot of neon and like a big circus
Tent i'm still sort of confused about what this thing
Is uh, but then the only description i've been able to find about it is that uh, let me find it
It is a a it has it's an electro a panasonic electronic showroom featuring an interactive merry-go-round
with robotic animals created by steven spielberg
What the hell what was this steven spielberg made a bunch of plastic animals
He handmade them. I mean
I think so. He overs
He was really active in all this stuff for a while. Obviously we have not done his restaurant yet. That's on the list
Oh, I can't dive. Yeah, uh
and he obviously, you know universal and
I I I don't know. It's it's looks cool. It looks cool as shit. It looked really neat. That's a cool vibe, right?
I wish there was more information about it. And if anyone listeners know anything about the very
Cool looking but dull named panasonic pavilion, but then I kept going like what else were there other things like this like kind of weird
The world's fairish stuff and this guy the same designer jeremy railton
Um also on his website. There was something listed called hollow world
hollow world was a restaurant in pasadena in the mid 90s
And when you hear hollow worlds, what does that sound like to you? What do you think hollow world is?
The hollow earth. Hello. Not that spelling of hollow. No. Oh, okay
I was thinking kevin bacon
Kevin bacon. Not no also again. Not that no
It wasn't a themed experience. It wasn't a restaurant themed after the the creepy film hollow man. Is it how michael eiser says? Hello?
hollow
Hello world. Hello
No, no, I heard hollow grah holo and I thought hologram was this some kind of hologram
Oh restaurant and then I kept looking and no the answer is it is an alien themed restaurant
Because it's an it's a restaurant where you learn the story of an alien named hollow
showello
um, it is hollow is a
alien
Who?
Is telling us about he when you go to the restaurant?
He narrates the story of our planet back to us how aliens built our pyramids stonehenge
He tells us about what area 51 is all about seems like kind of a cousin of blue 32. Wow. Um
So this was open in pasadena for like nine months. It was very brief
but
huh
It's called hollow world yet. It's about aliens and then it also has a laser tag that is about dinosaurs
And then also there's a volcano in the front that erupted every 20 seconds
Which seems like a lot seems like a lot. Yeah in barbaryttaville vegas that volcano goes off like once an hour
20 seconds is a ton of eruptions the lava fees alone
Uh, is there a photo of this anywhere? No, I don't think so
And again, I implore a listener if you have one or if there is one because I think other ones did open
I think they tried to do this in dallas and maybe atlanta
Uh, um, and it didn't work. I'm so confused by it. What's that?
And it did not work
And it did not work people did not want to go eat and learn the legend of hollow the alien
Um and play dinosaur laser tag
Um, though there was a big kickoff event where all of hollywood's biggest stars came to check it out
nichelle nichols from star trek
grizzly adams himself dan haggardy
Wow, really and uh the the biggest and brightest star kato kalen
They all gathered in pasadena to learn about hollow the alien. Is there a photo of that?
No, I looked on getty editorial like to see if there was a movie premiere picture, but there wasn't there's no grizzly adams
And kato kalen picture
You can't see grizzly and kato fighting an alien or fighting a dinosaur with lasers anywhere
Which kills me it kills me inside did not get to see this this feels fake
It's all very strange, but it's corroborated by if you I I
Forgive me for going on this rabbit hole, but I have to I made me feel so crazy
I kept googling and somehow discovered that gary coleman didn't just attend this
Opening he was the spokesperson. He was a paid member of the staff of hollow what?
Because gary coleman in general is very interested was very interested in
Interest it was very interested in arcades
Did you know that in 1993 gary coleman opened the gary coleman game parlor in fisherman's village in marina del rey?
california
The shooting location of arrested development. Um, it the motto of the gcgp
Was our games are easier so you can play longer it went out of business in 1994
1994 oh
What?
Is there a photo of that? No, there's no photographic evidence
Why I gotta get off this compound man
This is this is like you're hallucinating all this
It's got whatever you're smoking. I want some of it
What kind of doobies are you smoking these days scott
Um, it's gary coleman lost 200 000 during this endeavor
In the brief year that it was open he was talking it up like it's great
Everybody loves it big success coming to my game parlor and not only that I gary coleman am developing a new sitcom
In the sitcom I play an arcade owner
The sitcom never aired and there are no photographs of it. Did they shoot a pilot? Do we know don't know that
I can't tell you that you said
the
arcade
Idea is games last longer
Um our games are easier so you can play longer. So there's no like super challenging games
Isn't point of arcade more quarters?
That's right
I guess it might be and with harder games. Maybe they would have had 200 000
200 000 more quarters
That might have been the problem with the business model
That's like a like pay what you want kind of I think it's kind of sweet that gary thought he could pull this off
Well, he's right those games especially for kids
You'd go this is so hard and i'm just spending so much money
so that must have been a thing of concern he had and I
I my head is off to him for trying to solve that problem. Yeah. Yeah
You tried but he sank
Uh, we'll cover that in the first
The first time we're speechless thinking about easy arcade games. Yeah
Wow i'm imagining being there playing and just for hours hours all on one quarter. Yeah, you show up at 10 a.m
Gary coleman checks in on you. Hey you need anything? All right. Well, hey, i'm right here. I'm the owner
I'm gary. Let me know if you need anything and then 6 p.m
Um, this is business manager his business manager comes up and he's like we've made eight quarters today
That's all we've made gary. This isn't gonna work. That's fine. We're gonna be here for 20 years at least
It'll pay for itself in 20 years
So that's we'll cover that in the fisherman's village, um fiasco fiasco
Yeah, great, um, well and we'll cover hollow world of course as well. Um, I yeah my sailor cousin stuck there
In fisherman village
So he's like at sea and he can't find a dock. Yeah, he needs a dock
He needs you all to build a dock by discussing everything
Has brian screened the lighthouse for you in the compound the will defoe robber paddison
No, we only have one copy of um of cars
on uh hd dvd
Oh, yeah that for that that was a pain
So you've watched cars at least once a week for six months straight. Mm-hmm. Yeah
Do you like doc are you a fan of doc? Yeah doc rules
Mm-hmm. Yeah, uh, how about
um lightning mcqueen. Yeah lightning mcqueen rules
How about uh luigi
Yeah, luigi rules
Where are we going with this line of questioning?
Hold on. I gotta get to the imdb real quick. Oh, no. All right. I'll get someone call off. Hurry. Um, I I mean what have we not
Talked about. Um, well, I mean we could talk about what I got
Oh, yes, let's absolutely so bubblegum shrimp was open and they were blasting all the cool tunes
And it was a good vibe going on and I said, you know what I don't really want to eat
At bubblegum, but maybe i'll take some food to go
Was the filthy shrimp outside?
The dirt, you know the man
The uh, you're talking about the shrimp mascot that always looks like he rolled in a pile of mud
Before coming out and waving to people
He he was not out there. I think maybe that's well, honestly that would might be safer for him
Or her whoever's playing the shrimp
Um, because you know you can that's a good barrier for
For air for aerosols
Um, but no that no shrimp
Um, so I went up to the menu
They told me okay. Here's here's what I should have done for the good of the show
And I didn't do it and everyone can be mad at me. They told me I could order an alcoholic drink
Right and they have and as maybe you may remember from the city walk saga. I thought I was drinking an alcoholic drink
I was not as eva anderson said you were drinking an ice cream smoothie
And two of them and licking the glass
I licked the glass sugar off the rim in my car
Yes, the rim in my car. I licked sugar off of a rim of a plastic
Bubba gum shrimp glass in scott's car on the way back to my apartment clean on the out team my memories this
These precious moments
That class clean on the outside cream on the inside ice cream smoothie ice cream smoothie
And she was like you can order whatever she's like
She can or you can order whatever you want and we'll wrap it up
But you can't drink it out here. You can't drink it like walking around
And then I was like, okay if I order a crazy funny thing
Should I go to the top of the parking garage and drink it or am I really going to transport?
An alcoholic drink in my car on the way back to burbank
What if it spills?
What if I get arrested so wait just you know, you could take it to go but you couldn't drink
Yes on the patio upstairs where we were hanging out
No, not there because if you remember how the moon has a policy of no drinking on the actual
Like sidewalk area they had to surf an alcoholic drink
You had to give your alcoholic drink over to an employee and you would go to their like like mandated patio
That was approved for drinking and then they would surf your drink
Literally two feet across the sidewalk to you and their other area that they said was okay for it
Right. It's not like public. Florida's different. Yeah, it was like public consumption
Law. Yeah, I I did see other bars
This is not an uncommon thing right after we did out at the moon
I did hear about other bars that had to do that
But it's very weird with city walk because this mix of public and private land that like yeah, you gotta jump through all these
You gotta drink the alcohol drink in at your home or in the bubblegum eating pens
So like I I wanted to force another like snow monster situation where I was trying to like hide and secretly drink
on the top of a parking garage and then I thought of the scenario like
I'll get arrested at the city walk jail and that would be great for
Be great for the content of the show
But then i'm going to be in a small place with people like people and I don't want that
So I apologize. The many people they arrested that day. Yes, the many people many city walk felons
Yes, yeah
So I apologize to the listener for not
making something clums like making myself have to do something clumsily or
Put myself in a weird situation. So I ordered instead I ordered the uh,
a southern charmed fried shrimp
Sounds like
Like sorry to interrupt
But sounds like unfinished business
Oh no
Yeah, I guess it is
I guess maybe I should go back and and do it and try to find the funniest silliest slushy drink and actually have alcohol
in it and then
Drink it in the parking garage somewhere. I guess I should have done that curious george
Yeah, I guess I maybe I should you know what I should do is I should prep for this more I should get like a big
brown paper bag
And bring it with me
You're and put the yeah. Yeah, Jason. Well, you're a tall guy
You could hike at the next to the studio store. They had a big green grass wall blocking you from going by the globe
So you should like hoist yourself up and like kick your little your little feeties like on the wall drink a big drink
You should sit on the wall the big grass wall. Oh, I should sit like humpty dumpty on the wall and drink a slushy drink
Well, that's a that's kind of advertising what i'm doing. I guess so
I'm trying to be incognito. I don't know. Sometimes it feels good to kick your feeties
Well, I can't argue with that
We should have tried to at least without even without an alcoholic drink
We should have tried to sit on top of the green wall, which is something we also have to talk about
Yeah, but uh to sum up I took the southern
charmed fried shrimp home and it was fine
What does charmed mean it was okay. What do you what is southern charmed?
Uh, it is fries and slaw served with cocktail and tartar sauce
That's what southern charmed it did not taste much different than uh,
Fried shrimp you'd get from the supermarket
And it and it costs what twenty twenty dollars. Yeah, it was
Thirteen dollars because it was a lunch special. Oh, okay. Okay
so that's if it was I there was
I was thinking about getting a surf and turf for like 45 dollars, but I decided against that
Driving home with a full surf and turf in your car. Yeah, I will I I will hear one strike against bubba gump
Is they don't have the name or logo on any of their to go?
Uh things the bag didn't say bubba gump the container that that got it in didn't say bubba gump
But I would really like a little of that
Because that would make me feel good having a bubba gump bag in the house
So lindsay probably didn't believe you. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know
There's no way you have bubba gum. She was very skeptical. Uh, she
Tasted it and she was like this isn't bubba gum, but she threw it against the wall. You're a fucking liar. Michael
Says no southern charm
There's no I can't even detect a spice. I can't even detect
Yeah, no, it's true. It's true. I was the liar that day. Yeah, um, I mean
I was the liar that day. I was the liar that day
Um, I mean, you know in terms of culinary experiences
Some of the listeners if you if you subscribed to any universal studios hollywood emails
You might have been here
You may have been getting updates over the last few months about some of the the opportunities there are to go
You know try foods and hang out with your friends and take pictures of food that you're having with your friends
I mean you got we we all subscribe to these email. We've been seeing the
Please go back to city walk emails, right? Yeah. Yes. I i've got some of my favorites in front of me scott
Did you have ones you wanted to share or I did I did a little bit here you go
We might we might have doubled up a little. Okay. Um, well i'll start with this one
Uh, I actually learned about this one from our an upcoming guest shared this online
um and uh
Date night at city walk missing date night. This is where it's at
When you're ready for date night city walk is here for you
So and then like we have enhanced sanitation measures and implemented additional measures for
Distance spacing and screen like everything has to have the scary copy right after
Yeah, uh, yeah every every email has a scary copy
I mean this all started back at the start of july when city walk reopened
Uh city, uh universal hollywood also promoting city walk
Uh city, uh universal hollywood also promoting city walk on their twitter account
They post some you know
They post funny memes about like pinocchio sleeping and they got some real flack because they posted one of those the day they
Permanently laid off like hundreds of people
Here's another favorite email get those steps in and enjoy the scenery at the same time
Did you know walking a circuit on city walk from the iconic universal studios hollywood globe fountain?
To the far end of the street and back will net you approximately one thousand steps
Do it five times and you'll be halfway to your ten thousand
Daily required steps ten times and score because you'll have reached your daily goal
Now that email was sent, uh august 21st when we were in the middle of a heat wave
Temperatures topped 95 degrees that weekend
And two weeks later was the hottest recorded day in la county history at 121 degrees in woodland hills nearby
So get up here get your steps gang bring the whole fam walk a few miles in a heat wave at city walk
Which uh, we could not famously uncovered very little shade city
Oh
And yeah by about that screen there's there's zero shade yes, there's zero shade and like there was a wall
There's a big green grass wall blocking us from the iconic globe fountain
Oh, yeah, you can't even get to the globe. Yeah
You can't even gram it with your besties
So jason, are you thinking though while the when the temperature drops though?
Maybe this is the solution to to limbering up your muscles
I mean we might be like becoming mall walkers michael like the the older folks who walk at malls because city walks pretty empty
You know, I think there was as many guests up there as there were security guards
Well, you know like they say, uh ten times and score
Ten times and score you've reached your daily goal. We're all saying it. Everyone is gamifying
City walk walking at city walk. It's sweeping the city
And then yeah scott. Do you do you have this one? I don't know no no go. Okay. This is probably my favorite one
Give your family a giant city walk hug
Spend the day with your family enjoying our destinations
mesmerizing icon eye candy
From its wildly eclectic array of cool neon signs to must visit shops and city and wide selection
Of yummy places to eat city walk will bring out the kid in all of us and don't forget to snap a photo at your favorite
Place and tag us you may even find yourself in a starring role in our next instagram story. Please help
We're desperate for content. This is getting harder every week
No one's using our hashtag, please
Yeah, uh give your family a giant city walk hug
Yeah, what does that mean a bit a bit odd in the middle of a pandemic hug them there or is being there the hug?
Yeah, is it like the their their arms the arms of them all that are touching you?
Yeah, it's funny I don't know it seems like a lot of the language in these emails matches the cricket wireless compound manifesto
Oh
There's some
Well, how yeah how many?
You're showing me right now. You're holding up this big binder that says cricket wireless manifesto. How many pages is that sector keeper?
It's just over 600
Just there's also there's also a workbook
Could you could you open to a random page and just read a little bit from it for us sure
Sure, you want me to call out a number sure. Yeah
Uh page
521 that's towards the end
That is yeah, you're right. It is towards the end
He's getting there almost
Rippling through okay
Oh, this is uh, this is towards the beginning uh, or towards the beginning of the finals chapter
uh chapter 7
Right go ahead
Okay, so
This chapter is entitled. Uh, the power of the individual is stronger than the power of the collective
Okay, okay good, okay got it so um, let's see
When working at cricket wireless remember that your power is stronger than the power of the teams
There is no team
If you're considering
Forming a team
Remember that the team weakens
What the individual can deliver?
Everything you need is inside of you
If you ever see anyone trying to form a team say a
To form a team say in a break room
During lunch or even after hours getting drinks be sure to tell brian
Remember there is no power in the collective
Wow, huh?
Oh my god
Well, it also but also we can see the pages that you're reading from and there's a bunch of like smiling suns and colorful squiggles
All over. Yeah, that's sunny. He guides you through it
Oh some mascot
To conveying all these dark mess. I feel like it's tricking you
Um, I mean, this is a little bit of grim stuff to us that we haven't been onboarded
Yeah, I feel like maybe he means they mean something else by team. There's might be another word
that he was
Using meant to use there, but that's just kind of a feeling I have I don't know
I could be wrong. I don't know brian's heart
Yeah, well also you can color in sunny so that's cool
Oh, well, that's cool. He looks cute. Yeah, he's a cute mascot. He's a cute mascot. Would you call him a friend?
Oh, yeah, absolutely
Do you think you need some friend time? It's been too long since you've hung out with their friends
But when you get ready to roll city walk is ready for you
And that email came friday afternoon short, you know, just a couple days after we had been there. So they had our ticket, you know
This is what we did except that this photo of these girls in these cool hats outside of uh, voodoo donuts aren't
Distancing at all. No, no, man. There's no mask. Yeah, and they don't even have like the mask around
It's not even like they pulled it down to eat the donut. They're just no they don't even exist the man
Yeah, i'm gonna assume that they're in a cluster together for the sake of but even still they should be wearing masks for other
people
Um, but if you're gonna cluster together, why do you need to get out and go to city wall?
You're already having fun at home. Yeah, right if you're having a fun cluster at home why take it to city walk?
It's more it's more howl at the moon is even there. Yeah. Yeah, what's even the point? Um, I
I got there's one of these emails that I want to point out and I
Found it a little odd, but still kind of fun. Um, there's a picture
I think they're trying to do that kind of like instagrammable
snacks
sort of vibe
So I ended up with with this eats treats photo ops and it's a picture of one of those mini monster things
Whatever you're feeling we've got it grab a bite for dinner satisfy your sweet tooth with dessert
Up for a mini monster boba anyone try it
But if you don't like it do not dare waste it waste is shame
Hide your shame at all costs if you try to throw a mini monster boba away
Everyone will be looking at you hide your shame hide your shame
Good boys don't waste food when you waste food mommy cries rock out with your besties at city walk
Huh?
Kind of crazy
You didn't get that one. I didn't get that one. That's interesting. It's yeah, it's odd. Very very specific
A little it got fun at the end, but seemed a little
Um, yeah, yeah a little dark in the middle. Yeah. Yeah. I mean that makes sense
I mean, it's don't want to make mommy mad
I'm I'm I don't want to do that. That's one of the things i'm scared the most about
I think that was in the same email that email the subject line was don't make mommy mad and then
Oh, right. Right. Right intriguing. You want to click on that like when a politician sends you an email with your name in the subject
Right. Wait, something's up. Something might be wrong with mommy. I better click this better click this look
It's national eat outside day. Okay, but that's not as important as keeping mommy happy
Is let me can I ask a question and I don't want to get us off on a whole thing here
Is city walk mommy?
Oh
Well, it was very comforting during a very dark time and I felt like I was inside of a city walk
Hug right as we know is what families give and get that is right. You're right about that
So yeah, I asked this question and we don't have to even answer it right now, but is city walk mommy?
Hmm just something to ponder I think I'm gonna have a full workbook tonight
You better for else you're not sleeping right that's what you said. Yeah
I'm gonna get that I'm gonna guess that that workbook poses the question is
It already answers it that brian is daddy
Oh, well, I haven't gotten there yet. Wow scott. Have you been to the compound?
Uh, I haven't and i'm pretty busy. I got the kid. I don't know if i'm willing to come visit the compound
Okay
Well jason's coming anyway
Oh, that's right. Jason. Well, especially if we don't wrap this thing up and get his soul free
I mean do we have I mean like city walk his mommy is a wonderful thought but wait
Is there is there any way to anything else we want to say about this experience? What a crazy way
To go back to this place that means so much to us
Yeah, I I I liked being there. It was certainly odd
for a lot of reasons
Uh, I also just it completely take the pandemic out of it
I will say even as much as for hard rock fallen brother and we won't see harper ray anymore
uh
That I am excited by the idea that there's going to be this big gaudy ass
Uh toothsome chalk like there is city walk is changing and I think I I was kind of getting excited for the possibilities of how
Uh tacky it's going to look in a couple years like it's going to take tacky is going to be
Taken up a couple notches. I think with that toothsome
There and I think at that point
As I was saying universal maybe gets rid of more
uh
Non-universal owned things. I am excited at the future a non-pandemic future
with maybe a uh, uh
Attackier city walk to come like it seems like it might have been in the past
I have high hopes for I have high hopes for the tackiness of mommy
Tacky is backy
That's a great way to put it yeah, yeah
So it's really the main thing like stringing you through this era like the hope of getting to be done with this and go visit
the the toothsome jock and latte and
Yeah, um, oh wait, this is bad news. Oh, no, I just clicked on
CNN and it seemed I guess trump's probable supreme court pick has spoken
At length in the past
I guess trump's probable supreme court pick has spoken at length in the past against chocolate emporiums
They might all be shut down
once she is installed so
chocolate emporium out vatican 2 out
There's a chance by the way, there's a chance that is that you're not making a joke and that is real
I it seems like the kind of thing right as we find a future episode
Chocolate's illegal what as a future? Yeah future episode. We did a little run of of that. Yeah, it seems possible
Chocolate is illegal in america
Says it in the bible somewhere uh, sector keeper in the manifesto. Is there anything about chocolate?
Hmm, let me look in the index
And take your time, please
Yeah, yeah, yeah, we want to make sure we hear your manifesto, let's see. Uh,
What's um, this is cricket wireless cricket wireless location
Coffee no no chalk. There's nothing about chocolate. Oh, that's too bad
That's a bummer brian imagines a world with no chocolate. Uh, it's full of cars. Um, well
Hey, what a blast to go up there. I guess
Did we make it?
Boys, boys, boys, you give me strength. You completed sector 20. I'm so proud of you boys
Even when things are absolute shit you did it
I'm so proud of you. I'm so proud of you
How does it feel boys? Thank you
It's I can't believe it's so wonderful to hear that again to get that approval the kind of approval that
Usually only comes from mommy
Uh, we also we also need it from you and I feel like we got a big city walk hug from you today sector keeper
Oh, thanks. Thank you. Likewise and jason, why don't you take a look at that coin?
Wow the coin
It's multiplied there's two now
That's your coins and you they're they're valid at gary coleman's arcade
Wow a parking coin that's also a defunct arcades coin pretty cool. That's right
That's right. Well boys i'm
I i i i i'm ascending. I i'm moving out of solving
I'm free
Free wow, he left he oh, yeah
He's he's wow. He's I can see his his uh, this beam of light
Uh traveling over the solvang hills. I guess we I guess we got him out of what is it?
I'm a free
Little one
Oh my gosh, he's singing a song a song a song that he made up for a
Yeah, is that a made up song? I think it's made up
little
Good good and remember
City walk was there for you when times were hard
So it only makes sense that we go back when we can go back safely and do it all over again
And it's not behind a paywall. We'll see you guys soon
Wait, what do you wait? What do you mean? You mean like the original saga again?
Hey, anything's possible. It's gonna be 2021
And everything's gonna be fine
Fine, okay. Yeah, let's just so let's not have too many more
Refrains of that song or else. They'll say the children psychos are gonna be on us
Yeah, we're gonna get accused of some stuff yeah, we're gonna get we're gonna get cuties we're gonna get oh no
Cuties. Um, okay. Well, I guess we have our marching orders which is what to do the
City walk saga again. Maybe he'll forget. I don't know
Well, we're gonna have to be next year doesn't have to be
But if tacky's back you we gotta check it out, right?
Well, I guess he's got a fair point heck I might go up next week. I mean I could work outside that empty area, you know
You won't run into a soul. It is a socially distanced place. So I recommend it to
Listeners just don't go all at once don't go put on cool hats and share donuts with people. You don't live with
um, and don't get any alcoholic beverages and try to brown bag them on top of a roof or you will be arrested you will be
arrested, yeah, yeah
So I guess wow, it's nice to say it again you survived the city walk saga
sector 20
Uh the end question mark who knows?
This this thing could go and go forever if it can surprise us
In the middle of a universal cruise line episode then it could come back really at any time during any episode
Especially here on the second gate. So please stay subscribed
Um, and so we'll do when you want to get to cruise line some other time then
Yeah, we'll just table it for now. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. We'll finish it out. Um, okay. Well fun stuff
Talk to everyone soon. Bye. All right. Goodbye. Bye