Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, the second gate.
I am, well, I mean, I'm Scott Gardner, but today I'd prefer to be referred to as Scott
1, spelled without the O, let's say SCTT-1, and I'm joined by...
My name is Mike Carlson, but for today, I'll be M, let's take the I out, MKE, which is,
is that an airport abbreviation as well?
MKE, like Minneapolis is something, Milwaukee, I think, the Milwaukee airport.
MKE-, let's say, who?
You can be one, we can all be one.
Let's not diminish ourselves.
That's true.
Oh, you know what? No, no, no, here's what it is.
Here's what it is. I hate to waste everyone's time.
MKE-L, Mike L.
Oh, yeah.
Wonderful.
I got it.
All right.
And also here today is...
I'm going to go a similar route, and this is J-N-J-A-S-N.
Wait, wait, wait, can I plus it up with J-8?
J-8-son.
Yeah, perfect.
Yeah, okay, yeah, let's do it.
Plus it up with confusion.
Yeah.
Today we are talking about...
I'm so happy to be talking about the adorable purple robot who lived at CommuniCorps, specifically CommuniCorps East.
You may know him just from merchandise, from a recent retro poster that was put out.
You might know him from the opening day special of Epcot Center.
Or you've never known the name of this character, or you've been wondering when the hell are they going to do Smart One?
There's any amount of answers here.
But I feel like we've done a lot of dives into Snark with lots of bizarre European parks and collapsing malls and whatnot.
And I'm just excited to gush for a while about our cute little buddy.
Yes, he is adorable.
I think there was one opening joke a couple of years ago at this point in the podcast about how we wanted him as our best friend, something along those lines.
I should check that.
Hardly a joke. Just a statement.
Hardly a joke.
Yeah. Just something we believe.
Yes. He is a character that I'm sure I saw as a child, but it feels like I knew him my whole life.
I feel like I might have as well, but it's very hazy, of course.
In my case, early 90s fuzz. I don't know what was going on with him.
He wasn't around much longer after that.
Because if you don't know the full...
I mean, you probably do if you're on the second gate, but this communicor became interventions and then things modernized and got all VR lawnmower man everywhere.
And we didn't have the simple charm of the early 80s robot community.
The magic of that robot that looked like he was built...
I mean, he looks good, I will say that, but he looks like he was built for Lost in Space or some 60s.
The 60s robot tradition was lost along the way at a certain point, which is a real shame.
I'm very fond of this area of robot, obviously.
I mean, I think Rex ties into it a little bit, although Rex is a little more wiry.
And I do like my little simple stout robots.
As I've said before, my wedding cake toppers were R2-D2 and Ernie, who is the little stout robot from Expo 86, World Fair type thing.
You know, Tom Servo is kind of in this family as well.
It's not that I prefer Tom Servo to Crow or anything.
I maybe like them both equally, but just Servo is another example of a little simple and stout.
Classic robot. I mean, like, would you put Rosie from the Jetsons in this category?
I guess a little bit.
Yeah, just not stout enough.
Maybe she's not short enough, I guess. If she was shorter, I suppose she'd fit this.
Short is maybe what I mean. Yeah, yeah. I like Rosie.
She's adult sized. She's sassy, though.
Yes. Which is fun.
I think I prefer as little personality as possible.
I like, you know, in the way that smart one is just kind of I'm smart one, like as little going on.
Let's not complicate it. I guess that negates Tom Servo, who's got a lot of that, dude.
Do you like lost in space robots?
I do. I'm not like I do not have that memorized thing. I've seen very little.
I honestly I have not seen a ton of lost in space either. I am a big fan of Dr. Smith, though.
Yeah.
There are many super cuts of like great Dr. Smith lines and he's very theatrical and I enjoy him as an actor.
He was a voice in Bugs Life, I believe one of his last roles that act.
Oh, that's right.
He did a lot of voices, too. Yeah.
Mm hmm.
I like that design.
I'm sure there's others in this family, sort of like simplified, like as little going on in the face as possible.
That helps.
Well, you know, we'll get to it. But there's a robot that is this is going to be a little bit of a backdoor pilot for a different robot.
And I'll say I'll say the name now, but we'll get to it might be a little later.
Yeah, yeah.
Very famous robot that has a similar kind of blank face.
Very famous.
Yeah.
Well, I have his credits here.
He's pretty famous. He's more successful than like the his Adam Baldwin kind of brother, Pulsar.
Well, who's ever heard of Pulsar, Jason?
Huh?
I haven't even heard of Pulsar. I missed Pulsar.
You know Pulsar.
Do I?
You know, the the I'll give you a hint.
John Taffer.
Well, is he using a robot to clean up kitchens across America and bars?
No, he Pulsar was a robot that he opened a nightclub with.
Oh, yeah.
This is the dancing robot from pulsations from pulsations.
Pulsar seems a lot like Seiko.
Pulsar seems like a variant of Seiko.
That is a brother of Seiko.
Made by the same company.
Yeah.
Oh, wow.
Okay.
Yeah. Pulsar is not as famous.
Yes.
No.
Seiko. Seiko has been on the Goldbergs.
Seiko would introduce James Brown on tour.
Seiko is on Family Guy still.
Well, I'm comfortable jumping around.
I mean, we're because I can tell you how I came to Seiko in our our recent research because okay, so we're you know, we're all picturing this this cute purple robot and I prepare to do my research and I'm thinking, oh, the first thing that I'll do is go watch that opening special of Epcot Center where with Drew Barrymore and Danny Kay.
And that's where there's a little scene where Drew Barrymore introduces Danny Kay to smart one.
And then I get to that scene and it's a little bit of a surprise.
And then I get to that scene and it's not smart one.
That's an incorrect memory on my I assume there's a robot in that part.
So that's got to be smart one right now.
Guy rolls up way taller.
Big weird kind of bug eyes and introduces himself as Seiko.
So I don't know what happened.
I guess I just assumed if it's Epcot Center, I'm not sure.
I guess I just assumed if it's Epcot and it's a robot, it's got a smart one.
And smart one's in it later.
Right. Very surprised by this whole Seiko thing.
Yeah, they give Seiko like kind of a hosting spot.
And Seiko is not like a Disney robot.
Seiko was just a very, very famous robot.
Extremely one of the biggest stars of the 80s.
A puzzle made robot. Yes.
When you think of 80s. Amazing filmography.
I mean, that's certainly true.
Yes. Yeah.
But did you guys heard of Seiko Tilt?
That's really the limit.
Because I can say I didn't know Seiko.
Seiko and we know.
OK, so I guess we're just going to get the Seiko stuff out of the way now.
Funny enough, I'm looking through YouTube and I see the same clip you're talking about,
which I didn't even really remember.
And I go, oh, there's that robot.
This is exactly the same time as it breaks on Twitter that a movie Seiko is in,
Rocky IV, Rocky buys Paulie a robot for his birthday.
And then later in the movie, people theorize that Paulie changes the gender of the robot
in order to comfortably have sex with it.
There's only two weird scenes with this robot in Rocky IV.
And I have not seen Rocky IV all the way through, so I'm extremely confused.
I guess I knew there was a robot.
Boy, is it baffling his presence in the movie.
There's so much in Rocky IV you would love.
I'm surprised that's not one of your top.
I should. I'll do it tonight.
I think Rocky IV would probably be your favorite of all the Rockies.
Oh, yeah, definitely true.
If it's got some bizarre plot elements that doesn't match up with the rest,
a la Star Trek IV and the whales, then certainly it will be my favorite easily.
So word has come on Twitter that Sylvester Stallone is doing a director's cut of Rocky IV
where he's going to cut out the scenes with Seiko, which is madness.
And this happens exactly at the same time as I'm looking at this YouTube video.
And I go, what the hell?
And like Seiko meets Smart One in that video.
They have a photo of it. They meet each other.
And it literally happened within a minute of me seeing this news.
I woke up from a nap that I took right before we started recording
and still in a dreamlike haze checked Twitter and the first thing I saw was Seiko.
And I thought I was imagining it.
Like, why would it after years of dormancy, I mean, besides being very, very famous,
why suddenly is this hour is Seiko news breaking?
I know it's crazy.
And there was an exchange.
Did you see the Twitter exchange, Mike, with Stallone?
Did he respond on Twitter? I saw him on Instagram.
I think there was some Instagram.
Was it Instagram where someone said, please don't cut the robot?
And he says, I don't like the robot anymore.
I did see that. Yeah, that was Instagram.
That's one. And the other one is, wow, a director's cut.
Does it does it expand on the relationship between Polly and his robot?
Sly Stallone official comment.
The robot is going to the junkyard forever. No more robot.
No, come on.
God, this is this is wild.
Nothing this year has made me mad until this moment.
Finally, boy, seriously, fuck 2020.
Yeah, I was fine with everything that happened this year, except for this robot news.
It's all been great.
So are we going to get, you know, OK, after years and years, the people being
oddly, brutally furious at George Lucas, people seemingly calling for the literal death of George Lucas
because he changed some things in his movies.
And do I like the changes? No.
But I think it got a little extreme, didn't it?
I think our our people versus George Lucas, I think we got a little too angry about like,
what is this going to happen now to Stallone?
Not that it should. Nobody should be mad that mad about any of it.
But he should at least get a little taste of Lucas rage.
Well, I think maybe the audience isn't quite as strong as far as Seiko love is concerned.
But he's very, very famous, though.
He is very famous. But I mean, there's a lot of people that are very famous that you go,
well, do they really have any fans?
You know, I mean, not Seiko. I'm just saying we don't know the size of the audience.
I hope you're right. I hope Stallone is about to get an onslaught of shit.
I mean, he's going to get it from us for sure.
I'm just saying I don't know.
Is it days of our lives that Seiko was a cast member of?
Seiko was a cast member on Days of Our Lives. Seiko is in SAG.
Seiko is in SAG. Seiko was in a Carly Simon music video.
Yes. Yeah, this all spun out for me.
Yeah, Carly Simon gives him a big kiss on the lips.
Yes. Carly Simon really like kind of gets pretty wild on it.
She's kind of draping off, like sort of hanging backwards.
It's sort of like the sex scene in Showgirls, besides the sex scene.
You know what I mean?
I don't care for that stuff in Showgirls, but I love it here.
There's no actual copulation, so that helps.
Let's be clear also, the European vacation is over and Mike is back to square one.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I've reverted.
Look, that happens. That happens. People regress all the time, you know?
You get all these ideas on a vacation, we're going to come back and wear this kind of hat,
and you know, it'd be wine tasting, and fancy meats delivered, and then you don't do it.
But yeah, I got home and there was an episode of the syndicated show VIP on, and I said, no, no more.
He started singing, give me that old time religion.
Yeah, and I'm back to square one.
Cover up, ladies.
So the thing I was most excited about though when I did my little research jag, of course, is the Seiko's musical career.
Oh, yeah. Wait, I didn't quite hear. I didn't save the... Oh, yeah, yeah, go for it.
Seiko has two songs. I found one of them, and we'll save the second one, I guess.
Much like ALF not so long ago, European music, correct?
Yes. This is called Monomi Seiko.
With Seiko et Chloe.
Seiko et Chloe.
I couldn't love this more.
We're just going to play like a minute of it, I think.
I should have... I should have fast forwarded, honestly.
Man, they're just giving pop singles away around this time.
Yeah.
So that's about being friends with Seiko. My friend Seiko.
There's a cute girl in a yellow top leaning against him on the cover as his duet partner.
And there's another song he has too, but I can't find it, according to this one video.
East Side, perhaps.
Yeah. I'll look. I'll look.
Yeah, I'm pretty excited. Look, I hate to get a Smart One episode going and then immediately put the spotlight on another robot, but your research takes you where it takes you.
And look, I like Smart One. Smart One's cuter. I like Smart One more physically, visually, but the career just isn't as robust.
I can't not play also this. You mentioned one of his achievements, but I have to play this little moment.
It is our belief that we will bring this sound back to our galaxy and enter into many, many years of friendship with your population.
The only and ultimate form of intelligent communication is soul. And the master of soul is James Graff.
He's just nodding his head. He's like he slides around and kind of like on wheels, I suppose.
He looks kind of like a big vacuum cleaner. I mean, like, you know, I just I just revisited Get On Up with the horrible Chadwick Boseman news.
And it's a fine film, but you sort of lose that like in his breakdown period, the shit like this was happening.
Like, I guess it wouldn't fit with the tone of the movie, but it is funny to think, you know, things going on tour with robots and stuff.
I mean, if we obviously we wrote that movie, it would be like Seiko would have been like a co-star, I think.
Yeah, an equal partner like Seiko and Seiko sing with.
Oh, Chloe. Chloe. Yeah. Yeah. That's its own, you know, that's just on us.
Yeah, but that's a different movie with Chloe and Seiko.
That's a different movie. So and then as I was starting to say, so the full story about the Seiko's less successful brother, of which there are multiple,
Pulsar was used. There was a nightclub outside of Philadelphia that there was very expensive.
They were opening it up. John Taffer, of course, from Bar Rescue.
This is part of his myth making. His myth making is that he ran Barney's Beanery and then he.
Oh, that's oh, I'm so upset by that news.
And then he ran the tiny little Troubadour. Those were like his early bar management jobs.
But by that, is that do you mean the club, the Troubadour or something else called the tiny little Troubadour?
The Troubadour is how they always used to refer to it on the radio.
I don't know if you've I guess only I have heard that.
But the Troubadour, I forget the guy's name. Yeah, it's a very famous venue in L.A.
I've never heard the tiny little Troubadour before.
I feel like that's what K-Rock always called it.
Maybe I just listen to a lot of L.A. radio when I first moved here, drove around doing P.A. work.
But so then Taffer, like as he gets more successful, like he's hired on to help open this pulsations nightclub.
So for the opening, they had a UFO come down from the ceiling, a hatch open up on the bottom and fog come out.
And coming through this was this robot named Pulsar.
And the crowd went wild. Pulsar cost four hundred thousand dollars.
And Pulsar was not the only Seiko, you know, kind of robot.
Six legs Great Adventure had a similar robot named Sci-Fi that you could see in the park made by the same people as made Seiko and Pulsar, I believe.
Wow. This robot did.
There was a Simon type of game that you could play on his chest.
That's what that said. Yes.
Well, that's fun. Well, you can still buy a robot like this, the new version of Seiko.
Did anyone find this? No, no, no.
Here it is. Three hundred and forty five thousand dollars.
He's got like a weirder new face with a little too.
I think, Scott, you probably not like this because it's a little too human or humanoid.
I mean, this he's this face is scarier to me.
Definitely. Yeah. Yeah.
It's a little more war of the worlds.
It's a little more alien, I guess.
But they're not really calling him Seiko, but they're saying this is the robot that was in the Screen Actors Guild.
So they're like saying this is like the new version of Seiko, but for whatever reason, they're not saying Seiko.
What's also weird is that you can buy the Robbie the robot from Lost in Space for thirty two thousand, much cheaper.
Maybe it doesn't move at all, I guess, though.
That's probably when you buy this is it's not just alive.
It's not just running around your house like helping myself to your food.
I think the Seiko one is supposedly kind of alive, but I don't think this Robbie the robot from Lost in Space is that the lost in space robot.
Mm hmm.
We know that's forbidden planet.
Yeah, this is for a bit of a way.
That's Robbie the robot, which is different.
Damn it. I'm confused now.
Yeah, there's a lot of space robot looks like this.
You're right. I'm sorry.
Danger. Yeah, the danger.
I made that same mistake.
Yeah, it's tough to keep them straight.
I also got confused because the robot we're supposed to be talking in his early version was named Robbie.
Yes.
What?
My original name was Robbie.
So I'm confused.
I'm confusing all my robots today.
We got to start giving out like follow along textbooks for these episodes with visuals.
I mean, how does anyone just drive or only hear this and keep any of it straight?
I don't know.
They just wait for like us to talk about like what meets Jason has in the house.
I think just like they zone out until it's all just fighting time until they said they said that.
They said they said the name Jim Sarno.
I'm back on board.
I'm back.
I no longer confused.
Sarno stands.
Yeah.
Well, I hear I mean, if we if you want to transition back from Seiko into smart one, I mean, maybe the best way to do that is with so.
So the aforementioned Epcot special that I mentioned, I sit through the Seiko scene.
What do you mean?
Where's smart one?
And in fact, you have to go halfway through the episode to a different scene in order for the two of them to meet.
And here's this little moment.
Hey, Judy.
I mean, that is that is like stranger danger.
Seiko is.
Yeah, I'm a little uncomfortable with the hitting on and it's a little forward, don't you think?
It's a little pick up artisty, but I will say it is interesting that there is some gender fluidity involved in the story of smart one and Seiko.
Oh, one of them.
Yes.
They both are portrayed with pretty different voices.
Just kind of kind of switched.
It happens way later and in right in the film Rocky for Seiko for now, for now, because he's like, starts the film male and then transitions.
Right.
Yeah, interesting.
Well, which I guess there is there is that question with smart one is what is the gender like clearly portrayed as female in this special and the lips are sort of more female and lipsticky.
But then there's a lot of literature that says he kind of kind of unclear.
I think it's unclear.
I don't think we're ever going to really solve this.
I guess maybe I mean, I would like to think that they had some real clear idea of what they were doing.
But of course, the answer is probably, oh, yeah, we forgot.
We forgot.
We forgot to clarify that.
I realize there's also there's there's a little bit of fluidity going on also with Ernie, the expo robot, who was my wedding cake topper and who I believe was the bride, despite being male in the in the World's Fair, say in the expo setting, which is kind of a nice thing about all of these robot that with their featurelessness that, you know, they you can quantify them however you wish to.
The robots can be any gender they want.
There's no that's what I declare.
Which voice is that?
I have a news.
Oh, no.
One of our other I have a news declared that toxic masculinity was dead.
So I felt like he was the one to deliver the news that the robots any gender that they want.
That's fair. One of our other profiles and courage.
We really got to figure out a name for these these character profiles.
Oh, yeah. When we when we focus on a rat in the rather than an attraction, a character.
Yes. Yeah. Right.
Yeah. Well, wait, don't we on the isn't the literature technically on the page around that it is character meet and greets.
I don't know if anyone ever think that's right.
Yeah. Yeah.
We there's no need for us.
We never ended up using any of these sub labels, but I like it.
We're doing a character meeting today.
Yeah.
Showed up unexpectedly.
Yeah. Like, you know, Tigger showing up in a booming that's like everyone.
Yeah.
Or like there's footage, pretty good footage of people walking around communicator and, you know, the Epcot Minnie Mouse with the crazy silvery outfit is in it.
And once or twice she like they're filming and she like photo bombs.
She like jumps into frame and starts waving to the videographer.
It's very nice.
That's wonderful.
Is there enough meat on the bone to do an episode about the characters in their space costume?
You know, there is.
Oh, man.
I would like to find the topic that there isn't an episode about that's actually maybe, you know, we do that so much.
Oh, is there an episode of this?
Blah, blah, blah.
The answer is always yes.
Let's find one.
We all agree.
There's not anything more than like two minutes to talk about.
Not right now, but I'm saying.
Yeah.
I'm like, eventually get there of like the three of us don't want to talk about this more than two minutes.
I am I am days away from starting.
I have a couple of Disney Hotel or Disney establishment matchbook collection.
And I feel like that's the next stage of quarantine.
Oh, you're you have one already.
I have a couple.
Well, Jane got me like some Caribbean Beach matchbooks with like a vintage hat she found.
You're going to expand this.
Yeah, because they look really good.
I W Retro WDW, I think, has like a big like scan of all of them.
So you're going to become a matchbook collector.
I might I might become a matchbook collector next to the coffee and the baseball caps and the comic books and just saying there will be a full episode about the matchbooks, the hotel soaps.
I mean, you know.
Wow.
Great.
I mean, this is like I'm trying to think of a better old school collecting you could get into here like stamp collecting, I guess, would be like a like a funnier old school.
I tried that as a kid.
It didn't really stick.
Really?
How many stamps did you have?
I just whatever was around the Elvis stamps were really big room.
The Elvis stamps came out.
Sure.
I feel like they really advertise those.
Interesting.
We all have to be collecting stamps right now.
It's our civic.
It's the only way to defeat tyranny is to buy some stamps.
That's true.
Yeah, that is.
I think it'll that'll do.
That'll work.
Just fine.
I'm sure.
I got the Bugs Bunny ones.
Yeah, you got to get the Bugs Bunny ones.
How about did Ernie and Bert Bert collected bottle caps?
Am I correct?
I believe that's good.
Were you ever a bottle cap collector?
I don't think so.
Yeah, that seems that seems.
What's the point of that?
It seems fine.
It's not a design if you like designs and stuff.
Huh?
Well, I support your matchbook collecting.
Thank you.
Keep us posted.
Let us know in the episode.
Just feel free to jump in at any time and say, I got a got a Polynesian now.
I got mannequins.
My other mannequins matches.
I've seen some scans of like different Pleasure Island ones.
I you know, look, I and everyone's going to be like Carlson's like, oh, he thinks it's
funny to collect all that stuff.
Meanwhile, he just got a notification that his super shredder neck action figure has
been delivered at the door and he's so excited.
He just got it on his phone.
Do you need to pause and go get it?
Feel free.
I'm an adult unless you guys want to see it because we've seen pictures of it.
It's very impressive.
No, I can I can wait.
I mean, I guess the listener doesn't want to hear us go, whoa, wow.
Oh, he's got the helmet.
Probably don't want to see.
He's got an ooze.
He's got a little ooze thing.
He holds it out.
Oh, good.
Let's do well here with collections.
Let's get back on topic and you can pull yours out, Mike.
I think you did on a episode that will come out later, but I got my smart one right here.
I don't know.
You have it.
I didn't realize you had it.
I did end up getting it.
That helped me think we should probably do an episode all about him.
We're both holding up our smart ones.
You recently got him.
I did recently.
I I've never done a full batch of Park stars.
I've recently piecemealed them and I I got three that are kind of to my specific error.
They're all very 80s, 90s.
This one, the funmeister, the pleasure island emblem and sunny eclipse.
Oh, yeah, he's great.
This is my robot butler here to rise.
It's robot butler.
Good to see him.
These are these we have talked about Park stars.
These are the closest really like we have to in in Park character toys.
I am a little happy and concerned because this company Super 7 has gotten the Disney license and they do really good work and they've already released the you know, if you see those like retro figures that are three inches, there's like, you know, like how G.I.
Joe is like three inch scale, like really small figures and they never would get the likeness essentially to those kind of old school figures.
There's a whole line of those of like Jaws back to the future that are very like not detailed, but they're retro.
This company Super 7 makes those and they made a line of Haunted Mansion ones, which those are cool.
I'm into those.
But they also make a line of figures called the Ultimates, which are seven inch elaborate the figures and they've just released.
They're doing three.
They're doing Sorcerer's Apprentice Mickey.
They're doing Pinocchio and they're doing Prince John from Robin Hood and they look amazing.
Line up.
I think they I here's my feeling is they were like, let's pick two mainstream and like a Hipper choice.
That's my guess.
And you're you're you're using the word hip hip for Prince John.
Yes.
Because he loves the thumb sucking.
I heard from Robin.
You're right to point out the absurdity, but I think the Oliver and Company Robin Hood properties are very popular with your box lunch hot topics.
So you're seeing so you're seeing that being catered to this.
So I'm saying that I think we might be perchance on the precipice of getting elaborate in park character toys.
New finally.
Yeah, much better.
You see this one is he got.
Wait, can you suck his thumb?
Yes.
Look at you see that one hand there that has the little thumb out.
Oh, that's a thumb extender.
Oh, great.
You got two different cause.
Yes.
Anyway, I think there might be a scenario in a few years when we're getting like a sunny eclipse toy.
That's the dream.
So I hope so.
You know what else also got me thinking about smart one and want to address him finally is there was just another one of those van Eten auctions and I didn't end up doing it.
But there was one of the things they had for sick because I just I just I get emails with the digital version of the catalog.
I just search for Epcot Star tours.
I mean, mainly those two.
And I this time around, they had an original smart one wind up boy.
Well, it was going for I don't know what it ended up going for, but the starting was like 150 and it's smaller than the park star, I believe.
So yeah, I think I saw that didn't didn't do it.
Consider it.
There's a lot of them on eBay.
They aren't so rare.
I might I might still at some point.
But of course, now I'm wondering a little more if there's Seiko March.
I'm sorry.
They started to be bailing on but it's you're not going to give away, though.
No, no, not bailing.
No.
But while we have him out, I mean, let's just talk about him.
What do we like about it or her?
Yes, smart one is purple.
And there's some pictures, especially that make the purple like shy like shine.
I don't know how to even describe it.
Shiny purple that is so cool.
So right up our alley of like as kids being like future, the future is shiny and purple.
And that's what everything's going to be.
Yeah, it's a really appealing purple specifically.
It's it's that Disney plastic shot.
It reminds me of like it's like a freshly polished Dumbo the elephant in the morning or like the cars in the cars.
Right.
They get they get those they get their plastics looking so nice and and the smart one in person must have been a sight to behold.
And yeah, the toy doesn't quite I mean, the toy is just painted.
They have a similar paint scheme for all the toys.
The toy doesn't quite capture that shininess.
Not quite actual robot had.
But I think it gets the cuteness.
I mean, I think smart one translates really well to the simplified Parkstar format with its the little little glasses,
looking eyes, the the little pronged eyeballs that sort of look like the parts of a cassette tape that spin.
Yeah.
And and then that and then that little mouth, that little light up mouth that's a little more like yeah,
it does feel a little more lipsticky in the real one.
But I like this, this simple little mouse here.
Just amazing.
You know, maybe this is what what you were saying.
You like shorter robots.
Maybe when you look at smart one, you you think of all else, you know, let me speak for myself.
I think of, oh, this would be a great sidekick for me.
I'd love to have this guy or this girl tagging along on adventures.
Yeah, sure.
There's a sidekick.
There's like a very friendly.
I don't know.
I don't know what it is exactly.
But screen in the belly.
Like, I feel like screen robot as a kid when like a robot would have a face that was a screen or a belly as a screen.
You're like, oh, that's helpful, too.
We could use that like, you know, as we're on adventures.
Yes. Yeah.
That'll come in handy.
And I don't know if I don't think smart one had any other mouth modes.
But you know, if you went on a smart one adventure, that if things got lightly perilous, that then the mouth would turn into a little like stressed squiggle or just an open.
Oh, you know, to indicate fear or discomfort.
That'd be cute.
That would give you a little relief in a stressful situation.
It would be very cute.
Yeah, I think.
Yeah, I guess it's just the everything is like circles and ovals on smart one, which is.
Oh, yes. Those little like those shoulder circle parts are wonderful.
Yeah. Yes. Yeah.
Even like even the arms like are kind of like blown up balloons like are there like.
Yeah, like balloon animal shape even.
Yeah, that's a very good photo.
What you just pulled up.
This was a magazine ad by Sperry, the computer company that was a sponsor of Epcot and that I think specifically sponsored smart one.
Yeah, look at I mean, look at that old photo like how many of those little star lights there are a little flares that the silver hands are looking shiny and wonderful.
Yeah.
Those are like half circles.
The hands are like half circle or a severe cut in half.
Yeah, good hand.
And I like I always like the old ads where it's like Sperry, the official computers of Disney World Eastern Airlines, the official airline of this.
Like these companies that don't exist anymore.
Like I was reading a little about Sperry and there were just the divisions were just sold off for part like Unisys has a bunch of it.
And then like I forget who else it says, Lockheed Martin, Honeywell, Raytheon, like they all have bits and pieces of this company now.
But for all intents and purposes, it no longer exists.
Theranos, the official blood testing company of the Walt Disney World Resort.
I'm sure these companies were just as insidious, but I feel like I'd be so queasy if it was like Tesla takes over the old world of motion building or something.
I guess I kind of look on Apple favorably, but then they do something crazy every now and then.
There's always if you dig a little bit, there's always a little.
Yeah.
All these companies gave them money, right?
That's obviously how a sponsorship works.
Oh, yeah.
Well, Sperry, I think also was their internal computer system and seemed to from one of these, maybe even the ad you just showed us, Mike, I think was responsible for the scheduling program for original Epcot Center employees.
I mean, that's something to get into on a future communicator or like the backstage magic episode of like, yeah, a big part of communicator was like all of the computer.
You can see the computers that run Epcot Center and partially Disney World at large.
Right.
Which are it's just those like big old banks like hallway after hallway of them.
Yeah, just like file cabinet looking super computers.
Yeah.
So, yeah, smart one.
He also like the design.
There's some other obviously characters we've come across in our our research that don't feel iconic.
He feels iconic to me, but I don't think he looms large in people's memories other than like the hard cores.
I think it's just him.
I think like the way he looks and because I don't like the actual little smart one show doesn't seem isn't super notable.
No, I mean, it's interesting, but it's not.
I think maybe some of the lack of remembrance might be it's not like there was then you go see the smart one show that's really mind blowing.
And, you know, he like his backpack lights up and he rockets around the room.
It's nothing like that.
So you're going off of pure visuals, which are very strong.
Yeah, I mean, he yes, basically his whole thing was voice recognition technology, which was used by people picking up like a rotary phone around him and talking to wait their turn for the other.
Like the other phones to go.
You picked up a phone and got in a virtual line.
It feels like yeah, it feels like, you know, he was destined.
He or she was destined for greater things, but it didn't happen.
You know, it's like trying to think of a good musical equivalent.
You know, there was somebody in a band and you were like, well, that person is going to break out.
And it just didn't happen that way.
You know, you felt like that person was meant for bigger things.
Well, like, you know, the trapeze, the stunt oriented percussionist in the Halyx story.
Sure. Yeah.
He assumed that they were going to go solo and there was not an opportunity to.
Right. I mean, like, yeah, like, you know, whatever.
Buffalo Springfield breaks up and, you know, two of the members go, Crosby, Stills, Nash and Young.
That didn't happen here.
They take this thing down.
And of course, we know what happened, which is very funny what happened.
But yes, I know it's we got to wait.
We have to wait. We have to wait.
If you don't know. Oh, man.
Yes. The future of Smart One.
Oh, boy. We'll get to that tease.
Yeah. But yeah, there was like a little like it's a number guessing game that was played with, you know,
like up above Smart One is a miniature version of a basketball scoreboard.
But I forget what you call like when it's the giant.
I the one that's not screens, the dot. Yes.
Yeah. Yeah. Like a like a an old school airport, you know, destination.
Yeah. Like I think like the word I have no words like the freeway.
Like in L.A. story when Steve Martin talks to the freeway signs.
If you had seen that. Yeah.
Yeah. So those are visible for everybody to see.
And there's little there's little guessing games like a smart one trying to guess a number from one through nine
or trying to guess your your birth month, little simple things.
And I do have the vaguest memory of of doing this.
And I might be conflating this with something else in my childhood.
But I I feel like whether this or anything like it where a computer was supposed to guess something like it would not work.
And then I would blame myself.
I would assume somehow that I did something wrong.
Not the not the system.
Well, it shows you where my head was that as a child.
Let me ask you then, because the thing it reminds me of, I'm wondering if you had positive experiences with the old Copperfield Magic specials
where they're like, all right, come up to your TV, touch the screen, touch a number, touch a room.
Like we watched some of those recently and that's kind of spooky.
But it is kind of more just a slightly more complicated process of elimination game like smart one is playing.
They must say that as determined outcome seeming.
Yeah, I kind of recalled maybe trying to do that as a kid and it not working.
Yeah. And maybe it was me.
It might have been me because my wife and love those and they seem to work.
I try to win recently and it worked because they're all on they're all on YouTube.
Huh? Well, I watch if you aren't using this quarantine to watch every Copperfield special.
And I don't know what you're doing.
You're wasting your time.
You could see tricks he was still doing in Vegas as of February 2020.
There is a special did I bring this up on the previous episode?
There's a special where David Copperfield splits down the middle, tears apart a Honus Wagner baseball card and then puts it back together
and does it in front of the cards owner, Wayne Gretzky.
And the and the cards co-owner who bought it with Wayne Gretzky was the guy Bruce McNall that like coin thief.
Whoa, you didn't bring that up.
I had so much Bruce McNall stuff.
But yeah, they co bought the most expensive baseball card in the world, which David Copperfield tore up and put back together.
Wow. Wow. What a time.
Bruce McNall. Yeah.
Yeah. I hope he comes up with.
There's another hour. Yeah, he is not the topic that we can't do an hour episode on at least.
My favorite new characters of the year.
Smart One and Bruce McNall and Mr. Kato.
There's been so many. We virtually met so many wonderful new friends this year.
Yes, that's true.
So, yeah, it's like. Yeah, I'm trying to because like, obviously Figment is the star of this era when it comes to Epcot characters.
Which is funny that they're both purple, so they feel affiliated.
There's certainly merchandise where they're hanging out together and they're friends, not rivals.
Right. And then like, yeah, what other fame like a robot butler?
What other character?
Kind of in there, but not doesn't feel like a candidate to be the icon of the park in the way that the other ones do.
Could be.
I feel like I've seen Buzzy from Cranium Command kind of as the third.
If we're doing the Epcot Big Five, I guess we've just named four.
Who's in there is the three headed troll.
Kitche Cabaret guys, the Kitche Cabaret characters run a lot of merch.
Yeah. Oh, yeah, that's true.
Yeah. I mean, Dream Finder, I guess in there, too, with Figment early.
Yeah.
But I mean, part of the marketing.
One. Yeah.
Well, sure.
Part of the marketing of Epcot in the early years, though, was it's for adults.
There's not a lot of characters running around.
There's one Mickey and Minnie.
But if you don't want to see characters, come to Epcot.
Have a beer.
Which I think makes both Figment and Smart One important because they were the kids characters when there were almost none of those.
If you went looking for cute in 82, you're getting two sources for that.
And both of them are purple.
Mm hmm. Yeah.
And purple. I mean, purple goes a long way, I think, in my kid brain.
Yeah.
Jason, were you into purple as a kid? I know Scott and I were.
I liked it a little, but I was much more of a blue kid.
I had a lot of blue stuff. Still do.
There were kids that were trying to like push this purple as a girl's color agenda in elementary school.
I remember this. I remember saying my favorite.
You're very mean.
Well, right. But I just I remember like saying my favorite color was purple and I was like, oh, purple is a girl's color.
Like, no, pink is. That's what I would say.
That's how you would reinforce the binary.
Right. I was still on the binary.
Yeah. Yeah. I wasn't some progressive kid.
I was just I was like, no, I know for sure Barbie is pink.
Barbie's for girls. Barbie, of course, factors into Epcot as well, which we haven't gotten to.
That's true. Yeah. Why haven't?
Yeah. That one's that one's waiting for sure.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. What I have caught in our future, I think there's a lot to cover.
But oh, I know something we have to have a time.
There's not that much in terms of appearance to discuss, but we haven't talked about smart ones.
One. Oh, yeah.
When I think that is a lot of the appeals smart was when smart one lifts straight up and down or or down to up that wand, that feels like such pure optimism.
That is hope for the future. That's lighting a spark that's leading the way like a like a bandleader that's that's conducting.
And in the recent communicator retro artwork, they put all those newer retro posters they put out that the communicator is represented by smart one holding that wand up and there's a little spark hitting it.
Yeah, you know, yeah, look at that. And with that little that little magic dust trail coming off of it, it's why I don't ism.
But I they had that up, I believe, in the Epcot preview center and we were there for all this stuff like they theoretically were going to do to Epcot.
And I was just like, why are they not selling this stuff?
And then I found out there was I don't know how I missed this, but in July they sold like a 200 edition run of this and a few other posters and they sold out very quickly and they were ninety dollars apiece.
So that sucks. And now, of course, they're being flipped on eBay for a lot of money.
I wonder how much they did have those cool shirts with which I bought Epcot forever is the term they've been using.
Yes, that's the name of that show.
Yeah, yeah. And good news, I was playing with my baby and he was kind of sparking to those Epcot stripes and colors and the little emblem part in the middle.
I was like, oh, hey, look at this. Maybe it's starting now.
Granted, he's also he's mainly really into the ceiling thing, but still I'll go I'll take over and get it.
Hey, that's pretty good. I mean, yeah, obviously you have to start.
I mean, we've talked about this before. You have to slowly indoctrinate.
You have to slowly program him. Yeah.
Yeah. Introducing little elements the way you introduce it.
Yeah, a little little little starts and fits. Yeah.
Not going to not going to push it, but not going to push my pro Epcot agenda to it.
But it'll just naturally be living in it.
Is the right inevitable.
We do use there is a contemporary hotel.
I have my contemporary hotel toy, which I light up from the inside and we have been using it essentially as a nightlight.
Like the glow of the rules. It's so great.
That's another tease for later.
Oh, yes. Yeah, yeah. Let's come.
We're probably not too far. No, no, no.
What else we got about smart one?
Well, his I mean, do we call this does Jim Sarno is that the creator?
Is that the guy who just sort of built him? I think that's what he was saying.
He designer designed him after getting kind of a rough sketch idea of what they wanted.
And he was Jim Sarno was an imagineer who I was very interested.
I watched an interview with him. He worked on Teddy Ruxpin.
He worked on the project to add that scene in hell on Mr. Toad and Disneyland.
Yeah. To add it. Was it not there at one point?
Well, they expanded all the dark rides and I'm pretty sure they added that last section.
Like everything got a new scene or two.
Well, on those dark rides when they did the Tony Baxter fantasy land expansion.
And he worked on the Treasure Island in Las Vegas. Oh, hey.
Yeah. This guy, Jim Sarno, a legend. Wow. What a career.
And yeah, he he initially was calling smart one Robbie Robbie the robot.
I found a video of him like pulling out parts that he got.
Yes. Do it center. Yes, I saw that. Yeah, that's pretty delightful.
Like the initial the model of smart one was just all really basic, you know,
in a PVC kind of stuff and just bought for 15 bucks.
Yeah, Mike, you were right on the money when they're like, yeah, here's a sketch.
Go figure it out. Because he talks about going to a hardware store and just spending a day sanding PVC pipe.
The neck was just a half used tape roll.
Like, it's so crazy to see it like, oh, yeah, that's smart one.
Yeah, that's smart one. Yeah, that's the bones of smart one.
Yeah. And he seems it's really kind of sweet.
He seems like he really, really loves smart one and has a lot of affection for him.
And he's like he even like mentions like maybe smart one will come back.
Yeah, like like I don't know if that's any inside information or if that's just because of those posters.
He mentions the posters of smart one.
So it seems like Jim is very fond of the little guy.
Well, what could they do with him again?
Because I mean, that forever show seems fun.
But I when you think of like what is the ultimate Epcot experience?
Maybe like a big smart one being piloted around a barge in that show, like a 40 foot smart one.
Yeah, I mean, that Epcot forever show is OK, but they haven't put a ton of fun stuff like that in there.
So, I mean, I would like that.
Obviously, the easy like the one that seems like the easiest chance is he goes in the queue for Guardians of the Galaxy cosmic rewind.
Yeah, I mean, and I like that.
I mean, I would like to see him maybe in his own little thing, his own something.
Well, maybe one will inspire the other.
Maybe he shows up as a walk around or a roll around or like he could be just outside by one of the fountains.
And he conducts a little show with the fountain and music or something like something like that.
Oh, that's great. With a little wand with a little one.
He's making the jets go. Yeah, like he's doing.
I mean, I don't know if that you could tie some bullshit about communicating with nature, water, I don't know something like they don't do any of that.
I think Rex is a DJ. Yeah, he gives a shit.
That really isn't that I mean, they created their whole backstory and everything.
But ultimately, it's just that wouldn't be fun if he was a DJ.
I think that's the spirit they need to pursue more often.
Yeah. So in some like hub thing, you could put him.
Yeah, doing something fun. I don't know.
I feel like now we know Rex has a love interest in Roxanne, the France only character.
But I'd like to think that, you know, if we're painting smart when his female or not, whatever, possibly a pair there.
I like to imagine that that little Seiko scene happened.
There was a little too aggressive with its hey, beauty.
And that, you know, maybe smart one left that scenario, bumped into a bumbling Rex who is a little more charming and they had more of a natural meat cute.
Oh, I just better in the face of this, you know, this far too aggressive Seiko interaction.
Yeah, they may organically developed early.
They have more of the same energy, I would say.
So I would see that there in a better match. Yeah.
Yeah, that's nice. That's a nice Disney World fan fiction.
Yeah. Flash fiction.
People still say that or is that word from 15 years ago?
I don't know. Ask Jason. He's the closest to knowing.
I mean, I think people still ship characters.
I don't know that the term is bandied about as much.
Yeah, it's like the golden age of like Tumblr and stuff.
Right. I haven't heard that people have been using quarantine to catch up on their shipping.
Because I want to do all the shipping they've been meaning to get to. Yeah.
Yeah. I've been wanting to pair up Seiko and Rocky.
Trump is slow down.
Trump and Louie DeJoy have slowed down shipping actually in an attempt to steal an election.
It's gross. I don't think we should do it. Yeah.
Want to make shipping less efficient.
AOC was really grilling Louie about shipping. Why characters can't be shipped anymore.
Or at least not so fast.
Why can't I ship? Who would AOC want to ship?
Hey, pick two here. Wait, just turn behind you and just point to two of your park stars.
And you're like blind and then we have to ship them.
Oh, OK. OK. I have all the robots actually down here with me.
I have both star tours. Oh, you want to put them back up so they're in the mix or do we take them out?
Yeah. Yeah. Let me put them in. All right. They're going to be. Hold on. Let me. OK. OK.
Mm hmm. All right. I got one here. A blind ship. OK.
And I am doing a second one. I knocked one over. That'll be the one.
OK, I have Barker Bird from Tiki Room and I can't think of his name.
The one from the outside who tries to get you to come in? Yeah, I think so. I got to check his name.
Yeah, the Carnival Barker Bird and Big L.
Maybe we should just ship them as friends. OK. Maybe not. Let's do one more.
The sizes are. I don't know. I like them. Wait. OK. No, no, no.
We should do try to. We have to take what we're given. No, no, no. Let's let's do it.
How do they work, Jason? All right. How do they meet?
I think they meet at like one of those like you hear like Hanson.
The band Hanson used to run like songwriting camps for songwriters
and they'd pair up like disparate like they pair up like one of them,
someone who does like chart like Katy Perry kind of hits and then weird out.
And then they'd have to write a song in a couple of days and record it.
Right. I think they're at like an animatronics like, yeah, we're the musical.
We're the musical animatronics. You know, there's been invited to Hanson's animatronics only this year.
Yeah. Songwriting. Yeah. And they got a lot of retired.
They got a lot of the rock fire people, the showbiz pizza people.
And they got a scary fantasia land, the monkeys and the king that we learned about.
It's international. They all went to Oklahoma to hang out with Hanson.
Yeah. And one day like these Sundays are allowed to just kind of free like write songs.
And some days like, OK, you got an assignment. You got to get Crest in there somehow.
You got to think about hope for tomorrow and how Crest toothpaste is going to get us there.
Wow. Which encouraged and so maybe Barker Bird encouraged Big Al to smile.
Got the first real smiles out of him in years.
Yeah, they've been inseparable ever so they and now Big Al sings only happy songs.
I'm in love with Barker Bird. I mean, that's sweet.
That's nice. Yeah, that gives me hope for the future.
Yeah. Smiling as big as I'd be smiling with the help of Crest.
I think this will be if we did segments anymore, this should be a regular segment shipping my Park Stars blindly.
Yeah, I'd do this again. Well, we know we'll throw out of ideas.
Then we'll throw the Ninja Turtles in the mix and then it'll be like Leatherhead gets shipped with
let's say shredder. Yeah.
And see, this is so much healthier.
I mean, this is like, you know, people say like Twitter has only gotten worse as the Tumblr generation has migrated as the website fell apart.
And they just pop in and go like, sorry, Karl Marx, you're canceled. Martin Scorsese, get out of here.
It was so much better when they would just be like, yeah,
Krang from Ninja Turtles is in love with Princess Bubblegum. Got it. Got it.
So do we need to take Tumblr back over? Yeah, we. Yeah.
We need a healthier outlet.
Guess what? The mid to late 30s generation are going to hide for a while on Tumblr.
We've just had so many recessions, international catastrophe.
We just need to relax for a while and get like Big Al and Barker Bird stuff, you know, rest our brains.
And it's not weird stuff. It's just romance. It's G with mild PG elements.
Holding hands. Yeah. Very wholesome. Like the Duffy gang. Not a sex thing. Pure love.
Perfect love.
To quote the message. Well, are we are we getting to smart ones?
Yes, we are. Yes, we are.
It's what I call smart ones party down arc because he very much is a is a bit of a star and then ends up in a in a fine industry like a fine,
you know, in no judgment on people who, you know, bartend.
I would like I would like anyone listening that doesn't know where we're going with this.
Think in your head, where do we think smart one ended up after they took the robot out of communicator?
All right, you got it. And now we're going to tell you smart one ended up in a steakhouse in the contemporary resort as a greeter slash to drink holder.
I don't know how much tray holder. Yeah, I think it was.
I think it was just I don't think they'd actually the robot actually brought anyone drinks.
I think it was just a cute little thing at the at the front.
But I have to feel like it. I had to think when that hotel was like the big convention spot, there was some surly guy like hammered guy like, God damn it.
God damn it. You stupid robot. I asked for a gimlet, not a Tom Collins.
Which I would think, yes, that smart one got yelled at by a lot of drunk people.
No problem, sir. And like, that's a really sad, a sad situation.
Don't be optimistic about the future.
What was the name? Didn't they change it to like X?
The name was X one eight four six.
No longer smart one. Now, X one eight four six.
And that is because that was the extension.
If you dialed the number of the concourse steakhouse at the contemporary resort, if you picked up the phone in your room that I actually kind of like that.
I didn't know what enemy it could. I think it's that it's kind of cute.
But they strip smart one of an identity.
Yeah. I mean, yes, yes.
But, you know, I just I just think how much I would have liked to encounter this at the time, because this was in 94 that this was put in and around 2000 due to technical malfunctions.
This was stopped. I don't know how much that was even started.
I'm not convinced they they did this. There's a lot of documentation.
There's no video. Did you find any video?
No, no. Most of the proof of that this happened is from like an internal Disney newsletter.
But that gives you one great bit of info, which is that.
All right. So the primary function of the robot is to greet guests within the concourse steakhouse and help celebrate special occasions like birthdays or anniversaries, just like Chuck E.
Cheese X one eight four six can serve drinks or food and entertain guests who might be waiting for a table.
He may occasionally pass out samples of monorail ale.
I know about monorail ale.
First of all, I love some. I'm looking at a picture of him holding five drinks.
I mean, that sounds great.
I mean, how happy I would be if I could if we could escape this dark timeline, I could go sit in the concourse steakhouse, have a passable steak and have my favorite little robot roll up to me and ask monorail ale, sir.
I mean, it's a dream. Yes, of course.
And you'd be like, and then you'd be like, you'd call the robot smart one and it would be like, I do not remember that name.
And then you like try to jog its memory and it would be like, there would be like you'd see something in the eye.
And then it would be the last time you tried to guess a number.
And then like it would be like you could see you did it and then like it realized that it had a life before this.
What did you say? Get me out of here, Scott, please.
I remember now you are only hope.
So then I've got a I mean, I'm looking at a picture of the concourse steakhouse and there's a potted plant, which is not that different than the size of smart one.
So maybe either I lift up the potted plant.
Maybe I like quickly go change clothes, pretend that I am a mover or something like, oh, yeah, just move in this plant.
I got to put on a voice that'll help with the run.
And and I am like, here you go. Just scoot as I scoot and then just like get it onto the elevator.
Put him in a maybe I have to get a new suitcase for it.
And now I have to carry like a one ton item to the Orlando airport.
But yeah, this works. I think I could break them.
I get to live with them. Yeah.
Oh, what a dream. What a dream scenario.
He serves a drink and then you steal the robot and then I steal from Disney.
Yeah, not here. We can't talk here.
Get me out of here. Get me to the McDonald's.
Get me to the odd property McDonald's.
They don't have microphones there.
This is not safe. They'll try to repurpose you as a grimace robot.
G.R.M.A.C.
Pretend you're a robotic brother.
I five. I like the five is the yeah.
Yeah. This feels like they always everyone always flirts with this idea.
But we never truly get a robot giving you drinks or an alien in the canteen.
A serving you and Galaxy's Edge.
It's always a concept I think we hear about in blue sky phases and you see it here and there.
But it never sustains. It never lasts.
I want an alien or a robot to wait on me at a restaurant or a bar.
But yeah, is it possible? Maybe it is not possible.
I think they always crunch numbers and go, look, it's too expensive for this robot.
And like, does a server really need to wear this stupid makeup? Come on.
Yeah, we make this. It's a hard job to begin with.
There wasn't nobody. No robot served you at that Cheers bar with the robotic likenesses of Norm and Cliff where they sued.
Wait, you know the story, right?
Oh, vaguely. Yeah, very faintly.
Yeah, there were there were robots of the Cheers characters that this one Cheers bar and they were pretty grotesque.
I believe I think they were like those scary puppets from D.C.
Follies. It was, you know, they're kind of like squishy and terrifying.
But they did kind of resemble Ratzenberger and went enough that they sued successfully.
And this concept did not get any further.
I don't think there was also a robot Woody serving anybody.
I don't think or and all alternately, Diane.
Yeah, Rebecca.
There's a bar in Vegas, I think by Planet Hollywood that is a robot mixing your cocktail, but they're just arms.
There's no cute face. There's no personality as far as I can tell.
So it's like that's I like it, but it's not it is giving me that personality.
Also, I'm sure everybody told you Mike to go to the robot restaurant in Japan.
We fucked up and we missed the show.
Well, I mean, that seems interesting that robot restaurant, but it isn't it's it's a lot more complicated.
I feel than what I want when I hear robot restaurant.
I just want a robot to roll up to me with a drink.
I want exactly what this was promising with smart one.
Right. Yes.
Yes, I've seen video of it. It is.
It seems crazy. Yeah.
So who will crack a sustainable idea with a robot?
Maybe there is one operating now. We don't know.
If you're a listener and you know, let us know.
Let me say this as well.
It's 2020 service industry restaurants.
It's a bad time.
We're all afraid of this disease and we're trying to reopen restaurants.
But there's there's bad people out there being very rude to the staff and it doesn't feel safe.
And you know what would make it safe?
Robot. I don't want to go over placing anybody's jobs, obviously.
The robots. Here's what should happen.
The robots should be doing the work while the wait staff stays employed to stay home and are given the tips that are handed to the robot.
But that's sorry robots. I don't know.
I don't know. That's going to be a problem because are these robots sentient?
I guess they would have to be to some extent to do this.
Then that's cruel as well.
But they don't need money.
They like to be appreciated, though.
Well, well, so you say thanks.
And someday when it's safer, you give them a kiss like Carly Simon.
I mean, I think you need to ask the people who ended up owning SmartOne, the Florida Robotics Club,
it is full of a picture.
It was smart when in the back of a truck.
Yeah. Oh, man.
That was the conclusion I read is once they took him out of the steakhouse, he was either given, sold or exchanged for services to the Florida Robotics Club.
So they have him.
Supposedly. I know kind of where the trail went dry and I didn't see much about the Florida.
Who knows if that Florida?
I don't know if it's the Florida Robotics Club or a Florida Robotics Club.
Why don't we know?
Why is that that guy on Disney Plus is running around finding broken helmets and shit?
The prop culture.
Why? He did a whole season and didn't even consider trying to find SmartOne.
You're on you're on notice host of prop culture.
Turn it turn in your pork pie hats.
You're on death's duty.
I'm tearing the stripes off of your Smash Mouth Steve Harwell-esque shirts.
You don't deserve to wear the until you find SmartOne.
He he might I mean, look, he might know where everything is, you know, just not telling.
He knows where all the bodies are buried.
Oh, that's how he so he got the show greenlit is bribery.
Like if you want the SmartOne return, you know what?
If you want the shrinking machine, you'll do as I say.
Give me a show on your new streaming platform.
I'll say that's your edge Crescent Lake.
You know what's good for you.
You'll give me a streaming show.
They try to make that show, though, seem like he's like, oh, I'm just the guy who's here and I'm going to try to find all this fun stuff.
Meanwhile, he's like an archivist.
He works for the company.
He knows where everything is.
Yeah, they're doing a whole dog and pony show.
He's making all this stuff.
He's just like scattering all these things across the globe.
Yeah, like surely.
Let's get a Jason Sheridan in there who truly knows where none of this stuff is and make him find it with no help.
I'll do it.
That's a show.
Not this guy who knows where it is.
And he goes, well, we hope we can find something today.
And it's like, oh, look, it's Mary Poppins and Burt's wardrobe.
I didn't know that, except he did know that he knew exactly where it was.
He has access to the archives.
No, I'm doing the full Da Vinci code national treasure, like ripping down.
Yes, you have to do posters scanning.
You have to scale the wall at the Disney Archive.
You have to get in there past guards.
You have to put on a disguise.
That's the show.
That's a good show for realistic masks.
Yes, like mission.
You have to do a whole mission impossible style mission.
Yeah, climbing up sides of buildings.
And that's what you want.
As we learned on the Ace Ventura episode, this is what Jason wants to scale the side of a building.
Oh, right.
Sure.
And go down again.
So he loves heights.
He's the height miser.
I love it on the height miser.
He's grabbing Walt's like little just throw in the little seven dwarf Oscars at the screens in the Monorail hallway at Imagineering.
It's like, what's behind here?
Yeah, like imagine the imagine the Disney building in Burbank over here.
But it's the Dubai scene in Mission Impossible 4 where he's on the top of the building.
Jason with a cord.
He's running along the building with a cord to jump through a different window to get to, let's say, the the bed from Bedknobs and Broodstinks.
The missing knob.
We have three of the four, but it won't be complete.
This is a fucking show.
Man.
Yeah, there's no action on prop culture.
No action whatsoever.
No action.
I think I think what's happening is that, OK, so if you've been to Burbank, if there's the animation building that's Sorcerer's Hat and there's a tip.
And I think up in that tip, what I'm worried is happening is that Smart One is has been captured and locked away by Seiko.
Oh, finally.
You are mine, cutie.
Oh, my God.
After decades.
Now that you are not working for that hotel bar anymore, you can be mine.
But when Jason kicks in the star on the side of the search, there's that.
Seiko, freeze.
Don't move a muscle.
You said I couldn't find anything.
Good news.
I found Black Widow's gun.
See, then Seiko is like, what are you doing in here?
Bob Iger.
And then Jason pulls the mask off.
And he's Jason.
He was dressed as Bob Iger the whole time.
Oh, no.
A different Ithaca grad.
I was.
I was fooled because I could feel the Ithaca on you.
And it was confusing.
Ithaca energy.
Ithaca vibes.
Robots can read this.
Of course, who else would know all of the subs made for late night stoner
consumption?
All of the town specific calzones at that DP Doze.
Oh, subs.
Oh, yeah.
It took me a second too, but yes, I like that joke.
The chain restaurants only located next to college campuses.
Wings with a Z. DP Doze calzones.
Can we get Bob Iger on the show if we promise that we won't ask him anything
hard and that it'll just be Jason reminiscing about some reminiscing about
shops?
Has he done what?
Let's look into what interviews he's done.
Yeah, like, promise him there's this is all softball.
He did Bill Simmons.
I know I'm aware.
We're on that level.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, we're right there.
Things just got busy.
What would that pandemic?
Yeah, but once it winds down, it's time for time for sub shop memories with.
Oh, my God.
Not a single not a single Disney question.
You and I never comes out.
You and I barely talk.
Jason just asks.
Just reminisces.
I'm aware of that.
And they describe what their experiences were.
We describe our experiences.
We have to give them a little bit of time to talk about something going well in the
Disney outlook in China.
We do have to give them 15 minutes for that.
Sure.
Look in there.
We're like, come on.
All right.
So we'll cut it.
We'll cut it.
It's like the Lanzaluzios.
Yeah.
Even if he tries to cram some of that stuff.
Yeah, 15 minutes about the success in China and then like, OK, great.
So let's talk about.
All right.
Let's get back to Rogan's corner.
The combination laundromat liquor store, sub shop pizza restaurant.
And then we bring in Mitch because there's a legend of an interview.
Do we talk about this on the show?
I don't know.
So did you say that on the interview?
Did we talk about this on the show?
Do you know what I'm talking about?
Yes, you saw it or I who saw it?
One of us saw it.
Bob Iger talked about what he was watching.
And this is a couple of years ago.
We think that Mitch I feel like I heard Bob Iger say that he watched his love and like
love and that's what be aware of the work of Mike Mitchell.
Yeah.
So Mitch will be on this episode too, because he'll know Randy from love.
I like ask about Star Wars and how they suck and we don't want that cutting into the sub
time.
Do you really?
Mitch wouldn't just be nice, you think?
Mitch going at like when he met JJ Abrams.
Yes, bro.
Yeah.
You would just be like, Oh, hello, sir.
Nice to meet you.
Well, all right.
So some talk with Jason Bob coming soon.
Mm hmm.
Um, it's also smart ones rescue from the claws of Seiko coming soon.
Thanks to Jason swinging in on a rope.
And that's our smart one episode.
We really did it.
We like to bring it back.
Smart one encourages people to use their imagination.
Maybe.
I don't know.
Look, I still don't really know what smart ones personality is.
I just makes me happy to look at a ton of meat on the bone.
Friendly.
Really?
We got 80 minutes.
Yeah.
Minutes out of it.
And now I'm just going to.
I don't think I said you survived.
I guess.
You survived it.
And now I'm going to survive the rest of the day by just imagining that I'm sitting at
the what's it called?
The concourse steakhouse and that X one eight four six is bringing me round after round.
Refresh your Chardonnay, sir.
It's well, it's 1994.
So can I try one of those Zima's everybody's talking about?
Very good choice, sir.
Very popular right now.
I have a special bottle tucked away from the Fes Parker winery.
Oh, very good.
Here's a here's a little tip then.
And you can save that and not pass it off.
I will give it to a human because I know tips in your case.
Get yourself a nice wand.
All right.
I will, sir.
Boy, 1995 is going to be all right.
All right, folks, thanks for listening.
Goodbye.
Bye.