This is Podcast the Ride, the second gate.
Here now, Scott Gertner.
Welcome to an emergency solo Podcast the Ride,
the second gate.
This is actually the first ever one host only
Podcast the Ride.
It's an unprecedented move, but then again,
these are unprecedented times.
And if you'll allow me to explain
and get some thoughts off my chest.
I've had, I'm Scott Gertner by the way,
I've had an extremely busy last few weeks.
It's all good things, everything's good,
but it became imperative schedule wise
that I take one episode off.
And I discussed this with Mike and Jason
and they agreed to take the reins.
That said, I was of course aware of the risk of doing this.
That by taking an episode off,
I was setting myself up and you the audience up
for an episode that was non-Theme Park related,
full of bizarre statements and points of view.
And of course, setting up an episode
that is a relitigating a matter and a story
that has come up on this podcast,
frankly, far too many times.
And as I checked in with Mike and Jason,
are you guys good on that episode
that you guys are just gonna do?
There was a smile, there was a glint in their eyes
that I could see over Zoom
because that's how we communicate.
There was a level of mischief
in talking about the episode
that ended up coming out earlier today.
I was beginning to smell a rat,
but what kind of rat would it be?
Would it be a Chukko-scented rat?
Would it be a Buffett-plane-scented rat?
And then around midnight, I refreshed the app
and along with you the audience,
I discovered two words staring back at me, mocking me.
And those words are of course, Casamigos tequila.
Now, ironically, this episode exists
because I was seeking to take some time off
and yet now I've created more work for myself
because I've realized that I need to do
some kind of rebuttal piece,
encounter to the episode that you may have heard earlier.
And I'd like to do that right now.
Mainly, I would like to raise three primary objections
and there's more that I could do,
but there's three big ones that I wanna bring up
regarding the Casamigos episode
and in general, the continuing, never ceasing presence
of Casamigos tequila on this theme park podcast.
So I'm gonna discuss those three objections right now.
Okay, objection number one.
My co-hosts have time and time again failed
to convey to me and perhaps you the audience
why the Casamigos briefcase story is a good story
in the multiple tellings of this story on our podcast.
Neither Jason nor Mike has conveyed
why the story is interesting.
Is it supposed to be funny?
Do I hear the story where some very rich people
give other rich people briefcases full of cash?
Am I supposed to hear the story and laugh at the story?
What is it that makes this story worth telling
so many times?
What is it that is so great about the story
that it continues to thrive despite our friend Nick Mundy
being so bored by the story
that he literally unplugged the microphones
being used to record it?
Why does it continue to maintain?
I feel like I ask for explanations
of why the briefcase story is a good story
and what do I get?
I get the story told to me again
as if the answer is in the story itself.
In 90 minutes, there was no conveying
of why this briefcase story is good.
I will continue to ask for this, not just for myself,
but for you the audience.
We need to know why.
Why are the gentlemen behind Casamigos celebrated
for selling their liquor to a liquor conglomerate,
but the folks over at Ballast Point
are criticized, villainized for doing the very same thing.
I failed to know, but I will continue to fight
for answers for you.
Objection number two, the price point.
As Casamigos continues to come up,
there has been discussion of how it is too expensive.
Despite the perverse fascination in this tequila,
the big wall for my co-hosts in trying it
seems to be the price point.
When I realized that Mike had never tried it,
his defense was, that's a lot of money.
I believe at the time he said, $65?
I'm not gonna spend $65.
Then I listened to the episode that they just put up
and the number changed.
The number became $45.
And that was still too much.
Mike is self-discounting.
$45 is not an unreasonable amount of money
for a nice tequila.
In fact, I was just a Trader Joe's
where Casamigos was available on the shelf for $39.
That's not only a reasonable price for a nice tequila.
It might be the cheapest premium tequila on the market.
In what world is $39 not a fair price point for the,
I Google what other premium tequilas cost,
your Patron's and the like,
and you'll find them to be more expensive.
When the price is relitigated again in today's episode,
Jason says that he's always had an aversion
to spending money for comedy.
As if buying a $40 bottle of tequila is the same thing
as buying a stinky wig for a UCB sketch.
If you buy the bottle, then you have the bottle.
Then you have tequila to drink
and good tequila that doesn't burn.
And there's a lot made out of this burning issue,
but you know what doesn't burn?
Premium tequila.
You know what does burn?
Shitty cheap tequila.
You get what you pay for.
And if you pay slightly more, you know, $40,
the highest number in the world,
then you get a liquor, the tequila that doesn't burn.
Objection number three.
During the episode, Mike said the word agave several times.
The word is of course agave.
And you, the listener, deserve better than superfluous use.
So I made it to the end of the episode miraculously,
and I discovered my podcast partner's business plan.
Their plan to start their own podcast, The Ride Tequila.
And while I appreciate their consideration of me,
despite my absence, them wanting to include me,
I officially hereby reject my 20%
of Buenos Chicos Tequila.
If this 20% were handed to me in a briefcase,
I would spit on the briefcase,
ruining both the money and the leather.
And let me tell you why.
Because I have decided to take a page out of their book
and branch off and start my own premium liquor line.
["The Ride Tequila"]
Some of us like to play by our own rules.
Some of us are a little rougher and tougher,
and don't get stomach aches from drinking too much seltzer.
Some of us like different black keys songs.
If you're part of that, some of us,
grab some Mollo Nino Tequila.
Singular and mollo meaning bad.
Mollo Nino is distilled by taking premium tequilas
that are made by combining George Clooney
and the Rocks Tequilas,
pouring that combined tequila down the toilet
and replacing it with Chardonnay.
Mollo Nino is the only tequila that contains no tequila
and certainly no agave.
But we do add a fresh squeeze
of the most premium fruit there is, grapefruit.
Who gives a shit about grapefruit?
We do.
Mollo Nino Tequila.
Wait, I should tag it more.
You know, made for podcast bad boys.
Wait, made by podcast bad boys for...
Look, I don't know, I'm gonna sort that out.
Sorry, wait, sometimes it feels good to be mollo.
Okay, I'll tighten it up,
but you're gonna see that ad soon.
It's gonna be very well produced.
And mainly what I'm gonna demand
from my co-hosts in the future is transparency.
Transparency about episodes
that they're gonna do without me.
Transparency about why stories about briefcases
full of money are interesting.
You've survived Podcast the Ride,
Scott's Casa Migos rebuttal edition.
Thank you for listening.
May God help us all.