Forever.
Dog.
Warning.
Today's podcast episode is somewhat unique and calls for a different kind of introduction.
This, as you may recognize, is the Twilight Zone Tower of Terror, opened in 1994 at Disney
MGM Studios.
Still in operation, waiting for you.
We invite you, if you dare, to learn how each host was scared of the ride during childhood,
and in some cases, adulthood.
And discover how 21 kinds of tobacco make for 20 wonderful Chesterfield smokes.
Today on the return of Hauntcast the Fright.
Welcome to Hauntcast the Frights, the Scream Park podcast hosted by three headless men
and their ghoulies.
I'm Scott Gravedigger, joined by...
Take it.
My name is I kill girl stone.
Girl, like girl, not girls, not girl stone, like grrrr stone.
Sorry, sorry.
You kill girls specifically.
I just said girl instead of grr.
That really screwed everyone up.
I'm so sorry.
That was confusing.
Anyway.
He almost got away with it until his confession was laid bare in a funny Halloween name.
Then 25 girls have been recovered.
All the listeners of his podcast suspected, but they never knew for sure until that fateful
Tower of Terror episode.
People suppressed so much until in one episode it all came out.
But hey, let's also bring in...
Jack-o-lantern slime-a-din.
Oh, great.
I'm glad we refreshed the spooky name banks.
It's a pleasure to talk to you both, I kill and Jack-o-lantern.
And it's a pleasure to be here in Hauntcast the Fright once more.
I'm excited.
Due to various other things like our tour last year, our mini tour, there were other
things going on in October.
We didn't get to do the full month, but we've got it cleared out.
This is an October full of frights and delights.
Yes.
The first...
Well, technically we did miss one Friday, but it's going to be plenty of Fridays.
Five Fridays.
Five Fridays in October this year.
Yeah.
Four.
You don't want to do too many frights.
Oh, yeah.
People get rattled.
Five main feed frights.
Too many.
Just seeing the scary logo that we have and hearing the scarier music and hearing our
scarier names is putting all the listeners at severe risk of shrieks and diarrhea.
If we did it five times all month, it would just be too sustained and you couldn't eat.
How often during Hauntcast the Fright do the listeners have just horrible diarrhea?
I don't know.
I mean, at least when a new one pops up in their feed or when they see a tweet.
You get into the meat of the episode and maybe you're only diarrhea-ing seven times or so,
but you know there's a lot loaded up at the beginning.
It's like somebody...
Or even seeing the name Tower of Terror or Snow White's Scary Adventures.
That's a little diarrhea pang every time.
Right.
Or they hear like, oh, Jason likes 100 grand bars better than Milky Way.
Ah!
Have a horrible diarrhea because they heard that scary thing about Jason and Halloween
candy.
He'll never find zero bars in this day and age.
Oh!
Yeah.
So it's a fright around every corner on this podcast in October.
There's a lot to talk about with this topic.
We're doing a big one.
It's a big, big one and we're being big brave boys to do it.
That does make me think with the candy discussion.
There's no treats trail this year, obviously.
All this stuff's happening and we don't have to go over it.
I guess Jason, do you end up buying extra candy just to have around?
How do you handle a quarantine Halloween?
Well, look, as long as the aisles of your local supermarket and drugstore seasonal sections
are well stocked, I'll be fine.
Are you, Jason, are you going to wait for discounts or are you going to buy during the month?
I will probably buy a couple of times during the month.
I think CVS discounts a lot.
We got lunch once in between recordings and I came back with bags of CVS Reese's Eggs.
Easter Eggs.
Scott, are you a Reese's or a correct pronunciation Reese's man?
Well, I was going to say, yeah, I think I'm a Reese's.
OK, got it.
OK.
But you, though I'm not even sure your answer, Mike, because you did say correct, but also
it makes me think you like saying Reese's better.
I think it's funny saying Reese's, but I Reese's.
Now look, I look, I'm not I'm not I'm not not guilty for mispronouncing.
I called a what did I call a guava, a guava, a guava, a guava.
Yes.
Multiple.
So look, I already so I'm screwing up, too, here.
So I'm not I'm not out of the woods.
Yeah, yeah.
I well, I'm going to try it on for size.
Maybe I'll shift to becoming a Reese's person.
It didn't feel right.
I think I'm not like having the joy and abandon that you need to have to say Reese's.
You need to be a much more of a free spirit to say Reese's.
Yeah.
So too uptight.
Well, I'll work on it.
I'll try to drop that word in to our conversations all month as much as I can.
But for now, let's tackle where you guys we're opening with a with a bang.
We're doing a big old major, major attraction.
This is exciting. Twilight Zone Tower of Terror.
Been looking forward to this conversation a lot.
And I think as usual, we'll put a little bit of a put it in a little bit of a box here.
We're going to mostly just talk about Florida and the California version,
not Mission Breakout Guardians of the Galaxy, not Tokyo version.
We haven't done Paris, but Scott, you've been there and this is that is pretty similar.
So it just is exactly the same, I believe, as as California
only with worse theming on the way in.
That's the I can get that out of the way right now that you just sort of like
even they managed to do a little like some lead up.
It's kind of weird in the corner over there in California Adventure.
It is like it's odd.
It's certainly not the grand buildup of Sunset Boulevard in Florida.
Still better than France, though, or you just kind of like round a corner
and pass by like a poster for signs or something.
It's an out of date movie and then just, oh, Tower of Terror is here.
And the other thing that makes me crazy is that you can see the back,
which is unthemed.
Like if you're on Harbor Boulevard,
if you're at Harbor and Cotella, the former location of Nixon's
hamburgers, of course, you could, you know, you could see the back of that building
and it's sort of unthemed.
But you let that slide with Disney.
You know, they they don't really theme the back of the Cars Land rocks.
You know, that's not, you know, they dress the side that you're where you're in the park.
Paris, you're just in there and it's just like a like a blank facade.
It's terrible.
So I'm sorry to start on a on a sour,
you know, but that does clear out every everything that there is to say about the France one.
I there's I was going to say there's one other thing they have extra little like
they have like different scenarios they put in the elevator
shafts on special like weekends as well.
They have like a little bit extra magic with like some more dropping
that I just they announced.
I don't know if they've actually put it into put it into use yet,
but they announced it at a certain point.
So they're trying different things.
And they also kind of do a similar thing in Tokyo with like they have.
Yeah, there's some scarier iteration.
Yeah, that they they advertise specially.
I mean, that's sort of true of all of these in a way
that they've like found ways to to randomize it and increase the scares.
I mean, that's when I when you think of Tower of Terror,
you definitely think of of the ads and that not only there are the ads when it open,
but then there's this other wave of I'm trying to remember.
Oh, like, you know,
that they are every drop and like double was it double trouble?
Like they had so many promotions.
I know what you mean.
Like the one the one I wrote down was T4.
So it's like the fourth iterations, they're calling it T4,
and which maybe implies that there's up to four drops or maybe more like big drops,
which also had the phrase the tower is in control.
Yes. OK, so the very first iteration was one big drop.
Yes. Two years later.
Really? Yeah. Yeah.
And and you have to imagine maybe a little anticlimactic
because there you waited so long those first few years.
It was the the star of the the the park at that point.
Do you remember, Jason, going on this because I went on this pretty quickly.
Like when it was open, we just happened to be going that year.
That's or it was the year after it was Rock and Rollercoaster
and Tower of Terror were both open.
And I was in this open in ninety four, right?
Yeah, not before, but didn't Rock and Rollercoaster open in ninety nine.
That was a while there. Right.
All right. Then I'm confusing my own trips.
I went on this pretty quickly after it was open.
So maybe I'm confusing my two trips with Rock and Rollercoaster.
But I remember not being like let down by the drop is really what I'm getting at.
Yeah. I mean, the buildup is so satisfying.
As for me, I think I think it opened in between like trips my family took.
So I think I would have gone on in ninety six.
So it may have been two drops at that point, but it was still brand new.
Still like our two 90 minute wait, at least.
I just remember the first time getting the full extended queue
and the gardens were so cool.
Like it was so it's supposed to be dilapidated.
But Disney is so good at landscape architecture.
Like the dilapidated gardens are beautiful.
And the other thing is there were misters hidden everywhere.
So it was a little spooky and also much needed
because it would have been like the middle of summer.
Oh, sure. Yes. Yeah.
That's a cool way to do it.
It kind of seems like fog or something.
I also remember when this ride showed up on the scene.
Obviously, I didn't I didn't actually go on it until with you guys in last October.
I it opened, I think, because I went in 92 and 94.
So the second time I went to Disney World, it was there.
And I remember feeling more unnerved
everywhere at the resort because of the mere existence of the tower.
Wow, really?
Is that you would see it from Epcot or you'd see it from a hotel
or you'd see the ad with the like shaking elevator, the billboard on the way in,
or you'd see it on the in-room TV.
It like loomed over the whole trip.
It like just just the notion of it made my second time there so much scarier
because you knew you were going to do it press.
Yeah, no, because I knew I wasn't going to do it.
I didn't do it then. Oh, I see.
OK, you when I was not.
No. And I and maybe the maybe the inner shame of knowing
there wasn't even a chance that I was going to give it a shot.
Yeah, I felt similar with Alien Encounter because that was also new. Yes.
Maybe maybe that whole trip was just shame in the back of my.
Yeah, shame that I wasn't going to do it.
And also like what happened to this place?
This was a magical place for little kids full of castles and fairies.
And now there's so much horror around every turn.
Why did they add things young people might enjoy and be thrilled by?
Disgusting. Didn't make any sense to me.
There's more looks behind the scenes of my favorite films.
And that is all they should ever add.
I felt anxiety because of Alien Encounter,
because I was like thought it was awesome when I was reading about it.
And then we got there.
I famously, of course, if you listen to the old episodes, chickened out.
And I was it definitely like it like stuck with me the whole trip of like
your dad and your little sister went on it.
And you didn't, you loser.
But I wasn't like. Yeah.
I was once it was like this side, we had gone to Magic Kingdom
and I wasn't going to go on it.
I guess I kind of put it out of my mind.
Yeah, yeah. I mean, I didn't I didn't build up the bravery until last year.
And I'm so glad.
I mean, as I've said before, really, Tokyo was what did it.
Because Aaron, when we were there, my wife was like,
you're not going to come all this way and not go on this tower of terror.
And thank God, because that thing is incredible.
And then it like, you know, it made me have to go do all the other ones
and guardians and everything.
And Aaron was very that was maybe her biggest trip disappointment
because we were she was newly pregnant at the time
and that she was really looking forward to doing
the Florida Tower of Terror.
So apologies to Aaron if you're listening to this.
We'll we'll get there one day.
Yeah, I I do remember since you both mentioned being scared as children
going when this was open, I was so excited to ride it at the same time.
All of the marketing for it featured footage of people
standing in an elevator that drops.
And I was like, this is insane.
Disney just puts you in an elevator, standing up and you're going to drop.
And then as we're like, this is like driving me crazy as we're like in the line.
And I'm like, oh, there's Rod Serling, obviously, as a weird little child.
I love the Twilight Zone.
I'm so excited to see Rod Serling and the queue and everything.
And then the doors open and there's seats and seat belts.
And I'm like, oh, my thank God.
Just thank God.
But I feel like it was another one where, like, my memory as a child
and I'm probably just misremembering is I could not get a straight answer
from cast members like when I would ask, like, does the rock and roller coaster
go upside down or does the outer limits flight of fear?
Like, is it super scary?
Like and no one would tell me.
And I did that once.
And there was a there was a refresh of Space Mountain where I went and asked,
OK, when this was redone, was a launch added?
And maybe I didn't have the word launch at my disposal.
And I had to say, like, does it have the thing where it goes super fast
all of a sudden, which if you say that to a Space Mountain employee, they're like,
yeah, yeah, like, yeah, it's a fast ride.
What do you I could not get a straight answer.
And obviously they did not add a launch.
So I braved it anyway.
But that was my launch fear.
Even the like the idea that they might have put one in there was too much for me.
Launch that's interesting because, yeah, rock and roller coaster is my first launch.
But I don't know when it when it when is the first time you knew what a launch was?
Do you think how old do you think you were?
Well, when did they start putting them in there?
I mean, yeah, rock and roller coaster could have been the first one,
like around then and mummy. Yeah.
Yeah. I mean, I was a down by the time.
Oh, yeah, I was I was a teenager who was deathly afraid of the
mere notion of launches, just to clarify.
Not a child. Wow.
I think just because I wasn't even that familiar with launches
when I did rock and roller coaster, I realized that made me feel bad.
I've said this before, so I'm not going to get that far into it,
but it made me feel better because it would go quick.
It would be over quick.
I hate the suspense of roller coaster.
I hate the suspense.
I don't like the slow climb up.
Like, that's why when we did hang time, which is the thing that like
it's like just puts us like in a chair slowly going vertical.
That's the most anxiety inducing thing that I can do
because it's just all suspense.
And then the ride is fine.
Which so it's interesting, like this kind of ride,
it is the first Disney drop tower, and they've done less themed ones
like the Malibu, which that one just shot you straight up.
Like there was no buildup that wasn't like you climb up very slowly.
That was just like, yeah, similar to Dr.
Doom's Fearfall, that was like an off the shelf sort of thing with no theme.
At least Dr. Doom, they the queue is pretty good.
And I've I've never done a legs dangling drop ride.
Sure, sure. Really?
Never, ever. Wow.
I'm not saying I've never done.
You've never done Fearfall, never done Fearfall.
You've never been through the Latvarian embassy, never been to the Doom bot.
Well, Michael, this is I can't believe this. Yeah.
OK, look, next time we go to Orlando or I go to Orlando, I will.
I I don't even want to say it.
I will do Dr. Doom's Fearfall.
I I did it like four times because you just go out the exit
and like go around the corner and get back in line.
I don't because you're you're a brave boy.
You were you were a brave boy and still are.
And I got to see those views.
I got to see those views.
I try to cut I try to cut you down by making fun of your Reese's pronunciation.
But it's just because you're braver than I am.
Oh, thank you so much.
No, that's what it's all about.
All of the undercutting, because you've had so many more years
of Tower of Terror experience.
That is true.
But I had multiple times doing the research for this,
where I truly felt like an idiot, where I am like learning.
I did. I did not know that if you stare at the Morocco Pavilion,
I didn't either. The tower, it did not occur.
Yeah, you could. It did not occur that they were that close,
that they built like minarets almost on top to make it blend in.
Tie together. Right.
So if you're in Epcot Center and World Showcase
and you're from certain angles, you're staring across at the Morocco Pavilion.
They colored this Tower of Terror to fit with Epcot's Morocco.
I know I never noticed that. It still fits in the sightline.
Yeah, yeah, I never.
That's very cool.
I saw the photo they had on whatever site I was on and it was I was like, oh, wow.
I probably stared right at it.
You didn't realize it.
Kudos. Yeah, we will.
The thing I was going to get to is that, yeah, this is the first Disney
drop tower, and I think it came out of they knew they knew they wanted to do that.
Like Splash Mountain before it, like this is a genre of ride that's very common,
but we haven't done it ourselves.
It actually maybe wasn't that common.
And I think the way that it mainly existed before is sort of like maybe
the only one of these we've talked about on the show is the Tower of Terror
ripoff that we encountered at Movie Park, Italy.
Again, I never remember the name of the land, but that that was this.
If you didn't hear the episode, that was this ripoff Universal Studios
that has a ripoff Tower of Terror that says Hollywood Tower at the top.
But that is not where you're in this this room that fits several dozen people.
You're in this like very claustrophobic little cage, basically, that rises up.
That that is the slow climb.
That's the thing that you would be afraid of. Yes. Yes.
So I think that was the main way that drop rides existed.
And in Disney's pursuit of trying to do a ride like this,
that's what maybe they were originally thinking that they had to do.
And if you've ever been on one of these rides or you heard us
talk about that that ripoff one, often how it goes is it's the slow
climb up to the top and then you jolt forward to the other track.
And then you go down in such a way that it curves you
until you're on your back at the bottom,
which is so weird and like low rent and carnivally like a.
Yeah, it's like it's like almost like you're on a water slide kind of thing.
Yeah, which that's weird.
Why do you accept it on a water slide?
Like, of course, I'll be sort of like naked and unattached to anything
and end up on my back, but doing it on a ride with a physical piece
feels so shady. Yeah. Yeah.
And that one of those is often themed to Superman, the escape.
It's so crazy how some of the most recognizable characters in the world
translated into any number of languages have the most like
rickety six flags, ask a death trap named after.
Well, that's I mean, that's obviously six flags.
I mean, that's part of the appeal is part of the thrills, you know.
It's a different kind of thrills than the storytelling,
like playing on the senses that Disney Imagineering does. Yes.
They made a deal with the devil, the Looney Tunes and the DC characters.
Like they are so rarely a good ride or attraction
based on any of this beloved IP.
I saw someone saying someone was calling us out, and I can't remember who it was
because we were talking about the fact there's no good Looney Tunes ride.
But apparently I forget which park it is.
There's a there is a dark ride, Looney Tunes in the park with the Alf
Gremlins that had the Alphen Gremlins. Oh, is that right?
And I wasn't he wasn't even on my radar, but it is kind of an old school,
like 90s animatronic ride.
That looks pretty cool. OK.
Cool, because it's like 30 years old.
Oh, yeah. Oh, so it's a little rinky did.
But like it's like feels like what we would have closer to
yeah, to what we're looking for when we were talking about that.
So we got it. We got to look into that more.
But well, that's the episodes we've talked about doing are like,
let's track Batman and the parks and maybe Looney Tunes should be added
to that list, too. Oh, yeah.
What have they actually pulled off?
And is this to buy one the any good?
Like, does that do justice?
Do we? Yeah. Not that we'll go to Dubai, probably.
We get free tickets, though.
I emailed the PR guy and we can get free tickets,
but I don't think they're going to fly us to Dubai, unfortunately.
But maybe now that we've been around for a while,
maybe now that we're a juggernaut of podcast podcasting.
Yeah. They got to put us up in first class where it will be safer
for us to fly. And right. Yeah. Oh, yeah.
And I also want to set up where we can have Jason recreate Tom Cruise's
stunt and Mission Impossible four.
Where he's which one's for which one?
Oh, climb in the building because Jason wants to do that.
You love heights. Yeah, that one looks OK.
You're the height. The new the new stunt.
I would be where you ride some motorcycle into the air and then parachute.
Spoiler alert for the listener who doesn't want to know.
It was it was on every like newswire.
It was on the Associated Press.
They filmed it. That's true.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
So you don't you won't do the new motorcycle stunt,
but you are willing to do the tallest building in the world running around it
on a wire. No, I said I would be interested.
Oh, you would. I'm more interested in the motorcycle.
You would you would rather ride a motorcycle off of an evil
Knievel ramp off the side of a mountain.
That yeah, because I I feel like the hardest part of that
would be learning how to ride a motorcycle.
Hmm. That seems like a lot of precision on a ramp.
I don't know. Did you guys know about this in Vegas at the formerly Strat
known as the Stratosphere?
You can go up to the top level and they'll put bunch of cords on you
and you can just jump off the building.
Yes. And you just slowly land.
Well, Lindsay and I watch about an hour's worth of videos of people doing it.
And I did too recently. Yeah.
And people just melt down.
They're standing at the top of this thing and they're like sobbing.
And the woman or the man who's working there, who's seen this a million times,
is just dead inside going, it's all right, it'll be OK.
And they'll be like, can you just push me?
Can you push me off?
And then they're like, they're like, we can't push you.
You have to jump.
Like you have to just know, but please just push me.
I just I'm so scared.
Like, it's going to be fine.
A lot of people have done this and they're just like they're not helping at all.
They're just like, go to go closer to the edge and jump.
And then finally, after like 20, some people like 15 minutes
finally just inch off the building and fall with a bungee cord.
It's like insane. I can't imagine.
I want to do it so badly. You want to do it?
Oh, yeah. Really?
Well, I want I've always wanted to.
OK, part of my love of terror terror as a kid, I was so excited
because it was so tall and I love being high up.
This is probably a short man complex.
But I was so excited for terror terror to go up that high.
And I think I've always wanted to safely safely jump off the top of a building.
Wow. I'm I'm kind of shocked because that seems so I would.
I would be the person melting down for 20 minutes, I think, at the top of the
of the hotel.
I am so I mean, it's like a hundred dollars or 150.
If you get a video, let's I was a little annoyed.
Let's take it out of the Patreon.
You're going to do that.
You know, you're going to jump off the top of a building.
Here's well, here's my one thing, though, is I think I would have to get contacts
because it would all just be a blur to me.
And I think I would want a crystal clear view of what I am seeing.
So I yeah, I am very impressed with this.
Like I just, you know, tentatively said that I would do Dr.
Doom's Fearful ride.
Now that the other thing isn't safe, but yeah, people melt down
on what you're talking about.
Yeah, like a big part of it is that you have to do the jumping.
Yeah.
Like that's my problem with skydiving, too.
And I know, like the first time you go, you're strapped to another person
that knows what they're doing.
Like I would have to be forced to do Dr.
Doom's Fearful.
I couldn't climb up a tower and then jump off of the tower.
A machine has to do the work for me.
So that's why the idea of actually stepping off of a building drives me insane.
So I am legitimately impressed with you saying you want to do this.
And we have to make this happen.
I think the one thing that worries me is just like, I don't know,
it feels like there's a lot of backup cables.
I watch them explain like all the fail saves.
But I think part of the appeal is that you just slow down
as you get close to the ground.
There's no snapback.
Like bungee jumping scares.
The snapback would scare me.
That does sound better.
You just, yeah, you just slowly land.
Yeah. Wow.
Man, this is going to be a great episode.
Yeah. Well, I don't think I was.
I wasn't planning on getting contacts anytime soon, so I'm also not planning on going.
You have a really boring logistic to do and then and the virus has to go away.
Yeah, the virus.
I mean, Vegas is a third open, but not not a ton of stuff to do.
So hashtags stratosphere in
it's getting wild in the event of 2024.
This is Tom Cruise of podcast the ride
and I'll go on the New York, New York roller coaster.
That's my pledge.
Well, I don't know if I feel comfortable with you going on.
OK, fine.
I've done it. I cannot recommend.
Yeah, I I will.
Gamble in the pleasure pit at the Planet Hollywood Casino
where the women wear like slightly more revealing clothes.
That's the danger I will face.
Oh, a lower cleavage. That's correct.
Yes, that's the danger.
I will put myself in in Vegas while Jason jumps off a building.
So I was starting to say just in terms of the history of the thing.
Yeah, the Disney, I think, was I forget where I got all this info,
but they were thinking about doing one of those where you end up on your back
to something a little more low renty.
And something has come up on the show before that sort of, you know,
pops in and out of the history of the Tower of Terror.
And that is this thing, Geyser Mountain.
I know, Mike, you love this.
Love this idea. Yes.
This was a Baxter thing.
Yeah, maybe it was. Yeah. At some point.
The main just being that it is like a I guess a launch and then a drop
ride where you are launching because a geyser is going off
and propelling your vehicle into the air.
There's a yeah, there's an episode of the season pass.
I believe it's a paywalled episode of the season pass podcast.
That's all Tony Baxter unmade rides.
Wow. Wow. This is in there.
And in addition, it would have gone back by where Star Wars Land is,
which also was a place that Ozland would have gone if the James Franco movie was a hit.
You know, walk around Franco.
Now it does. Which that'd be fine today, right?
Oh, yeah. Just replace him, replace him with the old guy from the original,
although they don't have the right.
They don't have the rights to that, though, but whatever.
Oh, yeah. I don't know what they do.
But just put another Johnny Depp.
Yeah, yeah. Johnny Depp is the mole.
Perfect. No problems. Johnny Depp as Oz.
Yeah. Yeah. So
but apparently the there was some proto iteration of Geyser Mountain.
That would have been the same idea, except it's one of those like, yeah,
you end up on your back a little more.
So they were like pursuing that is that a way we want to do a
drop ride and that that didn't end up working out.
But that was the first that Disney's may be thinking about doing it.
And it's enough in the air that it is one of the things originally proposed
in 1990 when they were doing starting to plan
the first big expansion of Disney MGM Studios,
because it was specifically a half day park at some point in time.
If you went it open, if you can picture it without that Sunset Boulevard area
and without Rock and Roller Coaster, there's very little going on.
And the expansion started and Muppet Vision was one of those things.
But they were talking about other stuff to do.
And I got some of this info, by the way, from Kevin Rafferty's book,
which I ended up buying and I highly recommend.
I think we've been overlooking Kevin Rafferty as a Baxter level person
right for a long time.
There's shows stuff in this book.
He shows up in a lot of like cool stuff.
I think he had his hands on a ton and more than you know,
because even five and really gotten to read the book yet.
I mainly read about Tower.
But like he wrote the lyrics of the Sunny Eclipse song.
Weird stuff like, you know, we don't really like this thing,
but the enchanted Tiki room, new management was this guy.
But then also, like he wrote all the songs for like, you know, the Maeder jamboree.
That's great. Like so many odds and ends and Radiator Springs Racers.
And one of my favorite things, Panglectic Pizza Port with Tony Solaroni,
which you get a big breakdown of in his book.
And apparently he also wrote some of, at least at one point in time,
Michael Eisner's intros for the show.
Wow. That's how much an all hands on deck writer this guy was.
He wrote the Sunny Eclipse songs and the hellos.
How that's kind of like how Marty Sklar would be writing like a lot of Disney's
like internal stuff for introductions on the show and that sort of thing that
that sort of connects to that.
Oh, that's right.
God, writing the copy on the TV shows and the attractions themselves.
That's cool. That's that's still the case.
But anyway, he and his book talks about the formation of this, right?
And how they're pitching a ton of stuff.
What can we do in this expansion area?
And somebody pitched a hotel drop ride.
And I think the idea was that there you find some there's some backstory
where there's a murder in a pool in the basement.
And then that starts making the elevator you're in act weird.
And that makes it go up and drop.
And and maybe Vincent Price was was pitched to be part of it.
The pitch it.
Yeah, the people pitched to be part of it are insane.
This cast of characters.
Oh, well, there's a there's a big one.
Or we'll get to that in a sec.
But the so it's some I don't know, Vincent Price, some weird story.
There's a murder in the put like the pitch was weird and everyone in the room,
Eisner included is like, but why does the so why is the elevator
react to a murder? It just wasn't really tied up.
He thought Vincent Price maybe wasn't relevant enough.
So it just kind of died on the vine.
Kevin Rafferty was not doing that pitch.
He was just in the room and he heard it and like something there, though,
like the idea of a haunted tower.
There's like that's pretty great.
And it stuck with him for a while.
And he even just brought it up one day to to another imagineer.
Maybe Kirk is his last name.
I forget exactly.
But they were talking about it and went like, well,
is there some way to revamp that idea and make it work in the studios better?
And they were talking about, well, is it about adding a property to it?
Like, is there some way to tie it into a TV show like the outer limits
they proposed, which we just talked about the outer limits right.
And at King's Dominion.
And then they got to Twilight Zone.
And, oh, that's kind of something.
Oh, what if you're kind of like in an episode of The Twilight Zone?
And then they were trading names back and forth.
Wasn't there a real thing called the Hollywood Tower off the 101?
Maybe it could be like that.
Oh, what if it's the Twilight Zone Tower Hotel?
And then Rafferty spits out, what if it's the Twilight Zone Tower of Terror
that just flew out of his mouth, improvised, and they both went, yeah.
And they got a new meeting on the books with Eisner.
Here's the pitch Twilight Zone Tower of Terror.
He's like, I love the name, but what is it?
They explain it more.
He says how this will be a elevator ride where it doesn't act like an elevator,
where it does things that an elevator wouldn't do.
He's like, that sounds cool.
Does is Twilight Zone relevant, though?
Frank Wells says absolutely.
They show the marathons all the time.
It's as relevant as ever.
Like, that's an institution.
It will always be. And Eisner said, it sounds good to me.
It'll just take money.
It'll take a ton of money.
And and suddenly this guy who's like done these weird robot shows in Japan
is in charge of a ticket attraction that he doesn't actually know how to pull off.
And a big important thing about the Twilight Zone,
the rights were available.
Oh, yes, was very happy to license it to them, you know,
and it fit perfectly within their movie and television studio production park.
Right, right. Absolutely.
But there was also I guess I skipped a step of that by saying all that,
because also in the air was this other hotel idea,
which I think is what you were alluding to, Jason, the hotel mill.
Yeah, the hotel mill.
Well, I the other name I heard, too, was Stephen King.
Yes, I also I found Stephen King was approached.
I found that, too, yeah.
Notable for taking meetings with both Disney and eventually Universal,
who at one point was pitching like a scary attraction based off some of his books
that would have included a fake loading where Pennywise,
the clown would have exploded out of the control room
and the ride would have continued.
Now, this didn't happen.
Of course, nothing goes away forever.
And that idea was worked into Revenge of the Mummy.
Oh, no kidding.
That's nuts.
A Stephen King coaster like all of Stephen King's IP
in one ride is what it seems like. Right, Jason?
Yeah, which kind of became the the idea for the TV show Castle Rock.
It like ties together a bunch of the characters in the town and everything.
Yeah. So it was either going to be Mel Brooks or Stephen King.
What I read about Mel Brooks is that they were trying to get him to shoot
movies at the MGM Studios,
Disney MGM Studios Park because they had a full production facilities
and they knew him and his son, Max, were fans of the park.
And on the Disney fandom for Tower of Terror,
it said Mel initially had to be sold on the idea of a theme park attraction.
After being explained that a theme park attraction has a lasting
effect of being in place and seen every day of the week
by 20,000 people for like 10 to 20 years.
And that, I think, is a big like keystone,
a big benchmark for like why these places resonate so much,
because they are so many people experience them.
It is a shared experience of like, oh, you can skip a movie.
You cannot see a movie.
But like so many people have ridden these things, you know?
Right, right.
So they end up with this idea that I what I figured out is that
I don't think the Hotel Mel was was a drop ride.
I think it was that you're going to be on a set
and you're taking around in a golf cart like that Hollywood Inside Baseball
that you're on a back lot going on a crazy golf cart ride.
But through the set of sort of a young Frankenstein ish Mel Brooks
comedy or and it was just yeah, it was it was gags.
Yeah, the village maybe would have been built.
The young Frankenstein Castle might have been there and like a village
and that you could walk down.
But who knows how far any of this stuff got, you know? Yeah.
Did he maybe take any of the ideas that were being formulated
and infuse them into Dracula dead and loving it?
I have not seen Dracula dead and loving it, even though I referenced it
not long ago.
So I won't.
We should probably I I feel like I might like you when the turn happened
and the Leslie Nielsen movies got kind of like less good every time.
I was disappointed then.
I bet now I would like watch the lesser Leslie's and go,
this is better than any.
Oh, yeah. Comedy film.
Yeah. Decade. Yeah.
I was watching some old Jackie Chan movies and I was like, this is so good.
These are so good.
These stunts are insane.
Yeah, like, yeah, it's just like a lot.
You're watching like a live stunt show. It's crazy. Yeah. Right.
We like old we like old things, I guess.
This is it.
No, I know I do kind of want to watch the lesser Leslie marathon
maybe coming for me. Oh, sure.
But I just think it's interesting that they were like piecing this together
so slowly. What about a drop right?
What about its Disney of James and there's a hotel?
Well, not quite.
Then we're and then it finally all crystallized in this in Tower of Terror.
And they started planning it and budgeting it and seeing if this was going to be
the thing. But it was as an expansion idea for Disney and James Studios.
It was up against a different Kevin Rafferty idea.
He was working on two things that were in contention to be the big centerpiece
of the expansion. And the other one.
And I don't want to spend too much time on this
because this for sure is its own episode, at least a second gate.
The other one that he was pushing along was the Creatures Choice Awards.
If you guys I don't know anything about the Creatures Choice.
I don't know that. Excuse me.
Oh, my God. This is why you have to get this this book,
Magic Journey, because there's photos of it.
I discovered some of this from some YouTube video that
that I didn't know where they were getting it from.
I'm watching the video going, excuse me.
And now I know it's from Kevin Rafferty's book, because this is without saying
too much because I'll have to save it for this episode.
I'm even I'm even like, do we just move this up and do it soon?
Maybe. But we'll figure it out.
But just to whet the appetite, the Creatures Choice Awards
involves a the host of the Creatures Choice Awards
is a character named Eddie Franken Murphy.
Wow. Yeah.
And there is art in this book of Eddie Franken Murphy.
Wow. Eddie himself heard the pitch like Eddie Murphy was aware
of the possibility of being Eddie Franken Murphy.
Whoa. I've never seen anything about this.
It's in some it's buried in some other YouTube video.
I don't remember the channel to go to British accent or something.
But I was watching it months ago, just jaw dropped.
Like, what are you telling me right now?
A monster award show with it's so it's so good,
mixed with the fact that Rafferty is working on Tower of Terror,
the great like, you know, now in every park attraction that is beloved.
Then this bizarre idea and Dick Tracy Crime Stoppers at the same time.
Like this and in the book, they detail conversations he had with Eisner
about like, wait, so it's a gun.
Yeah, it's a gun in the car, but it's like a fun go.
I don't know about a gun.
Like it's so that we've been, I think, underwriting Kevin Rafferty.
There's a lot in the Kevin Rafferty.
I think Crime Stoppers may be coming up too, we should say.
Oh, that's a good idea.
Yeah, I would love to.
Well, off Mike, about how soon you'll hear about Eddie Franken.
Wow. It's so crazy.
Yeah, we got to do that.
I heard that.
I'm seeing now that part of part of the reason is they couldn't get the rights
to Eddie Franken Murphy's famous characters.
Gumboo and Boogweed.
It's just too expensive to get those hilarious characters.
Oh, B.O.O. Yes. Yeah.
Boo. That's pretty good.
Sorry. I guess it's gumboo and booqueat.
Tis the season, you know.
I know. Yeah.
And he definitely referenced his work in Booverly Hills Cop.
And Boo Meringue.
And Boo Boofinger.
Oh, boofinger.
Wait, I might have been thinking of Boofinger.
Is he in Boomerang?
Don't doubt yourself. Yeah.
Wow. Do they all work?
Maybe. I guess.
My name is Boolemite.
Yeah, that's not quite as good.
Yeah. Shrek is just Shrek.
Yeah.
Anyway, we'll figure that one out.
This is just like this is where if I could just go
to Imagineering on a random day in 1990 and see concept art of all of this,
that these things are all being and that's just like a third of what they're
working on. I think that's why I can't abide by any by too much Eisner hate,
because sure, he messed up later, but he also enabled a world where like, OK,
what's my 315? The Creatures Choice Awards.
All right. Well, hurry it up because I got a I got a four o'clock
about Tower of Terror, about how to make an elevator move free standing down
a hallway. What a great time. Eisner did it.
He certainly did. Can I just ask one question?
What was the Creatures Choice?
What kind of a writer is that? Too big of a spoiler.
What kind of a thing was it? Like, what was it?
It is. And again, I'm glad I didn't learn more because this so I can't really spoil.
But he he claims in the book that it would have been an audio animatronic
theater show with the like scope
and amount of robots of the American adventure.
Wow. Oh, my gosh. Holy shit.
Yeah. My appetite is more wedded now. Good. I'm glad I asked.
Yeah. OK. Yeah. Unbelievable.
So to to come, we'll put it.
We'll put the pin in that. But there was he literally what a crazy time for this
guy. He has two projects in contention that one they realized logistically
maybe they couldn't do. And what Eisner was pushing and why this thing
really happened and why he was sold on it ultimately is what Jason said earlier.
We want teams. We want thrills for a park that at the time didn't have a ton of rides.
And I don't think a thrill ride initially.
This this one was it.
And it was incredibly expensive to do.
But Eisner kept pushing, I think, the benefit of a huge thrill ride.
I think it'll have a transformative effect on the entire property.
And it did. Well, I and I think a big impetus was that for a very short
amount of time, Disney eventually took the leap.
But in terms of Universal Studios, Florida versus MGM Studios,
Universal was had more guests for a while after they got their shit together.
After the first like year or so, it was beating MGM attendance wise.
So they're like, we've got to put some stuff in there.
And that's as you see, you know, Star Tours and Muppet.
And Tower of Terror down the line a little kind of helped it find its foot.
That it was always my family's favorite part to go to, like so.
We love the movies and we love TV so much.
And and it just everyone liked it.
And I feel like a lot of stuff that everyone in the family could do.
Yeah, yeah, definitely something for everybody.
And the fact that there is thrill rides and then like, here's this walking tour
that doesn't challenge anybody. Oh, yeah.
Mermaid show like it like it became such a big variety, especially after this open.
Yeah, yeah, I remember.
Yeah, we I don't know that we would have declared it our favorite,
but we were very into it, I mean, especially Twilight.
So which my mother is a huge fan of.
Like I think that it was it was checking so many boxes for us.
And then it's the other one.
Tower of Terror was put in.
It was like, yeah, next level, like finally had something.
I mean, great movie ride is very cool.
I guess I wouldn't call it like next level going on it, though, maybe.
Sure, maybe at the time, by the sheer amount of it, it's still not next level,
I guess, because there's already been a ton of animatronics.
So it's like it's really good and it's really fun.
But it's like Tower of Terror that felt like a next level thing.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Great movie, I think, got a boost from the length to not just the many sets
of animatronics, but like besides
Universe of Energy, there weren't that many long rides at the time.
Yeah.
Well, so to that next level point, part of it is one of the things that was
in Rafferty's pitch, which is that this elevator car is not just going to go up
and down, it is going to move forward.
And obviously so much of our audience is hardcore theme park fans.
But I think there probably are people
listening who only been to the California adventure version and actually don't
know that in Florida, the car moves, you get up to a floor and it lurches down
a hallway, which is some of the, you know, why we've been more OK with it changing
and not being Twilight Zone in California, because it feels like, well,
it never in California has been the ultimate version that was, you know,
had this effect that was even in the pitch.
Yeah, it's so it's like so much better.
We've said it a million times.
I'm sure it's annoying at this point of like how much more it adds to the ride
in Florida, and I wasn't even quite clear until I was doing some research about how
it worked.
Yeah.
Well, you want to talk about that?
Yes, real quick, though, I want to see if anyone came across this,
since you mentioned that push forward,
I found on one of the like fan Wikipedia,
Wikipedia, pages or fans sort of things, as it was describing the differences
between the East Coast, West Coast,
our terms, it was saying like, oh, and they took out the fifth dimension
sequence where you push forward in the Florida version, which the Imagineers
were never happy with, and I had never heard that before.
I don't believe it.
I I usually check stuff against multiple sources, but this just made me so angry.
I was like, what are you talking about?
They didn't like that's the whole that's the whole kit and caboodle.
That's the whole deal.
Like maybe what they were generalizing, it's not that they didn't like maybe
the more nuanced opinion might be, well, it's always problematic in terms of function.
That's the most likely part to break down or something, because it is interesting
they never reprised it, even the Tokyo one, which is really fantastic,
doesn't have that effect.
I mean, I've heard Tony shit talk, the California Tower of Terror, Tony Baxter,
because it doesn't have that secret.
He said, like, that's the big important
sequence in the ride, because it like that's when you finally like it breaks
your expectations of what an elevator does.
So that's why, like he says, that's so
important to the right, which makes sense, because that's really the moment when you
go, oh, I didn't know this could do this.
Which it's so funny that this got pitched
and sold to Eisner and Wells with no plan of how they were actually going to do that.
It's like, what a crazy that that tells
how much they were just in the money at the time.
Like, I don't know, figure it out.
And then Rafferty had to leave that meeting with Sklar.
And he was, I think, kind of freaking out.
Like, does that mean did he just say, like, do it?
Yeah, yeah.
You're in charge of an e-ticket now and you've got to go learn some stuff.
So I don't think they did have a plan.
And I guess so let's talk about what they they came up with.
Yeah.
What's the easy way to explain the technology?
Yeah, I don't know.
I'm going to sound like the biggest idiot in the world trying to do it.
I think it's basically there's a ride vehicle inside another mechanism that
makes you go up and down.
There's the shaft, but there's another you're
actually in a vehicle that crawls into the shaft.
And there's technically three parts.
There's the going up one.
There's the one that pushes forward and
there's the one that quickly goes up and down.
Those are three different mechanisms, three different.
So it's like a category.
OK, so there's like a big like, let's say that.
OK, like how can I say this the dumbest way?
It's a big cube.
There's a big cube with some ropes on it, cords, cables, another little box where
the people's chairs are go into that big cube.
That cube just lifts everybody up to the top.
Then the people leave their little vehicle out of that big cube.
They push forward.
They see all the fun stuff in the fifth dimension room and then they get loaded
into another big cube that's held by different ropes and cables.
Yeah.
And then it's mainly cubes.
That's what you do.
Cubes is what I'm talking about.
We love cubes on this podcast.
And then I think my impression was that it kind of freefall dropped you.
But that's not what it does.
There's like a mechanism that's basically
just shooting you up and down.
It's like pushing you up and down.
It's not just free.
It's not just sort of free falling you.
It's completely controlling your speed.
And you're going faster than you would if you'd free fall.
If they were just to drop like any like if they were just to drop the cable,
you would be going slower and feel like less intense motion than you would the way
they do it now. You are being pulled down.
That's a better way to describe it.
And the fact I saw is if you hold a penny in your hand as you fall,
you will beat the penny will hover in the air a little because it's falling at
the speed of gravity and you are falling faster than that because you are strapped
into a vehicle being pulled down.
I would recommend not doing that on the ride, though.
I would recommend because you might miss out on some of the hilarious bits that
people do as they're falling, some of the very good jokes that people like to
scream. I would say what do you do?
What have you had? What jokes are you talking about?
I they're just so funny.
I can't remember. I'm just laughing too much.
I'm not sure, actually, though,
because I kind of mention we've talked about it and like, yeah,
I know people like to yell stuff in the room and scream and we're not fans of that.
You can call us old men.
I don't care.
I like to sit and enjoy the atmosphere.
But Tower of Terror, I've never like I've never been like, oh, well,
there's that bit again.
I don't I think people just when you are at the top, when you're holding at the top
for a second, someone will go like, I could see my car like I feel like I've heard.
I have definitely heard I've never heard somebody do a joke like that at the top.
I do like to hear genuine people like, oh, my God, oh, my God, like, Tom,
you didn't tell me it was this like, you know, genuine anguish is very funny.
I'm not I'm not trying to troll or anything.
I just truly never like nothing sticks out to me when I'm at the top of any
of these drop rides where I get annoyed.
Scott, I guess you haven't been on many, but
yes, not enough for there to be a recurring trope.
Yeah, I can see my car.
Would that bother me if I heard it?
I don't know. It was my dad.
Maybe I would give him some credit.
It all depends on the delivery, quite frankly, you know.
Yeah, yeah.
So interesting.
Also, just like the parking lot is not in that view.
If you're being accurate, you cannot see anybody's car.
Yeah. So I have a problem with it on a level.
Well, I'm going to pay attention to this.
Do you find that you have that happen on Guardians a lot or no?
Guardians, like it's hard to tell.
Just it's so much noise.
There's so much the music is so loud.
Sometimes you can't even hear a rocket like.
I like his little jokes, you know, they're pretty polished.
Leave it to the professionals like a rocket.
Yeah, that's that's our stance.
That that yanking faster than gravity situation.
That's another thing I found in the
Rafferty book that they went and talked to the Otis Elevator Company, who did end
up putting in the elevator mechanism for this attraction.
And they went to a recently opened 50 story
elevator shaft that they had they had built for some high rise.
And they kind of just like talked about logistics.
And then they got went up to the top
and said, take this thing down the fastest it can go.
And there was reticence about that.
You sure? OK, well, let's give it a shot.
And then they did. And they didn't feel anything.
They didn't even have like any heart drop.
And they were like, that's really the fastest.
So, yeah, pretty much is.
And that's when they realized we can't just rely on what elevators already do.
We have to pioneer new elevator technology
if we actually want to be able to be weightless or really feel something.
Right.
But that is a funny thing that a real elevator company built this to do,
as is said in the Imagineering story, the opposite of what elevators are supposed
to do. Yes.
I think in the Imagineering story, they're talking about like the people at the
elevator company were like freaked out a little bit.
Yeah. Like we have to do the wrong thing.
We make this go the right way.
We make it make it do the right thing.
And now we have to make it do the wrong thing.
Yeah. Yeah.
Very strange.
The other thing that the moving through, I mean, I guess in a way the spoiler,
the end of Rise of the Resistance is sort of like a mini version of this and that
you're in a vehicle that moves into another little cage that drops.
It's sort of similar.
But this sort of is, is it the first trackless ride vehicle, that little
sequence, because it's you're moving along a wire that is guiding you.
Right.
That's a good question.
One end of that fifth floor to the other, the fifth dimension.
Maybe. I'm not sure.
That's a good question.
I don't think I ever realized those
autonomous guided vehicles, like they have batteries.
The batteries have to recharge in between like goes like as you are getting off or
getting loaded, like they are charging the batteries.
Yeah, it's the I don't I mean, I don't
understand a lot of mechanics and technology, but I truly can't wrap your
head around all the moving parts of something like this.
Yeah, which so I mean, that like I don't
have anything, you know, intelligent to say here about my experience finally
going on this other than a holy shit, like like waiting so long and then not doing
it till last year, I don't think I've ever seen a video of how the fifth dimension
where I think I'd saved it to try to be brave and do in person.
Yeah, it's jaw drop.
And I feel like we were we got lucky.
We were in a group last year that where I
felt like a lot of them hadn't done it either.
It was like getting applause and gasps the way that, you know, various rooms and
rise the resistance do and certainly for me and that boy that like split of that
neon light when you enter into that final, that is so haunting.
That is like such a stirring moment that I feel like ended up in my actual dreams.
That is so affecting and crazy.
Yeah, it's yeah.
That moment, I'm trying to think if that's that.
Yeah, like that's the most stark problem.
I mean, probably like it's such a I don't know why it's just like a simple.
That's such a simple effect.
And for whatever reason sticks out so strongly.
Yeah, there's almost yeah, there's like nothing happening.
Right. A door opens with a neon light that just sort of slowly appears.
And yet it's so much like more minimalist
and scary than a lot of what's in any other Disney attractions.
Yeah.
Yeah, I mean, I I did you guys watch any
Twilight Zone episodes to get ready for this?
No, not really.
OK, I I was
I watched the Nick of Time, which is one of the Shatner ones.
Be because that's one of the Easter eggs.
The four little devil fortune telling device is in the queue.
And I was like, I don't think I've ever seen this one before.
And as I'm watching it, I'm slowly dawning on me like, oh, this one is bad.
This one is not good.
It's just like I think William Shatter's character just is obsessive compulsive.
Like there it is in the way that at 20 the terror of twenty thousand feet,
he is right at the end.
This one is just like, oh, this guy is just a worry wart.
This I don't know the lesson.
And I think they just put this in the queue because the prop is distinctive.
But it's a good life.
I watched the first few minutes of and that is unsettling immediately,
which the kid with the powers.
Yeah, that's that's the one with that.
The Rod Serling intro in the ride is pulled.
Right. Yes.
Which is another thing that never dawned on me.
And it so much of it is in that episode, in his introduction.
Yeah, he says that like they cut it in the episode.
He's in front of a map of the United States, not in front of an elevator bank.
And the line I have tonight's story on the Twilight Zone is somewhat unique
and calls for a different kind of introduction.
This, as you may recognize, is then in the ride, they cut that off and they show you
ride stuff and I don't think you ever see Serling again.
But in the in the episode, it's a good life.
Then he actually kind of convoluted.
You're like, why are you showing America?
And then they end up with a boy who has
mind powers and can control people's thoughts as parodied on the Simpsons.
It is one of the ones of the Simpsons parodied.
Yes.
And you know what's another weird thing about It's a Good Life?
It was it's one of the four that is in Twilight Zone, the movie.
And it's directed by Joe Dante,
director of Gremlins, who directed the pre show video for Tower of Terror.
Yes, that's the deal.
And crazy.
Yes.
A lot of theme park movie credits to his name.
I feel like he's done other ride stuff.
Yeah.
Well, he did that haunted lighthouse for D that I am like very much want to know
more about the Christopher Lloyd thing that will play at Busch Gardens and Sea
World. I feel like there was another ride thing he directed that's I'm blanking on
right now, but like was was it God?
Yeah. Did the Tower of Terror, probably the most notable one.
That's a huge one.
Another reference to It's a Good Life in the hotel lobby.
There is a poster promoting the Anthony
Fremont Orchestra, which is a pretty good joke because that is the little boy with
the powers and in the episode he hates music.
Oh, that's funny.
Yeah.
Oh, that's a good little dry thing.
He would have, you know, he would have really hated that
that little intro to his episode was sampled.
In fact, the same one that's used in the ride,
the somewhat unique and calls for a different kind of introduction is sampled
on a song called Threatened, which is a song by Michael Jackson,
the final song on his final album, Invincible.
It starts with a little Rod Serling sample.
Another fun fact about the song Threatened, it sucks.
Awful.
That entire, you know, you can and there's things that are like,
you know, with everything going on, you're like, oh, but I want to retain.
I still want to listen to Billie Jean or whatever.
No one is fighting for invincible garbage front to back.
He rejected Rock Your Body, Timberlake's Rock Your Body.
He said no, so that he could do 16 tracks of just like,
oh, cha, ga, give it a try.
Put it on Spotify and see if you disagree with me.
I have a feeling I'm not going to disagree with this.
Yeah, I'm not going to fight you on that one.
That was a challenge to anyone.
Anyway, if you like the song Threatened
and you feel threatened by my dislike of Threatened, then I don't know the end
of this sentence. I don't know what I don't know.
Do we know?
Do we know Michael Jackson Road Tower of Terror?
Hmm.
Did he do a Disney World trip when it was out?
We know that he went to Fontasia land to go on the Michael Jackson, his own ride.
Yes.
Yeah, feels like he must.
Yeah. Did he get the idea?
Did he say, like, I want this to?
Yeah, that's my question.
To start like the Tower of Terror.
Right.
I don't see.
I just searched his name in the ride and nothing popped up picture wise.
So who knows?
We'll have to dig deep.
We can't.
Though there are many photos of people on this attraction.
Do you guys have good photos of you on this?
Do you have childhood photos of you up at the top?
That's a good question.
I don't think we have any childhood photos of us doing this.
I have from recent trips.
I have some of the cool videos they've been doing recently.
Yes.
This was the first ride at Walt Disney World that had on ride videos offered to purchase.
They put you in a fully in an edited video
of like with shots of like the whole tower and then the thing crashing.
But then inside they cut to like
an actual video of the whole cabin thing going up and down.
And it's like kind of in slow motion.
It's pretty cool.
Well, do we do?
We don't have the video of us.
We don't have any of us because I did not have a premiere pass at the time,
which allowed me to have full photo pass privileges.
That came with because you at one point
had the pass that works for both marks because you went to both with it.
When I like the West Coast and East Coast.
Right.
When we were planning our first Florida trip, I crunched some numbers and I figured
out that if I upgraded the annual pass to a premiere pass, I don't think it makes
sense anymore money wise.
But at the time it was actually the kind of reasonable.
And I was like, actually, if you just put the money, we're going to spend on the
tickets into the premiere pass, we can get the premiere pass and get more perks.
And that was part of it.
Geez, like your video.
My family did that in when we were in the vacation club.
We went like back like two years in a row.
And I think we went in August and we knew we'd back the next year, maybe more likely
June or July. And it was just like, oh, it's let's just get annual passes.
Like this is cheaper than buying like,
you know, multiple sets of five day passes or seven day passes or whatever.
And you just feel like a king.
You feel like you can go part of it.
You know, having an annual pass to Florida, you're like, well,
maybe we'll go next weekend.
I mean, you don't, but you do feel like you have some freedom.
There's a freedom in knowing you could do that.
Well, also in the 90s, they had a lot more aggressive ticketing offers
which came back after 9 11 and are somewhat back right now.
Although we are not advising you to necessarily rush out and do it.
But I believe Universal currently has a buy two days, get three days for free,
which is not usually how economics works.
They're doing like six flats, like Six Flag offer where it's like,
walk by the entrance and get a year free,
wave at a Valencia teen and get a free year of admission.
Yeah.
Yeah. Within five miles of the park and it'll just automatically be on your driver's license.
You just like scan it and then you get into Six Flags.
That's right. Yeah.
Yeah. So
that might be coming back across the board after the pandemic is over.
At all. Yeah. The theme parks.
We've talked about the
the Rod Serling intro and we're maybe jumping all around a little bit.
But, you know, that's really fantastic.
I also just want to give it the credit.
I feel like I they're from the same year and I associate that video piece with
Forrest Gump in that the idea of pulling somebody from old footage was the most
difficult thing in the world to do.
It was like such a magic trick at the time.
And I think we take it for granted now.
And of course, if you do visual effects or anything,
you know, like rotoscoping is really difficult.
They had to cut him out frame by frame, which he's standing still.
So that helps you.
But if you watch the that's what would surprise me when I watched the real
footage that they pulled it from, that he was like in front of a totally different
background and they married it seemed it's not like he was like in front of a
green screen where they could just put something different behind him.
Right. Really like work that.
Yeah.
And the impression is very good, too.
That's very. Yes.
That guy, which I have his name written down here somewhere, he does the he does
a Rod Serling voice on the new Twilight Zone.
Oh, yeah.
When he like because he in the one that just came out.
Yes.
Oh, right.
Yes, because there's like this weird appearance.
And that's him.
He's back.
I shouldn't spoiler it.
His name. God, I have his name somewhere here.
It's bad. I think it's been something.
He has a name.
He has a person's name.
I'm sorry if you're listening.
You can look it up.
Joe Dante, the man who the name of the man who directed the intro, the rest of the
intro is great, too, that whole.
So this whole story of, oh, this is here.
This is something I wanted to talk about.
Jason, you brought up like what is the lesson?
You had a problem with like what's the
Twilight Zone lesson of that with that one Shatner one.
So with this five people get in an elevator, there's a movie star and her kind
of also Hollywood bow.
I don't know what he does exactly.
There's a move like a little kid actress,
actually Temple and her caretaker or nanny or something and a bellhop.
And these five get into an elevator Halloween night, 1939.
And he is struck by lightning and they end up in the fifth dimension.
What's the lesson?
What's the what's the Twilight Zone?
But remember, well, don't do well.
Now, the lesson for us is next time you check into a deserted hotel on the dark
side of Hollywood, make sure you know what kind of vacancy you're filling.
But I don't know what lesson those people are supposed to get.
Yeah, it seems like it's not their fault in any way.
No, I don't think that was.
Yeah, they were not at fault.
I some I've been some Twilight Zone's supposedly don't really have a strong like
lesson.
Yeah, this one is I didn't do, but.
Sometimes the adventure cookie supernatural, scary adventure, which I guess is what this
is, but Rod Serling certainly presents it as if we're supposed to learn something
by the end of this, it's got that judgy.
Yes, exactly. He's judging five people
dared to like a woman like normal.
She wore a fancy fur coat and is like
you're trying you like, I don't know, is that why?
Is she an animal killer?
Is it about fame?
Is it like they came to Hollywood with big dreams and they sold out like they
they only did commercials and they didn't do authentic film and make points about
the medium forward, right?
They just they were very basic.
Their ideas about film and culture were basic.
Did the bellhop steal from the customers of the hotel?
Did he like take luggage?
Did he pull schemes that way?
Maybe it was he being punished?
Perhaps. Yeah, it's unclear.
I think it's kind of a choose your own adventure.
Who's who you think is at fault and what they need to learn and what we
why are we caught up in it?
Why do we have to be punished?
Yeah, I know for their non crimes.
Yeah, these people got in an elevator and then it fell and now you're going to fall.
I think is it about not doing your research?
Maybe that's to tie together Jason's point.
Is it like you got to do your travel?
Ossity, you have to like read the reviews.
So this is on you for not reading the reviews of the Hollywood Terror Hotel
that say don't stay here.
It hasn't been open since 1939.
And maybe it's actually a larger point
because I'm sure Disney gets a lot of people complaining about lines and when
do they go and they don't know what the ticket situation is and what is a fast
and where do you get it?
And I'm sure Disney is so annoyed because it's just like, look it up, do your
research, and they made the Tower of Terror to say, we're going to pull.
This is what should happen to you who don't research.
You should go and complain.
You'll become ghosts.
We could do that to you if we wanted.
So learn your lesson.
When did the Hayes regular elevators?
You could have real elevator mishaps in the Swan or the Dolphin.
But instead, we're going to teach you this right.
When did the Hayes code take effect?
Could these be decadent pre Hayes code Hollywood denizens?
You know, the the the code that the government like manned the studios agreed
to a bye bye to not have like a woman sitting on a bed with her foot off the
ground to people smiling at each other like all this.
I'm still against a woman sitting on a bed in a movie.
Mike, you are a big proponent to bring back the Hayes code, bring up the Hayes code.
Yeah.
Separate beds.
Why are you and I love Lucy fan?
Yes. Yes.
That is that is the main reason.
Yeah.
Maybe were they this would have been too early or they aren't communists.
That's what I was just about to say.
Is it is a chance that five of them were
communists and they were being punished for it?
I wonder, is there is there a secret lesson
that the Imagineers know but we don't know and he's never said.
Hmm.
Where the end it was maybe even like shot in some regard.
And then they decided like, well, you know, you're not going to be in that room for too long.
So let's just kind of have it be a random horror event.
Right. And we don't want to offend somebody who might actually fall into whatever
these five people are doing.
Yeah.
They don't and they don't want to like if if the backstory is that it's the problem
was with the movie star and the guy that like they are going up to a room to have
sex before marriage and that is why everyone is punished.
Right.
And they decided, well, do we really want to like lay that guilt trip on anyone
living in sin who might be going on this ride?
We don't want anyone living in sin to go on the ride, but it might happen.
Right. And they knew that the subtext would be there and you could you could kind
of understand it maybe just without without having it as a conscious thought in your
own head. So and there are consequences for the other hotel guests, the people who
had to abandon their Mahjong game in the lobby, the guy who in the opening special,
they're like, look, someone got here from a colder climate, but they're overcoat down,
got their hotel key, got their newspaper and it's just left here.
So I'm assuming everyone evacuated when it was struck by lightning.
And that's why they left all their stuff.
I saw a lot about this Mahjong game.
And of course, my first question, Jason, is, were you a Mahjong kid?
No, I that is I don't know how to play Mahjong.
I don't know how to play backgammon or bridge.
And that's my heart.
My heart broke each time you said each of those.
I know, because I know I was like, come on,
bridge, and then it was not you didn't play bridge.
As someone who likes old timey bullshit,
like it is shocking that I have not learned those things.
We should learn how to play during quarantine.
That's a perfect time to learn.
Can we play like online bridge?
You need four.
We'll have to. Can we teach the sector keeper to play bridge?
Yeah, I feel like I that is a fact.
I know, but I could be wrong.
Maybe you need minimum four, but you can play more with bridge.
We got to figure this out.
I'm not sure online bridge.
I was a big Moncala kid.
I liked Moncala, where you put the stones in the little divots.
You played Moncala. The stones.
Yeah, I played Moncala.
We're all Moncala kids.
Yeah. Wow.
That means that the new tagline for the podcast.
Three Moncala kids.
Three grown Moncala kids.
Right. Maybe.
It's pretty reliable.
We'll roll it around in our heads here.
Whoa. Three grown Moncala kids.
I'm in. Wow.
Screw these other podcasts.
I'm never listening to Comedy Bang Bang again.
Yeah. I'm hanging out with these Moncala guys week after week.
We truly become a juggernaut of podcasting.
And Dubai flies us out after that, after we explode.
Yeah.
Maybe it's like Go, which I don't know how to play either.
The Japanese, the white, the white black pebbles that you turn over.
You're trying to get the whole board
as apparently they say, maybe even more complex than chess.
But interesting. Yeah.
I'll have to learn all these games.
Yeah.
Marks. Mark Silverman is Mark Silverman.
Yes.
You're like, I think it's Ben something.
I think I was thinking Ben Silverman, the former NBC executive.
Why do we all know that?
Why do we all know that Ben Silverman?
I don't know.
Too mired.
And we were warped by Disney MGM studios.
Now we know who executives are.
And Robert Evans, I think also.
Yeah.
You bet we do.
In trying to conjure back stories.
Well, OK, we haven't talked about this.
That and when we certainly we're not going to, because if you're going to.
I think this is a topic to cover in a
to divide off in a separate
haunt cast the fright down the road.
There is the film.
We haven't acknowledged the made for TV movie with Kirsten Dunst and Steve
Gutenberg, which now those those two play characters who are not in the ride,
but they are exploring as far as I know, the legend of these five who this mishap
happens to. And I think because of the movie,
there's enough information to cobble together, at least their names.
Carolyn Crissan, that's the movie star
played by Melora Hardin in
in the film.
Gilbert London is the movie star.
Dewey Todd, Dewey Todd.
Great name is the the bellhop.
Sally Shine is the little kid actress and the nanny is Emmeline Partridge.
Now, you might in the movie learn why they deserve to fall down in the elevator.
Maybe you discover they're all the living in various kinds of sin and bad people.
And it had to happen.
But I don't know.
We'll watch. We will get there.
Yeah, we have to do that.
Yeah.
But the the I'm sorry, the the
Disney dot fandom dot com has a little breakdown of all of these characters,
I think, based more on what happens in the movie.
And that leads to this trivia section for all of the characters.
And I clicked on this.
And this is, I think, some really fun
trivia that I learned about these characters.
Sally is very clearly modeled after real life child actress Shirley Temple.
This might be an indication that Sally's life as a child actress was particularly
hellish, given the amount of atrocities directed at the real life temple during
her time in the spotlight.
What? What?
Like, just because she's in like a dress
and has curls, that means that her life was hellish.
That's a kind of a leap.
You mean the actual you actually mean Shirley Temple or this actress?
Well, no, I know things happen to Shirley Temple.
But why does it then follow that Sally Shine had a hellish life?
I guess. And then, yeah,
I was going to say that is the assumption that any especially back then, any child
actor probably had just an awful time of it, which I mean, probably.
Yeah, you would have to assume.
But I just like that that is pulled from one shot of a girl moving from a desk to
an elevator. Well, her life must have been hellish.
She must have been starved and made to work for 48 hours in a row and fed a diet
of meth, sheep sperm and monkey gonads.
Additionally, then on the other page for
Emeline Partridge, the nanny, Sally Shine being made to resemble
Shirley Temple could be an indication that Emeline was somewhat abusive
regarding Sally's career and operations, given the tragedy.
Like, so now we're judging the the nanny, like the nanny beat up Sally or like was
going to throw her out of the out of the hotel window.
Look, where is this one trivia coming from?
I don't get it.
It was still a few decades before the Eddie Munster law took effect, you know,
before they got, you know, a little more protection for the child actors.
Was it? Wait, it's not Eddie Munster, though.
It's isn't it Jackie Coogan who was Fester?
With Fester?
I know there's the I know Jackie Coogan was a advocate for child set safety.
The Jackie Coogan law ensures the financial well-being of child actors by
mandating their employer set aside 15 percent of the child actors gross earnings
in a Coogan trust account where it can be monitored.
I got my spooky shows mixed up.
I would love if there wasn't any monster law, though.
Is there a different law you're thinking of that Eddie Munster,
the character from the Munsters enacted?
Maybe there was an episode where he went to like he went to the local government
and he got something like more like dragons are now legal in everyone's house or something.
Oh, sure.
So there was a zoning issue.
He made it illegal to discriminate in a workplace against people with the werewolf
widows. Yeah, you can't fire somebody just because they have a pointy haircut.
By the way, Al Lewis has been coming up a lot who played Grandpa on the Munsters.
Al Lewis was 42 years old on the Munsters.
Yes, I looked it up.
I was watching an interview with him and I was like,
he's still in the 2000s.
He's alive. Hey, he was in a grandpa age.
And then I looked it up and it was 42 and I was like, oh, my God.
As a kid, I thought he was like, oh, he's a 70 year old man.
Anyway, and now he's
now his memory lives on when Giuliani goes to a hairstylist.
Make me look like this.
Give me the Al Lewis.
Give me a haircut.
So we'll explore these characters when we watch the film.
My condolences to Sally Shine for her hellish life, according to this unpaid
fandom dot com writer.
But the videos need and then, of course, you go up in the shaft and you see them
all float away and disappear into the fifth dimension.
That's a really if you watch that video,
how the Tower of Terror works that breaks down kind of the schematic of where the
mirrors are, where the Pepper's ghost happens.
I don't think I realized that, you know,
you're looking down this hallway and then it all disappears and becomes stars and
just a floating door and that the full setup there is there are real walls.
It's all actually there, but it's a scrim so that you can fade it down.
And once there's no lighting, you can see right through it.
The characters, your Sally Shines at all are all down below.
Like there's a mirror bouncing from from below your point of view in the shaft.
And then it's a rear projection making the door.
It's like all of these, you know, classic theater tricks all working in tandem.
Yeah, it's crazy how a lot of that stuff, even on newer rides, it's like, oh, yeah,
these are the old tricks. These are just the old tricks.
Like, and this may be it may be slightly upgraded, but like mostly just the same
fun stuff that always works.
The theory, yeah, the theory is always there.
Scrim stuff, scrim stuff.
I was just going to say the scrim on the not scary farm
scrim at the end of one of the mazes where you'd be walking down like a normal
like hospital hallway and then the lights would flicker and then the scrim would
change and you'd be looking at hell, it would have like the walls you could see
through and it was hell with a giant demon like, yeah, very cool.
Cool as hell. Yeah.
Yeah.
I walked into that.
What have we what are details we haven't talked about?
I got a Sally Shine thing
because she came up, of course, one of the little Easter eggs in there
kind of connects mentioned elsewhere in the ride.
Sally Shine has a little stuffed Mickey Mouse and that is the like there's hidden
like Easter out the ride. But the thing I I don't know.
I must have seen this before, but not process the implications in the library
where you can find a number of Easter eggs.
There's a piece of sheet music and this was an actual song from the time period.
But the and the full title of the song,
I'm going to read it in how I think it's supposed to be said.
The sheet music is called what?
No Mickey Mouse.
What kind of party is this?
What?
Which I mean, that people just used to call songs very long sentences or like
my beloved, I my dearest, that sort of thing.
But the presence of that sheet music of the Tower of Terror, just imagining
a Hollywood lush walking into this hotel after it had been struck by lightning
going, what kind of party is this?
Like it's such a dark joke.
Is there a way to get our hands on the sheet music and try to do a cover of this
without hearing any actual recorded? Oh, wow.
That's a great idea. Oh, is that possible?
I don't know.
That might require like somebody needs to have photographed that really well.
Yeah, the full lyrics do exist.
I'm back on Disney dot fandom dot com, really the unofficial sponsor of this
episode.
When when Noah planned his famous
I'll try to make up the melody when Noah planned his famous arc, he knew just what
to do. He searched until he found a park and walked off with the zoo with lions,
tigers, monkeys, donkeys.
He sailed the ocean wide and when he lined them up on deck,
was then some cuckoo cried.
What? No Mickey Mouse.
What kind of a party is this?
Well, that's the official melody.
I think that's the official melody now.
That's probably it.
Yeah, they call it then later vote for Mickey Mouse.
Let's make him our next president
to a Congress.
He's sure to say meow, meow.
OK, how dry I am.
Have one on me.
What the fuck is this song talking about?
Mickey Mouse used to tie one off in the 30s a lot more.
Say meow, meow.
Tie one on me.
Meow, meow.
Well, you know, and then he'll cry.
Give me the facts.
Give me my axe.
I'll cut your tax.
He'll show us all what can be done when he's in Washington.
So this is this starts as a song about Noah, the Ark and the Zoo.
And what kind of a party is it without Mickey Mouse and then becomes about how we
have to elect Mickey president, during which they call him Bolsheviki.
I don't know.
The strangest song in history.
I mean, I'll look, I'll elect Mickey as president right now.
It wasn't my first choice in the primary, but
certainly better, certainly better than what we have.
Look, look, Jack, look, me and me and Pluto and the boys
and tune down, dogs.
And that big old Pete was after me and
Clarabel.
I'm trying to think.
There's got to be like a quirkier characters that I'm forgetting here
that I could reference for this joke to be better.
Mortimer, Mortimer,
Fresh Boy Mortimer, M, M dog,
Seabelle.
We used to go down to the old swimming hole,
play with the nickels.
Donald, Donald, if you don't vote for me, you ain't a duck man.
There. That's it.
That's it.
Oh, God.
Look, we're voting for him.
Don't worry. Yeah, we're doing it just because we make fun of it.
Doesn't mean we're not.
You don't yell at us.
We're voting for Mickey.
We're voting for Mickey, of course.
They also this song then was covered in 1970.
They did a new version of it performed by Phil Harris, the voice of Baloo.
And in that one, they updated it and they put in the line, let's give,
let's give Nixon's house to Mickey Mouse.
Phil Harris in a song
proposes ousting Nixon and putting Mickey Mouse in there, which truly could anyone
have any objection to that in 1970?
How much like atrocity could have been avoided?
What a national.
I mean, the whole fabric of the country
could be different if we'd all listen to Phil Harris.
Well, that's true.
And also, if you look up Phil Harris's famous album, The South Will Rise Again.
Oh, no.
That's a real.
Sorry.
You told us that.
Sorry to break that to everyone.
Oh, no. All right.
Don't always listen to fill.
Just know we got it.
You said always listen to Phil Harris.
I have a sound bite.
Don't you?
Whatever Lincoln project within our show is
well, they project to oust Scott Gardner from podcast.
The right Mickey project.
The animated.
No, no, no. The animatronic Lincoln project.
Oh, there it is.
That's what it is.
Well, they they spent 10 million
rotoscoping footage of Phil Harris to dab.
So
well, we're all right.
Cover of this song coming.
Cover of this song.
Oh, my God.
What a sidetrack.
There's funny little I mean, they're the most kind of the more infamous like little
dark jokes, the pin board with the letters in the lobby for a long time.
You know, the letters that you just like push in the black felt for a long time.
That said at the very bottom, it said Evil Tower.
And after 9-11, they took out Evil Tower and replaced it.
Really?
I think now it says you are doomed a little more, a little more generic.
But that makes sense.
Yeah. Probably a good call.
Probably a good call.
Person who realized that the person who was like checking the ride and then went,
oh, oh, oh, yeah.
Well, while I'll this is less dark, I don't have much information about this fact.
But Michael Eisner, maybe you guys do.
Michael Eisner suggested maybe we could make it a real hotel.
Yeah.
Cool. Which I love the idea of that.
But I think logistically, that was a big pain in the ass.
He was right.
That would come to pass.
Hotel built in the theme, but California Adventure, Disneyland, Paris, Tokyo,
Disney, like, well, it did happen.
Yeah.
And we've talked about this before on the show.
I don't like and Star Wars is doing this, of course.
But the fully themed hotel seems like it's just a money printing machine.
Like a full, like spooky Tower of Terror
hotel would be like sold out before every other hotel if it was themed as well
as like the lobby of Tower of Terror.
Absolutely.
Maybe now they can just do like a suite.
They just put in like one room that's a like really lavish experience,
because I don't think at this point you can fit rooms into that structure.
No, it'd be too late.
No, it's too late.
They, of course, at least rumor wise,
we're talking about putting like a Tower of Terror bar lounge,
which is, you know, a fantastic idea.
And I'm shocked that they didn't do it because like, yeah,
all all people, as we've said before, all people want to do is hang out and linger
in these areas and environments longer.
You just want to let you want to last a
little bit longer being in this vibe, being in a vibe of a ride you like.
Yeah, they could get it at the top somehow.
Well, then you have to build a real that doesn't malfunction.
Yes, there would have to be regular.
I mean, the idea that you could stay in a hotel and if you if you stayed at like
the top floor, you'd probably have to pay the most money.
But then you could take the elevator down like you could take the ride down to
start your day every day would be the greatest thing.
He I looked this up in Eisner's book
and he did want it to like not only to have a real hotel surrounding it,
but that you the ride would drop into the lobby.
So like where people actually checked in,
people are like landing and screaming.
This was definitely what he wanted.
Great.
He also I don't think we've talked about this on the show.
There's something that he cites a lot.
And in this case, he says, well, it's you know, it's kind of I always try to go
for the craziest idea, kind of like the Mickey Mouse Hotel.
There's a story that he tells as an example of this is the kind of out of the box
thinking I wanted to bring to the Disney company, the area where the animation
building is now in Burbank, where there's a big sorcerer's hat
that was undeveloped at the time.
And when he got to Disney, he proposed
building a huge hotel that is Mickey Mouse, like it's a giant 200 foot tall Mickey.
And you could live in his arm in his foot.
I mean, I guess in his crotch, probably.
I mean, it's all on the table.
You could live in his seat.
You can. Yeah.
Can I do you have any seats rooms left?
The seats, the seat room is the non
smoking section or maybe it's the smoking section.
Or it's the end.
Do you want to be how desirable is the seat on what to the general?
Was there windows in this proposal?
Would there be like a window seat room where you could like.
So then Mickey is just like full of that's what I'm getting.
Yeah, it doesn't seem like it seemed like it would be like the Star Wars
Hotel, where it's like there's not really windows.
Maybe there was like screens inside to simulate like cartoon land outside.
Right, right.
Well, you black out the windows and any touches of black.
So like his legs or like around his hand, you put the windows on the black colors.
Huh?
It's so insane.
It's like how it's like Dr.
Evil being in a big statue of Dr. Evil.
Yes, it is.
Yes.
It feels like, yeah, it would come to life then it would get like cursed or like
the Ghostbusters would get that plasma and use it to bring Mickey to life.
Like in a Ghostbusters 2 with the Statue of Liberty.
Like that would be.
Well, that's you know, that was done, you know, to to like bring good vibes to New
York and I think good vibes are needed everywhere right now.
And if only if only a 200 foot tall Mickey Mouse could walk around and wave
to everybody. Oh, my God. Yes.
That would do a lot.
Well, don't fix it.
Jackie Wilson.
Jackie Wilson played.
No, and he could
lift me higher.
He could pick up the old tail of the
pup building, the old big hot dog and eat it.
Yeah, take a big bite out of it.
Oh, that would be great.
That would be the moment that would bring America back together.
If Newsom's not going to open the parks,
he needs to devote, I'd say, 60 percent of the state's budget to making a giant,
really a Gundam. Yes, that Gundam that they signed.
Yeah.
Yeah, we've seen the tests of that.
Yes, we need to do that.
But for Mickey. Yeah, I think that's right.
And I want to pay for it with my taxes.
Yeah, I insist.
Yeah. So
whereas I think I've lost my train of thought thinking,
fantasizing about a Mickey, fantasizing about a giant Mickey and being able to
wave at him and live in a seat,
we could talk about
the
what changed in the in the DCA
or the opening of that.
Not to we know we could circle back to any detail to the other one.
But this is where when I was talking about Geyser Mountain forever ago,
this sort of grew out of some proto Geyser Mountain pitch in the late 80s.
Apparently, they were Disneyland was getting close to doing Geyser Mountain
rather than the Tower of Terror, like it was we were going to get a totally
different version and it was going to be in that zone that is now Galaxy's Edge,
as Mike said, and they were maybe honing in on a plan to do that.
And then California Adventure opened and it was a disaster and they needed to bail
it out as quickly as possible.
So this idea was vacated from Frontierland and they I remember how quick it felt.
Like the DCA was only open for a little bit and I was like, all right, screw it.
Tower of Terror. Like take that parking lot out.
It's it's becoming a tower.
Yeah. Yeah.
It's it's very reminiscent, I feel like,
of the story they tell about pirates in Disney World, where it's like they're
going to build a Western River expedition or whatever.
And then it's like people are mad.
Oh, wait, just throw pirates in and it's going to be less good.
Yeah, it's like the same kind of panic,
panic move with us, like a less good version of the thing people like.
I heard this other interesting point of view about what makes the the Disneyland
and the Paris ones a little lesser, which is that by the show, the queue,
basically, everything happens out in front of the tower.
And then the tower is,
wait, am I getting this wrong?
Oh, I'm sorry. OK, the fact that the show scenes are in the back in Florida allows
the tower to be the furthest, the closest thing to you, the guest looking up
at the tower thinking, should I go on this ride or not?
So it kind of seems taller.
You can get closer to the big scary part and it really looms over you,
whereas it's all set back in the California and Paris ones because the queue is up
in the front. Right.
That's all that seems a little obscure, like I don't know how much damage that
really does, but I guess it's I guess it is true.
It does make the building less imposing.
Yeah. I mean, the Florida Florida is being set back seemingly like feeling like it's
on a hill, you got to walk up a little bit and immediately it immediately sets the
mood in a much better way than the one did in California, because California just
turned a corner and it's right there.
And they did a better job when they revamped California Venture with the red
car trolley to make it sort of feel period appropriate.
But it's still just like sitting there
and it just doesn't have the magic, especially like at night in Florida.
When you see it, it's it feels so set back in the way that like Frankenstein's
castle feels or any sort of scary building in a movie or something like it's just so
much better. It just it immediately starts the vibe.
I feel like when you get the Sunset Boulevard ramp up, similar to Radiator
Springs being set at the end of that whole drag of exactly.
Yeah, it's like you have like a it's like a cue before the cue a little bit.
So you're really ready to do it.
What's right, actually, in the right.
I feel like when I was a kid and like,
you don't know what it is at all other than, you know, you drop and it's scary,
like walking up to something makes it feel, I don't know, for whatever reason,
it just makes it feel more intimidating just the way that that that it's set like
that.
So, yeah, I mean, they obviously had not much of a choice to really they just were
like, we've got to dump it somewhere.
So let's yeah, I think so.
And that space made sense and they're tying it all together.
And it's going to end up tying into Marvel, too, even though they've done this
odd kind of out of place re theming of it for now.
The
I guess the was my other point about it.
Oh, I think the other thing
by dropping that fifth dimension thing, the capacity increases a lot.
Right. Yeah.
Like the least reliable part of the ride is gone.
And there's three drop towers instead of
wait, just wait.
No, there's two in Florida. Correct.
There's two in Florida.
So it's OK.
It's four, four things to get you in the back of the building, four shafts to get
you up to the fifth dimension.
There's two fifth dimensions on top of each other.
Those two go into no.
Wait, go.
It all feeds into one.
It all it slowly kind of narrows down.
There's crazy blueprints, too, of like.
And so the elevator is going to lead the shaft and go through the lobby, then go
through the boiler like there's crazy blueprints for like they because I think
that's why the lobby is so good.
Like you said, Eisner wanted it to end in the lobby.
The lobby is so detailed because it
might have at some point in time be considered to be a show scene.
You know what it's like? Brackets is what it is.
Four narrowed down to two.
Really think of it as brackets.
Yes.
And then the California, it's three shafts with six different places to enter with two
levels so that they can load.
Yeah, you're either up top or up or down the bottom and you can load at either one
of this so they can have a car ready for the tower while the other one's doing.
Right. And there's only this is
I was confused up until like a year or two ago when it was like, yeah, you also
like kind of load into a vehicle on the tower out here.
I didn't I didn't realize that because I one time I go, oh, I see now where like
the mechanism like hooks to pull you forward once you're done with the ride.
And then you when you push out from the exit, you get loaded into this little box
and that little box, that cube, excuse me, the cube, the cube, the three cubes.
So that cube is always working.
But the cube changes like it goes up and down to go back and forth between the
levels. That's the most confusing way I could have said that.
But the cube is always working.
The cube is always working.
But the little cars are not always working.
They're alternating.
Yeah. Yeah.
This is why, look, you listen to the show for the jokes, not for the, you know, you
can watch your detailed explanations on YouTube, but in those, you're probably not
going to get that joke. You're not going to get the jokes, voices and all that fun stuff.
The cubes and 100 grand bar references.
Al Lewis talk.
No, I've seen fresh baked Disney.
He doesn't just wander into an Al Lewis discussion.
Come on, fresh baked.
He's alarmingly on.
Yeah. What is that?
Come on.
So, yeah, cubes, folks, cubes working.
There's some fun tricks.
There's some fun tricks in the California one.
Rooms become star feet like there.
It's not I'm not saying it's not cool,
but if it had come along first and then the Florida one came along,
could you imagine how blown away you would be as opposed to the other way
around where in one summer when one summer California got abbreviated tower
of terror and abbreviated revenge of the mummy is so funny.
Right.
And dark times, dark time.
And of course, this will save this for the actual mission breakout episode.
But I California then solved, I feel like solved a problem we didn't know existed
by making the drop sequence more entertaining and a little longer is still, I think.
Yeah, yeah, I think you can't because like basically what I'm saying is like
after mission breakout, which I know mission breakout is controversial still,
which I don't I'm a big fan.
It's like my favorite ride other than like Big Thunder at the resort.
Like I have to admit it.
I go on it almost every time.
If I can go on one ride, it's oftentimes that
I think it's really I think they did a really great job with it.
But the actual ride itself.
So when we went in Tokyo's and then we went back to Florida and the actual drop
sequence basically just happens in the dark with no music and it feels a little
underwhelming, but that's not its fault.
I don't want to be negative here because
before I was spoiled with the drop sequence of Guardians of the Galaxy.
There was I didn't think twice.
I didn't think twice about it, but it is randomized now in Florida.
Yeah, it's still fun.
And then but you get a taste of that at
Guardians, too, because you don't know what song you're going to get.
It kind of changes and the footage changes.
It almost feels like now that you now that I've seen the Guardians,
you would want something similar with the Twilight Zone where like you stop,
you see a weird, creepy scene and you go back up.
Like there's there's something to do there.
I don't think you can do that, though,
especially in Florida, because there's nothing there's not much in front of you
in Florida in California, they just repurposed the normal Tower of Terror
scenes and areas to be with those have the screens and have the one like control
room part over at the there's no scenes in the tower.
I guess that is the California innovation
that along that which makes enables that guardians experience that the doors open
and you don't know what you're going to get in Florida.
The doors only open at the top.
Right. Because, yeah, there's just no other spot.
I don't think there's any depth to those to that area because you're right
in front of the building versus California where you had there was room
because that's where the show scenes were in front of the building or in the front
of the building. All the towers bring something to the table and they all like
elevate each other and raise your expectation for the others, except for France.
You stay in France.
You didn't you didn't bring Jack shit to the table.
You know what France needed?
I Rod Sterling experience I once had, which was if the car has his archives
because he taught there towards the end of his life and every Halloween they would
do a Twilight Zone marathon and a number of years they would just use the DVDs.
But one year they used original masters like transferred original masters,
which includes the Chesterfield cigarette commercials.
So you got to see like a solemn tobacco farmer in his fields and then a full
marching band pops up from the fields and they play the Chesterfield song.
And then at the very end of the episode,
Serling says and stay tuned next week and make sure to while you're watching,
enjoy a delicious Chesterfield cigarette, 21 kinds of tobacco for 21 wonderful smokes.
And I have tried to find these commercials for years to no avail.
But it is so funny that and Sterling, like in a lot of his intros,
like the intro of Nick of Time, he's sitting in a diner booth smoking a cigarette
on camera. So you would plus up France by giving a cigarette to every rider of the ride.
They love cigarettes in France.
And so I think just put it in there because, you know, they oh, that's the other.
That is one because I was wondering what do the French like the Twilight Zone.
And there's that episode, the occurrence at the Al Creek.
What's the full name?
An occurrence at Al Creek, an adaptation of an Ambrose beer story.
It was a short film that won the best short at Cannes and the Academy Awards.
And the Twilight Zone people just licensed it for the Twilight Zone.
And it is really creepy.
So there was a French connection to the Twilight Zone.
Interesting.
Did anyone watch the Kirk Cameron special?
Jason? Yes, yes, I have.
Do we have another hour?
No, I know we did some of the highlights.
So they basically like the first part of it is like
K Fabe wrestling term for like in universe, like it's a spooky hotel.
And then like the second half is
imagineering talk and like the actual creation of it.
And
there's a couple of things I really I like about it.
He he basically like when they're doing the transition, he like explains the
legend of the Tower of Terror and then to transition out.
He explains that Disney built a recreation of the hotel.
So like it's like try they were like, how do we square this circle?
It's real. But why would it be in a theme park?
So they're like, and he's like, so Disney built a real version.
And it's like, there's no real need for what for this piece of exposition.
And then they go into and then I think
pretty quickly we get a little Eisner blurb.
And he basically just he's excited about it.
He doesn't say anything particularly funny.
But what I like about it is that all of the lower thirds, anyone who's like name
pops up on the bottom of the screen, it gets introduced with a piece of like
lightning shooting at it.
So it's like it's like it's like crack.
And then it like Michael Eisner appears on the bottom.
And it's the same with like Marty Sclar.
It's like Marty Sclar on the bottom.
And they're like, I love that.
Very jumbo shrine.
That's real stupid.
Yes, it's not as aggressive, probably as the noise I'm making.
But there's an absolute there's a noise and a lightning strike.
And then Michael Eisner appears on the bottom of the screen, which is exciting.
Kirk Cameron is like 50 pounds soaking wet in that he is like so tiny and he's like
wearing like the stop making sense suit and none of his
suits fit.
And they have written him the most flowery like narration dialogue.
He's not nailing any of it.
He looks like such a dweeb.
Like I wanted to squirrely him.
They're making him do like old timey dialogue.
And he's doing he's doing his best.
They should have had Robert Evans.
They should have just hired Robert Evans to do it.
Or even like a Jerry Orbach type.
They should have had an old man do it.
But yeah, Kirk Hammons are real dweeb.
And of course, now he thinks, you know, the hotel is haunted by demons.
Now he thinks the real tower of terror is
the DNC headquarters where the Democrats do their devil worship.
Yeah, well, he likes the story of the people in the elevator just suddenly
disappearing because he thinks it's kind of like the rap.
Yeah, they were living in centers, centers, kissing actors who aren't your wife.
You can't kiss sectors who aren't your wife.
Mike, there is a moment in that, Mike,
did you catch the moment in the special with the one Imagineer talking about drawings?
I probably watch it, but I'm not sure
what you're which part you're talking about off.
OK, they interview an Imagineer.
I forget his name, but he's talking about being in meetings and he's working like
in the meetings, he's like always doodling.
And he said a word that I'm like, oh, that might be a new show word.
He says, I'm sitting with a sketch pad making roughies.
I did not pick up the roughies making roughies.
I rewatch it like five times.
I had to hear it.
Make sure I heard it right.
Make sure I heard him say making roughies.
I had never heard roughies before.
That's like that.
I feel like that's something you might have said as a child, like you when you
were feeling rammy and then you would make roughies after that.
You tumbled around too much on the playground.
You were making roughies.
You too. You and your brother.
Stop making roughies.
Wow, I did not catch.
Yeah, we it's it's a new show word.
We love roughies.
Send us your rough.
If you have your if you have any access to exclusive Imagineering roughies,
we want to see them.
We'll pay top dollar for your roughies.
And
listen to that podcast,
Bind the Paywall with Tony Baxter, because he talks a lot about his roughies.
Cash for roughies, call one eight hundred cash for roughies.
Wow, roughies.
Is that is that just like a cute thing that guy said or is that actually a term?
I think it's just a thing.
He was he met like rough sketches, rough doodles and stuff.
But roughly I never heard roughies before.
Wow.
Maybe it was something they said in the office.
But it just it just it's I'll never forget roughies now.
Yeah, no, it's a very memorable way to say it.
Well, I'm saying it now.
It's we're all saying roughies.
They're all saying we're all saying you're hearing it more and more.
You're hearing it.
Uh, I had I had one.
Oh, we actually as we talk about sitcom stars going into this attraction,
I think it's come up before, but I just want to reiterate, I find it very bizarre.
That both Step by Step and Family Matters
did Disney World episodes, they where they went to the Tower of Terror.
And it is the same right operator with the same blocking.
It is like like two characters.
Every the
elevator is already full, the car is full.
And then two characters stop at the door,
kind of address whatever plot situation is going on while a creepy bellhop kind of
stares at them.
And then he starts the ride and like, see you on the other side.
And it's the same guy.
And that's really weird.
But then on top of that, then I was I found both of these on Hulu.
And I rewatched them.
The episodes are both called We're Going to Disney World.
They have the scenes happen in the middle of part two, where they were both
in the middle of a two parter and they aired two days apart from each other.
Wow.
So if you were a big watcher of both of these shows, as I was, you got to see the
same scene at the Tower of Terror twice in a week.
Wow.
That's so funny.
I guess they maybe shoot it on the same day.
Yeah, maybe the same next like just double back to back, maybe next like one day.
Next next day.
That's like filming the you film the American version and the Japanese version
immediately. Well, we got the set here.
The camera set up. Right.
Let's just knock them out.
And that's funny.
Yeah, yeah.
You know, but you know what I like to talk about is is the exit.
When you when you come down in the Florida Tower of Terror, I forgot about this.
You come down in a little room with it,
with a little screen with the kind of famous Twilight Zone, like what do you call
it, a spiral or something with the black and white
and the music playing.
And you're like, you don't end up in the same spot you started and which is very
cool.
And there's a lot of little trinkets and stuff in that little.
It feels like you just got dumped in a
little room and then your car spins around to like gets you to the exit.
And I didn't realize it until I went on it a couple of years ago that Caesar,
the ventriloquist dummy from one of the famous episodes called Caesar and me, who,
of course, the dummy is real and the man is fake is the big revelation.
I'm sorry. Spoiler alert.
But Caesar is sitting there in the room
and I got so excited to see him and I'm I like Twilight Zone.
I'm I didn't know his name was Caesar.
I'm just trying to say, like, I'm not like, oh, my God, it's Caesar.
But I said, oh, my God, it's the dummy.
And I was very excited because I am a big dummy.
I'm a big dummy fan.
Yeah, there's two dummy episodes of Twilight Zone.
Yes, there's another dummy one, too, where I think that dummy is meaner.
OK, maybe I'm actually confusing my dummy episodes.
It is Caesar in the right.
It is Caesar for sure on the right.
But I can't remember.
Maybe I'm thinking of mixing up my dummy and I apologize, folks.
I'm just a big fan of dummies, not necessarily the Twilight Zone episodes.
But I'm right.
So any Night of the Living Dummy Goosebumps book.
Big fan of that. Yeah.
Have you ever seen the Mystery Science Theater movie Devil Doll?
I have not with a creepy
the dummy's name is Hugo, I believe.
And there's something that
my wife and I say every time, like, like very often when we're drinking wine,
which is that which is very often would end the that is that the you know,
that is also kind of a possessed dummy and he wants to have wine.
And then the ventriloquist says, but you can't have wine, Hugo.
You're just a dummy.
Like, I want wine.
I know what wine is.
Give me some.
We when we decide we're going to have wine, we really often say, I know what wine is.
Wow. So you're you're dummy fans, too.
I guess I am, too. Yeah.
Well, you're a you're a Caesar guy.
I'm who are you guys?
Who are your dummies? I'm a I'm a Hugo guy.
Jason, who's your favorite dummy?
Oh, well, I
from Batman, from Batman, the animated series.
Is it Scarface? Is that his name?
Oh, Jason, are you talking about the toy I have right here?
Yes, that's right.
Yes. The ventriloquist and his dummy.
Scarface, of course.
Yeah. This is one of the greatest toys ever, by the way.
That is great. Yeah.
It's kind of funny that we all like dummies considering that we are freaked out
by things and I'm so scared of like creepy baby.
Right.
Things. Maybe I just maybe I wouldn't like a baby dummy.
Maybe that's the line.
Is there such a thing in media?
Oh, my God, there has to be a baby dummy that would scare me.
That's a good question.
I mean, do you think Caesar is cute from the Twilight Zone?
That's a question I have.
I think we like these dummies, but I don't think any of us are calling me cute.
Let me send a photo to everyone.
I like Hugo. I don't think Hugo is cute.
OK, here we go.
I mean, I don't care.
We go just so we're all on the same page.
Here's a picture of Caesar.
You're I texted it to both of you.
Yeah. And then officially is so cute.
Look, I think I'm sorry, but like a big,
thick eyebrows are just kind of kind of get in the way of cute.
You can look good or handsome or sharp.
I don't know that I would call Caesar cute, though.
No, Jason. Yes.
You think yes.
I don't know.
I like I like those cheek the cheekbones with the eyebrows.
I think are cute and the Stoge got a big Stoge.
This is a semantics issue.
I think he looks cool.
I like him.
You like to be.
I think he's cool.
Not cute. You guys are crazy.
I didn't know the Twilight Zone dummies.
I didn't rule yet.
I have not ruled.
I have just posed the question and I'm just listening to all
the different things I'm going to rule.
I'm going to say,
I think he looks cool.
Yes, exactly.
He's cool.
Not cute. It's very clear.
I'm glad sometimes there's sanity on these cuteness.
I just think I'm look, I'm not troll.
I'm being fair and balanced.
That's a phrase I came up with.
Well, then we'd like to know more.
Obviously, I love when creatures are put into my Twitter feed.
So if you think you have a dummy that's cute,
if you can think of a baby dummy, and I'm not talking puppet,
there's baby puppets.
Yeah, it has to be a ventriloquist dummy.
Yeah.
A baby.
Do you think that there's a ventriloquist equivalent of baby Grinch or baby?
I mean, if I look up baby dummy.
Well, what about that baby Navi that we've been bombarded with that everyone's
Carly and our various members of our Facebook group are like, I blame you for
this, they're getting the Etsy ad for this Navi baby.
Like those
multi hundred dollar doll babies you can adopt that like crazy people.
Do you think that's cute?
No, no, no, I hate the I hate that.
Absolutely.
And as I looked up baby ventriloquist dummy, there's just I'm seeing like a real
child's Halloween costume where the lines are drawn on his chin and he's got the rouge.
This I hate.
I very much make the rules clear.
Well, I do like some ventriloquist dummies.
A real child as a ventriloquist dummy is not cute.
This is bad.
No, no, I will not be making my baby Halloween's coming up.
No, no, no, no, he's going to be truffles.
He's truffles. All right.
That is cute. All right.
But next year, yeah, I'm seeing that a gentleman who's a ventriloquist named Paul
Zerdin has some sort of baby dummy that he uses.
I don't know anything about the act.
I just see a thumbnail that he is working a baby puppet.
So we'll have to look into that.
See what we think of Paul Zerdin.
You know, I'm watching it.
It's neither here nor there.
It's not, you know, he actually really this this so-called baby could all be
just as easy as a 95 year old man.
So it's
I don't know. I think I think it doesn't qualify.
Oh, and then he later read in the same video.
He does bring up an old man immediately.
OK, all right.
I just think I think also like in this,
again, we've been talking too long here.
I do love old dolls.
I I I'm fascinated with
I don't know. I'm not going to go with you on that.
Like I'm fascinated by, of course, Robert, the evil doll.
Well, sure.
Who is terrifying.
I'm not going to I'm not going to tell you I think Robert is cute,
though I do feel bad for Robert.
You know, if you don't know, this is Robert and you're he's and he's
like the basis sort of for like the Chucky legend, like the inspiration for like
haunted dolls.
I see.
And I well, what's an old doll that you think is cute?
Well, I just said I'm a fan of old.
I didn't say I think all the old dolls are cute.
I'm just saying if it's an old doll, I like it.
Scott, are you going to dress your child like we all I'm assuming we're
dressed for picture day in school, like tiny little dolls like boys and girls
alike dress like tiny, fancy little dolls, which was very popular in the 90s.
I am there's a big there's a picture of me in a full sailor suit as a child.
Yeah.
Of course, there is.
I don't know if I have a hat, but the rest of it is the sailor suit.
And Jason, that's just what he wears to a party.
Well, it's oh, yeah, especially when it's Fleet Week.
All aboard must produce this photo.
Yeah, I find the sailor suit photo.
Jason, do you have to have a sailor suit photo?
I don't know about sailors.
I feel like I had an unseemly number of turtlenecks as a boy like Robert.
Like a young Robert Evans, like a young Robert Evans.
Yeah, turtlenecks and sweaters.
I did find.
Well, you guys like this.
And I'm assuming it was just written
because it's clearly my mother's handwriting, a letter to my grandparents
dated September 1988.
I came across this the other day, written as if I had written it.
What?
It is like I finally got my haircut and I kicked and screamed.
But if I'm a good boy, I'll get a toy,
a little toy, a Kmart and get to ride a ride.
So the the keystone for the show was implanted in my brain a lot longer ago
than I thought. Wow.
I'm being ruffy.
But yeah.
Wait, what's the other phrase?
Ramy.
I'm being Ramy and I got into ruffies, but I but I got a little doll anyway.
I got a little an old doll, a little old doll, a little old doll.
And we're going to be dressed the same
two sailor suits, same size, please.
Child Jason, a little older child, Jason and current Jason would very much have
both enjoyed the Henry Bemis action figure that is very hard to find from the
Twilight Zone. Henry Bemis, the Burgess Meredith character from time enough at last.
They have these toys now.
I know they're so hard to track down.
Yeah, they're very expensive.
If you do find them, they always have them.
I don't want a house full of Twilight Zone toys.
This is a recipe for them all to come to life and bother me.
What about like a full size Caesar, though?
You could just sit overlooking the crib.
Hi.
Hey, you wake.
Wake up. Hey,
get up. Rise and shine.
The day's always been.
Have a cigar with me, buddy.
They really in the gift shop, they should sell that.
Oddly, I think I would dress my baby as Caesar.
I don't know the safety level of prosthetic eyebrows for infants,
but you could if I discover that any are safe, I'll consider you do like a headband
with the eyebrows attached.
Oh, that's not a penny.
Yes. And the rest is skin colored.
Yeah, that would be good.
And then like you could work on that.
I'll find this.
I was going to say, do you have a could you find a bottle that looks like a big cigar?
Give me another hit of that
little extremer smoke coming out right like a very thin bottle that looks like a
cigar that you'd put in.
This ain't bad.
That's good.
I think Disney really blew it not having these items available in the gift shop
for the Tower of Terror. Right.
I want our Twilight Zone branding.
We want our cigar bottle disguises and eyebrow straps for babies.
Oh, of course, I have I guess I should mention that I have the Terry Cloth
Hollywood Tower Hotel Bathrobe.
Mm hmm.
And it's great.
It's you wear it.
It's very practical.
Oh, yeah. I still use it.
Yeah. It's hanging on the door.
We're in overtime here, but you you're a bathrobe guy.
I'm a bathrobe guy.
Yeah.
I love to be one.
I have one.
I just never I never do it.
Scott, what are you a bathrobe guy?
Yeah, I'll do it.
Everyone's OK.
Yeah, I got one.
But, yeah, I don't know.
It's odd to do.
Jason, are you a bathrobe?
I can't imagine constantly.
Are you you're like an everyday bathrobe guy.
Am I wrong?
Yeah, sometimes.
What?
Get out of the get out of the shower, put on that rope.
You're like a Robert Evans type where like you would imagine he just wore like
a smoking jacket around the house or a bathrobe.
So like you are just like a lounging your
robe after a shower for hours unless you have somewhere to go.
Yeah, weather depending.
Sometimes that's a little too cold.
You know,
the difference being
milk and cookies replacing vast sums of cocaine.
Right.
Besides that, sure.
Maybe Jason is a Robert Evans type.
Should we do we get out over time?
Have we done it? Can we do it?
I think we can do it.
I think so.
Yeah.
Haunt cast the Fright, an episode that a while ago was mostly about the
Twilight Zone Tower of Terror.
That's a blast.
It's nice to talk about such a such a fantastic ride, a lynchpin, an institution.
And as we said, almost this almost has to become a yearly, a mini yearly series
because we have to hit Japan, we have to hit the film.
And of course, an entire episode devoted to the systemic abuse of Sally.
Sean is very evident from the one unspeaking shot of.
Yes.
Do we think Mission Breakout?
That's not counted, right?
Because it's not spooky.
No, I think it's not.
But it is a Monsters After Dark, the Halloween overlay.
That has to be an Haunt Cast the Fright.
Maybe on a second gate, maybe behind a paywall.
I think so.
I think those are the rules.
So we have to cover it in the off season and unless we do Monsters After Dark first,
it gets very right.
We could do Monsters After Dark first.
And you have you have not you've done
Guardians, but not Monsters After Dark now haven't done Monsters After Dark.
Right. Which I love.
Spooky.
Yeah, my favorite.
Does sound cool.
All right. So this look, we're not done with these towers.
We'll be back in the tower.
We may have to be
similarly over in the Creatures Choice Awards to we'll figure that out.
Hey, like we said, there's a lot of Haunt Cast the Fright to come.
We got good topics, good fun coming up.
So stay tuned.
What's a monster?
What's a Halloween pun?
Stay Glued to your
podcast app and be sure to
skeloscribe to that's horrible.
Skeletal Skeleton subscribe.
Look, I don't know.
I'll tune these up later.
The point is go to podcast the ride, the cemetery gate for both three
booness episodes. That's good.
That's perfect. Yeah, very good.
Yeah, that's great. I close that on a good one at Patreon.com
slash podcast the right.
I'm not going to spookify that one or the URL won't be right.
OK, very important. All right.
Well, we'll see you soon.
This has been a forever dog production
executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett
Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit ForeverDogPodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple
podcasts, Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at ForeverDogTeam and liking our page on Facebook.