Forever.
Dog.
Warning.
The following haunt cast contains the excitement of television show activations, toy buying
bots and a giant pumpkin mere feet away from slightly discounted shoes and pants.
Get in the car at a safe distance and enjoy drive through haunts on haunt cast the fright.
Welcome to haunt cast the fright, a haunt cast so scary that when you tell your non-theme
park people about how long our episodes are they scream in terror.
My name is usually Mike Carlson, but this month's it is Spike Narleson.
Jason.
Do you change it?
I changed it again.
It's been a ballpark that yeah, I saw it.
It's been some controversial ones this month, but that's I think non-controversial.
That's just fun Halloween.
Joining me as always, usually Jason Sheridan this month.
This month, Jack O'Lantern slime it in very consistent, very good Halloween name.
I yeah, I wrote it down so I would remember.
Thanks.
I worked on it for a while.
I was worried if I just went with Jack O'Lantern, Jason, that's like a fucking improv warm up
nonsense.
I like that too though.
I'll be honest.
I like that too.
Or Jason Jack O'Lantern.
I think it works either way.
Joining also us as always, usually Scott Gardner.
Well, I was thinking if we're all kind of experimenting, like what is the rule dictating
that we'd has to reflect our real name in some way?
Because I'm Scott all the time.
And if I was just something similar to Scott, what's preventing me from just being Rick
Zombieberg?
I just want to change it up.
There's nothing preventing it.
I think that is sort of the fun.
It sounds a little like it.
So it's like a version of you.
But if you want to do a whole new persona, I think that's good.
Yeah, I think so.
I'm just, I don't know, Rick is a cool name.
That's a name I'd like to have every, just for a little bit.
And it's not a parody of anything.
I don't know what the non-Halloween version of Rick Zombieberg is.
Maybe it's like Zellberg or something, but it doesn't matter.
I'm Rick Zombieberg from now on because I'm sick of my own initials.
That's fine.
What if I just go by Ice Pick from now on?
Okay.
Hell yeah.
That's so cool.
My name is Ice Pick now.
That's what would call me that for the rest of the month.
And maybe forever.
We've got to break out of these rules.
Like, what is this unspoken that it has to be a pun about your, like, let's go wild.
Let's go hog wild.
That could be, I don't want to say what Jason's is, but if Jason's was hog wild.
Hog wild is pretty good.
I was going to pitch Mr. Murder.
Is that better or worse than hog wild?
Lateral?
I mean, they're both, they both have their good points, I think.
There's both big reasons to like those.
It's still up to you to choose ultimately.
That's what we're doing.
With me embracing being Rick Zombie Berg, it's all about grabbing the reins of a new
persona.
How about Dr. Murderhog?
I like that.
Hell yeah.
That's kind of best of both worlds.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
And I had a doctor in too.
So you're like, you have like a lab coat that's covered in blood.
And respect.
Yes.
The most, the scariest thing you can have on your coat.
That's right.
Sorry.
Dr. Murderhog.
That's good.
Yeah, I think anything.
Now, if we can remember selectively through the episode, you know, we're going to default
to what our regular names are, but it'd be nice to, you know, you know, we're talking
about like drive through haunts and, and, well, the former Jason, I went, went and tried
one.
But if I was like, no doctor, how was it, was there like a big backup?
Because it's, you know, like, was it, how many people were there?
I mean, I mean, did you have a good time, doctor?
Yes, I did.
I did.
I was a little concerned at first.
They certainly had the place markers for like, oh, if it's running long, they even add like
from this point, 50 minutes.
Yeah, that feels good.
That feels right.
Mm hmm.
Ice pick.
Does that seem like something you could make your way through?
Yeah, it does sound like that.
Oh, wait a minute.
Now I have a different voice.
The voice changed entirely.
Wow.
Yeah, no, but that feels good.
Being called ice pick feels good and it makes me feel different.
Tossing it away so casually.
Yeah.
Just like, yeah.
And I've actually forgotten your name, so tell me what it is.
Rick Zombieberg.
That's right, of course.
I'll write it down so I don't forget it.
OK, yeah, and Rick, you were just talking about it.
You're talking about your whole, this whole Zombieberg family and what you were doing.
How did that go?
How was that?
Oh, yeah.
Well, there's so many of us by the time you get the Zombieberg cousins out and the, you
know, some people are only, you know, it's a hyphenate, you know, Zombieberg and Ghostlington.
So you get the Zombiebergs out and the Zombieberg Ghostlingtons.
So, you know, you're talking 50 people come into your Halloweens usually.
But, you know, now it's all going to be on Zoom.
So it's all it's all fucked.
Yeah, I hear that.
Yeah.
Well, that's good.
That feels seamless.
I like I'm loving this new persona.
It's injecting some life into this Halloween season, which, as we've said, is, you know,
is hampered by the current state of affairs.
And what we're here to talk about is Halloween experiences that you can do and that we went
and did in the Los Angeles area.
But there's stuff all over the country you can do.
I like that we're trying to break out and, you know, make something happen in a drive-through
fashion or a virtual fashion.
I applaud the creativity on the parts of everyone doing these kinds of things.
Yes, it's yeah, they're making the best of a bad situation.
And I think, you know, there's a variety of these things, which is nice, too.
I think a lot of people are doing a version of this.
I think so.
And I think we've all like we all did something pretty, pretty different.
As fun as some of what we've done here in 2020 is, I think it can't help but make you
nostalgic for Halloween's gone by more classic Halloween's like when you were a kid and when
you could actually do the trick or treating.
And I am more now than ever incredibly nostalgic for my favorite Halloween, which was in 1994
on which Halloween I got to appear on The Tonight Show with Jay Leno.
This was a thread left open months ago.
This was discussed deep into our longest episode.
It was buried under minutes and minutes of content in our episode about The Tonight Show
Ride, which is available on the Patreon.
So if you didn't hear it there, I basically I had a family friend who worked in the music
department on the Carson and then the Leno Tonight Show.
And there was a sketch going on and I was obsessed with the fact that I knew somebody
worked at that show was mind blowing to me.
And I could go like be in a bit.
I felt so much like Bart on the Krusty Show in the what birth I didn't do it situation.
Now, it didn't go that far because Bart had a line.
I was just one of many, many trick or treaters.
And I'm wearing a mask so you can't tell it's me.
I'm wearing a Richard Nixon mask, which I may have said in the other episode.
I thought, well, maybe Jay will appreciate that as he is a political setterist.
A very sophisticated one.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So we know if only we had him now to sort through the ins and outs of this complex situation
we're currently in.
Anyway, all of this is just to say, you know, like I'm not going to play a clip of it because
it's just lengthy.
And, you know, you basically just see a Nixon in the mix as the sketch goes on, including
the mainly starring health guru, Susan Powder, who is famous, of course, for her catchphrase,
stop the insanity.
As I may have said in the other episode, none of this was explained to me, like what it
was going to be.
It was just like, okay, go out there.
Like there was never a rehearsal.
This was never run, nor did it need to be.
That was, you know, they did the right amount of preparation and not overthinking.
So all this to say, that clip will be available on our Twitter so you can watch it.
And I'll make sure to circle which one I am, just so you know, because there'd be no other
way to know.
But in finding the tape, I had an interesting discovery because I was like, well, what was
the rest of this episode?
Like, what was a, like, I don't think a lot of people have like a tape of a Leno episode
in general from that era from 94.
And this was a jam packed episode because there was a remote done by Bill Maher, who
was a correspondent who was reporting from Tiny Tim's wedding.
Do we, I don't even, I'm not sure I even know how to explain who Tiny Tim was.
Yeah.
Yeah, like a musician fringe character type guy.
He had a novelty song guy.
Yeah, he had an interesting voice.
He was an eccentric.
Yeah.
I don't know there.
Is that it?
Is that about as good?
I think so.
He was famous for getting married on the Carson Tonight Show and then he was like, they
seemingly tried to do it again, but very half-assed just with these Bill Maher check-ins.
So that's going on.
I remember being in the hallway and passing by Richard Simmons at some point, wearing
just full exactly the Richard Simmons wardrobe that you'd want to see.
So I thought that was really cool.
But then I was trying to remember like, who was the musical guest?
Because I remember thinking like, oh, well, what if then the show keeps going and then
I basically get to see like a concert?
What if the musical guest is one of the people I really like?
What if it's like a cool band like Hammer or the Beach Boys, the two music acts that
I liked at the time?
And then I remember being disappointed like, oh, it's this sucks.
It's like a grown-up band.
It's a boring adult band.
And I never knew what it was until rewatching the tape.
The band in this episode was Big Star.
What?
Yes.
Beloved Colts, like one of the most respected bands in history.
I mean, it was this like reformed version.
Right.
Big Star was Alex Chilton and a guy with Bell was the other guy.
I don't know why it's not coming to me.
It was it was Alex Chilton and then other people like hired guns.
I think Chris Bell was the guy who was in the band, but he died.
He died before 1994.
Oh, gotcha.
Okay.
Wait, in that year where this was happening?
No, he died before 1994.
Sorry.
Oh, before 94.
Okay.
He died in I'm looking it up now, 78.
Oh, gee.
Okay.
Long ago.
Yeah.
Anyway, this just lingered in my head is like I wish that band wasn't so boring.
And now I've realized it's like one of the most revered, like, you know, quietly adored
bands in history and they were like so in this room at this time, like in the same room,
Halloween 94, Jay Leno, Matthew Broderick was there, Jennifer Tilly and Richard Simmons,
Alex Chilton and a nine year old Scott Gardner and a Nixon mask.
Wow.
That's wild.
Could not believe what song did the big star play?
They did in the street.
Oh, yeah.
Not too long after became the theme to that 70s show as covered by cheap trick.
So yeah, iconic song.
Like they barely performed live ever.
This is going to be one of the only television appearances of big star.
I'm not even.
Yeah.
I'm not even that up on like where they went sort of after they stopped putting stuff out.
So I'm surprised.
I don't even know the timeline of like why they were on the tonight show in 1994.
What was going on at the time?
I think there was a there was a live album they were promoting or something.
That could have also just been like, oh, the albums are finally on CD because I was like,
wait, were the albums even at print 94?
That's true.
A lot of people, a lot of bands did perform in that context, like the reissue of such.
Right.
Interesting.
Wow.
So anyway.
I mean, it wasn't like you were supposed to know, like get excited about Alex Chilton at the time.
No, and I was I was insufferable enough as a 17 year old talking about Alex Chilton,
let alone if I was nine, I mean, I would have been the worst.
I as a nine year old who brought a Richard Nixon costume to a TV show.
And then like I have this other memory of like this is an exciting time for me.
This was I must have gotten the bug to be in in media because right around the same time,
it was right after this, like in the same week, I went to a recording studio
to record a Christmas album with my boy choir.
The St. Melchurch boy choir.
And we did, you know, mostly standards for, you know, kind of, you know,
like ring Christmas bells.
My really really.
And I remember that I wore a big old like didn't fit me tonight show hat
to the record.
So I'm feeling like so high on my own shit.
I've just been on the Leno tonight show.
Now I'm recording my album and I walked into it and I was not friends with anyone else in
the boy choir.
We did not get along.
And some kid is like, where'd you get that hat?
And I was like, I was on the show and he was like, no, you weren't.
And that was the end.
And I didn't argue back because I was too scared to.
Oh, wow.
You said no, you weren't.
You were like, yeah, you're right.
Yeah, he's probably right.
He's bigger than me.
Maybe.
Never mind.
Actually, he's more confident than me.
He's much shorter, but extremely confident.
So he's probably right.
I've apologized a million times for doing that.
It's just whenever we get in a tiff, I see that guy that boy choir.
I'm looking at you in my zoom window like I bet Jason doesn't believe I was on a tonight show.
Prove it.
I will.
Show the hat.
Putting this tape on.
And you might think that I'm just going to circle an arbitrary kid in a Nixon mask, but it was me.
He'll turn and you'll see Scott Brown hair and you'll know.
Do you think if you had like, we're like, well, yeah, I walked by Alex Chilton.
He was like, whoa.
No kidding.
That's one of the guys.
Oh, man.
The guy saying the letter.
Boy, he's one of the guys who made me want to get into recording.
That's why I'm in this studio to cut Merry Christmas from the St. Mel's boy choir.
That would have fixed it, I think.
Would have shut everyone up if only I knew.
So I failed.
My lack of musical knowledge at nine failed me.
I'll try to post that whole album, too.
I'll try to do it in a lossless format like a flack, like an FLAC.
Yeah, yeah.
Highest quality.
You could play it on Neil Young's Pono.
That would be like the version.
Neil Young's short lived.
I'll try to get a hold of him.
If I can get Neil on the line just to oversee the fidelity of it.
I have a memory about recording that Christmas album also, which is that
when it began, we were promised $100 each and a CD of the album.
And it ended up being $25 in a tape.
That prepared you for a career in media better than anything else.
Yeah, really.
All was contained in those couple months, wasn't it?
And I got into it anyway.
And I had to because when I got hit by those lights and I got to share
the stage with Susan Powder herself, I had to keep going.
So anyway, that'll all be a video on the Twitter and the album,
we got to wait till Christmas.
We got Halloween to get through first.
Oh, man, you have the album.
Oh, sure.
The album's around.
Yeah, yeah.
I could scan the cover also and try to prove that one of the blurry
dots in the red robes is me.
Could you do a remix to of it maybe for Christmas, like an EDM style remix?
Maybe so.
That depends.
I can't promise how in tempo Bill the piano player was.
I don't know that you could set a metronome to it.
I see.
But I'll bring it into garage.
If I got to cut it up, I can do that.
All right.
Well, that's exciting.
That's a good tease.
Yeah.
I knew I was playing the long game.
The audience for these things wasn't there then, but I knew someday I'm going
to accrue a rabid podcast audience that is going to really want to hear my falsetto
on Christmas album.
Wow.
So did you look at that Big Star performance on YouTube at all?
It is.
Yeah.
So you can just watch that.
I'm not going to post that for you, but you can watch Leno introduce.
Yeah.
And so, yeah, two of the greats in the same...
Alex Chilton rocking one of his classic songs and me rocking one of the best masks
ever worn by a child.
Man, if only you had wandered out on the stage as Nixon and gun backup vocals on in the street.
It would have been the soy bomb of its day.
This episode is going to need...
Boy, anyone who doesn't remember the 90s well is going to need a glossary to recall
the Big Star and soy bomb.
Yeah.
These references, we apologize to the younger listeners.
But go check out...
Check out Big Star and check out Chris Bell's I Am the Cosmos solo album too.
I've never really listened to it because I'm afraid it would make me too sad.
Oh my God.
It sounds very sad.
I Am the Cosmos is the saddest song you will ever hear.
It is truly like you put headphones on and it is the sound of a heart breaking.
And I don't know if there's any song that I think is sadder than that.
Yeah.
I mean, because I've...
Some of those big stars like Kangaroo, it's very, very morose.
You're really being a state.
That seems like too hard of a drug.
Oh my God.
It's been this year.
Yeah.
Those albums are pretty good, but yeah, 13 might make you a little too introspective for quarantine time.
13 though is like a fun bop compared to I Am the Cosmos.
Yeah, that's a little...
It's a little uplifting.
Yeah.
It's sweet and nostalgic and makes it sad, but certainly like, oh my God, I Am the Cosmos.
It's great.
Anyway.
This episode every year is normally titled Mike loves haunts, but this year it is...
It just gets longer and longer of like the boys love appropriate,
safe Halloween experiences and also are losing their minds.
Have some things to say about Big Star and 24, 26.
Is that right?
Is that math right?
26 year old tonight show episodes?
Yeah, but only the ones I'm on.
I mean, I'll watch some old tonight shows definitely in other contexts.
I've spent a lot of...
I've spent the last couple of weeks watching a lot of 90s MTV movie awards also.
So yeah, I'm off the deep end.
Just audience, be glad that Scott didn't find an organic way for us to talk about the rumor
of McCartney releasing McCartney 3 in December, the long awaited follow up to McCartney 2 from 1980.
Yeah, because then we're in three hour territory.
Yeah.
We're never getting out of here.
But to viewers back here, let's get out of here.
Let's get out of here.
Back here.
Let's get out of Halloween 94 and we'll be back to Christmas 94 soon for the boy choir.
But Halloween 2020, we're stuck.
We got to stay distant.
We got to stay in our cars.
What did we do?
How did we overcome this?
What did we...
How did we all get into the Halloween spirit?
I genuinely don't...
I kind of know what Jason did.
Mike, I don't know.
I'm sorry.
Icepick, I don't know.
Doctor, I'm curious your thoughts about the drive through.
How do we get into it?
Well, I think I'll start with mine.
So there are a variety of things we were talking about that different places are doing.
Varying levels of scares, varying levels of production.
I think everyone's doing it their own way.
I saw Downtown LA has...
And I forget the name of it, but they have a more specific family-focused thing where
they still hand out a bag of candy.
I'm not sure if they do it in the way that Taco Bell does the COVID theater of
having a rubbermaid.
They put the bag in and hand it to you through the window,
which is COVID theater in my estimation.
But they have something like that, I believe.
So everyone's being creative.
Everyone's doing their best.
And I was looking through stuff to do.
And I will say upfront, I should have done something scarier.
Because I...
Look, I'm the toughest one of the three of us when it comes to haunts, okay?
Not in everything else, but haunts, I'm the toughest guy.
And you have to acknowledge my toughness when it comes to going through haunts.
And my love of haunts.
Ice Pick loves haunts.
And the Haunted Hayride...
Now, maybe I was trying to look for an excuse, but the Haunted Hayride is supposedly scary.
They usually do it at Griffith Park and they're doing it in, I believe, San Dimas?
Yes.
Yeah, by the dusty raging waters.
By the shuttered, for now, raging waters unused this summer.
Oh, and Ted's hometown?
In hindsight, I think that probably should have been the thing I did.
But it was 90 minutes away.
And I will say the idea of getting scared of my car did scare me a little bit.
That seems a little more scary for some reason than having just a teen jump out at you from
behind a corner.
You think it's more scary?
Yes, I do think it's more scary.
I would rather be...
I think it's less.
Really?
Because I would rather be walking through, have an ability to move and react.
There's something about it if it's like, I think there's like five teens all crouched
around the car and there's loud music being played outside and they're just going to keep
popping up.
I guess at a certain point you get desensitized to it.
But there's something like that feeling like trap that I don't like.
Do you disagree?
You know what I'm saying?
There's a trapped feeling of like, I can't even control it all and I'm not going to put
my car in a drive and run them over.
I can run faster.
I can hide behind a Valencia teen at Six Flags, but I can't hide behind anything here.
Well, but I think, I mean, you can hide behind your steering wheel.
That seems comforting to me.
You're in the car.
You're hidden.
Yeah, you're in the car.
There's two types.
I guess I could crouch down and put my hands over my head to just not look.
You're right, I guess.
I hear them.
I hear them hitting the window.
Go away.
The scarier stuff from what I've because there's videos of a lot of these online at this point
and like the scenes happen either far away from you or they get close to your car and
you're in park.
Right.
Yes.
Because they can't have you.
You can't be driving and get scared and run off.
Take the wheel and just swerve off the road and run into a bunch of people dressed like
Frankenstein.
Yeah, that's not going to happen.
So anyway, all that to say up front, I did find something that was pretty highly rated
from the way from what I was reading, something called Knights of the Jack.
And this is in Calabasas.
And it was sold out up until November 1st.
And I had to do what I love to do, which is checking to get tickets.
You got to do it.
You haven't done it all year.
I haven't done it in regards to tickets.
I certainly have checked to get NECA Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles action figures, but I
haven't done.
Can you talk about the thing that you did today?
I don't remember if that worked out.
Which thing?
The bot.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So, well, this is a little Scott.
There's a long story.
No, try to make it very quick, low quick.
So basically what was happening is these Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles that I love that
are made by this company NECA.
They go up for presale, or not presale, their main sale.
And it's like, you'd never know what time it goes up.
The target website is confusing.
And the first couple times they put them up, they put up Metalhead, I believe.
And they put up Casey Jones.
These are all the cartoon versions of Ninja Turtles.
They were bought instantly by bots.
And I was just like, I'm good at getting this stuff.
I'm good at checking.
And I was beaten by the machine.
I was beaten by these machines to get these toys.
And this is especially early on in COVID where it's like, I'm not trying not to go
into the stores as much or whatever.
So it happened again.
And I got so fed up, I looked into buying a bot.
I looked into buying a program that could out-bot these other bots.
You were going to create life.
I was going to create a being designed to buy this one toy and then wander the
digital earth for 10,000 years.
I was going to, you know, you had to have a real son, Scott.
I was going to have a digital son that could procure me sweet nostalgic toys.
Your son buys you toys.
And that's all he does.
Inevitably, it would have been a Star Trek situation like Professor Moriarty on the
holodeck where he wants to get out of the computer somehow.
And I'm trying to make that happen for him and he's wreaking havoc.
But it wasn't going to get there yet.
So people, I think also people who deal with this stuff like this happens in sneaker sales
a lot where there are bots.
And I know people are very anti-bot.
So I apologize.
The only reason I was doing this was not to get the toys to flip.
It was just to procure the toys for myself.
I was becoming a bad boy just so I can get my toys.
So I had a guy in Sweden make me a bot.
This has not come up before.
I don't know.
There's a lot of weird stuff in my life that hasn't come up before.
Let's be honest.
I made a guy in Sweden to make me a bot that could get this stuff pretty quickly.
And or in the end, whenever they went on sale.
So the long and the short of it is he definitely worked on it a lot to get it to the point where
it could take me up till like the purchasing screen.
It was never, it never worked perfectly.
It would just auto refresh and then it would load and get me to the main screen.
And I only used it once because then as soon as that, almost as soon as the like next sale went
up, Target kind of fixed the issue.
They'd outsmarted your bot instantly.
Well, they didn't outsmart the bot.
It's just the Target system got better for purchasing these turtles.
So as soon as they were up, they would last for at least like five, 10 minutes,
basically rendering my bot useless.
I paid, I'll be, I didn't pay it.
I pay a hundred dollars for this bot.
So it wasn't like a top of the top of the line bot.
I've been told bots could cost you five grand if they're very sophisticated.
So what is, what do you, what do you, do you ever see anything like what?
Okay.
So if you, okay, if you want to know, there's a program called Python that is a program that
basically can take control of your Google Chrome.
So basically what this does is it's just automatically has certain prompts to put in.
So you get like a text document, you load in what the website will be for the item you want to
purchase. And then you put in like your credit card information, all that stuff,
sort of in a script in a text document. And then you still have to do this.
Yeah. Oh yeah.
Yeah. Coding language.
Like, yes, I had to learn.
I had to learn.
Discover.
I had to learn a little bit.
The Mike's newest discovery is not an obscure movie or band or anything.
It is like a decades old, very basic coding.
It is a coding.
Yeah. So, so essentially, you know, this, this, this nice man in Sweden made me
a document that I could place all that information in.
And then it would load auto load and essentially it would just like refresh the page until the
sale went live and then would load it into the card and go through all the screens.
And that's what it was doing. It wasn't, I look, I wanted it to be like, hello, Michael,
what are we purchasing today?
Another toy from your childhood. What's wrong with you?
He still gives you the business like Dr. Smith and where that robot was.
How about we try, how about instead of spending $25 on this, you try therapy.
I redirected you to a different website, better health.
Wait, better help. What did we read? Which one have we read?
Which one have we read?
They're not paying anymore.
We don't owe them. We don't owe them knowing what the name of it is.
Okay. Wait, so you can't then like reprogram this. You can't now take the bot and say new mission.
You are going to check fast passes within the Disney world app for the, for P for fans of my
show who are lucky enough to actually get to go to a theme park.
No, the bots, this is a thing I learned very quickly. The bot has to be
specifically made for the website that you're using it for just because it's the way every
website is a little different. So no, this is not some, I mean, maybe there's like, again,
there's a $5,000 super bot that can check almost anything, but yeah, this one has to be
specifically programmed for the target website, but I really, I have not used it.
So I wasted a hundred dollars essentially.
What's the bot doing now?
The bot is sitting here on my desktop. He's sleeping. The bot is sleeping.
Also, Scott, don't be ridiculous. There's no fast passes right now.
You got to get park passes. That's what you got to get.
As my family learned, we booked a trip to Orlando a year out. Like, well, let's be optimistic about
the end of 2021. And they assured us in a few days, you'll be able to pick which parks you
want to go to which day. And we're like, ah, we haven't given that enough thought.
When are these park passes in effect to? Oh, the answer to that early 2022.
That system is set up till now.
Oh my God. This thing that I hate about Disney World that other people seem to like where you
have to plan your trip. Now it's literally true. All right. So just think about what you might want
to do 14 months from now. This is, it's even crazier.
Yeah. So, yes, I think that's going to be the way for a little while now.
Probably. Yeah.
Whenever Disneyland opens. Yeah. I think that's probably going to be similar.
But anyway, well, set us up with your Swedish guy.
If the Swedish guy has time to help us and everyone listening to the show, that'd be great.
I will. I will do that. But yes, the bot right now, there's really no need for him.
And yes, look, I look, I was getting desperate. You know, I need these dumb turtle toys.
I just got the rocks. I just got the rock soldiers. They're just, they're
beautiful toys. Do you remember him from Ninja Turtles?
No, he was Crane's rock soldier from Dimension X. His name is General Trag.
I mean, I like him. Yeah, he's great.
What's not to like?
It's great. So I approve. It's wonderful. It's wonderful what you're doing.
Good, good, good.
If this bot lives kind of where you recorded the podcast, right? So he's listening to everything
you're saying and he's heard every episode you've recorded lately. So you could, if anything ever
happened to you, could the bot replace him or replace you? I think that's probably true. I mean,
it's probably like, I don't know who watched Star Trek Picard, but sort of, spoiler alert,
Data's consciousness has been sort of living while Data's been dead. So I think maybe I might,
like everything about me as a person is now stored on the computer in my bot. So there could be like
some sort of epic adventure sort of to go through the internet and retrieve my personality, my whole
programming, if something happens. We could put your personality into
General Trog and he could tell us about Jason. His name is General Trag. Trag Jason. God damn it.
Get it right. Humans make mistakes. Not like your bots. You have to cut out some slack.
Bots can pronounce all the characters names correctly. Granator, Leatherhead, Metalhead.
Trogdor the Berninator. All your faves. I will be known as General Trag from now on, not Ice Pick.
All right. Let's cross that out. Ice Pick General Trag. Okay. So General, let's get back to Knights
of the Jack. Okay. Knights of the Jack. All right. So I saw people talking about this and that they
really liked it. So we drove to Calabasas. I got a ticket. I was checking all day. I did this manually.
This was all brain power, no bot power. And we went, Lindsay and I went last night and we drove
to Calabasas. Nice getting out of the house sometimes. And the Calabasas is around like what's
called, I guess, the Santa Monica Mountains, which I've really never spent too much time around.
They're not particularly nice looking mountains, but it's mountainous and you know, it's got,
there's scenery. So we get there and this was the first round of the night for this experience. It
was 6.30. So I'm assuming like most of these, and you'll tell me if you guys did a similar thing,
you have to drive through this long winding, essentially a queue. And the queue for this
wasn't like full of cars, but it was so long and it was so bumpy. I was like,
are all four of my wheels going to burst? Well, let's put this in context because this is on a farm.
Yes. Thank you. Thank you. It's King Gillette Ranch is where this is located,
which it's normally a walkthrough. It's always a lot of jack-o-lanterns, but it's normally,
I think, a walking, cider, probably cider donuts sort of fall event, Halloween event.
Yes, that is correct. So we're driving through there and I went, is this whole thing
going to be on this terrain? Because I was like, I don't know if this is,
should we just turn off now if this is? And luckily it was not. Luckily, after we got through this
queuing part, it was not so bumpy, but I was pretty worried for a couple of minutes.
I was wondering, okay, are they going to, are they going to, they should have warned us about
this, that we should have brought a Jeep to this. Not the case, not the case. So just telling you
everything. So it's a long stretching thing and we're driving through and we're a little bit early
and we, there's a lot of fun, like kind of cardboard cutouts of monsters and it's very
friendly or whatever. And we see a sign that says tune your radio to 100.1 FM and we go, oh,
this makes a lot of sense. There's probably a soundtrack to go along with this and you play
it on your car. This makes a lot of sense. This is probably what's going to happen here.
So we start driving in and it's, I don't know, has anybody seen, let me, I'll show you,
I'll share the screen real quick just to give you a sort of an idea of what everything's like.
And I have some videos too, and I can post those. So it's like, you know, this is sort of the vibe
we're getting here and this is the website and it's just kind of like, it's very, things are
nicely decorated. There's fun little things there. So we're sort of driving and there's, you know,
displays that are similar to this. There's, you know, skeleton on a motorcycle or whatever and
different pumpkins and, and we're listening to this 100.1 radio station and it's like playing
like Grease Lightning. And we're like, this is really a Halloween song? And then I'm like,
and I'm like, wait a minute. I go, this isn't, this isn't in, this couldn't be in sync because
everyone's going at different intervals. So like, what are we doing listening to the station?
And then also like bad to the bone starts. And like, we're driving through like some like
atmospheric things and we're like, wait a minute, this station is just for the queue area, isn't it?
And Lindsay's like, did I just hear a train noise outside? And we rolled down the windows and it's
like, oh, the audio for the whole thing has been outside for many minutes that we've been driving.
Wait, were you listening to K-earth? Like the old East station?
Yeah, it was just sister golden hair every other song.
So it wasn't the whole time, but for a couple of minutes, because there's this fun, like aliens
have landed in like a pumpkin spaceship and it's like, we're like, well, this isn't the right song
for this. What? And we're like, maybe I go, maybe I should just turn it off and put my own thing on.
And it's like, then we finally, we heard it and we're like, oh, okay, got it. This is what it is.
So then we were finally a lot of hiccups, a lot of confusion. Now we were on a, a even enough road
and we were actually hearing like the music and stuff playing. And here, let me share a couple
videos. Just wait, I can say while you pull those up that I just was curious what the history of
this ranch was. And at one point, Bob Hope owned it and he gave it to the Catholic Church to some
specific order where they ran a seminary, but then it became a seminary for a different thing,
a new age church called the Church Universal and Triumphant, which is some new age, like most of
it's in Montana. It seems to be an outgrowth of Christian science and Mary Baker, Eddie,
like she coined that phrase and yeah, I don't have time to read the article, but you know, some,
certainly people have called it a cult. So it may be questionably something resembling a cult used
to happen here where a pumpkin spaceship has landed, which seems like maybe the like
potential ultimate event of a, what would probably be kind of a fun cult.
Yeah. Yeah. It seems like the land, now that you say that, cause I didn't read that before.
Now that you say that, that makes some sense. Cause there's a lot of interesting buildings
around this location and it's got an interesting vibe without the fun Halloween lights and music.
You go, what is that building? Okay. That looks like, is it, oh, that looks like a church of some
kind, but not really. There is like a weird vibe to the, to the architecture. But they didn't really,
I mean, there's, I guess they, they brought, they put up some like lights on the actual building
itself, but there wasn't any like recruitment or anything happening that I saw. So, so yeah,
here's the, here's the gist of some of it. Okay. So basically, yeah, there's just different little
vignettes. Now you can see the screen here, right? Yes. And some of the vignettes are confusing
because some of them, as I said, aliens, pumpkins, and then it'll just be like Hollywood.
And they're playing the Hollywood song and it's hard. I'll post, I'll post some of this.
And you can see there's a Marlon Brando pumpkin from the Godfather. And it's sort of hard. There's
James Bond or Sean Connery. Now it's hard to cause cause I was driving. So it was hard to like dictate
exactly what I needed to get a video of, but there was also a section of pumpkins for Hollywood
couples. So there was a pumpkin with Tom Hanks and Rita Wilson on it. Cause Lindsey was like,
Oh, Rita Wilson. Lindsey was like, Oh, you have to be really good at pumpkin art to convey Rita
Wilson. It would convey it. I'll say it conveyed it. But Lindsey was like, Oh, are these, are these
like going to be like deceased celebrities? No, no, no. Some of Hollywood's hottest couples in fact.
So yeah. Not Alex Chilton and Chris Bell. Not that I saw, but again, I was driving, you know, I
couldn't, I couldn't focus on everything. So basically, unless I miss something, there are
just a lot of sort of random vignettes. And on the website, it was like, you know, you know, ours,
our drive through is not so scary, but there's some spooky stuff. Unless you're five, there's
nothing spooky. There's nothing. It's fun and atmospheric, but I think I was hoping there was
going to be a little of that. There is a good little section here that I'm going to share with
you now. That's an unlicensed night member for Christmas. And they pump snow and that's very fun.
And yeah, so they do some fun. Is Gosling weighed in on this yet? I haven't seen
Gosling if he weighed in yet. Maybe he's trying to get in all, he probably, you know, he probably
hasn't gotten tickets because he's not as good of a checker as I am. You go into King Gillette
Ranch, you want to, you don't want to see Christmas stuff. You want to see spooky stuff.
My favorite part of it. And I think that they, maybe if I was giving any notes, I would say more
of this, please. Is there a, is an area old west type and there's a spook easy. Yeah. Yeah. See,
like this is a little bit more, I want a little more of that, a little less Rita Wilson. That
would be my note in general. But there's some nice vignettes and I think this is good if you have like
young kids, I'll say that. I feel like a lot of these things are maybe geared to that, which is
good. And you know, a lot of the pricing on some of it was sort of high and you're like, well, if
that, if that, you know, whatever 60 to $90 isn't being spread, it's for people. Right. You're really
getting your value there. And like, I'm showing you something else. These are some really great art,
some really cool looking stuff. Yeah. Cause a lot of this stuff I was reading about it is hand
cart. Yes. So it's like, there's a lot of artistry to it. But just sort of, there's my face you can
see in the corner there with a mask on. They told us we had to wear the mask while the window was
down just to be safe. So in case you were going to make fun of me for wearing a mask.
I know we had a similar experience. Yeah. So, so basically I, I, it is a little bit pricey,
but look, it's a lot of work to put on. You're paying for the fact that you're not doing a bunch
of other Halloween stuff and chances are it would be good if you had a kid. And I just want to tell
everybody the bumpiness doesn't last and do turn off the radio once you start, because I was really
sure we were just going to be listening to like random seventies or eighties rock or going through
it. And I was happy to learn that was not the case. So, wow. Knights of the Jack. Just to go a little
further, the church universal and triumphant was a doomsday cult. It was this one woman, Elizabeth
Claire prophet. She said that the world was going to end in 1990 when Russia and the U S got into a
nuclear war and then that didn't happen. So the cult just kind of Petered out. I think it exists
maybe in some regard, but it got a lot quieter. Also the woman who founded it, everybody, all the
followers called her mother. Well, why isn't the maze about this? Yeah, that would be like,
it's haunted by Elizabeth Claire prophet. This would be awesome. And I'm sure some of these other
mazes have like sort of more narratives, cause I think that's what I would, I would have been like,
yeah, you can make like an interesting story, but yeah, that's that writes itself. You get the
ghost of Bob Hope involved. Selling her the deed. And then yeah, as soon as like the world is about
to end, that's when you exit like, like Mr. Toad. Are you just survived? Yeah. Yeah. Right here. It's
you, you're Reagan and Gorbachev yelling at each other. And that's a period piece. Yeah. You have
teens play Gorbachev and Reagan and they go on the sides of your car,
applying your Gorbachev birthmark paint every night, psyching yourself up to do it again.
I got this. I know this character. So yeah. So, well, there it is. Really fun. Well,
love it. So a doctor, Dr. Murhag thoughts about this year's.
Well, do you want to hear mine or do you want to hear some of the like other parks around the
country? Oh, let's, well, let's do that because we're talking about LA things, but you, it sounds
like you looked into some stuff that our, our friends around the country could maybe check out.
Yeah. I mean, the first, so back in July, I saw an article that I sent to you guys about like,
uh, when I give them credit, it's called the haunted road. It's in, um, Florida, Orlando area.
And they, there was an article in theme park insider. I think a lot of places picked it up
because they were seen to be one of the first ones to say, like, uh, we're going to do a haunt,
but it will, you will drive through it. And, um, uh, I watched some videos of this. Uh, it looks,
it looks very cool. Uh, you know, they, this one is scary, but the scenes are all pretty far away.
Uh, there were some spooky, some ghoulies who got pretty close to the camera person's car and
screamed at the car. Um, but everyone's got mass on, um, they're, oh, there were kids in like glowing,
like those purge mass, like that the characters in the purge where like kind of weird looking mass
like that. Um, uh, it doesn't seem like it, like I said, it's a lot of, maybe people pop up
10 feet away from your car and scenes play out, but I don't think they want to do jump scares
when you're behind the wheel of like a 3000 pound sedan. Um, there's another one in Kissimmee called
scream and stream the, what was interesting about these, uh, was that it's a little off the beaten
path. So it was like pitch black and dirt roads. So certainly adds to the ambience screaming stream
had a giant floating deer skull puppet. Um, and that looked pretty, uh, cool. That looked pretty
insane. Uh, what else sticking to Florida? Bush gardens, Tampa was doing a Halloween event,
just scare zones, no houses. Um, in Chicago, the old Carlson, uh, neck of the woods, uh,
there is a haunt. This is the craziest one I've come across. It's called alley of darkness.
It is a drive in haunt. So you drive in and park, and this is the copy they had on their event.
Our haunt is set in an alley in the shadows of the red line where a horrible incident occurred not
long ago. You'll settle in with a drive in movie experience that sets the narrative, the undead,
the undead, demons, zombies, and more jump out and rock your car accompanied by sound effects
and sprays of blood. That's right. Your car gets covered in blood. You may opt out. Uh,
yes, yes, I do. Our drive in haunted house where you are confined to your car for 30 minutes. So
you can't escape the horror until the end. Uh, and then it wraps up. We cannot remove every drop of
blood. It will be clean enough to drive on the road and you cannot for any reason short of heart
attack, leave your car or open doors or windows. What? This is a lot of terms. Wow. I need to get
some, one of my old friends to go do this or I get like, make my dad, I make my dad do it.
Uh, I have to thank, uh, for any com stock for sending me that they host of the girls like us
podcast, uh, sent me this and it is still the weirdest one I've come across. Wow. Um, no videos
yet of that online, but, uh, yeah, if you're in Chicago and you want a messed up experience,
go for that. That is, that sounds messed up. I don't want your parents to mess up one of their
cars. Okay. It's only going to be a pain for them. Yeah. What if you rent? Well, I'll tell them to
rent a car and then do it. Um, let's see what, and there, so there are some walkthrough,
well, there, there's more LA stuff. There is a walkthrough experience. I forget, um,
on the way to Palm Springs, they like built a house set, but it's all like tarps outside.
Seemingly there's a big strangers things drive through thing that's happening downtown. It's
not happening until like right before Halloween and, uh, it runs until January, but it's the first
like few weeks sold out really quickly, but probably the biggest haunt for our audience
might be interested in is universal Orlando just said, fuck it. We got two houses. And the thing
about universal Orlando is they, uh, up to very, like very recently were full steam ahead going to
do horror nights with some changes to the point where most of the houses were done enough that
eventually they canceled the whole event, but then they did open up the houses, uh, revenge of the
tooth fairy and bride of Frankenstein lives. And you can find videos of both of those online,
revenge of the tooth fairy, kind of a walkthrough, a messed up storybook narrative where a child does
not want to give up a tooth to the tooth fairy. And then everyone starts getting murdered by fairies
and bright up Frankenstein lives appears to be so dark. It will not show up on camera,
but the sounds were very good. Great sounds, great sounds, young quality.
Now that I said all that here is the best thing I have read about any haunt this year. And this
is coming from screamscape who I have to give credit to. We teased them in the past because
they have stuck with their old website, but during, you know, COVID times, their posts have mostly
stuck to just the facts, but there is one rumor that they report it that I have to read aloud
because it is so funny. Um, so one of the rumored houses for Halloween horror nights, uh, there was
a bunch that kind of leaked. The one was going to be haunting of Hill house. One was going to be
themed to the music and persona of the pop star, Billy Eilish. So that house did not go up this
year. And while most of the other houses that are completed, there's very good chance they could just
put on the shelf and put in warehouses and spaces backstage so they can do them in 2021.
I'm sorry, this is still universal, the Billy Eilish, uh, potential experience.
Correct. Yes. So, but screamscape reported that the Billy Eilish house will not end up being used,
should some of these houses get used in 2021. Uh, per screamscape, the reason it won't return in
2021 is that Billy Eilish is personal theme slash branding will be changing to something
not dark before Halloween horror nights 2021 rolls around. So if you're a fan, get ready for
that new personal brand and that's coming to the Eilish household. Wow. Interesting.
She's going to be a sweetheart. She's going to be like Jessica Simpson in 2001. Wow.
We'll just have to wait and see. We'll just have to wait and see. This is confusing.
We already went back and forth on Taylor. She was all about bats and, uh, you know, thrusting.
And then she became about butterflies and colors. I like how do, how are we supposed to keep track
of who's light and who's dark? The Hollywood vampires famously turned into the Hollywood nice
guys and then back to Hollywood vampires. It's so confusing. Well, the sun came up, so, you know,
what are you going to do during the day? Only concerts during the day for a little while.
Right. Yes. Um, that's so strange. Well, that seems like a real, that's a pretty big spoiler
for the forthcoming Billy Eilish output. Yeah, really? Yeah. She's going to try smiling for a
change. You know, it's wrestling. Sometimes feuds are telegraphed. Like they're like, well,
this seems like it's what wrestle the big match with WrestleMania will be this. They're setting
up 18 months out, 12 months out, you know? Sure. All right. Well, prepare for that everyone.
Prepare for that. The only thing we don't know is if we will still be in lockdown by the time
Billy Eilish's new phase is occurring. There's no way to know. Let's hope by the time there's the
smiles and sunshine tour that we could go see it in person and not just from our cars.
Yes, we hope. So, onto my haunt or my age appropriate Halloween drive through experience.
So I went to, um, it was called Haunt-a-ween and it's still going for a little while longer.
It is in Woodland Hills, California. Uh, Mike, I have to say, uh, unlike you, uh, yes, we did
discover roll your windows down to hear the audio. There were a lot more signs
at mine. Uh, the roads were very smooth because this took place in an empty mall parking lot.
Yeah, that's one of my childhood malls. Uh, cause I grew up near that and the Topanga Plaza
and this is the one that died. This is the dead mall of the bunch. Um, but that's like the theater
where I saw, you know, so many classics, Independence Day and men in black and, uh, um,
you know, it was, it was nice and peach colored or really the color that aged really bad. And it's
one of those places where they've started doing weird, like there's like church services in the
AMC now, hopefully not now, but for the last couple of years, I remember there's like parts
of the parking lot that are not safe to go in anymore. Like, I dunno, a bunch of people live
in this garage now. Like it's this, this time has not been kind to the promenade. That is the,
is that the one that has the crown books in it? I always forget. Yes. Yes. Yeah. It's still a
crown books for a really long time. That is maybe one of the most shocking things we met my friend
and his wife there a few years ago at this point. And is there a Maggiano's in there?
That's right. That was still going strong. And the, um, the Maggiano's has the deal where if you buy
an entree, they give you a free one to take home. Oh, you know, my parents are at that Maggiano's
all the damn time. Yeah. They get her. You had a free dinner every time you eat dinner there.
And then we were walking around in this creepy dead mall and we turned a corner and there's a
crown books, a long dead, I thought book chain. So maybe that's the scariest thing in this episode
is that a book chain I thought was dead for years was still operating in this mall.
Beyond the grave. Uh, and it was, it kind of felt also like everything in there was from 20 years
ago. Cause it was a lot of used books, I believe. So yeah, kind of a get them out of here sort of
weird that mall. I'm so delighted. I'm glad they have never, there's been lots of rumors of ways to
re-theme, uh, lots of boring ways to turn this into, you know, boring apartment buildings or sites.
It's going to be boring, whatever it is, but right now it is open and available to do big, weird, like
pumpkin tunnels and stuff. So what would you think? How was it? Uh, it was good. I mean,
they're just utilizing the parking space, the parking, the parking lot. You don't go inside,
you don't drive through the crown books. I wish you drove through. And also there's a big shiny
outdoor mall across the street and like an Amazon grocery store, some sort of drive through dispensary.
I think that was already closed for the night, but we were very confused and interested what that was.
But well, that's the one where we did the weird, that's where we did the, not the void,
but the other one. Yes. The other virtual thing that I assume is doomed due to the current
situation. Yeah. And then we went to my childhood hot dog place, Flukies. Flukies kicks ass. Flukies
great. Flukies episode coming soon. Flukies, thank you. I'm so glad I hear it. Here is guys, so you can see the map of the
events and where the mall is situated versus the drive through experience. You know, I really, we
liked it. I have to say it was pretty well staffed. Like they had a lot of people working
with, you know, those wands, those glowing wands that you direct traffic with.
Everyone was kind of freestyling it with those traffic directing wands. Like one guy was really,
like, he really told us to roll the windows down. It's like, no, this means stop. This means stop.
And then we drove by someone else who was doing a similar motion. I went to stop and they just went,
happy Halloween. And they were just clearly like waving their wand around to celebrate the whimsy.
I ran into a few wand situations as well, right? When is that a come forward or is that a like
scratching your face? So happy people are working, but also like a little stressed out by the other
ones. I also, you know, it did not dawn on me. I mean, just to get here, I had to, I was like,
I haven't driven on the freeway at night in like six months. So that was a bit of a trip.
And then was that okay? Oh yeah, it was fine. It was just like, oh yeah, this is so weird.
You know, I haven't either now, not since I had to go have a baby. That was like,
that's the only time and many, many months. Didn't you go on knots to eat the chicken?
Not at night. I went at like, oh yeah, I guess. Yeah. All right. Wow.
I hadn't thought about how scary it's going to be.
The other thing is like, yeah, as Mike alluded to, like these are very narrow lanes and
especially in a mall parking lot where they've just set up like handrails, they have essentially
made like pen lanes. Like you were driving one to four miles an hour through like car switchbacks,
like, you know, going, snaking around to go through these little scene lets and stuff.
So it was a little stressful, honestly, at first to be like that confined and that going that slowly,
but eventually, don't hit the cones. Exactly. So yeah, I mean, there, it started off with like a big
like Jack-o-lantern tunnel. I'm going to share the screen again, because I have like a bunch of
pictures. So it started off with like a big Jack-o-lantern tunnel and a pumpkin patch.
And there was a, what we do in the shadows tunnel, which I was like, oh, did they record voices? Like,
will the characters talk to you? And I'll just show you, they just kind of bent one of the billboards
that are around LA into a tunnel shape. Yeah, wait a minute. This is just like, imagine driving
through a poster. This was going to be on like a hotel at Comic-Con and they repurposed it for this.
Yeah. So kind of cool to see like a 12 foot high Mark Proshk and a six foot high FX on Hulu logo.
And yeah, I first, so, so then you, you went through a pumpkin patch,
a couple different like pumpkin scenes. There was some, there was a pumpkin patch with like
funny jokes. And then there was this big LA sign with a Kobe Jersey, similar to Mike's Hollywood
sign. Everyone's got the city on the mind. That's kind of weird though. That is weird. Yes.
The Jersey of a deceased. Yeah. We, we, we, yeah, we started off, we started off, I should say,
with like a man and like kind of Joker makeup came up to us and he asked, do you want to play a game?
Are you ready to play? And then he shoved, he shoved a pole with a basket full of candy in
the window and dumped it on Jane's lap. And that became a reoccurring thing throughout the night.
A Joker approached you with a pole and a thing of candy at the end of it.
Oh, no, there were pirates. There were vampires. There were most importantly,
characters from the new HBO Max original, Roald Dahl's, the witches at the very end of this,
there was like, you drove through the town from the witches and they gave out candy, a very funny.
What was your, Jason, what was your hall on the, at this place? This seems like you got a lot of
candy. Yeah, that was the other thing. Cause this, this event was also similarly priced $70. And I
got to give them credit because we thought it was like over. And then it turned out we were only like
halfway through. And so by the end of it, this filled a reusable trader Joe's shopping bag.
So my God, a ton and a big variety. Yeah. Wow. A very big variety. We didn't get candy at all.
And I will say about ours, I thought it was half over and it was actually over.
Wow. But yeah, so this, I mean, there was a skeleton band. There was a scene where the
skeletons were having a party. There was a pumpkin headed man who was just kind of picking up loose.
Hey, I don't know what his deal was. And yeah, trying to remember what other seeds. Yeah. The
whimsical skeletons were very fun. A lot of whimsical music. There was a pirate who kept
like popping up. He would follow, like follow the cars from scene to scene. Very fun. There was a
very fun moment where like one of the guys was dressed as a vampire and Jane realized she knew
them and asked, are you so and so? And he went, yes. Like he kept doing the voice and he gave
us extra candy. We eat. So my God, here's here's a strange and the dog with the dog.
Yeah. The dog just slept on the ground next to the candy.
That was the other thing they didn't really, we should have thought ahead of like they're just
dumping the candy in both our laps. So they kind of had to pick up the floor candy and put it in a
bag to transport it. But it was good. I think all in all, by the time we got in and went through
it all, it was like 30, 40 minutes or so. And they may have had too many people working in the
pumpkin patch because someone almost gave us a second pumpkin. And we're like, no, no, we got
the pumpkin. But you got to pick which pumpkin you want it. Like that was cool. So yeah, I thought
this was really fun. Yeah. Windows down, mess on. And they had fun like Halloweeny music pumping
through everywhere. And it was a really nice time. It's all made so much more surreal. Like you're
describing jokers coming up to you in your car and then it's all like in the shadow of
the long dead Macy's where I would go get my school clothes.
It's just some of the strangest. It's eerie, but comforting. I'm just glad things are happening,
but they're all very surreal to look at. A giant Mark Proch. This is all so strange.
Oh, this is a, this was a skeleton beauty parlor where the skeletons are getting their nails done
and fripped. I like that. Here's the, here's the party. Of course you see they got the big guys,
the Home Depot big guys. Yeah. Thought about getting the Home Depot $300 like 12 foot skeleton.
If I had a front yard, I would absolutely get it. And money also that I didn't spend on a bot.
Yeah, that's true. Yeah. Your, your skeleton money went to the bot. Right.
Well, I, that seems pretty strong. Um, yeah, I would recommend it. It was brought to you by like
sponsored by Butterfinger party city and FX. So you end up with a lot of candy.
FX. I, I don't quite know what material support they provide it, but the party city stuff,
you know, everything's the, the costumes aren't like our night's quality, but everyone was having
a lot of fun who worked there. And it was like spirits were high. Oh, it was spirits were high.
Spirits were high. That said it was 80 degrees at 8 30 PM the night I went. So it was a little weird.
The Woodland Hills is hot. That's true. Yeah. Are you guys comforted as Comic-Con fans?
Are you comforted seeing activations again? Have you missed like the answers? Yes. Big,
big billboards masquerading as experiences. The answer is yes. Uh, missing Comic-Con.
There's been a lot of things that I have. I've expressed outwardly that I've missed,
but I have not expressed that I miss seeing like trains reskinned with a TV show or a movie that
I'll never watch. And I'm not saying that's any of the things you're talking about. I'm just saying
that nine times out of 10, when you see a billboard of Comic-Con, you're never going to see, you're
never going to watch that thing. But I like some weird, it's like a show about like the young
Chronicles of the guy who built Chuckie. It's like some. The maker, the toy maker.
The toy maker. And he's like, why is he this like brooding 22 year old British guy? Why is he
shirtless? Yeah. So hot. The guy who made Chuckie. They're going to go like kind of suggest Chuckie
abstractly in the opening montage, but he won't actually get built until season six. That's right.
It's on Epic TV. You know, you're never going to watch it. You don't even have the means to watch
it. You wouldn't know where to find that available with a map. Of course on the Hilton Bay side,
there's a big poster for Scott's new show Kincaid, the origin story of Ruben Kincaid from the Partridge
family. Oh yeah. Well, thanks for reminding me. I know I got a lot to do. I got to work on Jaws 19.
I got to get Kincaid ready. I'm glad Comic-Con got canceled because I was not ready for my panel.
Yeah. So next year there'll be a 15 story Kincaid poster. I'm really excited. He's hot too,
by the way. I was going to say we found a really great actor to play the Partridge family's manager.
He is 22. He is British playing American and he is oh so hot. Yeah. And you will not see the
Partridge family until season nine. You might get a phone call and you think it's Danny, but you know,
you're not sure it's ambiguous. He drives by a hospital and they suggest Danny was born. He was
just born. You just hear a baby cry. Right. And he goes, oh, and then there's kind of like a little,
he like picks it up and then he tells me I'll be seeing that baby someday. Well, that's all well
and good for you, but due to executive shakeups, I've been brought in to fix Gail, the Dorothy Gail
Wizard of Oz prequel. And I am not optimistic about the chances for this show. It doesn't help
that the star Billie Eilish is changing her whole persona branding. That's totally got overshadow.
Yeah, man. Yeah, she's going to be in persona change meetings from here to 2023. You're never
going to get any time with her. Right. I'm getting no material support from cider, which of course is
the brand new streaming service for Martinelli's apple juice. There are no help whatsoever.
Cider spelled S Y D R.
Sire. It's $14 a month. We've got a launch in the fall. Guys, why aren't you listening? The tie in
the cider seasonal tie. I don't understand. I feel like I'm shouting at a wall.
We're comfortable launching with only long form cider ads. We think we'll build the audience
with that and then we'll give them some original IP. I will say, hey, H.R. Max deserves more credit
because they had witches houses. There are people dressed like the characters. I think I'm not really
that familiar with the book and previous movie, but from the trailers, it looked like the one
character that talked to us in a spooky accent was dressed like an pathways character and they had big
houses and stuff. And so that was fun. I've heard they have another. They have an in your car
experience based on the vow, the Nixxiom documentary where you sit in your car in a big
line for nine hours and nothing ever happens. Well, that you have been taking the producer
role on the producing the documentary about that cult that Mike's Jack O'Lantern festival was used
to. Hell yeah. Yeah, we're in and out after the vow. This documentary is 13 minutes long.
It's going to be jam packed. We're going to plow through it. It'll be a real quick bite. You know,
I've been saying ever since the vow, I have been saying that people want quicker entertainment.
They want their content and quick, quick little bites. Yeah. That's what I'm going to do. Damn
it. I've been on the record about loving quick bites many times. I know we remember famously. So
um, OK, my experience. So there's with me doing any sort of Halloween haunts experience.
There is a lot for me to triangulate to not only the ongoing pandemic, but also my baby's frequent
nap and sleep schedules. And most importantly, me being afraid of haunts of things that occur
in the dark. Even the the things that you guys just showed me seem perfectly pleasant,
but I would always be afraid that around the corner, as Mike said, there were some teenagers
shaking your car or putting blood on it without my permission or a joker with a candy basket.
Get away, get away, get away from the car. You swerve into the mall.
I'm going to go hide in that Macy's, my favorite Macy's. I don't want any of this. I wanted a
different vibe. So that is why considering all of this, I decided from my experience to take a
10 a.m. visit to the Halloween experience at the Citadel Outlet Mall. Whoa.
So this has come up on the show before, but again, for the non Los Angeles people,
if you're if you're driving on the five to or from the five freeway to or from Disneyland,
this is probably the most like notable site of your trip to Knott's Berry Farm or Disneyland,
because suddenly after a bunch of really industrial boring stuff, there's suddenly this giant,
what looks like an ornate Middle Eastern palace. Or I've also said it kind of looks like a Mario
Fortress. Like it's like it's like a level eight. And first of all, neither here. I mean,
we could do an entire we'll do the that was one of the keepers we met, I believe was the Citadel
guy who sounded like a real drag. But this was apparently a former tire factory.
If you were I don't know why I'm saying this. Now, why does it look like a Middle Eastern palace?
Well, because it was a tire factory. You see, doesn't really answer it. And then I just remember
Aaron and I went there a long time ago and we were like, whoa, so it's themed. So it all looks it's
all this Assyrian vibe. That sounds crazy. And then we went back there and it's all just behind that
big building. And it's like the most boring place you've ever been. It's like it's like there's a
lot. There's a couple of them all that like inside look exactly the same that on the way to Palm
Springs. Like they all feel like they're in the same. Yeah, yeah. Camarillo like that. That might
just be what all they all of them are. They don't you're not paying for theming. It's as bare bones
as it could be. I guess that's what an outlet mall's all about. So I have criticized this place for
dullness for not delivering on the promise of the Assyrian palace that you see from the freeway.
But for Halloween, let me tell you, it's a whole different story. I brought the whole family,
I can say and thus making this probably the first themed experience that my son has been to. So
that's a that's a big moment. Yeah, pretty exciting. So over by the food court, there is
their main claim to the big thing that they are boasting about up on those those video billboards
that we know from our Disneyland drives that we never get to do anymore. And they're advertising
up on those big Jack, who is the largest pumpkin in Los Angeles. Wow. So they say I wonder if they're
allowed to make that claim, partially because the big jack-o-lantern Mickey is not available for
public consumption at Disneyland. So maybe in another year, they couldn't say it. Although,
I saw big Jack, and he's pretty big. Jack might be bigger than the than the Mickey.
Big Jack is 16 feet tall. He's 15 feet wide. Yeah, he weighs 1500 pounds, and he's surrounded by 40
plus bales of hay. That doesn't feel as special. Now you guys showed me so much hay. I think you
everybody saw a lot of hay. Anybody. Anybody going any of these haunts will see a lot of hay. So if
you're a fan of hay, this is your year. Big Jack is also surrounded by a spooktacular garden of
giant sunflowers and candy corn. And this is one of those. So, all right, this is this little cutesy
experience. And in another year, I might have been more, where I'm going to the immersive theming
of an actual theme park. And pre-having a child, I might have been like, oh yeah, so they got
like sunflowers. Those probably look stupid, right? It's fun. They try something. I don't know.
This was to me in my current state breathtaking. This was wonderful. It was great. It was wonderful
to see big things, big cartoony cloth things. My boy like stood and like stared into the flower and
and held it and was one of the most fascinated I've seen him be in something. Like he did register
this is something different. So now I am like, bless you, spooktacular garden. Why would I ever
have been snarky about this before? Thank you for entertaining my boy. We then proceeded to do the
experience that, you know, they don't want people to go in and just be see Big Jack and leave.
They want you to go explore the many offerings of the outlet mall, which is pretty much open.
So that's why there's an activity called Let's Track Jack and his friends. And this I like
because there we got some original IP involved. You go to like a visitor's center,
past a bunch of brochures, and they give you like a map of the mall and then stickers of all of the
characters that you might meet and their names and you have to go look for them. Now, if you
plan on doing the Citadel tracking Jack and his friends, you might want to hit the skip button a
couple of times because I'm going to spoil some locations for you. But Kitty Cat was at Michael
Coors. So if you're looking for a hint though, also just go to Michael Coors. That's one of the
12. You got to find 12 friends. Mums with a Z who is a mummy was outside of Ruby's, which is a
chain that I am shocked has not gone bankrupt during the pandemic. Somehow they've made it.
And then best of all, Skelly the Skeleton was outside of the Rocky Mountain Chocolate Factory.
Rocky Mountain Chocolate Factory, the home to Truffles, the large sad bear who we love so much.
Aaron, we've talked about this and God bless our audience. Our audience has now posted a lot and
sent us a lot of photos of them comforting Truffles, the sad bear who needs some emotional support.
I've loved seeing all these. Please always keep them coming. But a lot of Truffles live indoors.
So we haven't seen Truffles in a long time and we've been at home taking care of the boy.
So rounding it, realizing, oh my God, that's a Rocky Mountain. Is he out? Is he out? Oh my God,
Truffles is out. He was wearing a mask and a confusing, I'm sorry, a mask, not like a
Halloween mask, but the, you know, that we all have to wear because of the disease. And also a
confusing costume that was like a cape and a necktie once. I didn't really know what they were,
but I, and it's, you know, hanging off of them weird and bad, but I would expect
nothing less from my buddy. I might as well screen share. You can take in this wonderful site.
We got to introduce my boy to our favorite bear who, by the way, for a long time, I've said this
before, this will be his first Halloween costume of his life as being the sad bear. Aaron was so
happy to see him. I was so happy to see him. This was truly heartwarming. He, as you can tell,
he's very excited. He's very, he's as invested as us. Not certainly not just looking off somewhere
else. You should see, you should see Big Jack too. Just tell me what you, do you think this?
I was going to say, can you go back to the picture or the closeup picture of Truffles
real quick? And I'm going to make a really disgusting comment. Yes. I might know where
you're going. What's your observation about Truffles? The mask that's like clinging tightly to
his snout. It definitely looks like the lower half of Borat's yellow swimsuit with his testicles
being stared. His mankini. Yeah, there you go. That's sort of the, I just get a vibe from that.
That's just me though. He probably needs to wear a bigger mask, probably to get the full coverage,
but I'm glad he's trying. Truffles is always sad and in this trying year, I just hope he doesn't
have it even worse. Though how could it get worse for him? He just seems so glum, no matter what.
He's sadder than Eeyore. So we always like to stop by and make him feel a little better. I believe
we may have done this. I think Aaron did this without touching him because germs and all,
but you could still lend distance support. I thought you were going to, when you said
disgusting, I thought you were going to comment on the multiple stains on his shirt. I mean,
that's gross too. Yeah, it's not ill fit. Also the tie reads, trick or treat, be so sweet,
give me something good to eat. Be so sweet. And then the tie is also stained. Well, with chocolate,
he is a hungry boy. He's a grown boy. He's named after chocolate or treats at least.
What do you think of Big Jack here? I mean, yeah, he's great. Yeah. I like him. Pretty huge. I
think maybe bigger than that, Mickey, right? Yeah, maybe a little by a little bit. It's interesting.
Obviously without comparison to where they're both located, it's kind of hard to tell.
Yeah. Yeah. But you know, it satisfied me. I also liked that one, here's one of these big sunflowers.
Really impressed my boy. And I liked that it was in front of a flip-flop shop. One of our flip-flop
shops, plural. One of the, you know, an old fallen brother, which we just found out is no longer at
City Walk. Does this count as a Citadel saga? I mean, if this knocked it out, I'd be thrilled.
I can't remember who the keeper of that was, but perhaps we'll ask them. We can, yeah, yeah,
somebody can text that particular keeper. Will you, for one Halloween, have your child be Richard
Nixon? Well, I do have the mask. I may have thrown away the mask at some point. I don't know. You
know, after my whole life's story of being really into presidents and, you know, and then how
how insane and damaging the last four years have been. I think I'm going to keep my son away. I'm
going to keep him away from the idea of presidents as long as possible. Like until he's confronted by
photos of them in a classroom, I'm going to pretend they don't exist. I'm not going to say the word.
That's fair. Seems like a planet. He's just looking at like a white pumpkin. This is,
I can't tell you how much this warms my heart. My overall, my summation of all of this,
this we we did this in less than an hour. It was definitely a little mundane. It took place at a
place I just called specifically not very well themed. And it is without a doubt the best thing
I've done in 2020. Our spirits soared. Even we miss driving to Disney. We miss that bad drive.
Oh, yeah. What's the 710 and is the 10 crowded today? And like, we got to get over.
The interchange is on the left this time. We miss all that. We haven't got to do it with the kid.
So even like driving halfway to Disneyland, we were like a glow leaving this outlet mall.
Oh, and I forgot the detail that if you track Jack and his friends successfully, that your prize,
there's a number of them, but you can get a free soda at Charlie's subs. You can get a pretzel at
Auntie Anne's. Pretty good prizes. Not so good for my little Jack Tracker who cannot have any of
those items. The only prize they could have offered that would have made us go do the whole thing is
just is three ounces of smelly formula. That would have like, oh, real well, his favorite,
his favorite treat. But did your child turn to you at any point and go like,
since we're halfway down the five, can we just go to downtown Disney?
They've set up a limited time shopping experience in stage 17 and we can get our picture under a
play it side. That's when I was coming into this realm, a spirit whispered to me a ghostly boy
spirit. He was full of youthful enthusiasm, just like me, Papa. He said, please take your boy there
so he can live. He can walk in my footsteps. The Disney outlets at the Citadel outlet
reopened a few months ago and there was lines around the block to get that discounted park
merchandise, that clearance, like grad night that never happened merchandise. Here's the thing about
the outlet malls. They're not really outlet malls. It's all this big scam. This is how I feel. This is
the end of the episode, I'm guessing. But like I've been in those Disney outlet stores and there's
like a little clearance section, but everything else is regular price. Yeah, it's not cheaper
there. It's not cheaper in most of these stores. There was a day. I think there's like two in
Orlando that are like really, really dirt cheap clearance stuff. Well, that's a different thing.
They closed the one in California. Yeah. But there is one in Orlando, I think maybe still,
that actually has cheap discounted stuff. But yeah, these outlet stores by and large,
not much different than a regular store. There was a day we were driving back from Disneyland,
maybe. I don't know if we did an overnight or something. I think we had just ended up driving
back like on Black Friday or the day before Thanksgiving or something. And the traffic was
unreal. I mean, it's always really bad around there, although not currently because no one's
going anywhere. But like it was so awful one day and we were like, wait a minute, is this like
pre Black Friday at the outlet mall? And indeed it was. And once we passed it, it was so crowded.
There were police everywhere directing. Like this was, you know, like a Coachella audience had
descended on this outlet mall. And for what? For slightly cheaper flip flops? I guess. Yeah. I,
I, you know, I feel like I went in an H&M, which has cheap clothing. It's the same. It's the same
price. It's fooling. It's fooling us. Yeah. I've never been fond of this place. I have to say
until now, until they gave us this wonderful, less than an hour until they showed us big Jack.
I mean, I will always, I'll always have a different view of this place from now on. They
made Halloween real special, maybe even in a way, if it's possible, more special than the one that
I spent with Jay Leno and Alex Chilton. Wow. Well that's, I mean, you just said it all.
I tied it all back to the beginning. I guess that's the point where you end the episode and say,
you survived haunt cast the fright local haunts edition. Here's hoping that next year we can
go back to the way it's supposed to be getting screamed at by teens. Yes. And that Mike can go
have the Halloween that he wants and the Jason and I can have essentially the one we are currently
having where we stay. I, I'm working on Jason though. What do you think, Jason, will you declare
one that you'll go to at least one of these with me next year? Are you willing to? This was supposed
to be the year. This was like, all right, I'll go to universe. I'll do the polished one. You know,
I'll do, I'll, I'll, the polished one. No, they're like high budget, like, you know, it has the most
liability insurance that that's the other thing I thought about all these drive-through haunts,
especially the small ones. What, what must that liability insurance be? And here's a
300 cars a night and a bunch of people directing traffic who just learned how to do this a week
ago. Good luck. All right. So Jason will be at Horror Nights next year. I'll do it next year.
Done deal. And, hey, as for us next week, hey, we know what's happening next week. There's only
one topic it could be. It's the topic that we are parsing through as slowly as possible,
as slowly as driving through a pumpkin tunnel bumper to bumper. We're heading back to the Haunted
Mansion next week. I, I don't know. I guess we usually don't say it, but you know, we, we know
what week it is. We know what we're doing. Get pumped up. I'm going to go back and listen to the
previous episodes because my memory has been destroyed this year and I don't know where we
left off. So I figured it out. So I know how to kick it off and it's, I think, I think we'll be
fine. How far will we get? Only time will tell. And I'll obviously go to the Cemetery Gate,
the Patreon for the bonus content where we've had, I think two of them have come out and we got one
more spooky episode for the month before we go back to the regular second gate. And that's,
of course, at patreon.com slash podcast, the ride. Hey, and Merchant T public. Oh, we got,
we got a Haunted Mansion, or a Haunt Cast the Fright design for shirts and other things. I
use your imagination what it could be on. And yeah, that's that. It's been a fun month.
So for myself, Rick Zombie Berg, Dr. Murder Hog and General Trag.
What does General Trag say? Well, you have the last word. He says, we have to stop those neutrinos.
All right. So stop the neutrinos in your life. Stop the metaphorical neutrinos
by plundering this country by voting vote those neutrinos. I forget every
The neutrinos were Scott. They were those three like space 50s, like kids that like
were hanging out with the Ninja Turtles. I'm sure you would notice you would recognize them.
Michelangelo. They're not wait. Are they not bad? No, they're good. Oh, shoot. Oh, never mind.
Vote for the neutrinos. Oh, God, vote neutrinos. Get neutrinos in the White House this year. Yeah,
for sure. All right. Thanks for straightening me out of General Trag. And we'll be back next week.
Happy hunting.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo, and Alex Ramsey. For more original podcasts,
please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts,
Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts. Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following
us on Twitter and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.