Forever.
Dog.
Warning.
The following podcast and this warning were recorded right before the 2020 election.
You listener are hearing this on Friday.
And no matter where things are at by then, we truly wish we could all process the news
by doing one thing.
Drinking at Disneyland.
Kate Raft helps us rosé the day away on Podcast The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, hosted by, well, at least one guy who today is talking about
the thing he misses literally the most on earth.
That being drinking at Disneyland, I'm Scott Gardner, I'm that guy.
Mike Carlson, I don't know where it lands on your list but I'm sure it's on it.
Mike Carlson It's on it.
It's a nice little parsley on the plate, certainly, but it's maybe not.
It's not the main course.
I don't know.
I want to say it's better than parsley.
Parsley is really superfluous.
Dr. Josh Birk It's not bringing a lot to the table.
It's like mashed potatoes, a good solid mashed potatoes with butter on the plate.
You don't need it, but oh, you're so excited to have it when you're eating dinner.
Mike Carlson Sure, sure, sure.
Not the primary course, but it's there and it's doing its part.
Jason Sheridan, meal analogies or whatever.
Jason Sheridan What was that?
Mike Carlson Meal analogies or however you feel.
Jason Sheridan I'm just marveling at the upgrade from parsley to mashed potatoes with gravy
and butter.
Very skyrocketed up the charts.
Yeah, I mean, I like it.
I feel like in quarantine, I've become practically a teetotaler, not by any choice, just because
it was depressing me or just putting me to sleep.
Jason Sheridan What's teetotaler?
Mike Carlson Like doesn't drink.
Jason Sheridan I see.
Mike Carlson I think I've had a couple glasses of wine and some white claws and that's been
the extent of it.
Jason Sheridan Well, because, you know, sitting in your place and drinking is not as exciting
as wandering around a space, you know, breathing fresh life into this themed environment that
you love to go so much.
You know, that's the way to do it.
That's the way to consume alcohol.
It's not stuck on your lonesome.
Mike Carlson Yeah, at the Uva bar outside at 3pm on a weekday afternoon.
Jason Sheridan Hell yes, the greatest.
I should say that this topic comes courtesy of our guest who is from the podcast Hot and
Rich the podcast.
This podcast is self care and from Jack AM.
Please welcome Kate Raft.
Kate Raft Hi guys.
Thanks for having me here.
Jason Sheridan Thanks for coming.
Kate Raft I love drinking at Disneyland.
So this is a passion of mine.
Jason Sheridan Is it a meal like for you?
Is it mashed potatoes?
Is it a different type of food on the plate?
Kate Raft I feel like I would say it's like the appetizer.
It's the appetizer.
It's a tasting menu of alcohol.
It's like you have to pair it with every aspect of Disneyland.
I would say it's like, you know, it's a hearty appetizer.
Jason Sheridan Oh sure.
It can eek into dinner that can make you have to order a smaller dinner.
Kate Raft Exactly.
Like a too big appetizer.
Like wings maybe.
Jason Sheridan Oh sure.
That can be sort of inconvenient if you also order the bigger.
Kate Raft Right.
It's like a wings appetizer.
Jason Sheridan Or like a sampler with like the wings and the mozzarella sticks and the
potato skins and you're like, well I want a little of each and it's like, oh I feel
disgusting as the entrees.
Kate Raft Right.
It's like jalapeno poppers too which like you didn't really want but they're in the
platter so you try a couple and it's heavy.
Jason Sheridan Those appetizer hangers on.
The ones that like would not fly on their own.
But they know the right friends to get into the appetizer party.
Kate Raft Exactly.
Jason Sheridan Yeah that makes a lot of sense.
I think depending on like Kate would you say when you go to Disneyland it's like is this
a like how do you do it?
How do you structure your day?
Kate Raft Okay.
So like I've had many evolving eras of drinking at Disneyland because I am from Southern California
so I used to go a lot as an underage person and that so that routine is different than
my current drinking routine.
So I guess I should start with the past and just quickly say that I used to bring like
we would get diet coke bottles and fill them with whiskey and bring them and like go to
the bathroom and like chug whiskey and like do like shots of it and then go on rides as
like teenagers.
And it was so disgusting but it was really a big part of my life.
Big part of my youth.
Also sometimes like buy sodas in the park and then secretly they go pour a little flask
into it.
That was our method.
It got really elaborate where I would like sneak alcohol in in new and fun ways.
So there was this one time where I put a flask of whiskey inside a flaming hot Cheetos bag
and I made like a fake lunch that I packed like a banana into like stuff I wasn't even
going to eat but just so that if I had to open my bag or you do have to open your bag
so they would just see lunch and not a flask and it worked and it was great.
Oh yeah.
Now looking back are you like was this overkill?
Was this more about the thrill of the chase?
Definitely didn't need to do all of that.
It was not necessary.
Sure.
But fun.
Super fun to do.
Covert operation.
So fun.
But I would say like my current thing I love just like a rose starting off with a rose
in California Adventures.
I like the Lestel Rose that they have there.
It's like the cheapest one.
It's great.
Now which are we talking about from that like outdoor from that like Napa area you order
at the counter.
Yes.
The counter.
Or is this a sit down situation?
The counter is where it's at.
I like that.
I also like to go to Carthay, circle the bar there and have like whatever their seasonal
cocktail is they have like different ones for like different holidays.
So like the Halloween one is like some apple cider old fashioned type thing.
That's pretty good.
I don't think I know about the seasonal ones.
They have a Christmas one too I think.
Do you get different like are there like non drinkable decorations in these typically?
Yes.
I still have them in my freezer.
The Halloween one has light up pumpkins that they put in.
Little mini little jack-o-lanterns that they put inside the drink.
It's great.
Yes.
I have had this drink and you do get a little plastic keepsake.
Or is it a skull?
It might be a skull actually.
I can't remember.
I think it is a skull.
I think it's like a melted little skull or it looks like a candy apple skull kind of
a thing.
Yes.
You get a lot of, I feel like Disney does a lot of, you get a little toy with your alcohol
sometimes.
That's a nice thing about Disney.
I love that.
For the children.
I mean I feel like Disneyland is not for children personally.
I feel like it is for the drinking aged adult.
And I'm fine.
Do you think it's like better even for the drinking aged adult than a child?
I feel like yeah.
I mean I don't have children.
So who's to say if I'll change my mind on this if I ever do.
But I think it's like it rules to be a childless adult.
I know there's so many people that talk shit about childless adults who go to Disneyland
and get drunk.
But I have to just own that that is what I am and it's what I enjoy and fuck off.
Okay.
I'm going to get wasted and buy like a $20 cocktail that comes with a toy and then I'm
going to keep the toy as a memory of my fun joy.
Hell yes.
And who are you hurting with this?
Is there anyone making this observation?
I'm always curious like how does this affect you?
Why is this bothering you?
Why are you raining on many parades?
People hate to see just like, people really hate to watch someone like piss their money
away.
And Disneyland is so expensive.
I think that just upsets people that it's just like a hemorrhage of money that you should
be spending it on a child, not your selfish adult self, I guess.
I don't know what it is.
I think it's like, I think that generationally as you go back the generations, I think you
know early and earlier when you were growing up you would have to shed anything you liked
as a kid.
You'd have to cut that off.
Yes.
You'd have to cut off anything you liked as a child.
Like 80 years ago it was, at 13 years old you cut it off, you don't like it.
Then it maybe moved up average to like 15.
And we're maybe like in the first generation where a good majority of people have not let
it all go.
So now we're incorporating an adult, an adult element into another fun thing we enjoy as
children.
Yes.
Which is nice, honestly.
As long as you're being, as long as you're not hassling children, I'm not like, I don't
have a jug of moonshine and I'm hassling some kids.
I'm just, I'm enjoying a nice buzz while I'm walking down Main Street.
It's lovely.
Yeah.
That's great.
And I think it like, it's a way to refresh the experience.
If you've been there a zillion times and you need ways to make it new, then different alcohol
pairings kind of help make it new and also kind of give you the like fuzzy swirliness
that you probably had when you were a little kid and didn't understand what it even was.
You know what I mean?
It like, it's, I don't know.
Like it's, yeah, it's, it's, it sets you back.
Like you feel like a three year old.
Yeah, you got to, you have to kill enough brain cells that you're like as dumb as you
were as a child.
And then yeah, you start to question the reality.
You start to question if like maybe one of the pirates is real.
Exactly.
Which I guess would be an argument for doing drugs there because which we are, we do not
typically do.
Kate, I don't know if you know this, we're good boys.
We're very good boys.
Yes, I know that.
We follow our...
I know that about you.
Everyone says that about you guys.
Sure, sure, sure.
Yes.
Oh yeah, yeah.
No, that's...
Sure.
If you ask just general reputation, that's the answer.
I think what if we had to go by each of us when we had our first drink of alcohol, it's
over 20 for all of us, right?
Or no?
No, no, no.
No, I started like 17, 17.
Pretty good, Jason.
I think I had a shot at a college party at like 19.
Okay, I'm the old...
I think I was at least like 20 or 21.
Wow, okay.
I think it was 20.
Wait, this is new information that's going on.
Yes, it is.
Very wholesome.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I had my first beer with my dad on my 21st birthday on the outdoor patio of the rainforest
the now closed rainforest cafe at downtown Disney.
Wow, oh my God.
Wow.
That was your first legal drink?
Was it the rainforest cafe?
I think that was my first...
Now that you say that, yes, I think that would technically be my first legal drink.
And it was the thing with the shortest wait.
He was visiting for the weekend and it was probably 60, dropping to 50 as our meal regret.
It was miserable weather in October.
This October, it's 90 degrees in Los Angeles.
That October, it was the appropriate fall weather.
You know what that makes me think of?
I don't want to sidetrack too hard here.
Scott and I saw a concert a couple years ago, a Mr. Ben Folds.
And there's a song he has, he wrote a song, Still Fighting It, about his son who had just
been born and he talked about how he was going to have his first beer with his son when his
son was older.
And I believe Ben said he had the beer with his son that night at the concert.
Oh, that's cool.
If I remember correctly.
Or if you're a fan of him, you certainly know that line.
And then we're like, everybody's like, that line, it happened this evening?
I love that.
I believe so.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, you better believe I listened to that song and thought about having that moment
with my son who's a baby right now.
And so maybe...
How long can we push it off?
Maybe it'll be like 14.
Does that seem like appropriate?
All right, great.
Celebrate him starting high school.
Are you going to do it at the rainforest?
Oh, I guess it's not there anymore.
But are you going to do it at downtown Disney?
It's closed.
Oh, it seems pretty likely, right?
Given the history.
Yeah, the uva bar.
The uva bar.
Yeah, uva bar will outlive us all with that funky 90s font.
I will say that uva bar was also a big part of my drinking routine for a while.
I think before, they used to only have beer and wine for a long time at California Adventures,
right?
Or they had other stuff, but it was always really...
They would serve really weak margaritas or something.
This was probably 10 years ago or something.
I think they've always had margaritas over by the Wharf, that area with the Chinese food
and with the Mexican food.
I feel like my friends and I decided that those margaritas weren't strong enough, so
we would leave California Adventures, go to the uva bar and each take double shots
of tequila and then run back into the park and be slightly more buzzed.
Yeah, I think that it just is a rule of thumb for drinking tips, I guess, at Disney.
In park, fruity, colorful drinks don't have as much alcohol.
You probably should go to an actual bar to get the full alcohol content for a drink.
Because I think, yes, oftentimes it's just covered by sugar.
And that, of course, doesn't bother me that much.
But if you're looking for an actual full shot of something in a drink, I think your best
bet is the bar somewhere, an actual bar.
It's very clear in my mind at a time Mike and I went down on a Friday, early evening,
and went to the mad tea party bar stand.
I think we ordered mojitos and I watched them pick up what looked like a milk jug and dump
it over ice in the cup.
And then they plopped the plastic light up ice cubes on top.
And I was like, oh, the drink was already mixed in the jug.
This is what we just paid $16 for.
Yeah. Jason, are you talking about the mad hito?
Because I think that's what you're talking about.
It was not a regular mojito.
It was a mad hito.
I'm looking at the menu right now.
The madness comes from even a lightweight like me felt nothing from that drink.
Yeah.
And I think it's probably wise to have...
Because those are the spots where people are probably consuming the most alcohol.
So it's probably wise to give everybody, most people less.
That is probably smart.
Disney has stumbled upon the best way to control drinking.
You just charge an arm and a leg for everything.
And even partyers will call it at a certain point.
Although Mike and I also were at the Steakhouse 55 bar once at the Disneyland Hotel.
And the older couple next to us were really tying a few on and talking about getting back to Pasadena.
And I was like, oh, I am worried about this.
Yeah.
Yes, that was scary.
I remember that. That was too intense.
And you guys offered to drive them back.
Well, we did. Jason and I drove them back.
And then we came back to Disney.
It was unclear to whether they were husband and wife, brother and sister, what their relationship was.
If they wanted Jason and I to join them for a quad, a quad, is that what you call it?
I guess that's what you would.
Yeah.
Yeah, a Pasadena quad.
It was a real chaotic energy that night.
They were just hoping you had a hotel and that you might set like,
do you guys want to, if you want to just relax a little before that drive or not drive home at all.
If there was a like a free hotel room, he could have spent some time in, Jason would have done it.
You know, I never look a bargain in the eye unless they turned and was like,
can you get us a lift? We're staying at the Knott's Hotel up the road.
Oh, but then Snoopy could join for a be a fifth.
Well, that's true.
That's an Anaheim quad.
I mean, Buena Park.
Buena Park.
Well, you're discussing Anaheim quad and then it becomes a Buena Park quad.
Yeah. Or Quint, if Snoopy.
Quint.
Becomes a Buena Park Quint.
Right. That's absolutely right.
So Mad Hito's.
We're talking about Mad Hito's.
So, yeah. So Kate, your Rose seasonal cocktails, do you are you're not probably as insane as we are about,
like, knowing all the maybe like spots to do stuff, but you go to the hotels.
Do you ever go to Trader Sam's?
I do. I know. I know most of the spots as well.
I mean, like I'm a theme park person like you guys, you know, I mean, I didn't mean to insinuate you.
I'm in the trenches in the trenches, finding the hotels to drink at, you know,
depending on where you park, which parking lot you get shoved into, there's different options.
But I love Trader Sam's and Trader Sam's is like where I go at the end of my way home,
like like the end of the day with like a tiki drink at Trader Sam's.
It's always so fun.
It's like when you order certain drinks, like certain animatronics, it's like very rainforest cafe
because they have like little shows that happen in the in the bar, like little like thunderstorms and shit like that.
Like it's the best.
But like an intimate rainforest cafe, like a little more like like
a crafted black box theater version rather than a broader.
Yeah, if you order the shipwreck, that's what a volcano erupts.
And then there's that drink that you have to get.
It's like I forget what it's called, but it's for like four people and it has like a fire
and you like flick cinnamon into the fire or something.
Have you forgotten that?
I know what you're talking about, but I can't think of the name of it.
And it comes in the big like ceramic and I forget what it is.
I got a version of it in Orlando and I got the Nautilus, the Nautilus, I guess, cup, you'd call it
that it came with and I have it. It's on the mantle downstairs.
I know the cup.
It's like a punch bowl. Yeah.
But that yeah, Trader Sam's is really, how can I say to make myself not sound so lame?
Very special.
It's very special.
It is very special.
And yeah, it's it's it's a great end of the night.
They also have stuff like during the have you ever seen this during the holidays?
The volcano erupts and snow comes out the top of it.
Wow. I had no idea.
That's incredible. That's incredible.
That's art. Yes.
Be there. That's art.
I'm sure they're I mean, they have a whole outdoor thing.
But you wouldn't get them.
You wouldn't get the experience if you sat outside.
Yeah. The outside is nice if the weather is nice.
Yes. Sitting outside is not bad.
You can hear the music.
But you don't get the show.
There'll be a performer outside playing some flamenco guitar.
And they've expanded the back area now to have more drink service,
which Jason and I enjoyed while we were crashing the Theo Awards last year
or attempting to the theme park awards.
And there was just a bunch of people in dresses and tuxedos.
And then Jason and I like roaming around,
roping around, hoping to get noticed like two losers.
By hoping to get noticed by non famous.
Yes. Not by no way.
Solidity like internal theme park industry.
Yeah. Now, yeah.
Like somebody like an accountant that works for the Walt Disney Company.
We were hoping maybe listen to one episode.
And looks at the Twitter to know what we look like.
There's two there's two factor there they have to follow.
A lot of steps to this plan anyway.
Steakhouse 55K.
Have you been? I haven't been.
Is that that's the one in the Disneyland Hotel?
Yes. Yes. And I have not actually been to the main restaurant,
but they got a little lounge going there and you can order off the main menu
and you also can get get drinks there.
And they those those are actual drinks.
That sounds great. Yeah.
I've been to the one at California at the Grand Californian.
They have like a lounge bar there.
I've been to that one.
Yeah, the Hearthstone Lounge.
I'll toss that out as like a dark horse favorite pick
because it's usually pretty empty.
And you can also just order a drink there and then just take it into the lobby
and sit on one of the big lobby.
This is the massive California Grand Californian lobby, often empty
and a very nice place to enjoy a drink.
But what's the sight of one of the most upsetting things?
I'm remembering this now.
I did that trick once and I witnessed one of the most upsetting things
I had seen on a Disney property,
which was someone just put a baby down on the couch
and started changing the diaper on the couch.
And I can see the bathroom.
I could see the entrance to the bathrooms like 20 feet away.
And I'm just like sitting there, just like holding a nearly finished beer.
And I'm like, OK, I'm going to finish this and get the hell out of here.
Wow.
Scott, that was the traumatizing event.
Sorry, Scott, you have a baby like, is that normal?
To. Well, I don't know, because I've never been in public. Right.
This is not an option in the current time that what flesh to me, though,
is that you might, you know, like there's there's been the change of tide
where like, you know, if you gave side eye to somebody breastfeeding a baby,
that would be weird, like because we've accepted that happens in public.
And but changing a bit,
nobody finds anything like beautiful about changing. Yeah.
This is not like, yes, do it to wherever you please.
The fact that I was like finishing a beverage, maybe having a snack
and like other people around were eating and there's just like, ah, waste.
Hello. Human waste is fecal matter.
Yes. Very good.
OK. The thing making it is.
Did you see it? Did you see the shit? Did you see the baby shit?
I did not know.
You know, I looked away.
I looked away too quickly.
When I was that was my question, Kate, as well.
I did not want to know if you didn't see it, then, you know, it could have been.
Were you know, it's not it.
It definitely could have been.
Downplay your trauma, because like that is trauma.
What you went through.
I'm not. I was.
Yeah, I'm not so offended by somebody doing it in public,
but the idea that like a piece, a piece might fall out easily.
Yeah. And that's.
Well, this is again, I having been around a lot of baby shit.
I think you're not really dealing with pieces.
It's a little more. Yeah, you're right.
It's a little more squishy.
One. Yes. Like semi solid.
It'd be strange.
And if the piece like we're able to like roll or bounce or get near your beverage,
that seems like beyond.
I mean, it's just a little chaos where like I should have said, like, hey,
if you want to go to the band, I'll watch your stuff if you want to go like.
You would say that.
No, I know.
No, I just extricated myself from if they had said, like, hey,
can you watch our luggage and just go to go change the bait?
But then also like, well, at that point, why wouldn't you just have the bag?
Man, they're just cast members everywhere.
I don't know. It was. Why are they talking to you?
They did it. Thankfully, they did.
A man in his 30s alone drinking a beer
in a lobby of a hotel at a Disney resort.
Why not talk to him?
I mean, the truth is that there's shit all over Disneyland.
It's just that like usually like we don't see it.
And also, like, there's tons of people constantly shitting themselves at Disneyland.
We don't see it because it's there's adults.
There's adults that need a diaper change.
I mean, I was one of my like most
like traumatic Disneyland memories was I shit myself as a child.
And I like and I was so like embarrassed.
I was on a Girl Scout trip and I was like nine.
And I was like so embarrassed that I shit myself.
And I didn't tell anyone that I shit myself.
I didn't like want to deal with it.
So I just like left the shit in my underwear for like hours at Disneyland.
Because it went on all the rides.
Maybe I was younger than nine.
Nine now seems kind of too old for that.
But like it was bad. It was bad.
I like left the shit in my like pants.
And then like we had to like someone's mom had to like drive me home.
And everyone was like, what's that smell?
And I was like, it's my Disneyland shit.
Like I don't it was so embarrassing.
Wait, did you cop?
No, I didn't cop to it.
But like I feel like everyone knew, you know, like, you know, kind of like,
if there's like if there's like a minivan full of like four girls,
like, you know, who's the girl with shit in her pants?
Was there anything else about you that would have made them think, oh, yeah,
that's in line with Kate?
I think I was just like, I'm really like, I'm not a quiet person.
Like I was a very like extroverted child.
And I was not talking at all.
I was like, I was like, I'm sure they could tell because I just like wasn't talking.
I was like, I remember being like very silent.
Just like in my own shame.
That that has to happen at Disney 50 times a day.
Constantly many times a day.
And I'm saying with like an older kid, obviously, it's happening with little kids
that still have a diaper, but like even like, yeah, kids in the seven to ten range
constantly. Oh, yeah.
In a way. Adults, too.
And do you? Yeah.
And adults, too. Yeah.
Because you end up stuck in lines.
You're in places where you've put in the time you've put in the legwork.
You know, you don't even know where a bathroom is if you're not there all the time.
So now you're going to like not you're going to give up your spot and go deal with.
I mean, look, I wouldn't do this.
I'm not justifying the doing of this.
I'm just getting myself in the head of someone who would
shit their pants and then go on the Matterhorn 15 minutes later.
Say you're in line. Yeah.
Rise of the Resistance.
I know there's a virtual queue, so it doesn't quite work.
But it's say opening day Little Mermaid.
It's four hour line. Wow.
You wait three hours, 45 minutes.
You're so close. You're alone.
You're a single man in his 30s and you shit in your pants.
Oh, God. I guess you could ask the person behind you.
But then. No, you're never getting that spot back.
Because they're going to be gone.
It's a long line.
I don't know. It's tough. I shit my.
Also, Rise of the Resistance maybe is good because you are like trapped.
You're on a resistance, not a resist.
You're on a what's the fake one? First order.
First order. Yeah.
Well, you're on a first order ship and you can't go backwards.
And Little Mermaid, you could technically leave.
That's true. You're right.
If you once you're once you're off world on Rise of the Resistance,
you have to just live with that shit. Oh, God.
OK, you have to get through the you have to get through the Star Destroyer
with shit in your pants.
Get back to Batuu, see Lieutenant Beck and then Lieutenant Beck
will allow you to go to the bathroom.
Oh, my God. Lieutenant Becker Becks.
I can't remember back. I think back.
BKK. Yeah, BK.
I also also I was thinking about this when you're when you're at the grocery store,
if you use the front little thing that kids sit in, it's a it can be a shelf,
but it also is a seat.
How many kids are sitting in that with a shitty diaper?
Every every single one. Right.
So you so people put their bread in that like right after.
Hopefully it's not out of a bag, hopefully.
Although in some cases you maybe are getting like a sourdough
loaf where you sort of bag it yourself or it might like slip out.
Yeah. If it's not fully contained, if there's like one way out for the bread.
Exactly. Yeah. Yeah. It's gross.
Not about any of this.
I use that for cans.
I use that spot for canned goods exclusively.
I've never used I'm not using it again now.
Yeah, I don't know. You put it in my head.
I thought about that. Yeah.
But it's good that we're all paranoid shit.
Yeah. Well, I think I am a little more germ-pair.
I'm a little more because of Covid.
I am definitely more aware of I think how things actually spread.
Yeah. That's the down that you say that.
Sam's might be one of the biggest psychological hurdles
once everything calms down a little and stuff opens back up
because Sam's is is that the most intimate like attraction thing?
Oh, yeah. You're getting droplets for sure. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
Sam is full of droplets.
There's for sure aerosol spread.
They do it. That's one of the things when you get a drink, they do.
Who's ready for some droplets?
Globules at you.
Yeah. Like a social distance, Sam's inside would be impossible.
It's not possible.
Yeah. Yeah. You couldn't put up barriers between people on on the actual bar.
So you end up with two customers.
Forget sharing like a fishbowl with someone else.
Yeah. I mean, I guess the alcohol kills somewhat.
But yeah, as far as a straw is concerned.
Are we never all going to share a big, a massive teaky drink again?
Well, have we before?
Well, we have maybe not.
Yeah, we have at Howl at the Moon.
Oh, yeah.
The Universal City Walk now closed dueling.
I loved Howl at the Moon. I loved.
Oh, were you out there?
Let's take a jaunt over there, Kate.
Let's take a jaunt to City.
The best part about Howl at the Moon is that they convince you that you can like
like there's a raffle, like a fake raffle that they do when you come in
and you like give them your email address.
And every every single time you do it, you get an email back saying
you won the raffle, you and your friends get a free party at Howl at the Moon.
Like if you come like in this time period.
And so like anyone can just have a free party where like everybody gets
like half off drinks.
You just have to like they were doing this.
They were doing this grift to us last whenever we did this a year
and a half ago, two years ago, we all got the free party.
It's the best. I love it.
It's I've been to many of those free parties and they're great.
And I love the wood, love the dueling pianos, love the what don't
don't they have like bucket buckets of like beers there and stuff like that?
Yeah, it's a great place.
That's what yeah, that's what we were.
We were drinking a bucket of blue alcohol, slime of some kind,
like just thick sugar blue slime.
Love it. In a terrible, terrible stuff.
And I think I I don't think I'm rewriting history.
I think I even who I like, I like at least one or two sugary drinks.
I think I said this is disgusting.
Yeah, you called it.
And the other thing there were it was like four dollar,
like Stoli or Sky Vodka or something.
Yeah. So yeah, we had we had one night.
And then, yeah, when we went up to City Wall a couple of weeks ago
just to check it out and how the moon is closed there.
I think it was supposed to reopen on Hollywood Boulevard, though.
But it did for like a week and then it just closed for.
Had so sad, I think they called it.
Yeah. So yeah, so we'll see.
Maybe that'll come back.
Kate, did you party at City Walk as a youth as well?
No, no, we were more Disneyland people.
I didn't party at City Walk as much, although, you know, I love City Walk as an adult.
I had my birthday at Bubba Gump last year.
Oh, gee. Yes, a great place.
We should have had you on one of our many, many episode series
about City Walker or downtown Disney.
Had we thrown that out, do you have a favorite place?
If you if you had to pick one to talk about at City Walk or downtown Disney.
OK, good question.
Downtown Disney, my favorite place.
It is the Uva bar.
Like, I love the Uva bar.
I was pumped for the Uva bar.
I really thought, yeah, very excited.
Just go there for a while mentally.
Even though, like when you try to justify what's great about it,
there's like nothing in the list.
It just is a place where there are chairs and glasses of wine.
There's something so great about it.
Nothing you could say to just yes.
Yeah. No, I love it.
I think maybe for that reason, because you
maybe it is the lack of theming or anything.
It's nothing. It's nothing.
It's like a certain it wipes the slate clean.
If you're like getting tired of little kid stuff
and like cartoon characters and balloons in your face,
do they go be in the most vanilla place in the world?
Also, special shout out to the downtown Disney Sephora,
which is where I used to go and put sunscreen on for free
every time I went to Disneyland.
Wow, that's a good hack.
That's a great tip.
So really good.
Everyone do that.
You don't have to bring your own sunscreen.
Just go put it on it's for it.
They've got free trials of everything.
Wow, I've never heard this really excellent tip.
This this is might be a game changer because like if you
bring your own sunscreen, so you bring a big bottle,
do you carry it all day?
Leave it in the car.
Oh, but plastic balloons that I don't know if you guys
have ever experienced this.
You leave like hand sanitizer sunscreen in a car
and then it just warps if the car is too hot.
It just like expands.
So like single service Sephora is a great.
Yeah. And you can really like you can use the free samples
of some very expensive sunscreen.
For free. Right.
So like celebrity.
Yeah. You get some like, you know,
celebrity brand sunscreen.
Some like some Kylie Jenner, Kylie Jenner shit over there.
Yeah. Yeah. Like some like Twitch star.
Has Andy Gerber sunscreen.
Yeah. Yes.
Casamigos, Casamigos, Casamigos branded sunscreen.
They should do.
Could you imagine?
They should do a sunscreen line.
Casamigos, him and George.
Oh, yeah.
Randy and George should do a sunscreen line.
Oh, yeah, because they're always out like talking to the workers
in the field who are making the tequila.
I need that sunscreen to protect them and the workers.
They're good friends.
And they're there.
Two guys with like, you know, wealthy looking skin.
I would I would buy some skin shit from them.
Yeah. Now, I think pretty accurate.
That is the way to describe that sort of like leathery.
Yeah, like like like a healthy, expensive leather.
Mm hmm. Mm hmm.
Yeah, like a nice recliner.
Yeah. You could make a nice recliner out of George Clooney
or Randy Gerber's skin.
I like that. Or line your car with it.
Yeah.
Could my the seats in my car be made out of George Clooney skin?
I like that.
Mm hmm.
Would you wait that that implies that you were previously aware of Randy
Gerber, who comes up on this podcast nearly every episode.
I mean, I'm a big fan of the Gerber family.
Kaia, I love Kaia.
Cindy Crawford, love her.
The son has a bunch of has like a bunch of face tattoos.
Oh, yeah, there's love the Gerber.
We did we did an episode on Casamigos on our Patreon,
and we I only briefly touched on the family,
but the family has a lot of seemingly drama surrounding them as well.
Them.
Um, but I just tried to we just tried to focus on the business side.
Of the Gerber of the Gerber brand and the Gerber group, of course, the three,
the three men in the Gerber family who all are part of the Gerber.
The Gerber group. I didn't know about the Gerber group.
Yes. And I'm trying to remember.
I think there's Scott Gerber.
There's Randy Gerber.
Right. Yeah.
And there's a third there's a mysterious third part.
No, it's Casamigos as the mysterious third partner.
Yeah, that's that.
He's the party boy of Casamigos.
But the Gerber group is a different thing.
Those are the three brothers in the Gerber family. Wow.
Scott, let me bring you back into the fold real quick.
I have a question since you brought up the Uva bar, which I
I know is one of your haunts.
I have only very briefly been there.
Have you been to Uva bar since downtown Disney reopened?
No, I haven't been there in general.
OK, I'm I'm certainly thinking about it.
I'm getting the I'm getting the hankering.
And, you know, we actually haven't recorded an episode since this new plan
that they are going to open some of California Adventure,
specifically for food, drink and merchandise,
which I'm very excited about.
I feel like I might give it a shot.
And this is maybe the way to finally get back to drinking at Disneyland,
even in the tiniest regard.
I don't know if you know about any of this, Kate,
but I think what they're saying is an outdoor version of Carthay Circle
and the smoke jumpers, the
aviation themed restaurant next to Soren will be open.
It serves the bad hamburgers.
That's like the worst. Why?
Why that one of all the of all the culinary experiences?
But why not bring why not bring the Food and Wine Festival back then instead?
I I agree with that.
I don't know if they're I don't know if it's just proximity.
Like there's some money reason why they only want to open that little area
right when you enter the park and why not?
That's like all they can like reasonably set up and staff and lights.
Because you have to have something sit down, right?
Like because you can't like have a bunch of people like walking around.
Yeah. Getting hammered. Yeah.
No, but they have the food and wine people are eating and walking around drinking.
Like, yeah, I'm not really sure the reason.
I don't. Yeah, I'm not sure.
I those Daily Beast, that big expose about outbreaks and doubt that Disney has me
so spooked like I don't know if I will try it out.
Wait, I don't know about this. Oh, no.
Oh, didn't it? Well, then I texted that.
And I think September, I think, wasn't it?
Was it September, September and August?
And basically like Disney is not like communicating about like if someone is
they're not doing a good job at letting other cast members know it's positive.
There are positive tests.
They weren't letting the union know in a timely manner.
And I was shocked this wasn't brought up when there were
everyone's complaining about Gavin Newsom's opening plans.
But there was a statistic about like
colleagues would disappear for days at a time.
And no one knew why 11 people from the 12 person horticultural irrigation team
didn't show up to work for a full week.
My God is a section of the article.
So, yeah, that combined with the lines we had been seeing at downtown Disney.
I think the thing that appealed to me going up the city walk was how empty it was.
Yeah, no, not at all.
Oh, no. But they're killing full horticulture groups.
I guess not killing them.
Well, yeah, it seems like people people were OK,
but it doesn't seem like they were doing a good job.
They weren't testing on site.
So, oh, man, yeah, we'll see about that.
I mean, I think if you go in the middle of the day towards these reopened
downtown days, I'm sure the crowds are a lot less.
Were you saying that there was no one at CityWalk?
It was when we went up there, it was pretty light.
There was as many security people it seemed.
I went and and it was crowded and it was scary.
To Universal CityWalk, it was like was the with the polling place open.
Do you think that you remember if that?
No, I went like months ago.
I went probably to I went probably too early in the pandemic.
Like it was like it was like one of the first places I went to
to just like see about going somewhere in public.
And Jack and I went we like got our temperatures taken and and it was like
I was expecting no one to be there.
It was like fully packed, like all the restaurants like were full.
Bubba Gump had all the outdoor seating like completely filled up.
Like it was it was scary.
There's like long line to get into Hot Topic, long line to get into Voodoo
Donuts. It was like I think, yeah, you may maybe went when like everybody was like,
oh, my God, it's open. We got to go.
I think I think that remember that time period when like restaurants
like fully opened for some reason in May?
Yeah, I think that's like when I went and it was like they weren't inside.
They weren't eating inside, but it was still like very scary. Right.
Did you just get out of there or did you try?
We did like one lap and then like immediately went home because it was too scary.
Wow. Wow. You know, I was thinking before this episode, I was like,
well, this is one where we're going to talk about COVID a lot and where we'll say
a lot of things like, you know, because when you go there and you know,
you get the wine and then, well, you know, not right now.
But and I was thinking how if only this is like this may be a little idea
of an invention or some tech or an app that somebody could make.
If there was like in three years from now when all this is, I hope, done,
if like there was some kind of app that could extract mentions of COVID
from every podcast episode where we all had to talk about it for a long time
so that they are listenable in the future. Yeah.
So we don't have this shadow on us.
I feel I mean, it would be it'd be a lot of work.
This this app would if it extracted all of the COVID references,
it would be just like over a year's worth of material between every podcast
that has to talk about it. Sorry.
OK, go ahead. You should just replace.
You should just like have some word that you say instead of COVID
that will be like evergreen.
Like we can't go right now because we all have, you know, a conference.
We're all at a conference.
We're all at a convention.
Like that'll be fine.
Like people will be like, oh, well, they had a conference.
They were out of town. Yeah.
What if you replace COVID with conference?
Like, well, we can't go because of the conference.
It works.
It does. It works because of the conference.
Trump's response to the conference has been horrible.
It's just some I just love.
Sorry, I've been sleeping really bad just because I'm scared about
where everything's going with the conference.
I hope we get a vaccine for the conference soon.
Hmm. Not as good.
Yeah, works for me.
Yeah. Well, someone someone developed this.
I think a lot of people say the conference isn't real, but I mean,
people are going to the conference. Yeah.
A lot of people in Orange County deny that the conference exists.
The conference is the most popular event in American history.
That's my other thing that worries me about downtown
Disney, period, is the location in Orange County.
That was another memorable bar experience.
I had an Orange County at Disneyland once at California Adventure.
I like waited an hour to get into the Cove bar, sat down.
And before I could say hello to the bartender, some like
skeezy looking Orange County, Crestpunks walked up to the service bar,
ordered two zombies to go and got served before me.
And I was just like, no, please.
I've just been waiting, waiting in the sun for an hour.
I just got snaked by these guys with backpacks that are mostly straps.
I don't understand what's going on.
So you hate the whole county now.
I, you know, it's a strange two guys
caught in front of you in line and now the county's on notice.
I well, it's, you know, all the other there's other stuff in Orange County.
It's not a shortage.
I know the opinion is correct, but yeah, yeah, yeah.
Which, hey, that's one thing to talk about.
We all live, you know, sort of in like Valley, LA,
you know, this this part of the city.
Disneyland's way down in Anaheim, Orange County.
We love to go and drink a good amount.
But at some point, somebody's got to worry about the drive home.
How much do you wish there was a more reliable transportation back and forth?
How great would that be?
I would love if that existed.
Have you done the train?
I've always wanted to try doing the train, but it seems like too complicated.
You have to take a bus.
I've gotten. Yes, you have to get bus.
I've gotten so close to trying it.
And then it's always just like, but then you got it.
It's another 90 minutes on the trip, maybe both ways.
I think so. And it's just it's too hard.
My sister took a one time when my family was here and she was working
and she took a train down the train got delayed about five hours.
Oh, she showed up at like midnight.
It was crazy.
It's some of the risk.
Yeah, it's off. It's extremely off.
I've tried to figure this out on behalf of the company.
Like, is there just a shuttle bus that runs every 10 minutes
from some spot in L.A. from the lot or from the studio? Sure.
Mm hmm. Like that would be nice.
I mean, I'm I've rarely ever had enough to drink
that a nice five hour walk in the sun won't, you know, get me sober.
But it would be nice to go.
I could have a I could have two drinks at the end of the night
and get on a bus and be OK. Yeah, that would be. Yeah.
Usually I'm just eating so much food that like I can't ever really break through.
Like, I mean, as a as a teen, we would get like blackout drunk at Disneyland.
But now that I'm like 30, I just I can't like ever really get that drunk
at Disneyland because like I just eat so much.
I mean, I love the food there.
The thing I love almost more than the drinking is the eating.
I mean, they're both they're tied. They're tied.
They're tied. But yeah, I never I can't get that drunk.
It's also yet so much walking and sweating.
Like you're just you can't retain any of the poison.
Yeah. On a like light day, you're getting those 10,000 steps,
at least pretty easily on a on a fairly typical day.
You're maybe getting like 26,000.
Like it's a ton of what's like way more than you do.
Regularly, like you'd never like actively go on that amount of hike or something.
I remember maybe somebody better than me would.
But yeah, you do so much exercise that counteracts it,
which I think helps you go for that, like long distance.
I've been drinking since 1030 a.m. or whatever.
Yeah. The hardest I've ever really got, I feel like the hardest
I'll go is like two Carthay Manhattans back to back at 2 p.m.
And then that's the best.
When you get like slight, when you get like a heavy buzz
at Carthay Circle in the middle of the day
and you don't have anywhere to drive anytime soon and you're just like,
that's the best. I miss that. I miss that feeling.
Oh, yeah. I guess, especially if I have a fast pass for mission breakout
and I'm leaving with two Carthays inside.
I mean, that's there's nothing better than that.
Yeah. Yeah.
Kate, one of my favorite.
Sorry, Scott, we were saying.
Oh, so it was one of my favorite experiences.
It made like this is way up there in the Disney and drinking was like
having a weird little Anaheim expedition with my wife, Erin,
on the way down, going to the Anaheim Fries Electronics,
discovering that it had a weird space video that played in a loop all the time.
It was a really rainy day.
And then we like raided in the rain and then got into like very warm
Carthay circle and then had a couple of Manhattans.
And by the end of it, I was like, I'm going to be the guy on the screen.
They like like what I was so fired up from the Manhattans.
I'm going to figure out a way that it's not going to be that old astronaut.
It's going to be me. And then I did it.
It happened. And this was the entire I don't know if you know about this.
I know all about this. I followed this very closely.
It's something I as someone who also loves fries like
this was big for me when this happened for you.
Oh, oh, wait, because we talked about this.
That's right. Because you you grew up near the is it El Segundo?
Yeah, the Manhattan Beach, the Hawaiian one.
Like Tiki themed, the Polynesian themed fries was my hometown fries.
And I'm just proud to be a hometown fries girl.
To be so lucky to grow up with one in your backyard,
it's almost better than having a theme park.
I'm very blessed.
I had a very blessed childhood at that fries.
It's where I got my first iPod.
Oh, wow. It's a big fries for me.
These do you remember like a they're still selling that generation?
I know they stopped right after that one.
It's a top notch fries.
It's a great price.
Mike, you were heading somewhere, though.
Oh, I was just going to ask, because, you know, you're talking about blackout
drunk, of course, this makes me retroactively as a kid, very uncomfortable.
Like, was it in my kid brain, it was like, oh, like you.
People were just looking at you and it was like you were danger.
It was around every turn because of employees.
Or was it literally no one cared?
And like you just had a nice.
No one cared. We would just like rage hard at like World of Color,
like chugging like water bottles full of like Evan Williams.
Like that was the vibe.
It was great. It was pure teenage bliss.
It was great.
So it was just pretty.
So, yeah, because because I would imagine the scenario is I'm whatever 13, 15.
Even if somebody had like a little like travel size bottle of liquor,
they like showed me before we went into security.
I would have been sweating so profusely the whole day.
I feel like. But it's obviously like no one cares.
I think it's like I feel like it was different because we were like we were like cute,
like teen girls and like you just get away with like so much when you're like,
a privileged like teenage, like sweet looking girl.
So we would like I don't think we like thought rules applied to us.
I mean, it's a big problem.
It's why a lot of problems in the world exist because of that phenomenon.
But it worked really well for us at the time when it came to sneaking alcohol into Disneyland.
We like weren't that scared about it.
I guess like sometimes I would like, you know,
when I stopped bringing them into the water bottles and started bringing them into flasks,
then I would try to hide them and that would be a little more stressful.
That's harder. Yeah.
Yeah. But like Marissa Strickland has told us about like Grad Night shenanigans at Disney.
I mean, Grad Night is lawless at Disneyland or.
They banned it.
By the time I was a senior, they banned Grad Night for my school because like someone OD'd or something.
Wow.
That's right. I remember that being a punishment.
I don't think my class did it, but I think maybe a different class at my high school.
That is the punishment if somebody, which is so crazy.
No Disneyland for anyone.
We had to do ours at Dave and Buster's.
That was our Grad Night.
It was at Dave.
Was that it was like in, I think it was like in Orange County somewhere.
It was like a far away Dave and Buster's.
I remember being on a bus for a long time just to go to Dave and Buster's.
Not as good.
Irvine or something.
Probably like.
It's not bad though.
Jason, we were at a Grad Night and I do think there was a kid that was, am I wrong?
Were you here?
There was a kid that was, I think it was like a kid that was like a kid that was like a kid.
That was, am I wrong?
Were you here?
There was a kid that was too drunk and there was a problem and a security, like security was trying to figure out what to do.
Yeah, someone had to intervene.
We were trying to hang out at like a mad tea party or something and not be hassled by some drunk teen.
Yeah, we just wanted to hear covers of songs for our youth.
We just wanted to see wholesome covers with words cut out, I'm assuming.
Yeah, so.
I'm not sure I know an example of what you mean.
This is the kind of thing that was at the mad tea party.
Well, there was a set list that they would do every night.
Princess Let's Go Crazy was in it.
It was like a Blink 182 song in there, I think, as well.
We'll get to this on the mad tea party episode eventually.
I'll find the full set list, but I think there would be a word or two.
I think we would think.
Word or two.
Here comes an inappropriate line in one of these songs and they would like change it to make sure it wasn't offensive.
I don't think it was like.
I'm trying to think of a dirty Blink 182 song.
I don't think it was.
I don't think it was so bad, but I think they changed a little things.
Yeah.
I when you were when you were talking about like blackout drunk, I was I was recalling that there's there has been one time in my life that I was that at a Disney park and it doesn't fit with the topic, technically, because it was at Disney World.
And I don't even know if blackout well, I don't know, like vaguely on the line.
I'm saying blackout like pretty liberally.
I mean, like just drunk, capital D drunk.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That line where you know the difference.
Yes, it's not like I remember how I got home and such.
But yeah, but yeah, definitely the drunkest ever was which was started with a pregame at the California Grill, which is on top of the contemporary hotel in Disney World.
And that's where you can like get the monorail from the hotel.
You just go down into the lobby and it passes through the hotel.
And there was a monorail ride that was so drunky.
And I was just like, let me look at photos of this.
And I just found one that I did not know existed.
And I'm going to share the screen so you can see this.
This this right here is the drunkest ever been on.
Oh, my God.
I think it shows.
Wow.
That's so good.
Ten years ago, I'm like swinging between like bars.
I'm like dangling off of a we had the car to ourselves.
There was nobody else in there.
And I'm like my feet are up on the seat.
I'm like swinging like a disrespectful teen.
Really?
There's no other way to say it.
And I'm like, I mean, I'm given a very cool finger that is also between my legs.
So it looks fairly sexual.
What you're trying to do.
I love it.
This is this is Pete.
This is peak.
Cool.
This is so cool.
I am.
It's pretty I felt cool.
I certainly felt good.
Look, here's some other I'm like hopping between.
Wow.
Cars.
Teens do.
Look at these.
There's friends.
These are people.
Pirates of the Caribbean shirt.
These were the yeah.
The shout out to the Cadillac Brothers.
So we came with them.
But yeah, pretty pretty pretty.
Wow.
But if the worst thing that I did was like jump over some seats in a monorail car where
we were bothering no one else, like it's not like I was like kicking children in the face.
I'd say that's not so bad.
Can you go back to that previous photo?
Yes.
Yeah.
This one?
Are you?
I'm trying to figure out how many shirts are you wearing?
That's a lot of shirts.
It was cold.
This is December.
Oh, it's December.
And since I'm from California, I don't have warm clothes.
So this is always me in New York, too.
I don't like have a nice thick coat.
I just wear like six layers of regular clothes.
And that's actually how they taught us in the Boy Scouts.
That's how they teach you to dress for like cold weather, hiking and camping is because
rather than one big coat layers so you can just take them off or put them on as needed.
Oh, yes, indeed.
You were being responsible.
Yes.
One sense.
This is a this is a photo of a responsible person.
So there's also me on the.
Oh, wow.
Oh, that's bad behavior.
Pretty bad behavior from the good boy.
When we started this podcast, you know, Jason and I did a lot of up up at research, opposition
research type research on Scott and we did not find these photos.
And I don't know if we would have started the podcast.
I don't know.
Yeah.
We realize the whole thing entirely in a monorail.
It's disrespectful.
That's right.
Yeah.
I will defend I will I will proffer defense because we were down last year and I was on
a bus once to Disney Springs last year and there were some retirees that were gone.
So I had to say at Disney World, they kind of encourage the vacation spirit, the vacation
indulgence, because let's be frank, they just care about the bottom line.
So there were some people who were you were the young person version of gone and they
were the like used car dealership odor version of gone.
So, you know, well, I didn't have to drive anywhere when you're in the vacation kingdom.
You can just go crash at home and I made it back safe.
And and I remember did Harry Potter for the first time the next morning with like the
thickest hanging over.
I had a very long.
Oh, sure.
What does it take for me to not do I just need to like in light of these recent photographs,
I just want to say that I'm I'm learning.
I'm progressing like wait, do I does the public apology do it or is there going to be to make
a donation to Montero carpets?
Yes.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I will say I'll find out who cleans them.
I'll find out if there's a service and I'll like invest in a new vacuum.
You better hope, though, that those brothers you were with don't pull a bubble in ski and
go on podcast, the ride and sell you out.
And you better hope that there's a lot not a laptop floating around.
Yeah, because if if more comes out, you will be punished with the you will no longer allow
to be saying the phrase cocktail or alcohol on the podcast.
You will only be allowed to say adult libations.
No, don't make me do it.
No, Kate, there's this thing I've been complaining about for a long time.
I think that we are the first podcast about Disney parks where we'll say like we get drunk.
We got drunk with drinks because almost every other one dances around the phrase for like
like the longest little socially distant dance until they finally get to.
I may have had a few special potions or two, perhaps an adult libation.
I don't know. I won't say anymore.
I see that that I mean both ends.
This is a time where both ends of the spectrum are actually very tedious.
So like I sucked upon an adult libation on one end and the other end of like, here's the places to get Jack Daniels at Disney.
We're like, all right, guys, these guys.
No, thank you. Not for me.
Either of you. I found a picture.
I found a picture of myself as a drunk teen at Disneyland.
But it's not this is more wholesome coming of age.
It's not as good. It's not as good.
Hold on. OK, here's here's me.
Yes. This. Oh, you have a mustache.
So here's what we would do.
Here's what we would do.
We would we would get drunk and then we would make the face painters paint our faces at the face painting booth.
But they have very strict rules for what adults are allowed to get or like non-children.
So they can't give you a full face paint.
They can only give you like a partial face paint.
So we would just get the mustache from the pirate.
Oh, which that that's good.
That reads is like, you know, you got a porn.
Yeah, it was truly annoying. It was like in that era.
Remember when like mustaches were funny as like a thing as like a cultural thing that was like around that era.
I am. There was an article recently, I think, in like Vulture or something that was about the people.
It's like, well, I got a thing.
I got a mustache tattoo on my finger in 2011 and I'm still dealing with it.
Yeah. And that is the funniest thing I can like.
I like Colin Oates, a ton, definitely one of my favorite bands, and I've seen them live a lot.
And this this like dissipated a little.
In fact, I saw them in Vegas and there was none of this.
But then I saw when I saw them at the Hollywood Bowl one time, the amount of fake press on mustaches with these fucking irony hounds attending this show.
This is not good. Don't like this mustache parade.
It's not about the mustache. It's about the music.
I've never been. I look, I'm on the record.
I've never been a mustache, fake mustache guy.
That's good.
The whole memeifying of must that I know the cell over Tom Selleck, you know, I like Tom Selleck fine, except for his political views.
But that's you know, the mustache.
What I could take a dark period of history when we like memeified mustaches.
I don't think it was a good era.
But maybe maybe it was a simpler time.
You know, it was like we weren't all so that was enough for us.
Just like a funny mustache.
We were at brunch.
We were talking about must.
We were at brunch and we all had mustaches and the cats videos.
You know, those were the days.
Oh, no, I found an actual picture of me as a teen black much more.
This is a better.
OK, there's I have a bunch of them from like this one trip where we got drunk as teens at Disneyland.
Send us any you're willing to make public.
And we can black out people's eyes if we can add a mustache to my friend.
Her parents bought us a hotel room at the Grand Californian.
Wait, can you see this?
This is us getting wasted in the hotel room.
Here's me like I'm front and center drunk with my mother, a different mustache, different mustic, clearly a different occasion.
And I'm like, just gone.
Gone. Here's me like also wasted on the big grizzly rapids rapids.
Oh, these are great.
Here's yeah, here's us at the Ariel's Grotto.
Just drunk out of our teenage minds.
Truly just for your having your having the best time jammed into a phone booth.
The truly not an appropriate thing.
Now that's old fashioned fun.
Yeah, that's what we look around here.
Doesn't work in the era of the conference.
I would get fake.
I would get drunk and I would get fake names stitched onto Disney hats.
So I've made up a name that obviously isn't my name.
I got it stitched onto a hat.
Wait, in this in this case, the name is Moxie, which is like something a teenager would think is like a cool name.
I feel like hilarious.
Yeah.
I was just wondering if you had a friend named Moxie.
I had no I didn't I never met a Moxie.
Is there a chance like Jason and I are like in the background of one of these photos like being probably probably I mean, look how annoying.
Can you imagine like the level of annoying we would be as a group?
There's like five of us.
We all have different like face paints on.
And we're drunk teenage girls.
It's a great is a great vibe.
But you spent money on property and that's the only thing that matters.
That's the only thing that matters.
There really is.
Also, I feel like, you know, there's a level of public intoxication.
But like, what's the worst you guys are going to do?
You're going to like run around and yell.
That's what everyone's doing.
Exactly.
Right.
Yeah.
That's yeah.
You're doing that.
You know, even at a concert, this would be a problem.
You're not a sporting event, perhaps.
But here it's what's the desire.
Here's the poor employee that had to like indulge us with our face paint.
How many times did you get a mustache?
Honestly, like I had an annual pass and I did it every time for like a full like two years or something.
Like it was a bit.
It's not like a great part of my life.
I don't I'm not proud of it, but I did it a lot.
I did it like way too much.
Like when I say that was a dark time in history, I mean, that was a mustache.
Memes were a dark time in my personal history.
I was very much like a mustache person.
I thought mustaches were very funny.
I thought it was funny that I had them painted on me.
Looking back, I must cringe.
I must cringe at my past self.
But what are you going to do?
I mustache.
I don't think you should feel bad, though.
I do think the volume that apparently exists of you with the mustache maybe does make it funny.
Maybe if it was one off, you go, well, that wasn't the funniest thing in the world.
But if you have like two years worth of pictures of it, I do kind of.
I really have a lot.
That's a pretty that's a commitment to a bit.
Yeah, that's a real.
I mean, I am serious about committing to bits, so I guess I guess I haven't really changed.
Which wouldn't you, though, you say it's a dark time if you were afforded the opportunity to safely go tomorrow to Disneyland, get a mustache and drink a lot.
I mean, this this area you describe as dark.
I can't lie.
Do you have a recommendation of a restroom for a bunch of teenagers to take shots at the family restroom in the bugs world?
Is it still there?
Oh, it's gone.
Oh, no, it's family restroom, though.
If you can get one that's not like a main restroom, like one that you can lock the door and it's just you guys in there.
That's the best place to go do shots.
Well, that Tiki that Tiki room single single stall bathroom or is there maybe there's two.
That's a little bit of a traffic area, though, but it is very small.
I wouldn't I you can lock the stall in Carthay Circle, but you can't lock the door.
Yeah.
So I'm not sure I'd have to go do some recon here to find out.
And you never encountered you never all came out and then had some employees say, wait a minute.
What were you all doing in there?
No one like ever said you smear week of booze and your name isn't Moxie.
Is it?
Show me your ID.
Moxie.
I'm not sure.
I knew I'd catch you again.
You thought you would disguise yourself with that mustache.
Nice try, Moxie.
This is all what I thought would happen.
If I was hanging out with you and I was a teen, I would have been like, oh, my God, they're going to know they're going to know you're not Moxie.
I would like just be like freaked the whole thing.
They fell for it.
They thought my name was fucking Moxie.
Those fucking losers.
They believed every last word of it.
Those fools.
There's still people that go, you remember that Moxie?
She was very nice.
She had a mustache.
There's a very special girl named Moxie.
Another another fake name I got once was I just got Britannica on the back.
Well, that's the long that they did it.
Impressive.
I picked a long one.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's good.
The stitcher.
I'm it's like it's like Westworld.
You know, you can go and have a new identity just for that day.
It's a good point.
We would do that.
We would get drunk and like to talk to people in like British accents and stuff and like pretend we were we were just little annoying little trolls.
But it was fun.
That's yeah, that's a real teen bit.
Yeah.
Or like the funny guy at the office just starts talking in a cockney accent for no reason.
That would drive me up the wall of my old day.
Just purely annoying.
Like yeah, the opposite of charming.
Yeah, I've had like guy who won't stop doing Stewie from Family Guy.
That's pretty rough.
Yeah.
I've also had like guy who won't stop doing Jason Bateman from Dodgeball.
Oh, specific.
Why that one?
Yeah, very specific.
I was I was going to say, Scott, you bringing that up.
I do have some pictures from when I went with the my my high school marching band at 18.
I have my friend.
Sober climbing all over like you were doing in the monorail.
I mean, you might do that with even without.
There are some alcohol for me to overcome my reverence for the place.
That's really what it did.
And knocked out my inhibition and my the inherent utmost respect that I have for monorails.
Of course.
And then I'm remembering because of Disney World, I actually think the most ridiculous thing I've ever done in my life is I've been in the
I actually think the most drunk I ever was at a Disney park was two Disney World trips ago when I went with my friend Luke and his wife.
I was a third in their vacation in there, not a quad, no sexual things, but a third in the vacation.
And we were at the Abracadabra.
And I think we may have had three Manhattans at the Abracadabra, which is right by a center right by.
I can't think of the name of the entrance.
Help me out here.
The greatest entrance.
The International Gateway, International Gateway, of course.
And Kate, it's a magic themed bar.
I know.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Yes.
It's fantastic.
Could there be a magician doing a trick?
Sure.
But there's not.
Oh, well.
But Luke and I, Luke's wife had gone to the bathroom and Luke and I were sitting there and there's a woman with her husband and they had been drinking.
And this woman came over and was significantly older than us.
And in front of this man, and we assume was some sort of a partner, just started hitting on us, basically propositioning us.
And like an insane and like kind of like insulting Luke's wife as well in the process.
We were like in what regard?
Like what?
Like a day?
Nothing.
As far as insulting, like was nothing major.
But like it felt like dismissive, maybe dismissive is a better word.
Like kind of like, oh, like you both of you are very attractive, both of you are very handsome.
Like who's that?
Who's that?
Who's that woman over there?
And we were like, we were with it enough to know what was going on.
And then the guy was just like in the conversation, like enjoying it or just helpless to stop it.
And I remember Luke's wife came back out and like we just we bolted as fast as we could.
And we're like trying to like instill to this day, we're trying to actually figure out the series of events that led to this.
Like because we're trying to piece it together of like we didn't talk to this woman before because we were leaving.
We just stood up and then this woman started to hit on us.
And so we're still preventing this.
There's one event in this series.
The event is you guys being friggin hunks.
Don't sell yourself short.
All right. Well, thank you.
I appreciate that.
We're both about six three.
We're both from the Midwest.
I don't know.
Yeah.
Corn fed.
Corn fed hunks.
We're both corn fed hunks in our mid thirties.
Hunks of corn.
Yeah.
They were fed so much corn that they got so so tall like a corn stock.
That's my problem.
I do.
Every time I hear the term corn fed, I just think of like boys getting like force fed tons of corn.
That's the picture it conjures.
What feels like an animal.
It was like a thing.
And like milk.
For some reason, like milk and corn.
Like I picture like a big bowl of corn with like a big jug of milk and like that's all you eat.
I definitely drank a lot of milk and ate a lot of corn.
That's what it feels like being someone from like Southern California, like L.A. area.
I'm like I've never I had never been to the Midwest.
I just thought that's what corn fed meant.
I don't think that's totally wrong.
It's not.
Yeah.
School lunch came with carton of milk every day.
Milk with cereal for breakfast.
Milk with a glass of milk with dinner.
Yeah.
Sounds gross.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Would we ever you know, this episode.
It's called drinking at Disneyland.
And yet we've made the leap that this is about, you know, adult libations.
We could have devoted a whole lot of this episode and still could to all the various milks that you could drink.
So many milks.
There's a lot of milk.
Yeah.
I don't mean that Star Wars stuff like that's that doesn't technically I want to I want like cartons of milk.
Well, that's something we figured out a few years ago where if you just want a little snack, you can order the kids meal or once or twice a day.
Once or twice.
I've seen Mike order the toddler meal, which is usually just a scoop or two of mac and cheese and a carton of milk, maybe some apple slices.
Well, what I'll do is I'll I will order that if it's an app in app because I don't want to say toddler meal because I don't have a child.
But if it's in the app and I can just like I can just place the order and then pick it up, then I don't have to actually like say it's a child's meal or the toddler meal.
And if I get to go in a couple years, you can use my son as a cover and get your milk.
Scott Scott Scott Scott.
Give me the kid. Give me the kid.
Give me the kid.
Hey, here we go.
You run.
It's free.
It's for him.
Hey, it's for this this this thing.
This kid.
I hear him by one arm using the app with the other dragging him along the ground.
Yeah, not for me.
It's for him.
Well, Mike, this is kind of breaking new.
I just got this changes.
Texted this to me coming to McDonald's Disney World Happy Meals.
I know I know all about this.
OK, there is a series of McDonald's Happy Meal toys to commemorate, I think, the 50th anniversary of Disney World.
And it's you know, they very much they very much seem like stuff we collected when we were kids.
But it'll be like Mickey and the Tower of Terror at McDonald's.
Wow.
Which is very exciting to see the parks represented at McDonald's.
I think those are appearing soon.
You know what they should have?
You know what they should have as a Happy Meal is the the now non-existent McDonald's french fry booth outside of
Thunder Mountain Railroad.
They should have a toy.
Yeah, like Westwood.
They should have a toy of that of that little cart that used to sell McDonald's french fries.
Yeah, I think at the time people thought that was a little odd.
But now I think we're almost nostalgic for that.
It was like I was so sad when that went away.
But you know, they replaced it with like the they put the chimichangas there and those are pretty good.
So, yes, correctly, it says Westward.
I guess that's not it.
That's not at Disney World.
So it wouldn't count for the 50th anniversary.
Happy Meal.
Oh, sure, sure, sure.
Yeah, this was this was my one of my favorite spots.
This french fries stand.
You could just get french fries and drinks.
Yeah.
Whoa.
And it says there's gold in them.
Darf.
I didn't know that.
Wow.
That's great.
Yeah.
Well, if you want to do the the full episode about the french fry cart.
Yeah, we're ready to go on and on.
I have a lot to say about that cart.
One of the best carts in all the land.
It's that's also that's the era.
And I like now Disneyland especially has gotten so crazy expensive.
And I know like, you know, getting a drink and having annual pass all nice privilege we all have usually been able to afford.
But ten years ago, it was such a different money landscape for Disney.
Like the annual passes, they were just given away like you could basically get an annual pass and go a decent amount for like slightly over a day ticket.
And now it's like 50 times that amount of money.
So I romanticize that era, too, of when I had first come to L.A. and was going to SoCal resident.
When my family came to visit like once or twice the first time, they would get like a few day park hoppers and we'd go down there.
And then they're like, oh, you live here.
You can turn this into an annual pass.
I was like, what? And they're like, yeah, this pays like 30 bucks.
I was like, OK, and then you just have an annual pass for a year.
Yeah, it was it was fantastic that that era.
It was like Six Flags where like they were cheap.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm nostalgic for the time before I paid, you know, nearly a thousand dollars upfront for an annual pass to a place that now has been closed for eight months.
Because of the conference, the conference, the conference.
I like if I just hadn't gone that one day, I don't know what I mean.
At this point, it's becoming it's like starting to loop around the full year.
So maybe I just get it back or most of it or or I can go so far into the future.
There's rumors now because Tokyo Disney is canceling annual passes.
They're just canceling the program and people are thinking it's possible they do that here for a little while.
So who knows? I'm not saying what comes of me.
They're going to they just going to take my money to get it back.
Probably broke. Aren't they?
Aren't they running out of money?
They've already have my money, so they're not going to give it back to me willingly.
Well, Tokyo is refunding everyone with the passes.
Yeah, I mean, we'll refund here if that's what they're doing.
But I think Disney is getting cash for the Oriental Land Company that runs Tokyo.
Disney might have more cash on hand and the ability to just refund it, especially if they have like government subsidies.
So, yeah, I don't know.
I'm very curious to see if Disneyland would cancel the annual pass program because I feel like it would just make everyone even matter.
They can't do that. I feel like they can't.
They won't do that.
I don't know.
Well, their business model out here at Disneyland is like 70, 30, 80, 20 locals going to Disneyland, which is what Florida has become.
Usually it's the reverse in Florida. It's mostly tourists and a small percentage of locals.
But, yeah, it'll be interesting when the parks reopen out here.
Can I talk about a way that Disney could maybe get some of this money back in their pockets?
And we've touched upon this here and there.
The idea, this general thing of that you can drink in downtown Disney and you can drink in California Adventure, but you cannot drink in Disneyland Park proper unless you are sneaking it into a restroom.
Doesn't it seem like if they're going to bring it back, isn't now the time?
Like, why not?
Obviously, they started doing it in Galaxy's Edge.
That's the tradition is starting to crumble a little bit.
Why not?
I feel like people will be so ready and so excited to drink in Disneyland.
And I wanted to bring up this question.
Drinking spots, if you could put some spots into Disneyland proper.
And, you know, space is limited.
It doesn't always have to be a sit down restaurant.
We know they can't build those super easy.
But we were just looking at the Westward Home McDonald's fry cart.
If there was this kind of thing for beers or adult sarsaparilla or what have you.
I mean, like, are there places where you wish you could get a drink themed to the land that you're in?
I mean, a Pirates of the Caribbean bar would be like so perfect.
You could get like rum drinks and like.
I mean, putting it, you could put that like in the New Orleans square, like where all the pins, pin shops and shit.
Just knock out one of those overpriced jewelry stores and put in a bar.
Yeah, yeah, yes.
Yeah, I mean, they already have the like alcohol free mint juleps.
That's an easy switch over.
Once that white you want a non alcoholic.
That just seems like I mean, if you're a youngster perhaps, but like just like to use the name,
there's something about creating a new mocktail idea that's interesting.
And but like to take something that you know is supposed to have alcohol and just not have it seems odd.
It's we I think I've said all this before in piecemeal on the in the last three years of the podcast.
But yes, it like mint julep with alcohol.
You can get a beer at the Golden Horseshoe or at a restaurant over by Big Thunder.
I think I've even proposed the idea of leveling that restaurant and making a like a double decker restaurant of some kind, like a saloon that you can overlook.
Yes, indeed.
Yes.
Some sort of observation deck in Tomorrowland where you can get a neon blue gloatini with a little cube that lights up and you get any overlook Tomorrowland in the park.
That's a slam dunk.
And then there's one more and I'm trying to think of what what it is.
Jungle Cruise.
Jungle. Yes.
By the new area, the new tropical hideaway is a perfect place for a small variety of tiki drinks similar to Trader Sam's and do the mugs, do the sell the mugs as well.
But they're different mugs.
You got to go in park to get these mugs.
This is all slam dunk stuff.
And you don't have to don't let maybe don't allow it.
Walk around if you really need to like ease ease into this more.
You just have it be like local like in the in the actual.
Do like similar to like Ogo's that method like you know sure if an hour in there or something if you need to if they're concerned about like IDing people or that sort of stuff.
I mean, I recognize that there are a lot of minors and people underage who go to Disneyland alone or whatever.
And and it's safe and it's comfortable.
And so I get that concern.
I think there's a lot of pearl clutching on the topic of like alcohol going in the park walk Walt walked in.
But what was a lush?
I mean, I've had a lot of his drink is like pure like gasoline.
It's scotch over crushed ice with a twist of lemon rind.
And it's it's like this is just drinking scotch.
I thought it would be.
I thought it's I just ordered it because like it said it was Walt's drink and I didn't even read the description.
But it's like it's just drinking scotch.
Yeah, it's just scotch over ice, which is is a drink I like to have.
I am again a total lightweight so I can have one at Disneyland if I'm driving because I maybe if it may be a second if I'm like walking around and eating a big meal for hours.
Kate, I do agree with what you said.
I just eat all day.
I just burn off the calories from walking around so much.
I'm just constantly eating.
I just started packing Clif bars more when I go to the parks because I'm like I cannot spend money on like a shitty sandwich.
You know, they're not shitty.
None of the food there is shitty.
How dare you?
Some of the food is magical.
It can be magical and also like you got the best drunk food.
While I'm thinking of it is the hot Cheeto esque mac and cheese cone at the.
Yes, at the cozy cones.
That's my go to like I'm drunk.
It's the end of the day.
I need to eat something.
I love those cones.
They're so good.
And I like that.
And they're like you can eat while you're eating them.
I know how this could be 50 percent better, but there's something very satisfying about the texture of the bread in the cone.
That's like very satisfying to eat when now it's like not the best tasting bread.
But you do like there.
I don't just something in your mouth.
It's nice.
The bread is so like pillowy and like yes, just good.
It's so good.
And I'll get like the chili in there once in a while.
That's very good.
Jack. Yeah, Jack.
I like to get one of each and we try we try each other's.
That's the cone method that we do.
One of my sleeper favorite drinks is at one of those cozy cones, which is the the lime made with vodka in it with the.
Our alcoholic cones.
Yes.
The pomegranate is like a pomegranate foam on the top as well.
It's like a sugar foam that I love.
Scott and Kate, you guys grew up here and I don't know when California Adventure was opening where people scandalized by like this park across from Disneyland will have libations or was it just like, well, we know Epcot and MGM studios have it in Florida.
So, yeah, I guess it makes sense if our second park has it.
Well, I'm happy to say I was in high school and I was not in any source of place that would be scandalized by this idea.
I'm thrilled to say I mean, I wouldn't put it past myself to be checking some lame message board, but it was certainly not in the newspaper.
I don't think it was a big deal.
I think it was my mom is like loves like Chardonnay.
I'm sure like and I went with her and I think I remember her getting one and not thinking it was weird.
Oh, yeah.
What am I saying?
They for the marketing of the first one was like we got Robert.
It was very like it was very wine, California wine centric.
Yeah.
Although I have a I have a quick anecdote about the opening of California Adventures because I was like went there like before they I went there right when it opened with my parents because they got divorced.
Okay, my parents like said that we have to have a family meeting and I like, you know, find out they're like getting divorced.
And then as I'm like a crying like 11 year old child, I'm like I say like, I thought when you said we're having a family meeting, I thought we were going to go to Disneyland.
And then my parents like stop like what they're doing and say, okay, well, let's go to Disneyland.
And then as like freshly divorced couple, we all pile into a car with my like newly divorced parents and like go to Disneyland as like a family.
And it was very awkward.
It was the day that they told us.
And as a weird like curve ball, we get there and Disneyland is like, well, if you go to California Adventures and go to Disneyland another day, we'll give you a free ticket.
So because they were like trying to get people to go to California Adventures and not Disneyland.
So like the first time I went to California Adventures, I was like crying the whole time because my parents had just told us they were getting divorced but still insisted that we all go.
And it was like so fucked up and I like hated California Adventures for years because I like associated it with my parents divorce.
And like really the only way I was able the only way I came back to it was as like a teen getting blackout drunk.
So actually, I feel like I just had therapy and this all makes sense now.
You know why you that's a very good reason.
That's insane.
Well, and what a weird you've been to like, all right, fine, we'll go to Disneyland.
Well, you know, you could all come back again sometime, you know, all of you as a family together.
Just come back.
The second time my dad didn't go.
So.
Oh, man.
Whoa.
This is heavy stuff.
It was just my mom that time.
My newly single mom.
Wow.
That was the primary demographic of California Adventure the first couple of years was children of divorce and divorced dads going like, where do I take them?
This one's cheap.
This is like Disneyland.
Is this right?
I don't know.
I got a lot of my mind.
It wasn't like fully fleshed out as a theme park yet.
Like it hadn't really it had like such a small amount of rides.
It had the the roller coaster and then this ride called Mulholland Madness that they got rid of.
And then like the the Ferris wheel had like almost nothing.
It was just like a weird sad theme park.
I was expecting to go to it was first of all expecting to go to Disneyland, then found out my parents got divorced.
Then I found out then I expected to go to Disneyland again.
And then it ended up being California Adventures.
It's like a metaphor for the rest of your childhood.
Like you thought it would be Disneyland and instead it was early California.
It was first couple years without even the Tower of Terror California.
No Tower of Terror.
Yeah.
That's wild.
I feel like I will always if I'm looking at photos of like barely themed scaffolding and a dinosaur thing sunglasses, I will think of divorce.
Kate, do you remember a ride going on a ride that day called Superstar Limo?
No, but I feel like that rings like some vague bell.
It's a it's a it was very quickly changed, but it's one of the I guess probably one of the least or least liked rides in the history of parks.
Yeah, it was a it's now the Monsters Inc ride.
And it was basically like you're going through Hollywood.
There's Drew Carey.
There's Jackie Chan.
And it's like there are like these weird caricatures.
No, I didn't go in that one.
I did do the the American Idol experience.
I think was around that time.
Yeah, was that in or was that in California?
Do we have that in Disneyland or the American Idol experience?
Yeah, that was definitely at MGM Studios.
I was thinking millionaire.
Oh, maybe a million.
Yeah, maybe that's what it was.
Who wants to be a millionaire at California Adventures?
Yeah, that's what it was.
That was that was there.
That was there.
That was that we did that when my parents got divorced.
That that was there.
You know, in Superstar Limo, you can pass by weird dummies of Melanie Griffith and Antonio Menderes, who are now also divorced.
Wow.
Oh, there you go.
50 50 odds the last few decades.
So, you know, what are you going to do?
I'm trying to think before you go.
Oh, can I add one more to the like what where there should be drinks?
And I can't believe we hadn't thought about this before.
The Mark Twain.
If that if the Mark Twain was a booze cruise, dear lord.
That's where you put the mint juleps.
Yes, with alcohol, finally where it belongs.
Do you think they sell on Mark Twain?
I think for safety purposes, maybe you sell right outside.
You buy it and then you board the Mark Twain because you don't want maybe for time purposes.
There's not enough time to get everybody a drink.
Right.
And then also like old booze while you're waiting there, which is just this kind of weird corral anyway.
That's very boring.
Right.
Yeah.
Jason, are you offended by this notion?
No, I kind of like that.
That one, I think for safety's sake, everyone only gets one.
Like that's the only time for one.
Yeah, it's only like a 10 or 12 minute lap around.
So but I'm saying the bartenders will only like a bartender who says I can only give you two.
Like, you know, as if you were buying for yourself and your guest or your date or whatever, like some bars won't fill your like you take a tray of stuff.
Like if they were like, I can only give you two, buddy.
So that people aren't getting sloshed and falling off a riverboat.
No deal.
I want seven shots and I'm jumping.
I'm swimming the rest of the way.
I think it's a limited menu service bar.
I'm sorry to sorry to break it to you.
And you can't.
Not if I get back there.
Not if I bust.
So I get one drink that gives me the confidence to go back and steal the entire bottle, run around the ship, take command of the ship, blow the whistle and then perfectly swan dive into the river.
Well, that's what some message board like people are afraid of that they will be like when Flanders orders a single white wine spritzer and wakes up married the next day in a destroyed hotel room.
Well, here let's that brings me to the last thing I wanted to bring up, which is the like when we talk about like where does all this come from this odd like like no, no, no.
You cannot drink in the Magic Kingdom.
Now you can if you pay for this expensive club or if you're a guest from someone there and you can drink right outside of the Magic Kingdom, but you cannot drink in Walt's special place.
I was like, where does this actually come from?
And this is discussed on some message boards and they find an actual quote.
This is from 1956 and somebody is asking Walt Disney.
Why is your park different than like a carnival?
And he says, we got no liquor, no beer, nothing, because that brings in a rowdy element that brings in people that we don't want and I feel they don't need it.
I feel when I go down to the park, I don't need a drink.
I work around that place all day and I don't have one.
After I come out of a heavy day at the studio, some sometimes I want a drink to relax.
And then that's an odd out of context.
It cuts off there.
He may have just like gone on to talk about how much he loves drinking for several paragraphs and I don't know.
But that's the source.
This is what we've been picking apart for a long time, much like something out of the U.S. Constitution where we've spent decades like, well, what does it really mean and how can we stretch that?
What did the originalists say?
The originalists.
These are like Amy Coney Barrett with Walt and Disneyland.
These are the originalists who are trying to see that as gospel versus a document that should be changed or a philosophy that can be changed.
I think that if what the stupidest thing I've said this before, I think.
But like, OK, if you want to say this is a family place, there's no alcohol in the grounds.
I really can't argue with that.
No alcohol. Fine.
But if you can get alcohol five at a five minute walk from the entrance to Disneyland, what are we doing here?
What fake thing are we upholding?
Yeah.
You know, like the Uva bar is not far.
California Avengers not far.
What are we doing here?
I agree with that.
I agree even to some extent with the Walt Disney quote of like the park is rich enough.
It's substantial enough.
You don't need this.
Of course.
We we think, of course.
On the other hand, it's it does feel like a quote of its time because it's like, well, you had a tobaccoist on Main Street.
Like people were just smoking everywhere.
You didn't have gum like this park was designed by your pet peeves.
There was no gum.
But God forbid if people couldn't have us light up a delicious Chesterfield, people had nicotine coursing through their veins.
Women were getting fitted for brassieres on Main Street.
Like it was crazy back then.
The idea that you could have a sugar the craziest thing you could do a sugary cocktail in Disneyland.
Come on.
Yeah.
Also, and I'll credit this YouTube channel called Midway to Main Street that made actually a great video that proved that it lands kind of where we're landing.
The video is called Alcohol at Disneyland, the letter versus spirit of Walt's wishes.
Oh, my God.
Come on.
We really are in like not just Constitution, but like biblical territory.
We're picking apart the old text, the sacred text and the sacred Jedi text.
And he makes the point that, well, if we're being countered to carnivals and carnies, apparently that's why Walt didn't want people to have facial hair in the early days.
Was that like, well, because carnies have.
Are you still not allowed to have facial hair?
No, you can.
No, you can now.
Yeah, it has to be.
Right.
OK, I guess Disney didn't find anything funny about mustaches.
So sad.
I went, you know, when I worked at Universal Studios, they like I had some review where they docked me for facial hair, which I think is the most funny thing I've ever done.
I've never had the ability to grow, but I was like, seeing if I could and I had some just some weird speckles and and they said, Well, yeah, you just can't have the facial hair.
And I was like, wait, you have a full beard, though, right?
Yes.
And then are you or you could be clean shaven.
So it's but what do I do in between?
I don't know.
You know, like, I don't know.
I mean, yeah, it's a weird thing.
You know, I mean, I'm like, you know, you know, I'm not like that.
Yes.
And then are you or you could be clean shaven.
So it's but what do I do in between?
Well, I don't know.
I guess you just can't be here.
Yeah.
You have to grow the full beard before you can come back to work.
I was so confused by that paradox.
Was there like a Mr. Universal in 1930 said, you know, you can't have someone working here with an in between facial hair.
You've got to figure out the spirit and the letter.
Carl Lemley, Carl, somebody's picking apart his letter in spirit.
Who cares?
That's the thing about Walt.
At the end of the day, like, who's he?
We don't got to listen to him.
He's an old racist guy.
Like, much like the U.S. Constitution itself.
Amen.
That brings us back to that point.
All right.
Everyone make sure to vote this coming Tuesday.
Yeah.
Everybody who's listening to this, make sure that you get out there on Tuesday and vote.
When's this coming out again?
I think it's going to work.
Let's check each other's calendars anyway.
Get out there on Tuesday and make sure that you vote.
Vote early, vote often, you know.
Anything else we want to shout out in terms of on the way out here, specific cocktails, specific things we like?
Yes.
One of my favorites and maybe my favorite of all the fun, colorful drinks I like, Mickey's Fun Wheel.
I believe you can still get it.
It was at the formerly the Cove Bar.
Now it's the Lamp Lighter.
Is that right, Jason?
Yeah. Lamp Lighter Lounge.
Lamp Lighter Lounge.
And that had multiple colors to it.
Scott, do you know what I'm talking about?
Yes, because I have it pulled up in a tab to Lamp Light Lounge.
Gorgeous.
It's a beautiful drink.
The thing that I, the story when we went there together is that the thing at the bottom, whatever it is at the very bottom, I think does not have alcohol.
And maybe it's just pineapple juice.
And you got the drink and just started sucking right from the bottom and then were saying, this is my favorite drink.
And then the bartender came and said, oh, actually, you're supposed to mix it up.
And then I think they might have done it for you.
And then you were really disappointed.
They probably did it for you.
You're helpless.
You're the large, you're the tall man, as we've established from the corn and your hands are clumsy sometimes.
I like the idea that the waiter or waitress at the bar.
I'll do it.
And swirled it for me.
Yes, I do like that idea.
That may be.
I guess that part doesn't seem accurate.
But it must have been then that you swirled it and then you were like.
Well, because the problem is, yes, I think you're right.
I think the bottom is just sugar or something, juice or something.
But I wanted to maintain the fun because basically it's like there's a very light blue at the top, like a thicker, more opaque blue under it.
Then there's a red.
Then there's a yellow.
I wanted to keep that cool color look going the whole time I was drinking it.
But to get a much more smooth taste, you should mix it all together.
So I was trying to just go level by level, which probably you get less of a fulfilling experience that way.
But you get to still get your color levels.
I thought this was of the same ilk of thing as you having what you called one of your favorite drinks you ever had at Bubba Gump and then discovering there was zero alcohol in it.
Yes. So that's true, Kate.
So two years ago we went and I thought I had ordered an alcoholic drink with it with added fun colors.
And it was, as Eva Anderson put it, you just ordered an ice cream smoothie.
Wow.
So, yes, I didn't realize it until later that there I was like, I don't think I'm feeling anything.
I don't think there was alcohol in that.
Oh, I had a drink I wanted to shout out, and I think you can still get it down there.
But it was specifically kind of angled for when Cars Land was opening.
And it's a beer.
It's a racer five IPA.
And that's pretty easy to find in California.
I think it is a California brewery makes it and it's just a very solid beer, but it's got like a race car on it.
So we're like, we'll serve this around the car stuff.
And I was like, I admire that's a great attention to detail.
You know what?
I've been sitting on it the whole time.
And since you bring it up, I did for this and I haven't been drinking due to a headache.
That's that's how cool I am right now.
But I do got a red trolley ale right here, which is my favorite thing to get what I miss so much having in Cars Land.
I'll open it up at the end here.
Also, I love that thematically that you can get on a red trolley in California Adventure and the and the rocks are red.
I've said it many times.
I don't have to keep saying that I like this beer in Cars Land.
What I got to do is open it up and have some drink.
Yeah, yeah, that's right.
Anything else you want to shout out?
You know, I feel like it's all all the drinks I like have been covered.
But shout out to to just the people that go to the Carthay Circle Bar and go by themselves.
Because one time I did that and it was lovely and I just hung out of the bar by myself and had a drink.
So shout out to all the the lonely Carthay Circle Bar bar hoppers.
Bar bar bar flies.
Same time, which we hope we can do again.
Hello stranger.
Well, can I briefly I'm sure I've said this before.
I was at the sometimes I've done a show at WonderCon, which is over the convention center.
And I'll take the opportunity to go down early.
And like if I'm doing a comedy bit or something, I'll work on it at one of the bars.
And I went into Trader Sam's at noon and a guy came in and the bartender was like, hey, Joe, how are you?
What do you have in the usual?
And I was like, wow, that's all I want.
Yes, boy.
I saw that at Napa Rose once the bar at Napa Rose at the Grand California.
And yeah, it was clearly the regulars going.
That's a that's a big spender regular.
He looked like he was ready to spend money.
Yeah, they got fancy stuff.
They got fancy stuff.
And in looking up that place, they have a cigar menu.
I did not realize.
Wow.
Oh, evidently.
We're going to have to do cigars at Disneyland soon.
You got to.
That's the traditional spirit of the letter of the law.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
He has no problem.
Well, there's zero problem.
I have I forgot.
I wanted to shout out the the hotel, like the off brand hotels that are nearby on that one street.
I forgot what it's called.
Yeah, I forgot the one that has like all the like shitty hotels like a couple of them have free happy hours.
And you can just like go get like a free drink.
But you have to walk.
You're staying there.
Pretend like you're staying there.
That's a good tip.
Look, I have not actually heard that tip either.
That's like that's up there with the sunscreen tip.
Yeah, I've got some good tips.
I will look at any hotel.
They have to look into that and find the wrong hotel.
I went to one.
I don't know if I got away with it or what.
But if they've cracked down, I don't know.
Or you ordered a drink and didn't pay for it.
The hotel guests get you know how like some hotels have like free happy hours.
It was like one of those.
I think you get like you get like one free drink.
I don't know if they I don't know if I did more than like one drink.
But I mean, you got a tip.
You got to look into it too much.
It's free.
Of course.
Always tip if you get a free thing.
Yeah, you're stealing from a hotel.
You're staying at.
Yeah.
Can I ask one more question?
If you if we're you know, like here I'm enjoying my favorite beer from Disneyland.
If I or any of the listeners at home wanted to drink as you drink at 15 in a bathroom, what were you?
What were you hitting?
How do you make a cake?
A warm like almost hot water bottle full of let's say Jim Beam.
Jim Beam.
Uh huh.
Is it Jim?
What is it?
It's Jim Beam.
Yeah.
Beam.
I'm on both.
It's a bottle of like a Jim Beam whiskey and probably like, you know, a watery Diet Coke chaser and just chug as much as you can because you're you only have a limited amount of time where you're going to be in the bathroom.
And it will last you like probably, you know, 30 minutes or at least of walking around.
So get a hearty chug and then wash it down with some watery Diet Coke.
That's the 15 year old cocktail.
And make sure you get some face paint accidentally in your mouth.
Because it's because you're because you're sweating from the fake mustache that you that you thought was really funny to get.
I might pitch that that cocktail is called the Moxie.
There you go.
That's how you make a Moxie and Kate Raft.
You survived podcast the ride.
Thanks for being here.
What a blast.
Let's exit through the gift shop.
Is there anything you would like to.
My podcast Hot and Rich.
It's also a Twitch show on Tuesdays and Fridays at 4 p.m. Pacific Twitch.tv slash Hot and Rich.
And that's it.
I'm at Kate Raft on all the things.
Hey, wonderful.
Great.
Sure.
Hey, great.
And we're podcast the ride on all the things.
And you can get three bonus things every month if you go to podcast the second gate at Patreon.com slash podcast the ride.
Good stuff.
And I guess in the spirit of the fry cart that we all determined we like Westward Ho.
Forever.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts.com and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.