Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, The Second Gate,
with my good friends, Michael, Scott,
and my favorite student, Jason.
Favorite student, what the hell?
What Barney?
Why not me?
Oh, he's just such a good student is all I'm saying.
Student, when do you judge academic abilities?
I'm a teacher now.
Like kind of a second career.
Yeah.
The show's not going.
My show was canceled.
I thought we were just friends.
Friends, why did this power dynamic suddenly shift?
No, I'm in charge now.
The whole show is going to be this play.
Barney's the fourth Mike now.
Yeah.
Podcast The Ride, Second Gate, here we are today.
I'm busting out an old impression.
Probably my earliest impression ever, I believe.
Did you like do that around the house?
Yes.
Oh, interesting.
My sister was like three years younger than me.
So she was watching Barney.
It was right for her age, but I was fascinated by it.
She had a Barney doll, and I used to do the Barney voice
with the doll constantly.
That was like, I love, that was so much fun for me to do.
So it's back.
My voice, my Barney voice is back.
I'm a little hoarse.
I think we might be in a similar area.
I also have a younger sister and I felt, yeah,
she watched it a lot and I felt like I had to not like it.
And I was aware that there was a lot of Barney hate,
but maybe I did some like hate watching.
I definitely would like sit and watch Barney,
even if I like snarked it and made fun of it.
Maybe it was maybe for a lot of kids,
it occupies that slot of like the first thing you were too old for.
Or like sort of felt that way or felt pressured to feel that way to grow up.
I think that's right. Yeah.
Yeah. I had a little brother and he loved it.
And I wanted to hit Barney with a car.
Like I agree.
You were the cynical kid who hated Barney.
I hated it. I hated it.
I knew I was supposed to hate it.
Why do you want to hit me with a car, Jason?
I just did it like,
and it didn't have the refined sensibility of Eureka's Castle or a David the Gnome,
you know, that stuff that I liked when I was in like preschool.
Well, yeah, it is.
Or the like Sesame Street with its genre parodies and genuinely funny sketch style writing.
Barney certainly is a little more soft in a lot of ways.
It is an uninteresting show.
Yeah. Not sophisticated at all.
Yeah. Not subversive at all.
But there is a dividing line.
I think it's the line between old millennial and young millennial is like old millennials hate Barney.
Younger millennials loved Barney.
And it's such a fine, you can really just cut the generation in half, I think, at that moment.
Yeah.
Yeah. I mean, I have a lot of affection for him now because of like just goofing around with the doll.
You know, you did everything like kids would do, like I would go in my sister's Fisher Price fridge
and I'd be like, Barney's drinking alcohol.
Like that was like, I'd have like a little plastic cup and he'd be like drinking it fast.
And who knows what that means to a kid?
But I would be like, now Barney's drunk.
Barney has a gun.
Barney would fight with, yeah, I would have him fight with like characters too.
And I'm trying to think of who would be to the same scale because this was a Barney doll that was like
sort of similar to the Barney that's in the show that comes to life.
In case you don't know where we're going with this, there is a Universal Studios Barney show and play area
that we are actually going to talk about if you're wondering.
In Florida since 1995.
Since 1995.
Going even recently and maybe its days are numbered or they're limiting it for now.
The show has been going during COVID.
Okay.
Yes.
This show has been going for 25 years.
This show has outlasted Jaws, it's outlasted Confrontation, it's outlasted Back to the Future the Ride
and that's so fucked up.
Tower of Terror at DCA.
It feels like, this show does not feel like a linchpin and yet it's just like, it is a real like
titan when you say the timeline like that.
Yes.
It kept its head down, stayed out of the way, just chugged along, has outlasted the Barney TV show
which stopped making new content on the regular in 2009, although the reruns still air.
Currently on something, a channel called Universal Kids.
Did anyone know about the television channel Universal Kids?
No.
So that's where...
That's one of those like deep cable like if you still have cable and there's the weird 2000 channels.
Yes.
I believe it used to be Sprout.
I kind of remember Sprout.
I do know Sprout.
I'm familiar with Sprout.
So wait a minute.
Sprout became Universal Kids.
Universal Kids.
Or it was a segment on something like, I don't know.
PBS might also use that branding.
But yeah, Barney is still going strong.
And to give him the benefit of the doubt, I was trying to figure out, oh, is it because it's popular with international
guests because there was a Barney World Tour that World used lately.
I think it was around 2015 that mostly hit the United Arab Emirates and Saudi Arabia.
So there may be still...
But no theme park presence besides this, correct?
I am not sure about that.
If there's other Barneys.
I think this is the only one.
They touted it as the only place on Earth where you can see Barney every day.
Oh, that's crazy.
I will say I didn't even know this was there.
I didn't know this was here.
If I've been to Universal a few times, I didn't know you could get your picture taken with Barney.
I don't have that photo and I'm a little upset.
You genuinely didn't know until we talked about doing this?
I don't think so.
Maybe I saw it on the map, but I didn't realize what it was.
I don't think I ever wandered back into the plaza with the fountain and the statue, which I like the statue.
It looks like Barney is using his dump truck seat to hover in the air.
Wait, did you just call Barney's seat his dump truck seat?
Yeah, he's got a big seat.
He's got a big dump truck seat.
Barney's dump truck seat?
Dump truck seat.
People online talk about everyone, the moms in Pixar movies have dump truck asses.
So we say seat on this show.
Who says that?
Dump truck?
People, this is a thing.
What websites are you on?
This is a joke on Twitter.
Because Mrs. Incredible.
I've seen Mrs. Incredible be referred to as thick, but I have never ever seen dump truck ass in reference.
Yeah, but we say seat here.
So Barney got a dump truck seat.
He's using it to hover off the ground.
What other mom has a dump truck seat?
By the way, we're getting into dangerous territory.
We're getting into dangerous territory.
He can't even talk to animals.
Jason is trying to open it up for his perverted ways.
Barney's an animal.
That's true.
I'm just saying you brought in the mothers of the Pixar movies.
Well, I just didn't want it to make it seem like I just came up with the phrase dump truck ass out there.
I learned about it.
Wow.
Got a big dump truck seat.
I guess that's true.
The Barney statue.
One of the few statues that we don't have to pull down with shades.
This statue can stand.
A southern monument that can stay.
The Barney statue at Universal Studios Florida.
That is south of the board.
Yeah, that's south of the Mason Dixon.
Although I've seen older millennial kids try to go in there and tear it down because they hate them so much.
I'm surprised, Jason, you didn't try to drive your car through there and knock the statue down with your car.
You hated Barney.
I hated Barney, but I have to say reading about this did endear him to me, especially because there's like weird sections of the Barney Wikipedia where it's like some thought.
You know, some people think Barney led to a sense of entitlement among millennials and didn't teach enough about how to deal with difficult situations and unpleasant realities.
And I was like, Oh, that's shut up.
That sucks.
That's stupid.
Also, if anyone is complaining about millennial entitlement in 2020, get your fucking head examined.
Like freaks.
Still, that's still a talk.
Still a talk.
Just inherit.
We were left an awful world that just gets shittier and shittier.
Why do we want anything?
Why do we want things?
You know, why does a joy, a bright purple dinosaur?
For God's sake.
Yeah.
I think that Barney himself is a good design and is a character.
Like, ultimately, the show is nothing.
The show is just Barney praising, like, kids for like doing art projects, which is this is a bit I've done.
I've done with Lindsay around.
I'll just be like, that's a great macaroni painting.
Like, like, that's like most of the mostly what the show is.
And then like a kid is like a very minor problem.
And then they sing like, if you're happy and you know it, clap your hands.
And I don't even there's like there's not a ton going on, but the design of Barney is good.
Yeah.
And that's all you need, I think.
I mean, it's well, I'm a bigger fan, I have to say, of original Barney.
Well, go back like the first couple of videos where he's darker purple and boxier like this one, this side view where he's just got like,
a full rectangle mouth.
This is my Barney.
I think I don't think they should have softened these.
I like I like sharp face Barney.
I am a big fan of sharp face Barney as well.
I like there was him with a little beanie with a propeller on it in there that you showed.
Now that's good.
Yeah, Scott.
Now you bring it up.
I would like to play a clip from the original Barney, which was called Barney and the Backyard Gang.
These were the videos before the TV show.
Yeah.
Right.
So this was this was the the pointy pointy Barney.
Before they partnered with PBS.
Yeah, it's just individual.
Right.
And I did not watch this like first run.
This is just something I came upon today as I was researching.
You can see that Barney is I'll say this a little unnerving.
So here we go.
He's not quite as bubbly.
Starting in a kiddie pool.
This is when Barney appears.
The kids are all in a pool, which, yes, that's a little weird as well.
One more.
Well, I'm only one.
I'm only one.
And I'm only one.
And I'm four.
My kid sister.
She follows me everywhere.
Well, that's just because she is.
It's like also a sitcom, which is bizarre.
You're welcome to stay.
So are the rest of you.
You know what I always say.
Yes, mama, we know.
All right.
I have queued this in the wrong place.
Well, but you reminded me of this is another reason I like.
Well, I do like darker purple sharp face Barney.
I don't like that they originally the tapes originally included this mom
character played by Sandy Duncan.
I've spoken against Sandy Duncan in the past because she's one of those
perennial.
I don't know.
I don't know either.
I'm not sure.
I've not seen Sandy Duncan before.
I'm sure.
I've not seen her before.
I'm not sure.
I think Sandy Duncan is a very good actress.
I don't know.
I think Sandy Duncan is a very good actress because she's one of those
perennial Peter pans, which may be factored into my negative pan feelings.
Just she just like epitomizes the kind of like frighteningly friendly
entertainment that was that I believe my mom was reared entirely on
She is Sandy Duncan is to Barney.
What Haley Mills is to say by the bell slash.
Good morning, Miss Bliss.
Right when she was dismissed, we don't want this lady.
We just want to.
We just want to see what the kids are doing.
I think yes.
Sandy Duncan went away and the show sword.
This I believe is the correct area of the place I want to play.
But just that did give you a little hint of like there was this weird mom character
and it felt more like a sitcom more than just like Barney hanging out bad.
I like khaki mom shorts that are kind of what my tour guide uniform was.
Universal Studios.
Not a fan of the shorts.
All right.
Here we go.
That will go next weekend.
Okay.
So Sandy Duncan laughs.
Boy, that's good news.
We can make believe we're at the beach.
What do you mean?
Well, we can close our eyes and make believe real hard.
Close your eyes in a pool.
Never.
That's not how it's done.
I did.
No.
Over here.
Are you?
Wow.
What?
That's just by wind.
A powder guns.
Oh, I'll get swimsuits.
Why is he just laughing?
That's saying he's not saying anything.
Terrifying.
He's very friendly.
This hug has been going this entire time for the whisper.
Jason, since you were the chime and was her.
He is a dinosaur.
So like, he doesn't say it.
He just like laughs like a main, like a little like creep, like a little pervert.
He's like, I don't get a good vibe from this Barney is what I'm saying.
No, this Barney's definitely scarier.
Yeah.
Like he's less good for kids.
I realize, but I just like him more.
And look, he was later on.
He's wearing a sailor suit.
Yeah.
Young Mike Carlson.
He was.
And young Scott Jertner, as I determined.
Yeah.
They go into like a fantasy where he's like a sailor in the air.
The effects on this special too, or this tape are pretty great.
They're flying a tub around.
Yeah.
So anyway, I mean, that's, that's his old department.
This is backyard gang and his voice is also a little bit lazier.
It's like, it's like Homer first season or something.
Yeah.
Oh, hey.
Hi.
I'm Barney.
Get some frosty chocolate shakes.
So yeah.
It was also, yeah.
Barney was kind of Walter Mathi at the start.
Right.
So that was not my bar.
If you look at the VHS cover, they're really pushing like, actually I'll just share the
screen.
Like, look how they present it.
So much is Sandy Duncan, the point that like, she's way bigger than Barney.
Barney's like almost cropped out of this photo.
This is a picture of Barney.
I couldn't even tell you the name because there's so many names Barney and it's in the
three wishes.
Is it called three wishes or Barney and the backyard gang, which is way smaller or starring
Sandy Duncan, which is the biggest text or sing along with us.
Like there, this is all over the map.
This, this is some very poor, like this could be shown in a graphic design class.
Make sure your title is clear.
And then you have the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the,
the title is clear.
I mean, I guess they thought Sandy Duncan, we're like trying to under, yeah, underplay
Barney.
Yeah.
Cause Sandy Duncan, I guess they thought was the draw at that point for people who loved
wholesome entertainment and should never be the draw for people who loved wholesome entertainment
and never be the drug.
She was the rubber stamp of approval to me.
Hmm.
Well, I, we should be happy.
If anything's making millennials feel entitled or whatever, or presented too much of a fantasy
It's smiling.
Sandy Duncan showing you there's no problems.
You just to be chipper and dance your life away.
We should find out what the darkest thing Sandy Duncan was in.
Like what piece of entertainment?
Cause it seems like, yeah, she was only in happy, smiling, family friendly fair.
I assume you're looking it up now.
I think so.
Was she in like, was she ever.
And like leprechaun three or something.
She was leprechaun's mom or something.
Leprechaun three.
I don't know.
I'm not sure.
It seems like pretty just Disney.
It seems like million dollar duck and such.
And thank God Sandy Duncan was not brought into the, the universal attraction.
I have a point about the, the universal stuff, which is that.
I mean, some of Mike, you not knowing that this was there, it is this very tucked away
corner of the park that might be easy to miss that might like a lot of guests, especially if you're just in pursuit of
Diagon Alley or stuff that's more recent, you might just like overlook this whole area in general.
It is a little tucked away.
And in fact, this, I might declare this the weirdest name of a land, quote unquote, anywhere in major theme parks in
Disney or universal is mostly they follow.
Mostly like, all right, I see what this land did.
I see why it's called this.
But this whole area being called that Barney, of course, lives in Woody Woodpecker's Kids Zone.
Right. Yes.
Yes.
And the attractions in Woody Woodpecker's Kids Zone are.
Wait, I'm actually boy, this one surprised me.
Animal Actors on location.
So the Animal Actors show is part of Woody Woodpecker's Kids Zone.
Even though I was fairly certain that was part of World Expo, the other weird named area of that part.
Yeah, I know the western boundaries of Woody Woodpecker's Kids Zone is the Animal Actors.
Yes, that's correct.
A little dog from that show got out the other day was wandering around.
They were chasing him down by the movie makeup.
Pretty fun. Pretty fun little clip.
They got the dog, though.
They got the dog. Yeah, it's fine.
OK, that's good.
Back in your cage.
Yeah.
The elsewhere in Woody Woodpecker's Kids Zone.
OK, day in the park with Barney.
Curious George goes to town, which is another playground thing.
Woody Woodpecker's Nuthouse Coaster, Fievel's Playland and ET Adventure.
All of these.
This really underlines the schizophrenic nature of the universal kids properties.
We're like, what child?
Who are your favorite characters?
Well, I'd have to say Barney, Curious George, Woody Woodpecker, Fievel, ET.
Oh, and there's a SpongeBob gift shop.
What? There's a SpongeBob gift shop.
And currently there is.
I'll show you guys.
Currently, there's this.
What are I believe they're calling character moments because they are not doing some shows and meet and greets right now.
So Barney and BJ and Baby Bop just stand on a little stage and sing a song and wave to the crowd.
OK, that's all right.
There's a Fievel banner behind them.
Yeah, that's a cowboy hat.
Fievel brand. Yeah, Fievel's.
Yeah, I didn't even know this much land existed back there either.
This is like because this is what they were talking about.
Maybe putting Nintendo in for a while before it was going to go in Epic Universe.
And then who knows? Maybe it goes back here.
Yeah, they don't build that third park.
It's a huge plot of land.
And I remember going to Universal for the first time and being so excited despite the fact that I was so easily scared.
My family loved Alfred Hitchcock.
So to stand in front of the Bates House, the Psycho House, which was the set from Psycho 4 that they put in the park.
And you could get your picture at the bottom of the stairs.
And then next door was the original Universal Hard Rock Cafe that it was a big deal that you could enter from outside the park or inside the park.
Right.
That's an area I have intense nostalgia for.
Yes.
For whatever reason, being around that old Hard Rock, I don't know what it is and the weird.
I remember looking up at the scary Psycho House and it's so weird.
They just kind of arbitrarily also built one here that is not or in Florida that is not the original one.
So strange.
Yeah, this was all like a weird vacant trail until they put really disparate kids playgrounds throughout it.
It does feel like Poltergeist where they tore down a famous horror house and built like a very supposedly friendly, family friendly like house with Barney in it.
So like it does feel like this space might be haunted.
Mm hmm.
But I remember that observation being made that like they turned they tore down the Psycho House and put Barney up and that if you didn't like Barney, that was kind of a way to like damn it.
But I also don't think that's entirely accurate.
I don't think the show literally sits where the Psycho House was.
Right. No.
But it's it is it is interesting.
Like what I did not go to Universal when this Bates Motel was set up.
Like I was not there then.
So it's like was animal was animal actors open day one in Hollywood.
I keep saying Hollywood, Florida.
I believe so.
Yeah.
That was there.
Bates Motel animal actors.
Well, no, there wouldn't you wouldn't have had a view of one from the other like yet around a corner.
Yeah.
And then ET is weirdly there that doesn't really fit into this like calling it a kid ride isn't exactly right.
I mean, there's kids who couldn't go on that ride or would find that ride scary.
Yeah.
But I love the Fievel slide.
I love the Fievel slide.
I love the animal actor show.
I still do if I've ever at either of the Universal parks.
It's like, oh, what do we do?
We have some time to go.
Like we can go to animal actors.
I will always opt for animal actor show.
We got to do that one.
You talk about things that haven't changed.
And it's like that's you feel I mean, they're they're doing it right now, obviously.
But hopefully they are back at some point and you'll go like, oh, my God, still Mick Jagger monkey lips.
Still like embarrassed monkey who had their towel stole.
Oh, yeah.
He was covering up their groin because they got pulled out of the shower.
Like there's something real nice about.
Wow.
Some things never change.
I mean, I kind of like the fact that kids know it is barely.
It's just so odd.
It's such an expensive piece of real estate to still be stuck in like nineteen ninety five.
It's so funny.
And I am surprised.
I have not.
I have found myself bored wandering around Universal Orlando before, and I'm amazed I have not gone back here.
Like I I have never even been in like the Barney.
I have no memory of the Barney Plaza.
Like I guess when it opened, maybe my brother, I think he would have been too old for even he would have been too old for Barney by the time this show opened.
Hmm.
When was the last time you went on the Fival slide?
I don't know.
Is that one of the ones where you like have to be under a certain?
I feel like my parents did it with me.
I don't know that they actually say specifically how big you have to be on some of this, because like there's a Barney Playland here or it's called.
What is it called?
Barney's backyard.
But like, for instance, the Grizzly Challenge Trail at Disney's California Adventure, that's, you know, anybody can walk and climb that.
But there are little tunnels on the ground floor that are mostly for the kids.
That are mostly for children.
But you and I, I could fit those.
You and I went in this tunnel about five years ago, I think.
Oh, yeah.
I can squeeze in.
And I believe right before we did, like a young teen ran up to the tunnel, looked at it as if he was in a cartoon and went YOLO and jumped in the tunnel.
I do remember this.
Yeah.
And then you went in and I was like, well, I got to try it, right?
So, yeah, it's, it's, I don't know.
We probably, you probably could go on the 5-0 slide now.
It's just, it's, look, people would maybe look, look down on you a little bit because that's for children.
It's possible.
It's not as big as the Challenge Trail.
The Challenge Trail still, I think you can get away with it because like it's got big enough stuff for adults to.
Well, my white whale is the Pterodon flyers, I think it's called, or the Pterodactyl flyers.
The one over at the Jurassic Park at Islands of Adventure.
You have to be under a certain height.
And when I was like 12 or 13, whenever it opened, it was brand new.
So there was like a two hour wait for this rink eating thing, but it goes above the whole land.
And you know, I like to be high up, but I still, I never got around to riding it because it doesn't eat up a lot of people per hour.
So it always has a long wait.
And now I'm too tall.
While we're on the topic real quick, and I know we've touched on this a little bit.
I mean, we all, three of us, I assume as kids were into what you'd call a play McDonald's play place.
Chuck E. Cheese ball.
Like, right.
We're all in that zone.
I think most kids are.
It's not that unusual.
There was a place called Leaps and Bounds.
I remember Leaps and Bounds.
Yeah.
By my house.
That was like a three story tubes ball pit thing that I just was my favorite place.
It was maybe open for a year.
Maybe lasted a year.
And I think we went there when I was a little too old too.
We had like somebody's birthday party in like fifth grade.
Yeah.
And like we're a little too big to be going through those tubes.
But I would love an adult tube business.
A business where adults could crawl through tubes.
And I know we have like, what I've brought this up before, tough mudders and you get shocked and you're muddy.
And like this is temporary.
And I don't want that.
I want fun, colorful tubes in a big building, but big enough for adults to go in.
And look, the way I feel about it is YOLO.
You know, you only live once.
And let's have some adult tube fun.
But even, I mean, not like now though.
Not in a few years.
In a few years.
Let's celebrate the end of the disease.
But by, let's all like, all right, it's over.
Let's all just go touch everything we can all the time.
Let's, yes.
Let's all go crawl on our hands and knees through a dirty tube together.
Get like, get like a log jam of humans in the tube.
All breathing in.
And we'll say, and we'll all be taking deep breaths of each other's exhale and going, oh, isn't this nice?
Do you remember when we couldn't do this?
This is fantastic.
Big cuddle puddle in the tube, everyone.
We'll have a cuddle puddle in the tube and enjoy all the germs from each other's mouths.
It's going to be great.
So you're describing a non-sexual orgy.
This has nothing to do with sex.
Nothing.
This is all about fun and wholesome.
This is what Sandy Duncan would approve of.
Just tube fun.
This is just tube fun for adults.
For adults.
It's fine.
And it sounds better than those like drink a beer, throw an axe.
Of course it does.
Look, I'm not against throwing an axe.
I'll throw an axe if somebody invites me to do it.
Sure.
But what would you rather do?
Crawl through a bunch of tubes and go in an adult ball pit or throw an axe?
It sounds way better than like, oh, come to the Instagram museum.
Oh, it's the Museum of Ice.
Like, fuck you.
That's not a museum.
You build a shitty set.
Fuck off.
I agree.
Yeah, that's a weird area.
Like sometimes I'll think about doing them for the show.
Like there's a Britney Spears Instagram and then like, wait, why is it $150?
And like, none of this is the sets from the video.
This was like a, this is a closed Kmart a month ago.
There's nothing historic here.
I don't need to do this.
I get that this business I'm proposing, there's going to have to be a lot of waivers.
There's going to be a lot of waivers signed.
There's going to be a lot of people hurting their knees.
There's going to be a lot of like debilitating cramps happening.
Yeah, that's the issue.
Just the, your body maybe can't handle it as well.
I think though, and I'm, I'm a little feeling a little run down as I think a lot of us are at this moment, but I feel like I can still go if it comes to high octane tube fun.
Well, it's hard to know until you're, I have not had my tube fun tested recently.
I just think, I know this, you know, people, you know, they go like I was on the high school basketball team.
I could still play, you know, if push comes to shove, I think I can, I can still go.
I'm talking about give me an hour, hour and a half in a play place.
I think I can still do it.
I don't think I'm going to be passing out or anything.
I think I can still hold up is what I'm getting at.
I can still go on lots of slides.
I can go on lots of slides.
I can do like a flip into ball, a ball pit.
I can skate like kind of scale a little wall.
I'm trying to think of how to describe how they would have it.
You know, those are like little like, it's like a fake rock climbing.
Yeah.
For kids, it's not a little inclined.
Yeah. Yeah, I can, I can still do it.
I can, I can do a tiny one.
I'm not going to a climbing gym.
That's another thing where I was like, I don't, I don't see the appeal.
I don't. This is not for me.
Yeah. I mean, I trampoline parks, I think are getting close, which I actually have not been.
Yeah. And I've still been wanting to have like a birthday at one of these,
which I assume will end in like half of my friends getting a broken ankle,
more like landing on their neck and like we have to go to the hospital like 25 minutes in.
Everyone's like, what are we doing here?
And I'm like, it's fun.
We're all in our mid to late thirties.
Well, I hope Gio enjoyed walking.
Well, he could.
He had a good run.
Yeah.
Decades worth of walking.
He'll be fine.
Whatever shape he's in after that.
So anyway, I, I, I love the place.
Clearly.
I'm itching to play.
I think the most iconic piece of Play Place, I don't know, iconography is the office at Officer Big Mac,
a play place where you can climb up and go in his mouth.
I think that's the thing I'd most like to have, certainly, if I could own one of those and put it in a backyard.
Right. Which I guess now that I'm thinking about it as some sort of jail.
Yeah, that's a jail.
That's that's like getting kids accustomed to what it would be like to be held in a detention center.
So but yeah, that's that I was both excited to be in that and scared also because my memory of that Play Place thing was like it was it was on an incline.
You would climb up and then you'd like try to kind of fight to not slide back down to where the ladder was.
And there'd be a bunch of kids in there and it was just like, you know, mad.
There was Thunderdome in there.
Yeah, I feel like it's one of my only childhood, man, like like all of age three.
I remember one time being in that burger cage and that's that's it.
It really takes the pressure off me as a parent.
Like if he gets upset, I'm like, you won't remember this.
I mean, you like you, you'll remember like one thing per year, maybe.
And not this year.
No way.
Yeah.
My memory is off.
My memory of it, too, is that it was about 10 feet tall.
Of course, I will show you the reality of what it is.
It is, you know, maybe four feet off the ground, three feet off.
Is that it?
Is it your memory of it?
Like it was like a towering, like two story.
Yeah, yeah, absolutely.
Here it is.
Wow.
That's shocking.
Yeah, I didn't.
Yeah, like a very small girl is exactly the height of the pole in this picture you're showing.
But it felt like you felt you were climbing Mount Everest.
Yeah.
Was there like an observation deck because there's holes in his hat and his constant hat.
Oh, maybe.
Oh, yeah.
Could you climb up and see in there or is that just like so kids don't suffocate?
It's a good question.
It is.
I don't.
It is open air.
Oh, the tube, the tube.
Yeah, I guess you needed some holes in there just to be safe.
Yeah.
I wonder just out of curiosity.
I'll look this up while we're talking how much this would cost because it looks like
people have bought them and put them in their backyard.
Well, I've looked into expensive McDonald's items before and the thing that I found is
that a lot of them, while relatively affordable, cost like $800 to ship if you aren't in the
area where it's being sold.
And at least in one point, at one point in time, these were being sold very heavily in
the Chicago area.
So perhaps you could use your family connection.
And if somebody has a car that can move one of these things, you could get that discount
and truck it back to Los Angeles and put it in your apartment.
You know, this is the stuff our parents didn't think of.
This is what we were denied.
The thought of like, you know what we could do?
We could buy some old fast food restaurant play equipment and give it to our children.
They weren't creative at all.
No, they didn't think to do something that I did recently, which is watch a trade show
video from the 70s shot on a millimeter film encouraging McDonald's franchises to buy
these things and showing you product by products like the apple pie tree will delight children
of all ages.
This is really like dingy red tinted film.
I mean, I love this is like the definition of the kind of thing I want to watch.
But I would like show my if I told my parents, hey, remember how we would play at the McDonald's
Playland?
Well, recently I found a trade show film.
They'd go like, what did we do?
Why didn't we?
How'd you end up locked in your childhood and only getting more and more boring by the year?
You spent your 30s in the 1970s having key parties and putting meat into jello molds.
We spent it watching old trade show videos on YouTube.
We are not the same.
We spent it on eBay trying to find the vintage McDonald's playground ride fillet of fish
play play spring toy that sold for $500.
Was that like one that you'd sit?
Is that like a sort of a bucking bronco pony kind of little?
Yeah.
Okay.
Five hundred bucks, hundred dollars shipping.
Where where's it shipping from?
Oh, let me I got to look it up.
It's already sold.
Oh, this was from Wisconsin.
Midwest.
Yeah.
I bet that officer Big Mac thing sells fast.
I don't see any of them on here.
I bet that one's that.
Yeah, that's tough.
Maybe we should do a this.
This could be a we could take a little time.
But if we eBay Barney and see what the most expensive item is.
Oh, that's good.
We never plan these anymore, but we could do a little, you know.
Oh, sure. Yeah.
Yeah.
Souvenir Smackdown as we go.
I like when they just come up mid episode.
Sure.
Let's get it back to Barney.
Yeah, I have to give universal credit.
It does seem like in nineteen ninety five money, like they spent a good
amount of money on this area and this show like Barney was huge at night in the mid
nineties like and I I watched the video.
I watched the video of one of the last ones before it was put on ice for covid
scale backs like this show was running where peak.
Boo comes out and goes like remember to social distance and keep your masks on.
And yeah, that was a lot.
That was a lot to handle.
But watching the pre show, I was like, well, this is a pretty nice theater.
They built like a goofy house.
I was like, oh, this is a whole different room.
And then there was like a cloud sequence like the rain clouds were raining and
then the rain stopped and there were doors behind it.
I was like, oh, this is actually pretty good.
And then the whole show is a theater in the round, which I think that's interesting.
You don't see that often in like theme park shows.
It's like Dane Cook at Madison Square Garden.
That's right.
That's like exactly the same vibe when Barney comes out with Baby Bob and BJ.
And if you look, if you look from at the Barney stage from above, it's got the big
Sufi, it's got the big Sufi logo on it.
The super figure, the Sufi.
Barney and Dane Cook, both a lot less in the public eye since 2009.
That's a good point.
I am.
Yeah, we should talk about what the what the show is.
Yeah, there's a theater in the round that you build to, but you get there and it's a
little like outdoor.
Here's where we gather everybody up in a little house and a waterfall looking thing,
like Jason said.
And you you're you're you're waiting and then you start seeing little doors open and
that is the appearance of peekaboo.
The character's name is peekaboo.
Do either of you I didn't write it down.
What's the his full his or her full name?
They make it so that man or woman could do it.
Yes.
Patricia Aloysius Bartholomew or Patrick Aloysius Bartholomew.
I see.
Condensed to peekaboo, which is his name because it is his favorite game.
Right.
Yes.
And he is what a professor who knows Barney.
Yeah, that's sort of the vibe of it.
A professor.
It's very similar to the Eminem.
It's not that similar to the Eminem professor, but it's the same.
It's a narrative functionally.
Mm hmm.
Yeah, he's Barney's friend.
He's your hookup.
Like, no, no, I totally know him.
Just stick with me.
I'll take you.
You've also got a is it an animatronic or is it a puppet?
And how do they time it to speak at the right time?
Because there's a big parrot named Bartholomew.
Oh, I couldn't tell.
What is it?
Like, is it live operated?
But there's nobody behind it.
I'm not sure what you're looking at.
I think it's a puppet.
Yeah, I think it's they might be able to cue just the lines like on a like we always just called them carts.
Like the in the student radio station cause they still some old like equipment where like it was a big box.
You would like plug a cartridge in and it would play as soon as you hit the button.
There was no lag like on a cassette.
So I think stunt shows have some of those set up where like as soon as you hit the button, the sound plays.
I feel like any character that's not the human, it's all recorded.
They're not doing any like the puppets and the costume.
People are not doing any crowd work.
They can't.
That's correct.
Yeah.
And eventually, yeah, Barney, Baby Bop and DJ are are pre-recorded.
Yes.
And doing clear.
I was like, let me look up earlier choreography.
Can I see a video of this from 1996 and then like recently mid pandemic and it is the same.
They all like go to the center and the I love you song and play like and it's the same little carts with inflatable animals.
This is like the exact same show.
They've been doing the greatest hits on tour forever here.
No new albums.
And I have to say the like 2020 audience, while a little small, the kids were into it.
They were digging this show.
They were clapping along, playing along.
Like I, I, I do think this is good for kids.
Like repetition, kids like simple songs, like, you know, I get the appeal.
And when you design a theme park, I think it's left out of the discussion a lot of like, well, you need to appeal to ages two to eight.
If you're going to be a family theme park, you have to distract very, very little kids.
You have to entertain them a little.
Sure.
I mean, my only plus up for this would be like a turtle talk situation with Barney where he could actually respond to the kids.
That would be all I would, I would want from it.
He can, they can do the same songs.
Yeah.
They can do, they can do kookaburra sits in the old oak tree.
They can do that classic.
But I just want, I want Barney to do a little crowd work like Dane would maybe.
But just a little, you know, be able to react live to some, some change in the audience.
He doesn't have to go Rickles.
He doesn't have to, you know, let's put our purses in the circle.
Let's put our purses and dance around.
I just want to dance.
Oh, are you a German guy?
Oh, a Nazi?
Not Rick, not Rickles Barney, but like a little, a little loose, a little loose crowd work.
This guy looks like he's got an itchy asshole.
Yeah.
For going Dane.
If you're going Dane.
Yeah.
It's hard to say.
Let's go hit up the BK Lounge.
I, yeah, I mean, it's, it's cute.
It's well done.
It's like the lighting cues are nice.
It seems like a good high tech theater.
That water effect is good.
Yeah.
I mean, it's hard to like, you know, you can hate on Barney, but I don't, I don't hate on this show.
This seems like just well done and entertaining if sort of oddly perhaps irrelevant.
I mean, maybe a three year old doesn't care.
They'll like look at whatever.
But when you're dealing with like the micro generations that like, you know, when you're dealing with preschool age, I feel like this show hasn't been on since 2009.
That's like three generations at least who don't really, I bet don't really know Barney.
Yeah.
I would unless, yeah, I guess that they're showing reruns and I guess it probably is all up to the parents.
If the parents have some affection for it, then they'll show their child Barney the reruns or whatever.
I don't know if you can stream Barney.
I don't know if there's a Kimberly Clark diaper streaming service that exists.
There might, it might exist.
I think if you are a theme park is probably the best place because like you could introduce like a two or three year old to Barney, the pre show, the show.
And then there's a gift shop where you can get the dolls at the end.
And like that's an entirely self-contained bubble.
So you could get a kid to know nothing about Barney.
And within the span of an hour, they could be like, all right, I'm all in on Barney.
This is my new favorite thing.
Right.
Oh yeah.
Little stations that teach them.
Yeah.
It's just my only credit as an adult.
My only criticism of the show is it's not, it's fine that it's for kids.
I don't need, I don't need body humor, of course, but like versus the peanuts show at nots, the peanuts shows at nots, which are certainly not sophisticated oftentimes, but they do a little, you get a little something.
You get your thriller parody, which spooky nights, you know, you go, you get a little, there's a little something for the parents.
There's a little like interest.
Like this feels like, you know, put a costume on Barney once in a while.
Let's change up a song.
Let's do a parody song.
Like, you know, like Chuck E.
Cheese does.
Like, let's do a little, let's play with the Barney IP a little bit.
He can get loose.
Barney can get loose.
But that doesn't have to be so uptight.
That's by design though, isn't it?
Like Barney made just for the kids, like Sesame Street and other things like that.
Kids for the kids and for the parents get a little too.
Well, sure.
I just think I think it's more of a, I think it's more of the whoever's controlling Barney as a very specific idea.
Yeah.
Barney is.
And then also it costs money to do any changes and they would prefer to just keep this thing the same for 25 years because who gives a shit?
It's for little, little kids.
I came across this, that this show was written by Jason Sorrell, who wrote the the haunted house.
He wrote the the Haunted Mansion of Pirates of the Caribbean books, longtime Universal and Disney creative person.
Wow.
And his first run at Universal.
Every year I found this on like a wiki and then I looked on, I found his LinkedIn page and he does listed under his credits from his first few years at Universal.
Wow.
Oh, that's cool.
Yeah.
I like that.
You know, you know what you got to give him credit for and kids must love this.
This is like a good like magic trick illusion and maybe the first that they get to see is the transformation of little doll Barney into big Barney.
Yes.
That's got to be huge when you're a kid.
They do live the thing that they did in very poor special effects on a VHS in 1989.
Yeah, it's the the I am a big fan of the doll Barney.
From the second version of the series, that's like very round.
Yeah.
I won't call him like a dump truck doll.
I won't say something like that that Jason would say, but I his you know what I'm talking about how he is very rounded, very pleasingly round.
He's pleasingly round.
I mean, that's right.
I'm not going to deny that's right.
But it's sexualization of Barney.
No, it's just you know, just you love a perfect sphere.
You guys like those ice cube spheres, you know, we do like that.
Yes.
You see this?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Cute toy.
Definitely a cute toy.
Yes.
But but the dolls were not like the dolls were actually not as pleasing.
No, no, but the perfect camera ready one.
Yeah.
More so.
I also one thing I think my feelings about Barney as a kid were mixed, but I can certainly say I did not like baby bop.
Baby bop really.
Yeah, baby bop is is yeah, there's not a lot.
The baby unfortunately has kind of a grating voice.
Yeah.
It's like really crazy.
I can't do it, but yeah, me like and then BJ.
I have not as upset about, but I feel that BJ is a real poochy.
Like, oh yeah, it is like cool in a generic way, but otherwise does not really bring a new dynamic to the table, does not influence the dyad.
If you will, if you're going to introduce a third character, they should really bring more to the table than just being like also a dinosaur, but who like is on a scooter sometimes.
Yeah, he's I mean, he's got the cool gym shoes and base in like sideways baseball hat.
And then he's baby bops older brother.
Okay.
Was this their attempts to reach out to you or me, Mike?
I think because did they sense that there are a lot of older brothers who we need to pull into the fold.
I think you might be onto something because I do think when they introduced BJ, I, it certainly piqued my interest.
I was certainly like, well, who is this new cool dinosaur?
Now I, they didn't stick the landing because I wasn't like all in on BJ, but I certainly was like, who wouldn't mind getting to one of these BJ dolls?
I didn't, I didn't have one, but I'm just saying I think, I think that was probably part of it.
Barney was a very paternal figure.
He was, he was in charge.
So baby bop was a character the kids could relate to.
But then they figured, okay, well, they have to have a girl character and a boy character.
And they definitely like BJ is like Bart, their version of Bart Simpson.
Yeah, BJ shooting cans.
Shooting cans with a BB gun in the backyard, setting off sparklers and fireworks.
Did they think they would trick us by having a he's yellow and has spiky hair?
They kind of tricked me though.
They tricked me for a little bit.
So it's kind of worked.
I just think they needed to make him a little bit more engaged, like his personality better.
I was too into cable at that point, cable from the X-Men.
So they've, they had given BJ a giant gun and a lot of pouches, maybe, but the yellow, yellow wasn't enough for me.
If somebody could, and look, I, if we call for fan art, if someone could in the audience draw a Rob Liefeld BJ.
I would lose my mind.
I just, God.
Scott, Scott, I got to tell you.
So, so Rob Liefeld, Scott in the nineties would draw these like crazy.
You've probably seen the pictures of it.
Crazy muscle men characters that like doesn't make sense proportionally.
And I'll show you this real quick.
He is the co-creator of Deadpool amongst other like extreme like this Captain America.
This is Captain America image comes up a lot.
Oh, I recognize the incredibly detailed, incredibly detailed anatomically all over the map.
But like now has kind of come back around to being like outsider art.
Like it's just so garish.
Somebody also made, somebody also made this.
Yeah, like this is what he would look like shirtless.
And somebody's done what real life Chris Evans playing Captain America would look like with the proportions of.
Right.
Like this is what he would look like.
A mammoth rib cage.
These characters all have dump truck packs.
Exactly.
Yes. Yes.
So round.
So if somebody could draw like a jacked up BJ.
Beats Rob Liefeld BJ.
Yeah.
That would be great.
But we also know I don't think I was we were maybe way off of the show by the time they introduced who I guess is BJ and baby bops cousin Riff.
Yes.
You guys know about Riff.
I know about Riff.
I hate Riff.
Orange.
I really hate.
Now this is interesting because now he reminds me I think Riff is kind of in the family of an Aladar.
Well.
I think he bothers me the same way Aladar bothers me.
I thought I can't get on board with that.
I can't caught into that.
No.
So Mike you don't like Riff.
I don't know a lot of I'll be honest I don't know a lot about Riff.
I don't love the look.
He's kind of he's got kind of like he's like half asleep.
Yeah those eyelids are very unsettling.
I'm not against him but I don't think I think of the four designs he's the least interesting design purely from an aesthetic point of view.
The other three are I think pretty well designed.
Riff I don't know what's going on with him.
He's got like no he's got like like.
Come on Riff.
Kicking.
I don't like I don't like Riff at all.
I like it when he's kicking more.
Maybe Riff might be the funniest character now that I'm looking at but I'm not sure.
I'm kind of warming up to Riff.
Riff is clearly the gazoo of the great gazoo of this show.
I mean I'm looking at a clip on YouTube now I've not watched it.
Learn to dance with Riff and maybe we'll use this clip to determine if we like Riff once and for all.
Sure.
I don't know Riff's voice at all so we'd all be experiencing this together.
Let's experience Riff for the first time and really give Riff a fair shot.
All right.
No judgment Riff.
No.
Okay Riff.
Bring me over.
This is your American Idol audition.
Okay.
Let's see what you got.
And you'll be happy to know he's got a little ukulele so that's also another strike in his favor.
All right so here we go.
Just can't get enough.
Wait a minute.
Yeah.
Just can't get enough.
So we're watching okay so right now we're watching some sort of music video.
He's not Riff is not speaking but he's dancing a lot to Just Can't Get Enough.
Is that Riff's voice?
That sounds like Barney to me.
All right I gotta find Riff talking here.
Barney on YouTube has 1.4 million subscribers so.
Guess it is working.
Yeah it might still be.
Popular.
I'm Riff is the name of this video.
Yeah and there's pictures of him with like he's fishing now and I kind of like that.
No I'm out on Riff.
No.
Oh Scott he's playing the sax.
He's playing the sax Scott.
Unmute.
Okay hold on hold on.
You're right you're right you're right.
That's sax though.
Okay so here we go.
This is I'm Riff.
Hi I'm Riff.
Oh Scott you like this music.
Oh Scott.
I like the kind of music I like yes.
Hi I'm Riff.
Let's go have some fun with Barney.
No.
Okay Riff has.
No raspy voice no.
Riff has a lot of vocal fry going on.
Yeah not into it.
Riff also smokes.
Like Riff smokes parliament longs.
Riff is a poor man's Tommy Pickles from Rugrats.
Alright one more clip here to see if we can save Riff's reputation with Scott.
Hi to hell you everyone.
No Heidi Ho get out of here.
He's playing the sax Scott.
Only one character left to say Heidi Ho and that's Mitch.
What are you guys up to?
We just planted these yellow flowers.
Cool-a-rama.
Oh they look great.
Thanks.
It was a project for our scouting club.
No no.
Out on Riff.
It's a scouting club.
A club is a group of friends who plan things.
What the fuck is Barney's voice?
Alright so this is another thing we haven't gotten to.
They changed Barney's voice and it's really weird.
Like it's much different.
It's like ill.
Yeah he sounds weird in the last so many.
So points for the Universal show.
It's the original voice Bob West of Barney.
And he also was the voice of Pasquale and Jasper of Chuck E Cheese.
Wow.
Oh my god.
Did not realize that.
That's great.
That really.
I mean that's three icons right there.
What a great VO guy.
Yeah.
Who like worked at the company.
I think in all these cases or he got his start at Chuck E Cheese.
He like wrote the shows or was part of the creative and then did voices and that.
He was like the king of Texas children's entertainment because Chuck E Cheese and Barney all came from the.
Was Dallas or I don't know.
I mean somewhere in Texas.
Yeah.
Another person with a connection to the Barney show at Universal.
There was a woman named Lauren Mayhew who's worked in the parks a lot.
She went from playing baby bop in the show in the park to then getting word that they needed a new baby bop like costume performer on the TV show.
So then auditioned and then got the part and took over the role like wow for the TV show and then eventually also went on to do the world like audition for the like one of the national or international tours they did too.
So she played baby bop and then I believe he had a little bit of a career in the show.
Baby bop and then I believe after the show ended went back to Universal and has worked in the park and done the character again.
Wow.
Oh geez.
It led to a job.
Yeah.
Wow.
A different job.
Yeah.
It's kind of in the same neck of the woods job but I thought that was cool and there's interviews with her out there about she's worked a lot of jobs in the parks.
Does anyone know anything about the guy who was in the Barney suit on the show.
I've heard.
Yeah.
You go ahead.
I think I know you're I know what you're talking about here.
Well if you were if you're pre if your preschool age stop listening to the episode because the guy's name is David Joyner and he was always Barney and all live shows and on the movie and all the all the things.
And today he is known as a tantric massage therapist and the well he you know he explains how his the being in the suit in you know that's a very physical act and he considers that like having to be in this costume all day that got up to 120 degrees and was so you know physically taxing he calls that tantra.
Like tantra isn't necessarily a sex thing it's just being able to like have the stamina to do something forever and he says how the energy I brought while in the costume is based on the foundation of tantra which is love everything stems grows and evolves from love love heals and allows you to grow.
So he's you know he's this very spiritual person as I said tantra isn't necessarily a sex thing in this case it certainly is because his practice is sex you could get you go to tantra harmony dot com and you know tell him your issues and he will have sex with you and part of it is that in order for all the spirits to get through and for it to be more as blissful as possible it has to be unprotected.
So no condoms involved if you're going to have sex with the guy who played Barney.
Yes.
Sandy Duncan would not approve of this.
They're kind of at opposite ends of the spectrum in terms of people involved in the franchise.
She might Sandy Duncan would have maybe problems with phraseology like here's a quote from him.
When you go down on a woman it should be just like you're saying grace like blessing the food you're about to receive.
No food in the world.
Oh wait I should do it as no food in the world.
When you go down on a woman it should be like you're saying grace like you're blessing the food you're about to receive.
No food in the world can compare to goddess nectar because spirit is involved before you taste the goddess nectar give thanks.
My kids win.
This metaphor doesn't track for me because I always found grace to be very like perfunctory and fast and that doesn't that doesn't.
Oh you're right.
Yeah right.
A thousand percent.
Yes.
If that's what you're doing if you're if you're going down on someone with the speed of grace like I know my family is great.
And then the father son.
Bless his food.
Yeah.
Food.
That's a nice is not satisfying to your god.
Yeah I feel like that's a way to build resentment not connection if that's your approach to the act.
All right.
The name of the father.
All right here we go.
Look click click.
Okay.
All right.
Very good.
I don't think this I don't think this performer knows how to treat his goddess.
That's my.
This thing is pretty uniform across David joiners discussions.
There's a lot of reviews of his services which are glowing.
People are pretty excited about all this.
Is he any help.
I'm not sure if it's yelp but he I mean so he controls the reviews.
I see all people.
I mean it sounds like people had a wonderful time.
There is a vice article about all this and there's people who seem kind of well there's people who just straight up say.
This is prostitution.
What he is doing.
Yeah.
Money is being exchanged and you have unprotected sex.
Then this is sort of a shady thing.
I don't I don't want it.
I don't know either way.
I don't want to cast judgment condoms block the energy is a pretty iffy phrase.
Condoms block the energy.
Oh my god.
I do.
Everyone does sign a consent form though.
So that's good.
Oh my god.
Everything's on the open up.
That is really that is really dark.
It's pretty crazy.
He also apparently was like pretty vocal about all this.
He was not running this practice while doing the Barney show.
But I think if you met this man and talked to him he would start talking about tantric stuff.
So they didn't they let him do the show.
But attorneys said that he was not allowed to teach practice or talk about tantra while under contract playing the character because that is a lawsuit waiting to happen.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Hmm.
So he had to bid this bid this to do.
It was not like Sting where he could make it part of his persona while still doing his art.
Right.
Well he didn't bid it a do.
He just kind of edged.
He just kind of built up over years and then the tantric energy.
He stored up the tantric.
Stored up the tantric.
I'm sorry.
Too much of my tantric energy being blown off card because the 1994 Northridge earthquake.
That was just Barney shooting.
An extinction event.
Oh man.
I am I also I'm pretty sure that I was once around this man because you know I like doing things at hotel bars as we all do.
And there's a really good one.
There's a good like bar at the top of a hotel in Glendale.
Yes.
And we had a birthday party there with the with the thinking that like oh because it'll kind of just be us.
There won't be like some other massive group of 200 people who are competing for space with.
And one time for Aaron's birthday we went up to this place and it was packed.
It was 200 people and we didn't know what it was all about.
It was like the most raucous incredible birthday party we'd ever seen.
And I think it may have been if it wasn't I think it was a woman who the party was for.
But I remember we sort of intermingled and somebody was like see that guy over there.
He was in the Barney suit and people were he was like holding court.
People loved this guy.
Everybody's talking to him.
He's king of the party pointing at everyone.
Wow.
So I guess the guy's popular.
I'm not sure if he was popular with these people because of his work.
That's hard to say.
But well we know there's another rooftop bar that's local that has a swingers night once a month.
Yes.
That's right.
So it's only parties of 12 nerds and raucous.
Yeah.
Sexually liberated groups.
There'll be times in massive numbers.
Times when we've tried to go.
We are definitely not.
Time to go to the bar and it's like no no no this is swingers night.
You have to be a swinger to go up there.
That's right.
That's happened several times.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Oh man.
That's what happens at the rooftop bars.
So if you're interested in a session with David Joyner go to Tantra Harmony.
It's not an official ad obviously.
No he didn't pay us.
This is just what Scott is doing.
This is out of the kindness of his heart.
Yeah.
Just just to spread the word.
What do we miss?
Barney.
Barneyville station.
The play area.
I did miss this.
All right.
Let's let's yes.
Mike has pulled out the Barney's backyard page on the Universal website.
Now let's get away from all that salacious material and let's start with the train which
I'm squinting and says BJ's Express.
All right.
OK.
Great.
A Barney as a yeah Barney as a train station and a train of some kind here.
I'm not sure if that's in actual like Canon on the newer show.
I don't know.
Go to go down to the copy a little bit.
Hmm.
Hop on BJ's pop on BJ's Express train and plan a pretend to get away.
Oh.
It's not like.
Oh yes.
But then on this plan getaway there's an actual murder.
No one is leaving BJ's Express train until we crack this case.
No need.
It was riff.
Oh I know it was riff.
I've had a bad feeling about riff since day one.
I like riff now.
No riffs a murderer.
Even if riff murdered someone on this train I'm liking him.
That might improve my opinion.
I suppose.
Riff was a murderer.
Riff is a saxophone playing dinosaur train murderer.
Riff is male.
Yes.
I think so.
That voice is like a French.
See she.
Riff sounds like an Orange County divorcee.
Riff is like a rock and roller.
Like riff can play instruments.
Yeah I'm looking up Riff's personality is all about music.
He hears music everywhere he goes.
Which ties directly into his theme song.
I hear music everywhere.
The music.
I guess we got to do this cute poll for riff.
The music tells me to do things.
I think it's important that people see riff playing the sax though.
To be, to give a full determination of if riff is cute.
That's the most likable riff that I saw yes.
But I can't give him points just because of sax.
Just because riff is associated with easy listening music.
It's typically a way into my heart.
I'm going to find riff playing more easy listening music to convince you.
I mean this makes me want to like take riff and take riff footage.
And put some of the stuff I like under it.
Your David Sanborn or your Tom Scott.
If you have an hour during this week that might happen.
Yeah sure.
I'll give it a go.
Well what have we missed?
I do have some Barney eBay results if we want to do a little.
I have some yes.
We might have found the same thing.
Maybe we're looking at the same.
Are you doing like by highest price?
That's usually how I do it.
So we're probably in the same zone.
I didn't look too hard.
So if you have anything good I'll keep it blind.
No I don't have anything particularly good.
Well we don't have to do it.
If nothing's that good.
Well I will say nothing is that good with Barney.
But I do think I found the mother lode when it comes to McDonald's.
Geez.
A full play land.
20 train.
Twenty one thousand dollars.
Twenty one thousand.
It's everything.
It's the little it's the little boppers.
The filet of fish.
Yep.
A little Bench tree sitting next to grimace.
This is the ultimate.
Geez.
So twenty one thousand is how much they're asking for it.
I don't know.
It doesn't say where they're located though.
You know.
Free local pick up.
Should I make an offer.
Should I make offer like a hundred.
They're not going to get twenty one thousand.
What do you think they're aiming for.
Fourteen fifteen grand.
Yeah probably.
I bet they would take fourteen thousand.
Yeah.
I don't have a home.
Go ahead and pay.
Go ahead and offer.
All right.
Here I go.
Fourteen thousand dollars.
He did it.
He's typing it in.
I don't have a house with a yard or a house in general.
Yeah.
But I do want to buy fourteen thousand dollars worth of McDonald Playland equipment.
Of course.
I know we all do.
That bench with Ronald.
It's the bench where Ronald's sitting in the middle.
Can you imagine like like putting that in a whole house like I guess I could I guess
there would be no problem with it.
People would actually be the envy of the neighborhood.
Yeah.
I guess some of the neighborhood.
All right.
Fine.
So people put up fun Halloween decorations giant things.
Now I think people are slowly more comfortable with.
Yeah.
You could do a front yard display of McDonald's.
Absolutely.
If you could get the bench with Ronald on it flanked by the two by like two Home Depot
12 foot skeletons like that would be just so great.
Mm hmm.
Well there's something to shoot for.
Maybe the Patreon will go up and give us each an extra twenty one thousand dollars next
month.
And well we could you could.
Well you can come.
How about you could come be in the Playland if we buy this.
That's a good idea.
Yeah.
And then we'll sell tickets to it like Homer.
Yes.
Well that's our theme park.
Right.
That's where this has to go is that we actually build good boy land.
Well sure.
And with Ambassador Sandy Duncan.
No never.
Statue of Sandy Duncan.
Not allowed in good boy land.
But I and I will be performing down on Grandpa's farm.
Imagine a place.
All the songs from Day in the Park with Barney.
I like down on Grandpa's farm.
I like down on Grandpa's farm too.
I had to say.
Barney song.
I thought all the songs were solid in this.
Imagine a place I liked.
I really liked in that one song when they all they had their laughing simultaneously down pat like for sinking the mouth movements all together.
I thought that was pretty impressive.
Technically the people in the costumes doing a good job.
I like when they push the carts around with the inflatable barnyard animals.
Oh yeah.
Skunk.
And that's fun.
Yeah.
I had to know another note though.
You know where's Riff?
No.
Where is he?
It shouldn't be in this.
Everyone's going to pretend.
A bunch of people on Twitter are going to pretend to like Riff.
An unknown Barney character for good reason.
As soon as they see a GIF.
Because I said I did not like it.
As soon as they see a GIF of him playing saxophone they're going to fall in love.
Seems inevitable right?
Yes.
We love Riff now.
I wasn't pro you know you can't judge a book by its cover because I was anti Riff initially.
But the saxophone put it over the edge.
So yeah.
I guess.
All right.
Only with a saxophone and only if Riff doesn't talk.
I don't want to hear that horrible voice.
So if you block that with a saxophone then fine.
I mean we'll put it we'll put Riff against that baby Aladar and see.
Even like what if people like one or more than the other.
So I mean I think people with saxophone will really like Riff.
The only time I've been way wrong is Mr. Six.
People love friggin Mr. Six.
Yeah that ratio was yeah higher than you might expect.
Yes I thought Mr. Six was more divisive but people love a dancing old man.
Yeah.
Six Flags should have looked at that data and brought him back immediately.
Well they fucked up big time and it's you know I'm just glad that the people responsible for firing Mr. Six only went on to do many many more extremely lucrative jobs.
That's the way.
Wait I have one more thing.
I saw YouTube comment and I found no proof of this but in speaking you know.
Oh I know exactly where you're going to continue.
Yeah okay okay.
Yeah yeah yeah.
I found it.
This is from Lord Vader 0727 who has a little Ewan McGregor avatar.
Me and my friends were at Universal the other day and during the show Barney started whipping and nae naeing and it was hilarious.
Yes I saw this a few months ago right.
Yes when did this happen.
How can we find footage.
Yeah I was looking for it too.
I also saw that comment and it's the Beetlejuice show at least that happened when that was popular.
Yeah.
Yeah why whipping and nae naeing today.
Well I mean I don't I would be thrilled if it said Barney did the Gangnam Style dance.
Oh could you imagine.
But this is what I was talking about before.
I want that in this show.
Yeah.
So I want him to floss.
I want him to throw up a dab.
I want him to do all of that and the crowd's going to go wild for it.
And then I want Riff to do the dab and I want Riff to floss.
I guess that would also make me.
Imagine Riff flossing.
Everyone.
Okay everyone calm down right now who's listening and close your eyes and imagine.
I want you to do this thought exercise.
Imagine Riff imagine he sets down his saxophone and then Riff starts flossing.
How can you be mad at that.
Oh and a theater in the round where he has to rotate to make sure every section of the audience gets to see him head on flossing the beautiful park set.
I like the set.
I like the set in the theater.
I think it's good.
I think they did a good job on the sets on these.
But yeah Riff.
Riff.
Is there Riff.
Is there a Riff too.
No Riff flossing would be great.
Yeah.
Riff flossing is a blessing.
No food in the world can compare to Riff flossing because spirit is involved.
So give thanks.
You survived I guess the ride.
By second gate with a bunch of Barney stuff.
And yeah I don't know.
Do we all sing I love you you love me.
We could say just remember I love you.
Just remember.
The hosts love you.
I don't know.
Just remember I love you.
You know what I mean.
And I love you.
Okay bye.
Bye.