Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast contains gushing, fawning, breathless praise, and at least one
brief joke about a robot or something.
It's Horizons on today's podcast, The Ride.
Welcome to podcast The Ride, the show where we like to say, I'll take the city.
Yes, it's always exciting.
I'm Jason Sheridan, joined as always by Mike Carlson.
Yes, I'm here.
I always say that I'll take the city.
You know, it's one of my merch items I sell on my personal Etsy shop.
Oh yeah, the front says, I'll take the city and the back says, yes, it's always exciting.
And then I also have, yeah, like athletic pants that say that on the butt as well.
On the seat, excuse me.
Yeah, and then you have small shorts that say, I'm serious on one cheek and the other cheek
says, well, I am too.
Like unusually confrontational.
Look, it's a big ride today, folks.
I'm going narrow.
I'm sure there's lots of lines about the future I could have started with.
Scott Garner also here as usual.
Yeah, I wear a hoodie that says, stretching frontiers into reality, which is what Leonard
Vickers, the General Electric VP of Corporate Marketing said what this attraction was about.
Um, I yeah, and then my and then on the and then I wear pants that on the butt say I ride
for Leonard Vickers.
Have we we have never talked about Leonard Vickers on the show before, I don't think.
No, this is the first time in five minutes getting straight into Leonard Vickers.
We have to get you know, we have to get stuff out of the way because there's so much stuff.
But can Leonard Vickers get it?
Um, I don't have a photo that one of the only Google results for him is an obituary and
the photo used is a candle.
So I cannot off of that determine whether he can get it.
OK, well, we'll come back.
We'll find like young hunk pictures and then we'll determine that later.
Oh, wait, no, wait. I do have a photo.
Wait. All right. From Progress City, USA.
And just to explain, General Electric was the sponsor of this Epcot attraction we're
talking about today.
And all right, I will share my screen and please announce if you think that he can get it.
I will say he's not as good as he card Walker.
Yeah, that's what I'll say. I don't want to put him down.
I don't want to say can't get it. I need to see more photos, but I will say he's no
E. Card Walker. That's all I'll say.
He's he's in a suit in front of like a wall of equations, like on a whiteboard.
That's what we're looking at. He's approximately
62 years old or 34, depending on like the time period and how people aged.
Yeah, I look, I don't know.
Getting it is I think he may have once been able to get it.
Let me be nice to Leonard Vickers. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Look, we got we got a lot of stuff.
We got a lot of stuff.
But shout out to Progress City USA, a great website and Twitter account I've read for years.
Folks, we're talking about horizons.
The most I will say, and I've seen lots of other people saying it, the most beloved closed
attraction when it comes to all this.
It's got to be. Yeah, it's got to be. Right.
Maybe Maelstrom is closed, but you know, the bones of it are still there.
And even then, that's Maelstrom is not nearly the horizons.
Original journey.
Original journey is up there.
It's for sure there.
But is it just because we can see at least see Figment even in this bastardized version?
Maybe a great movie ride.
Yeah. Yeah. But I I don't know.
Not to me.
Yeah. Yeah, it could be this.
Definitely could be this.
Yeah. Hey, and we're hitting early Epcot.
Barely not original Epcot.
This was a year delayed.
But it's pretty early Epcot.
And it is shameful how little of this we've done.
We did Universe of Energy and then haven't touched one in a little bit.
And so we'll start getting through them.
And this one is huge.
Is this is it maybe a result of us
enjoying things where we can like talk shit and make fun of it?
Like the American Dream Mall or some of these, you know, bizarre things
that we cover as opposed to this where I mean, I'm so excited to talk about it,
but I think it's going to be an episode full of like and then the bad thing.
That was so good.
And then the music that was so good.
The sea base. Look, it's two stories and there's animatronics on both.
And there's it's like a die cut.
Yeah, Jason, what you're trying to say is it's so good.
It's so good. Yes.
I mean, it's a lot.
It's very earnest love for this thing, I think, with all of us.
I was trying to figure out what the comedic angle on it was,
because I also thought, oh, no, this is going to be just a gushing episode,
which I'm sure people like.
I think they like that.
But they do come here to podcast for the laughs.
I was trying to like, I'm like, oh, I think, you know,
we could joke around about this interesting tidbit.
So I have a couple joke notes to try to make sure
that there's some levity in this episode.
I mean, that was, you know, but maybe I'll forget them.
My funny discovery, I've watched this ride through now like four times,
which is not unusual when prepping an episode.
But this ride is like 20 minutes long if you watch all the endings.
So I feel because I just there's just so much.
I was having trouble remembering and wrapping my head around.
And about an hour ago, as I was watching the last one,
the thing that struck me as funny is the dynamic between the grandparent characters.
And they're like clearly like each other,
but they they do snap at each other every now and then.
Were you referencing that earlier?
Is that what that little back and forth was about?
Yeah, I the I'll take the city.
Yes, it's always exciting is like begrudgingly like, yeah,
they're making a good point.
But the best I think is the lines when they're talking about the floating city.
And the one says, I'm serious.
And the other says, well, so am I.
I don't remember this little this little bickering.
Well, well, so elderly couples still fight in the future,
no matter how hopeful it is. Yes. Right.
Did let me ask this right up top.
Did this make you sad for the state of the world?
Oh, yeah. Watching this video, because it certainly made me sad.
I anticipated this.
I was I and I was thinking I feel like we have to put a moratorium on discussion
of how the future is bleak and not as good as horizon there,
because the more of that that's run through this episode, this will be a miserable slog.
Hey, I hear I hear that.
That's why I want to get out of the way right now.
Is that I was watching it and I was just like, oh, yeah, that would be.
Oh, yeah. Wouldn't have been great if we were like here by now. Right.
I am optimistic.
I do agree with one of the mission statements of the ride that this future is possible.
All you have to do is get rid of fossil fuels.
The current iteration of wage labor, policing, the military industrial complex,
the current concept of nation states and nuclear weapons, which, yes,
that sounds great.
Let's go for it. Let's have horizons.
Surely the DNC and Nancy Pelosi can stay, wouldn't you say, Jason?
I mean, look, as long as they're ripping up paper and clapping,
that's all that's all I care about.
Hell, yeah.
Commemorative scarves, man, these ballers, they're going to bring
they're going to get us to horizons future.
There there should be a new version of horizons where an empty political gesture
is one of the scenes, and then the next scene we see what happened.
So it's like Pelosi clapping.
And then all of a sudden, we're on the moon and a moon base.
We've colonized the moon because of that gesture.
Oh, it inspired people so much to be the best version of themselves.
Yeah, it created harmony on Earth and enabled an international cooperation
to build a brava centauri.
That's right.
So that could really draw the parallel, I think, in a future version of this.
But again, that's maybe that's future brainstorming.
I don't even want to get there.
I do think there there's a funny, realistic version of this where it's like,
wow, we have a colony on the moon thanks to SpaceX.
Oh, the founder of SpaceX is tweeting about a local worker
that's trying to rescue a child.
He's calling him a pedophile again.
And this is really in the moon colony is on fire.
The first instance of fire in space.
Elon Musk is spending most of his days trying to debunk covid testing.
He really should be more focused on his futurism, his future colony.
Why is this colony just thick with blunt smoke?
Has been for years, apparently.
This is a weird I don't want to, like, over explain this thing,
because I think many of the listeners just absolutely know what horizons is
and have it memorized and have been wondering when we're going to get to it.
But I feel like it is a product of it being gone since 1999,
that there are a lot of people who don't really know it, didn't get to go on it.
And in doing so, I mean, the basics of it are
early Epcot attraction, open to year late.
It is where mission space is now.
And it is like a hard ride to synopsize.
It is a yes, it's it's a it's a dark ride that is about the future.
It is visions of futuristic life,
sometimes from the past, the ideas from the past of what the future would be.
And then you get to see a bunch of ideas from 1983 of what the future could be,
which I'm on record many times as saying is the best future, the most optimal future.
Some of these futures make my heart stop.
They are so beautiful.
It's it's it is a weird, wonderful ride.
Yeah, it's it's I I thought this while I was watching the video.
And then I saw that I think internally and some other people thought of it
kind of as a sequel to the Carousel of Progress.
Yes. Which, of course, if you don't know one of that is that's like sort of the
history of technology in America and whatever.
And with a little now, of course, it has a few quote unquote future scene,
which is 20 years ago, future scene, which is less fun.
Although although my favorite thing in the ride, certainly is fun.
And also due to the cyclical nature of trends, VR came back around
like rugby shirts came back around.
So it stuck around long enough to be kind of relevant.
Oh, voice activation is real and very inconvenient now.
It's here and it's a pain in the ass.
And every version, not perfect, every version of iOS.
The dictation just gets worse.
At least if you have a Philadelphia regional accent,
it just doesn't understand what the fuck you are saying at all.
Yes. So, yeah, it's like it's like in the same vein.
They use the Carousel of Progress song in there, which is nice,
which I was really like kind of impressed by that thinking of like,
oh, a ride sequel is really a cool idea.
Yeah, which we don't see a lot of.
I guess I guess I've talked about before the Monsters After Dark
Guardians Halloween Overlay, which is kind of a sequel in the same ride.
But I was like, oh, yeah, this is like this is exactly
like this is completely then a continuation of that idea.
And on a bigger scale, more, you know, longer ride, different kind of ride.
A sequel in a different place. Yeah, is pretty rare.
Let me ask you this, because I did not know.
I guess I knew it was in the spirit.
I knew it was sort of related
to the Carousel of Progress and the song was in there.
The GE sponsorship sort of unites the both of them, at least initially.
But did you guys know that it was the same family?
Because I had never put that together.
When I did not. Yeah.
When I started the research, it started to come up like
the same family in theory.
I mean, this is like a heightening and expansion of Carousel of Progress.
Yeah, yeah, we take them into the future.
The way distant. Yeah, I did.
I did not know that it was they meant it to be in the same
canon mythology.
I mean, this is predating like see, of course, the society of explorers
and adventurers that was going to connect rides
via this like group of horrible rich people.
The international tyrants. Yes.
Yeah, which we love.
We will still do an episode of that soon.
But yeah, this is predating that by years.
And I really I will admit that as a kid, I went on Horizons,
but it didn't loom large in my head until I was older and reading about it and stuff.
It wasn't something that I was crazy about, like figment or something.
Right. But well, let me let me say this about my childhood
feelings about it. And this is me.
This is in general, I think a lot of Epcot put together
because I went when I for the first time, I think when I was seven.
And in my head,
I have like such strong, evocative memories of Epcot in general,
maybe not specific things, but I remember the feeling of going on
lots of very long, claustrophobic, creaky, shadowy rides.
There's so many of them.
And so to me, for a long, long time,
Horizons, Spaceship Earth and World of Motion were all just tangled up in my brain.
And I did not know probably until we started doing the podcast.
I had not completely untethered like, OK, which is the one with like
the horse and the buggy and the horses jumping,
which is the one where there's like a guy in a tunic with a scroll.
That's a beard guy.
But then there's also a beard guy in a capsule with a chicken like
like they're all similar styles of animatronic
and all similar styles of very small vehicle
that you're in for a long time that moves upward and clanks along.
I just I remember like the base feeling of all of it,
but I could never pick them apart for the longest time.
Yes, I completely agree with that.
I agree with that, too.
This the thing that sticks out in my mind,
like the flashes of childhood for World of Motion is the overturned
like horse cart, you know, street scene in this.
Probably the robot, but robot Butler never really was.
There was always an image of him somewhere, even in shops or something.
But choosing your own ending was like what stuck with me for this ride.
Like going back and watching it, I was like, oh, well, the first
like third of this ride is so like bonkers and abstract.
And like I feel like it wouldn't get away with that anymore.
It feels it feels like a lot of this.
A lot of the stuff adding to the legend of this ride, it's like
imagineering firing on all cylinders had to make some minor cuts,
but they still spend a lot of money on this ride.
It's loaded with animatronics.
It's got like an A-list team of people working on it.
The corporate sponsorship like actually seemed to be contributing ideas
and not demanding like light bulbs shoved in there.
And like we're we're into the, you know, message of it.
And we're into like having their name on something positive and uplifting,
as opposed to like make goofy, hold a Pepsi, you know,
that would never happen.
Disney is a coke corporation.
But, you know, it's just a lot of elements are just working correctly.
Yes, for sure.
It's also a period.
I mean, I think because Epcot obviously has a rocky history of it
being a real city when Walt was envisioning it, and then it's switching over to theme park.
But they were trying to stay sort of true.
Like they were really trying to stay true to like Walt's ideas.
So I feel like Future World is like like they got to do an art album.
They got to do an art concept album, whereas Scott's saying they all blend together.
And I completely agree with that in the same way that whatever the suite at the end of
Abbey Road blends together, it's like all kind of of a piece.
It all kind of can.
You could probably sub in different scenes for each ride,
and it wouldn't be completely out of out of like or wouldn't be completely jarring.
And the other thing is that Horizons was the keystone.
It brought together all of the communication and transportation and innovation.
And all of these ideas are kind of present in here.
Even the sea, the literal seas, energy like it all shows all the other pavilions
kind of feed in to this GD Captain Planet ass ride.
Where like it just makes makes a larger piece.
Yes, it would have almost made more sense now with the new version of Future World
if they had just taken out pieces of all these rides and just thrown them into Spaceship Earth
and made Spaceship Earth like a greatest hits of original Future World.
Oh, that's an idea.
That's a good idea.
That would have been I mean, I guess it's still possible.
But like then you can at least like get a lot of the iconic stuff from this this these rides,
because it sucks that like Horizons is gone because it feels like Horizons
should have been pirates.
Like it feels like you shouldn't have been able to touch this ride.
At least you could update it and make it new and cool.
But it feels it feels bad to me that Horizons isn't there, obviously
in the same way Figment isn't the same.
And I don't know, I'm not I'm not mad about like Spaceship Earth changing.
But this being gone 100 percent.
Yeah, it's very strange for something that and it wasn't there that long
when you add it all up.
And right in the last few years, it was pretty spotty, whether it be open or not.
So it got kind of like a not graceful exit.
I think I only went on it on my first trip.
I don't I don't think I don't think I got to say goodbye.
Yeah, I don't I don't have a memory of going on it.
When did I close in 99? Is that right?
Yes, it closed like January 99.
That was a big thing I saw mentioned.
There is a website called like Horizon Timeline,
or if that's what the page on the website is.
And they made sure to point out that despite Epcot being at capacity
on the night of December 31st, 1999, they did not reopen Horizons.
Horizons, like in fact, they closed
Horizons a year before the future was supposed to start, which is darkly funny,
but like a little grim. Yeah, no, a very grim.
Yeah, I did not go on this because I went in 2002.
So I probably had.
Yeah, I probably went on it when I when I was like 12 or 13 for the last time.
Or maybe like, yeah, something like that.
You know, it's another thing with them.
Sorry, the other thing with them just like
mushing up all together and being this sort of unique little concept album is
that you don't see any of your friends in them.
Like it's all either anonymous animatronics or they are portraying,
you know, Jules Verne or like a real like man from the from the Roman era.
And like you get you get no Mickey.
You don't even get a fox on the hound.
You get nobody that you know,
which that's not a complaint for me.
It's just like it was like so much to take in as a seven year old and so like,
like just like odd and melancholy and not what I expected.
A theme park would be at all.
Actually, you add Maelstrom and Mexico Boat Ride to that, too,
which are also sort of claustrophobic, sort of darkly lit.
That just that a whole half of the park is so and the and the scary dinosaurs.
Like Epcot was a like moody theme park.
Yes, it's a moody concept album of a theme park that doesn't give you the hits
from the Magic Kingdom, it doesn't give you what you want.
It's a challenging it's challenging, which is why so much of it is gone.
It's why fans like it.
It's like no, no, no, no.
Sit down and listen to it, because if you actually like really listen to it,
you're going to get it.
But people who only have a passing fancy just want to hear the hits.
They just yes, they just want those first early albums of pop pop songs, which are
great. This is the marketing, though, right?
And this was the mission statement for Epcot is was for the adults,
for the adults who are coming, staying at the contemporary water skiing
when they weren't at the park, you know, and and a permanent world fair,
a showcase for ideas.
I mean, just the concept art alone, this beautiful like
book cover painterly art of the Herman Herb Ryman paintings, not Herman,
are just so great for Horizons.
I don't think I know that exactly, but
I think I know what you're talking about.
Yeah, I have it here.
I mean, he did that famous painting of the castle.
But then this was an early one for Horizons.
And then look at this.
Look at this big. Oh, yeah.
Oh, it's sort of like it feels a little more like 60s of an art style.
And, oh, boy, just like, you know, raise a sunlight flesh and through and so much
color hitting everything is this family with two little girls in hats.
They can't wait to go meet their friends at Brava Centauri.
Oh, there's some swingers over here.
If you can see them, Warren Beatty, I think that is his pocket.
And with someone's wife, it is.
Ali McGraw, it is Ali McGraw still.
Wow.
Yeah. So it's.
I guess I understand why all this stuff has closed, but it does.
It I guess it's for us as adults, not
necessarily for even the general population of adults.
If you took Spaceship Earth, just throw figment on Spaceship Earth and he's
your guide through the best of all the Epcot rides.
How about that? Oh, yeah.
You got a fun, fun person for the kids, fun character for the kids.
That's pretty interesting.
Yeah. And just do something else with the bit like is the back half just more of
like that's like you end up doing your
like, well, why don't the screens just show you these videos where you choose
your future path instead of bad like 2006 era Jim Chab.
Yes.
Or it's your mom would send you.
Yeah.
So anyway, I mean, we're doing some of the end of the podcast.
Now we're doing sort of our concept album
podcast because we're sort of starting with the end.
Yeah. Well, and that's sort of that sort
of outside the box thinking is what you get with Horizons.
You know, when you get a business genius like Jack Welch involved, the oft mentioned
on 30 Rock, GE executive Jack Welch. Yes.
Who eventually appeared on 30 Rock.
I don't know if he counts as a
what I was calling for CEO performers like Eisner and Brandon Tartikoff.
He's a little bit in there if just from that one appearance.
Sure. Yeah. He helped think of this.
He did a real thing.
I he was I think the original CEO, Reginald Jones, and then Jack Welch was
like his lieutenant, who would then
take over the company and would be revered by the fictional Jack Dongy.
But they don't. Yeah, they don't talk about Horizons on 30 Rock.
No, they don't.
References, no.
But it is funny that GE would go on to own the other theme park company down the line.
No, that's right. Oh, yeah.
But then with this, it's like incredibly
ambitious and very adults, which is sort of what their theme park property
is a little more.
It's like it's almost universal esque.
And it's it's adultness and darkness and ambition.
Yeah, yeah, it's it's it's funny to think that
it's funny because the company hasn't thought like this since this.
Like MGM Studios, definitely like for
Disney, MGM Studios, definitely for the parents as well.
But that's much more all the stuff they've put in there is much more kid
friendly than any of this up. You're meeting your friends left and right.
You're meeting C3PO and Indiana Jones and Rod Serling
and Busby Berkeley.
Yeah, what
Jimmy Durante or wait, no, who's in the which gangsters do you meet?
James Cagney. There you go.
I'm all the kids favorites.
Ray Bolger.
All of them.
Yep.
So, yeah, this is so this is the only
time in the Disney company history where they were fine with no friends,
which I like as a kid.
I did. I appreciated it on a certain level because you get bombarded with friends
at the Magic Kingdom, you get bombarded with friends at MGM Studios.
So I like the different vibe of Epcot, you know, sometimes it's nice to be away
from your friends. That's what we're saying.
You need a little, you know, you need a little break.
You need a break from your friends.
You just need like nine months to a year and a half away from all of your friends.
We all need a quick nine to 18 months.
Yeah.
So, yeah, it's interesting.
So that's.
Yeah, I, I, I get why it's not there, but I was just so feeling so nostalgic for it
while watching this or something I didn't feel nostalgic for as a child.
Yeah, I didn't have so much fun as a child.
It's funny, Mike and I talked to a student group at UCLA the other day.
And as we were talking, that's right, you can be impressed.
I, but as we were talking to them, I realized because they had a horizon zone
in the back of my mind, I realized like, oh, my God, were you all born
after this ride closed? I think that timing works out.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
A lot of people, we only went on it once.
Yeah, it's I feel like it lives on through through videos and articles almost
primarily, one of which I will quote real fast just to say the scope of it,
because he broke it down real, real well.
Our friend Doug Jones, who wrote a great article in Dangerous Minds about it,
just he spelled it out really nicely with these stats that I copy pasted.
Thank you, Doug.
Fifty four audio animatronic figures,
seven hundred and seventy props, twelve projectors and a pair of massive
Omni-Mac screens, groundbreaking technology at the time spread across 24 sets
set in the year 2086. Incredible.
So madly and the show building is so massive when you're looking at it.
And it's not just it's not a fake facade.
It's not just for show.
Like it's so tall because they had to fit those giant screens in the middle.
Omni-Max is the type of domed screen that they use on Soren.
And I guess that's not the exact type on Soren, but back to the future,
the ride definitely.
And they had to be huge.
This is the first ride to to use them.
And you also just technologically and I'm jumping around a little bit here,
but with this interactive ending that it
builds to where you choose the future that you go to, which interactivity already
is a huge thing this ride is doing for the first time.
But also, I think until watching the Martins vids, I didn't realize how they did it,
which like you're like on your way out of the ride.
You were watching a little like flight simulator path to a future destination.
And it's this crazy thing.
I think you're like going along a screen,
but the projector is traveling with you.
So you're like the projector is mounted and like four cars all collectively pick
which future that you go to and then you're like moving along with the screen,
which feels very Harry Potter ride.
Like it's all these like early analog versions of things that are a little more.
I don't even want to say commonplace.
I feel like Horizons did things that are mega blockbuster moments in rides
of the 2000s and 2010s.
Yeah, I mean, we were talking about the
Haunted Mansion episode where you'll see a really cool thing in a new ride
and you'll be like, hey, what cool new technology is that?
And they're like, oh, it's Pepper's Ghost.
You know, like, oh, yeah, it's a really good illusion that still works.
And it does feel like maybe, yeah, like this one, it's like they probably still
use this type of thing. I think so.
All of the technology. Orange scent.
We get an orange scent in it.
Which is like the thing that people are
nostalgic for in Soren over California as opposed to the later one.
It's I think we've agreed the superior
smell, even with all the many smells in the new version.
But they did orange.
They did an orange smell first.
I think that was probably very rare at the time.
I don't think. Yeah, we were talking about it.
I don't think there's any other orange smell anywhere.
I mean, before 1983, I don't know.
Somebody will correct that, I'm sure.
I don't know if it's a correct analog.
You can think of what the actual one is.
But what we're saying is like incredibly
influential, Ride did all these things that were done, you know, later to more
success, but they did it first in this concept album thing.
It's what is it Velvet Underground?
What is it? What are we?
What is this? The Velvet Underground of Rides?
That's a good question.
Is it television?
That's a good one. Like big sprawling long songs.
Yeah, it's not pop singles.
But if you want a little challenging 10 minute experience, absolutely.
I think that's pretty close.
Maybe the television of rides.
Television is a band, by the way, for the younger listeners.
Yeah, Mark.
It's not a ride about television.
It's you know, watch televisions on it.
They were comparing it to the band.
Yes. Right.
Scott, you mentioned the Morton's Vids.
It's the thing that struck me in that not
just like the seven projector array for the ending, but the schematic for the
Omni-Max sequence where like it spirals around like it.
It just seems like when you look at it as a blueprint, it's one of those ones that
looks like an impossible architecture and one of the few where the like it's not
just a square show building behind it, it's like, no, it.
Yeah.
That shape of the building extends behind it.
It's such a unique looking building and something that is, I think, missing from
Epcot, you know, now. Right.
Right. Yeah. The blueprints are so confusing to look.
I still haven't wrapped my head around all of how it works.
Are you saying do you just say that it's
like it's not one projector on top of your vehicles?
It's seven. Oh, I think it's like seven.
That's how they did like a half moon almost of projection.
Wow. Wow.
That kind of fans out in front of you until you get back to.
The other folks, if you haven't if you don't, if you haven't seen this ride it
through in a while or you don't remember riding it, search on YouTube Horizons
Revisit, which is like a cleaned up, deinterlaced,
restored ride through that is like it's so rare you get like a quality video
of these long gone rides.
And it is like it's a 20 year old ride.
And a lot of times those look like shit on YouTube.
Yeah. And they cleaned it up.
Retro WDW and the Lake Wainovista Historical Society cleaned it up and put
this video out and it is wild to watch this.
There's so much stuff like even watching it through a couple of times.
It was like, I forgot about that.
Like there's so much, especially because of the first, like I said,
chunk of the ride is so abstract.
I definitely I hate to keep coming back to the concept album idea,
but you're saying there's just so much.
I'm like I'm just scrolling again.
I've scrolled through this now 20 times, but there's so much stuff.
And then I remember hearing that when they were talking about building Westcott,
Tony Baxter was talking about there was going to be a 45 minute boat ride
that would that would like be just go along the circumference or not.
Yeah. The edge of the park, essentially.
And there would be four stops.
You could get off whenever you want.
It would be like the train, the Disneyland train, except it would be
full scale dark ride for 45 minutes with like pirates drops, like drops, like at
the start. And I feel like, all right, like they're just getting going
with ambition here and they're like, let's throw everything at it.
We don't have to do anything like we're we're we're feeling so emboldened
by the success we've had thus far that they were like, we're going to throw
everything at this thing and we're not going to not going to apply any of the
rules we would you would assume they would have for a ride like this.
And then like World War Two breaking out, a conflict in Europe happened and everyone
tripped on their own decks.
So
that being you're saying the Euro Disney, the Euro Disney, which kills like more
ambitious, bizarre, like non IP rides like this, which probably would have been
strewn throughout the 90s if they had that not happened.
Yeah, I mean, it's really the thing that
like made Eisner blink, like it like made him like threw him off.
I think you start to see like the decline and there's a list
a theme park tourist, I believe, made a list of like here's everything that got
closed or delayed because of Euro Disney fallout.
And it's it's Tomorrowland 2055 Westcott,
the closures, 20,000 leagues under the sea in Florida, the horizons.
You know, it was a miracle that Animal Kingdom was so good when it was.
Right, right, right.
Rough year.
Maybe the maybe the roughest until this year, I would think.
Don't we think to get Disney back on track, they need to build Westcott and have
a 45 minute boat ride with no IP on it?
Absolutely.
Bring the ambition back.
Get crazy, guys.
What do you have to do?
Deficit spending, folks, you know, don't be afraid of it.
You got to spend your way out of a recession.
Your way out.
Also, what I'm doing with toys.
For sure.
You know, nobody's going to want the like we should.
This is the point beyond which we're not going to want all the presidents.
Right. Like if we do it here,
if we do it not with Trump, then like we can't say nobody will say it was Trump's
fall. Let's just like do it with Biden.
We're done with all presidents and repurpose all of the robots and make them
like animatronic, like do something like this again.
Put them in a space city or add them all to pirates.
If nothing else, just like throw all of
disperse the presidents into different pirates of the Caribbean's across the globe.
Oh, and not and not change anything about them.
Right. They're just the presidents.
A lot of them already look like weird old, you know, Martin Van Buren can be drunk
on the bridge. James Garfield is harpooning somebody.
Oh, yeah. Oh, that's yes.
That's a great idea, honestly.
Like obviously have throw a bunch of presidents in the ballroom in the Haunted
Mansion. Yeah.
Or pirates just build 46 more wells to dunk them in.
They have it coming.
They're going to build Biden to do that.
They're going to build Biden still, but put him into pirates.
Hey, man, back in my day, dunking into well, that's party.
Look, Jack, he's saying that as he comes up for a second.
Dunk me harder.
Hey, look, fat.
Malarkey.
That's more fun.
Look, fat. You're lying with the pigs.
You're not going to get the map, you know.
A real play, a replacing depth, even just with Biden
releasing, replacing Jack Sparrow in general, popping out of the barrel.
Yeah.
And on the chair at the end of the ride.
Yeah. Yeah.
He's completely spinning the yarn toward to you.
Is he is he surrounded by treasure?
What's Biden's dream room at the end?
Ice cream.
A bunch of ice cream.
Yeah. A bounty of ice cream.
Pine Scalore.
You know, if Donald Trump Jr.
heard this podcast, he'd be so mad at us.
Like they go into my they insult my dad every single episode.
And then when it comes to Biden, what's the joke?
He loves ice cream.
Podcast The Ride is soft.
They're biased.
And they were and they will be banned from podcasting in term two.
Yes.
Sloppy podcast.
The ride is no longer hot.
Not like NASA.
Yeah, wait, we're all being not optimistic.
Trump is the Trump made space hot again.
That's like horizon dreamed of doing.
That's true. He did make it hot again.
Right.
I let me let me shift gears into
what you started talking about, just the building and the architecture.
This is one of the best things about it.
I could stare at that building all day.
Oh, my God.
It's hard to say because I like so many of those old pavilions.
But is probably the best.
This big, crazy diamond UFO spaceship thing, this big angular, weird steel with
the sign up front, that that amazing logo,
just aesthetically before you even get in the door.
And it was a bummer when it closed, but at least like before they just crushed it
down the side to start building mission space, even like seeing this thing over a
fence still was kind of nice. I just like I just wish the building was there.
Yeah, it had the full hat trick.
Great sign up front, great building.
And then the logo icon, the minimalist Epcot Pavilion icons is great.
My favorite one, I think I will declare I like a lot of them.
I like all of them.
But the the little like angled path to the horizon and the lines get thinner
and thinner as you get up to the horizon line.
Yeah, that little icon logo is wonderful.
They pack so much information in there and yet it's still really minimal.
I love it.
Here's my here's my like, oh, I feel dumb because I didn't process this.
I feel like I had heard over the years that this was kind of the, you know,
touchstone, it combines a lot of the elements of all the different pavilions.
But like if you stare at the building,
the vertical lines on the front go to a point, they go to a horizon at the top of
the building. Oh, interesting.
Did not catch that. Yeah, no, I didn't catch that either.
I I will also this this building has just given me this permanent attraction to
big austere buildings from the 80s built in office parks.
I can drive around because of this.
I'll be driving around, you know, Irvine or West Lake Village, California,
or the area around Fashion Island and Newport Beach.
Sometimes I will see a building and a corporate logo out in a big in a big lawn.
That's an important thing. Also, it's got to be a big austere,
sort of unfriendly, but imposing, but fascinating building.
And then a big lawn and then and then a like round sign up front.
I've got to put the land in this, too.
The land is also a very cool building.
But I,
I don't know if anyone can think of buildings where they've been to or work or
something that are like the Horizons building.
I can't get enough.
Like if I get a Horizons vibe from a building, I just it's it's like
the Ratatouille bite that the critic takes.
It just like flashes me back to it just takes me back to childhood.
And I feel good.
Well, I think there's going to be a lot of building
hunters now looking out for you. I hope so.
They know exactly. Is there a hashtag you could throw on this?
What you were talking about here?
Hashtag Horizons esque.
OK, yeah, that's good.
Think about it.
The two horizons for me, the building, I always think of, I don't know if you've
guys have seen Star Trek, the next generation, when they would do like we're
beaming down to a planet, an alien planet, and they will do like a
kind of a painted looking like far away shot of the planet with some buildings.
And then they'll just cut in.
It's obviously a shitty soundstage on the Paramount lot.
Like it's really like beautiful looking
picture of a planet with like cool looking buildings that are similar to the horizons
in the early Epcot buildings.
And then it cuts in.
It's just like it's either like Griffith Park or it's like some studio, some sound
stage on Paramount.
But that but the buildings to me get that give me that very like Star Trek vibe.
And yeah, it's a Logan's run thing, too.
Just like this should be just one model on a giant table that you only see for 10
seconds at the beginning of a movie.
But in this case, you get to go be inside it for a really long time.
Yeah, yeah, it is.
It would have been nice if they could have preserved.
I don't like keeping negative and talking about it, but like it would have been nice
if they could have preserved some of this a little more with Epcot.
Well, you also have the problem that
and this seems alternatively debunked or not debunked.
I can't tell, but there's at least the theory out there that there is a sinkhole
under this building and that might be some of the reason why Horizons went away.
Right. Yes.
And I think other parts of the building deteriorating, too.
I rewatched the documentary about Hoot and Chief, the guys who would constantly
sneak into Horizons and walk around it because there was no security system.
And one time one of their feet went through rotten plywood
and that that has led to a injury, a pain, reoccurring pain in their foot.
They still have.
So they don't always keep everything up, up and going, maybe more now.
I feel like OSHA is a little more aggressive now, a little more.
But like what Scott was talking about on Haunted Mansion, it was like there's a moat
in the Madame Leota room in Haunted Mansion.
Oh, yeah. You can't walk up to her.
You would just fall.
Yeah.
So obviously these are already not designed for people to hang out in them casually.
Yes.
Oh, the other thing from that documentary,
this OmniMover vehicle has no restraints so you could just vault over it.
Oh, that's right.
That's why they were able to.
Yeah.
This is by Matt Serrano, who did the Halyx
documentary that we got to be a part of.
And yeah, it's so fascinating.
These guys shot all this footage of themselves running around, getting off
the ride and going and like we can go be in the scene for two full minutes before
anybody catches us. And it's all about like the.
All right. So there's a gap, this amount of gap between cars.
And we know if there's one that where there's six empty spaces,
that means that we won't get caught.
Like they figured out all the rhythms of it.
It feels oddly akin to like when you hear about the guy who learned how to game
Press Your Luck, the Lanny game show and like, all right, I figured out the code.
I cracked the code by watching it for hours and hours and hours.
But yes, so strange.
They just yeah, as opposed to safety bar lowers for you, they just jump out the top
and can go hang out with the family and feed the fake seal in the ocean world.
Yeah, I feel like they spent the collective,
like many hours just hanging out in the horizons.
Yeah, I mean, I am delighted by that story, but don't do that, folks.
Please don't stress me out.
Stress me out.
But a wonderful with some perspective,
with a couple of decades perspective to look back on it.
It's like, well, that's kind of cool.
Pretty impressive.
No way. I want people to go hang out there right now.
The parks aren't open.
Now is your time to sneak in.
What's the book about museum?
Is it the head?
The name in my head is like Basil E.
Frank Weiler.
Like, what's the book about staying over in a museum?
Yeah, I know what you're talking about.
I might weigh the hell off on that name.
You know, there's a book about spending the night in the museum or a movie called
Night at the Museum, I was going to say, the movies.
Anyway, everyone.
Yeah, go do that.
Go find a vent to crawl into.
No one will find you if you go live in Rise of the Resistance for two months.
Have your royal tenenbaums evening
living in Anaheim, Rise of the Resistance.
That's right. Yes.
Am I way I weight?
Basil E.
Frank Weiler is it is that the museum?
Yeah, kids, yes.
Siblings run away to the Metropolitan Museum of Art in New York City.
Got it right. OK, few self corrected.
No apology necessary.
Let's continue.
That's a funny.
That would be a funny episode.
Is we each bring in the weirdest kids book we were obsessed with or like kids think
we were obsessed with because I got some of my grandfather's books from the 1910s.
And some of those good books are weird.
Thanks. I don't believe that.
Yeah.
Can you throw can you can you just get a wetter appetite?
What's the name of one of these books?
The one that sticks out.
Well, there's two that stick out.
One was just called Boy Scouts on the Moon
and then another one,
which my family just laughed at because of the old aphorisms.
I believe it was called Poppy and the Pickled Peacock.
And that was like a blockbuster movie,
that kind of like rep alliteration back then that just drove people wild.
It was like the train driving right at you,
people losing their mind, which is surprisingly not in this ride.
They've got the moon, the moon with the ship in its eye,
like anything that references the early days of cinema.
It's got the moon with the ship in the eye.
Right. Earth. Yeah.
I am just real quick with that.
You reminded me with that kind of thing, like weird turn of the century stuff.
My my grandfather, who was a writer, I think
the least contributed some material to something called Captain Billy's Whiz Bang.
Which do you know about Captain Billy's Whiz Bang?
I think that's yeah, that's a ref.
That's also a reference to something.
I can't remember.
I think it's in the Music Man.
Oh, right. Yes, I think you're right.
It's the Music Man. That's what I'm thinking of.
I yes, it is. It is.
Yes, you're right. Wow.
No, wait a minute. It's in.
It's in You Got Trouble, isn't it?
Yes. Yeah, I believe so.
Is it a thing that's warping young minds?
This was kind of.
Yeah. It was like the Mad Magazine of its day, like a sort of like cheeky,
racy body magazine.
And just in Google imaging it, it looks
like I just found a cover that seems to reference the fatty Arbuckle incident.
Like they're parodying that in a Mad Magazine style.
So
surprising no one.
I have a copy of Captain Billy's Whiz Bang around here somewhere.
Whoa, whoa.
They put out a facsimile like 10 years ago, some like book publisher, comic
publisher, I have no idea who put it out, but I found it at a store and I bought it.
Wow. Wow.
I find it and see if there's a Gartner original in there.
Carl Schrader would be there.
Schrader. Check out Carl Schrader if he's in there.
Given Fatty Arbuckle the what for?
Yeah.
Anyways,
away from the 1920s into the the 2080s.
This is clearly.
What's that? Was that the year it was supposed to be?
100 years forward?
Yeah, apparently.
Again, thanks to Doug Jones for highlighting that fact.
I don't think I realize that, which is that you then you wonder, well, how could
it be the family from Carousel of Progress?
But of course, they jump 20 years in time in every scene.
The Carousel of Progress is a magical family in general.
They're like a bicentennial man situation.
Like how could the same family go from
the turn of the century to the 60s to the 90s or whatever?
And I guess it keeps going.
This eternal family makes it all the way to 2086.
They're like another kid's book, Tuck Everlasting, the family cursed to never die.
But it wouldn't be a problem if you got
to live in this world, go into this future.
But I guess we're we're going a little out of order because the well, OK, before
we this is going very haunted mansion, we talked about the outside
the the inside, then you just walk in that first room
and then you see a big display of like the flight itinerary.
Like this is your airport.
Here's where you could go, depending on which gate you go to.
And it says Futureport, just that.
Oh, my God. This like octagonal.
I don't know how many sides it is, but like just the font of Futureport,
the crazy places you get to go striped with pink neon.
Every room in this thing is such a aesthetic dream for me.
That feels like
like in your dream house, one of the rooms looks like that.
Yeah, absolutely.
And also with Dreamhouse, you I was thinking how much I would like to have.
This is a thing that's in a couple Disney rides, but it's in this too.
Once you board the attraction right before you take off into the ride proper,
you are facing a wall of like pink slats.
I guess the slats aren't pink.
It's like glowing pink,
just like a big wall of light.
And then those like oval shaped like futurey.
I don't know how to describe it exactly, but it's in Space Mountain.
When you get off of Space Mountain, those kinds of things, those it's future slats
and the Star Tours in the line as well.
I would love for like just a wall to be like that in my house.
And I don't know how to do it.
How would you how you would have to get somebody to make like you'd have to go
to like Nick Offerman's place to get him to make you future slats, maybe?
I think so.
But I feel like I'd be going on and on about, you know, it's like this I've got
a right horizons, which is kind of this cool image of the future.
Provincetari.
And, you know, it's all because I lived
in the 80s and he would just glare at me the entire time unmovingly.
It's possible.
I get so insecure.
But maybe you just say, well, do it and you'd be fine.
You've given him money and he does it.
And look, I'm paying you, Nick.
Yeah, shop up the shop up some future slats for me.
Future slats, I've never seen at any of these Disney auctions,
future slats on the menu.
I wonder if it was built into the like the support beam.
It was built into the drywall or something.
Maybe. But I think don't isn't it?
It's probably comprised of a bunch of smaller pieces.
Another anyone let me know if you know how.
What do you know about future slats?
Listener Hashtag Horizons, as cash tag future slats.
I like, yeah, I was just gonna say, like,
I would want a hallway to lead into the room, too, that has sort of that plastic key
kind of vibe, which is also very like Starship Enterprise.
Well, big time.
Yes.
Yeah, monorail ish.
All of that.
Yeah, feels like part of a modern.
Yeah. Yeah.
Monorail has that kind of thing, too.
Yeah, absolutely.
I got to crack it.
I got to figure it out.
I think even before that boarding, like you were saying, the departure board
all around you, there's a lot of glowing colored lights.
You go around some corners and then you get on the ride.
And when there is a hundred and it was
something like one hundred and seventy four ride vehicles on this Omni
Mover system, I never remember waiting a long time for Horizons.
Well, I think that's right.
I mean, that's the problem, probably, other than the sinkhole.
Well, yeah, that that, too.
But but it was nice that it was a ride.
I feel like the outdoor
the outdoor section of like the spaceship Earth Q backs up a lot.
And that can look a lot worse than it is.
I really don't have much memory of the queue for World of Motion,
but I think it's Horizons.
You get the leaderboard and you're pretty quickly at the loading area.
And and not.
And then the first thing you see, you see this crazy ride.
It's like an Omni Mover, but it's got walls on the sides and it the track is above you.
It's not below you.
Feels like it feels like Harry Potter in a way.
These like a little these little pods that are that face flat.
They're you know, we were also we're talking about Ghostbusters.
And we looked at the vehicles for a proposed 80s Ghostbusters shooting ride
that never happened, and it felt like the vibe of these ride vehicles a little bit.
I love the color scheme.
I feel like Ghostbusters would have been similar to it's like that
that like reddish orange that's the backing and then just like black silver on
the front. They look so cool.
I'd also love like a die cast one of these.
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
That's I mean, just in general, like the nostalgia merchandise seems lacking from
Horizons, like give us the building, give us a little building, give us a little toy
of the building. Oh, my God.
One of the kits you put together that's
mostly like just really cut up your fingers if you try to do it.
I let's give it to you. I'll do it.
I will destroy my hands.
I bring that up.
I could not find a lot of real vintage merchandise on eBay for Horizons.
I found a lot of T public accounts selling like the logo.
So if you want the logo, you can certainly get variations of it.
But I really didn't find a lot of like vintage stuff out there for sale.
I just think this was not appreciated at the time.
Like, yeah, in hindsight, I think the
groundswell of support has happened, but it just at the time, I just don't think
it was moving enough people and we can see that now.
And they're not like exploiting it for nostalgia money.
They don't they don't see it.
I think I think it's there now more than they know.
That's what I'm saying.
I guess the fact that those guys were
able to sneak around the ride for so long and that they could count on giant
stretches of ride vehicles that were empty going through constantly.
That sort of tells you it's a bummer, too, because like in like Sinbad ride in Japan
and we were only there for a few days, but we went on in a couple of days and it was
like that was empty, too, and I was like, I hope this doesn't mean this is going away.
But it does feel like sometimes great rides aren't people aren't going on them.
But some of that is they're efficient.
Oh, yeah, for sure.
And then both Sinbad and this one obviously was an omnivore that was very big.
Yes, that's definitely part of it.
But I feel like maybe that maybe works like Haunted Mansion is can get through a
lot of people, but is, you know, usually as a decent line.
It's pretty backed up. Yeah.
So I wonder if it's like those evil money people at the parks look at it and go,
well, this this line is isn't longer than five minutes.
Means it's not that popular.
Well, maybe they had dreams of a ride
that would give people seizures and make them sick.
They just had to get in
a ride that could
affect you negatively for the rest of your life from the people at Compaq.
All right. Oh, my God.
We had to do Mission Space.
Mission Space.
I'm also getting the sense now that there's a dedicated Mission Space fan base
that I did not think existed.
Maybe we'll run into them.
About. Yeah, we've been negative about
Mission Space, or at least I have.
And I think Scott is Jason.
Are you well, I less negative.
I think the first time or two I wrote it,
I was very impressed at what it was able to simulate.
And then the last time my family all went down, we all walked off and everyone needed
to sit on a bench like everyone's like, I need 15 minutes to collect myself.
Everyone was like, oh, like between headaches and queasiness.
Oh, yeah. No, that's my experience.
I think visually, I think the Spaceship Earth building is
cool to look at.
Mission Space or Mission Space.
What did I say? Yeah.
Spaceship. Yeah.
No, Spaceship Earth rules.
No, Mission Space.
I think the building's all right.
But compare going deep dive on Horizon for like a week now.
It's just like, oh, man, it really makes Mission Space look like shit.
It's also a ride that is 15 minutes of sitting on a bench.
Yeah, that's true.
Best way. Seeing the best stuff,
seeing the looking at a screen the size of like a Nintendo DS.
And that's you're watching.
That's another thing that's unique about it.
It's like three times as long as other OmniMover rides, but it's
a third as long as the moving theater kind of rides.
And I don't really know what else falls into that category.
You know, it's just strange.
It almost reminds me of Rise of the Resistance in its like weird multi act
nature and that you explore all the parts of this little campus in many different
ways that combine here's the animatronic zone and here's the screen zone.
And here's a different kind of screen zone.
It's just it's all over the place.
Yeah. And I think that maybe part of its
Genesis, like it had so many different names.
They were going to call it Century Three,
but they were concerned international guests wouldn't understand that.
At some point it was just called Horizon.
And then we got Horizons briefly was considered the name briefly considered
was Future Probe.
And everyone's like, oh, that's the medical implications on that.
We're all we're all aware that we have probes in our future and yeah, but it's
good, it'll help us take care of potential health issues.
But I don't want to think about them when I'm on a ride.
Did they did they want to call Body Wars Future Probes?
More accurate, that's what it is.
Yeah, yeah, that would make sense.
Just the ideas jot it down.
That's early idea was for innovation and
enterprise, which became science and in a venture in a venture.
Then, oh, what's this one?
GE really wanted it to be about Thomas Edison.
That seemed like it got scrapped pretty quickly.
A another name I came across, the Incredible Time Machine,
Colin, a journey into the worlds of science and invention.
That doesn't really roll off the tongue like Horizons.
No, I mean, Horizons is a great name.
Yeah, it also sounds like it could be maybe like a rehab facility
or the name or the name of your yearbook.
Yes.
Yes, for sure.
I look back at 2003.
Right.
It is a great name, though, but it is not so specific.
No, I got to say, though, this Century 3 piece of concept art is awesome.
Well, yeah, like I wish they sold a decent print of that.
That's all vehicles going in a big starburst.
That looks real cool.
Century 3.
Century 3 is a cool name.
I do like Century 3.
Yeah.
I think there's a vehicle in the ride labeled Century 3 somewhere.
I think that's right.
Yeah.
Well, let's get into some stuff.
I mean, I don't know that we have to room by room it, but I guess in a way,
I sort of until watching ride throughs, I sort of forgot all of the past of the
future or the future. Wait.
Yeah.
The future that never was.
The past. Yeah.
Which that's another thing.
There's a lot of Spaceship Earth.
Also, you end up watching old footage with kooky music, like da da da da da da,
which also I think happens on Dream Flight.
I think I mushed that up in my head, too.
But it's neat.
You see Jules Verne in a pod with a dog.
I guess I'm confused by that.
That's how he thought he would get to the moon is
in a little pod where he'd be standing and have a little trunk.
Yeah, a chicken.
I think the chicken would provide eggs, maybe.
Well, they were also like his idea was like, well,
what if you built a gun big enough to shoot a man to the moon?
Cool.
Yeah, you'd write like, you were in the bullet.
Yes.
And then you bring one chicken with you who you hopefully is pretty regular with
egg production, which then do you have to bring a hot plate so that you can
cook them up in there?
Could a rocky style.
Oh, sure. Yeah.
Eat them. Eat them raw.
Pure proteins straight out of the shell.
Yeah, that's all you need.
I mean, that's everyone else is overthinking it right now.
We just get in a giant bullet and go to the moon with a chicken.
Now, should I strap myself in inside the bullet?
And the same question goes for my dog and my chicken.
Or do I just stand without a seat belt?
Hmm.
I think you probably should.
Well, if the bullet is completely the
correct human size and there won't be any room to bump around in.
Oh, no, no, no.
Jules's vision was that there'd be a lot
of room and that the chicken and the dog are untethered to anything.
And that he's just in a full, thick suit, like a big, starchy 1800 suit.
I don't think it's occurred to me how insane this scene is until right now.
Yeah, no, you're right.
It's a good point.
Standing through my trip to space.
It feels like correct because of all the other like, oh, DaVinci and Michelangelo
paint, but that's like normal stuff compared to this.
And when you also meet Jules Verne, this
ride came later, but you meet Jules Verne in the old dreamatorium or whatever that
ride, the Visionarium. Oh, yeah.
There's multiple else.
Magic Kingdom then also had a Jules Verne thing.
And then Doc Brown's obsessed with Jules Verne.
And then a lot of there's all these things that are like this is the future.
Jules Verne and so much Jules Verne in the parks.
And Jules and Verne were Doc's kids in the cartoon.
And in the movie, technically, I guess.
Yes. And somebody pointed out when I
posted a picture of me with my finger in an inappropriate place on the monorail
after a few too many adult libations, and somebody said that it looked like Verne
at the end of Back to the Future 3, who's weirdly pointing to himself.
Oh, right, right, right.
Whatever the hell is happening there.
So I'm sorry.
Yeah, that's a pretty bad own.
I'm sorry I looked like Verne.
That's something to aim for, is to not look like Verne.
Look like Verne.
It's funny, name your kids Jules.
Jules and Verne is such a, oh, what a tribute.
Your father must have your mother must have loved his work.
But then, like, if it was like, hey, Verne, it totally loses any.
Like if you're completely out of contact,
just like then you just think of Ernest's friend Verne.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You are introduced after your brother.
Yeah, right.
Jules, at least you go Jules.
That's a sophisticated name.
You go, hey, Verne, what's a Verne?
Yeah, yeah.
And Ernest ruined it forever.
Ernest. It's Ernest's fault.
There's also like things for a lot of people.
I'm sorry. There's like little lanterns in this Jules Verne car, too.
I kind of can't get off of it now.
Like you had to do would you have to like light a candle inside these?
Yeah.
And then there's drawers, but the drawers aren't baby locked.
Like these drawers would be flying around.
He's the first.
OK, the first things I'll say is that he looks like he's in Jeannie's bottle for my
dream of Jeannie. Oh, yeah.
And then second, second, he
it's like Ed Wynn in Mary Poppins a little bit.
Oh, yeah.
So it's like he's laughing and he's
floating and like you don't get the sense that like he's in space here.
No, not really.
The the there's like kind of a tube at the bottom, which maybe answers a question
that I had, which is how are Jules and the dog and the chicken doing their business?
Bottom tube.
Yeah, bottom tube.
You shitting the bottom tube.
I shouldn't underestimate him.
He thought about unless it's unless it's just one of these like lanterns isn't a
light, but like it's not lit and they just like keep putting their droppings into
the top of that.
Could that be sort of like the exhaust?
Could that be helping fuel the propulsion?
Oh, maybe so. Yeah.
In case it loses any energy from having been shot out of a giant gun.
Right. Exactly.
And then, of course, we know that the bullet ultimately ends up in the moon's eye
and that the eye winces and it seems mad that a bullet he's not the moon's not dead.
But here he is right now.
There's that moon.
I love that trip to the moon moon.
Yeah. And that was what comedy was in France for like 80, 90 years until they got Jerry Lewis.
They were still just laughing at the moon with a with a bullet spaceship in its eye.
They gave it awards every year.
Yes, every year.
Once again, the best actor, the bullet moon.
He did other movies, romcoms.
He fell in love with the sun.
The French loved the smashing pumpkins tonight.
Tonight video.
Finally, a return to form.
We haven't liked the movies since the professor.
Billy Corrigan is our prime minister now.
What else is in that old time?
Are there other animatronics in that in that initial run?
Well, there's yeah, there's all the like kind of illustrated version of the Da Vinci
stuff, and then it kind of very quickly jumps to like a 1930s pulp
future with with the infamous robot Butler and a lot of just art.
Everything is art deco, the windows, the chairs, the avid.
I think they reference the Avenue of the Planets.
Does that get referenced in Tomorrowland 94 as well?
All right.
I future that never was, I think, is a reliable theme park
stand by.
It's always good.
I like any version of them, essentially.
Yeah, that I love that weird future.
I like a little robot Butler.
I like this.
There's a big there's a hair cutting machine that tans you.
And if you watch the videos, you see a close up with like the different settings.
You can go to Hawaiian tan or Palm Springs tan.
I think that's where Great Big Beautiful Tomorrow is playing in an old timey fashion.
There's a woman in a bathtub at some point.
That's a Hoppin future.
It's a Hoppin.
That's the same version of it's a big great big beautiful tomorrow that plays
when they are demonstrating the radio they have in the progress.
Yes.
Like the very
don't don't don't don't don't don't don't.
It's like a real like
John T.
Describe that I guess John T. is the word.
Yeah.
How many people like this is
what is the percentage of people that went through it and went, oh my God, this
is a sequel to the carousel of progress.
How many people knew the carousel of progress to begin with?
Right.
They're like, oh, yeah, they had probably just been on it that morning
and already lots of yes.
I don't underestimate the progress lamp, the version from the World's Fair,
because if you were from the the tri-state New York, New Jersey,
Pennsylvania, like area when the World's Fair is, that was a big thing.
My dad always talks about going to the World's Fair.
So then everyone who was a kid go into the World's Fair.
Then they can hop on a plane when they're adults two hours away, go to Disney,
see the carousel of progress again.
So kind of primed for like a big horizon sort of thing.
Sure.
But I'm still I think I feel like what Mike is saying is like,
if you're like a sunburnt like Budweiser drinking half shirt guy from Florida
in 1983, maybe your World's Fair knowledge is low.
Yeah.
But, you know, every you could be always surprised by the type of World's Fair fan.
You know, you never know who loves the World's Fair.
Shouldn't judge a World's Fair fan by its cover.
Who cares? The secret flame.
There's a lot of talk about, you know,
automation right now because of the pandemic and some companies are now going
to probably use this opportunity to accelerate to automation and to
replace human workers, I will say from this scene,
if they do it with cute robots, I think we'll all be a little bit more happy
with it, even though it'll put a lot of people out of work and cause some strife
for a while.
All good. Yeah. As long as they're cute.
Yeah.
Fine.
Don't deal.
It's like this dish this dishwashing robot, I think, deserves more merch.
Robot Butler sort of I think has become the most famous.
Yeah.
He's got the merchandise.
I've got Scott.
Do you have him in a Park Star?
I don't have him, no.
But they made him.
But I feel like Dishwashing Robot definitely deserves some love.
A little more attention. Sure.
Yeah.
Where do we go from here?
Yeah, we were in that Screenland,
lots of future visions and Buck Rogersy stuff.
Yeah, there's the version of the future.
The next two scenes are both kind of neon
wire work scenes, which are really art movie concept albumy.
And apparently we're put in as a cost
cutting measure, but I think are so cool to look at.
There's the movies,
popular culture kind of movie versions of the future.
And then there's the neon, like modern 1950s view of the future.
Yeah.
I mean, you could definitely like, obviously, these are videos.
My memory isn't so clear of the ride.
But yes, as you're saying, like you can tell it's like not as expensive as robots.
But you're watching it like this looks awesome.
This looks like a cool like real life Jetsons.
Right. Yeah.
When do we end up on?
When do we end up in OmniMax?
So the OmniMax is next.
And this is right before it is the second of three of like kind of transitional,
like colored, like cloud sequences, which I I think work pretty well as a transition
rather than just like black, like totally black room.
I think that's kind of like the lights are synced up to the talking.
Oh, that's right. Yeah.
Oh, the 1950s.
There is a great dialogue exchange about like, wow,
we thought the 1950s, that version of the future is pretty out there.
And then the grandmother again says, like, well, we all wanted to have some fun.
You know, everyone keeps bringing up fun
in this ride, which is very funny to me.
The
these these lines, again, have not lasted like the Carousel of Progress.
I assume just because it's not as round as long.
But I they haven't they didn't stick with me even as much as they did with you.
Did you were you listening for the old people talking and writing down?
Or was that just something that struck you?
It just struck me after a few viewings of like, this is very funny.
The naturalism they tried to make this the way they tried to do this dialogue.
It is it is funny because
there I guess I guess, yeah, what you're
illustrating is they're still sort of playing on the old trope of like
the husband and wife hate each other.
They're going to be passive aggressive.
They're not applying sort of the like like Start to the Next Generation's concept.
Gene Roddenberry's concept of the future was that by and large, humans had
resolved their interpersonal conflicts. Right.
He was like he was talking about like, you know, they're really just trying to like
go about the universe and try to deal with problems that come into contact.
They come in contact with.
But the Disney futurism was still it was still like, well, the husband and wife are
passive aggressive and they cut each other down.
And that's just how it always will be.
So they were still going with an old school
like sitcom way of approaching their future characters.
It's optimistic.
But you got to get a little lock horns in there for mom and dad to laugh.
Are the lock horns represented in Toon Lagoon?
That is a great question.
I could be wrong. Are they King Feature Syndicate?
Well, I'll have to look that up, otherwise I won't get to sleep tonight.
So, yeah, so from the cloud sequence, then you hit the OmniMax screen sequence.
We see some DNA chains, which is like a pretty new thing.
I think we were to DNA aware at that point.
That all looks cool.
Had to be computer rendered.
If I could nerd out slightly on a thing here,
there is some cool synth stuff going on in the sequence kind of throughout the ride,
but especially in here, there's a real synth landscape happening.
And I was like, I wonder if I could figure out who did it.
I wonder if I could look it up.
I looked it up. It's a guy named Michael Bautiker.
Michael Bautiker is one of my favorite
names that you see in albums,
liner notes all the time.
I was so excited to see his name.
He's a Thriller guy. He's all over Thriller.
He's on all my favorite stuff, which is like Michael McDonald and George Benson
and Al Jarreau. We Are the World.
I think the beginning, the big synthy part of We Are the World is him.
He did the score for Buckaroo Banzai.
So that's a cool one.
Pleasant greatest love of all by Whitney Houston.
Mainly was very excited to see Michael Bautiker's name because
we on the Main Street Electrical Parade, we talked about my thing, Lords of Synth.
Lords of Synth is about like people like analogs of
Agergio Moroder and Vangelis and Wendy Carlos.
And to do Wendy Carlos, I was like, I remember tossing out like,
now that's got to be one of those old keyboards.
It's like an old Moog and it's got like all the patches, all the wires.
So go find that.
And then some production designer is like,
those are extremely expensive and very hard to find.
And so he just went searching for people who had just actually had working
equipment from that era, like what Wendy Carlos would have used.
And where did he end up finding one?
From this gentleman, Michael Bautiker.
We used a real old keyboard.
I looked up what it is. It's the Moog System 55.
We used a real like vintage piece of equipment.
And I remember being told, if you break this thing, this costs like two times
the budget of this entire piece, so do not be extremely careful with it.
We were.
I didn't know until after we shot it that it was this is from the collection
of this guy who played on Thriller.
I'm 80 percent sure he played the creepy,
awesome, evocative synths that play while you're waiting for Captain Eho, like outside.
Like there's all this ambient stuff at the beginning.
And maybe, maybe some of this Horizon stuff was played on that thing that we got
to use as Carlo Windows's synth in one of my favorite things I've ever been a part of.
Was it plugged in on doing it or was it just for the look?
Just for the look? No, no, no, we didn't.
I think you'd need like a real technician to figure out how the hell to operate it.
And I remember the actress being very tentative, like, OK, I heard the scary
warning and we're like, just bash the thing, keep plugging stuff in and out.
And she's like, should I though?
Yeah.
And you are still paying for the repairs.
But it was very funny to see Josh Fadum take a pratfall through it.
Didn't end up using it in the cut.
It just didn't work.
But it was fun. I'm glad he tried it.
And yes, I will owe money to Michael Bodeker for the rest of my life.
That would honestly, they'll give you a good excuse maybe to see him once in a while.
Oh, my God. Yeah.
I've been wondering if there's a way to contact him.
Here's a check. Here's your check for the month.
What I heard is that because when I asked, like, why did this guy lend it out?
And he said, well, I explained the concept
and that it was referencing, you know, Wendy Carlos and stuff.
And he was like, that sounds cool.
Look, I should charge you way more, but I just want this thing to be a part of it.
I think he's just like a nice guy.
So, yeah, listen to his cool stuff, especially in this Omni-Max room.
This guy rules.
That's very cool.
And accompanied by like just really, again, abstract, but pretty beautiful.
Like, it feels like an art film when they cut from a city to a microprocessor.
Very still kind of new in the popular
consciousness at the time, and then crystals and the ocean and DNA strands.
And at the end, just the sun.
Yeah, this is in that zone of like scary Epcot films.
The films announcing Epcot were scary.
The films in the Universe of Energy, the movie at the end of Maelstrom,
just these like strange narrator free.
You're just left to free associate what imagery is all about.
There's so many films in Epcot and all of them extremely stark, all of them very adults.
There's nothing where somebody's like doing a cute voice and talking to you.
It's all like just like criterion type
scary 70s documentaries.
It would be these are the you would be like if you were
if it would be like the equivalent of like taking a film class in college and
they're like, now we have to watch like 2001 and now we have to watch.
These are the challenging films.
These are. Yeah.
You're not going to do your Wizard of Oz is in your Indiana Jones.
You're getting like Stan Brakhage ink blots, paint, paint drops and stuff.
But I love I love scary star Epcot.
But of course, things get a little friendlier when we go to the future.
And this is the meat of the thing that you are.
You visit three very different visions of the future, which are essentially land,
sea and space, I guess, land.
You could be more specific and say desert.
Well, you see the irrigated desert.
The grandparents live the city.
See, that's where the city is separate from.
Is that that's a considerate part of land in general?
Yeah, land is kind of split in two.
That's another cool like a film cut almost where it's like you see the apartment.
They're like, I'll take the city.
Yes, it's always exciting.
And then they kind of transition into the the deserts, the reclaimed desert,
where the daughter is in irrigation, agricultural engineering.
So does the city not count as one of the futures?
Because I was going to say we should like pick a I mean,
I think we still could in general, but like at the end we should discuss
what's our ideal future. I don't know if the city counts,
but that's where I want to be. I love that city very much.
Well, it's always exciting.
It's always exciting.
It's always if I pull up this and for good listener, forgive me.
But we'll describe it.
Triangular buildings with weird like
Orby things coming out of them,
like the fountains out front, perpetual dusk, like this beautiful pink dusk.
I want to be here so very much.
It's like there's buildings that look like the Studio 54 logo, essentially.
I mean, I think this picture I literally did send to somebody involved in Moonbeam
City, I think we're chasing this vibe or it's always pink dusk
or this this orange one, too.
Like I have nothing
productive to say.
I just love these places so much and I want to be in that apartment.
I want to I want to be where that Carousel of Progress guy is wearing his jumpsuit.
I want to be playing his orb keyboard,
his weird light up nonsensical instrument.
I love this world so much.
Yeah, I feel like it's an aesthetic that
I kind of never goes out of style.
And one thing I saw mentioned in the genesis of Horizons is that people's
visions of the future had kind of matured a little in popular culture.
You know, you had Blade Runner, you had Alien, you know, and very grim and grimy.
And this kind of marries the two of like a mature version of the future.
But it is hopeful. It is optimistic.
You know, yeah.
And realistic and realistic.
Yeah, it still seems realistic.
Mm hmm.
Yeah, it's not so well, it's all like based in current technology.
It's all like several steps beyond technology that we have, like the
irrigation machines, I guess that's a lot of steps beyond.
But I guess this is that's kind of one of the most striking parts of the ride is
fields that's being plowed by these giant machines that
feel like they like if reprogrammed in a wrong Skynetty way could do a lot of damage.
These feel like War of the Worlds a little bit, but they're friendly.
They harvest oranges for us.
Yeah, fine.
I mean, they're not as cute as the dishwashing robot, but yeah, they're friendly, I think.
I was just reading an article.
There was one there was a climate scientist that was very alarmist saying
that we're already past the point of of no return as far as climate change.
Although I've seen now other people say that's not completely true.
We can always turn it on.
But he was saying that there needs to be like massive
machines built to pull carbon out of the air.
Right. Yeah.
We'll figure it out, right?
We're going to get them.
Which I mean, humanity in general is like, you know,
how I was in college, like I put everything off to the last minute.
Like a lot of people are.
As we saw with the virus and we saw how well that went.
Yeah.
So maybe we'll build these giant machines
to pull carbon out of the atmosphere, like a couple of weeks before the planet dies.
And just like college Mike Carlson,
we knew about the problems for a very long time because, like,
reclaiming the desert for like lush green space, crops, desalinate,
desalinization of saltwater to make it consumable or usable in crops.
People have been thinking about that for hundreds, if not thousands of years at this point.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And we got a week at a.
Yeah, you know,
there's this guy.
So Mark Zuckerberg broke the world.
And then, you know, we'll get to the desalinization, you know.
But yeah, I mean, there's no.
Yeah, all the futurism is rooted in like reality of the time.
And so we're saying now is still stuff that needs to be done or still
possible things that could help turn some problems around.
I'm trying to think, is there anything in here
like they didn't forecast everything, they didn't forecast like celebrities
going to Swedish clinics to get teenage blood to stay alive longer?
Like, I assume Quincy Jones is doing.
They forecast it like Pluots, like the lemon orange, like
creations in this ride, you know.
Wait, yeah.
No, hang on.
This is something I never caught.
And I copy pasted this big stretch.
By the way, this world that we're talking about is Mesa Verde.
That's the that's the land world
which, of course, oddly is a is a recurring location in Better Call Saul.
So Horizons used it first.
Disney gets you in.
But yeah, Mesa Verde world.
And it's yeah, we're dealing with with irrigation.
One of the characters in it we follow is like a farming person.
And there's a shelf that you see that's a bunch of fruits.
And I never put it together that they are weird, hybrid fruits of fruits that we have
in them. Let me see.
There's this ivy that you look at, but it's not a regular ivy.
It's called Circuit Egg Ivy.
I don't understand that one.
Pepcumbers.
I guess that one's pretty clear.
And I like saying the word flavor grapes.
Well, now that's just
so you're going to show me regular grapes, but tell me that this one tastes
like a lemon and this one's a kumquat.
I mean, that's a that's lazy naming.
I think the idea is sound.
Yeah, yes.
But the texture and experience of eating a grape is good.
And I would be interested to try different flavors.
If a great surprise to you with its flavor, yes, that would be cool.
This one's black licorice.
You
so jelly bellies.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You popcorn.
Popcorn grape poop.
And then pin.
OK, how do you say this?
Pine, I guess it'd be pine anas.
Pine anas. Yeah, yeah.
Or pineapple. That's got to be delicious.
That kicks ass. Yeah, I would.
I mean, that'd be a drink.
For sure. Yeah, yeah.
And loranjes, limes and orange.
Also Michael's his own oranges.
I want I need the assistant, the loranjeets
need to give me a basket of loranjes or I can't start the meeting.
If you go into Lauren's office, do not eat the orange.
It is just the bowls of loranjes are just a test.
You're not going to get update if you eat the orange.
Yeah.
Guys, I'm realizing because I know a Mesa is like a geographical, you know,
like a plateau, but it only occurred to me just now that the name Mesa Verde is a
wordplay because Mesa, I believe the translator is telling me it is also
the Spanish word for table.
So technically Mesa Verde means green table.
Huh? Oh, greenery harvest.
Yeah. Right. How about that?
So that so that they named it is a national park.
So they named that.
That's what's a cute name.
Yeah, that's a cute name.
Or it could just be named after the national park.
And I'm going too far.
Maybe. I don't know.
I didn't realize until
Blankchek and Griffin Newman did great
episodes there.
There's a Mecha's run and they're back to the future.
Episodes have been great.
And I didn't realize till he pointed out
that Hill Valley is like a conundrum impossible in all these years.
I never put that together.
Hill Valley makes no sense.
Yeah, that's funny.
I had a joke that's been there the whole time.
And it's just a it's a little Easter egg.
You get it later.
And then we all just went like, hmm,
that's the degree of
I like it when I like Christopher Lloyd yells.
That's more what I was focusing on.
OK, so I mean, this one's cool.
Bravas and Tari.
No, you end with that.
I guess the next one is what's the sea called?
Sea Castle, Sea Castle.
Yes.
So a great transition here where the granddaughter teenage granddaughter is
talking to a video conference call
of her boyfriend, who they call a beach bum.
She's like, he works, he works on a floating city.
And then it cuts to the other angle
where there's an animatronic boyfriend and the video girlfriend.
I believe the boyfriend in the video is a young Tom Fitzgerald,
one of the lead imagineers on this ride.
Yeah, I guess so.
I you know,
yeah, I threw it out to a friend of the show Bugman Buzz Buzz,
because I know he shares the my fondness for like Epcot attractions being weird
and scary and just like being up at night and exploring these claustrophobic
spaces. And I'm like, I'm just like, what is his main thing with Horizons?
Because I know he's going to have one.
And he said
the that there would be that you see characters as on a video screen as real
human beings and then as robots is so clever and so like also like off putting
and upsetting a little bit and like when you take each individual side of it,
that you're watching a robot whose boyfriend is a real man.
And then you switch it and it's the other way.
And he was like, yeah, who are these actors?
Like, does anyone track them down?
So interesting finding out that one of them wrote the ride.
And the other one, apparently, I had her IMDb.
Her name is Corinne Cook, and she has some fun credits,
including that she is in a movie called Malibu Hot Summer,
which has also been released as Sizzle Beach USA.
And this is one of the first, maybe the first film credit of Kevin Costner.
Oh, yeah. Wow.
So check out Malibu Hot Summer.
Let me see if I can get a tagline on it real fast.
Three girlfriends who find careers and the hottest offer of their lives in.
Wait, what? In Malibu Hot Summer.
What's weird?
I got confused by the grammar in that part way through.
Fuck you, Malibu Hot Summer.
I want to add to the unsettling.
I'm sorry, the dialogue they actually call that what they call him is a beach boy.
Not. Yeah, it's Beach Boy.
Yeah, Beach Boy.
And the dialogue is because she's defending the Beach Boy to her parents instead
of flirting or is it them the parents bickering instead of flirting with that
Beach Boy, he is not a Beach Boy.
As if that's so bad, as we've determined
that these are now plans that I have to join the Beach Boys.
And I would think that any parent in law would be very proud of me.
Yeah, like this is another where they're
like sort of just going in the going with the past because, you know, in 2080,
obviously, the Beach Boys will still be touring in 2080.
And I'm going to be the most like tangible original member.
Like, I'm propped up by robotics like he actually did meet
Mike Love right before he died, so he counts.
He's the one with the most legitimacy.
You look like, of course, the emperor on Exegol being
arm, a kooka arm behind you
puppeted to sort of tap a keyboard and play
Kokomo 2070, the update that we did.
The concerts are now only vibrate are real vibrations.
You can't hear it.
It's just you're hearing them like on these low tones.
Yeah, yeah. You have to you have to be a precog.
You have to be in the precog tubes to experience the tubes.
And you will be on the floating city,
but it is not the beautiful utopia of this floating city.
It is called an atoll.
Oh, yes, the plane by smokers, floating atolls.
The Deacon and his posse of Beach Boys.
Yeah, he's a marine biologist and they call him a beach boy.
Beach boy.
Odd disrespect to that profession.
I do. I mean, that's obvious.
I feel like that's a thing in the 50s and 60s where parents would be like,
you're you're good for nothing surfer boyfriend, huh?
What a real loser he is.
If he was respectable, he'd be dying in a factory right now.
Yeah, he'd be in up in St.
Clairs, the jungle, putting the meat pieces in the casing machine.
But all these I mean, all these old parrot heads, they would love a beach boy.
Yeah, they'd be like, oh, great.
You're one of us.
I'd say so.
Yeah. Well, and these guys have so much fun up there.
They get to show kids some seals and float around in the ocean with some
projected scenes. Right.
Yeah. Yeah. They're having a lot of fun in this.
So this one's like a competitor.
It's tough to the three are all competing for best future.
It's hard to determine.
I don't know which button I'm going to press at the end.
Yeah, I mean, I didn't watch a lot of Sequest DSV as a kid, but I certainly did
put it on Peacock last two nights ago.
How'd it go?
I have like
I have like affection for it exists for remembering that it existed when I was
young. Yes.
The vague idea of it.
Yes. Yeah.
So I don't know.
I like the idea of all of this, but I don't know yet.
I'm still well, do we do we bring the third one in?
Do we bring Bravo Centauri in as the option number three?
A quick shout out for the number of animatronics in that two story sea castle
scene. Yeah.
And then you see the people enjoying their dinners
in the little like porthole viewing stations.
This is also where you get the grandmother saying a very Kurt.
Well, so am I.
Is just very dig it.
Take a look at that dialogue exchange.
It's funny to me.
Why are they so upset?
They live in that awesome loft apartment in Triangle City.
They look at dusk every day.
I think it's dusk from morning to night.
It's always dusk there.
They said it's only a few minutes to go and see their kids, but they also had the
option to video everyone's video chatting.
That's a funny thing that where this ends up is like it's a birthday and people
can't be there in person, so they all just project videos of themselves.
And that's a future that we have realized.
Why we had spent a whole year of virtual birthdays.
Isn't it as fun as Horizons?
Yeah.
Yeah, it is fun.
Wow. Grandma got on the machine.
Well, that's and she's synced up in her singing with mom who's off in Seattle.
This rules just as good.
Well, no problem.
My son-in-law and his family would choose to live nowhere else.
Whatever they said.
Boy, Horizons could have predicted Zoom
backgrounds and all the fun that we've had with those.
Definitely enough ideas for how to play with Zoom backgrounds to sustain
two years worth of Zooming.
I'm realizing now I should have.
Yeah, I know here now I'm doing it.
Let's get back to the let's get back to the fun.
You know what I want to say about the future.
It looks like the Cloud City.
Yeah. And Star Wars.
That's neat.
Which is the place to be.
Which is what and any of these hotels
I think would be more fun than the Star Wars Hotel they're building.
Oh, yeah. Being a Cloud City Hotel.
Yes, would be very cool.
Yeah. And that tiny little cell prison cell on the Star Wars Hotel.
We'll see. We'll go.
We'll have to go try. I'm going to go.
I'm going to pay $900 a night to go to this hotel.
Pay a rent a month just under a month's rent payment.
Yeah. Anyway. For who?
Nine hundred dollars.
Ooh, OK.
Living in a closet.
All right. Move again.
So the word space from Bravo Centauri.
Bravo Centauri.
Now, just in general to talk about, like, you know, we're deciding here.
Living in space, there was no fantasy I had more like that loomed in my mind than
living on the Enterprise as a kid.
So while we're this is a little bit more like clinical.
Yeah, yeah.
It's not as fun as a space as Star Trek.
But, man, watching this, I'm like, yeah, that's as a kid.
That always felt like the coolest thing.
I think I would definitely have picked space as a kid.
Yeah.
Well, you get to be upside down in this one.
You get upside down animatronics in this one.
Yeah.
The the the hanging OmniMover setup really adds to the like floating through
underwater, floating through space,
I think really heightens that in a nice way.
Also, the going from ocean to like there's a little bit of blackness in under the
ocean and then little stars show up and then you're in space.
A lot of cool theatrical tricks.
Yeah. Transitions.
Yeah, it's it's like I'm trying to think and maybe this is unfair to like Little
Mermaid, but it just like it feels like it's doing so much of a better job
simulating you going and changing like terrain.
Yeah, like Little Mermaid, you go under water.
And like obviously we've talked about that.
Like the original idea was like it would feel more like you're floating.
But Little Mermaid always to me feels like you're just on the Haunted Mansion
like OmniMover track for the most part.
But this together, this they went all out,
really trying to immerse you and make you feel like you were switching
scenery and switching terrain, switching gravity.
I have a question.
Maybe you guys can confirm for me about one of the tricks in the birthday party
scene in space, the video screens, are they animatronics kind of like poking out
of the video screens? Is that right?
Was I imagining that or is that a pepper's ghost?
Is that a pepper's ghost?
Yeah, that's a good question.
Because they are coming out of it, essentially.
It's hard to tell from a video.
Yeah, yeah.
It's just kind of a funny choice of like, oh, did this get built first?
And then they had to resort to filmed footage for the other ones for like saving money.
I don't know. I do like it.
It looks like it looks like it looks like pepper's ghost to me.
Yeah, that's my guess, because like on the video
and I'm just scrolling here to try to on this video, I'm looking at it does look
like pepper's ghost, but I don't know that to be a fact.
Hmm, not sure.
I don't have a lot about the space stuff.
It's cool up there.
I like seeing people upside down.
I like seeing, you know, little jumps suited kids.
I guess I wanted to be a jumps suited kid.
I want to be like a bill mummy.
I don't know.
Kids in space always have a good time.
Yeah, kids in space.
I definitely knew aliens very bad time.
Ender's game.
Mm hmm.
Yeah.
All right.
Kids don't always have a good often kids have a horrible time in space.
But are you talking from Alien three?
Newt, what happens with what's up with Newt by then?
No, too.
He gets.
Well, no, it knew it is an alien aliens, which is alien, the second aliens.
And then in between aliens two and three, he just gets killed off screen.
Oh, oh, no.
Oh, aliens, aliens, the third aliens.
It's just like he's dead.
But Newt's a girl.
Oh, yeah, you're right. Sorry.
Newt dies, Newt dies in between.
I'm forgetting.
OK, movies.
That happens for sure.
Newt dies. OK, OK.
No, I for some reason, I'm in Alien three.
So I don't know.
Depressing. Well,
now I guess we're all right if we're picking if we're picking a button,
if we're picking a return path or if you had to live in one of these futures,
I guess I guess that's really the question.
Do you like because now we get these three
awesome model sequences that are like Star Tours before Star Tours,
like the biggest model sets ever built, the shoots that took two years.
These things are so awesome.
These little like minute long simulator sequences.
But what do we choose if you had to take
one of those paths and then live the rest of your life and Mesa Verde or
Brava Centauri or Sea Castle, what do we pick?
I think I always picked Brava Centauri or Sea Castle.
Brava Centauri used in all of the marketing material,
the the in-room, I watched an in-room loop from 1992,
that little short snippet of space flight, I feel like was they just got marketing
material for years out of that footage?
Oh, yeah, like disconnecting from the docket and kind of and start to fly through.
Yeah, yeah. And I was like, I have that footage lodged in my brain and I could
never remember what it was from. And I sometimes I forget it was it was
Horizons. Yeah, this.
OK, so wait in the if I'm choosing, is it I'm going to live here for the rest
of my life? Hmm.
Is that what the exercise is?
Well, I don't know.
Maybe we're just maybe we're just picking a button on the ride.
If that makes it easier.
Oh, OK. Yes, that makes it a lot easier.
What do you want to kill you?
The pressures of underwater, the pressures of the vacuum of space or the
unrelenting heat of the desert, the pressures of big city life?
Oh,
I think I'm going space
because, yes, all that Brava Centauri stuff.
And even though it's not quite the enterprise, still you get to float around.
You got the jumpsuit on
and there's still like just that that fantasy as a child, I think, is still too
strong. You know, yeah, I think I got it.
I got to go as cool as the city is right on.
I think I'm going Mesa Verde.
It's not that Mesa Verde is that cool in and of itself.
And I don't know if I want to work in irrigation.
I don't know if I want to program those giant machines, but I would like to smell
oranges. And I think that model sequence, that flight path is extremely cool.
I like that you land on a little like
helipad outside of like a future New Mexico build it like this.
The vibe of like future Southwest, I think, is so awesome.
So maybe I'm going with that one.
Maybe maybe C is too claustrophobic for me.
Like that path is cool.
And they the little model footage that they shot, they made it look underwater by
using like fog effects.
They didn't actually shoot in a tank or anything.
They simulated it with fog and smoke.
So that sequence is cool, but it's also it's also murky.
Like if anything leaks, I think down in Sea Castle, you're in a lot of trouble.
So if I go to Mesa Verde, then I can go
hang out in pink Triangle City whenever I want.
And I think I'm set.
Well, Mesa Verde, that's the that's the that's a long term choice.
Yeah, sure. Yeah.
And I get that.
It gives you more flexibility.
You know, being close to your parents,
I'm still pretty close to my parents where I am now.
I didn't make the leap to Los Angeles,
which is equivalent to you guys making the leap to the sea or space as you did by
moving here. Yeah, I think I would choose out complete the triangle.
I will choose Sea Castle because different things.
Well, we all make different things.
I don't know. I just feel I like being by bodies of water.
I like staring at a lake or staring at the ocean.
If I can't sleep, I automatically put on like running water, mountain stream waves.
I think it's just one way I reset my brain.
Certainly it's one of the ways I have
managed to sleep during our current future.
Well, you are a beach boy.
I am a beach boy. Yeah, I love the beach.
You don't. Yeah, you don't deny it.
You don't think you don't find that to be an insult, as the grandparents intended.
I can barely hang a framed photograph.
I am not an engineer of any
irrigation or marine biology or or space.
I am solely a beach boy.
Have you ever hung a picture?
I've hung a picture.
I just when you start to get into you got to find a stud.
Oh, is the drywall strong?
And I just hate all that shit.
Depends what you're hanging. Yeah.
Well, yeah.
No, we'd all be screwed in terms of working in any of these places.
Yeah, I don't know.
I don't know if they accounted for podcasting
as your employment in these worlds, but it may be interesting.
Now via Zoom, we know that we can do this distantly.
So maybe there is a future in which we're
recording this podcast separately from space, the desert and under the sea.
Yes.
But popping out of our frames in a hologram fashion
and wishing each other happy birthday.
Yes.
The ride does not the experience does not end there.
So as you get out of the ride, there were a couple different versions of the exit.
One
was a beautiful hand painted mural called
the prologue and the promise by Robert McCall.
And I'll bring it up.
I have it right here with Robert McCall in the photo.
You can see him right there.
Real. That's the scale of it.
He's as big as the people in the.
Oh, my God.
That really shows you how huge this thing is.
Yes.
And so this only lasted a few years before
they subbed it in for like a glowing GE logo.
And I asked around in preparation for this episode because I saw one blog that said
they preserved this canvas, they preserved the mural.
And I asked some of our peers, do you know where it is?
And the answer was, I think it's been lost.
I don't think I don't think at least anyone at the moment knows.
So if you know where the prologue and the promise and the rock, the McCall estate,
you know, recall was a big like space age painter
and they have it on their website and I'm sure you can get a nice print of it.
And it's a very beautiful painting, but only lasted a little while.
It's a mural about the promise of the future and they lost it.
It's gone. It's destroyed.
Well, I think it's just things happen in like 30, 40 years.
Like you take it somewhere, you put it in a warehouse and God knows where it ends
up and then the building it was in is destroyed.
But I did not realize I only stuck around for a little while.
Hmm.
Well, they scattered Horizons things all across different parks internationally.
Those are little ways you could experience Horizons elsewhere in the Disney park
verse, one of them being these the three amazing model sequences of flying
to your future destination are all used at or were used at the end of star tours
in Tokyo Disneyland.
I think I mentioned this a little in our episode about the Pangalactic Pizza port,
but basically it was like a post flight thing.
You would end star tours.
Then you go up to this bank of monitors and see all of the offerings of these
different settings and a big screen called TourScan.
And there's a little robot telling you about all of them, about desert and space
and sea. And that robot was the robot named Dan Android,
which delights me as much now as it did a year ago when we talked about that.
So check out the Pangalactic Pizza port on the second gate.
A bunch of other things like robot parts and various Horizons odds and ends were
all dumped on the France back lot tour where they pretended these were props for
movies or something instead of a ride that almost fell into a sinkhole.
The France back lot tour, we clearly have to hit it because Disney just put out
this video saying here's what's coming up in the future.
And one of them,
I forget, I don't know which of you tweeted this, but that that the concept art of
here's Catastrophe Canyon and here's a big cars truck smiling at a fire.
It is the creepiest imagery.
Somebody on Twitter said it reminded them of the everything is fine dog.
Yeah.
Finally, the cars can feel pain.
The cars can scream.
I was Jason Tweedy.
I figure it's human and Jason's voice.
I like that. But yeah, that Fred's back to her.
What a bizarre mess.
I so I don't know.
They like strewed a bunch of horizon shit all over there.
I forget what.
But I don't know. I think they did this ride dirty.
I think it was replaced by a thing that is that a lot of people don't like.
I remember I think I might have been in
Disney World at a point where they were mid destroying it.
I'm not totally sure.
Just seeing it with a fence around it was bad.
Or maybe I'm just conflating that with that.
I've seen photos of that a wrecking ball went through half of this beautiful
building. It's such a bummer.
I don't know. Such as just a not graceful end to a really cool, ambitious attraction.
Yeah, it is brutal.
The operating schedule of like fall 93, the GE sponsorship ends late 94.
Horizons closes.
It reopens December 95 because
Universal Energy was being re redone and World of Motion was being redone.
And July 9, January 9, 1999 was the last day of operation.
There were some tests that supposedly in fall 99, there were some press groups who
got to go through it, but it just never reopened again.
And that's very sad because the the people who worked on this, just a murderers
row of the imagineers were Marty Sklar, George McGinnis, Claude Coates,
John Hench, Rolly Crump early on, like Tom Fitzgerald.
We said, like, so many people that just come up in the history of the Disney parks
and theme park design in general were like had a hand in this music by the guy.
Who co-wrote the music for Sunny Eclipse with Cal David, the voice of Sunny Eclipse.
What do we think of the theme song?
Oh, yeah, I think it's a nice one.
I think I mean, I'd love just they need to put out a vinyl or wait, there's an Epcot
vinyl, isn't there? Maybe there is and I don't have it.
If there's I should get if it exists, whatever has all these songs, because as
we discussed, I do like living with the land, the song.
Let's not have confusion about that.
That I listen to the land is the song.
Oh, OK.
It's a jeez.
Minor differences.
Listen to the land.
Yeah, there's an official Epcot album.
I don't know if it was put out before or after Horizons.
But yeah, when you say the official song,
do you mean the like easy listening kind of like track?
Yeah, I mean, I can play a snippet real quick.
I also have if we're going to I also have the unreleased demos.
What? Really?
Yes. Why?
Because they're on YouTube.
Weird. Wow.
Uh, let's just get a little taste here.
So this is the main one.
I think I'd like it if it had no children on it.
Children's choirs I'm not a big fan of, but the instrumentally, I think it's wonderful.
It's like the Carpenters or something.
It's lovely.
And there are five different demos I found on YouTube here, and I'll just play one of them.
I'm not going to you can go and find it yourself.
But they were doing some different styles.
Tomorrow,
like the heartwarming side of the friend,
where we work, where we play dreams come true every day.
As we reach for new horizons,
we have learned to get more out of living.
I like this.
This sounds like the song they would play when the world ends, like when the last
night is snuffed out, is an epilogue for humanity.
This is this song plays during the end of something.
This time there is space as we reach for new horizons.
This is what music will all sound like in the future.
In the year 2080.
This, though, you know, back to albums,
you know, Prince has been releasing, the Prince of State has been releasing these
albums full of like five discs of demos.
How about we start doing that with these
rides because you know, multiple versions of songs exist.
Obviously, they had to work on things and they tried things.
Absolutely. Yes.
Let's get this for all the rides.
Let's get an official releases remastered.
Yeah, every instrumental track, every false attempt.
And let's make that weird orb keyboard exist because I'd buy that.
That's what I would.
I'd spend $20,000 to buy that if it worked.
Yeah, I agree.
The theme song brought up a big thing we have missed talking about.
If we can dream it, we can do it.
The much misattributed quote,
which D23 had an article, the D23 website or no, was it IO9?
I forget now.
This has been confirmed over the years as all these guys start to age and like no
one is telling the like really good dirt stories yet, but everyone is calling their
shots of like that was me and Tom Fitzgerald says, I'm familiar with that
phrase, I wrote it.
Now, why is this an object of fuck you?
I thought of dream and do it because it is often credited to Walt Disney.
Right.
And for years, I thought Marty Sklar wrote it.
But, yeah, I think Fitzgerald,
one of the former Gawker Gizmodo sites had a here are fake Walt Disney quotes.
And here is the actual context for these quotes.
And that was one of them.
You when you say fake, you mean ones that people think are him, not the game I
played a couple of years ago with everyone, and I made up generic quotes.
Yes, ones.
But they are similar of like with the power of imagination.
Even a poor man can be rich.
You know, like it's like Walt did not say this.
Fuck you.
I thought of the world has room for all of the magic we could ever imagine.
Give me some fucking respect.
Very important phrase.
Yeah.
So that is that is a thing.
Also, I did not see the video for this, but it appears like much of early Epcot.
There was a grand
opening ceremony with a lot of people in white jumpsuits.
And you love to see it.
Yeah. Yeah.
Holding big future tennis rackets with an Epcot logo as the net.
This looks like a hell of a party.
Wonderful.
I think I thought of a good way to go out with these with these quotes and just
thinking about like the futurism of Walt Disney or Tom Fitzgerald and the hope
and these visionaries who created and inspired this very hopeful ride.
And to to combine that with the visionaries that we actually ended up with,
I'm right now going to share my screen.
I'm going to go to Elon Musk's Twitter and let's just I think let's go round.
Robin and all three of us say one of the last thing, if it's just a retweet,
it's not going to work.
But let's just find the last coherent things that he's tweeted and say them
in the most Walt Disney fashion that we can.
And this will be a beacon to the future of now or the future of 2020, not to the
horizon's future.
Let's see.
And I haven't screened these.
So this this might not work.
I don't know.
Oh, I think it's going to work great.
All right.
You know, there's a saying that I often think I stop and think to myself.
And it's this Tesla holiday software release is fire to fire emojis.
I guess I'll go next.
Well, there's something I always would say.
Cobra Kai is a deep cut.
And this next one's confusing.
I wonder if there's a more clean.
Yeah, I want for you.
It's hard to vocalize the galaxy brain.
No, no, no. Yeah.
And now he's just been tweeting about the launch.
Oh, no. Here, I should just keep trying to find one because he was got a positive
covid test. Oh, that's right.
Or two positive covid test, two negative.
Wait, wait, what did he tweet about the that's that's what we close on.
Yeah, he's been tweeting.
He's been trying to like debunk Kovac.
He's he's on a mission for months to debunk.
OK, OK. Here's what I'm going to do here.
What, Jason, you should close it out.
Will you just look up whatever he tweeted about having covid?
And in the meantime, I will say our final
things, you survived podcast, the Ride Horizons edition.
I hope you feel nice and hopeful.
And if you do share some of that hope by interacting with us,
you can choose between the three choices of Twitter, Instagram or Facebook.
And also be sure to check out three bonus
episodes every month at the podcast or at the second gate at patreon.com
slash podcast, the Ride.
Did you find any that?
I don't know if you have a phone or computer handy.
I didn't mean to just command you there, Jason.
No, I got it. OK, great.
So so in the words of our great futurists of today,
let me set this up a little like they they would in the style of the ride.
Yeah, these futures might seem far out,
but they are possible with the power of imagination.
And progress and something extremely bogus is going on was tested for covid
four times today, two tests came back negative, two came back positive,
same machine, same test, same nurse rapid antigen test from BD.
If you can dream it, yes, you can do it.
Goodbye, folks.
This has been a forever dog production,
executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner,
Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify or wherever you get your
podcasts, keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter
and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.