Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast-a-Ride, the second gate.
McGruff 2, the sequel.
Will it be like Attack of the Clones, or Empire Strikes Back, or The Last Jedi?
You'll have to stay tuned to find out.
My name is Mike Carlson, as always joining me, Jason Sheridan.
Yeah, when I saw Attack of the Clones opening day, one of the biggest pops I'd ever heard from a theater-going audience when Yoda pulled out a lightsaber.
People went nuts.
Sure. Did you pop so hard?
We were very excited. I didn't know it was coming, you know?
So you did pop so hard.
I did, yeah.
Scott Garner's here. Did you pop when you saw that, Scott?
I didn't see it in the theaters. So when you say all those, McGrowen McGruff says all of those sequel names, I'm not sure what he means by what his feelings are about any of those.
Not sure either.
Empire Strikes Back is the worst.
Yeah.
What do you mean? It's his dad. Makes no sense.
The sequel trilogy is better. I love the sequel trilogy.
I didn't like any of them until JJ.
I can't wait to get bombarded from all those investor day announcements. We're all going to remember and enjoy those programs for many years to come.
All 10 series.
Sorry. So we're too excited. This is going to happen a lot, especially over the Zoom where we're all like, we want to do the voice.
We don't want to talk like him.
Cheaper by the dozens coming back and I couldn't be more thrilled.
It's been a real shame living in a world without the mighty ducks. About time Emilio took matters into his own hands.
I hope it's grittier than the original.
Counterfeit hockey pucks are a danger. They could explode if hit too hard.
Make sure to only buy hockey pucks from a licensed dealer.
Counterfeit duck calls an entire other piece of business. I'm more lenient on those, honestly.
I'm good friends with a guy named Wild Wing.
And the Iceman. He got done dirty.
Mascots remain close. Once in the mascot brotherhood, always in the mascot brotherhood.
We're only getting started here, folks.
We've got to save the voice. It's going to be a raspy time for all of us. We might all end up feeling it.
Boy oh boy, McGruff 2. I can't believe we're there and not just because, you know, the anticipation is assuredly incredibly high.
If you don't know, we did an episode a while back, a pretty well received episode, I have to say, from what you, the audience, tell us,
which was devoted mostly to a McGruff album called the Smart Kids album. McGruff's musical career.
There's some other stuff. Some of the Burger King era made its way in there, but I think that it seems like that's what we're going to explore a little more today.
Yes. And so just, yeah, just in case you, I'm sure if you're on the Patreon and you've listened, you've heard McGruff 1, but just in case,
let's do a quick refresher because there's an album called Smart Kids and our, I think we all agree, Smart Kids is funny because McGruff is singing, but it is also good.
The album is good. So like, we'll just play a little bit. This is alcohol, the song Alcohol.
Like this is a good groove.
I re-listened today. It hooked me right.
Hey, open up your eyes.
This is called Make Your Body Last.
That one snuck up on me. It's a side two and you think it's kind of tipping by side two, but then this shows up.
Yeah.
I also, I haven't listened to him a little bit and I listened to a couple of the tracks this morning and I went, man, this is great. This is not faded. This is not a novelty. These songs are great.
You know, yeah, we've all, you know, they've all stuck with us, I think, ever since. Hopefully with some of you, the audience, hopefully these are classics to you now.
My strongest memory, post McGruff 1, was that there was, and I don't know who it was, but there was a guest who came over to your apartment in the recording in your apartment days.
And it was somebody who was a friend of ours, but like not as mired in everything as us.
So we were explaining the situation with the McGruff Smart Kids album.
And I think whoever this was kind of filled in the gaps and said like, oh, and it's actually kind of good.
And Mike, your response was, it's really good.
Like you had, there was like a voice quiver. It like shook you to explain how really good the McGruff Smart Kids album is.
I had like a slightly orgasmic reaction to what you're saying.
You popped kind of hard.
That's completely, I don't deny that at all. I don't actually remember it because I probably, that's probably happened a lot to me in the last couple years.
You couldn't pick out which instance it was. Yeah.
Yeah. Somebody's gone like, oh, so it's like, yeah, it's like, it's like good or something. And I go, no, no, no, no, you don't understand.
It's great.
Am I going to kill me?
Yeah, I'm going to kill you. It's really good. It's really good.
Yeah. So, yeah. So it's, it's a fantastic album. It's on YouTube.
There's a little bit of a cult around it. I think there's a little bit. People who know people, if you know, you know, is what I'm saying.
Yeah. With McGruff Smart Kids.
Kind of an underground kind of a college rock sort of vibe at this point.
Yeah. Yeah.
And it's, I think we've said it's like sort of an indie rock lo-fi masterpiece.
Like, you know, it's, it's very analog. It's very drum machine. It's got the cassette hiss, you know.
It's very, it's very cool to like it, I think.
I think so. I think it also makes you cool.
And I, yeah, I like every sound on it. I think the instrumentation is fantastic.
And that's maybe my biggest question heading into McGruff 2 is are we going to feel the same way being that like, of course, it's completely in my wheelhouse and probably your guys too, that something recorded in what, 86?
That that's going to like have the exact kinds of keyboard and drum machine and sax vibes that we like.
But is, is it going to work to head into the perilous 90s where sounds get a little cheesier and dicier?
Yeah, I hear what you're saying. And this was a concern going in.
And I do want to let the listener know in general that I'm unfortunate.
It's unfortunate to say that the songs we'll be listening today, I don't believe are as high quality as SmartKits.
Well, look, we're going to have a lot of fun today.
And I will say, do I have nearly 40 songs ready to go in iTunes?
Yes. Yes, I do.
Oh my God.
Okay, should we all take an extra bathroom break right now?
Do we load up on supplies?
It sounds like you are announcing a McGruff 3 in a roundabout fashion.
Well, I just, you know, we're not going to we're not going to gush over these songs like we did SmartKits, I don't think.
I could be wrong. Maybe McGruff 3 will have to happen because this episode goes too long.
But I'm just saying that I want the listeners to know ahead of time that I don't think there's a couple bright spots that really surprise you.
You go, well, that's cool. That's pretty cool.
That actually reminds me of SmartKits, but it's not going to be as good as SmartKits.
And again, I want to say we're going to have a lot of fun, a lot of laughs.
But this is more what you think of when you would think of a McGruff song.
Okay.
I mean, I think we're going to have a lot of fun with that children's song with limited effort, perhaps, in putting the song together.
But as long as, I mean, we're learning lessons, right?
I mean, that's that's a lot of it.
There are plenty of lessons to be learned.
And I will say that there's a lot more making McGruff into some sort of Jesus-like figure on these songs.
He's pulled up in a way that he does not.
McGruff, you know, you think of him as a musical artist.
SmartKits was when he was like sort of pretension free.
He was just sort of purely in it for the music and to get kids to stop doing drugs.
These songs, he doesn't sing a lot on these songs.
He lets kids, he's obviously got an ego at this point.
He lets kids sing about him and puts it on an album.
You know, he's kind of he's in the I am a god stage of his career.
The Kanye, the Yeezus, I think.
I was wondering. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And like the the is it like the hustle isn't there as much that the insecurity of the early era that feels very far away now.
The urgency is missing. Yeah.
These songs.
Well, I think it's important that you you calibrate us correctly here.
So, you know, we don't get our hopes up, but it's you do have to explore a musician,
a prolific musician with honesty.
And, you know, we're we're big Prince fans.
We talk about Prince a lot.
Where I think we're more we've been more excited to see the 80s vault opened up than the 90s.
Well, where I think we're honest about how we feel about the 90s Prince body of work.
But when you find the gems in there, they almost shine brighter because they're mixed in with a lot of rocks and coal.
What's the end of that metaphor?
Yeah, coal, I guess coal, because coal is kind of bad, even though it like I guess you I guess it's used to heat.
So there's some use to it.
But coal is the stock.
You don't put it you put it in a stocking is and that's supposed to be like you did bad all year.
Yeah. Take this coal.
That's bad. Yeah.
So but amidst all the coal, there will there could be some diamonds and pearls.
So maybe that's what I'm I'm curious if any of these will prove to be the late era masterpiece, a lot of diamonds and pearls.
What's McGruff's diamonds and pearls?
Right. And like you could say that McGruff's revolution, which of course, Bobby Z, Wendy and Lisa, his his revolution are I'm looking at a McGruff book now from the Burger King tape.
His revolution is there.
Members are Anne, Anthony, Joy and Miguel.
So that's print.
That's gross revolution, I think.
And we'll talk about that more when I get to because I have this book just for Book Four of McGruff Cares for You cassette.
So we'll get there at a certain point and talk more about the book when we get there.
Well, maybe we should.
You know, I don't want to delay the music too much, but we should say that there's been considerable effort put into attaining all of this music, which only Mike has been through.
Mike is now the supervisor of the McGruff estate, and he's kind of curating all the material for us.
The you know, we're kind of executive producers on the project and you the patrons are the listeners, the motivated McGruff fans.
So this is a surprise mostly to Jason and I.
Yes. And we had some Indiana Joneses, some Lara Croft, Tomb Raider-esque archaeologists helping with us.
Our friend Andrew Grissom gave us one of the cassettes with a book.
Yes.
And then I went, I double checked the date on this email.
This has been almost a year in the works this episode because.
Yes.
I, a gentleman named Alexander Hoffman wrote and had come across one of the cassettes in like a collectible store, antique store in one of my home stopping grounds in like South Jersey area.
And he sent it to us to the Forever Dog Address, along with a second cassette that he found.
And then to on top of that, a listener named Ian Rich sent us a bunch of digitized files, like very nicely organized digitized.
Digitizing? Oh my God.
Yes. With metadata, with like album art, like a properly named too.
So thanks to you all for your excavations.
Thank you heroes.
Yeah, our true heroes.
Thank you heroes for making McGruff 2 possible.
Yes, it really helps. It really helped out. So yes.
We appreciate it. However, don't copy music for the most part.
I mean, somebody bought the tapes at some point in time, but I don't want to look on Napster and Kazaa and see a bunch of McGruff on there.
Technically I could still sue you guys, but I won't.
Alexander and Ian and Andrew.
Alexander, Ian and Andrew, just pass a drunk test and then all will be copacetic.
Piss onto a strip and send it to me.
I'll sniff it.
That's a pregnancy test, not a drug test.
Piss on a stick.
I want to know if you're pregnant too.
I got a lot of questions.
If there's a red dot, you're pregnant. If there's a green leaf, you've been smoking marijuana.
Is it a baby or weed?
Anyway.
Oh man, McGruff, the greatest. Okay, so.
Let's okay. Let me organize myself here. There's a lot on the table, as I said.
So yes, McGruff released four Burger King cassette tapes called McGruff Cares for You.
Cassette one through four.
And we had played a couple and we'll get to there that we had played a couple from cassette three.
Okay, which is on YouTube.
That's the only one that was kind of available publicly before we got into this endeavor.
Right. So we played a little. We'll refresh when we get there.
And then so I'm just setting those four up.
And then I also found another very not documented album called McGruff and Scruff and the Crime Dogs,
which I don't know where that was released.
There's really not much information on it.
I haven't even seen a cover and maybe I did a bad job researching it.
But do we know that the time even like where it falls into this discography?
I think it's in 94 ish because so basically I found this album
because I have been hunting for the person who wrote Smart Kids.
And we do have a name at this point, but I have not had any contact, but I thought I found the writer of it.
And I messaged him over and over again and never responded.
And finally, I think maybe on LinkedIn, I had sent an email and he responded.
He said, Oh, I didn't write Smart Kids. I wrote a different McGruff album.
And at first I was saying, Oh, it must be the Burger King ones.
No, the answer was no. He wrote another one called McGruff and Scruff and the Crime Dogs.
And I will say that one musically, I think is better than the four Burger King tapes.
And again, we'll get to there. So I'm just trying to tease exactly everything we've got going on here.
So we'll get to we'll get to that. I think it's after the McGruff Burger King tapes.
So also, what is the cut off where we have to do part three?
Is it if this goes beyond two and a half hours?
It's a good question. Yeah. If we go over two and a half hours and we have like 30 percent left,
I think we'll find a natural stopping place maybe before and go ahead.
But I don't know. I think we can. You might get tired of some of this quickly, so I will see.
OK, yeah, I have three and a half hours left on this SD card because I've been negligent of clearing off source files.
So, yeah, but I can always you know, I can always clear.
I can always clear, you know. Well, I'm running out of space on my hard drive because I have found 12 more McGruff albums that you guys don't even know about.
What? Wow. This man was prolific.
We've all been very prolific on our LinkedIn burners that we made for this show.
You don't want to make it on LinkedIn.
He got I think I signed up for LinkedIn to email McGruff has most of his best stuff still in his vault.
Yeah, I got three Smart Kids era albums in the vault.
No one's heard them and I have to wait for me to die for McGruff to die.
Scruff is going to have to decide.
I've instructed him not to let anyone hear any of it.
But if he betrays me for a buck, I don't have a will.
So good luck sorting out the estate.
Sorry.
Okay.
So all right, Burger King McGruff cares for you.
So this is the start of the whole what do you call it?
Not a trilogy, a quadru. What is that word?
Cycle?
Quadro. No, no, it's quadriology or something.
Okay.
There's it's a word that's like not trilogy but four.
Well, it's all McGruff's quadrophenia.
It's yes. Okay. Well, that's good. That's good.
So this starts out with like the McGruff worship and it's called a whistle for McGruff.
And it starts out right away.
McGruff, McGruff, McGruff.
He's a crime dog.
He's our guide.
And he's always on our side.
Yeah!
McGruff's a kind of friend who cares for you.
He understands the things that kids go through.
He'll help you any place you go, go, go.
He'll show you what you need to know, know, know McGruff.
He comes to see us in our schools.
He speaks to us as prom dog rules.
He shows us how to help our friends and how to be good citizens.
He shows us how to clean our block and how to always lock the lock.
He taught us how to use the phone when we are in the house alone.
McGruff!
The phone.
I feel a little condescended too with this one.
I agree. Yeah.
It's very basic, you know.
Yeah.
He's tough on crime.
He warns us of dangers.
I like this part.
He tries very hard to keep us on guard.
A good bridge, yes.
He helps us a lot.
He's McGruff!
When things get tough, you need McGruff.
He's there for you all of the time.
You never know when you've got a problem.
So this should set your expectations where they're at.
This is sort of what we're at.
On occasion you get a little interesting musical breaks.
But in general, you're going to have a bunch of not great kids singers.
Which is funny.
He's tough on crime.
He also looks sharp.
He looks so good in a trench coat.
Yeah, wouldn't McGruff be like, a little too much kids.
You don't need to butter me up this much.
It's not really about me.
It's about stopping crime, I guess.
Never been comfortable with compliments.
Not me, us.
That's my catchphrase.
He's from a generation that doesn't want to open up.
This would be embarrassing to him, I would think.
You would think, but he allowed it on his album with his name.
I guess it's kind of like when a TV show says previously on.
It's like, well, sometimes people come in later on.
Right.
So that is, by the way, that is the tip of the ass kissing iceberg.
What?
You ain't seen nothing yet until we get to a song later on this album called
Wish.
That is a dreamlike ballad.
Dreams of only McGruff being in your life.
I'm excited for Wish.
There's a lot of laziness on this album.
This next song is called Phone Smart.
McGruff sings on this, which I like, but this is some of the laziest
melody I've ever heard.
Like just.
Hi, it's me, McGruff.
I got a question for you.
Who's your best friend when you're at home alone?
McGruff!
Your best friend when you're at home alone.
I'll always be your friend and I'll always tell you the right things to do.
But your best friend when you're at home alone is you.
So he does kind of do it there, but he still takes the compliment.
But you gotta be phone smart.
I thought he was going to say a lot.
When you're home on your own, you're never alone.
What is this melody?
When you got the phone, the telephone.
It feels like he's making it up on the spot.
Phone and telephone.
Here's how to be phone smart.
Now he doesn't get out of the song.
Have your parents make up a list of all emergency numbers for you.
And people to start.
I'm fast forwarding here.
To get phone smart.
Phone smart.
This isn't even good enough to be a commercial jingle.
This is nothing.
This is a demo. He's screwing around.
This song is not fleshed out at all.
If you've got a phone.
And your phone is smart.
The biggest gaps in the melody ever.
Just take a little while.
And learn to use the buttons.
Or dial.
At least that's a rhyme.
Than anybody.
That you need.
You can reach with lightning speed.
If your phone is smart.
That's right.
I mean, phone smart.
Come on. This is track two on the album.
Let's get a little energy here.
McGruff. Gee whiz.
The voice is weird to me also.
It's very weird.
It's kind of higher.
Our impression doesn't work as much.
It's got to be a little more.
I'm getting.
You veer into the Yoda zone.
If you aren't careful.
But this seems pretty good.
There is something on tape too.
Where he sounds hammered.
But that's a problem with this song.
He went right from the viper room.
To the recording.
He never went home that night. Didn't sleep.
Just got in the car from the viper room.
I do as I say. Not as I do.
He was drunk on the phone song.
He was not being phone smart.
Right before recording the liquor song.
He's not practicing what he preaches.
Not at all.
And again, like track two.
There should be a better melody on phone smart.
This is like.
The McGruff of smart kids would not allow phone smart.
That bullshit phone smart melody.
To happen.
So yeah.
So it's a bad start to tape one.
Unfortunately.
An artist metaphor here.
Where you're so anticipated.
From that first one.
The next one is going to be a masterpiece.
Maybe Lauren Hill comes to mind.
Because she's sort of like.
That was a pretty perfect first album.
And then it was a lot of.
I don't even remember what she did second.
Like a weird unplugged.
Or like a badly drawn boy.
With a really good first album.
And a very sloppy career following that.
Well that's a name I haven't heard in a long long time.
It's as current as I get.
2001 era.
Casey or Dewey music.
I think that's.
I think that is absolutely correct.
Analogy.
So yeah. So anyway. I mean it does get better.
So he does a little right and wrong.
There's this thing called right and wrong song that comes up next.
And.
It's so tubby. He explains like a game.
Everyone ready for our sing along?
Ready.
And.
We're all going to sing the right and wrong song.
So clap your hands and sing along.
Loud and strong.
You tell me which one's right.
And which one's wrong.
Here's how. Clap your hands once for right.
Like this.
And twice for wrong.
Kind of a confusing game.
That's right. You got it.
In 1917.
Columbus sailed the ocean green.
1917?
That's wrong.
In 1492.
Columbus sailed the ocean blue.
See.
That's right. You clap once.
It's a confusing game.
Yeah. It's a confusing game.
I will give him credit because you could rap like Paul Revere over this.
I think.
In 1907.
That's right. You got it.
You have to know the story.
You know so well.
But two bad brothers.
I can't screw with the line up.
There is none higher.
In 1492.
So I appreciate that he's kind of getting into rap there.
But that's a bad.
That's nothing. That's also nothing.
That song is nothing. Now we get to track four.
And we have a skit.
Oh. Also not something I like on my albums.
I agree.
Great albums are ruined by inessential skits.
Yeah. So he has a skit.
Track four. Like we're already off to a snoozy start.
And it's track four with a skit.
The only reason I'm going to play this is because it's about a little girl not answering the door because a man who's pretending to be a delivery man is trying to get in and steal her.
Steal her.
I will play it.
Steal her. Not rob the house.
Sort of the implication is he's going to kidnap her I think.
But the only reason I'm playing this is because I'm pretty sure the guy who does McGruff's voice is doing the guy at the door.
And I find the fact.
I think. You tell me.
So we'll set the plan here.
Okay Melissa.
Let me fast forward here a little bit.
Package for Peterson.
Thank you. Just leave it there.
No you have to sign for it.
You have to open the door.
The door's locked.
Just leave the package.
You have to open the door.
It sounds like Joe Biden.
Come on now or you'll get in trouble. Hurry up.
I'm going to get more McGruffish.
She phoned next door. Listen.
Hello.
Mrs. Garcia.
Mrs. Kim. There's a man who wants me to open the door.
He wants me to sign something.
Open up.
Don't open it.
I'll be over right away.
I'll try to get his car license number.
Kim.
Dial 0 for operator.
And ask her to call.
Mrs. Garcia's. You're in there kid.
I'm sure this package is important.
Is it not?
Operator.
I'm home alone and a delivery man.
Says I have to open the door.
So basically Mrs. Garcia calls 911 and they find out that yes indeed that man was a criminal.
Oh my god.
This is still hold over from like the satanic panic error.
Like I feel like we got the tail end of it.
You know when we were growing up.
Uh huh.
So yeah.
Luckily Mrs. Garcia was there.
I'm fascinated. It's like hearing Gilbert Godfrey's real voice.
If you ever heard that it's very strange.
Because Gilbert Godfrey does not sound like you thought he sounded forever.
He actually is a human man's voice.
I want to show my range.
I'm tired of being typecast as a hero dog.
So.
Yeah the guy finally got to flex his acting muscles a little bit there.
And maybe he appears other places on this.
I don't think he's one of the children.
I don't think he's that good.
Oh yes.
It would be funny.
But McGruff.
Mommy and daddy.
My pinky and my daddy.
Mommy and daddy said it's fine if it's a friend of theirs to get in the van.
Mommy and daddy liars.
No.
Yeah.
So maybe he's a prize.
I will say Mrs. Garcia I wasn't.
Mrs. Garcia might have been a white lady.
I'm not sure.
You want to listen to that.
I could be totally wrong and I apologize if that's not right.
Anyway.
So the next song I'm skipping it's called it's only a dime.
And it's about how if you take a dime from your mother.
You're going to eventually rob like banks.
That's not what he says because that would be funny.
You're in a better and I would play it if that was the case.
But that's the message of like it starts with one and then you then you're off and you're a criminal.
You take a dime from your mother like it's all like you're going to do.
Who knows what you'll do.
It's a it's a gateway crime is what he's saying.
I think there's a chain shortage in this country.
Now is not the time to steal dimes.
Stealing dimes the ultimate crime.
Dimes are important.
So here we go.
We're getting here we are now at Wish and Wish is the most ambitious song on this cassette.
And I'll just I've already kind of set it up.
This is the song where they just kiss McGruff's ass so thoroughly.
And here we go.
It's also like a romantic ballad.
It also sounds like.
Sounds like.
I want to hire him pony up kids.
It's weird.
The song.
We're in love with him.
The girls too.
Share my seat.
Yeah.
Plenty of room here McGruff.
Key change.
I wish McGruff would always be my bride.
I wish he was our house when he could.
I wish McGruff lived in our neighborhood.
I'm part of every neighborhood that takes a bite out of crime.
That's my job.
That's what I do.
I kind of like this one.
And if you listen to everything I tell you.
Learn how to take care of yourself.
Well you know.
That's like having me right there.
I'll be there for you.
This is good too.
Because I care for you.
We'll be there for you.
Alright that's basically that's the gist of it.
I mean it's surprising that he goes I'm marrying your mom kids.
I'm part of your family now.
You got your wish.
It's yeah why are two songs that have to like mythologize this dog?
Like it's this guy's he's got a big head.
McGruff.
Maybe it's McGruff's obviously McGruff's creator at this point.
Started being like you know McGruff is great.
He like maybe the creator and the writer is like.
McGruff is worthy of this Jesus level.
Yeah it is very Jesus level.
Like that I'm in every neighborhood.
I'm all around even if you don't see me.
I can always hear you.
And if a priest takes a piece of bread or a wafer.
And says McGruff be with you then and then you eat it.
You're eating McGruff.
Two sets of footprints and one set of footprints.
One set of paw prints on the sand.
If Dylan can go gospel why can't I?
No.
I'm God.
McGruff is Jesus.
I don't know what the Holy Spirit is.
The Holy Spirit is my music.
I wish there was a third.
There was a BJ or Griff in the McGruff verse.
Maybe Griff.
Or is not.
Yeah.
Griff was initially supposed to be part of the McGruff family.
Like it was painted like a dog.
Like the suit was made for McGruff.
And McGruff rejected him.
Put him up for adoption.
Sell him to those Barney losers.
They won't know any better.
He could still play sax on some of the songs.
I'll hire him.
Dude's got chops but I don't want him hanging around all the time.
I don't want to have to feed him and clothe him.
I'll hire him but not raise him.
Okay.
All right.
So wish.
Are we that?
We are six songs in.
Yeah.
You know what this is reminding me of?
The swing from Smart Kids to this.
And it's not a perfect metaphor.
And I'm not a Ramones expert.
But do you guys know End of the Century?
The Ramones album, it was like their fifth album.
But they had Phil Spector produce it.
Oh, right.
I know this.
And it.
He pulled a gun on them.
Yeah.
He pulled a gun a number of times.
He does that a lot though.
But that album has some skits.
Like some radio skits.
It's only 34 minutes long.
I like the album, but it is very much like a pretty sharp change from like early Ramones
sound.
Is there a lot of like, we love you, Joey Ramone.
We love you, Mark Ramone.
I mean, it sounds like when you like the Ramones, like got a bunch of Ronettes records and like
tried to marry the sounds.
Well, you can't be mad at that.
Yeah.
I know it's all right.
But I don't.
I pull the difference with me is I pull a gun on my producers.
I'm the boss of you, Phil.
Phil.
Phil was scared of me.
You run off to that castle of yours.
Stay there.
All right.
The opposite of the Walla sound, really.
This this music.
It's very thin, in fact, and it makes you appreciate the production of Smart Kids.
Yeah.
It's like a paper, a thin piece of paper of sound.
Easily crash throughable.
If you lean on it, it breaks open.
Yeah.
All right.
This next song.
Now, this this next song was a surprise to me.
It's called Stay Clean.
And it's like somebody woke up.
It's like the album wakes up a little bit here.
Like pretty like, oh, OK.
What is this?
It's I feel for you.
You can make your daydreams come true.
And do whatever you want to do.
First kid talent, I feel.
Just.
Don't do drugs.
You can live your life as you please.
Like a real good groove.
Yeah.
Good things will come your way like a breeze.
If you just stay clean.
No drugs.
Not you.
You can climb a hill and be king.
Climb a hill and be king.
You can have it all.
Everything.
If you just stay clean.
Stay the way you are.
You can be what you want to be.
Pretty good.
Yeah.
That's a pretty good groove that could have like you could you could see a version of that
being on Smart Kids.
Mm hmm.
Yeah.
The first one that's of the caliber.
It also it is all very principles that there's so many protege's.
He's really like given the spotlight to the protege's and the some of those as with Prince
some of them are good, some of them are bad.
I think that last girl was a good protege.
Right.
She was who?
Yeah.
Who is the who's most successful Prince protege is Sheila E technically a protege.
You'd have to call I guess Sheila.
Yeah.
That's the Sheila.
The most not the Carmen Electra who's fine and other mediums.
But the Prince album is not the best.
A cultural icon certainly.
But the album maybe wasn't so successful.
I always remember his lake, one of his late period protege's Bria Valente.
As much as he could pass it over to ladies and gentlemen, Bria Valente.
Bria Valente.
Which is just fun to hear.
It's fun to hear him say that name.
That's a good name.
I'm sure she's very talented.
But yeah, that he bundled that see he bundled three CDs together.
I remember at Target.
At Target.
Two of his CDs and then her solo album.
Yeah.
At the time.
Well, that's what this is.
This is a bundle.
This is a corporate tie in.
Right.
Yes.
Okay.
This song.
This song is funny.
And maybe I don't even want to set it up.
Just listen to what he's saying and then where the music goes.
Hi, boys and girls.
It's your old friend McGruff, the crime dog.
Let's talk about crimes committed by somebody with a mask.
Yeah.
The crime is called arson.
He's talking about arson.
Arson is when a person sets a fire to a building.
It's pretty serious, right?
Now, if you ever see anyone try that, tell a grownup right away.
He's right.
The first sign of arson or any other fire is usually smoke.
Right.
Now, if you're home alone and you smell smoke, remember this.
Smoke from a fire can be just as dangerous as the fire itself.
Smoke can creep up on you and make you unconscious.
Smoke is sneaky.
Yes.
Don't take chances with it.
He's right.
One, two, three, four.
If you smell smoke, even just a little whiff, get out.
What?
Get out.
Don't take another sniff, get out.
What is this funny joke?
I like this, John.
Get out and tell a grownup get out.
It's a no-smoke jitterbug.
Get close to the floor, get out.
Get out, get right out the door, get out.
Out, out, out.
And shout about it, get out.
Out, out.
Tell the neighbors all about it, get out.
Out, out, out.
And shout about it, get out.
Out, out.
Tell the neighbors all about it.
And if there's no fire, you can still feel cool.
Think of all the fire drills they have at school.
Even when they don't smell smoke.
Got the message?
OK.
Let's play the I smell smoke.
I'm going to ask you some questions.
Number one, when you smell smoke, should you try to find it?
Find it?
Never mind it.
Get out fast.
How does this game work?
Number two.
It's unclear.
Clap four times if you smell smoke.
Leave it alone.
Get out fast.
There was a long pause before the questions because he had to take a plug of cutting.
How do you smell smoke?
Yeah, so I just like arson is a very important crime.
Now let's play like a like blues brother song and celebrate arson.
Wap babaloo ba no smoke for you.
I feel like I got so many warnings in school, like all of the drug stuff and and inhalants.
And I feel like we watch at least two after school movies in school about like watch out for arson or like your friend might be an arsonist.
And I looking back, I'm like, is that why I was such a nervous child?
Because I was constantly being warned about the danger of the world of like serial killers calling to see like you have to foil a serial killer with my mom can't come to the phone right now, but she's here.
Like I that was just a thing in the 90s.
Yeah, it was.
We all got fed a lot of this stuff.
I mean, I will say it's, you know, things happen here and there.
I remember, but it did feel like you were going to be consistently fighting off abductors.
Yes, like that was going to be a consistent part of our lives growing up, like constantly lying to adults of like, no, my mom is she's here.
I can't come to the door right now.
But your friends are all turncoats and addicts who are going to get you hooked on something.
Yeah, yeah, that's true.
Don't trust friends.
Friends are bad.
I don't ever have one.
Imagine being my friend instead of meeting someone.
I'm here.
I woke up here.
I'm very dear mom.
Yeah, so I'm McGruff certainly was part of that.
I mean, you got to warn kids about a lot of things, but maybe it doesn't have to be unrelenting.
Yeah, yeah.
Point, Jason.
Yes, I am.
I did meet an arsonist growing up and I'll never forget it.
I do have a story about meeting an arsonist and I'll see if I can say this quickly that there was like a family gathering and there is an older cousin in the family who would often have bring boyfriends to things where you sort of even as a 12 year old or whatever it was like.
That's a shady boyfriend, wasn't it?
And she brought this guy who was like kind of little and squirrely and intense and like a little too fit and kind of manic.
Right.
And like, hey, good to meet you guys seem like such nice folks and hey, little Scott.
Hey, what do you what do you run your bike a lot?
Okay.
And just kind of a weird energy from the guy.
And then hours into this family barbecue, this guy stops everything cold and says like, you know, you guys have been so nice and accepting to me that I feel like I just want to be honest with you and open up to you guys.
You seem like good folks.
I've had some problems with arson in my life and I have it has happened several times.
I've burnt down several buildings and it has it has been tough for me to progress and to to move forward.
But I just want you know, because I, you know, I'm enjoying being here so much.
I just want you guys to know that because I feel free to tell you who I am and what I'm struggling and trying to process.
And then I remember that this this family member's father, who was just dead silence until the father goes, all right, and then just leaves the house like for a while.
And then we never saw this guy ever again.
Wow.
Oh, my God.
My childhood was like very nice, but very dull.
A lot of the time just like pleasant.
Well, that was a nice gathering.
So the time where like a little like a little like coked out squirrely arsonist admitted that he's an arsonist.
Oh, my gosh.
Wow.
Yeah, that was that was a fun story for my childhood.
And I think as McGruff would say, it's never that easy.
Most most arsonists are not going to announce themselves to you.
They're just going to do the arson.
Right.
I appreciate his honesty.
Yeah.
You know, he's struggling with it, I guess.
But if I heard that this same guy started like three of the fires that have been ravaging our part of the state, I couldn't be that surprised either.
That's a good point.
There's a fire truck outside my house right now.
It's probably him.
If you heard if you had heard this tape before that incident, would you have tackled this guy and placed him under citizen's arrest?
Maybe a dog told me that you're bad news.
Get out.
I'm taking you to the police.
What about it? Get out.
You're like singing the song like while crying, holding this guy down.
If you meet an arsonist at a barbecue, there's one thing that you can do.
Get out and tackle him.
Bind his ankles.
Get out.
Grab an extension cord from the garage and tie him to a tree.
If you see a stranger lighting a cigarette and then rubber banding six matches around it to make a slow burning fire starter, tell it out.
That was one of the movies.
They told us how to commit arson.
Arson did it the same way every time and it always worked.
And I was like sitting there watching this.
Like, why are you telling us?
Why are you telling us this trick?
McGruff.
I'm telling you every step of what you see somebody pulling out a spoon and then starting to boil the spoon.
And I don't know the steps enough of free basing drugs.
So I'll stop there.
I'm a good boy.
McGruff.
Right.
It's like Breaking Bad.
Breaking Bad.
They had to make sure that the meth steps were out of order so people wouldn't learn how to make meth.
Oh, is that right?
Like you couldn't watch it and then purposely.
Well, you probably could figure it out and look Google it.
But apparently they did steps out of order for making meth in the prep scenes so people wouldn't know exactly how to do it.
Oh, huh.
Technical consultant McGruff.
Right.
I know how to make it.
And I know how to show it so it isn't easily copied.
I make the purest meth there is.
Watch me do a batch.
But then don't do what I do.
The purest crystal.
All right. How many how many minutes are we into this?
I'm not sure.
47.
Okay.
All right.
That's not crazy.
You could have said like an hour forty five and I've been like, yep, makes sense.
I just think you have a promise of McGruff three is I mean, but God knows if we make it through, then let's make it through.
Well, we could.
I mean, we could stop.
We could stop at the end of this next one.
Oh, no, that's not.
I don't think that's enough.
I think we got the next album.
The next cassette.
Oh, not the next.
No, no, no.
Okay.
I mean, I don't think McGruff three is out of the question, even if we get through all the songs today.
Somehow.
Sure.
Hmm.
Well, another yearly series, then we just keep.
Yeah.
It should be.
Is there a crime prevention day that we should be doing this on?
National no arts and day.
It's very.
Yeah.
You bring up a good point.
Okay.
So this is cassette two.
We're at cassette two of McGruff cares for you.
The Burger King series.
Now, I will say tape two is a little bit experimental.
Oh, there's a different vibe on it.
Like McCartney to it's a lot like McCartney to.
I agree.
This is McGruff to the official album of Gruff to where we were a week away from McCartney three as we're recording this.
Oh, so excited.
I wonder how does it compare to McGruff three?
Well, McGruff three has the alphabet alphabet or song on it.
Oh, and Zards, right?
And Zard.
Yeah.
Yes.
Which we didn't know what they were, but somebody pointed out that that's just a slang for hazards, which I believe is correct.
Oh, sure.
Yeah.
It's gonna be a good album.
I'm covering Zards.
I'm doing a couple McGruff tracks.
Yeah, they recorded in the eighties, like after he was done with Elvis Costello.
He'll collaborate.
Yeah.
This song is called You're a Winner, which is a nice sentiment.
And you'll hear what I'm saying.
It's a little more.
Life is full of choices, small ones and big ones.
It's a spoken word.
Small ones like deciding which pair of socks to wear today.
Big ones like what you want to do when you grow up.
You can be just about anything you want.
That's very Prince.
Yeah, yeah, actually.
It's to put your mind to it and stay in school.
You're a winner, not a quitter.
You'll be all right, cause you have what it takes.
Stay in school.
Don't put on the break.
Some kids know what they want to be.
Maybe a police officer or a teacher.
But a lot of folks don't decide until later.
Stay in school and you'll have more job choices.
Do your best to keep your options open.
It takes education, not just wishing and hoping.
The choices you make, you choose them.
Keep your options open kids.
Are going to be with you all along your way.
Some kids decide to quit school.
When they get older and have to earn a living, they learn a tough lesson.
Dropouts don't get the good jobs.
And rather than work at a job they hate for little money,
some of these kids turn to crime or drugs and lose everything.
They may even end up in prison and that's no place for a winner like you.
That's true. There are no winners in prison.
You're a winner, not a quitter.
You'll be alright cause you have what it takes.
Stay in school.
Don't put on the break.
There's no such thing as a born loser.
But everyone is a born chooser.
And winners...
I get the crazy melody here.
Like it feels like he's improvising this over this track.
It doesn't feel like a lot of time was put into that.
There's a winner to be found in you.
Like his singing is off, you know.
So there's a little bit of that.
The first part is a little experimental and I like that.
There's a little more of that on this album.
Confusing message.
Boy, I didn't know what that song was about by the end.
Again, yeah, not focused like Smart Kids.
You know exactly what each song on Smart Kids is about.
This one is like all over the place.
He's talking about like college and options.
Shale.
You're not inherently...
You're not a loser.
That's not inherent, but you are inherently a winner.
And you can lose that if you don't go to...
There's too much going on here.
I appreciate the ambition, but stick to one or two things.
Core messages.
The game.
The game of the...
The game of the song.
The drug song.
Yeah.
The Be Smart song.
Okay.
So Check It Out is the song that I was referencing earlier when I said it
sounds like he recorded this hammered.
That one wasn't it?
Oh man.
That one was not it.
You ain't heard nothing yet.
A little more lively.
Like, you know, it felt like a little lively, you know.
Yes, I agree.
I joined Hill's song and my pastor Carl Lentz has inspired me and reinvigorated me.
I think this album has got better stuff on it.
It's got some more interesting stuff on it.
All right.
I'll start out with Check It Out.
It doesn't get drunkish till a little bit later in the song.
By the way, it starts out like back in the USSR.
It's an airplane engine warming up.
Before pilots take off a plane, they go over a checklist to make sure everything is right.
Magnetos.
Check.
Altimeter.
Cylinder head temperature.
Check.
Flaps down.
Pilots go through a whole checklist before they take off.
Okay.
Well, you're a pilot too when you take off and go someplace.
So before you take off from your house, go over your checklist just like a pilot.
So the premise of this song is that you're a pilot when you leave the house.
And you need to be prepared in the same way a pilot is with all your stuff, which I guess just means bring your wallet and keys.
Yeah.
Did this inspire the Adam Sandler song from that last special keys while at phone?
Perper house.
Or you think about checking for your keys while at phone.
It's very possible.
This is from a gruff.
Yeah, you stole it from a gruff.
Yeah.
Okay.
Let's do it.
Let's go through it.
Have you memorized your whole address in case you ever get in a mess?
ral.
The whole address of the city and state.
Did you practice that and get it straight?
Check.
Do you know your phone number, area code and all?
Whatever you are, you can just make a call.
Check.
Telephones, you know, come into style.
It gets worse too.
Learn how to use a touchstone and a diamond.
Telephones come into style.
You may need some change.
So have you got a quarter to put in the payphone slot?
Check.
Two pilots are always better than one.
Are you taking a friend along on your run?
Check.
Do your parents know where you're going to be?
And did you remember to take your keys?
Check.
I want to tell you one thing more.
You're going out.
Did you lock the door?
Lock the door.
Check.
Am I doing it right?
Lock the door.
Barney gumbling it, you know?
Yeah.
He's hammered.
He's drunk.
McGruff, McGruff, you're drunk.
McGruff, you're drunk.
I'm fine.
Fuck off.
Remember the style of the house you live in?
Mid-century or Gothic?
Rancher colonial split level by level.
What kind of roof?
I do remember that was a big change when we had to start using our, for our younger listeners,
when you had to start dialing the area code before your seven digit phone number.
And then a change when phone calls stopped being 25 cents and started being 35 cents at a payphone.
What a pain in the ass that was.
I vaguely remember that.
They're stealing a dime from you.
They're stealing the dime from us.
Like your mom.
And that was the little cuts we used to have to deal with.
I remember the holidays where like, you know, the president, the outgoing president, it's like, well, he's mad at Iran's Revolutionary Guard.
And a month later, he's made of toilets who have to flush too many times.
The world has changed since 1994.
If he had focused on the toilets, I think he would have won reelection.
Yeah.
There's always a winning message.
They want us to get different light bulbs.
He should have felt he needed to focus on being mad at toilets, light bulbs and Lady Gaga.
Lady Gaga too late.
And then John Bon Jovi, he just that was so intriguing, but he should have been talking about Bon Jovi at every rally.
Yeah, I agree.
And then McGruff, he was not very nice.
We love our law enforcement, but McGruff was not nice to me.
He's got a Messiah complex.
He's got these children, these little kids.
They walk around, they think he's God.
I did vote for him in 2016, though.
I thought a businessman shake things up.
He ran his business as well.
I figured he'd do it.
He'd do the same thing for the government.
I voted down ballot Republican every other race.
But when I was with him until I was with him until covid.
I mean, everything else was great.
The economy, fantastic.
McGruff stocks were soaring.
COVID though, I know I get it.
I would have put on a whole covid album.
Warning people what to do.
It's time I present Trump because if I had lead time, I could have put out my covid album and none of this would have happened.
If I had distributed emergency copies of McGruff says, don't get covid.
Let's talk about washing hands.
Got to start with six feet away.
Let's talk about indoor gatherings.
But I can't go in the studio to record that and I can't set it up at home because I don't know computers.
I'm not a Pro Tools guy.
I never made the leap.
I need the studio, man.
I need an engineer.
My nephew is good with that, but he will not come over.
Says we're supposed to stay at home.
Get out.
Get the covid germs out.
If you see a covid germ, tell it to go home.
The scram, scram covid.
You're not wanted here.
But covid germs says he's supposed to be inside.
He's got a package for you.
Tell him I've got your number.
You're a germ.
Hey, it's me, covid germs.
I'm outside.
I just want to say I'm sorry for my early April release.
Herd immunity is the way to go.
We didn't know much back then.
Sweden, Sweden was right for a while.
Look, Fauci changed his mind about the mask.
So we're growth can't change his mind about stuff.
Oh, God.
That's a good idea.
The whole yes, the entire.
Well, maybe we'll see.
And then just like the dark like now protests shouldn't do those either.
I don't make me mad seeing those on TV.
Oh, yeah. No, he doesn't like the protests.
They're against his friends.
I haven't.
And I won't watch the NFL either.
I said it.
Oh, it's Sarah.
The wall guys out NFL's out.
He was friends with Reagan, folks.
Yeah, come on.
We know where he stands.
The first half of the album is about wash your hands.
And the second half of the album is about don't take a knee.
And then the closers just Nixon shouldn't normalize shouldn't have normalized relations with China.
Still bad about it.
It all goes back to tricky.
The message out of there is very thick.
Oh, God.
What are we 90 minutes?
Yeah, one hour.
Let's go back to the real the real deal, man.
I've lost my place.
OK, this song is called Respect is a two way street.
The Lincoln Project song experimental.
Listen to this beat.
Bring it back to Coram.
Respect is a two way street.
Show respect to everyone you meet.
I've been around and found this to be true.
Give respect and it'll be good right back to you.
Pretty good.
That's a good little keyboard riff synth riff.
Consideration is the key.
It costs you nothing to give others courtesy.
Put yourself in their shoes.
Life is better when respect is what you choose.
Respect is a two way street.
Show respect to everyone you meet.
I've been around and found this to be true.
What kind of world.
Hi, it's me, McGruff.
It's OK.
Your tape recorder is not broken.
That's the sound of something going wrong.
Wrong.
Now, McGruff here.
That's what happened.
That was the most Robert Evans delivery I've ever heard.
Wrong.
All right.
It was also kind of bug.
That's what happened.
Oh yeah, yeah.
There is nothing wrong with your stereo cassette.
It happens to people who get hooked on drugs.
And drugs are a real hook, like a fish hook.
Once most people get hooked, they can't get free again.
Just like a fish.
Some kids you know, even some kids you like, may offer drugs to you.
They may even give them to you free.
Why should they give them to you free?
Well, two reasons.
One, misery loves company.
They're hooked and they want you to be hooked too.
The other reason is this.
Once you're hooked, they can sell you drugs.
They know that.
They seem just like the other kids you know, but they're pushers.
When someone offers you drugs, think of a big sharp hook.
Drugs are a hook as sharp as it can be.
Drugs are a hook that never lets you free.
Drugs are a hook, you know what hooks can do.
Drugs are a hook, they're not for kids like you.
Drugs are a hook, and any kid who's smart says I'll pass up the hook.
Cause I don't wanna start.
That's right, you're right.
That's right, drugs are a hook.
Okay kids, let's play the song.
The whole little game.
What's a little tiny river?
That's a brook.
Not a hook.
Who makes food in pots and pans?
That's a crook.
Not a hook.
Alright, this is off game.
Who's the guy police arrest?
That's a crook.
Not a hook.
What's something that you read?
That's a book.
Not a hook.
What catches fish and catches kids?
That's a hook.
Look out!
Drugs are a hook, as sharp as it can be.
Drugs are a hook, that never lets you free.
Drugs are a hook, you know what hooks can do.
Drugs are a hook, they're not for kids like you.
Alright, that's a hook.
Drugs are a hook.
With another confusing game.
Who wrote Citizen Kane?
That's a mink.
Not a hook.
That's right.
Where you get your money from.
That's a thing.
My mom's wallet, dime at a time.
No, you go to jail now.
No!
Don't hit me!
For crux in charge, you want to end up like Specter?
Then fall in line.
This is why California's three strike law needs to go nationwide.
I'm running for DA of Los Angeles.
Just had those elections, but I don't care.
I'm running, I'm doing my own election now.
I'm going after this reformer.
Stop the steal.
Stop the vote.
I'm throwing myself in there.
What's Joe Biden?
That's a crook.
That's right.
Well, he heisted an election.
Hunter's laptop is a thing to look at.
Tony Bobolinski is a good man.
Everything Rudy does is perfect.
It's off game.
We said he doesn't like Trump.
Alright, I'm exhausted.
He doesn't like it.
He didn't vote for him, but he believes in the fraud.
Yeah, he believes in the fraud.
That's how it is.
No, just because I didn't vote for him doesn't mean millions of upstanding Americans.
They did.
Reagan won with 48 states.
So did Donald.
Drugs are a hook.
All drugs.
Imagine all the types of drugs you can think of.
Put them all in a pile and watch them all turn into one giant hook.
But then the hook is going to get you and multiple people.
It's not different hooks for different friends.
It's again, the message is confusing.
If this were on Smart Kids, the message would be very clear.
But it's not.
There's some tidiness to that.
Those are really polished tweets.
There's not a word wasted.
Like a good sketch, you know what it's about from the first two lines.
And that's what every song on Smart Kids does.
And I understand you want to get crazier and more experimental.
And that's what he's doing.
Again, this is his sign of the times.
It's a big sprawling effort.
Right.
Many, many songs.
But maybe it would have been smarter in a way to tighten.
I don't know.
But yes, sometimes.
Yeah, there are double albums that should have, could have been killer single albums.
Yeah. Yes.
And this might be this is four albums that maybe could have been one.
Okay.
I would take I do think there's a strong album in here.
Which I would, with all my problems, I would put Drugs Are A Hook on the main album.
I would put Wishes or Wish.
Wishes.
There was one.
Or Wish. I'm sorry. Yeah, it was Wish.
I mean, all the ones where he sounds drunk, I would put on the main album.
Right, of course.
And the least, the less McGruff there is, it's not making the tight, the Scott cut down.
It's got to have more McGruff.
That's obviously, he's the star.
Yeah.
Not the protegees.
This song is called Map and a Plan.
Ken, he's like obsessed with like planning before you leave the house.
That's one of the top issues.
This again, second song about it.
Let's talk about you taking a trip on your own.
It's a trip.
Away from home. Maybe even outside the neighborhood.
How do you do it?
With a plan and a map.
A plan is an idea of where you're going to go.
And a map is how you're going to get there.
You could draw a map yourself.
Or just draw it in your head.
A plan and a map.
That's the way to go.
How to explore the Florida.
How to explore the Florida trap.
With a plan.
This is on the cut down.
This is on the director's cut.
How is the motor landing done by man?
With a map.
And a plan.
How does a bear find a place for a nap?
With a plan.
And a map.
How does a bear find a place to nap?
With a map and a plan?
Does a bear have a plan?
Don't you think it's instinct?
Sorry, I mean smart bears like the ones I know.
Like Smokey.
Just because McGruff is a hyper intelligent anthropomorphic animal doesn't mean most bears are.
Most bears I think are doing their things on instinct.
All animals are born choosers.
And some choose to talk and be smart.
And others choose to be owned by humans.
And it's their choice.
McGruff, that's problematic.
I'm not sure I'm going to be able to do that.
I'm not sure I'm going to be able to do that Historically.
McGruff, that's problematic.
Shut up!
McGruff, you're drunk!
I don't care!
All dogs could be cops if they just were motivated and didn't quit like me.
Alright, that's the gist of a map and a plan.
This next song is called Lock It.
Another kind of ballad.
But there might be a change.
That's nice.
I will say, he does a lot more crooning
on this album, which I can appreciate.
He's crooning a lot, which he doesn't do on Smart Kids.
So I appreciate that he's trying up a different vocal call.
So I appreciate that he's trying up a different call.
He can do, I'd like to see him do a Seth McFarlane-style standards album also.
None of it's about safety.
It's just pure standards.
He could throw in and be like,
I got you under my skin,
but make sure it's not an infection.
Make sure you got an ointment.
Like he could add things to the classics
that he could add.
Anyway, right back at Lockheed.
He starts, baby, it's cold outside,
and then stops it, then it slows down.
There's nothing wrong with your tape machine,
but some songs are problematic
by today's standards.
I always check a Christmas standard
to see if it fits today's
times or not.
I didn't hire
a new partner because I didn't want to
subject someone to that.
Oh.
Uh, uh,
okay, wait, hold on, lock it.
Traffic noise, when it rains outside,
it's okay with you,
cause there's lots inside,
for you to do.
That's true.
Yeah.
Home is the place
with the cozy bed
and a pillow to rest
your sleeping.
I'll fast forward a little bit.
What?
When you come in,
lock the door,
just lock the door.
That's what it's for,
It only takes a minute then out.
That sucks.
Just lock the door,
as hard as a rock.
Just lock it tight
with all of your might.
Lock it up,
it only takes a minute,
it guards your home and
everything that's in it.
Especially you.
And once you're inside, pick up the phone and check with your folks.
Or phone a neighbor your folks really trust.
If somebody rings the bell or knocks,
don't open the door unless it's somebody
your parents say is okay.
So that's like a
band on the run where it has a big change
in the music.
It starts out
a different vibe.
I'd put it
on the best.
I like the start.
I like the ballad-y start.
Let's see here.
Sorry, I'm trying to roll through these stranger...
So many of these songs are like,
hey kids, we know you're curious and
you're wide-eyed about the world.
Knock that shit off!
Be afraid of drugs
and what's under the sink
and what lies outside
of a locked door.
Have you ever thought
what's in your closet at night?
Think about it
really hard.
Could it be a monster
or a murderer?
Think about it really hard.
Basements are
easy to sneak into
and from there,
somebody would just have to drill
a hole in your closet
and then they could be there for days
and you wouldn't know.
It's easy to drill a circle under your bed
and have the bed drop out
under the house.
You've seen cartoons.
It could happen right now
at this very moment.
Any tunnel that you see could just be
a painting on a brick wall.
Am I even the real McGruff?
Someone could have killed me
and replaced me and given you bad information.
Trust your neighbors.
You've got to think about it.
Trust your neighbors and let's say, call in the phone.
Then make sure to lie to them and tell them
no matter what hour of the day,
your mom is in the shower
and can't come to the phone.
I'm talking to you little Jason Sheridan.
Be afraid of the world.
It's all scary out here.
When you have to do laundry as an adult,
you're going to get freaked the fuck out.
Your whole week is going to be shot.
You're going to cancel all your plans.
Just cause of laundry.
Laundry is a scary thing.
When it's time to get rid of objects,
make sure to really work yourself
into a nice lather.
I'm going to be a good boy.
Make sure you get into a nice lather.
Each one is important.
It earned its way into your life.
You're just going to throw it away?
If the object goes, the memory is gone.
The object has a brain and feelings.
Think about its feelings before you throw it away.
Would you throw away your mom?
Marie Kondo can do nothing to assuage your fears
and intrusive thoughts.
If there's something you got at a carnival
like 12 years ago,
first watch Toy Story
and realize that inanimate things
have very complex arcs
and emotions.
But when you're older,
just make sure you learn the difference between
the toy and the man the toy is based on.
And just to be clear,
just to be clear,
you're going to be a good boy.
You're going to be a good boy.
Just to be clear.
This is not Buzz Lightyear the toy.
The real man.
Don't get confused
by actor's tweets.
Assume that they mean
that they're tweeting about a movie
about a man who a toy is based on.
If you don't understand
what an actor is saying, just assume
they're telling you to vote.
When will we get the movie
called Ham
based on the pig
that the toy Ham
was based on in Toy Story
not starring John Ratzenberg?
American hero John Ratzenberg
starring Chris Hemsworth.
Lightyear opens a can of worms.
A great can.
Leave the can open
and let every worm out.
Look at them crawl.
Cans and the sequel to Cans Worms.
This isn't about the worm.
This is about the can that the worm
came out of.
Oh Lord.
This is why we can only do
how many more on this.
We have like 30 songs left.
Well, how many more on this
one?
Yeah. Well, how many more on this
tape? Two songs are left
on here. Okay.
Then what? And then how much would that
leave us with
four? There would be enough
that they could be a hearty
enough stew if we did a McGruff
three, right? We wouldn't leave
either side too thin. For sure. There would
be a hearty enough stew.
Hearty stew. McGruff's
favorite food. I also. Yeah.
Oh no, I lost the playlist on my
test. It got deleted.
Be careful. Learn how to
be computer smart.
It's here. I also. Look.
Also, there is also.
I'll say right now.
I got something else too that I haven't even
revealed for this episode.
Well, if that's the case. If that's the
case, I think the two songs
and your big reveal, that sounds like
maybe the home stretch.
To me.
I think probably that's right.
Because I'll be honest, I'm exhausted.
Yeah. Yeah. No kidding.
From smiling too
much.
From tapping our toes and from
clapping to answer McGruff's
game questions. This has been
a big physical effort.
Right. So.
Yeah. So I guess. I guess
McGruff three. It doesn't have to
be a year from now. We can also say that.
We could do it in a few months. Yeah.
And I'm still trying to see if we can
get smart kids
interview with the guy who made smart kids.
So where did that land? You got
the name. This ended up being a false flag,
but it got us to a different album, which we
will get to. So that's good. But then the
smart kids guy
is who. Right. You don't have to say the name,
but what do we know?
We just. All we know is in a YouTube
comment, someone said, this is my dad who
wrote the album and put a name there.
Whoa. So we have a name
now. Somebody pointed this. Somebody emailed
this to us actually as well. And I'm forgetting
and I apologize for not shouting you
out. I will thank you
in an email and then I mean, I can
shout you out on the McGruff three.
If you've got any McGruff related
tips, email podcast,
the riot and gmail dot com
subject line.
Smart tips for good boys.
I'm sure I said this on
the other McGruff
episode, but I called the National Crime
Prevention Council.
Maybe I didn't.
I called them because it still exists. It's
very confusing what it is. I don't know
if it's like government funded, but it's like
they still technically own McGruff. So they
license McGruff out like he was on an insurance
commercial in the last couple of years.
And it's unclear
exactly what it is. And if
it's like, I guess Trump didn't cut the National
Crime Prevention Council because
there's still one person sitting in an office because I
emailed them and it was tough. And I called
somebody on the phone. I was like, hey, I'm looking
for, there was an album McGruff had in the 80s.
And I'm looking
for maybe like some information about it
and maybe who wrote it or put it together.
And the person,
it didn't sound like a very old person,
but just for comedy's sake, I was like,
this is sort of the vibe. Oh,
that album, eh?
Hmm. I remember
that. You know,
I'm not quite sure.
I do
remember it was someone who lived maybe
in Florida.
And I was like, okay, thank
you. But I'm not sure. I'm really
not sure. And I'm like, don't you have
any, where are, like, what
is this organization that's basically
all McGruff? It was like
started because of McGruff, which
I guess maybe we can get into that on McGruff32.
We'll do some more investigating there and
figure out what the National Crime Prevention Council
was or is.
I'm sure that's interesting.
It's now Trump's last hope
to overturn the election. They're the
one body. Yes.
This is giving me hope.
Do you guys know about this Reply
All episode from
really early in 2020
where it
started out with a guy was trying
to, like, tell someone of a song.
And it's like, what's this song?
And he really remembers a lot of it
in the melody and stuff. And he sings it
and he cannot track it down.
And they eventually
contact the Reply
All producers and hosts
and they start trying to track it
down. And then it just spirals
and it is fascinating.
Like, I was, like, sitting in my car
waiting for the conclude. Like, I was supposed
I was, like, a little
early for a thing I had to go to. And I
was like, I cannot leave this car until I
find the conclusion of this. It's
one of the best podcasts I've heard all year.
Yeah.
We'll see. Maybe it'll unfold.
Maybe we'll become embroiled in
some sort of controversy, like
incidents, controversy, who knows?
McGruff 3, McGruff 4, McGruff
5?
McGruff 10, in remembrance
of Michael.
Our friend passed away in pursuit of
the McGruff mask.
He got too close. McGruff
7, Michael in Hell.
And then Michael
takes Manhattan. The underworld. I'm in the underworld.
You're in the underworld. It's real now.
So, yeah.
So there's a lot of meat left on the bone.
I will also say, and I'm, people have
noticed, obviously, we've done some live
streams. I now, of course, have
a full McGruff puppet
that was given to me by Andrew Grissom.
Which is just
the most, one of the finest
gifts I've ever received.
And if you haven't seen these live streams,
I'm sure I'll do it
again at some point. It's so great.
I got to, I was working in an
office and Andrew showed up.
Yeah, he just like kind of made a noise by
the door. And then I looked up
and then I saw the puppet just move
into the door frame.
Peer in. It was a
really exciting moment.
What? Yeah, this is,
the puppet is from a school.
Somebody just stole it from a school
and just put it on eBay.
So, and he's missing a shoe. He has
one shoe, but he does have cool plaid pants.
Yeah. Oh, wow. That's very,
that's like Rodney Dangerfield caddyshack
pants.
Yeah, that's a very good point. You can take the coat off.
The coat is removable. Wow.
Wow. Have you taken it off?
Show.
You've seen what he looks like with that. Check it out. Yeah.
I just did a bit with him on a
show online and I took the coat off and put a
Tom Petty shirt on him. Oh, wow.
This is really disturbing. He's looking hunky.
This is,
if someone makes a puppet likeness
of you, don't strip it.
It's not fair.
I got no shirt on.
What are you going to do about it?
Is this one of your wishes?
Phone smart.
I gotta
be phone smart.
The pants don't come off.
So I guess I can post this. Yeah.
They don't come off for you guys.
Not cheap.
Phone smart.
So that's the most fun thing.
Kids, if Kweiluds were still around, I'd have
to warn you about them, but they're not.
So I'll just tell you I had a great
time with them.
To as I say, not as I do.
Can I throw out some, here's something
actually not McGruff related,
but close enough, I think, that you could use
the email subject line,
Smart Tips for Good Boys.
Have I ever said this on the show that
twice in my life,
I saw a school
assembly, there was an anti-drug
thing, there was a bunch of puppets
and mascots, and that it culminated
in a big vulture
using his wings
like a trench coat and revealing
lots of baggies and needles.
I moved schools at some point in elementary school, so I got to see this twice at two of the schools.
And I have, like that's one of those, like the song
You Can't Place, I don't have enough to go off, but
it seems possible, and
to remind you, I grew up in Southern California, if that helps, if this was a California thing.
But if you have a faint memory in your life of seeing a vulture
opening wings that were full of baggies and needles clipped to the wings.
Wow.
It was about, I know it was about like a chipper girl
who wanted to join, not the police, but some kind of squad,
like of helping kids say no or something.
Amazing McGruff wasn't part of this, but like it was something like,
I want to be part of the Be Smart Squad!
And this vulture showed up and said,
Hey, so you want to be part of the squad, huh?
I'm the last test. The final test is you got to take one of these things.
And then she said, well, if that's the test, then I'm not going to do it.
I don't want to be part of the squad anymore.
And she cried and the vulture left.
And then friendlier puppets came up and said,
He was a liar! That wasn't, he's not with us!
You passed the test!
This is first grade. This might be one of the most vivid memories of
the first seven years of my life.
That has to be like a tour.
Like unless that was completely just put together by your school,
that had to be like a touring.
It was absolutely touring because if it was at two schools,
then in different years.
And I remember the second time, it must have been years, it was more like 93, 94.
And I remember going into an assembly, not knowing what it was.
And then like, it's this again?
I'm seeing the vulture, the drug vulture again.
So if you have any, if any of that rings a bell, vulture, baggies, please help me.
I've been like, I've been losing my mind about that one forever.
Somebody has to have a videotape of that.
Like they had to have done like a demo of it too.
Maybe you have like them doing it in a warehouse to present.
Oh, to see like, yeah, do you want this to come to your school?
Here's an example of what it is.
Yeah. Wow. We had, yeah.
I mean, we had stuff that nothing is memorable as that, but like,
there were definitely people, we had a man that had,
that had lost his arms that played guitar with his feet.
Like Mr. Show.
That got to school. Whoa.
What's that? Like Mr. Show.
Yes. Yeah. Yes.
So like, then I know he did the rounds.
We had a guy, there was a guy, I think he's passed away.
His name is Richard Lederer.
And he would, he would like just, he had like a lot, he would be like,
why do you park in a driveway and drive in a parkway?
Like he had like all these like, this was like for seventh and eighth grade.
And I think my memory is that my friend,
we found his email address and my friend just started sending a mean email.
That makes me think of when I was in eighth grade,
we all, all the eighth graders got called to the auditorium and the principal
gave us a lecture about being role models for the younger kids.
And then sent us back to class.
And I just remember talking to my friends and like asking teachers too,
like, Hey, what was that? Why? Why did that? What, what happened?
Like, like I was the smart alec kid and, but, and,
and I was mostly interested in eighth grade.
I was mostly interested in Mark Wade flash comics, but I do,
I did like, you know, kind of know everyone.
Like I knew what was going on and I was like, what ha what inspired,
why do we have to do that?
Did you find out? No, I never got a clear answer.
And I don't know if people,
it was just general rough housing or something going on,
but like, I have no idea still to this day why that happened.
Yeah.
Aaron, my wife was in an assembly one time in middle school where there was a
yearbook where that the first page of the yearbook had like a guy who was
shaped like a star and he's just like standing really splayed out with a huge
smile, like I'm the star guy.
And people very quickly started drawing big boners on the star guy.
And I think maybe she didn't have that information when she went to this
assembly, like quickly everybody in the room that we got to have a thing.
And, and the principal, there's like a long,
long speech just like pacing back and forth.
And it's just, it becomes a general assembly about like not writing
offensive things in your yearbook.
And this, you will not believe in 2020 that this happened in a school,
that the principal of the school points to Aaron in the front row,
arbitrarily, we didn't do anything wrong.
It points to Aaron, looks her in the eyes and says,
how would you feel if I went up to you and I pointed at you and I said,
you're gay.
Jail, jail to that.
Yes, to jail immediately.
News story trending on Twitter.
Stripped, stripped of badge and gun, principal badge and gun.
I think this was a nun by the way.
Wow. Really?
So probably stripped of whatever you are following this.
You know, you're fucked cause they only answered to God's law.
So it's like international waters.
He pardons. Yes.
Yeah.
And his law changes, you know, the Pope, that's crazy.
The Pope has changed though.
You know, he's the God's law changes. God reconsider things.
Oh yeah. He kind of reevaluate. Yeah. Every seven years.
Anyway, he's just one of us, you know, he's just learning too.
It's just a stranger out of us.
That's right.
That's what I was going with there.
All right. Okay.
See, I'm glad we could like spit, you know, like splay out a little bit,
like the star man to stretch and we don't feel like we have to get to all these
songs, but we do need to finish the album.
Certainly. Yes.
So what's left?
We have two songs left.
Two song on a car.
This one is called Stranger Danger.
Okay. Like that.
Hear that? It's a warning buzzer.
If you've learned the right stuff from a gruff, a little warning should go off in
your mind whenever something doesn't seem right.
So Jason, that's what goes off in your head when laundry is coming due.
I got to say, I hate whenever a song has like a car horn or police sirens in it.
It's because if you listen to it when you're driving, you know.
Yeah. And that curb your enthusiasm where there's a commercial with honking in it
on the radio.
Oh yeah.
Same deal. Yeah.
Yeah.
Okay. Let's see how the buzzer works for this kid.
A nice looking man at the park says to him, I've got an extra candy bar here.
Would you like it?
No, the gruff told me about people who offer candy or toys or something to kids.
I've got to get someplace safe fast.
Hey kid, where are you going?
There's a lady with kids.
Lady, that man back there tried to give me candy.
Good thinking. You can run someplace near like a store and you can speak to a clerk or owner.
If you're not near a store or a firehouse or a school, run to a mother with children.
Not necessarily.
Can you help me find the police station?
Grownups don't ask kids for directions. No.
Grownups ask grownups for directions. Bad strangers ask kids.
And they ask for places that seem okay.
As a kid, you'll never get asked for directions. I want you to remember that.
That's something I didn't learn as a kid.
Wrong.
There's got to be a scenario where you get asked for directions as a kid.
I get asked for directions all the time.
I think they just see me and they're like, well, he's five foot nothing.
I feel like since I was very young, they're like, well, he's not a threat.
I could easily beat up that. Is that a man?
What did you say? Kids ask you for directions?
Kids, adults, whatever.
I feel like I'm always getting asked for directions.
You're saying kids aren't afraid of you because you're a shorter gentleman?
Anyone. I just feel like.
All right. Well, let's continue here.
Station or firehouse or school.
Don't talk to them. Walk away.
Walk away. And if a stranger gets out of the car, run someplace safe.
Listen.
Yeah?
So long, Susan.
Susan is outside of school waiting for her mother to pick her up.
Then a woman who's been watching her comes up to her.
Susan, there you are. Your mother sent me to get you. Your father is very sick.
She knows my name, but she's a stranger.
I'm going into school to tell a teacher about this.
No, don't touch me. You're a stranger.
She knew Susan's name because she heard the other kids call her Susan and her name's on her book bag too.
Mothers don't send strangers to pick up their children.
This was one of the top three fears in my head as a kid.
I was fully prepared for constant strangers knowing my name,
so much so that we had a secret code word between my parent, my mom and I,
that the stranger would know if she actually had to send a stranger to pick me up.
In case it does come to that.
Yes.
Yes. Which of course, why would it ever come like...
Look, my parents don't know so many people, I guess.
Yeah.
There has to be one that I go, oh, I know. Yeah, that's my grandparents.
That's a friend of theirs who's been to the house before.
Yeah.
That's my uncle or something.
The stranger had walked up to you and just said, fear.
Oh, I can go with them. They knew the code word.
The code is fear.
Okay, but this, don't worry, this gets musical.
Your mother would.
I think. Let's just remember it.
There we go.
Don't say anything to a stranger.
She's like putting on the ritz or something.
Stay away from folks you don't know.
Updated version.
Don't go any place with a stranger who loves taco.
Just how to know I won't go.
The instrument sounds so much cheaper than Smart Kids 2.
It sounds like they just bought the cheapest Casio.
And that's what all this stuff is being recorded with.
Yeah, that's what I mean.
It was still in the era of good instrumentation, Smart Kids.
Right.
Yeah.
Don't ever take a thing from a stranger.
Either a woman or a man.
Doesn't matter.
Get away quick from a stranger.
Run off as fast as you can.
Stay far away from a stranger.
I mean, that's the kind of rambly.
All these are very rambly.
It's like can tighten up, tighten up.
Yeah, we're getting thinner and like what the danger is for sure.
Right.
So yeah, I guess then we get to the last song, which is called the Knock Knock song.
Which is not the No No song, a song we like a lot.
But yeah, this is called the Knock Knock song.
I walk through the schoolyard ten feet tall.
Nobody bothers me at all.
I feel good with all my might.
Cause I'm right, I'm right, always right.
You can be right too.
If you learn everything on this tape.
I like this tune.
Let's play the Knock Knock game and see how right we can get.
I can't game though.
One knock for right.
And two knocks for wrong.
OK, first question.
When you're home alone, you should always lock the door.
Right.
How many knocks?
Sure.
It's the best way to take care of your home and yourself.
If a stranger offers you candy, he's very generous.
Wrong.
You bet it's wrong.
Take off fast and tell someone about it.
Drugs are open.
It's a little generous.
You get a lot of candy.
Right.
You've never been more right.
I'm as right as a tail on a kite.
I'm as right as the stars at night.
I'm as right as a bright light on sight.
I'm so right, I'm right out of sight.
OK, let's get this one right.
Respect is something you just give your parents.
Wrong.
I'll say it's wrong.
Don't forget to also show respect to teachers, police officers.
Wait, hold on.
I thought he was making a complicated problem.
I thought he was making a complicated idea there, which was maybe like your parents might not be good people.
But I think what he was saying there was not just your parents, less than any adult that's a teacher.
I don't think he was saying like your parents need to earn your respect just like anyone else.
But that's not I don't think what he was saying, unless I'm wrong.
I think that's probably too nuanced, but also it does raise the question of like, well, wait, like police and teachers and firemen are also strangers to a certain extent.
Well, that's too complicated.
Too complicated.
Don't introduce that into a song, you know, you got to get it still got to be like catchy.
This is the thing.
I'll say it's wrong.
Don't forget to also show respect to teachers, police officers and of course, old folks.
In fact, show respect to everyone you meet.
The one tragedy of not doing this all in one section is tape four is a holiday.
The theme tape.
Oh, really?
What holiday?
Christmas.
It's all Christmas?
There's a little Hanukkah stuff in there too, actually.
But there's a song with McGruff and the kids go decorate an old folks home.
But we'll get to that on McGruff three.
Maybe it does have to be next year.
Christmas in July, though.
Maybe it does.
That's nice.
Yeah.
So we'll finish this out.
This isn't there's nothing so exciting coming up.
How do you kids get so right?
Getting yourself right.
Getting so tough.
Just learn the right stuff from McGruff.
You feel good when you see the light.
And you're right, right, right.
Always right.
You're sure a bunch of right on right kids.
Got any more songs?
I dance right as a big bird in flight.
I dance right as a snowflake is white.
I dance right as a big strong mistype.
I'm so right, I am right.
Out of sight.
I'm so right, I'm right.
So that's the end of tape two, cassette two.
We're fucking.
This is the click clack song.
If you, McGruff's going to say a question and then you clack your heels together.
Once if you agree with the statement stamp your click your foot against the ground as like a footstep.
If you disagree and take off your shoes and make no sound, if you have no opinion.
Or if it's too complicated, that's too complex of a problem to solve in an easy game like this.
And write me a letter.
So yeah, so I guess this is this was definitely more about like, this was more of a blues clues style situation where he wanted like call and response on like smart kids, which is more of a passive experience for the listener.
This he wanted to include kids so they could confusingly clap twice, which it's off beat like clapping twice in the middle of a song is hard and it's not.
But this is the way he would set it up with where it would be a fun clap twice.
Kids don't have rhythm.
Off the beat.
It would be like, you know, white people clapping.
Like one, the one and two.
I mean white people, bad people with bad rhythm.
One and three is when they generally clap.
You want to clap on the two and four, which is what Prince said to us.
He said white people clap on the two and four when I saw him in concert.
Oh, because he knew.
Oh, that's why they're wrong.
Okay. Yeah.
They. So McGruff is doing a lot of like bad rhythm clapping.
Very confusing. But he wanted it to be an immersive experience.
That's that's the step he wanted to take forward.
Like, right. So I appreciate that.
I don't know that he nailed it.
No, I think he nailed it.
Right. Like he's he's summing up the album.
Yeah. The lessons.
Yes.
Maybe making kids a little too confident.
Like when kids are like, I'm right.
You know, it's like, all right.
Well, let's let's have some humility of the knowledge we acquired.
What's some what's in the books that come with these?
Well, I only have one book and it's for the fourth one, which is the holiday one.
Okay. But it's basically just a lyric sheet and some drawings.
And this is first is a drawing where you're thanking again, thanking McGruff.
Thank you, McGruff, for all you do.
Thank you. Thank me for the harvest.
The harvest, the bouts of a harvest.
The weather is because of me, the birds and the bees, animals in the trees.
It's all McGruff.
Here's a picture of McGruff with two menorahs on each side.
Well, post this for this is coming out during on it.
This kind of is a Hanukkah present.
This right.
And yeah, so there's pictures there and then it has those bios of the revolution.
McGruff's revolution, the kids there.
And then it has phones, phone smart chart where you put your name, address, phone number, neighbors and phone number, relatives, first aid, police and other.
So it's just like you would fill it in.
No child has filled this in though.
Oh, you know, it does have it does have credits.
Oh, OK.
But we're not less interested a little with these a little bit, unfortunately.
I mean, I'd still be interested to talk about music by Angelo Natalie and lyrics by Sue Slocca.
I hope I'm saying that right.
Donald Booth and Angelo Natalie.
Any look up any of these people?
Brief. I did, but I didn't do it enough.
Let's just say that.
Sure, sure, sure.
And they it was recorded at the Carriage House in Stamford, Connecticut.
So that's wrestling and that's right.
Yes, PN McGruff.
I'll come from the same.
It's a great Burger King album of art.
OK, so we're at the end of this second episode.
And I will say this.
I was I was expecting we would get through more.
But yes, of course, how I was my hubris thinking that this wasn't more is crazy.
I'm just glad we get more.
I mean, yeah, we'd be so wiped, I think, to pack it in.
So I hope it's not disappointing.
We're not. I hope they I genuinely feel like some of the audience of this show
and of this episode might have seen the runtime and gone not for hours.
Boo. Right.
I understand that, but I hopefully what I'm about to say will make up for that.
So my thought process was.
Look, I don't want to see an artist go out like this.
You know, I don't want to see.
I don't want to see them sort of rest on their laurels.
Do you know, do some OK work, but not try to capture the spirit of smart kids.
So I will say I will reveal next week.
I will say I will reveal now I have helped McGruff record four new songs.
For an EP, an EP called Smart Teens, the Smart Teens EP.
And you will I will be putting this in the Patreon box right now for everyone to download.
This is a Patreon exclusive.
It'll be the clip that the songs will be patron exclusive at a certain point.
I'm going to probably put them up on YouTube and Apple Music.
You'll get downloads.
Our supporters get it first and they have.
They'll get it first. It'll be out. You'll have it for weeks.
And then at a certain point, I will probably put it up on YouTube because I spent a lot of time doing this.
Well, as because we've been saying, should we do McGruff two for a while?
Yes. And the answer has been like, I need a minute.
It's not ready. It's not ready.
I'll give everyone a little a little Genesis into this.
I think it's sometime during the summer I said to myself, oh, you know, be funny if I made him a gruff song.
And I was like, yeah, that would be funny. That's because I was like messing around with it very casually.
And then a couple of weeks later, I said, it'd be funny if I made a full album.
And then at a certain point, I said, I can't do a full album because this is killing me.
But I have I will say I don't I have demos of other songs that do exist, but I've settled on four that I like.
You polished it, which McGruff didn't. You're helping McGruff to to curate.
And it's basically I mean, what's taken longer, I think, is is my lack of engineering skills and producing skills.
But I'll say that there's four songs in this collection.
The first song on the album is called Vaping. Oh, very good.
He hasn't he hasn't been able to address that.
Vaping. Yeah. Track two.
This again, this is more for a teen audience. Track two is called Hook Up Apps.
They're not supposed to be on there.
They're not supposed to be on there. But in the future also, they shouldn't be on there.
Yeah. Number track three is called Raves.
The hot button issue of 2020. Absolutely.
Yeah. Yes. And track four.
It's about families. I'll just say that it's about different types of families and not letting other kids bully you for.
I'll just say McGruff sort of reveals a little bit about his own family in this this song.
Backstory. Oh, my gosh.
So I yes, that will be I think unless something happens, which I am not I'll say this.
I'm not 100 percent done with it. But by the time this comes out, I should be 100 percent done with it.
And it's probably in your inbox right now. Whoa.
These four songs. Oh, my God. This is huge. Huge announcement.
Huge announcement. Yes. Huge drop from McGruff at the end of the year.
Yes. Smart Teens.
Wow. So there you go.
There's a demo for a song called Butt Chugging. It didn't make it.
But I have it. It's kind of written. I just maybe for maybe for McGruff.
What ever since that movie, Narcs or what was it called?
Let's Be Cops. Oh, no.
Like Fun Runers. Oh, no.
It's John Cena. The John Cena blockers. Blockers.
I will say that in the lyrics, in the half written lyrics, I have blockers does appear.
The scourge of blockers. Ruining teen minds.
Vibe wise, it ended up being kind of more of like an early 90s song.
So I felt like it didn't maybe fit so much sound wise with these four.
Oh, you're kind of going for Smart Kids. I see.
I'm going for it. Look, it's not as good as Smart Kids, but I was going for Smart Kids and I was going.
The goal was to make it as good as I could make it.
Well, you got to aim for you imitate your heroes until it becomes its own thing.
And that's what you've done. You've set the bar really high.
And I'm sure as much as you're trying to be McGruff that a lot of money has come out in the process.
I want it to be, you know, like a McCartney chaos and creation where you go, oh, yeah, that's the magic.
I remember maybe it's not as good necessarily as the early stuff, but I can see it there.
I will say there is a little bit of a dubstep part in one of them, but it's not as good as the early stuff.
Part in one of them, but it's a little bridge.
It's just sort of a bridge. Nice. So there you go.
I. Yeah. Wait. Yeah. Any other genre to tip or are you trying?
Sure. I mean, I can see. I mean, people here for.
Well, first of all, I'll say this.
Another big part of me not of it taking a while was I learned very quickly that I cannot spend more than 30 minutes at a time singing like McGruff.
That's fair. Yeah. And then I was like, there were like two weeks would pass and I go, I got to do it, but it hurts.
So then I'd have to like figure out, try to figure out a different voice to sing with.
There's a lot that I have. That was a lot of my dragging my feet at a certain point.
There is a bunch of kids to sing instead of you.
Yeah, that's hard to do right now. I have to talk to the FBI about why you're searching a child singer on Fiverr.
I will reveal I there is another voice on the album that I added literally a week ago.
Wow. That you'll recognize in the podcast.
Steve Perry from Journey rarely does any music anymore.
He came back to. I contacted Steve Perry.
Zach Reno's voice.
Hey, all right. All right.
The King returns.
City walking. Wow.
Geez, he's in the background.
Yes. So, oh, genre wise, the first I think it's like a like kind of synth pop.
The first song is sort of synth pop.
The second song is a is a is like a jam, like a sexy jam.
Oh, boy. Like I wish I if you will.
I McGruff play like there's guitar.
There's two guitar solos on the second song, which I went like, is this indulgent?
It's like, well, there were guitar solos on Smart Kids.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
And sax solos.
The third song and sort of a droney synth.
And then the fourth one is definitely dream like dream synth pop.
It's very like kind of like fly like what do you want to make dream?
He is really the best word.
So then you get 90s and you could start doing like, well, how would McGruff have tried to do it like a his version of Radiohead or yes, what's his the prodigy or nine inch nails?
You can start getting because he was probably getting I think some dark industrial kind of stuff.
I for sure he was.
I think I have that sort of like 90s hip like early like 89, 90, 91.
Butchugging is like a 91 style rap song.
Like a Technotronic.
Fight for your right.
No, not like that.
More of sort of like old maybe it is like late 80s.
Maybe it's it's sort of a rave.
I don't know how to even describe.
You have to hear I can look I can play it for you at a certain point.
Now, now the legend of butt chugging.
That's going to be like one of those tracks you hear about and like I wonder if they're ever going to put out that chugging.
Is he going to finish it?
It's been working out for years, they say.
You're working on that.
Meanwhile, I'm just learning surface streets in case someone pulls over.
It's like, can you small man Woodland Crete large gnome?
Can you help me get to Van Nuys?
You know, no one's addressed you.
Odd shaped creature.
Help.
If you see Jason, leave him be.
Don't ask him for directions.
Maybe you know what?
Maybe I shouldn't put the songs immediately so people hear this and like like they'll hear it, get excited and then it'll come out like a day later.
Which how should we do?
How should that be?
Yeah.
Or dump it right now.
Yeah, I mean, right.
Probably.
Well, because they'll see this new episode and then they'll see the four songs and already the secret is already out.
I see.
Which isn't that big of a deal.
I'll leave it up to you.
The secret really is to you guys.
It should be up to the artist.
Yeah, all right.
I'll think about it.
I mean, you'll know when you know.
If it's not in right now, I mean, it'll probably be in right now.
Just don't want the album to get stepped on by the episode.
Do you want it all to breathe?
But, you know, like big surprise movie.
And albums or that that's that's kind of what it's all about.
You've really done sort of a Beyonce move here.
Yeah, I'll put it out like the day of and then this episode will come out like at midnight like it normally does.
And I'll put it out the day of maybe that's a smart way to do it.
Yes.
Very good.
Good really strategy.
Make a plan before you put out your album inspired by me.
So, yeah.
So happy holidays, everyone.
Wow.
So, you know, I'm going to leave it at that.
So, yeah.
So happy holidays, everyone.
Wow.
A Hanukkah present from McGruff and Mike to you.
This is huge.
Wow.
And obviously another presence to come next year.
So we have one thing to look forward to in 2021.
So far, the list is one item long.
McGruff three.
So get the positivity up everybody.
Probably vaccines eventually.
And also the episode could be like a celebration of that we're out.
The vaccine.
Sure.
Not until everyone gets the vaccine will we put out McGruff three.
That's good.
Yeah.
And at that point, somebody will gift me a full suit.
A McGruff suit hopefully.
Andrew Grissom will find it on eBay.
Well, if you know where there's a full McGruff suit, then email podcastwriter.gmail.com
with the subject line, smart tips for good boys.
Any other McGruff related information, any information about the vulture who came to my school several times.
Same email, same subject line.
And with that, you survived podcastwriter the second gate McGruff two.
Wow.
We did it.
What a blast.
I'm glad we're not done.
I'm glad our journey with McGruff is not over.
Right.
And now we have up to what are we going to we have to top we have to top we have to top
it with three and we'll see what we can do.
Well, full album or full I was saying Beyonce already the the the the film like the lemonade.
Yeah, that's true.
Yeah.
You have to make a 45 minute stylized visual.
Visual.
Like in its like he's shirtless in it.
It's kind of like Madonna's sex maybe.
Oh, yeah.
What you're showing us is already pretty.
Yeah.
It feels like a visual sexually challenging visual album.
So, yeah.
So we'll see.
We'll see what happens.
Wow.
Anything is possible.
Geez.
Yeah.
Anything is possible.
So check your inbox.
Download that EP and we'll get cooking.
Mike and I are getting to work on a multi-million dollar.
We're calling our buddy David LaChapelle.
It's going to blow you away.
But whatever we make, don't watch it high.