Five, four, three, two, one.
We begin today with a simple ho, ho, ho.
Hello to you on this two days before Christmas.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, The Second Gate.
I'm Scott Gertner, Jason Sheridan,
who suggested that beginning is with us.
We're hemming and hawing and you're right,
the simple ho, ho, ho was the way to go.
Go.
I'm Michael Carlson, I'm here.
My suggestion, well, my thought was I was gonna say just
anything with a hat on it is better.
Yeah, you know.
Putting a hat on anything is better.
There's this comedy phrase, always put a hat on it.
Put a hat on a hat.
That's right.
Put as many hats on top of each other as you can,
which I guess is what we're doing today.
Wait, Jason, I said your name, but you didn't say anything.
Feel free to.
Oh, that's okay.
Yeah, no, I'll just echo that.
I'm all for hats on things, especially a Santa hat.
Absolutely.
Now, is this an episode that we could get done in one sentence right now
by saying we're talking about when they put a Santa hat on King Kong?
Sure.
Yeah, I guess in a way that could be the end, but there has to be more there.
There has to be more to explore.
Right?
Oh, yeah, no, there's gotta be.
No, I'm not out of stuff to talk about right now.
No way.
They did a lot more.
They did a lot more than I thought.
That's true.
It's not well preserved at all.
No.
Really have to dig for it.
This is another classic podcast, right?
Especially the second gate where we're going off of one grainy camcorder
that was posted to YouTube and just trying to decipher as many details as we can from that.
But yeah, this is all about Universal Studios Hollywood and a holiday activation,
if that's the right word, a holiday overlay that they did that is pretty delightful.
I assume you've seen concept arts or our little thumbnail on Twitter.
But you know what?
Well, actually, really in a way, this is a two part topic because when you say Santa Kong,
there are several things that this could be.
One of them, of course, every year still, presumably, I don't know,
I haven't been up there in a second for obvious reasons.
They put a Santa hat on King Kong at City Walk who's hanging off of the building.
I mean, maybe that's what you think of when you think of Santa Kong, possibly.
Well, that's happened in the recent past, so that might be fresher.
That was initially what I thought we were, and then I remembered, of course,
that we've talked about the other Santa Kong.
So yes, I think that probably when people hear Santa Kong, they think,
oh yes, he has little mistletoe in his hand and a Santa hat,
and he's on that iconic neon sign at City Walk, which I think Evan Susser on our episode of the City Walk Saga
that it was one of the icons of LA, one of the touchstones of Los Angeles, maybe.
A weenie, one of LA's weenies.
Certainly a weenie, yes.
Yeah, I liked that grand proclamation.
I wonder if you feel the same way about the holiday version.
I like it. I think it's great.
Sometimes you get a beard. You don't always get a beard.
I don't know the consistency of when they put a beard on, if that was before,
and they stopped doing it, or is that a later addition?
Did they lose the beard backstage?
Did a disgruntled employee steal King Kong's Santa beard? We'll never know.
We'll never know.
I came across the beard, and I don't think I was familiar with the beard one,
and then I also came across, I'll share the screen with you guys, the summer equivalent of Kong.
He's got a little swim trunks on. He's got sunglasses. He's got some zinc oxide on his nose.
And I think that's pretty fun, too.
It is pretty fun.
I didn't know they did this.
Yeah, when was this? I've never seen this.
I'm not sure. It's a stock photo.
I found a lot of the Santa Kong stuff in stock photo libraries.
That's a little while ago because the hard rock has a different guitar.
It's not the iconic Eddie Van Halen guitar in the background. It's a different type of guitar.
Do you recognize the types of guitars at the hard rock?
Yes, yes, because that's not the iconic Van Halen guitar. I don't even know what that guitar is.
What are the qualities of the iconic Van Halen guitar?
Let's share the screen and let me show you.
Sure. You can see GameStop in the background, too, so that points it to a certain timeframe.
It's not GameStop anymore. Now it's Things From Another World.
That's correct.
You've seen this, Scott. This is the iconic Van Halen guitar.
We don't talk Van Halen a lot on this show. This design, you see?
Oh, I see. Okay. It's red and with a lot of crisscrossing black and white stripes.
We've only really talked about Van Halen in the way of Sammy Hagar Van Halen dreams at the end of the Power Rangers movie, of course.
But yeah, when they retired, of course, the hard rock at CityWalk out here, they just dismantled Eddie's guitar.
But that was the design toward the end.
Wait a minute. Was it around like... So in the same calendar year, we lost Eddie Van Halen and we lost Eddie Van Halen's guitar outside of the hard rock event?
Giant guitar. You're saying this now and I'm just realizing that you are correct.
Wow. Did he die of heartbreak when he learned that his greatest achievement was torn down?
You know what? I'm going to look into that. I don't know. We don't know for sure.
But see, here's the picture of the guitar before.
I never put this together. I guess I'd read the plaque that said that this was Eddie Van Halen's guitar.
But for being we're as close to CityWalk completists as you can be.
And I don't I was looking at a photo. I didn't I couldn't I didn't.
Clearly, there's a difference. One has flames and one has stripes.
But I was just not clocking any of this. Right.
I may have I may be that other one might actually be someone's guitar might be like Stevie Ray Vaughan's guitar.
I just don't know. So somebody might be get get mad about this.
Scott, are there any iconic guitars other than Prince's Prince symbol dick guitar that he played at the Super Bowl that you would like know off the top of your head where you'd be like, well, that's the iconic guitar of so and so.
I guess I just recognize a Paul McCartney bass.
A Hoffner bass. That's not a guitar.
Yeah. Right.
So what about Elvis Costello's Jazzmaster?
No. I like Elvis Costello. I don't know about that.
That's like sort of the classic guitar he uses in all the old.
OK, this I promise that'll be the last guitar I'll show you today and then we'll go back to Santa.
Today is guitar talk.
Talking Tars.
Mike, do you know do you know what guitar Bob Dylan was playing at that folk festival?
Oh, when he went electric?
When he went electric and then someone had an axe and they wanted to chop it up because they were so disgusted.
I don't know off the top. I want to say it was like a telecaster, but I could be wrong.
So don't don't get mad at me here.
That's Elvis Costello with his trademark Jazzmaster.
Oh, sure. Yeah.
You know, you know this, Jason. I don't know this.
He's just saying he recognizes the photo.
I recognize the well, yeah, I like early Elvis Costello.
I haven't gotten much far past like Armed Forces.
I will say that is my I want like a nice old Jazzmaster.
That's maybe my dream guitar.
That is extremely cool.
Yeah. Not replicated at CityWalk.
CityWalk. Not not broad enough for the masses.
I suppose. Yeah.
Maybe if they had appealed to the real music fans more, it wouldn't be in the process of being replaced by a chocolate Emporium.
With a chocolate robot and his chocolate robot dog.
When they're usually when Pump It Up is set at CityWalk is referred to the tracks from Milo Zyloto.
The cold light.
Don't wind up. I feel like I waited a hundred years for you to set that up.
I felt like I lived a whole lifetime waiting for what you were going to see.
What reference that was. And I was happy with it.
I'm just saying I was like, what is it? What is it?
I know you love a good Milo Zyloto.
Hey, that's probably how long it took Kong to grow into a full size.
Right. Yeah, I think that's right. Yes.
Hundred years.
When people say watching the detectives at CityWalk, it's about the plain clothes officers who monitor the comings and goings at the steam shopping mall.
That's right.
So Santa Kong.
Yeah, look, you know, that's great.
And I think they should do that kind of thing more often with the Sussers declared greatest icon in Los Angeles.
You know, I think if it had been a more normal, less horrible year, you know, the LA won a couple of the big sports championships.
You know, I think I think that happens again.
And you got to put King Kong in a Dodger uniform or in a Laker uniform.
I think everyone get a kick out of that.
I think that anytime you can dress up either at neon signs or robots in anything, do it like it more of it.
Like if you went on any of the famous rides and like all the pirates on Pirates of the Caribbean were wearing Dodger's uniforms, like it doesn't matter.
It doesn't even make sense.
You just go, holy shit, they're all dressed like Dodgers.
Now that what you're describing is an incredible ordeal.
That's so it's hundreds of yes, I that is extreme.
I for sure.
But maybe the Navi Shaman of Song is wearing a Dodger's uniform at the end of the at the end of the river.
In foot tall.
One that's just one big Dodger's uniform.
You have to make in in Florida.
Yes.
You're suggesting then like the every World Series champ gets the jersey.
Maybe for like a month after the win.
You sub in Vince Scully singing the song as well.
I know.
Hey.
But Vince Scully.
Yeah, because he's kind of like, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, heyontec.
Yeah.
So more of that.
What's the full name of that ride?
Navi River Journey.
Is that correct?
Yeah, I believe.
All right.
So the every like right after the World Series, it's the baseball River Journey.
Great.
Yes.
Fantastic.
Navi River Journey year around the bases.
A lot of changes since roadies been out.
A lot of changes going on.
The only one minding the store.
That's right.
Yeah, it's all getting crazy now.
So all right.
That stuff's great at City.
Just wanted to acknowledge that Kong does a great job year in year out.
But that is a stationary figure in a way.
And it's smaller than the main topic.
That being the King Kong that was part of the Universal Studios tour for many decades until it was burnt in a fire and no longer exists.
This is not an overlay of the new thing of the Peter Jackson screen thing.
This is a big robot, a big Bob Gerb built robot.
And every year, not every year.
Not it. Wait, no.
I said, why am I saying every year?
One year, one year, 2002, they put it in a Santa hat.
And Jason, you're correct.
More was done.
Would you like to discuss a little more of what was done?
Well, sure.
There is a pretty good video of this on YouTube.
And I was very delighted because I think I had seen the still image of Kong.
And but I didn't realize that like, oh, when you went in the soundstage, they had decorated all of the buildings with like Christmas lights.
And, you know, the guy is the tour guide is talking about like, and that's snow on the buildings.
It's not real. It's fake. It's Hollywood snow.
And I thought the best touch was a little CRT TV in one of the apartment building windows playing the end of It's a Wonderful Life.
I thought that was really charming.
Now, all right, this is where we're going to disagree, because I thought that was very stupid.
I don't like that's the overlay is if you don't know the what that what that attraction used to be, because it was a long time ago at this point.
It burned up in in 2008.
But I know it very well. I did it every day for a while.
So it was a soundstage that the tram would drive into.
And there's first like a city scene set where a reporter on the news throws to a helicopter reporter who's talking about some disturbance downtown.
And then the chopper hits some kind of problem and goes spiraling down.
Oh, no, what's going on?
Then we start hearing like military fire and a helicopter and you round the corner.
And there is King Kong himself in the flesh and he shakes each car of the tram and breathes on you as banana breath.
And that's the attraction in this one.
You get to the first scene, this Christmas lights.
And then instead of a scary news report, It's a Wonderful Life is playing.
What does that have to do with King Kong?
It's entirely unrelated.
Well, it's a spirit of the season.
And it gives him a chance to tie in that like, you know, when they were filming this, it was 90 degrees outside.
And so they really were pumping in that fake snow.
Of course, it's fake snow, Hollywood snow.
You're saying the fear, Scott.
You miss the fear from the ride.
Yeah, I think I'm when you compare it to the original story telling.
And also, I mean, look, this is having done this job.
What I liked was yelling a Kong and shaking my fist at him.
All the little trivia details could be fun, but wasn't, you know, the funnest thing to do.
And it can get a little lost in a room that's very loud and where explosions are going off.
I think it's what, you know, most of the tour are these little factoids.
I don't like that you drive in and now you got to hear more factoids where there used to be like a news anchor dying in a helicopter crash.
I mean, yeah, I get what you're saying.
But imagine like there was a rise of the resistance overlay where Kylo Ren was just trying to give you a present the whole time.
And he's trying like he's coming after you, but he has a present and it's a lot less sinister.
Oh, it's OK if you didn't get me something.
It's OK. Yeah. So he's like your presence here is enough sticks.
The spoiler. He sticks like a present like present through.
I got a long pole for you here.
Take it. This is your gift.
When he's coming through the top of the elevator like that is giving us a big sausage or something.
Right. He rolled us in a sausage at the month club.
I made a Christmas sausage.
Here it is. Take it. Grab it.
Grab it. No, come on.
Grab it. Yeah, that would drive away droid.
It's giving you a different vibe, but it's only temporary.
Well, hang on. The problem for me is not the vibe.
I like the vibe. I like that.
I really love that that King Kong is wearing a Santa hat.
I think I just don't think they did a good job of tying the first room into the second room.
It seems like we're in there's an unrelated situation going on.
Here's a city scene where it's a wonderful life is playing.
And now let's go somewhere else.
And there's King Kong in a Santa suit.
And you don't know why I'm missing the why.
Right. I mean, that examination is fair because I think we can all agree on the second room.
Oh, right. For sure. Yeah.
Let's say how much we like this.
And then we can maybe think about how this could have all fit together better.
But yeah, King Kong's in a Santa hat and Santa sleeves.
The first the top of a Santa suit.
And he's holding a giant candy cane.
That's a lot. They give us a lot there.
They had to make some really big sleeves.
Yeah. And there's a helicopter, but it's just hovering.
It's not firing bullets at him.
They've made peace for the holidays.
And there's snow falling. Snow falling constantly.
They must have run through a lot of snow to do this thing.
It looks like the outfit, the shirt Kong is wearing looks like they cut a hole in a fumigation tent.
Like it's draped over him in such a funny way that like most clothes aren't maybe like maybe a dress would be that material.
But in general, a shirt does not look like that.
It's not super fitted.
That's right. If you're borrowing a friend's suit or renting a tux, it is not proportioned to you.
So he might have borrowed this from another monster that it was meant for.
This was Rodin's Santa suit or Rodin. Wait, Rodin was Rodin.
I was thinking Rodin as well because I didn't want to just say Godzilla.
But now I'm like, I don't think Rodin. Yeah, no, Rodin would have to be.
That's like a pterodactyl. So yeah, Mothra is the Mothra. Of course, is the Mothra.
I apologize. Maybe it was the proportions of King Kong.
Maybe maybe a Gamera. Oh, yeah. Yeah, I know that monster.
Yeah. It was the suit.
Gamera was buried in. Gamera is a big Andrew Grissom fan to the show is a big Gamera fan, if I recall correctly.
Makes all the sense in the world. That specific monster.
I think I asked him once, what would you want? Like, I know you don't collect toys, but is there like a character you would have toys of?
He's like, Gamera, I think. That's pretty perfect. He'll text me if that's right or not.
Yeah, I mean, it's a great suit. And let me screen share.
And you guys probably have some of these photos, too, but just to point out a few.
I mean, my favorite one, and we'll make sure this is on Twitter.
This is a Getty Images photo for a press event. They did. Oh, two. Oh, I'm underselling it. Two candy cans.
Yeah, yeah. Double fisting candy canes.
I mean, anyone's dream for the holidays.
And just in this particular photo, he looks so humiliated.
It's like he's communicating. I do not want to wear this.
We got like a dog wearing a Halloween costume.
Yes. Well, and let's not undersell the soundscape in this room either, because he's not roaring.
Oh, my God. Yes, absolutely.
He's saying ho ho ho in like a deep King Kong tone of voice.
And I mean, it's what you want. It's what you you know, it's just so great.
I don't know how they didn't do this every year.
Oh, is it too hard to do it? Like, why not do it every year?
I feel like people would have been delighted by this.
I don't know. Yeah, maybe it was a budget thing.
I don't know what else they were doing. Was there odd feedback? Yeah.
Why not? The costume had been sewn, unless like he ripped through it by the end of the Christmas season.
Also, are we sure they only did it this one year?
I'm not sure about my thought. I cannot find proof of anything other than 2002.
But do we know if his breath still smell like bananas or did it smell like peppermint?
I was wondering that and I really hope that it's peppermint.
I mean, that makes a lot of I mean, I would not there would be no way they wouldn't have suggested it when they were coming up with this.
But I do wonder if it actually exists. I mean, let's ask the listener here.
Did you ever see this in person? Did he have peppermint breath?
And did it last for more than a year? Like other because this is not that well documented.
I mean, it's documented visually, but not as far as there's no Jim Hill piece on this as far as I can see.
Well, there is actually. Oh, I missed the Jim Hill piece.
JimHillMedia.com, if not written by the man himself. Oh, wait, no, it is. It is written by him.
I apologize to Jim. I missed your piece, my friend.
But he doesn't really have a well, I don't know.
He wait a minute. He says they would periodically try to find new ways to celebrate the season, including dressing King Kong in a Santa suit periodically implies that it happened more than once.
Yeah, doesn't seem like he has the most information either.
I don't think this is the most documented thing in the world, if you can imagine.
And who else? Yeah, Jim doesn't have all the info. Who else is going to have it?
I don't know. Maybe a listener if we're lucky. Right.
They were not doing it by 2006, which was my inaugural season with the tour guide program.
And boy, would I have loved to do unless they did. What if I'm wrong and I did it and I don't remember?
Wow, that would be crazy, though, missing away my own memories.
That would be crazy. Well, Christmas 2005, though, you got to remember the Peter Jackson Kong is coming out.
And maybe they don't want to like, yeah, the brand and do something that fun and that people like.
It's like how the Star Wars hyperspace hoopla went away as soon as Disney Star Wars was like, we're serious now. No more fun.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah. Even though then the actual King Kong thing.
What does Peter Jackson say when you drive in? I see it a million times, but yeah, it's really weird.
He says, like, all right, everyone, we're going back. Skull Island. Skull Island.
You're like, what? Where? You don't know.
And all I know, we don't know what's actually more.
There was all I'll say is one time I did it with a certain someone next to me, Biz Biz.
And now forever, I'll just remember going hearing Skull Island. Skull Island.
We're going back. We're going back.
And then we just saying the shark isn't working over and over again.
That's right. The shark.
The shark isn't working.
That way, if to clue you in, that's a reference to and this was burrowed into my brain working there as well.
That there was one of the things they love to tell on the tour is how the shark and jaws did not work really well.
And there's a clip that they play after the shark attack of Richard Dreyfuss calling in a fake like on the intercom.
And you'd always hear the shark is not working. The shark is not working.
That was a must play. I believe we had a list of optional plays and must plays that.
Yeah, I always saw. I mean, I probably done the tour in my life now 12 times, maybe some around there.
Sounds right. That seems right. And I've never. Yeah, that's always been there.
That's always been. I mean, it is an interesting story for sure.
The part that really that I got a little sick of doing over and over.
Forgive me if I said this on the jaws episode, which was feels like nine years ago at this point, but that that you'd always have to do the which would kill all the time.
And of course, the shark was named Bruce and it was named after Mr. Spielberg's lawyer.
I think that's what I would just try to make that pause more pregnant every time I did it.
We got to do a 10 second pause before lawyer.
We have to do the full you doing the tour episode soon.
I would love to discuss that idea. I think we sort of have talked around it, but if we haven't said it, just I think there has to be maybe an episode of just you doing the tour for us.
I mean, we've discussed the plans of this and how you two would be involved because we don't want this to just be right that I just talk.
And I think there's a good plan and I don't want to say what it is.
Right. But yeah, well, I mean, there's plans with the tour in general that we've had to put off.
But yes, that's true.
One of these days, we're going to end up with like, OK, this is one we did confrontation.
Santa Kong is in progress right now.
King Kong on the tour is a different thing.
The new King Kong on the tour is a different thing.
Skull Island, Scott Kong, Skull Island.
Yes, different scare actors.
And the City Walk Saga episode involving the King Kong, the King Kong sign.
Right. But here's the thing about Bruce.
Just in the news recently, Bruce is specifically I think some people are used to refer as like the one that finally worked like the the animatronic recently lifted preserved.
They found it.
I don't know if it's lost or is in a junkyard or something, but they restored the shark animatronic and it was lifted via crane into the soon to open Academy Museum in Los Angeles.
Wow.
Is that the scary one?
Is that the one that looks like the technodrome?
The shark, you mean?
No, no, the building.
The museum.
They've been building a museum that is so scary and Death Star-ish.
I think I know what you're talking about.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, it does.
And it's yeah, there's a giant.
The one main room is just giant empty space with pillars and each pillar is like this is Steven Spielberg's pillar.
This is Bob Iger's pillar.
Bob Iger's pillar.
I think it's whoever paid.
I think it was the angel investors or the advisory board or whatever.
Yeah, the Academy Museum looks a little bonkers.
Well, sounds like Bruce will be able to see Bruce in the next few years, maybe.
Hopefully we wish I well, you know, I mean, that's another like Santa Kong, of course, just makes me want to put Santa hats on everything.
I mean, Jaws didn't burn up in a fire.
Why don't they put a Santa hat on him when he pops up?
Yeah, strap. Yeah, he'll obviously have to have like it strapped to his chin and it'll have to be waterproof.
But maybe instead of the fin, it's a Santa hat float like you have a Santa hat on the fin.
How about that?
Oh, that's fun.
Oh, that's really cute.
It's shaped perfectly.
And instead of instead of those barrels exploding into fire, it explodes into candy.
Sure.
I mean, that sounds tough to.
Oh, yeah, that's true.
Snow, maybe.
Yes.
So snow explosion.
That's pretty good.
That's good.
And then the guy, the person doesn't die in the lake.
The scuba diver doesn't die in the lake.
They just get a stocking of.
Or they get like if you don't, you know, you don't want to maybe remake the animatronics.
So since he gets dragged into water, does he just he's invited to an exclusive underwater Christmas party?
That's good.
And you can maybe like say that the guide say that.
Yeah, yeah.
Looks like he's getting dragged to an exclusive underwater Christmas party.
All right.
Well, let's pull forward.
What is behind these candy exploiters?
What can you explain the red as the red is not blood?
It's I got that.
You just add a second jet that shoots up green color.
Oh, good.
So it's red and green and it's the spirit of the right.
OK, good.
Spirit of the season was liquid.
Liquid.
Yes, the two green and red.
I got to give credit to the I believe it was the Americana Memes account on Twitter who set up put a big Santa hat on the minion looking over looking down on the highway one.
I was one of one.
Yes, very good idea.
Yeah.
I mean, hey, it's been a hard year.
You imagine how much better we'd all feel these people who live with a view of that.
There's people who pass by it on a commute all the time.
If you were looking at a Santa minion every day, how much jollier would your stuck at home Christmas be?
Exactly.
Obviously, it seems like it's a very big thing.
But, you know, if you can dream it, you can do it is what I subscribe to.
So they could do it.
I mean, maybe it has to be more.
It can't be a cloth.
It can't be made out of cloth.
That has to be more of a piece like a plastic piece.
But yeah, plastic fiberglass.
But everything needs a Santa like Norman Bates Scare actor on the tram tour Santa hat.
Come on.
Like and he doesn't again, he can have enough to have a knife.
But maybe or maybe he has a knife and he has like a Christmas strudel that he has with him.
And he's like, does anyone want a piece?
He's like, yeah, yeah, yeah.
He's a oh, it's still a knife, but he's going to cut it up.
Right. He's going to cut the strudel up the Christmas strudel.
Yeah. Yeah.
He runs after the only my stipulation for all of these is that the Christmas specific exposition has to be fit in as quickly as possible.
It is anyone want a delicious Christmas strudel whipped cream or cool whip whipped cream or cool whip.
I have both.
That's great.
That's great. Yeah.
I mean, obviously, you don't want to lose the classic part of those those tram speeches.
But can they is it too dark?
Maybe. But you could say that subsequently right after that, that the the War of the World's plane crash was a Santa sleigh crash.
Yes. You put the you put the Santa sleigh in front of it and it gets broken and the present strewn about.
Could be all the same stuff, essentially.
And all right. And Santa.
Sorry, Santa is like Santa's there and he's alive and he's covered in blood and he's like trying to put all the presents back together.
And he's like, how he's here to yell at you.
Help me. Help me.
My sleigh crash.
Help. And he's trying to gather everything up to because like Christmas is going to be late this year.
I can still do it.
I swear.
Yeah.
And then you see any reindeer?
I found five of the eight.
The upcharge event then is you stop the tram there, you get out and you help him collect presents and put him in the sled and try to get the sled off the ground again.
OK, thank you for your help.
First things first.
You didn't see anything.
There is no one can prove there was eggnog in my blood.
I've been hammered for 2000 years doing this.
Never happened before.
I never even crashed into a bird.
I drive the sleigh better this way.
Oh, no.
Yeah.
More of this.
I have to say the the body-ness of Universal Parks, though, I am surprised that, you know, maybe it's too body when he with the tour guide was driving into the Santa Kong soundstage and is talking about like it's fake snow.
It's Hollywood snow.
We didn't go.
And I don't mean the nose kind of Hollywood.
You know what?
I usually around movie studio lots.
We're talking about a different kind of Hollywood snow.
That seems like evil tram voice might be the only universal character that could get away with that.
Oh, the stairs.
Yeah, the starway.
Yeah, the evil starway.
Sorry.
A character.
Different kind of snow.
When it gets you high.
Look, it's a wild ride.
But Francis Ford Coppola has remade his career multiple times and he's come back from the edge.
Godfather Coda.
Check it out.
Check out the Godfather Coda.
Death of Michael Corleone haunt house down in the lower lot.
Mission break.
Death of Michael Corleone mission breakout.
Coming to shutter.
A lot of different things there.
A lot of different subtitles, I feel like.
Yeah, just keep adding them on.
You know, it seems to me like the digital ones you could slide out a lot.
Like Transformers, just all of them as Santa hats.
Yeah.
And the walk around Transformers.
That's easy.
Do they do that?
They have to do that, right?
I got to look that up.
Oh, that's good.
You have Megatron say some Scrooge lines.
You know, these are not poor houses you can go to.
Yeah, Megatron should just speak in Scrooge lines.
A humbot.
Oh, that's good.
You're a figment of my imagination.
A crust of motor oil or some bad spark plugs.
I'm looking up Universal Christmas Transformers and they're just pictures of the regular ones.
So I don't think they've put Christmas Santa hats on them yet.
Did the show ever do like a Christmas special?
Oh, yeah, there was a Transformers holiday special, it looks like.
Oh, it has a comic.
I mean, that's cool.
Okay.
But, you know, animated would be better.
Right.
Blue.
Blue should have a Christmas, some sort of Christmas thing on.
The Raptor Blue, of course.
We all know.
I knew I just wanted to make sure everyone knew.
Blue from Jurassic World.
From Jurassic World, yeah.
Jurassic World.
On this show, we have to distinguish between Blue the Raptor and Blue 32.
It's a good point.
I didn't even think about that.
We have multiple.
Copperfield's friend.
Blues, yeah.
Yeah.
Competing Blues.
Blue, who is Owen Grady's beloved Raptor.
Right.
So, yeah.
Put a Santa hat on him.
What?
Fast and Furious Partiers, the very natural like car garage party dancers in Supercharged.
They all have, get Santa hats and like a punch bowl and white elephant gifts.
That would be fun if a couple in the background were like, oh, iTunes gift card, real creative.
I want to point out though, just in general about Santa Kong.
If you Google Santa Kong, this is looking like a somewhat popular phenomenon.
Like there are drawings of Santa.
This is a deviant art Santa Kong drawing of him in a very tight fitting that shows his fur off.
Quite frankly.
It's very muscular.
Yeah.
There's a shirt of kind of a Donkey Kong style.
I mean, I guess maybe this is Donkey Kong, but it's Santa Donkey Kong.
There's this, look at this.
This is cool.
This is like a kind of a display, Christmas display, and they have a giant Kong, probably a static figure, but it's got a Santa outfit on.
And you keep scrolling and there are a lot more of these.
So it's interesting that people think of, you know, this is sort of a fun little cute gingerbread like King Kong.
It's not like we take every character and Christmasify them.
So what is this marriage of King Kong and Christmas that seems fairly natural?
Right.
Is there something big and jolly like Santa?
I mean, he's not jolly, but he's right.
And here's the picture of him with the beard at City Walk.
So, yeah, I'm just wondering, yes.
Is there a movie we don't know about where King Kong dresses up like Santa?
I mean, that would have been in the results.
You would think.
Yeah.
Yeah. If there was like a Mystery Science Theater episode, that definitely would have like popped up.
But yeah, there is something.
Kong saves Christmas or something.
The marriage of it is perfect.
I mean, I think we're getting, aren't we getting a Godzilla Kong movie now that's going to be released on HBO Max the same day as the theater?
I believe that's coming next year.
Okay.
Yeah.
Well, maybe this maybe ties back to an earlier point.
If there isn't a King Kong Christmas movie and we want one.
And also, I do want more justification why the Santa Kong scenario is happening.
It's not enough for me to just tell me.
I think what the guide says before this experience starts is we're heading into a sound stage where one of the biggest stars in Hollywood is starring as Santa Claus in an all new spectacular.
What do you mean?
I want a convoluted story.
I want the most complicated justification for why he ended up dressed like this.
And do you think we could pow wow and figure this out?
Yes.
Okay.
My first thought is tied into the Santa Claus franchise, the Tim Allen Santa Claus franchise, which has ledged the lore of if Santa dies, essentially his killer becomes Santa Claus.
So, I mean, look, and Kong is a misunderstood character, a gentle character, but Kong really causes a lot of damage if, you know, he's unleashed.
So, Kong has to murder Santa Claus.
Mm hmm.
I see.
And become Santa Claus.
So Tim Allen gets murdered by King Kong in the movie.
You're saying it has to be a Santa Claus movie.
I thought maybe it was an accidental situation in the way that Tim kills Santa Claus.
Initially.
You're right.
That's probably where I initially was going.
But then just a premeditated murder might be funnier to me.
But maybe for a more family film, you're right.
It has to be like Tim Allen Santa Claus is a.
I don't know.
Does he imprison Kong?
Because that's usually what happens.
Kong gets taken in chains and then breaks free and like usually, you know, does a lot of destruction to the people who are imprisoning him.
Well, it could be that Kong has been captured and made to take into the North Pole to entertain the elves.
Oh, that's OK.
I like that.
That's good.
They'll be so amused.
They are so small and he is so tall.
Right.
But he's not meant to be.
He doesn't.
We know he's not supposed to be a sideshow.
That's that's you know, Kong needs to run free.
So it's safe.
Yeah, I think if Santa is an imprisoner of Kong, then I think, yeah, it's every bit of Kong's right to murder Santa Claus.
Right.
Can I I'm going to I'm going to toss out a different justification.
So for this, imagine Skull Island is just south of the equator.
So the seasons are flipped.
So around Christmas time, it would be summer down there.
You know, I do know.
So let's say Kong is just like, God, it's so hot.
I can't sleep.
It's so hot on Skull Island.
And I think it's so hot that I can't sleep.
It's just so hot on Skull Island.
And let's say he's just like, I got to find somewhere cold to sleep.
And he just starts heading north.
He just starts heading north, ends up at the North Pole.
Finally, it's like, now this is sleep and weather.
I'm going to lie down for a long winter's nap.
And then that's right when the Santa's workshop starts cranking, the factory starts pumping.
And he's like, I was so loud.
And he squats the whole thing.
And that's how he kills Santa Claus.
I like it.
I will say it's funny that your pitch contains at least from the sound of it,
45 minutes of a character trying to find a good place to take a nap.
That's a good portion of the film.
It's too hot.
I got to take a better nap.
The nap quality is really, really poor down here.
Well, you want a colder temperature to sleep in or else you're going to toss and turn.
Watch as King Kong has an epic quest to find the perfect napping place.
Will he find soft, soft snow that is as comfortable as a giant pillow?
See the student at HBO Max to find out.
Written and directed by Jason Sheridan.
So let's say some of the elves survive, all of the reindeer and Mrs. Claus.
And he has to deliver the toys and he's celebrating at the top of the Empire State Building
because for whatever reason they get delayed.
And New York City, he's like, I got to go to New York again.
And so he's at the top of the Empire State Building celebrating.
And she's in his hand saying, good job, good job.
And Kong is married to Mrs. Claus as well.
He has to marry her.
Part of the Claus.
Yeah.
But then they, of course, blow him away.
And he falls.
And they end the movie with Twas Christmas killed the beast.
And like whoever, whichever person in the military delivered the final shot to Kong's brain becomes Santa at the end.
Whoa.
And he's, yeah, he's a scary militant.
He's like Stephen Lang in Avatar.
So now you have to tease for like, what does it mean that this scary military man is going to be the next Santa?
Sergeant Santa.
Oh, man.
I'd like, well, I love a sequel that takes you in a completely different scenario where you only barely meet the character who then takes over the franchise.
And maybe this is sort of where the Jurassic World franchise is going, which is like, imagine if we could take Santa's technology and use it for military purposes in war.
Why we win every battle we ever fought.
That's right.
So this, this is a, I mean, we just used Kong to get us to just unlimited franchise, just to exploit the Santa Claus franchise.
I mean, you know, you'd have to like write the whole movie and link it, but you could using Santa Claus rules.
It's completely different types of characters.
Right.
If, if the, if Sergeant Santa was too militant and scary, then you did that.
The end, you find a way to hand it off to a little girl and then there's a cute five year old girl Santa.
You can take this into any genre you could ever want.
Right.
And that's great.
It is.
It is really great.
I assume they're, they should do something like that.
I'm assuming there's a eight seasons of a Santa Claus Disney Plus show Greenlit already.
Is that right?
That has to be coming.
That's probably right.
I mean, I think in the Godzilla Kong, like the current movie universe, you can, after Sergeant Santa, you can hand it off pretty easily to, I can't remember the actor's name from Stranger Things.
Finn Wolfhard?
No, no, she, she has the power.
Millie Bobby Brown.
She's in the Godzilla's.
Oh.
The current run.
So she, she like finds, let's say dead Stephen Lang or dead Stephen Norris or she accidentally causes.
Oh, I was just going to say, yeah, that's good.
But what if Godzilla kills Kong and becomes Santa then?
That's good.
Yes.
It'd be cool to have two, it'd be cool to have the like twin girls who summon Mothra.
If they're two Santas?
Twin Santa?
That's fun.
Yeah.
There's a lot of different options now for who can be Santa.
I mean, look, it's like the end of last Jedi.
Anybody can be Santa.
You know?
Yeah.
You want to make it populous.
Do you want to open and open?
Yeah.
I mean, you want Broome Boy to be Santa.
Broome Boy, Santa, sweep it up.
And then you go back to the George side and can a little midichlorian be?
Can a will be Santa?
Can there be, what if instead of one main Santa, there's billions upon billions of microscopic Santas?
Oh my gosh.
I'm sure George Lynch is making an experimental film about this exact idea right now in his garage.
He should just make them.
Like, just do them all.
How crazy would it be if Lucas just said, I'm doing it.
I'm changing every name.
It's just like, you know.
You mean he's making his Zan Stolo.
He just changes them all.
But yeah, yeah, just make his.
That'd be huge.
I think that's...
So you're saying he self produces like Billy Toppett.
You're talking like Billy, Billy Toppett formula.
I would like that level of production value as well.
Like a student film level, but made by George Lucas.
Because you know he saw these last three movies and he goes, that's not what happened.
That's not what happened.
He's the only one who knows what really happened.
And we might not like it.
Maybe no one likes what happens, but he's the only one who can really tell us.
But George could pick up a phone and like call Soderbergh.
It's like, can you come up here with your briefcase of iPhones and give me a hand?
Because like Soderbergh can give him a hundred dollars.
He just finished two movies today probably.
I probably, yeah, they got this Meryl Streep boat thing that's coming out.
Very exciting.
It's always on the cutting edge.
Oh, can I spoil?
Can I spoil what the name of the child is?
Grogu.
Oh, sorry.
It'll be like a month at this point.
I was making a joke.
I thought you were going to like spoil the end of Logan Lucky or something.
We haven't talked about Grogu.
I like Grogu a lot actually.
But there's a, not has not been on the show.
I don't hope he doesn't mind me saying this.
Charles Ingram is the theory that George named Grogu.
Oh.
That feels George-esque.
Yeah.
He's like Dave Fuller is like, I need a name for the child.
And George is like, um, Grogu.
Cool.
I don't know.
That's just a made up.
That's not a real, that's not sourced anywhere, but I like, I love the thought of it.
Like him back channeling like names like by his pool.
He didn't even have to think about it.
He didn't even have to brainstorm.
He just knew Grogu.
Grogu.
His name is Grogu.
Or they asked him and he, his phone, he accidentally landed on his phone and it, and it picked up.
Like George, we need you to tell us then.
And he was asleep.
And he just muttered, Grogu.
Okay.
Very good, George.
The genius.
Yes.
Perfect.
Anyway.
George fell asleep against his Academy Museum pillar again.
Someone's got to get him out of here.
Has George ever dressed up like Santa?
Oh my God.
He's very Santa-esque.
There has to have been a Lucasfilm party where he dressed up like Santa.
George Lucas Santa Claus.
People have done, no, no one's done art of this really.
People have dressed up adult Grogu, AKA Yoda.
That's, that's when you know, it's really like fully taken over when Yoda becomes adult Grogu.
Right.
I'm seeing fan art of George's Yoda.
I'm seeing fan art of George's Modoc, the Marvel character.
That's just a giant head and tiny arms and feet and legs.
Oh, oh, wait, wait.
I am seeing a little Photoshopped.
Here we go.
It's not completely what we want, but it's close here.
See right here.
Well, that's pretty terrible.
It's bad.
That is Lucas's head comped the wrong way into Santa's sleigh.
There is a guy here who's dressed like George Lucas getting a picture with Vader.
So we're just change it.
The other let's go the other way and change up the holiday tradition.
Can we go make Christmas wishes on George Lucas's lap?
Oh, my gosh.
The malls dress up as George Lucas.
Same beards.
You just have to buy a lot of like, you know, striped patterned shirts and blazers.
I think that would be yeah.
I mean, do they have to be Star Wars wishes or they can be any sort of like present wish?
Hmm.
I guess.
Yeah, that's a good.
Maybe you don't limit it.
Maybe it can be any wish.
For sure.
If you want a Star Wars toy, yeah, we go talk to or I guess you could also ask for like
American graffiti dolls or something.
Yeah.
Red Red Tails.
Tails.
Indiana Jones.
Howard the Duck.
T H X 1 1 3.
Or just will or you just want like details about the wills, which in case you don't know,
George was going to make seven, eight, nine about these mic like ultra microscopic beings
called the wills.
I'm still a little unclear on what they were, but they were like the micro by like, I don't
know, microbial world or something is what he said.
Smaller than midi chlorine.
I believe that's right.
Lake.
And midi chlorines are back on the Mandalorian.
So very excited about that.
Wow.
I gotta get caught up.
Big Rosario Dawson fan.
So happy to see her popping up.
In every part of the Buffalo, they're tying it all together.
Well, I mean, it may is a good way.
We clearly want Lucas to be doing more and to be active and doing something.
Can we convince Lucas to tell the Santa story instead and just give him like we're just
spitballing here.
But the starting point is King Kong takes over as Santa due to the Santa Claus.
We'd bring that concept over from the Santa Claus franchise.
It remains to be seen if we're going to use Jack Frost or not.
But, you know, feel free to just put the wills on top of it.
It's really all up to you.
Yes.
We got to get to George.
It feels like George has a lot of time on his hands.
So, yeah, come on, George.
Let's do this.
I got a trilogy of Santa and potentially King Kong related films.
Come on, George.
Make him in your garage.
Make it as we said, Billy Toppett quality.
Yeah, I would love it if George just in 2020 discovered like mumble core and just made a
movie of like semi improvised movie of like, oh, it's young people in the city trying to
make it.
And they're just figuring it out.
When will he make the American Graffiti sequel trilogy with the same characters?
You know, has he talked about that?
Oh, that would be fun.
Or the 80 year old seeing their kids and then but then also going backwards and seeing their
parents.
Right.
Mm hmm.
80 year old Harrison Ford drag racing.
Well, that sounds good, actually.
Yeah, I'm on board because there was an American Graffiti sequel.
Yes.
Yeah.
More American Graffiti.
Yes.
Was there a big I don't think there was a big chill sequel.
I think you need to tie in the boomer verse.
I need I like the boomer verse.
Does that include then what's the Alan Arkin, the Kaminsky method?
Yes, Kaminsky method is in the boomer verse for sure.
I think that's all part of the it's all part of the boomer verse.
Yeah, we should really detail a map of where it goes.
And yeah, which then the timeline where each movie and TV show lands.
You got to get an Albert Brooks in their conception.
I'm putting together a team for my next movie and it's Albert Brooks from real life or modern
romance, I guess, whichever.
Either way.
Yeah, geez.
There's so many great extended universe ideas here.
So many great holiday overlays here.
We want Santa hats on everything.
I want them to do it even though we can't go to the parks.
I want them to now more than ever go put Santa hats on characters, take pictures of them,
put them on Instagram.
Let us know that the robots are safe.
We want to know that they're OK, like that they aren't just like rusting into disrepair
All of these robots are just sitting stagnant, at least in Los Angeles.
Mm hmm.
Yes.
Please show us pictures.
Obviously, like on the jingle cruise, they did a little of this, but we want it expanded
and then like, oh, yeah, let's let's go other holidays, too.
Let's do a little more.
I guess I think this will still be a tease for a very soon episode.
Let's get a little more maybe Hanukkah representation also as well.
I know there's not as it's a Santa hat is a very iconic thing of the season, but maybe
some characters holding a menorah, you know?
Yeah, absolutely.
One of the pirates instead of a gun is holding a menorah at the end of the ride,
sewing in a menorah around that's on fire.
So do that.
Yeah.
Are there any structures that would make sense to turn into giant dreidels?
That's a very good question.
I'm not prepared at all for this, but I'm going to try to pull one out here.
It's gone, but the horizon's building.
Yeah.
I feel like that's easy.
Mm hmm.
Yeah.
What what like goes down at the bottom?
Right.
With a point.
Yeah.
I mean, maybe.
Hmm.
I'm trying to think here.
You could do it with.
What's like a square building?
I guardians the guardians towers.
You could maybe sort of suggest it because they're sort of in a tall shape.
And you put like, you know, you do those projections like they do those projection shows in France,
and they can make sort of whatever they want on the building temporarily turned it into.
Yeah.
Well, and you do those.
You go up and down in there with Monica music playing.
That's pretty fun.
Right.
So then.
Yeah.
And then change.
She like a character into the mench on a bench or something, you know, whatever.
More mench on a bench representation.
Yeah.
Into the parks.
That does feel like something that would end up in six flags.
Oh, yeah.
We've aligned with mench on a bench media.
Mench on a bench is like the biggest IP they have other than Looney Tunes.
I guess the DC characters, but then it's more relevant currently in a way.
Yeah.
Yes.
I think that's right.
Kids go nuts.
Wow.
It's mench on a bench.
Seeing mench on a bench with the six flags man would be just below people's minds.
Oh, you talk about meetups and team ups and putting together a team.
Right.
So maybe that maybe, you know, Mr. Six gets up and starts dancing and having a lot of fun.
Maybe that's what finally propels the mench off of the bench.
Gets them up and start dancing.
Yeah, I think that's good.
Is the mench a rabbi?
I know this is that we're probably wrapping up, but is this is is he an actual rabbi or is he just Jewish and he's a mench?
Just a good man.
Yeah.
Is he actually a hmm.
I don't know.
I don't have it.
Well, he's wearing, you know, like the I don't I'm not going to.
I'm going to use the wrong words, but you know, he's got like the the drapes over and forgive me for not knowing the term.
I don't know the term either.
I apologize.
But I see this the mench on a bench is a talking rabbi doll.
Yes, he is a rabbi.
Okay.
Mench on a bench has a bunch of friends also.
I don't know how we have we not talked about this before, especially considering that it's born from Shark Tank.
And I think one of you is a shark tank.
Oh, wow.
If not both.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Look, he's got he's got a blue.
Oh, my God.
Whoa.
Moose with a stuffed blue moose and his antlers are all Menorah lights and a little dog who's got, you know, the little like like patch at the spot on his eye.
And one of them is a Menorah.
Wow.
Yes.
And I believe that's a Maccabee behind him.
Oh, wow.
A warrior.
Oh, yeah.
Star Dale's David shield.
The moose has Menorah antlers and the dog has the dreidel eye patch.
Yeah.
Wow.
We got a we this is this is an episode, obviously.
I. Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Okay.
Most of the men I didn't know his name wasn't mentioned a bench.
Most of the mench mitzvah moose ask papa is his name.
Ask Papa.
Wow.
Good advice.
Yeah.
Hannah, the Hanukkah hero.
I guess that's the Maccabee dreidel dog.
Dreidel dog.
Wow.
Oh, boy.
This cuddly dreidel spotted Dalmatian is the perfect gift.
Plus, his special bandana even has a secret pocket to hold your dreidel.
Wow.
Dreidel dog has a pocket.
No, all of his spots are dreidels.
Oh, yeah, you're right.
Yeah.
Wow.
Are we are we rubes for not knowing?
Is this is the entire audience completely already in love with the mench on a bench gang?
Right.
And we and we just this seems like the most obvious thing in the world to all.
No, I think the mench on a bench verse is pretty new.
I feel like it was a success after they got the initial shark tank buzz and they've expanded.
Also, the dreidel dog mentioned a bark mitzvah.
Oh, it did.
And I mean, I just.
Oh, wow.
It did.
This is great.
This is all great.
Well, guys, I think we found our topic for next holiday season.
I think so.
On a bench verse.
It's nice to know.
It's nice to have a foot in the door this far out.
Yeah.
You know, yeah, let's start thinking about Hanukkah 2021 and wrap up this holiday season
of 2020.
You survived podcast, the ride, the second gate.
I can't wait.
Oh, my God.
We're going to we have a whole year to learn about all of our new best friends.
Yeah, I hope they make up new.
Yeah, I hope new characters become introduced into this universe as well in the next 12
months.
They could fit a lot in.
Yeah.
Yeah, that'll this will serve as a time capsule when there were only the six or whatever it
was.
Which which shark was it?
Because I remember this is one where they laughed.
They scoffed at first.
This is the silliest thing ever.
And then somebody saw the sparks and heard the sails and they knew that there was something
to mention on a band.
Now it's like one of the most famous shark tank products.
Yeah, I don't know.
I guess Jason's the watcher.
I only have seen a little bit of shark tank.
Was it was it Mr. Wonderful?
Wait, I found it.
It is a this is a Robert and Laurie Jam.
This is a Robert.
Wow, that's a powerful team.
Yeah.
Two of my favorites.
I'd put them in the in the top half in the shark.
Yes.
They certainly shot up the charts by the fact that neither of their spouses are being investigated
for boat homicide.
I don't know which one you're referring to.
I believe it was is Kevin O'Leary, Mr. Wonderful.
Yeah.
Yeah, I think.
Oh, no.
Mrs. Wonderful.
Yeah, this is wonderful.
Allegedly, allegedly.
OK, well, we'll also revisit that case and see where it's at next year.
See if there's been any leads.
But oh, boy.
So it's something to look forward to.
I hope something to look forward to next holiday season is the ability to see people or do anything.
That would be that would be nice.
It looks like that will be the case.
I'll say that.
I believe I believe so.
We have to hope so.
But in the meantime, as we close out podcast the ride for the year, I probably said some of this on another episode.
But thank you so much for and you, especially the second gate listeners.
Thanks for sticking around and supporting us all year and causing us to have a lot of fun.
Some of the only fun, I think, that any of us have right.
Probably are forced.
Yeah.
So thanks for giving us a reason.
It's yeah.
Hey, I was going to say it's been a great year.
I don't know if that's accurate, but we've done our best.
Content wise, we've done some good stuff and there's been a great I would think there's some great stuff that way.
But as far as the year itself, I would never ever put great and year together talking about this year.
Yeah, I think I've been thinking about my son being born this year and how I'm going to be filling out forms his whole life that say 2020.
Wow.
The second two, I'm just going to be like shaking like having flashbacks.
Maybe you just end all over the paper.
Can you just say like, say he was born a year earlier?
Can I? Yeah.
Can I cheat?
I mean, people do that for.
Oh, yeah.
I guess it'll be weird because it'll be like a year ahead of all the kids in school.
Well, it's you know, like, I mean, like old people start switching the years up for unknown reasons.
Hey, famously David Brenner lied about his age for years.
We all know that story.
Famously.
We all famously.
Comedian David Brenner, who he was lying like by five to seven years, I think, because he when he was a comic, when he was a young comic, people thought he worried like he was too old.
So he lied and said he was younger.
Oh, that's like Laurence Fishburne lied about.
He was too young.
He lied about his age, right?
To get an apocalypse.
There's also another thing I've been meaning to bring up on podcast.
Right. There's also a debate about how old Charo is.
Some people think Charo like there's a 10 year discrepancy.
There Charo's like 80, like 85 or 75.
I think she's older just because of how long she's been around.
But, you know, this is another controversy that I've been reading about online.
Some of the teases of what will.
Here's what's on tap for next year.
How old is Charo really?
Follow Charo on Twitter, though.
She gives a lot of updates still to this day.
And it's fun.
Mike, you've got me thinking now because I was about to bring up that.
Like I saw a lot of people saying the unofficial anthem for 2020 is the Mountain Goat song this year.
I'm going to make it through this year.
If it kills me, would love to hear a Charo cover of that.
Sure.
With the she plays flamenco guitar.
She's a brilliant flamenco guitarist.
So at the very least.
That sounds awesome.
Just do it on flamenco guitar.
Yeah.
So then we can end the year on a high note.
Only then we need you, Charo.
If I could, if I could get Charo to dub in the synthetic string flamenco strings I have on this theme for the second gate.
And Charo actually plays the do, do, do, do, do, do, do part of the song.
I think that would take it maybe to another level.
If we could debut a new, a revamped second gate theme done by Charo.
Done by Charo, which I assume most of the listeners know what we're talking about.
She'd have to do the five, four, three, two, one too, I think.
Oh my God. Yes.
Yeah.
This is actually probably not that impossible to do.
I wouldn't say so.
No.
I have a photo with Charo.
Do you?
Some odd thing.
I don't remember why.
Wow.
Sure.
I was just watching the longest, I know we're ending the episode.
I was watching a 15 minute clip of Desi Arnaz on the Johnny Carson Tonight Show where he's boring Bob Hope and Don Rickles with stories about Xavier Kuget and talking about Charo and how cheap.
Now I think listeners know, you know, we're hovering around 40% of the people in this story.
Yeah.
Bob Hope and Rickles, I think for sure.
And Arnaz, yeah.
But he, my God, he was boring these guys with how cheap Xavier Kuget was and that like Charo was trying to steal his money, he said.
And I was in heaven watching this garbage.
Kids today, all the kids are talking about Grogu.
Why isn't anybody talking about Charo?
Kuget.
Xavier Kuget.
Yeah, this is really where the kids head should be at.
Well, we'll get it.
We'll get kids head on heads on straight.
2021, we're gonna, we're taking it all back.
We're gonna set it all right.
Stay tuned here to the second gate in 2021.
Fun stuff in the works as always and Mention on a Bench in December 2021.
For all of us at Podcast the Ride.
Let's wrap this Europe and good night.