Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast is for family only.
If you ain't family, stop listening.
But guess what?
You're all family.
So grab the nearest helicopter that's as big as you
and hold on tight, cookie puss.
It's fast and furious supercharged
on Podcast The Ride or Die.
["Diamond City"]
2021, baby, Podcast The Ride.
The only theme park podcast where we live our lives
a quarter mile at a time.
And for those 90 minutes to say three,
three and a half hours, we're free.
I'm Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner here.
Yeah, Scott Gardner's here and I'm so happy
because my demand for the first episode
and for this topic was that Jason kick it off.
Cause I knew Mike and I would only be pretenders.
I knew we wouldn't do it right.
And Jason, you did it right.
You did it right, bud.
You did, thank you so much.
Mike Carlson also here.
I am here, yes.
And I want to say, Jason, you're not my friend.
You're my family.
Family, salute familiar.
Both you and Scott are not friends, you're family.
Well, we don't have friends, we have family.
That's right. That's how it goes.
So here we are, 2021, new year,
new season of Podcast The Ride.
What do we do?
Are we in season?
Do we do seasons?
I don't think we do.
I think it's just one big, we don't ask.
I don't know, let me do.
Yeah, so we, okay, not new season,
new year, new fun, new thrills,
still at home individually for now.
Yes, that part has not changed.
Doesn't mean we're not family, though.
Hey, with this holiday season,
families had to come together on Zoom,
and we're gonna be doing it for,
till November, when the fuck is this over?
Perceivable future.
Every article has a wildly different timeline
and answer for you.
We just better not be saying,
all right, baby, 2022, we're back.
Still Zoom, but it's pretty much gonna work.
We're really, they're vaccinating 150 people now,
a week in Los Angeles,
and we think they're gonna get it up to 175,
so we're gonna be on the list,
hopefully at the end of 2022.
Hopefully that doesn't happen, I'm just saying.
But we, who knows, who knows?
We're all gonna have to get jobs as doctors
just to get on the list.
Yes, okay, I don't wanna really derail
the whole episode by this, but I have wondered,
and I've thrown it out to you guys,
or floated the idea of, is there an opportunity
for me to use my checking abilities
to get the vaccine early?
I don't know that there is yet,
but I've seen different people go like,
hey, we wandered into that CVS,
and we just got a vaccine,
because they were running,
like the fridge was gonna,
it was gonna go bad in the fridge, essentially.
So they were just like, they saw five people,
and they go, hey, you want these vaccines?
Because we gotta get them now before they go bad,
and people got them.
So I was like, is there a way I can get on,
in the same way that I'm on PS5 sales tracker
that knows when a PS5 goes on sale,
is there a vaccine tracker Twitter account
that will send me alerts, and that'll say,
the CVS in Palmdale has 12 vaccines,
you should head up there.
That's a good idea, because in Washington, D.C.,
a bunch of the giant supermarkets,
the giant brand supermarkets are like,
hey, if we have extras at the end of the day,
first come first serve for vaccines.
And look, I'm sure I said this on the story,
you always wait around.
I was in line to get free Rolling Stones tickets
when they played the Echo Plex, which is a tiny place,
and I left the line early, and I found out later
they were just handing them out to people on the street,
because there weren't enough people in line.
And I learned a valuable lesson that day,
you always just hang around.
This lesson might save your life now.
Yes.
Very valuable lesson.
So well, it depends.
We don't know what's gonna happen past these,
sort of the most important groups to get vaccinated,
and if beyond this initial point,
they start doing it via boarding groups,
then you might be, I don't know,
you might be in luck,
and I would like to be in your boarding group if possible.
All right, well yes, if it's boarding groups,
if it's like, yes, exactly like Galaxy's Edge,
or getting on Rise of the Resistance,
it'll be groups of eight, I think is the max.
Yeah.
And look, we've all got each other's passes,
we've all got each other's annual passes
in the useless Disneyland app.
We can all help check, we can get off Wi-Fi, use data,
because that's gonna be more reliable.
We're all on the same healthcare,
and the same healthcare app,
and it's all very easy to use and very not confusing.
Same dog shit covered California plans, sure.
I'm on some sort of dog shit California plan, I believe.
But yeah, so I will pledge,
if there is a checking element to the vaccinations,
I will help us all get them.
But I don't know that there will be.
Yeah, yeah, but that's certainly your best hope,
it's all our best hope.
Yeah, we hope checking is possible.
Yeah, we'll see where this goes.
But you know, a tough year last year,
obviously, hopefully this year ends up a little brighter.
You know, and I think family has helped us get through it,
I think, and that includes you, the podcast,
the Ride family, you're not just part of our crew,
you're part of our family.
Now, of course, family, you know, still bickers sometimes,
you don't always get along,
and that's sort of what being part of a family is all about.
And with that, there's a new format
that we're going to introduce for 2021,
a new type of episode,
and this requires you, the podcast, the Ride family,
and the, well, I don't know, you know, Mike, this is your idea,
do you want to introduce us to this new episode format?
I'm just going to say the one word that will be,
I think, the title of the episode,
and I think you'll know what we're getting at here.
Gripes.
Because from time to, gripes,
from time to time on social media, I will see,
oh, so-and-so didn't like this rider,
they had a bad opinion, Jason didn't like, hmm.
I'm just trying to say, I'm not sure.
Yeah, I'm a pretty easy mark.
Jason likes everything, except for the Frozen ride,
and Epcot for some weird reason.
Okay, wait, he doesn't like the Frozen ride,
and he didn't like the Avengers Infinity War.
He likes every other Marvel movie,
but he doesn't like Infinity War
because it made kids too sad, he said.
I didn't, I also did not like
the West Coast Customs roller coaster
at Six Flags Magic Mountain.
Insane.
Yet another roller coaster trying to kill me.
So there's three things Jason doesn't like.
He didn't like walking through
the mostly abandoned Margaritaville complex, that was one.
No, I didn't. Four, four, four.
We've got four.
Can we get five?
Can we think of a fifth thing Jason doesn't like?
I mean, I've had some bad treats at theme parks.
There's definitely been some bad, like, stiff brownies,
some stale brownies and stuff.
Stiff brownies?
Stiff brownies, wet quesadillas at Margaritaville, you know?
Soaking wet quesadillas.
But is it on purpose wet, or is it?
Because sometimes you get a wet burrito and it's very good.
But if it's a wet quesadilla and you didn't order that,
and it's just like wet with water.
Wet quesadilla makes no sense.
It's too flat. There wouldn't be anything left.
That's not, you wouldn't purposefully order a burrito.
You got a lot of the substance.
All right, that's fair.
But yeah, I'd, well, I'll put that on my own list too.
I don't like wet quesadillas either.
OK, fine. Wet quesadillas.
Yeah, OK. If it's accidentally wet,
if somebody's made some sort of an innovation in quesadilla making
and they figured out a way to make a wet quesadilla,
I'm interested. But yes, if it's just wet, I'm that's on my list as well.
I also don't care for a stiff brownie.
I'm anti-stiff brownie.
I like a nice, soft, chewy brownie, not stiff.
Yeah, I mean, I like the corners.
I like the burnt corners. I'll do that.
But like, you know what I mean.
So what are we? What's great?
What we're getting at here is that, you know, say
Jason was a listener of the podcast and he heard me say, you know what?
I love eating a good stiff brownie.
I like it when it's stale. I like it when it's hard.
I want it to feel like it's some sort of a like a paperweight in my mouth.
I like that. He would say, OK, I have a gripe with you, Mike.
And then he'll there'll be a you'll see it.
We'll put it online and you would write into an anonymous prompt.
Jason Sheridan would say he's but he's anonymous.
I'm getting confused. He would say, Mike, I don't like when you praise stiff brownies.
And then I will see that.
And then we will respond to these gripes on an episode.
Yes. To talk to like talk it through.
Maybe either we'll get defensive or we'll say, you know what?
Maybe you're right. Maybe I've been too hard on stiff brownies
and I should reconsider them.
So we're hoping this opens up an interesting dialog.
We can chat about the different things.
And we also get to see maybe there's one thing that I always say
I don't like or like that everyone in the audience thinks I'm wrong about.
So we'll see sort of take the temperature of the audience to see exactly
if we're who if we're all in line together or maybe one of us has a really radical opinion.
Has there been some take that is not a hot take in a good way?
That's a that's a wrong take a cold take.
Is there some you know, is there a piece of information that we got wrong?
And you know that we we got it wrong.
We heard a little of this recently.
We're talking about we were talking about Dollywood and saying how it's hard
so hard to get to and isn't it in a dry county?
And somebody was like, enough is enough.
Guys, you are wrong about all this.
So things like that are helpful.
It's nice to be corrected.
It's a little bit of a correction segment, I think possibly, too.
But if it's just, you know,
yeah, there's something that we say over and over, we disagree with.
Or you want us to reconsider.
One thing is, did we do an entire park or a ride and we left out some aspect
or something that matters to you?
And we skipped over it brazenly and you want us to put a spotlight on it.
That's a gripe.
Right.
We talked I talked about like doing like a like lost and found idea on the Patreon.
We haven't done that.
Maybe that is the way to do it.
You do it under gripes.
Do we lose something in the past with a topic?
It's time for us to find it and and we can do it via your gripes.
Right. We can do a lot via your gripes.
Is I think what we're realizing, especially even now.
Now, keep the gripes.
Don't let's not make them maybe personal attacks.
But I mean, maybe if your gripe is like, look, like you've had the same haircut
for like seven years, I think you would look good with a crew cut or something.
As long as you spin it at that in a positive way, I'm not going to be upset.
Yeah. Keep it clean.
Keep it nice.
Although I got a gripe, if one more person sends us that Pixar
named the podcast thing, the guy with glasses in that meme looks like shit.
So I know if I get that one more time, I'm throwing this MacBook out the window.
No one in that is like us.
I don't understand.
I don't understand the meme.
I get that there's like three dudes
and like white dudes who do pocket, but like.
But then within that, how is that us?
I don't know. Well, like it's Al.
Al's from Al's Toy Barn from Toy Story 2 is in there.
There is not an Al among us.
That's not that's not right.
Yeah, Jason, if Jason, you're obviously responding
because you believe people are calling you Al.
I don't think you're Al.
I know. I don't think you're Al at all.
I mean, Al, if anyone's like Al, it's me.
I have all these goddamn toys behind me.
And you don't and you sometimes forget the lesson that toys are to be played
with and not stored forever, although you do take them out of the box.
You don't leave them.
You don't align with stinky Pete's philosophy.
I do not know stinky Pete's philosophy.
There was one time when I was moving some stuff around
and Lindsay walked in and she goes, you like touching the toys, don't you?
And I went, I do. Yes.
Got to let him breathe.
I wasn't touching like Donatello's penis or anything.
I was just like holding them and placing them and putting them around.
That's what she meant.
I wasn't like caressing his turtle cheek or something.
One of those where you give us the fodder along with the statement.
You're as with the foot stuff.
Saying it.
I was like, oh, this is a fun little anecdote.
I'll tell. And I was like, oh, now I'm opening up myself to like
the fact that I'm like molesting my toys as I as I play with them.
Mike likes touching the toys.
He likes taking his socks off in the log in the in the stiff brownie log.
And the stiff brownie log.
You know, I think we've at least maybe we're like it's
I'm already feeling good about this episode.
We've we've started a couple new things this year.
Is that I like I'm sexual with my toys.
And that Jason hates stiff brownies.
So we've got some new new things to play with in this upcoming year.
And I'm looking for it because I'm just going to make a soundboard of my voice
that just plays the the words OK, or not looking for notes.
And I'll just I'll jump back and forth between those two.
That's it. No further response on these grapes.
If I can figure out how to clip that pop song from a few years ago
where the chorus is just I don't care.
I love it. I love it.
I don't care. Yeah.
I don't care about your grind.
And maybe I think since the least resistant to gripes,
he doesn't like so this will be funnier.
Actually, you know what? I take it back.
Be as rude as you want to Jason.
OK, well, look, just because we haven't gotten a chance
to see our families or take a general meeting in a while
and we're just craving criticism, doesn't mean you have to be mean.
All right. Don't be mean to Jason.
That's the we're still good boys.
These are gripes, but we're still good boys.
So be nice. But if there's been some burning opinion, if you've had it for you,
we've been doing this podcast for a couple of years now.
And if there's something from episode two that made you mad
or just want to correct us on set us straight,
there's a lot of things that gripes could be.
So we've set up a Google form
that asks you if you have any gripes and you can put the gripes anonymously.
It's it's really like a little comment box, a suggestion box.
We'll put that in the link to this episode and we'll also tweet it out.
You'll you'll we'll make sure that you you find the gripes page.
And yes, we said it's anonymous.
If you want to put your name, feel free if you want us to associate you with this gripe.
But if you just, you know, if you want anonymity in a voting way, then feel free.
This also is not a requirement, but I was going to throw this in as something
that I think that would make us for me, it would skip a gripe to the front of the line
just because I would enjoy it.
You know, like with Jeopardy!
answering the form of a question, I think it would be nice
if the gripes started with the phrase, yeah, I got a gripe, all right.
So if you start your gripe with that, yeah,
I got a gripe, all right, Scott, your your Rex is overrated, whatever it is.
I just I think that I think that's a nice piece of the flow and I'd enjoy reading that.
So but up to you.
Yeah, I think that, yeah.
If your gripe is that you hate that and you don't want to
don't dictate some phrase to me, then that's a fair gripe.
Mm hmm.
I yeah, use that.
I mean, I think that, yeah, as long as we can do a little voice,
we're always going to be a little happier to do anything.
As you if you listen to the show, you know, anytime we can do a voice,
we all like to do it ad nauseam.
This is very true. Yeah.
So, yeah, give us the chance to do a little voice
and it'll cushion the blow of the gripe that is is coming.
So podcasts are at gripes and we'll yeah, we'll collect those and then put them up.
Probably as a Patreon episode.
I don't know, at some point the next month or something.
Yeah. Yeah.
So we'll brace for gripes, bracing for gripes.
And speaking of gripes, fast and furious supercharged.
Oh, man.
Better way to ultimate gripe.
The ultimate gripe.
We know I got to say, I watched one of those YouTube channels that like,
you know, does stuff about theme park history at all.
And one of them was laying it on a little thick about.
I thought the same thing.
Yeah, I don't I don't even know which one, so I won't call them out.
But yeah, I have a call out.
I know. Yeah, calm down.
But, you know, it fit the but we're trying to think how to start the year.
And we were saying, well, like a bigger one.
But of course, bigger ones, you know, we're trying to do this dance
where there's so many bigger attractions that we would love to do in person.
As we've now declared, we're going to do with the country bear jamboree
or, you know, this live shows we'd like to do.
What's a big attraction that we can let live in the awful morass of the zoom era?
I say fast and furious supercharge.
Let's hit the nitrous and kick off this year.
Right. That's how we roll.
As as Don Omar Buster rhymes,
wreak the villain and Jay Doe what's saying.
Oh, yeah. Oh, the whole gang.
Hell, yeah.
This is not we're not putting the Fast and Furious franchise
in this gripe category.
I have not seen all full disclosure.
I've not seen all of them.
It is on my list to watch all of them this year.
At certain point, I know they're very fun.
They're insane.
But we don't.
The ride itself is going into the gripe column here.
Not. Yeah, that's important to clarify, I think, because, yeah,
you don't want to be like the cultural snob who's these films that are.
Yeah, I think they're they're fun people like them.
People have a blast going to them when they open up.
And I it's just what they ended up doing with it.
Is. Yeah, I think.
Cause the reckoning at Universal.
I think it did.
I think it impacted what they're going to do for the future.
I think that's 100 percent right.
And I I rewatched the first one last night.
I'm going to rewatch them all now because I've watched them at like
half on USA, half on like an airplane.
And like they are very fun.
And I would go so far as to say I read one
like a review of them once of like
these are kind of more fun Avengers movies,
like especially when they get to five, six, seven
and they get to the spy stuff and all like it's like,
yeah, these are really fun.
Like I don't know.
The early ones are fun in their own way.
The middle ones are fun in their own way.
It's just wild.
And then they've retconned stuff like the watching order.
The movies is technically one, two, four, five, six, three, seven, eight,
because they retcon the order that they go in.
The character Han is technically the same character
from Better Luck Tomorrow that that actor plays and Justin Lin directed.
It's so wild.
The mythology of these movies.
Where does Hobbs and Shaw fall into the chronology?
Hobbs and Shaw, I think, happens directly either between seven and eight
or right after eight.
Oh, characters come back from the dead.
Like comic book logic applies, which is awesome.
Like it's so fun.
Which sort of happens in the ride a little not dead, but there's a, you know,
I mean, we'll get to it, but there's it doesn't really fall on the timeline
of the movies super well.
They have to nudge some stuff.
Right.
So, yeah, so we've just set that aside.
The movies are good.
Yeah, you know, here we go.
Absolutely.
And so so the idea of there there being
attractions of these of these films makes a lot of sense for something
that we're doing for a topic that we're doing in the near future.
I was trying to figure out, like, what are some of the biggest properties
that don't have an affiliated theme park attraction?
And in looking at what are just like the highest grossing film,
I just haven't looked in a while.
What are the highest grossing films?
And especially when you when you look at a list and like, all right,
how many franchises, you know, take over seven, eight slots in that list.
Infest and Furious is way up there.
Just like makes so much sense on paper for them to do something,
for them to exploit this in the theme parks somehow.
And when the first that it came up, one of those theme park
review videos reminded me that Fast and Furious came up as a rumor
when they took out the Back to the Future ride that they said, like,
this space is going to be used maybe for Simpsons or maybe for Fast and Furious,
which I think people were maybe happier with Simpsons because, you know,
probably if you're a big Badger the Future fan, you also like the Simpsons.
Fast and Furious is maybe less guaranteed that you.
Well, and around that time, Fast and Furious was not the worldwide sensation
that it became once they started just shoving people in there.
Just that's true.
And like the Rock and John Cena like them.
And yes, they thumb.
Yeah, you're right. It would have been weirder at the time.
Would have felt more akin to let's just make everything about
Brendan Fraser, mummy for a while.
Like, like, is this really going to I mean, those are good rides, obviously.
But, you know, I've made the complaint that there was a time at Universal Hollywood
where there were like three things based on that mummy.
And like that seems like a lot.
So, I don't know. Yeah, it seemed weirder at the time.
Now, of course, it makes sense to do an attraction.
But as we've said before, I think we said this before.
If you're going to do a ride based on the movies about fast cars,
would it not make sense to make it a ride involving fast cars?
Hmm. Speed, literal, actual speed, literal speed.
Yeah. But when one of the movies has the word drift in the title,
and you want to give us the opportunity to do a drift instead of like
sit between two IMAX screens.
Yeah, you would think like my first thought would be like, oh,
could they do some crazy like test track Fast and Furious ride? Yeah. Yeah.
And they obviously they could do that.
But like Cars Land, the Radiator Springs racer should be.
Fast and Furious ride, that should be the scope of a Fast and Furious ride.
Little dark ride, you see all your friends, you see Dom,
and then you have a fun, crazy race at the end.
Yeah, absolutely.
That's the plus up right that you just fixed it immediately.
Right. It takes up a lot more room.
But with the amount of money the Fast and Furious movies have made,
I don't think that that's crazy to devote that much space to the franchise.
No. Well, and here's here's the situation, I think,
because this was sort of shoehorned into,
if you don't know the full scope of the of Supercharged,
it exists as well.
You know, I'll just read off of the Wikipedia because I thought this was phrased
accidentally brilliantly. Fast and Furious Supercharged
is an attraction at Universal Studios Hollywood, Universal Studios Florida,
and was canceled at Universal Studios Beijing.
After the response to Florida, it became a defunct attraction
before it was ever an existing attraction.
So it is one of those in the long tradition of Universal
rides that is a freestanding ride in Florida,
but started as a stop on the tram tour.
And in fact, for a while has been the, as they put it, grand finale
of the tram tour, which was sort of missing like the big kick
at the end. This replaced the literal space where they they had the
the mummy tunnel and one of the many mummy things they had.
You sat in a weird tube that twisted you around, and that was the end of the tour.
So the desire to kind of go out with a bang on the tram tour makes a lot of sense.
And this thing was clearly based on the initial
good response to the King Kong
screen attraction that's kind of midway through the tram tour.
Yeah. And that brings up a couple of good points, Scott.
One, why does this one get so much more flack than the
reign of Kong at Islands of Adventure?
Is it just because Kong is more endearing to us
and there's a big animatronic at the end and there's a lot of fake rock work?
Animatronic helps a lot.
Yeah. And then you actually like go somewhere.
That little that little outdoor path is does a lot for you, even though it's very
short, it feels like they did more to make this its own fleshed out attraction,
to make Kong its own fleshed out attraction than they did Fast and Furious,
where they just it felt like they just kind of copy pasted the tram
show, except with like a weird Ghostbusters-esque
room with a refillable hourly employee talking at you before you get on the ride.
Yeah, it doesn't. It feels really this should maybe be a lesson.
And I'm not too imagineers people.
I'm sure there was much cooler ideas for it.
But like management, when it comes to just a little bit,
goes a long way in regards to to to Kong versus Fast and Furious in Florida.
Because it's like it's just the difference is a giant monkey head
and then maybe like an extra scene like there's an extra scene, I think, on it
from the one from the tram tour version.
And yes, the exterior is like pretty cool.
Is there there's extra like there's extra video.
So, right. So, yes, just a little bit more goes a long way.
And then, yeah, Kong does not get the shit that Fast and Furious gets.
Well, what I was starting to say there was that, you know,
I definitely did this on the tram and was like a little underwhelmed.
But I certainly wasn't mad at it.
And I think it existing within the tram lets you cut some slack.
But when you install this as its own big, new freestanding attraction
years later in Florida, I think the expectation goes up.
And I think a lot of people were like, it's not just going to be the tram thing.
Right. I think I even thought, is it elements of that?
But then it's its own ride system that is more like radiator springs or something.
And no, no party buses.
Right. Yeah, yeah, I think we all assumed, oh, there's no way
they're just going to plug it in because, yeah, the tram tour is good.
Like, it's good. It's fine.
Oh, it's like we're kind of watching a movie and like there's a there's a fun
couple parts. There's a lot of like universal tropes of screens,
like where something hooks to you and there's like stuff like that.
But no, it's fine.
But there's a way they're going to just port this thing over.
But, you know, money.
I guess money at the time.
So and the desire to just get it in quicker, I guess, if it's just
if it's just the screen version.
And now, so well, and again, Scott, you brought up that these are like
the last two of these movies grossed over one billion dollars each.
So like, yeah, get them in the parks.
Yeah. So, yeah, I kind of get that.
But what an execution.
I mean, I remember doing the Hollywood one for the first time,
and I was like, OK, yeah, that kind of makes sense.
But yeah, that to do this,
the same thing in Florida exactly years later is so funny.
Really strange. Can we I mean, can we cliff notes?
And I ask you guys this because I don't think I can.
Can we cliff notes what it is?
I think our listeners know for the most part.
But can we like, how do you quickly explain what this is without getting into like,
OK, so then Toretto and like
Letty comes in.
Well, and FBI.
OK, well, I guess we'll start.
Let's start with the Hollywood one,
because the Hollywood one is has the element of like
the tram tour that it's got to deal with as well.
And this was not the first Fast and the Furious thing on the tram tour either.
When this opened, they closed the Fast and the Furious extreme close up
where they used two car shells on Kuka Arms
and they launched them at you and then the cars to dance to gasoline.
I was thinking about this.
Don't we all love that much more than the ride?
I do think it's cute.
I have a. I won't go that far.
Did you have to see it a lot?
Yes. And that was the I'm forgive me, I'm sure I'm repeating things, but I
this that debuted the summer that I started as a tour guide.
And I remember when they getting the I'm in the training program.
Cool. And I just get to go on the tram and this is my job.
And I was so excited and get to, you know, I did the do King Kong first.
And like, I just love being there no matter what.
And then you start going up the hill and then like, wait, what is this thing?
And it I just remember feeling so deflated the first time
and then thinking I have to do this many times a day.
And it's you know, if I was in a good mood on those things,
I would have a blast with it no matter what.
But if I was just not feeling the tram that day, I the part where I really died
was like, and that's why we're going to talk about picture cars.
And then you and then you pass by a bunch of like mediocre
like a little rascals go cart and and then you go into this weird little
the corral and then to
there's a lot of like just sound effects without anything corresponding.
Like, OK, bullets.
And then you hear bullet sounds and then cars sort of
fly at you slowly.
And the two the two lines that just crushed my spirit every single time.
And again, give it a how about a hand for our picture cars?
Carnage and karma.
Take a bow, boys.
And then they would do a little boop, which is like now I'm fond of now
that it's gone, I'm a little more fond of it.
I can see how that would grate on you.
But as somebody who would get to, you know, see the tour once a year,
twice a year, maybe.
So, yeah, basically, if in case you don't want to talk about on the tram tour,
the cars would sort of do like a trick for you, basically,
like they were peeling out and like going to drive at you.
And then there was like an explosion.
They flew out of an explosion and then like, you know, as if
flying right as if you're the POV of the camera and it stopped.
They stop right at the point where they would hit the tram.
Right. And then that's when you would say those lines, if you could.
By the way, I don't want to be too much on the spot, Scott.
But if you could just give us your you're feeling really good,
you're feeling optimistic from the tram tour.
Give us the best line reading you could have that moment.
The take a bow, boys moment.
You wouldn't say, all right, how about a hand for carnage and karma?
Hey, take a bow, boys.
And then what was the line? It was like,
you got anything else to show us?
Oh, yeah, it was it was a hey, got any other moves?
And then I got so lean.
And then they just kind of like spun around.
Yeah, a little bit.
The Cooke arms are the things they have the Harry Potter
Forbidden Journey right on that's like can move all around.
So they would just on these two arms, the cars would just kind of like
dance, but not really because they can't really dance.
Turn and spin a little.
And you could see their undercarriage and there's nothing in it,
that there's facades of cars.
It's a lot of really unflattering.
You're getting like upskirts of the cars, unflattering angles.
I do.
We think that Luigi's dance at Cars Land
was a reaction to this dance.
I was trying to or Luigi's whatever it's called, something of the dance.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, the issue is that there weren't enough like just two people dancing.
And look, you know, if you're if you're having a wedding or some event
and there's only two people on the dance floor, it's a little a little pathetic.
But you get a ton out there, a ton of little coops.
And now, you know, things are really happened.
The second one, the line that really destroyed the spirits was
that finishes and then you say, take that dancing with the stars.
Now, I don't care.
I don't care for that line.
No, take it.
OK, the show in general, like in who from the show is on
the tram, who's supposed to be offended and why?
Because they dance to.
Could I say that if I danced a little
and then say and I say, take that dancing with the stars?
I mean, we're going to whenever we do a full episode on this tram tour,
we'll break it all down.
But it is it is confusing because you
you should say like, oh, these two should be on dancing with the stars.
Like that should be like the way better.
There may have even been was it an alter?
Did it just occur to me that that you you make it something about
like like, boy, you know, I got another name for that.
Dancing with the cars.
Oh, that's even better.
Yeah, perfect.
It's I I don't obviously I did that job and I loved it.
So my my problem was never with the corniness of it,
because there's like classic corniness, there's the corniness of King Kong's
banana breath, then the shark was his lawyer.
If it's like caked in corniness, I kind of liked it.
But then dancing with the stars.
What I take that take that.
I was going to try to clip gasoline to play under the intro to the show.
But it's just it's very it's hard to compete with because it's so infectious.
Look, Jason, I don't want to this is going to make the audience sad.
And I wasn't even going to say anything.
But I had an idea to put to bring the soundboard back to this episode.
But I'm having a problem with the operating system
working with the program that I was using.
So there will not be any gasoline played intermittently on this podcast today.
I'm not saying, though, it's out of bounds for future episodes.
Now I will promise there will be an episode in 2021
where all of a sudden gasoline will just start playing
here and there. We least suspect that when you least.
Scott, that was your first summer working the tour.
And that was right around. I first started going regularly.
And I was out here doing internships.
I was living close by.
So I bought a pay. I bought an annual pass.
And I went a lot. I was very cool in college.
And so I probably saw that thing a lot and saw you a lot.
That's a weird thing, the possibility that you took a
a tram and it was my tram tram tour and then walked and got
Taco Tuesday at Rubio's up at City Walk.
Long fallen, long gone, fallen brother.
Boy, those are the days, huh?
Yeah. Back when you had somebody trustworthy in office like Bush.
George W.
There was nothing quite like driving a golf cart up to City Walk
and trying to get six people's orders of one dollar
taco combos with six things of coke
and then driving down the hill at an 80 degree angle.
Yeah, it's so steep, steep, narrow roads.
And like a deer could dart out in front of you.
Yeah, you're in a fast and furious situation.
I just Luigi's Rollicking Roadsters is the name of that ride.
I was I was going to call it Luigi's Lord of the Dance.
Is that something else?
Is that like a short or something?
Why do I have that in my head?
I mean, I know what Lord of the Dance is.
Yeah. Not sure. You think that's.
Yeah, no, it's not.
I just put that in. OK, that's not that's not a thing.
Should be, though.
I feel like that's a joke Maeder makes for the parents.
It's something something, you know.
Yeah. But anyway, we'll get to the we'll get to the
Rollicking Roadsters eventually.
That's yeah, we'll get to that anyway.
Back to Supercharged, which is, by the way, the name of both
the Hollywood experience and the Florida experience, despite some differences
at the Hollywood part.
As we said, it's part of the studio tour and it kind of starts
with the guide driving by ending Wisteria Lane.
And then they go some version of like, oh, weird.
There's a 1970s Dodge Charger.
That shouldn't be there.
Or like that's suspicious.
So thanks, Karen, I guess.
Car stock car in a in a nice neighborhood.
I guess that's all it takes for someone to call in security at the universal lot.
But also, it's a movie studio lot.
Yeah, there probably is a period perfect car that should be there.
It's a movie studio.
Why is that weird?
And I don't know, maybe one of the desperate housewives is hanging out
with some some young hotshot with a cool old car.
I don't know what the desperate housewives do.
Truly, I don't.
I don't know what the show is.
And it's weird that it's still like a big before the grand finale.
See where the desperate housewives lived.
They'll be back soon enough.
They have to be back.
Yeah, they have to be.
And they're more desperate.
They're young. They're like it's a prequel and they're more desperate than
when they were older even.
OK, they've all moved off the street because only Felicity Huffman
still lives on the street.
She agrees to do the reboot because she needs money.
And then it's the next gen.
It's the next gen of housewives.
Yes, they're passing the torch, proving that anyone can be a desperate housewife.
Anyone can be a desperate housewife.
Well, we remember at the end of the full of the series,
there was a little girl with a broom broom housewife sweeping up
and she was sort of looking off into the distance and realizing that she could be
a desperate housewife.
Should we add the addendum to the gripes that we will probably not respond
to the gripes if they're about new Star Wars?
Oh, yeah, we're not talking about news.
No, no, no. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We're not following. Oh, it's a trap.
Sorry. I, I thought it was very cool
during the seven and a half hour Disney investor call where they
thoughtfully announced the, you know, a young Muslim woman superhero,
very diverse cast.
And then very close to that,
Patty Jenkins shows up and goes, yeah, USA fighter pilots, number one.
That wasn't tone deaf after the last century of US foreign policy.
That was it.
And she was promoting a rogue squadron.
Just say you played the video game in the 90s.
What are you doing?
What is this Air Force buying half the budget for the movie?
We're not going to talk about this either on the gripes episode. All right.
We're not going to talk about any of that.
So we'll talk about Galaxy's Edge, though.
So Galaxy's Edge is a game, yeah.
But we're not going to talk about how every other live action
Disney movie has to have like an Air Force approved, like person
getting out of the cockpit.
They all have to be sort of partially funded by the CIA.
Yeah, they all have to be.
Lady and the Tramp had a subplot of about a CIA agent.
Just three Larson. Be very careful.
That's one of the jets that if it rains, it explodes.
That we spent 40 million dollars on.
So be very careful with what you do.
I don't know anything about this jet that explodes, but we don't have time for this.
We don't have time.
My gripe is that we don't have time.
We hey, look, we're dealing with an attraction where the FBI has got a role in.
Oh, FBI agent Novak shows up,
who I assume was a character from the movies and then is not is some guy.
Oh, I think he might be original to the ride.
Oh, OK. Oh, so we have to maybe pay attention to this
because it's if it's original ride, I'd be FBI agent Novak.
Because the Rocks character agent Hobbs works for the US diplomatic service.
And that's different than the organization that Mr.
Nobody Kurt Russell's character works for in the later movies.
OK, so they drive fast cars and they sometimes they steal things
and they have parties and but then but then Hobbs,
the rock is after them, but then joins them.
I'm a little fuzzy.
So here's the the the cliff notes.
The first three movies are about underground street racing.
The fourth movie where Vin Diesel and Paul Walker came back,
shifted more to be about like heist stuff.
And then it kind of treads the line for the rest of them from like heist
to then they get amnesty if they help Hobbs.
And then they kind of become like secret agent heisters slash street racers.
Which people like more like that.
These are maybe this is where it's really cooking the franchise.
Yes. And it kind of lets them do anything.
Like, I mean, Vin Diesel does like Spider-Man stuff with like old mustangs.
Like, it's crazy.
Yeah, that's good.
I mean, I'm very excited to watch all of these.
Finally, this year, because it sounds like good nonsense.
This is this one sort of stems the most from
is it fast? Five is a fast.
It's the one it's the one from 2013.
That's the one that they're sort of.
One from the most that might be
is that Furious Seven, the last Paul Walker one?
Not sure if he is the first rock one that they're mainly addressing.
Oh, that's five.
OK. And they're they're enemies at that point.
So, yes, six or around six or seven, they're allies. OK.
Also, no gripes about the fact that we don't know these movies that well.
Yes. Sorry. I know.
I think the one that this ride is referencing the most
is the one that I saw in theaters, and I do not know one thing about it.
I can tell you what. I enjoyed it.
I looked up and smiled and clapped, but I don't know any plot.
I got it. It's six because the villain in this ride is
is the Shaw that Luke Evans plays and the Shaw that
the brother that Jason Statham plays who avenges
his brother, Luke Evans, is in seven.
So, yes, six. You're correct.
OK, OK. Six. OK, got it.
But so you keep taking us through Hollywood where there's a weird car
and we got to go investigate.
So they called into security and then that call gets overrided
by the FBI who tells you that there is an FBI witness
in the audience of the tram tour that pissed off Shaw
and Shaw is coming to get because FBI witnesses deserve to enjoy
the entertainment capital of Los Angeles as well.
They get to enjoy Orlando recreation as well.
The FBI gets overrided by agent Hobbs of the US diplomatic services
and he owns him.
He calls him like sweet cheeks.
Does he call candy ass cookie?
Plus, cookie. Plus, just kind of.
That's kind of something.
I kind of like cookie.
Plus, yes.
It's funny when the rock insults people.
Yeah, like that was that goes back to his wrestling career.
It's funny when it's all career. Yeah.
Insulted people. Yeah, that's yeah.
So he's doing a little bit of it here.
He's doing a little bit of it here.
So they're going to hide you out in a garage.
Sullivan's garage, which
I might be in one of the movies in the first movie.
That's just called Toretto's.
But at this point, they've had so many headquarters and locations.
And you are told by
Letty, Michelle Rodriguez's character and Roman
Tyrese's character that you're going to hide out in one of the very good
single or two shots shot on an iPhone used for the tramp tour.
Yes. Yeah.
OK, all right.
So we're halfway through the pre-show.
So we're we're we're pulling into the giant custom made building
made for this experience.
And there's been a big race.
Dom is, of course, won the race.
And there's a party going on, you know.
I didn't get that.
Wait, where was the?
Well, wait, so we're at the end of we're at a party celebrating a race.
That's why there's all those people.
OK, yeah.
And we love the party people, don't we, folks?
They seem very natural.
This is my favorite part of the whole thing.
These non-union background.
Well, just the effects of the people partying in like a little group.
Yeah. And then it's like repeated.
But I like the technology because it kind of makes it look if you squint,
it makes it look like there's actually humans kind of in the distance
partying in a little group.
Mike, I might have to call this a gripe because I what I wrote down
is that this is maybe my least favorite theme park scene ever.
The club scene before the dancing at the.
Yes. I called it the the shoved in the center dance party.
All of these people like oddly crouched together and being very still.
Let's dance, but not in such a way that our feet go anywhere that we leave this.
It's like they're they're in like an invisible cage,
like they'll trip a wire if they go slightly to the left to the right.
And then they get as soon as you see it.
What's that? You're not amazed by Mr.
Pepper's ghost.
I mean, sure, I guess I always like that.
And I like the that. Hey, it's a it's one of those Muzin holograms.
You know, a Muzin hologram.
I kept seeing that on theme park review sites as if I knew what that was,
like which is achieved via a Muzin hologram.
I don't know what a Muzin is.
That's a weird word.
I don't like the word Muzin.
It seems like something that would be wrong with your body.
Like if some weird if like, I don't know, like
like parts of your genitals are fusing together, that shouldn't be.
You're experiencing general Muzin.
Do you know what is it?
General Muzin?
No, no. What is the Muzin like illusion?
It might be a company name.
I don't know. As opposed to a style.
I don't hear a Muzin hologram.
It's not the holograms owned by that that evil guy, Alki.
Yeah, Muzin.
I look it's called Muzin.
It's a system. It's called Muzin eyeliner.
Infusingly, it sounds like a makeup, but it's not that.
It's it is a
Pepper's Ghost type thing.
It's invented by a guy named Ove Moss, M-A-A-S-S.
And I'd have to look further into it.
I guess it's been a long round for a while.
Just a weird word. What is it?
What does it mean? What is Muzin?
And you just Googled it and it doesn't have a definition?
Doesn't explain. No, it's just Muzin holograms are.
It's not somebody's last name, I don't think.
I don't know where this word comes from.
Jason, do you do you agree with me?
This is the best part. Or do you just are you in the middle?
Um, I I kind of like no, I like it a few minutes later.
I think the best part.
You mean when they show up and stuff?
When everyone comes in, like because I like that, too.
You know what I think it is?
I'm really trying to analyze here what it is.
Yeah, I like OK.
I like the effect a lot.
I think the effect actually is pretty cool.
I think it's reminding me of when I get to go like once
every other year to a douchey Vegas pool party or something.
I think, oh, yeah, which I don't like.
I like Vegas and I don't. Yeah, I don't.
I love why you do she Vegas pool party loud, loud, like just
the rattling your heart base loudness.
I love that.
So maybe that's what this is.
Maybe I'm starting to sort of feel like I'm at this big weird party.
I think I like it in the movies.
I like when they have the crazy parties in the movies, like when they go to
the unfortunately named Race Wars in the first one, which is God.
In the first, in the first movie, there's a big street racing event
in like Coachella Palm Springs area, and it's called Race Wars.
I don't know if that's supposed to be a joke or just no one thought to like
do another read pass on the racing wars.
They're fixed there.
Yeah, but yeah, but I like I like the parties in the movies,
but in just them dancing in this, I feel like there's just so many conceits.
I'm just a little tired from all the things that's like, OK,
I think I witness Shaw's after them.
The diplomat of the rock is here.
The crew, the family is going to protect us.
That that we don't know until a second later.
They said we would be safe in this garage.
And then Tyrese comes in with a bunch of ladies.
The FBI agent pulls a gun on him.
You know, I don't want to do it just to say a little more about this dance party.
I don't like about it because I don't object to the I don't like all
a dance party is fine with me.
I think that the problem is that, you know, if for anybody who deals
with with video or anything, the dull issue of title safe
that you have to in a frame, put everything a little bit in the center.
So in case the TV cuts something off, that it'll all be you'll see everything.
Nothing. No words will get cut off in the.
So you keep it in the title safe area.
This is a title safe dance party.
Everybody you enter a room and then there's like margins.
Like a P like a word document, there's margins in this dance party.
And I understand they have to do that to pull the effect off.
But it never this would never bother me when you're looking at just Ray
and Rise of the Resistance, because it's only one person
when you're trying to get 50 people into one room.
And now you have to just like, and don't do not shimmy
to the left or the right whatsoever or you'll get cut off.
It's unfortunately the only part of the ride they made title safe,
because depending on where you sit, you might miss a significant portion.
Yeah, no, no joke.
I didn't know until reviewing a YouTube channel
that showed the right side of the ride and the left side of the ride.
I didn't know if the rock was in the ride ride part
because I'd never seen some people,
some of the body count of the ride.
Oh, he does some of the murdering. OK. Yeah.
I think you guys are expecting too much of this new technology of the
fusion.
Manu shit, Steve Manu Shins,
how would you Manu Shins hologram company?
Yeah, it did cost six hundred dollars too.
And that's a great topical joke.
Manu Shins produced a fist fight and he produced a fusion hologram.
Yeah.
That's right. Right. He's the movie producer.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
The next gen, I think, will be able to get as many dancers
as possible in a warehouse, as many great ghost dancers.
I think that's coming.
OK, OK. So yeah, a little more.
Just don't make it so obvious.
Don't play.
I can see I can see the lines. I can see the margins anyway.
Yes. So they all are you.
You land and then they're all asked to leave as soon as you've seen them
for the first time.
And then and then Tyrese comes in and then the and then
a an FBI agent who's like, you can I guess I should have include in
that he's not one of the leads of this film franchise because he doesn't
really carry it as much as they do.
Mm hmm. I'm remembering now that when you said they got dismissed,
my memory is that we go through like like we see like here.
OK, I'm unlocking a memory now here.
Sorry to go back.
But the first time I ever went on this, it broke down, I believe, five times
in a row. We did not get to go.
We it kept turning around and going back in.
So I was in the dancing area stuck for a long, long time,
like like minutes and minutes and minutes.
And then we go in, the ride would break and then we'd have to go out
and turn around and try to do it again.
So I think I've sort of been like I have a comfort with the part,
the dancing part.
And that's also why I think it lasts longer than what you just explained,
that it was a quick thing and they're dismissed.
The OK.
And maybe you like it in a Stockholm syndrome,
where you were trapped, so you had no choice but to start to like
this odd hologram dance party.
Yes, that's wow.
I was with a friend of the show, Andrew Grissom, I believe.
Mm hmm. How does he feel?
I haven't asked him recently.
I think we both were like, OK.
Yeah, all right.
Mm hmm.
Agent Novak, original theme park, I.B.
Agent Novak.
Agent Novak, he he pulls a gun on Tyrese.
Tyrese says, we don't work for you.
And that's when an elevator is activated
and the big hero shot here comes Dominic Toretto and Letty
on a big like Mack truck.
And he says, we don't work for no one.
Now, this I like that is the moving physical set piece.
And then and then the holograms are on it.
I will give it up to that. That is very cool.
I like this too.
And I believe Agent Novak says something about I'm the one holding the gun.
And that's when the rock comes in and says, yeah, but mine's a whole lot bigger
because he has like a giant assault rifle.
And I have been on this experience before,
and I've seen people cheer like when these characters show up.
Yeah. Well, he always gets one.
Yeah. That's the idea of the rock gets applause.
I'll say and I'll after we finish Hollywood, I will explain my experience
as the only one who wrote it in Orlando.
People do like to see famous people in their rides
playing the characters they know and love.
So I do understand that part.
I do understand people like, yeah, it's the whole gang.
The whole family is here.
Yeah. Sure. Yeah, it makes sense to me.
Yeah. Yeah.
What doesn't make sense is why the the rock comes in with a big gun.
By the way, a lot of guns in that is maybe the gunniest attraction
in of the 2010s.
Like there's a holdovers of attractions full of guns
where you can't do anything about it.
But like kind of weird that, especially in 2018, like do a big gun show.
It's like there's probably the same amount on like Transformers,
but since like the guns are in a robot's arm,
it doesn't read exactly like that.
And it's like, yeah, so if a robot has a gun arm,
it doesn't read as bad as.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That makes sense.
But anyway, he'd like, yeah, his entrance is cool
and he gets applause and lifts a big thing and makes a cookie, puts joke.
But then everybody just kind of like files out of the room.
Nobody runs.
It's just kind of like, all right, well, we're in a load up
stroll, stroll, stroll.
It's like everybody taking a lunch break.
OK, because you need to establish another premise
that you have to turn off your phones.
You can't take pictures because then Shaw can track your location
and he'll he'll show up and kill everyone.
And it should be noted, no one fires a gun.
These guys just don't fire guns. Shaw has a flamethrower.
I guess a helicopter has a gun, but it's sort of like in Batman.
We're like, well, Batman's not pulling out a handgun,
but the Batmobile has a gun
and there's a giant gun that just runs through people.
Yeah, the Lincoln.
So yeah, it it it there is the conceit that they can track you.
And then, of course, Tyrese takes a phone call and it's like
and then the diesel very casually.
Vin Diesel or Michelle Wright.
Someone goes, well, Shaw knows where you where we are now.
No one tosses it off the stakes or nobody's concerned.
Just know that it feels like this attraction should have been a show
and it should have been just like stopped here, had all your favorites,
and they just do a little show for you and you drive out.
We don't need the action adventure part.
We just like hanging out with our friends for a little while here.
Yeah, like motor action.
I guess I like this part a little more, maybe than the like,
despite my problems with the title safe dance party, it I like.
All right. Well, this will.
So this is kind of fun and they're all a little funny.
And so the finale of this is going to blow me away.
But then and then you go in.
And if if it's my experience, half the time it works,
half the time, all of a sudden, it's just like the screens are what you wheel
into, like a room with just white screens on the side and drive right out.
But yeah, if it's working, if it's working,
you're transported to a parking garage underground, baby.
That is Jurassic Parking.
It has the you can see the T-Rex on it.
You're in a parking.
That's very funny. I did not ever catch that.
I didn't catch that either. That's great.
Yeah. All right. Now I like it more.
And immediately.
So I remember my reaction is immediately when we're on this.
And I was like, oh, it's exactly it's just Kong again.
And which is a worse version of Transformers.
I remember like my initial feeling of like kind of disappointment
because I was hoping they had used some like crazy new technology.
I knew it wasn't going to be a crazy roller coaster or anything.
But I just remember being like, OK, all right, all right.
Got it. Which if you haven't done any of this, you're sort of sandwiched
between two giant screens
that are very tall, that feel oddly close to the track.
It's an interesting effect.
But it's it's it's tough because it is just obstructed.
It's just a really obstructed view,
which like works a little better in King Kong because you feel like
our in the jungle and it's sort of chaos and what's coming through those trees.
Oh, it's it's calling like it feels like you're on a safari.
Like the inability to see is a little more and you forgive it maybe.
But here this feels a little more like you're supposed to understand
and comprehend everything.
Right, because you're moving to I mean, like the whole,
you know, you're trying to go fast, you're moving fast and fast and furious.
But like there's the sections where like you're kind of tangled in trees
or vines on King Kong, you're kind of stationary.
You're moving a little bit and like it's teasing that you're going to fall or whatever.
But in general, like if you're just stationary
and like stuff is happening on the screens around you,
you can take that all in more versus the tram, which is not
like a Transformers vehicle that reacts so well with screens or anything.
The tram was not built for this.
The tram is an old tram.
It doesn't have any cool effects to really give you like the illusion
that you're have any G-Force going on.
So that's why I feel like it just doesn't work as well.
Well, and it Kong is a simpler story.
The short, you know, three minute it and they they do a good job of splitting.
Like, well, here's half of Kong fighting a dinosaur on this side of the screen.
And then he literally climbs over the top and then he fights
more on this side of the screen.
But Dominic Toretto is not like if you sit on the one end of the tour,
you get a lot of the rock.
You sit on the other side, you get a lot of Dom and Letty.
And if you break it down even further, the story is that they hook up
two trucks without trailers on them and you're towed really fast.
Like Triple A tows you.
And it's a towing. It's the same.
Sorry, I stepped all over that.
That's funny.
Yeah, it's like this.
And it's what I was saying before, it's like the same effect as minions,
Transformers, Spider-Man, all of those rides.
There's a hook that gets attached to your vehicle to make you go.
Only the difference is you're just you're on a much less exciting vehicle.
It's an old tram and it just doesn't react at all.
Real a little bit to the movements.
So it's like, OK.
And then and then to the you're talking about seeing the characters, it's like
Kong is giant.
At the very least, you get to see a giant monkey head on the screen.
You're like squeal. You're like, I think that's Dom.
I think that's the rock.
I guess.
And then I'm on a less good version of the universal
dragging you through a screen trick.
Well, and someone points out because at one point that should be very cool.
Dom jumps out of his car and on to the bottom of a helicopter.
And at a lot of that point, he is the same size as the helicopter.
Because the way they film this, they had the actors in front of green screens
and then everything is CGI and the CGI sets the CGI city streets.
Everything is aging.
Was it aging immediately in 2015?
It started. The clock started ticking on that PlayStation 4 quality.
Yeah. Is there I have not seen all the Fast and Furious movies.
Is there one where Vin Diesel grows giant?
No, that would be cool.
Is that on the table, though, to the I asked the producers of Fast and Furious.
Is Vin Diesel growing giant possible mid jump?
He jumps out of a car and by the end of the jump, he's 70 feet tall.
Fantastic. Yeah, he'll be like a ant man or something like just let's let's do it.
Why not? I'm going to see if I can get a good loop.
Just like a gif of the of him jumping onto that helicopter.
It's so weird that the proportions change like crazy.
The frame rate.
I don't know is the is the frame rate of this 12 frames a second
or 700 frames a second.
It's something weird either way.
It goes back and forth between those two constantly shifting.
Hi, there's there's a lot.
All this is happening in like different cars.
Letty runs Luke Evans's car off like the road, like off a freeway.
The rock runs a car off the road with his big like assault vehicle car.
Yeah, a lot's happening.
It's OK.
It's not a bad idea for an experience because like, no, it's just like this is not.
It's probably very hard to render all this stuff, make it because like
there's like a lot of angle tricks with the screen.
And depending on which part of the car you're at, things look bigger and smaller.
It's just there's so many variables for that experience.
Like if it was just a VR thing, like with the basically the same premise
and the same like track or whatever, I think it's probably much cooler.
I bet this looks like good on somebody's headset, like somebody there.
There must have been a test of this where you sat and did it and were like, holy shit.
And then just once it moved to that tram, right.
Then you stretched out and like the person in the front of the tram is like
trying to peering back, trying to see it.
And it doesn't really hold up as well.
So, yeah, I mean, like I did Mario Kart VR in Japan.
Which I think they close that place, right?
By the time you were there, Scott.
Yeah, I didn't get to do it.
Oh, they've since yeah, they were sued that company.
Oh, but like Mario Kart is not as fast as Fast and Furious,
but the Mario Kart VR was amazing.
It was so good. Yeah.
So, yeah, I can imagine.
I'm sorry, not the VR.
The Mario Kart go kart on the streets of Tokyo were sued by the Nintendo people, I believe.
Oh, yes, yes. There was a and I didn't do it,
but we saw them.
We saw them when we were in the like the video game district,
essentially, like the people on tours like with Mario and Luigi hats,
driving go karts around the city streets, which I was like, that's cool.
But also like seems dangerous.
It seems like not a good idea.
No interest.
And yeah, no, I didn't really want to do it,
although I guess maybe to review it, I should have. But.
Hmm. Yeah. Oh, well, we'll review it when it opens in Hollywood.
Yeah, I don't.
You know, even as you're you talk about this more simple story of Kong,
like, OK, take all of this backstory on all of this stuff about, OK,
but now Shaw heard the cell phone and that like
once the ride part begins, the big screens, what is happening?
Are they they're transporting us to keep the witness safe?
Is that it?
Yeah. And they they they take out Shaw and the bad guys.
And then I think a bridges out and he yells, hit the nitrous.
And then he screams, ride or die, which I believe is said in the movies
pretty regularly. Right.
I think not as often as family.
But ride or die.
And that's kind of cool.
But I want to jump ahead a little and mention before I forget,
the ride ends with you landing in a warehouse full of shipping containers.
That's the exciting and the CGI warehouse.
Everything is CGI because they did the actors in front of green screens.
And then they they did it all CGI and everyone was just like, what?
What is this?
It's an abrupt ending to like this, this, that this part,
the big screen part is only 90 seconds.
So you're kind of like, what already?
Yeah, it feels very short.
I don't do we know how long the Kong part of the Tramp Tour is?
It feels longer, but it might not be that much longer.
Yeah. But, you know, it is disorienting for sure.
And it's all of a sudden, yeah, you're in a CGI warehouse.
You're also getting I don't know where Jason, where would you plus it up?
Where would you prefer they land?
I don't I think just the premise in general, like it really
toes the line between like this is a moviemaking experience and like these
characters are real. You live in this world now.
Dominic Toretto is real.
And if you keep it simple, you can get away with that.
Like Universal got away with like Ghostbusters are real once you enter this
building in Florida. You know?
Well, OK, I have I have a plus up.
They still land in the CGI warehouse.
But then two of the cars start dancing, dancing against Alina.
Carnaval party going on in the warehouse.
Yeah. Like in the end of Minion Mayhem.
There's a part there's a big adoption party.
Well, yes. Here's the whole thing.
They did not to I don't want to jump on what you're going to say about Orlando,
but they push this even harder in Orlando.
The plot is more is a party to get to.
Oh, but wait, a bunch of stuff happening in Shaw and all this.
So weird that the whole thing is about OK,
so there's a party and you're on route to the party.
And when you see the party bus, it's going to be great because of the party lights.
So get ready and then soon you'll be at the party.
Oh, a distraction. It's going to take us away from the party.
And then where's the party?
There's no party.
We forget about the party and is the party the gift shop?
There's no payoff.
The party know the gift shop is a supply store.
No, there is no party.
And the fireworks factory all over again.
We're going to get to Toretto's party.
Is the party the dancing at the beginning?
Was that do we zoom past the party and then there isn't another party at the end?
Oh, that must be it, right?
I think that's the party.
All right. Yeah, that must be the party.
This is a good transition into Orlando
because Orlando takes place in the San Francisco section of the park,
never mind the fact that the CGI streets
and the ride are clearly the streets of Los Angeles.
Ignore that town L.A.
Yeah, so yeah.
So this in in Florida, this ride replaced disaster.
Major motion picture ride, dot dot dot starring you.
And of course, Beetlejuice's graveyard review.
So in this house, we are already have a grudge going against this ride.
And so you go in through the streets of San Francisco and there's a lot of cars.
There's like cool cars everywhere.
And you go in through like a big brick building, big brick front.
There's cool cars.
And then you're in a garage, a lot of garage cues.
Look, the cars are cool, but these cues are just empty rooms.
They put barrels and tires and some cars like it's.
Yes. And the building itself is just a brick building with a fence.
Yes. It's like one of the worst facades of an attraction.
And not like Rise of the Resistance, they do in such a way where it's like,
there's no big here's the Rise of the Resistance.
It's like, oh, is this a ride?
And you know, like you're subtly navigating through this little forest thing.
You could do that or you could just have a little bit of a
or you could just have just a building.
I it's kind of.
Well, I think they wanted to keep the facade that looks like the chocolate company.
I always say the wrong pronunciation of from Delhi, San Francisco.
Yeah, Ghirardelli.
Oh, it's that building. It used to be a Ghirardelli.
Yeah, it's kind of that.
It's just a replica of like the headquarters in San Francisco.
The front of it.
And I guess the pre show money went to like the cue money,
went to the the two different pre show rooms
where where you are met by Pat and Jamie,
gender neutral team members who are help the crew.
And I I heard a rumor that these team members are pulled
not from the entertainment division where actors are staffed,
but from the operations division.
And that would explain why they are often stiff,
even by theme park standards.
Yeah. So it's interesting to me, though, that they were like,
well, we got to make some changes, you know, because it's going to be bigger.
And they were like more pre shows, more pre shows.
We got Pat and Jamie who talked to Ludacris and Jordana Brewster.
And and and then clearly they didn't want to just reuse the footage of
a they didn't.
Vin Diesel and the Rock show up as like waveform phone calls.
But Ludacris and Jordana Brewster are like shot as it.
I keep saying like I'm shot on an iPhone, but they are shot like they are Face
Timing in and they deliver the lines with the brakes for the cast member to say,
like, what should we do next?
Tej. OK, Pat, listen, I got party buses coming
because that's a big difference from Orlando.
The vehicle is not a tram. It's not the tram.
It's a party bus.
And now this I love.
This is my only thing I love is that it's a party bus.
There's no other ride.
That's a party bus before. Like, there's a guy like this idea.
I I'm pleased with this.
It's kind of it's kind of good.
It shows up flashing colors, kind of neon.
Yes, I like the view. Yeah.
You like the party bus and we like the party.
We like we like the party bus.
We like the party bus. Party bus.
Like ding ding ding ding ding.
That that that we did not again.
Scott and I did not go on this.
Jason is the only one who went on it.
It was a packed date universal.
We all had things to do and we both made the decision.
Doesn't seem like it's worth it, does it?
Well, I had I only had to get back to Cabana Bay.
Scott, did you?
Yeah, I was staying on property at that point.
So I literally this was the last thing I did before flying back to Los Angeles.
I did this ride.
I ate up a solid pizza at that pizza place in City Walk.
Then I went back to the hotel and got my luggage and then gotten a lift.
And I was just like shaking my head, eating that pizza.
I was like, the last ride I did was Superchar.
Oh, man. What was I thinking?
Yeah. So that was a more the lift ride was probably a better ride.
More immersive, more interactive. Yeah.
Yeah. So Jason has the first hand experience.
But from watching the video, I guess the party bus is good.
Yeah, I like it.
And probably you can see more than the tram because you don't have another thing
right in front of you. Right.
It's a little more tooled for the experience.
Well, and you know what?
What is much clearer in Orlando?
Just how many times in the Orlando experience they say family,
because they say family a lot in these movies, but the movies are two hours long.
And so it's kind of distributed.
The Orlando experience is like under 10 minutes.
So when you hear like our family will protect you, you're part of our family now.
And don't worry, our whole family's got looking out for your back.
You know, it's it almost seems like they're making fun of you.
They're all they're saying like, we're you think we're family.
Fuck you. Yeah.
On on that note about the repetition of family,
I have a clip from the opening of this attraction,
which had pretty high penetration of the cast.
It is a remarkable amount of the cast.
Ludacris is there and Tyrese and I think you're Dan and Brewster and then.
But it all builds up to a stunt car arrival of Vin Diesel,
who then once he gets on stage,
I just what I don't have is the first part.
You know, there's the theme parky thing of hang.
I can't hear you.
And then, you know, saying it as I say, so this is he's already said this once.
And then this is his second escalated time to really pump up the crowd.
Who wants to be a part of the family?
Who want to be part of the family?
And
pretty addictive, honestly, I was kind of that was that's been rattling
in my head for 24 hours.
I mean, I think he also yells.
I wrote this quote down.
I then he yells, who wants to see this ride?
I don't know why he chose to deliver those lines like Eric Andre.
That's what it's like.
I knew that was like something comedy.
Absolute God. Yes.
He is he's earnestly doing Eric Andre insanity
and he doesn't realize it's insane.
Wow. I said, what is that voice?
It's driving me crazy.
Also, I'm staring at the thumbnail of this and he, you know, it's
it's the cool chain link fence aesthetic in the warehouse.
And so it's just signs around.
And one of the signs says, thank you for not littering.
Cool. Hey, fam.
Don't litter. Family doesn't do that.
Family does not do that.
The opening of the Hollywood one had like a car doing a stunt,
like jumping through a, you know, a big sign.
I also saw some B roll of like the Hollywood opening
where you got to see a real Hollywood experience
of like a famous person being escorted away
by like a well-dressed handler saying, thanks, guys,
to the assembled.
And if you've ever been to a premiere or a real Hollywood event,
you've seen a famous person being surrounded by a reasonably nicely
dressed minder going, thanks, guys.
That's we're out of time. We got to go.
Yes.
Folks are getting you away from like some red carpet got like,
what's up? I'm movie junkie.
So you have 45 seconds. Wrap it up.
All right. All right. Movie.
Come on. Stop it now.
That's it. All right. You said, um, the entire time.
You were just nervous to meet him.
You said nothing in the first seconds.
Sign the first 10 by 10s. We're not going to do another 10.
OK, let's keep moving along.
Thanks, guys. Thanks.
Thanks, guys. Thanks, guys.
Thanks, guys. I feel like it applies to a lot of different Hollywood jobs.
Yeah. Thanks, guys. Thanks, guys.
Thanks, guys. It was fun. Switch it up, agents.
Thanks, folks. We're not.
We're cutting back on guys.
Come on.
I'm trying to think when we were at the Jurassic Jurassic
World premiere for the ride, did we hear any thanks, guys?
We would have if we tried to talk to anyone.
Yeah, I guess you're right. We didn't talk to anybody.
Maybe when we tried to have too many drinks,
they should have somebody was like, hey, thanks, guys.
We when I think when we tried to go upstairs, they're like, sorry, guys.
Wrong land. Sorry. You got to say you got to eat down here.
Oh, that's right. There is a VIP. Yeah. Yeah.
Well, I like this ride. We're all VIPs.
Right. We're sorry. Yeah.
I think we hear sorry, guys, a lot more.
Thank you. Sorry.
Sorry. Nothing to be thankful for.
So what's your podcast about?
Well, it's about the.
Sorry, guys.
You three are not family. You're trash.
Get the hell out.
Sorry, guys. Sorry, guys.
Sorry, guys.
Well, we're going to try to get more thank yous this year than sorrys.
Right. We're going to.
I there's another thing about Jason, about when the when Ludacris
calls in that he because then in the ride.
OK, so maybe something we haven't said is that,
you know, the tram tour, there's monitors on the trams for all
of the myriad of other things you do on the tram.
So they have to play clips of the characters like they do some expositional stuff.
And then when the ride's over, they cut to, you know, Vin and the rock.
And they all say, hey, thanks for being part of our crew.
So that same thing happens on the party bus.
But so it's a mix of stuff that they shot for the tour one where.
Yes. Like, OK, so it's shifts between when the ride's over
and the Buster Rhymes song is playing.
Then you get Ludacris, who is being filmed on a pre-zoom,
you know, there's like scan lines and either an interface.
But then you've got, you know, Vin and Tyrese and the rock
all leaning up against like a are they just in a golf cart?
What are they just like on a studio lot?
It's just like junket style.
Yeah. That was filming out on the back lot. Yeah.
They have a tripod.
All right. So Hobbs is talking to you with like a junket crew he brought.
But Ludacris is talking to you via like a secret
pirate radio, pirate video channel.
He's the computer guy and the crew. He's the computer guy.
That's how they communicate it.
He hacks. Yeah. I see. Yeah.
Is there a making of to know exactly who was in the room,
where even in the pre-show and this and like when it was shot
and was this shot a year later or was it all shot when Hollywood happened?
Or I'm always I'm always curious about that type of thing.
It apparently was Orlando and Hollywood were working on it together.
Like it was simultaneously being worked on.
Did anyone see there was somebody had pointed out that the rock,
the rock endorsed Biden and Kamala Harris, which
I think is his first political thing he's done since showing up at like
the Republican National Convention in 2000.
Oh, boy, really?
But whatever. OK, all right.
He's but he endorsed Biden and Harris.
And then somebody pointed out, hey, did you notice he's wearing
the exact same shirt in the exact same spot as when he inducted
pro wrestler Ken Shamrock into the Impact Hall of Fame?
So he was he was getting like he was getting a bunch of videos
done at the same point.
And he did he did them like run after the other, I assume,
because same shirt, same location.
And he endorsed the president elect Joe Biden.
And then he also said that Mr.
Ken Shamrock was worthy of his Hall of Fame induction.
What's this one for?
Biden Harris Shamrock, Terra Mata, bang, bang, bang, bang.
Yeah, it knocks them all out.
So I wonder if like one of these things was like rock just had to knock
this out, like a I got to knock out a pre show thing for for Universal.
Then he does some sort of political thing.
Then he does cuts a promo on, you know, Roman Reigns or something.
I mean, to some extent.
But of course, they did all have to like swing around on rods and sandbags.
That's one thing as for as much as you make fun of
how Vin Diesel looks on the digital helicopter where he grows 70 feet.
When you see him do the stunt in a green screen void, it's really impressive.
Like this is true.
This is a real stunt man.
He's done and Vin Diesel's doing it.
Like, why is the behind the scenes look so much better?
Because there's no bizarre, like spatial shift going on.
And I can see it.
I mean, it's not like it's not blurry.
And I'm not like peering over somebody's head.
Watch the behind the scenes, the behind the scenes is better than the ride.
It's cool. Yeah.
And I think in the movies, too, like they certainly use CGI.
I mean, the 2000s one, it's very funny when they show like
the sequence of like the night hit the nitrate and they go through the engine.
It's perfect. The logo in the original one
at the very time is amazed.
Like you can just see the evolution of filmmaking.
I think the second one is actually pretty bad with rough CGI.
But I feel like Tokyo Drift is mostly practical stuff.
And there are a lot of practical stunts in this movie.
That's why the CGI-ness is so odd.
Yeah. Yeah.
Which this like I've got a kind of a bigger point here about the weird
like what what makes this not work and why this is like, you know,
it's certainly in the running for worst screen ride.
And for as much as we went on and on about the Fallon ride,
that almost felt like more in its construction than in the in the premise
and then in the like technical side of it.
And I think the technical side is just rough on this on this ride.
Yeah. And I was just thinking about how, OK, so it does pay off.
Here's all your favorite characters and you're going on an adventure with them.
But in the Back to the Future ride, you aren't following Marty and Doc.
It's not about Marty on a hoverboard and you're following him.
And Star Tours is not about like
chasing a flying Darth Vader around like more of them show up in the characters
show up a little bit in the adventures continued in the new one.
But like when the characters show up as holograms mainly or in Back to the Future,
they're on little screens in which they do that.
Conceit on this thing.
Like that's I don't know, like when you're trying to fit your characters
into things, it's been done so much more successfully as
here's a little console camera.
They're popping up on the second monitor in some sideways
rather than like here is VIN and the rest of it has to be digital.
So it has to be a real digital looking VIN.
I think that's sort of the problem.
And you can tell why.
I think there was some pre version of Back to the Future where it was like
Doc's in a flying machine, like some big umbrella like old timey
pre Wright Brothers machine.
And I think it looked really silly and they bailed on it.
And you're just doing a DeLorean.
And I think Fast and Furious shows you why.
Yeah, it's I was I think it only works with the characters
in like a type of ride like this on the Simpsons, because they're already cartoons.
Yes. Yeah. Like that's the only because other than that, if you're going,
if you're on some sort of ride that's supposed to be very fast
or obviously Transformers because they're giants and it's totally a different
like type of screen ride.
But yeah, like if it's humans, it's like you're not really getting much
whizzing by tiny versions of the characters you like.
That's what when I was trying to when Aaron was trying to remember
if she'd been on this or not, she was like, is that the one
where you go by all the tiny people?
That's how it existed in her brain.
And I don't blame her when you think about King Kong, which we're not huge fans of,
but we all agree it works better.
You've got weird scale issues like you're saying with Optimus
like if the scale ever looks weird, it's because you're looking at fantastic
beings and you don't know how tall they're supposed to look.
But I do know that the that Vin Diesel is
is he short? Maybe he's short.
I know that Vin Diesel is somewhere between five and seven feet.
So when suddenly he is 70, I know that that's not right.
Yeah. Yeah, it's yeah.
It just doesn't. I mean, I there's probably like
using the Spider-Man Transformers system.
There's a version where you like the humans look better
because like Spider-Man is obviously the proportions are crazy,
but it's all pretty consistent feeling, whether it is or not.
It just feels consistent.
In my mind, the characters are all big, but like your brain
automatically gets used to like, OK, all the human characters are this big.
And it's something you don't even really think about.
Like he jumps on the hood.
My memory is like now that I'm thinking about it is like
Spider-Man is seven feet tall and like seven feet wide.
But it doesn't it doesn't.
It's not something you're thinking about because I think
because the scale stays pretty similar the whole time.
Yeah. Yeah.
But yeah, you that's that you get face to face with the characters,
which is, of course, what I like with Transformers and stuff is you get
little personal moments and then you get action adventure things here.
It's just like you're trying to figure out what's going on.
If Dom were to like grab the rungs of the tram tour
or of the ride vehicle and like lean into the car and like be like, hey, you.
And then he points and he's like, you're my family.
Then he goes and does it.
That's a little bit more what what I think people would want.
They get a little more face time with Vin, with Dom.
Grabbed the sides of the tram
and rattled them and screamed in your face,
who wants to be part of the fancy family?
Yeah, that exactly.
I think then you're at least you
you can't see the action if it's a little blurry.
You at least go.
Well, it was fun when he rattled our rattled the vehicle.
I have one more thing from Florida that I I went back into my notes
from over a year ago because I was like, wait, there was something in the line
that struck me as like, oh, that's not great.
And it's right before you get to the room where you get on the party bus.
Inevitably, there is like a, you know, a curvy ramp up
to get to the room.
And it's kind of unadorned.
Maybe there's one or two colored lights.
But they were blasting a song.
And I was like, what is that song?
What I cannot place it.
And then I immediately knew what it was because they said the name
and it went turned down for what?
Then I know that.
And I was like, oh, my God.
Like, and that's kind of a thing.
You know, I went back and looked at some of the soundtracks for these movies.
And there's some forgotten songs on there.
But I was just like, this is how you're building up people getting psyched.
Like a 2009 song on this like giant expensive ride.
It's turned out for what?
In an empty hallway like that's kind of grim.
You're more of a we know you don't like turned down for what,
but you love Opa Gangnam style.
Still. Well, I do like that.
And the Harlem Shake.
I wish they had done the Harlem Shake because then we well would have just flopped
around in the hallway.
I like to turn down for what belongs in the category of those songs, I feel.
Yeah, I think it's I thought it was just like I had not thought about
turned out for what in a while.
And it was kind of a big,
a big like right before you get on the ride moment.
But I'm done a it's been a couple of days now.
Has anybody done like using the C-SPAN cameras,
like the stationary cameras in the in the Congress building?
Has anybody done the Harlem Shake where it's the footage of just the senators
like about to vote and then there's the jump cut and there's a bunch of people
in fur coats vaping.
Like you do the jump cut to the post invasion.
Has anyone done that?
No, no. Maybe it's happened.
That might be.
It's a future for us.
This might be storming Twitter as we speak.
It's very possible.
So we'll see.
We'll see.
Someone's everything.
It's trying to get it.
Someone's trying to get an invite to a tick tock house.
The trip.
Were those the tip tick tick tock house?
Were they having the parties on New Year's?
Yeah, drip crib and hype house.
And I drove. I love really sad.
I heard about drip crib and I'm very excited about drip crib.
I don't like what they were up to, but I like the concept of the drip crib.
Sure. But anyway, could you could could we rename the you know,
because everybody you guys like varying degrees of little splashiness
in the in the splash mountain logs.
Could you do you want to think of those instead as drip cribs?
They're not logs, they're drip cribs.
I like the idea of that.
Yeah, I think that, you know, you could certainly.
OK, wait, wait, wait, wait.
The real hack at Disneyland or Disney World is you go on splash
mountain alone, you see if you can get the log alone somehow.
And then you lie down like a baby.
In the log, it's going to be hard because of the seats,
but it'll be like you can kind of lie on the side on the Disneyland one
because the seats are sort of in the middle and you lie down on it
and then you get the splashes all over your body.
And that's called a drip crib.
That's a drip crib.
If you yeah, if you duck under the whole thing, do the entire thing
curled in a fetal position.
Yes, exactly. And you bring your little blankie.
And then it gets soaked.
So, yeah, Jason, I mean, Jason will love that.
I'm not a huge fan of getting soaked, but Jason
loves all aspects of his body getting soaked on a rise.
Sleep like a baby.
Look, if you if you toss water on me when I'm sleeping, I'm going on.
That's how you activate the deep rim.
That's how you dream and start
the right.
Yeah, the ram gets activated when Jason gets soaked.
Yeah, nice.
So key sleep.
Oh, what a nice wet sleep Jason.
Turn him over, turn him over.
He's going to drown again. Turn him over.
He's having a nightmare about stiff brownies.
Stiff. No, I wish I would put some more water in that brownie better.
No, they need a stiff brownie needs a trip to the drip crib.
Yeah.
We should also mention this ride was closed from August 8th to November
21st, 2020, when Universal scaled back operations due to low crowds.
From this was their roto virus.
This was their Stitch's great escape.
This is the one where we don't have to bother to run.
They did this Barney
Poseidon's Fury.
Oh, and I think there was a fourth.
Hmm.
Wow. Geez.
So this is already on their shit list.
And like we said, it seems like this has to have been.
This was the point where, you know, I think theme park nerds were saying
five years before this too many screens.
This was the point, I think, where more casual people were starting to say,
all right, it actually was what some of them were starting to say was my eyes hurt.
I can't go on any more of these screen rights.
And now we're getting Nintendo, which is not that there's.
Yeah, there's elements, but yeah, no, there's practical stuff.
It is funny the difference between that.
The two different ways you would say it, depending on what kind of person you are,
that mean the same thing to a universal employee, which is we come up to universal
and play and go, have you noticed that the same screen tricks are being utilized
in Jimmy Fallon's Simpsons, Minion Mayhem?
And then the other person is going like, yeah, it's blurry.
It's blurry. I didn't like it.
And that really conveys the same thing.
It's the same thing.
They both land out.
They both landed the same conclusion of like, we fucked up with this
Fest in the Furious Ride. Yeah. Yeah.
Well, the point is the chorus grew.
I think maybe you needed it to get this bad for things to change.
Yeah. But I got a cute picture with Wax Vid Diesel
that you can really put your hands on in that gift shop.
They encourage you to touch the Wax Vid Diesel. Yes.
Yeah. And and and also I encourage strangers like, hey, man, hey,
could you could you hold my phone? Could you take a picture?
My friends have all fled the state,
but I need he told me I was part of his family.
And I really want a picture to remember that.
So I want to commemorate this sweet moment. Yeah.
Um, you need pictures with your family.
Yeah. Yeah.
I realize also the family, do they?
It's like very like an Olive Garden thing with the family.
When you hear your family is the whole Olive Garden.
Like they keep pushing that.
And it's the same thing with Fest in Furious.
When you hear your family,
has he done an Olive Garden commercial?
That's the one they're going to.
They can't be subtle about getting people back into these restaurants
when it's safe to do so.
They're going to have to yell about it.
And who better to yell than Vin Diesel than Vin Diesel?
That that brings up a good point, because I was not certain.
Like the character Dominic Toretto, I Googled what ethnicity is Dominic
Toretto because he's he's always talking about family.
He's always barbecuing forever.
He like the it's in L.A., but
and they're always drinking Carotas.
Dom always is giving people Carotas.
And I was just like, I have no way I am not.
And it seems like it wasn't until the there's a line in the Fate
of the Furious, the most recent one,
Dom says the Toretto's go back to Cuba like our family comes from Cuba.
And everyone was like, oh, OK.
Like, but does everyone in the movie go, oh, OK.
It seemed like on on message words, we were going like, oh, we thought it was
Dominican or Puerto Rican. OK.
The I also saw something that's a dominant Vin Diesel.
It's unsure of what ethnicity his father was.
It doesn't never knew his father didn't know his father.
Oh, man. I was hoping you were to say Olive Garden Italian.
You think I thought Italian at first, because I'm like, God damn,
this guy's talking about family a lot.
So he didn't he didn't know his family.
He didn't grow up with a full family.
He knew his mother. I mean, he knew his mother.
But I think there it is in question some of the lineage.
Well, I want to post that you have obviously you have that view
and Vin wax figure framed at your desk, I assume, Jason.
Yeah. OK.
So, yeah, we'll post that. You'll get to see that.
And that's the best thing that's that came out of this riot, I feel like.
Yeah, I think so, because it's the memories you keep.
And we got a koozie.
We got a koozie for our fan who went to the Chicago show and the Orlando show.
We gave him a koozie.
Oh, yeah. So that's good, too.
So those are the two things.
It inspired great koozies, who great koozie.
Look, we've heard a lot.
I don't know if Epic Universe is happening.
I think it probably isn't.
That would be my guess.
That's what I've heard.
But there's nothing official.
But I don't know why Fast and Furious wouldn't be on their plans to do it right.
Yeah. You know, like, oh, you build a rest.
You build like the Toretto house where they're always barbecuing.
And like, that's a restaurant.
Of course. Yeah.
A kind of fun backyard barbecue type restaurant like this could have.
Could easily slot into one of the epic universe,
which is, if you don't know, the third universal park that they were going to
build before the pandemic.
And but get rid of you could get rid of be fantastic beasts or how to train your
dragon land, put in a Fast and Furious land, do the barbecue restaurant, do that
Cars Land big expansive ride where like a robot Vin Diesel comes up to your car
and says something nice, which is nice to you.
And then you go on a little race.
And then you can put on, I don't know, another.
There's got to be a different maybe a Hobbs and Shaw spin off ride of some kind.
You know, I think these movies are too popular not to to do something else.
That's my it's well, it's a little it'd be cheaper for them.
They just got to buy like a mile of chain link fence.
That, I guess, is the aesthetic.
So, yeah, whatever.
Look, they got nothing's happening for a while, so I guess nothing's going to get
built, so nothing's happening.
It's not too big of a problem, but can't have too much.
A little Hobbs and Shaw goes a long way.
That movie made half as much as the Fast and Furious one did.
Really? That was less.
Well, that was less family.
It was like hanging out with your two uncles.
They didn't have the whole family.
But because Johnson and Diesel don't get along, so they're right.
They're replacing Johnson with Cedar.
As Dom's younger brother, Jacob, that was revealed in the trail.
A lot of stuff revealed in the Fast 9 trailer.
A lot of cool reveals.
So.
Maybe they made half.
It still made 700 million dollars.
Yeah, like 750 as opposed to one point five point five billion.
Right. Yeah. Just wanted to make sure.
Well, either way, maybe even more exciting than this ride or in a new land.
I mean, maybe the real detraction would be some, you know,
ancestry experience somewhere you like you.
You give you really do give a blood sample to somebody in the warehouse.
And then you get and then you wait around for 10 minutes for results,
kind of nervously.
And then it comes back and like, well, it came back.
Guess what? Your family.
Oh, every time it comes back that way.
Yes, no matter what, they still like run you through the motions.
And maybe they kind of like they come out like whoever walks out,
just like, I don't know, not looking good.
You start to ask like, so Jordana Brewster and Vin Diesel, our brother and sister.
Like, I don't I can't.
They don't look super like a family.
Don't worry about it. It's family.
Salute.
What what if it's like the exact same two pre show rooms on Avatar Flight of Passage?
And they're like scanning you to see if your family move around a little bit.
Move around.
All right. Your family.
Guess what? You're all family.
Rocket raccoon and then no right family.
Yeah, Rocket raccoon should tell us we're family and guardians.
Yeah, we love people say you live in France and you're proud of you.
I yeah. Well, we every ride should you should be told that you're part of the family.
Right. And then we our family should play on one of the right.
One of the ride sequences.
Beautiful. Well, we fixed not only this ride, but every ride, every ride.
And I, you know, this should be where I just end it
normally with the phrase that I say.
But I think I think in this case, we got to end it the way that the ride ends it.
And OK, so, guys, I guess with that.
You survived podcast the ride.
And let me tell you, you were lucky that you were riding with this crew
because the bigger the family, the stronger it is.
And if you want to get wild and act the fool because the party is now
and the party is here, then join our family if by subscribing
for five dollars a month at Patreon dot com slash podcast the ride.
We roll like Patreon subscribers.
This has been a forever dog production
executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner,
Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify
or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter
and Instagram at Forever Dog Team and liking our page on Facebook.