Five, four, three, two, one.
Up, up and away.
That's what I was gonna say.
Welcome to podcast there.
Hey, all right.
Wow.
While we both, that we're debating who,
if either of us had something and the answer is
both of us had a half something.
Wow.
It was up, up and away.
Cause today we're boarding the Mickey Mouse balloon
on podcast, The Ride, The Second Gate.
I'm Scott Gardner.
Mike Carlson was thinking the same thing as me.
We were having a standoff of who would say
the not thought out, non joke intro to the show.
And we both had the same thought.
So yes, I'm here.
What is it?
When we do things like that, it's not a joke.
It's just like, it's the most you would ever want is like,
that's nice.
That's nice that they said that.
A nod.
Oh.
A nice little introduction.
Oh, I saw that the, I saw the title of the episode.
And now yes, I see how that could play into that.
Yes.
Maybe like my mom would hear that and go, ha ha ha.
Maybe that she might laugh at up, up and away.
This is, yeah, this is the episode where you can play
a couple seconds of it for her.
Finally.
This is gonna be the rare snippet.
These are Jason, Jason Sheridan.
Hey, we don't, don't, don't, don't,
we didn't forget about you.
You're coming up up and away with us.
What would you have said, Jason?
Oh, thanks.
If we made you do it.
Probably something nasty.
Probably something not suitable for our moms.
Oh yeah, okay.
You would have said, yeah, you would have.
Some real crude, like yeah, nasty stuff
about balloons or something.
Let's get this fucking balloon fucking shit started.
These guys.
You fucking dicks.
You fucking listeners.
Yeah.
That's what you would have said.
That might have been the most I've sworn on the show ever.
Yeah, really?
Or just accidentally.
I think that little bit might be, I apologize,
but it's the second gate.
Oh well, so immediately now, my mom can't hear it.
Sorry. Shut it off, mom.
Sorry. Yeah, that's all right.
I assure you Mike's not usually like this
and in fact is very apologetic most of the time.
I am, yes, and I was playing,
I was playing a character just now.
Ha ha ha.
Wasn't me.
Ah, history's best excuse.
Yeah, I was in character, everyone.
Get off my back.
Now I'm back to being normal.
Just blame anything that the audience
doesn't like on a character.
Yeah.
On a character, yeah.
I was a character for the whole living with the land episode.
I of course love the ride.
I love the boat ride.
Hey, today we are talking about Ear Force One
and what is Ear Force One?
Ear Force One was a Mickey Mouse hot air balloon
and you might wonder if you have seen this before
and I assure you that you have.
If you ever saw Disney World,
maybe Disneyland promotional materials in the 80s and 90s,
I feel like this balloon was omnipresent.
It was like a way for them to kick it up a notch.
If it's not enough to just show a sweeping aerial view
of a massive theme park complex,
well, look at this.
We also got a Mickey Mouse head floating around in the sky.
This is a grand place.
You gotta come.
Yeah, this was, it's funny
because I do think that's what it conveys to children.
I never was like, I wanna get in this balloon,
but I was like, whoa, Mickey's in the sky.
It's like the bat, it was like a bat signal for me
saying come to Disney World.
Absolutely, they took over the air too.
Yeah, it was a 10 story tall balloon
made for the 15th anniversary of Walt Disney World in 1986
and they just got years of footage for openings
of specials and the vacation VHSs you would mail away from.
They got years of footage out of it.
Yeah, and it's still, does it still, they use it today?
Is that what I read?
I don't know the lifespan of a hot air balloon.
I see in 2013 they were still using it here and there.
I maybe saw something as recently as 2015.
I think it's rare and I think that it does not live
on Disney property anymore.
It seems to be in Idaho in a storage space for balloons.
Right.
Good place to store a balloon.
Obviously we all read a lot about Cameron Balloons.
Yes.
The maker of this balloon.
We did, Cameron Balloons in England,
they made this, Imagineers not hot air balloon experts.
They do have to outsource things that they want.
Right.
Yeah, Cameron Balloons and they not only made this,
the Air Force One, but also, I mean,
a bunch of shapes for Disney, which we can get to,
to give those all their due, but I also just wanted
to run through other things that that balloon company made.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Oh, please, yeah.
Let me share this.
I looked on their website.
Yes, I was doing a lot of work on the website.
Oh yeah, here we go.
Oh, okay, okay.
Well, we have some of the same things.
These are just the ones that jumped out at me a lot.
This is a Whopper, it's a Whopper hot air balloon
for Burger King.
This is a big Vincent van Gogh done in his style
and his painted style and with a hat.
You got, now this one's not a shape.
It's just a little, a little racy, a little body.
Again, I don't know if, now we're back to apologetic
territory. Jason, okay.
Let me say this.
The hot air balloon is a picture of a woman in a bra
and it's for Wonder Bra and it says, hello boys.
And Jason on the Zoom did maybe my favorite emotion
he's ever done.
He leaned in like real close to his computer
and adjusted his glasses like an older gentleman.
Like an older, well I couldn't.
Like, is that, like is that real?
I couldn't read the text at the bottom
because it's kind of folded over and it reads,
the one and only Wonder Bra.
I mean, he didn't do a classic 80s push the glasses down
to see a lady walking by move,
but he definitely did the like old man
who's a little flustered by the image he's seeing.
And I don't think the glass is fogged
as far as I could tell.
I couldn't tell, but the camera quality isn't so good.
I think there could have been partial fogging
in the glasses.
Could have been partial foggy.
Not sure, but there's possible is what I'm saying.
Hello boys, it says.
We're all staring at a picture of a woman in a bra.
Boy, this is the most inappropriate
podcast right episode yet.
I better keep moving.
This is too scandalous.
Cause then we get to my favorite one.
Yeah.
This is more our speed.
It's Sugar Bear.
Yeah, of course it is.
This is a hot air balloon of Sugar Bear.
Now what's, I know Sugar Bear,
but what cereal is Sugar Bear on?
Why can't I think of the name of it?
I've had it, Scott have you not had it?
Do you know?
I think it might be on the list too.
I liked the character, but I haven't had this cereal.
You know Sugar Bear, he's got like mellow eyes.
He looks like a little stoned or something.
He's a sleepy, he's a very casual bear.
He is Golden Crisp.
Oh.
Yes.
And it used to be called Super,
they had a Super Golden Crisp as well.
Super Sugar Crisp was an earlier name too.
Right, yes.
And they were like, it's like a Honey Smacks.
Yes.
It's like similar to that.
That was the Frog.
Sugar Smacks, right?
Yes, and yeah, what's the Frog's name?
Smacks, isn't it?
Oh, Frog's name is Smacks.
You might be right.
Yeah, that seems right.
Is it Frog?
Yeah, I think so.
What was the personality of Sugar Bear?
I mean, as I said, he looks very mellow and easygoing.
Genial?
Yeah.
Right?
I think that's correct.
General guy, I guess, is what he was.
And then, well, if you were on the website,
then I'm sure you also gravitated to this.
It's an Independence Day ship, the big destroyer ship
that was above all the cities.
They made an inflatable one of these
with a little basket at the bottom.
I mean, this is great.
Yeah, I love.
I would have flipped out if this was above my city.
I love this.
I mean, yeah, I've never seen this.
They should have flown this everywhere.
We were all, had an Independence Day fever
at the time, I think, right?
Oh yeah.
I love this.
Oh, certainly.
Yeah, so if I saw this, I would have been a little,
honestly a little scared too.
It would have been so big.
It would have been real.
I was freaked out coming out of Independence Day
a little bit too.
Yeah.
Rattled.
I was like, yeah, maybe, maybe.
Maybe this is coming.
Well, in the theme park tangentially related world,
I came across another one they did.
The inflatable me, the big minion.
Yes.
Hashtag spot Stewart.
It was called inflatable me.
I saw it called inflatable me, at least in,
I think I saw it first in a Daily Mail roundup
about the company and all their novel balloons they had made.
Not an inflatable Jason Sheridan.
No.
Oh, Cameron balloons.
Come on.
Come on, Cameron.
Make our dreams come true.
Yeah, will they make us a hot air balloon on spec?
Please, yes.
Please.
I mean, at least tell us how to do it.
They're like, they're the kings of these type of balloons.
It looks like.
I didn't do a ton of outside other balloon company research.
They have, if you look at their, they also have,
did you see the Ultraman they have?
They made-
Yeah, yeah, I caught that.
That's very cool.
They make, they call that fabric engineering,
which I think is more like
when they're not making a traditional balloon,
when it's like, yeah, and like it's in the shape of a man.
Then they have Cameron Classics,
which are your classic hot air balloons, which I like.
I like the name there.
Cameron Classic.
And then they also have extreme ballooning.
What's extreme ballooning?
Well, it's kind of unclear.
I mean, sometimes you see videos of like two hot air balloons
and then like a rope and somebody tries to like walk across.
And then there's also like balloons.
I think they can just go higher into the atmosphere
than like your standard hot air balloon,
which I don't think gets very high usually.
I mean, it's high for a human being off the ground,
but it's not like very, very high.
I think, I think it's like, I don't,
I don't have the numbers here, but it's like, it can last.
The balloon is like tougher.
It can last higher up in the atmosphere.
The point of it is to get, ascend and ascend and ascend.
Yeah.
Do not just float kind of above places
and promote a movie or a theme park.
Right.
I mean, I think there definitely should be
some sort of Mission Impossible stunt
that involves extreme ballooning.
I think that may be the missing thing.
It is surprising there hasn't been.
And then yes.
What's your guys feeling about hot air balloons in general?
Have you been in one?
Do you wish to go in one?
Oh, I would love to have given the chance.
Yeah, I would jump at the chance of that for sure.
I, I think we've, if it was for the show,
I will probably force myself to do it,
but I do not want to get in a hot air balloon.
It's too much.
It feels too fragile to me.
There's not enough around me in the sky.
I do not want to do it.
Well, it seems like the extension of you not liking,
heights, drop rides, not like tower guardians,
but yeah, you're more, you got limbs dangling around.
Limbs dangling.
It just feels like somebody's going to push me
out of the basket as a gag.
Like I'm going to go flying out of there.
I will also say, and I've said,
I've mentioned this before on the show,
when they would put a hot air balloon,
like the hot air balloon shape,
a car dealership would be promoting something.
You know, they put a hot air balloon or something was new.
I was freaked out by these as a kid.
Oh, right.
Well, do you count a big gorilla,
which scared you as a child as this?
Is this the same genre?
I think it is.
They're certainly related.
I think it is because I would see that.
I remember one, I remember some of these moments in my brain.
Like we were driving by then the Rosemont Horizon,
now the Allstate Arena, which boring, worst name,
but there was like,
I think it was some sort of a car dealership that was open
and they had like eight balloons along the expressway.
And they had like an animal, a couple animals,
and then a couple standard looking hot air balloons.
And I remember just kind of like,
I had to look the other way.
I remember being in the back seat of the car
and like looking the other way on the expressway.
We weren't even that close to it,
but like the idea of it freaked me out.
And then-
You know, like sugar bears smiling at you.
If it was one of my friends from cereal,
I might've been less scared,
but I don't believe I ever saw any cereal mascots
as balloons.
One of your breakfast confidants.
Childhood breakfast confidants.
That's right.
They knew all my secrets as a child.
Like the cookie crisp dog I would confess to.
They knew the secret of why you start at school
feeling like shit after your breakfast
was a bowl of cookie crisps
and a massive glass of orange juice.
I will say cookie crisp was too far for my mom.
That was too sugary.
So we were not allowed to have cookie crisp.
Did you ever have cookie checks?
No.
Cookie checks was sweetened checks
with just chunks of like butter cookie in it.
And I still regret not stocking up on it
when I was a teenager,
because it belongs to the ages now.
Putting it in cold storage.
Putting it in cold storage, yeah.
And then you like break it out for like celebrations.
Like an old bottle of wine,
you have a cookie check small box.
You got a little vintage here.
Getting it, shaking it in your hand.
Cask of Amontillado,
I get lured down to a basement.
My climate controlled cellar.
Yeah.
Where is it?
Let me out.
Vintage cereal.
Although yeah, you would,
I mean, you should write a story
about getting locked in a climate controlled cask
full of cereal.
Yeah.
That's pretty good.
I don't want to just to not have an error sitting there.
I was curious and the character from Smacks
is in fact called Digum Frog.
Oh, Digum.
Okay.
I feel very stupid because I know Digum.
I know the name Digum.
I feel very silly.
Thank you.
I don't, I didn't.
And now of course I'm upset because I discovered
that the original mascot was yet another awful clown.
It is Cliffy the Clown.
Oh God.
Cliffy.
Back when it was Sugar Smacks.
All right, this episode topic has changed.
It is now entirely about Cliffy.
Scott's gotta be-
You know what's something I want to say is that,
oh, what was that?
I was gonna say Scott's gonna be hopping into Air Force One
to slowly escape Cliffy.
Oh God.
Now I'm gonna be worried Cliffy is hiding in there.
I'm not typically afraid of clowns.
I'm not even sure that that's my reaction to
these clowns that keep coming up.
It's not, I think like,
not like any clown freaks me out,
but the specific ones that we are discussing.
And here's Cliffy.
I'm looking at him now.
Oh, you're looking, okay, good.
My mouse stopped working so I can't show you the screen.
Wait, which means he's stuck on my computer.
Oh God.
I better charge this thing
or I'm gonna be staring at Cliffy for a while.
Yeah, Cliffy's weird.
He looks very old, doesn't he?
Is this, were you talking about this picture right here?
Yeah, well, I don't like that cartoon one, the marionette.
Oh yeah, Cliffy, yeah.
Yeah.
They standed real weird.
What does he look like?
He looks like Ed Koch or something.
Cliffy, wait, here, here.
Is this Cliffy too?
He looks different on this box.
Wait, why is Sugar Smacks selling a gun?
This is the cereal with a clown on the cover
you can send back for a gun?
Famous American rifle.
Famous American rifle, free inside.
Yeah, you could get a rifle with your cereal back in the day.
Yeah, that was the default toy.
It was teddy bear or a gun.
This, yeah, I mean, you gotta know
why the country is the way it is
and you take a look at this and you go, oh, I get it.
Buy a rifle with your clown cereal.
Anyway, look, I think that there are clowns
who do not and would not bother me,
but Choco bothers me, Cliffy bothers me.
Look at this.
Whoa.
This is a nightmare clown.
He's got a tiny straw hat
with a big feather exploding out of it.
That seems to be his primary hat.
He's also kind of a conehead.
I don't like this Sugar Crinkles clown either.
He's terrible.
Yeah, look at this.
There's another free squirt gun inside
and this just looks like a.
It's a derriger.
It's extremely realistic.
Why does a squirt gun have to be black?
It could be a fun color.
To send a message.
Wait, Cliffy.
This is not the same Cliffy as this.
No, sometimes Cliffy is a conehead
and sometimes he's just like a scary uncle.
That's Ed Koch Cliffy.
Yeah.
But then this is a different one too.
Were there multiple clowns that advertised sugar specks?
They can't decide what Cliffy looks like.
They can't decide what their cereal is called.
This is just a woman.
Just some lady.
She from Superman maybe?
This is promoting Superman.
Oh, look at that dog thing.
Look at that creature.
Look at this.
This is Honey Smacks then.
That looks like the mask for The Shining
where she looks in the hotel room.
He's a banana split.
Yeah, yeah, that's a banana split.
Oh, it's a banana split.
Yeah.
Spock is on the cover here too.
And sometimes the mascot was Quick Draw McGraw
who is just not from cereal.
It's a Hano Barbera character.
Huh.
Well, we have-
Max is all over the map.
We have another, we have more to do
with the eventual Choco episode,
adding Cliffy to the pile.
No, one clown at a time, please.
Cliffy.
I think maybe we should just collect clowns
and then we feel we have enough.
Then that's when we do the episode.
There's already enough.
There was enough before Choco.
Oh, wait, Mary and Cliffy.
Who's Mary?
Don't buy a marionette of Cliffy
and do anything to me with it.
It's gonna be too expensive.
It's from the 50s.
It's not gonna be worth whatever it did
and whatever happens.
You're acting like we don't have a couple marionettes
already sitting around.
Don't worry.
Marionette right over here.
A little creepy boy.
Don't combine clowns then with ventriloquist dummies
and scary puppet stuff.
All right, fine.
That's enough as it is.
Ear Force One, I guess.
No more clowns.
Now I can't, God, we've had this runner about Choco
haunting me and being inside me
and now possessing me.
And now I think the spirit of Cliffy the Clown
has possessed my computer
because I can't look at my notes about Ear Force One
because my mouse stopped working
and I can only look at Cliffy the Clown.
Cliffy is now living with you basically.
It's like starting to work.
I'm inching my mouse.
Okay, got it.
Okay.
Uh-oh, Cliffy has turned off the command tab shortcut.
Uh-oh, you're stuck on Cliffy.
Cliffy is reformatting your hard drive.
Uh-oh.
Every photo of my baby is now a photo of Cliffy the Clown.
Cliffy loves disk utility.
That's his favorite program to use.
Oh, he's partitioning your drives now.
Uh-oh.
Cliffy the Defrag Clown.
Oh, Cliffy is photoshopping you into the basket
of the more problematic named Zippity Doo Duck.
You're right, that's a good way to get back on track
and away from clowns.
There was also a balloon of Donald Duck.
After the smash success of the Mickey Mouse hot air balloon,
and I gauged success by it existing and being photographed,
smash success.
So the next year they introduced a big Donald Duck head
as the Zippity Doo Duck.
Right. Yeah.
Name is kind of perplexing.
Donald did not have anything to do with that song.
No. Yeah, I don't know why you would wanna
tie Donald to Song of the South, but.
Yeah.
I guess they thought it was cute.
Well, I didn't know when that was a problem.
Yeah.
The song was still around and used just all over the place.
So it was fine then.
I mean, Air Force One really,
Air Force One is a plane.
Is that name that good? Yeah, that's a confusing thing.
I like the name, but, and I get it, but it's like,
Mickey should have his own plane called Air Force One
and it shouldn't be a balloon, that should be something else.
It would be named after a famous balloon.
It's also confusing because there is a plane
that you would see on the Disney MGM Studio tour
and that had Mickey Mouse on it.
And I believe that that was Walt's plane.
Yes. Yes.
And it was the plane that he used to spot the land
that he would gather up slowly in a shady way.
That's right.
To form Walt Disney World.
Yes, and I.
That's not Air Force One.
I came across the name of that,
people are saying that was just called The Mouse.
Really, that plane?
Yeah, that was what people referred to that.
I came across like three different Mickey based forms
of transit that we'll have to touch on on future episodes.
That's interesting, because they,
I wonder if that's the plane he used
for a lot of different things.
Because there were, I'm sure I talked about this before,
at Midsommar Scream two years ago,
imagine your tiny Norris who worked on the mansion
in New Orleans Square talks about being on the plane
with them going to New Orleans to find artifacts and stuff
to put around the land and put in the Haunted Mansion.
And I wonder, is that like the plane he always used?
Because she talks about going to New York on that plane,
going to New Orleans.
Yeah, timing-wise that works out,
because I came across stuff saying that plane was used
to go back and forth for the World's Fair.
So I believe it is that plane, but.
I'd be interested to know if that was like the standard,
get on the mouse, like he had his own like Batman,
his own Batplane essentially, and they just like,
we're fired up, we're going to New Orleans,
we need a new lamp to put in the hallway
at the Haunted Mansion.
And his office chair sent him into a tube.
Yes, like Batman Forever.
The best Batman film.
Yeah, and he didn't pass it along to that,
that didn't work for Eisner and certainly not for Eiger.
Right, no.
They dismantled the chair tube.
Right.
Oh, but hey, well, let me hear,
let me see if I can share the screen
despite my computer being hobbled
and being defragged by a clown.
Because this hot air balloon did appear
in an opening on the magical world of Disney.
And forgive me if it's not super edited,
I'll try, if it gets boring,
and you just wave your hands if you're bored
and we'll turn off the clip.
But this is Michael Eisner in Air Force One.
Looking at the balloon, the big balloon,
and it's in front of that dwarf building on the Disney lot.
I'm here with Mickey Mouse in a huge,
10 story high hot air balloon in the shape of Mickey's head.
Officially known as Air Force One.
Hello, Michael Eisner, head of the Walt Disney Company.
Mickey thought this would be the perfect place
to introduce tonight's Disney animated classic, Dumbo.
That's right, Michael, we're going up to meet Dumbo.
What do you mean, going up to meet Dumbo?
Well, he's flying over the studio
and we're gonna meet him in the wild blue yonder.
Oh, wait a second, Mickey, I have a family,
I've got children, I've got responsibilities.
Ah, Michael, don't be a wimp, this is perfectly safe.
Uh, and where are the parachutes?
Michael, relax, you're gonna love it.
Aw, enjoy tonight's picture.
Taking off, it's flying, off he goes.
So, there's a cute little moment.
Yeah, here's my thought about that
and several other bits that I found involving Air Force One.
There's also a Christmas special where Regis gets in it
and there is the wraparounds of an Easter special
where Goofy is in it.
And the implication in all three is danger.
It's always characters like, I don't know,
and I'll let you know, Mike Eisner's saying,
I don't wanna get in the thing, I got a family.
And Regis is, ah, what did I get myself into?
And Goofy's like, oh, shucks,
I don't know if you'll see me again, but.
And then there is no payoff for any of these, all three.
That would imply then a little scene
where the balloon's going, whoa, whoa, whoa.
But it's also a balloon that they own
and they can't imply that there would be a problem with it.
It'd be a safety issue.
So, it's just people, beat one,
people being scared to get in a balloon.
Beat two, three, and four do not exist.
There are no more beats.
I think that even in this day and age of Disney,
they wouldn't even imply it was on,
they couldn't even, the character couldn't even
be scared of it, I bet.
Yeah, that's true.
Yeah, they just say it's the most epic balloon ever.
And it's really gonna set the holiday season off right.
So now we're heading over to Disney World
for a performance from Megan Trainor.
Always Megan Trainor.
Could you send me that clip, Scott,
because I just wanna take out that little piece of audio
of Mickey saying, Michael, don't be a wimp.
And I wanna make it my ringtone.
Yeah, come on, Michael.
So I have an affirmation, don't be a wimp.
I just need that, I think,
to get me out of my shell a little more.
It's like, do it for him.
Yeah.
Like that touching Simpsons moment.
That's exactly right.
All right, you're gonna be scared of stuff today,
but do it for him, do it for the mouse.
Yeah, and that's, I mean,
it's a little bit of a bullying kind of thing.
He's calling me a wimp, but that's what I respond to.
Come on, Michael, do you wanna die a coward?
Yeah, Jason, you could dub some lines in too.
Yeah.
Piling on.
Let's do it and be absolute fucking legends.
Yeah, I need all that.
That would really help me.
So that clip reminds me of a big feature of hot air balloons.
Since their innovation, they have not progressed super far
in that still kind of not quite 100% sure
where you're gonna land.
You know, there's a lot of very nature dependent.
And that's, I found an LA Times story from 1987
where the balloon just landed on the,
I believe the soccer field of Cal State Fullerton
with no warning.
It's heavier.
Cal State Fullerton Public Safety Officer,
Tom Garrel said the pilot, whom he declined in name,
told him that it was normal procedure
to land at any safe available site,
even though the landing was at 540 PM,
was not caused by any emergency.
If you have a hot air balloon,
you can just land it wherever you want.
At least Disney procedure.
I mean, they were being followed by a van.
They deflated it and then put it in a van.
Has Harrison Ford crashed a hot air balloon?
Is that an onion headline I'm stealing also as I say that?
It is a good question though.
Yeah, cause there was that.
It'd be exciting to see him in Ear Force One.
Oh, it would be.
Maybe for Indiana Jones 5 when they're promoting that.
Get an 80 year old Harrison in there.
He'd be fine. Get off my balloon.
Oh yeah.
Cause he was, yeah.
Okay, after he's still the president
and after what happened with Air Force One,
they decide it's too easy to sneak onto airplanes.
So we need a safer form of travel
that less people can be part of a hot air balloon baskets.
Really hard to stow away in a hot air balloon.
They make a deal with Disney company
and the president of the United States
travels on Ear Force One,
but then somebody still sneaked on board.
Captain Hook.
Great.
Solves that problem.
Yeah, that's great.
Scott, did you answer is would you,
have you been in one or would you go in one?
I think I would.
I don't know if I would so actively pursue it.
Well, I was gonna say if a bunch of my friends
were going in a hot air balloon,
but like that's impossible.
You can't fit too many in.
You can't fit a ton.
I mean, a few, actually, I honestly,
my friends being in the hot air balloon
makes me wanna go on it less.
I don't want shenanigans.
I don't wanna get made fun of if I'm like kinda
crawled up in a corner somewhere.
For sure.
This thing's made for standin', Michael.
You could sleep at home.
Take a look at the view.
Let me give you a big pat on the back.
The back.
Cowards die a thousand deaths, heroes but one.
Yeah, so I don't know.
We'd all kinda go in it,
but Jason's the only one enthusiastically.
Oh, I would love to.
I wanna know though.
The height miser strikes again.
Did you guys come across the castle balloons?
I mean, I remember the castle balloon existing, yes.
I have some questions about the castle balloons
because there's a video about that retro WDW restored
of a couple who got their wish to go on Air Force One,
and they did it at a balloon festival,
which included this balloon of a castle,
but it's the castle from Florida,
and it's labeled Disneyland.
And then I found this picture
of what appears to be the same balloon,
but it's labeled Walt Disney World 20 years.
What?
And it looks like Sleeping Beauty's castle.
Yeah, I think it's the same balloon
that they changed logos on almost,
or at least the same design.
That's absolutely correct.
Yeah, I think it was Disney World first,
and then Disneyland.
Stole balloon valor.
Wow, that's crazy.
They really, were people furious?
I would be.
Yeah, interesting.
I'm always mad when the castles are mixed up.
In any casual context,
if it's, you know,
or if somebody does a Photoshop on Twitter,
or it's like a late night comedy joke,
wrong castle is used, it shows your lack of care.
There's a world of difference
between Cinderella castle and Sleeping Beauty castle,
and this is one of the main issues on my mind at all times.
I get your castle straight.
I feel like Ryan Reynolds tweeted a Deadpool joke
a couple years ago, and he was using the wrong-
Yes, and we talked about it, yes.
Yeah, that's right.
Yeah. Yeah.
Well, I was, I know I was mad.
Were you mad?
We were all furious, yeah.
Well, I'm always mad at Deadpool,
because he's always up to something.
He's always up to no good.
Well, that's true, that's for sure.
Mad at him because he swears.
Swear is like that character Michael portrayed briefly
at the beginning of the show.
Can I quickly jaunt over to my favorite
hot air balloon scene in media?
Oh, yeah. Okay.
Here, let me-
I don't know if I know what this would be offhand.
Oh yeah, like, do you want to guess?
I'll play the end of it.
Jason, do you have any guesses?
I have a guess.
Okay.
Is Buffett in the balloon?
No, but I'm sure maybe, I mean,
I have obviously not seen all media,
so if Buffett is in the balloon somewhere,
then obviously that might go to the front.
But here, let me-
Yeah.
Chipmunks movie.
Anyway, the Chipmunks and the Chipettes,
the big finale of the boys of rock and roll musical number
is them both getting in their own
gender specific hot air balloons.
One has bows for girls and one has tassels for boys.
Oh, there's also Davis at the end,
and the whole bit of the thing is Davis on vacation
and he doesn't realize that the kids
have followed him basically.
He's just an idiot.
Around all the places that he-
I have a lot of affection for this Chipmunks movie.
Yeah, me too.
Yeah.
The Chipettes, so much more fashion forward
than like Alvin Simon Theodore,
look like shit in their colored burlap sacks.
You know, that is a good point.
Compared to-
I never thought about that, but you're right.
The Chipettes in like 80s, like kind of like fun 80s gear.
Well, but the Chipettes newer creations, is that why?
Yeah, I'm sure that's why, but like Mickey Mouse's-
I'm not sure I'm in a 60s show, yeah.
If they were made for the 80s
and to have like Madonna light vibes.
Cause I like the vibe.
The vibe, Eleanor is the best.
She's got the tie.
Do you know what I'm talking about?
Yeah, that's cool.
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
They're all cool.
I don't know that you would call the Chipmunks cool,
but the Chipettes are cool.
Yes.
Yeah.
Jeanette, Brittany and Eleanor.
Eleanor is like the Theodore of the Chipettes,
but she's, I feel like it's dressed the best of the three.
She's got kind of a-
I've been pointed out that-
Oh, okay.
Just like a Diane Keaton vibe, I think.
Yeah.
Well, you know, tie.
She worn a tie.
She kind of has like a-
Yeah, yeah.
The thing going.
No, they're cool.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
Has it been pointed out that we're all,
the three of us are kind of the proportions of Chipmunks?
I think it has.
I think somebody made-
I think somebody drew that.
I don't know who it was,
but I'm pretty sure somebody made that happen.
Yeah.
Tall.
Shorter.
Yeah.
The lowest hanging fruit, it's literally so low,
it's buried in the ground for next season's harvest.
I mean, if I'm misremembering, please.
Yeah, please go ahead and draw it.
Draw is also as the Chipettes.
I'm interested to see that too.
Oh, that's fine too.
Which one's which?
So I'd be Brittany.
I believe, yeah, Brittany is the leader
and she's the regular.
The middle.
Yeah.
Cool.
And then I'm, yeah, Jeanette.
Yeah, Jeanette.
And then Jason is-
Oh, so I'm Elendor.
You're Elendor, yeah, you have the best look.
All right.
Pretty good.
Cool.
Yeah, good for you.
I like, as a kid, I think I liked Simon the best
and I don't think it was
because I thought of myself as Simon, but-
You knew you'd be the Simon of a group.
Yes, eventually.
At some point.
So we'll do a full,
I mean, there's gotta be Chipmunk theme park stuff
we'll eventually get there.
Is there?
Yeah, were they in a theme park ever?
That's a good question.
That feels like they must have been.
That's IT, it's just been there.
Yeah, probably the new, maybe the new stuff.
Yeah, I don't know, that's not as exciting to me,
but I'm sure we can find some fun in there.
Maybe not, or Alvin and the Chipmunks Live,
I'm seeing here at Universal Studios?
What?
Ooh.
Various live shows between 1998 and 2002,
but there's no information on this one website.
Okay.
2002.
Interesting.
That's still pre-CGI.
Right, the Chipmunks sue Universal Studios
for lack of promotion, is this about the movie?
Oh yeah, the creator of Alvin and the Chipmunks
sued Universal.
Huh, all right, well we'll look into it.
Yeah, we'll look into it.
Yeah, great scene.
Yeah, that's a great scene.
The Eisner and Mickey 32nd scene is a great scene.
Hey, well here's a weird use of the balloon of Air Force One.
Let me find it in screen share.
I don't know if you guys saw any footage or photos
of Air Force One in Red Square in Moscow.
Isn't that crazy?
Yeah.
I like, this is vaguely familiar to me,
and I think they took photos,
and I think photos were available as a poster or something,
but that's kind of wild, and it's a empty Red Square.
And I was like, what is this for?
Why did this happen?
Do you have any idea why this happened?
Can you picture anything for Disney done in Red Square?
Oh.
Were they taking him around the world?
I think you're hinting at something more specific,
but I feel.
I mean, I think that did happen to some extent.
And by the way, and as you mentioned that,
Air Force One was in all kinds of places,
like there's photos of it.
I mean, they took it to Euro Disney
while it was still under construction.
They took it to Niagara Falls, where it had a hat.
Yeah, wow.
It had a big birthday hat for Mickey's birthday in 88.
That's an Oz, the great and powerful balloon
in the Disneyland parking lot.
That's its own thing.
But yeah, that's the right reaction, I think.
Anyway, yeah, so the Mickey Mouse balloon was in Red Square
because of that thing, the Visionarium slash the Timekeeper,
the 360 movie that was in Disney World in Paris
with the Robin Williams robot.
Wow.
They are, I believe Jules Verne
is being whisked around the future.
And as part of it, there is one single shot
of Jules Verne in a hot air balloon
when there's other hot air balloons around in Red Square.
It's like a six second scene in this movie,
in one of those Circle Vision movies,
probably the most complex one
because it's the one that had a narrative.
But so you don't see the Mickey balloon in it,
but they shot it in the basket of the Mickey balloon.
Like we have a hot air balloon, we might as well use it.
I see.
Yeah, yeah.
But the weird thing about it is that this was done
in Russia in 1991, and then two weeks later,
there was a coup to try to get Gorbachev out of there.
Like when Yeltsin was trying to take over from Gorbachev,
so there was a big crazy coup situation,
and Mickey Mouse only barely made it out in time.
Wow.
The timing.
If Mickey was there during the coup.
Yeah.
Yeah, the balloon could have been burnt
as a symbol of something.
I don't really know the issues that were at play.
Again, as if you can't tell,
my knowledge of Disney history is very detailed.
My knowledge of world history,
even recent world history is not at all.
You can't walk us through the implications of Glasnost.
The lucid egg of Soviet Union.
That's what I was like, well, is it for Glasnost?
Or they're like, where are you?
American movies are here.
Probably Glasnost.
Probably because of Glasnost, I would have to say.
Probably.
That's for the, save it for the Glasnost episode.
Save it for the Glasnost.
Probably butchering that term, too.
No, I just found Glasnost the clown.
Oh no.
That's terrifying.
The Russian clown.
Did you guys see the pictures of the balloon?
And it's our favorite Glendale location,
Walt Disney Imagineering.
Oh cool.
Rising up above the shrubs.
Rising up from Bio Reconstruct on Twitter,
every theme park person's favorite Twitter account.
Oh, I missed that.
Here he is, you can see the Glendale Air Terminal,
the historic airport terminal
that is now part of Disney's massive
Glendale, California campus.
This is where Jim Cummings learned to fly.
Jim Cummings, the cranked out host
of the opening day special.
Yeah, it used to be an airport and now it's like part of it.
Oh, okay.
Or part of near the Disney campus.
Wow.
What are you showing?
Oh my God, these are crazy photos.
Yeah, and here's, they were doing like an event
for the Roger Rabbit opening
and for the same event, year four swung was there.
Wow.
I would love to drive by and see a big balloon.
Now, not in my younger days.
We all live not very far from Imagineering,
your three hosts, and we all know where it is.
And I think I might be the only one
who has actually done this, but I have driven around
and I've done it during the pandemic,
just like so much can I not get a taste of Disney
that can I like look over a fence
and see anything that's going on?
And the answer mostly is no.
I saw a big thing that maybe looked like, I don't know,
like a giant mermaid tail or something,
but it mostly had a tarp over it.
And I saw a half constructed miniature spaceship Earth,
which I sent photos to Mike and Jason quickly as I could.
Get a load of this, fellas.
A half spaceship Earth rusting in a parking lot.
This is bad.
This is like needing a fix.
Which it gives me a little.
I did it too, though.
Oh, you did a pass at some point?
Yeah, Jane and I drove through once.
It's a little interesting.
It's a very nice area.
They work in great digs.
Did you see anything?
Did you see any tarps?
I saw what looked like the net,
like the framework for the net structure
that they had been launching the Spider-Man creature,
like a flipping Spider-Man.
That's there for sure.
I saw just the scaffolding, no net or anything.
But you used to be able to drive by and see it like set up.
Yeah.
You'd have to catch it.
I think I saw it still with the nets.
Wow.
I don't wanna make anyone jealous, but I saw the nets.
The Disney nets?
Will there be nets when they do?
Cause we're talking about there's an effect.
There's a robot they're gonna supposedly have
on the top of the new Spider-Man ride
at California Adventure that is like a stunt robot
that does flips and they dress it up as Spider-Man
and he does like flips on the building.
I wonder if there will be nets to catch the robot
if it falls.
I guess there have to be, right?
Most likely.
Oh, you see.
You don't want that thing shattering
into many, many pieces.
Yeah.
It would be funny if the first time they try it,
like opening day of that Avengers campus,
it just eats shit and shatters.
Or just they misfire it into the Matterhorn.
Yeah.
It flies all the way from California Adventure
to the Matterhorn.
Legs are just kind of kicking out of the top for a while.
They don't know how to get up there.
Then it's a full day.
People think somebody actually crashed a plane into it.
Those robots are very cool if you haven't seen them.
They released video of them.
I pre-probably talked about this already.
Aren't they called like stuntatronics or something?
Am I wrong with calling them that?
I think I am, but.
They've made a new term.
Yeah.
So you can have like robots.
Guardians.
Guardians, guardian robots.
You can have robots like iron making land, you know.
But anyway, we'll hopefully see them sometime next year.
I hope so.
Or this year, this year.
Oh!
2021.
Yes, of course.
This year.
Of course, this year.
2021.
Year.
The year we're talking in.
Yes, we of course remember we know this.
And Air Force One is what we're talking about.
What have we not covered with this marvelous balloon?
I have a photo of it in front of the,
it's in a postcard in front of the Disneyland Hotel,
but that seems impossible.
I bet it couldn't be that close to it.
But this is what they used it for.
I like, here's really the question.
Did anybody ever see it in person?
Never.
And I ask you guys and I ask the listener
because I'm convinced there were not many opportunities
to see it in person.
I have a picture of one from the Disney Parks blog
that they posted like a throwback picture a few years ago
where it was parked around New Year's one year,
right at the entrance of the Magic Kingdom.
You can see the contemporary in the background.
You can see a big clock.
It's cool.
You can see, yeah, the clock is set up
for the 15th birthday celebration.
That's why the clock only has the number 15 on it.
I'm just realizing.
Oh yeah, look at that.
That's fun.
That's not a misprint.
Where's that clock?
Where'd they put that clock?
Yeah, where is that clock?
I gotta bring that out again.
See, see those holiday crowns.
Yeah, I never saw it.
I mean, it felt, I mean, like any of the big,
what are their big balloons?
They made those big balloons for the party gra parade, right?
Those are balloons, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, Epcot big balloons of the characters for some show.
Yeah, I feel like I never got to see the big balloons,
but I really also, here's the thing.
I may have blocked them out of my mind
because as a child, again,
I was scared of these things in person.
And I probably said this already,
but my father forced me to go up to one of these things
to touch it to try to get me over my fear,
which kind of worked.
And it was right by a Toys R Us.
It was right by the Toys R Us on Gulf Road.
And I don't know what business was opening.
It was giant.
So I went over and I don't remember how old it was,
but I did like go up and touch it.
And I felt okay about it.
But still I may not remember some of these things,
but I don't think so.
I think seeing Mickey, I would have remembered.
Every time you saw one of these big balloons,
you just, you blacked out and woke up at home.
Maybe.
Like from Orlando, you woke up back in Chicago.
That's possible.
Yes, it's a memory that my brain wants to forget.
I did remember that.
Rosamont Horizon series of balloons,
but maybe that's the first time.
I don't know.
We'll know.
What about Scabby the Rat?
Was he in Chicago ever?
What?
Oh.
Scabby the Rat?
Oh yeah, I know Scabby.
Who's Scabby?
Scabby is when a union is protesting a business.
Sometimes they will inflate this giant,
ugly looking rat balloon.
I'm sure Scabby had a lot of opportunities in Chicago
to show up.
Well, sure.
I don't think I saw him, but yeah.
I'm sure he was, he was been around.
I'm sure Rahm Emanuel knows Scabby.
You see Scabby show up outside the Disney parks sometimes
because you know, there's the union issues obviously.
Yeah, Scabby's part of the Disney family character.
Oh, an official Disney adjacent character unfortunately.
Hey, it's Scabby.
Would you have the same respect if Scabby told you
to not be afraid of Scabby?
You'd be afraid of Scabby.
Don't be afraid of me, pussy.
Does Scabby selling Mickey or does he sound like,
I assume he has like a cigar.
Probably.
Oh.
Yeah, I'm Scabby.
Hey.
Don't go on that.
I'm your friend.
Don't be a wimp, Michael.
I'm Scabby.
It's like a harsh,
Don't cross this line, Michael.
The tougher blue 32.
Cut your brake lines if you cross this big line.
Love, Michael, love.
That's what it's all about.
Hey, check out that woman.
She's hot.
It's blue but harsher, what Scabby sounds like.
Yeah.
It's the same dialogue though.
Yeah, Rob Paulson's doing the,
working on the Scabby movie.
Finally, you know him from protests.
Now Scabby's coming to the big screen.
Scabby's journey to become the mascot of
crooked corporation issues.
I'm surprised Scabby for being such a well-known character
has not been put in a TV or movies.
Somebody should really snatch that up.
Present, very present type-E in people's minds.
We see him all the time.
And I think we'll see him all the time this year as well.
I think that's right.
Maybe some problems that people have
with some companies.
Now there was a return of this balloon
for the 50th anniversary of Disneyland.
They made a bunch of things gold around that time.
I think we talked about it with Casey Jr.
that they painted a Casey Jr. car gold
and I think a lot of other opening day attractions.
And they made big gold ears for Air Force One
and they flew him around into the Grand Canyon this time.
And I mean like into the Grand Canyon,
which I think is hard to do, hard to navigate.
Imperils the people operating the balloon.
Shouldn't have done it, not worth it.
But it made it out, it didn't deflate, nobody died.
Wow.
So there was a gold era of this balloon.
Yeah, it seems like they could add stuff to it.
I mean, I don't know how hard it is,
but it definitely seems like it adds stuff to it.
So it feels like they could add stuff to it.
They could make him a little bit more like the new Mickey
on these new Mickey shorts.
Maybe they could add, they could change the eyes
around a little bit, which I like.
I mean, you could put a hat,
you can put different hats on him, you can put whatever.
I saw the hat.
I mean, that seems surprisingly easy.
Mm-hmm.
So I like all this.
I want more of it if we can do it.
I guess balloons are not as,
were balloons hipper back in the day?
I feel like we don't talk about balloons enough anymore.
It was closer to the turn of the century
when it was the main form of entertainment.
That's true.
Around. Balloon shows.
Yeah. Jason, did you ever want to go around the world
in 80 days as a child?
Oh, I can, you know,
I definitely have watched some versions of that.
I feel like I've watched some cheapy versions of that
as a kid, or like there was a cheapy like dollar store
VHS cartoon or something.
Is that your favorite hot air balloon media?
Is that, well, I didn't see, there was a,
was it called the Aerialist?
There was a hot air balloon movie that went on Amazon Prime
like a year or two ago.
And it like, the trailer was very intense
because I think it was the advent.
Eddie Redmayne?
Could Robert Downey Jr. do around the world in 80s days?
Is that another thing I'm making up
that he was announced for that I've thought like,
that I forgot, but I remember.
Fog.
It's just being called fog
because it's about Phileas Fogg, we all know.
You know, Phileas.
Phileas was Pierce Brosnan.
Phileas was Steve Coogan in that unpleasant.
I'm real, I'm putting together the Disney movies
that I least want to watch
and that will be all the way at the end of my quarantine list
are the ones involving hot air balloons.
I do not want to watch around the world in 80 days.
I do not want to watch Oz the Great and Powerful.
Is there a good Disney movie with a balloon?
There must be.
Well, yeah, cause you got to go to Disney Minus
to watch those streaming.
Oh man, Disney Minus was really sitting there.
Is he?
Has anyone's done Disney Minus yet?
I just wanted to pitch
cause I feel like the Donald one looks pretty good too,
but I had some alternate names instead of Zippity Duda.
That you found or that you.
No, I wanted to pitch.
If we bring back the SS Mallard.
Wonderful.
Kind of dry.
That's usually what a water.
It's the same problem with Air Force One, I feel.
Yeah.
I'm going to criticize all of this.
Yeah, okay.
The other, this one is very cumbersome,
but I think that's its charm.
Doonald the Balloonal.
You know, I like that one actually.
Okay.
It's kind of a lot of.
Yeah, I like that.
I like that.
Doonald.
No notes.
Smashing words together, you know.
That it?
That's the list.
Oh, that was a list of,
oh, okay, we're really settling in.
Unless you guys have any, okay.
You were like, I got some to pitch
and you should have said, I have two to pitch.
I burned out typing Doonald the Balloonal
and trying to fight against auto-correct.
You had to take a nap after that.
Yeah, I'd take a nap after.
You slept for 13 hours.
I pulled the sandbags off of the bed
so I could float a little.
Rested, and then he rested.
It feels like we're winding down.
We can start coming back to Earth.
Closing thoughts, I think you're right.
I wish they did things like this.
It did add to the grandeur of Disney in my head,
but I was always disappointed.
I didn't get to see it.
So that's my criticism.
I actually do remember thinking,
I think I may have asked my parents,
is that balloon gonna be here?
And they didn't know.
They didn't know what I was talking about.
But hey, I would have liked to have seen it.
I think it should have been more present
and I would just blame that I bet it's very expensive
to operate hot air balloons.
Yeah, I mean, I think it would have to be like,
yeah, it would have to be a,
it would have to be, they have to commit to it
being somewhere for a while and have a spot for it.
I think it's probably expensive to bring it,
do it this, move it here.
I think if they just carved out a section for it,
maybe they could cut down on cost
because it would just be there for a while.
But yeah, I think that's probably,
they're not gonna just keep it at Disneyland.
They have that big balloon at Disney Springs.
Disney Springs and in Paris.
There's a big balloon.
You can go up in that.
And that doesn't go very high at all.
I think that might even just be connected
to some sort of a wire still.
I don't know that they actually disconnect.
But why isn't that Mickey?
Well, I think it's, sometimes that stuff is,
again, susceptible to the elements.
I found an article where they took the balloon.
It was gonna be at a festival in Iowa
because I guess there was a very bad drought
and an economic downturn in the Midwest farming country
in the 80s and they had a big festival
and they were gonna have,
Air Force One is a big centerpiece of it
and the winds were just so bad.
They're like, we just can't.
We can't put it up there.
And that's a big issue, I think, with hot air balloons.
You're susceptible to the winds.
That's probably why there's a wire
connected to the one at Disney Springs
because you'd fly away. For sure, yeah.
In the Florida hurricanes.
Which is what starts Oz's journey,
but do you really wanna go on Oz's journey?
And the answer for me is no.
Do you wanna get stuck in a hot air balloon
with James Franco?
The answer is no. No, no, no.
It's universally no.
Well, did you survive Podcast The Ride?
Second Gate?
I think they did.
Mickey Hot Air Balloon Edition?
I think that they did.
Look at these other ones that we've been talking about.
I really like that Sugar Bear.
I like knowing that he's Sugar Bear.
I like Digum Frog and I do not like Litty the Clown,
who I will be working to expunge from my computer.
As this is being recorded,
I believe the Genius Bar is not super available
due to pandemic and shutdowns, so I don't know.
I might be stuck with Cliffy running my computer for a while.
Did you give, was there a prompt that said,
what do you give Cliffy remote access?
You may have accidentally clicked that
during the setup for the Zoom.
Oh, well, I did click a button that was,
a window that was so small that I couldn't even read the text.
And now I'm worried that Cliffy wrote
a big confusing Apple warranty kind of thing.
Just made it look like just a black line.
And then in that text,
I gave him permission to take over my computer
and eventually my body and soul.
Well, yeah.
And that little box, that little text box,
about 30 Cliffys are gonna come out of it.
Jesus fucking Christ.
That's like hatching eggs.
Like the, oh God.
Cliffy lays eggs.
Like aliens or their Godzilla.
No, the sugar smacks,
the 50 sugar smacks clown lays eggs
that hatch more of him.
Cliffy, the sugar smacks clown lays,
he has large sugar smack shaped eggs
that come out of his, I guess his asshole.
No, no, he's got a clue.
He's got to be dirty again.
I'm playing the character again.
And he, yeah, he shits out those sugar smack eggs
and then they hatch into little clownlets.
Oh God.
So you think that maybe it,
do they look like sugar smacks?
Like, so you think it's just a big sugar smack
on the ground, but then it hatches?
Football shaped, football shaped sugar smacks,
hatches and little Cliffys fully clothed too somehow.
Well, that's preferable.
I will give him points for modesty.
Okay.
But in no other regard, do I like this clown
or the clowns that he lays?
If they're born early though, they are naked.
Yes.
Okay, well go to term then, please.
Let the clown uniform just stay.
Yeah, cause that's the last month
is when the clown uniform grows in the egg.
And that's when every little clown gets its clothes.
Jesus.
After they lay the eggs in the subway, like you said,
like the Godzilla, the Matthew Roderick Godzilla.
Cliff with me.
Da na na na, na na na na.
Daddy and Jimmy Page's remake about clown hatching.
Clown hatching.
That's right.
Oh God.
I think I'm red in the face from this.
I'm so uncomfortable with this hatching clown notion.
I'm like, I miss Choco now.
You're looking a little clownish if I may say.
No, no.
I'm not red in the nose.
Rosy cheeks and red nose.
No, must fight it.
Must fight back.
Little clownish.
Scott, I'm taking over Scott's butt.
No, stop it.
No, we're ending the episode.
Stay subscribed.
I'm not laying clown eggs.
Stay subscribed to podcast the ride the second gate
for more for regular stuff.
Oh, here it comes.
I feel the first one.
No, no regaining my body, regaining my computer,
hitting the stop bar.
So that this episode ends the end.
Cloud with me.
Na na na na.