Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast is reconstructed from the bones of our superstar limo episode.
It also contains further arguments over cuteness.
Top Disney vocalist Huey Lewis and Ham in the pool?
Oscar Montoya joins us to talk Monsters Inc. Mike and Sully to the rescue on today's podcast,
The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the only theme park podcast that emits a very faint hint
of ginger at the top of every episode.
I'm Jason Sheridan, joined as always by Mike Carlson.
Yes, I'm here on Mike Carlson.
I insist though that this holiday we emit a gingerbread smell, but I am happy with the
ginger most of the year.
Sure, yeah.
It's a palate cleanser most of the year and then it'll just be an assault of like holiday
themed baked goods for like two or three months at the end of the year.
Strongest artificial gingerbread smell possible is what I like.
That's my personal taste, so I would appreciate it if we do it.
But anyway, let's see what smell Scott Gardner would like to hear or hear smell.
Jesus, I'm losing my mind.
Whoa.
How long have we been locked in our apartment?
Hearing smells.
Oh, man.
I'm high, man.
Trippy idea, dude.
Yeah, I know you should have like you should really dove in around the holiday.
You should have like grinded up a bunch of gingerbread cookies and just dove in.
That would have been a nice Christmas.
If you got to spend Christmas alone and then just like scar facing a pile of ground up
gingerbreads, one way to do it.
That is such a kid.
Honestly, maybe I'm in the minority here, but as a kid fantasy and maybe it starts from
DuckTales, but diving into just anything that's not water is such a like it sounds like such
an exciting, fun thing.
Obviously not something that would hurt you like coins, but the idea that you could like
swim in cookies or in I don't know.
I'm trying to think like whipped cream or candy like as a kid, I think I always wanted
to do something like that, but it's very impractical.
Did you guys share this feeling or am I alone?
Am I a weirdo?
Well, you want to do the like ultimate version of it where it like doesn't start to get gross
or inconsistent really quickly or like the material doesn't like break apart immediately
after the dive.
If there's cartoon logic behind it, then sure.
I was just what I flashed to when you said that I think one of the things I miss in Pandemic
the most is like chips and salsa at a Mexican restaurant, but I don't know if I really want
to swim in salsa.
So maybe if I could swim in the chips and just kind of bite them wherever I go and then
release salsa through some sort of like water gun situation so that I could like, you know,
just little spurts because I think swimming in salsa would maybe get a little exhausting.
Chips wouldn't you get cut up if you dove into chips?
That's what I'm saying.
You have to apply cartoon logic, I think.
Yeah, yeah, you're probably getting scratched at some point.
But like, okay, Jason, Jason here, how about this scenario?
It's a giant pool and they somehow figure out a way to cook a brownie inside of it.
So it's a giant brownie filled pool.
Would you dive in?
Because that would be soft and then you could eat your way out.
Would I dive into a solid object?
Yeah, but it's a brownie.
It's soft.
It's a soft brownie.
I think that would still injure.
If it was angel food cake, I think you could get away with it.
But I think the impact of the brownie.
Let's bring our guest in because he's not a log.
He's one of the hosts of the Inside the Disney Vault podcast and the podcast, Podcast Killed
the Video Star.
Oscar Montoya is here.
Hi, Oscar.
Hey, hi.
That's a that's a really good question.
I do agree.
Angel, angel, angel cake, angel food cake.
Yeah, because angel cake is not a thing that doesn't exist.
What is angel cake?
Angel food cake.
That is I think that might be the correct answer here for a soft like landing in some
kind of a non-water dive.
Yeah, no, no, no, no, no, no.
We're we're jumping into food.
And I think the thing is, like, I would want to dive into cartoon food.
There's nothing more delicious than cartoon ham.
You know exactly what I'm talking about.
The look of cartoon ham is like so delicious.
I would love to dive into a pool full of cartoon hams and just munch my way.
I like the idea of this a lot, but would the hams be like full kind of intact hams
that you would buy?
They're not like cold cut, the deli sliced.
No, not sliced ham like full ham.
I don't know what body part that is of a pig, but I mean, it's probably every body
part of the pig. But it's those, you know, it's like that.
Dark reddish exterior and the soft pink interior.
Also, the consistency of cartoon food or just cartoon stuff.
Like if we were living in a Roger Rabbit world where it's like we have our live action
selves and then cartoon selves, the cartoon.
People would have like this rubbery consistency, like very soft, rubbery consistency.
Right. Oh, am I crazy?
And thinking that like the way they've Disney's decided in Toontown, the cartoon
things are sort of soft and foamy.
Do you think the people would also be similarly soft and foamy?
Like the cartoon people, I think so.
Well, they're flex. I mean, obviously they're flexible because like, yeah, they get hit.
If an anvil shoots at their stomach, it bounces past and then they can.
Yeah. So I think there would have to be.
Yeah, they would have to be flexible in some way.
They would have to be soft in some way.
That makes sense.
They can't like feel like flesh and fleshy because they don't have flesh.
Right. No.
Not like muscle.
Yeah. Mickey Mouse.
I don't imagine having muscle and sinew doesn't feel right.
Right. Or like fur, even though he's a mouse.
Like, I know it's not quite like maybe a little bit of like a little like
frosting of fur, just like a little smattering.
But it's not like it's not like hair like our hair.
It's not like an inch of hair.
No, I think the Looney Tunes are furry or like fur and feathers.
I feel like I get that from the Looney Tunes a little.
But the Disney base is so like classic
inkblotty from the like hanging around from early days of animation that like,
yeah, I don't know.
I think soft would be right, because if you suddenly touched like Goofy
and it felt like a human man, it would be like, oh, this is not weird.
That's yeah, this is weird.
So what you're saying is if you touch Daffy Duck,
it would feel different than touching Donald Duck.
Whoa. What's the different?
Like, what's the difference here?
Well, I am saying that Daffy doesn't wear any clothes either.
He just has that one dignified color.
I think it depends what versions of the characters are talking about,
because the new Mickey cartoons, there's a red and stimpy ish
thing they do sometimes where they give a very close up face of the
shot of the face where you can see like detail and like bloodshotness and like skin.
And I feel like that might be the most.
If you were to enter that frame of the cartoon and you touched,
it would be the closest to maybe a human being.
But other than that, it would be what you're describing,
like a rubber rubbery feeling, perhaps. Right.
So I think it all depends because cartoon logic changes so often.
So sometimes you touch Mickey.
It feels like, oh, a cartoon.
It's like a bouncy house.
And then sometimes you touch him and it's like a decaying old man.
Oh, no. It all depends.
It all depends.
Well, in the instance when they show a close up of Mickey and he's freaking out
and his eyes are big and you can see like his skin and you can see what's happening.
I think that's that's when that might.
But then are we talking about the same Mickey, though, like is is the classic
Mickey that we all know and love the same as this like new
reiteration of Mickey, just like at a different time period?
Or is it like alternate dimension?
Yes, I think it's a multiverse.
I believe there's a multiverse of characters because they we've seen
different versions of the Mickey characters.
We've seen different versions of Looney Tunes.
There's been different types of drawings with them.
So, yeah, like in DC Comics, for instance, they call different Earth's
Earth, Earth, one, Earth, two.
So that's right. Make them in the Mickey multiverse.
There has to be like an Earth three, which is the new version of the cartoons.
And they're that's we're giving it away.
We're giving it away for into the Mickey verse is a billion dollar movie.
Yes, you're right about that, honestly,
because then one of the Mickey verses is just in theme park characters.
Oh, interesting.
That look like the ones you see there and they have their own world
and lifestyle, and they obviously feel more like felt.
Interesting. So, OK, so would one.
So if we're making this film, I would say franchise, because we are, by the way,
we are making this blue sky.
We're making it. Yeah.
Would one of the Mickeys in the Mickey verse,
would it be an actor inside of a Mickey suit?
Yes. Yeah, it would be like the Disneyland.
It would be like a and I think generally because it's Mickey
needs to be on the shorter side, I think it's often a lady that plays Mickey.
Oh, interesting.
So maybe the whole narrative could be like, wait, but I'm not Mickey.
I'm like Wendy.
Right. And they're like, no, you're you've been sucked into this machine of Mickey.
So you must be Mickey.
And then it's her journey of like realizing that the Mickey was inside her
and not outside of her. Right. This whole time.
Yes. Is a Mickey shaped pancake part of this?
Can there be a plot arc involving a Mickey pancake?
I think it makes a cameo, but I don't think it's part of the main.
Enough to say, I mean, one coming to life
and having thoughts and feelings would be pretty fascinating.
It's true. It's like Spider Ham.
It's like the John Mulaney Spider Ham is not the star of the movie.
You get some good, good moments, some good set pieces.
Yeah, yeah, sort of. Right. Yes. I like that.
But you're here today.
We're not talking the Mickey versus that we're talking about.
Monster verse. It's the monster verse.
It's your friends and Monsters Inc. Monsters.
Yeah. Mont. Sorry.
I want to say it with all the punctuation, because I think this might be
the theme park attraction.
Maybe it's up there with most punctuation and it monsters,
comma, Inc. period, Mike Ampersand solely to the rescue exclamation point.
So you got four kinds of punctuation there.
Yeah, this is this failed a grammar test, I feel like.
Yeah. Well, it's like jockeying with guard.
It might have been in the lead and then Guardians of the Galaxy
mission breakout might be challenging it now,
because I feel like you've got a colon in there.
I think there's a dash in there as well.
Don't forget disaster exclamation point
colon, a major motion picture ride, dot, dot, dot starring you exclamation point.
I get the game word for it.
You can talk for I think that's really the that's where you take the cake.
Yeah. Yeah. No one's topped.
I don't think anything tops for right.
We haven't found one yet.
Someday. I think for for somebody.
Yeah. Somebody will point out it's got to be one somewhere.
The big change we as has been acknowledged online, the big chance,
I think, is however they renamed Splash Mountain to be about Princess and the Frog.
I think it's possible it might bring five, but we don't know the name yet.
So we're waiting with bated breath.
Splash. Yeah.
You're right.
And Tiana's journey dash dig a little deeper exclamation point.
Double dash.
A little deeper.
Yeah, that's got to be right.
That's the big. Yeah, yeah.
It's definitely in there.
It just feels like a warning, like a passive aggressive, like warning
to the writers, like, come on, dudes, dig a little deeper.
Dig a little more fun on this ride. Yeah.
Oscar, I think initially when I when I asked you to be on the show,
you said, have you done Superstar Limbo and the timing had worked out
where I was like, yes, literally a week ago to do Superstar Limbo.
I mean, it's a very but this is a I mean, this is like
a reincarnated version of the next chapter.
This is a in the Superstar Limbo multiverse.
This is a different world.
It's so because it's similar, but it's obviously something different happens.
So this is Earth to Superstar Limbo.
Let me ask you this. Yeah.
Let me ask you this. Who would get top billing?
OK, in in this who I mean, it could be funny man Tim Allen.
It could be
this could be the stars, the Hollywood stars,
Antonio Banderas and Melanie Griffith.
Maybe in a way, Jackie Chan is the biggest star depicted in that ride.
Maybe like in terms of Jackie, we just fill in one of those.
Regis was the the very first star I think you see
leaning out the door, like waggling money at you.
What a ride. What a ride.
He's luring you with money.
You you were you had some Superstar Limbo fascination Oscar.
Yes, I did.
I've you know, I have to say I've never been on the actual ride,
but I have seen videos of it.
Hmm. I watched the video maybe once, twice every month.
Sure. Show my friends because a lot.
I don't what year did that ride come out?
Because not a lot of people remember that ride. Right.
2001, it was it was opened with California Adventure in 2001.
Right. Yeah. And it was such a weird.
It was just like a weird question mark.
And of course, it wasn't going to be evergreen.
Were they planning to update it every what?
Five years, six years like there was.
Could you imagine still going on that right?
I mean, I would love it in 2021 to still
do a ride 20 years ago, you know, like that would be such a fun time.
Time capsule for me.
But I don't think people would be down for that.
Even relevant stars, all of them at the time, let alone 2001.
Yes, it would be extremely bizarre if it stayed.
But but like, is there is there a celebrity
that's still relevant today that was on that ride?
I think Jackie Chan worldwide.
I don't think Jackie Chan has ever like retired.
I think he's still making movie. I don't know.
I think he's made a lot more movies in Asia than America recently.
And I think he still has the name recognition.
I mean, Drew Carey hosts the Price is Right every day.
Yeah. Just from sheer like how often are you in media?
I think it would be Drew Carey, but he looks especially now much.
Totally different.
I saw it and then now the beard is radically different.
So they'd have to add that.
Yeah. Well, Tim Allen is like he's had it.
He's been on that news show for like 10 years, I feel like, too.
Hey, which speaking of multiverses, that's true.
You know that there was an episode of that show
where whoever the hell he plays on Last Man Standing meets Tim,
the tool man, Taylor. Yes, I saw.
Yeah, I like it to explain that to me.
I don't I don't know if I'm standing.
He runs a fishing and tackle shop, but also is a famous vlogger
for his crankiness. I believe.
Jason, you know, far more than I thought you would.
I. I think that's all that is, is mostly what I know,
and that it jumped from like ABC to Fox.
And I is it still going on Fox or did it finally?
It's wrapping up. No, I think it's.
Yeah, on the way out.
Oh, but it's still there. Yeah, yeah.
But so I had to look up the character to Malin on that show plays Mike Baxter.
And through some justification that I don't know off hand,
perhaps another multiverse, the Tim verse.
Mike Baxter meets Tim, the tool man, Taylor,
the character from Home Improvement.
And there are scenes with two Tim Allen's talking to each other.
Like he's managed to.
I'm almost impressed by Tim Allen's acting prowess to be able to go.
Who is Tim Taylor as opposed to Tim Allen?
Because you think it's the same thing.
But I think what he does is to kind of dial up the gruffness
and sort of in this zone a little more and the whole which you know was
that's the persona, not Tim Allen, the man.
So, you know, I love this kind of horseshit.
This is like TGIF.
I wish things were this.
It's very TGIF. Right.
Yeah, weird. Yeah.
Crossovers and they did that all the time in the 90s.
They had a huge crossover events like NBC had those like weird,
like yearly crossover shows.
Oh, yeah. The black programming.
The blackout, that's what it's called.
I in what was that?
Friends Seinfeld.
Uh, what's the show with?
He was he's Ted Danson show.
Becker Becker. Yeah. Yes.
It was a CBS that I think that was that would have been a blackout with CBS.
Oh, wait. No. OK. Oh, was it?
Oh, it wasn't Boston Common.
I think that was.
Wait, are you saying that all the shows experienced a blackout on the same night?
Yeah. So all the.
Yeah. Must see TV this back when like must see TV Thursday.
There was block before shows.
All four shows were, I believe, took place in New York and there was a blackout.
And so they all made sense.
I think they all made sense on their own,
but they all had to work the blackout in.
In some. I got it.
I got the list and there's no way I could help you guess one of them.
You will never, ever guess the other.
OK, really?
OK, so similar to Seinfeld a little bit like stand up.
Vehicle also lives in New York.
They all have to be in New York to make this work.
NBC's sitcom star in ninety four is when this was.
Can you think of what that is?
Is the show named after the comedian?
Hmm. It's kind of a two hander, but one of them is sort of Seinfeld esque.
OK.
Oh, oh, I'm not going to.
So it's not.
It's not that guy who I always know the name.
It's not one of the Dabney Coleman shows.
Wait, how did you got that one?
Not the other. This is what show was.
Oh, my God.
I was going for Mad About You, a very popular show.
Wait, what was the show that you said?
Do you know the name of the show?
What was it called? The show is called
Wait, my internet's blanking.
Mad Man of the People starring Dabney Coleman.
I don't remember the show at all.
I just remember Dabney Coleman, a guy, an actor.
I barely remember.
I remember the name from the 90s.
And I feel like I was talking about it to you guys of like,
you know, Dabney Coleman had two different sitcoms back in the past.
Wow. Wow.
Wow. Now I need to Google search and see what he looks like.
He was in a lot of kids movies.
I'm trying to think what the what the bigger with, you know,
the Beverly Hillbillies or Tootsie he's in.
He's in nine. Isn't he the boss in nine to five? Yeah.
Yeah, I think that was the biggest one.
He sort of looks like Dr. Phil in this picture.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah, sometimes.
Clifford is in Clifford. Yeah.
There you go. Oh, he's in the towering inferno.
OK, yes, I remember him. He's everywhere.
He should have been on Superstar Limo.
Put Dabney Coleman in the mail, honestly.
The ride would have still been there.
It should have been renamed the Dabney Coleman experience.
Yeah.
It's just like how they get into the blackout.
It's three of the biggest shows ever.
And then Madman and the people gets to coast on the way for the blackout.
That's what I I was like, it's not Ned and Stacey.
It's not Boston Common. And it was just out of madness.
This is some of the most obscure trivia I feel despite being network TV.
As I as a very young, nerdy like tween,
my one of my favorite things to do in the summer was to watch this
programming block that USA Network aired called.
They was it was either prime time in the A.M.
or P.M. in the A.M. and they would show sit.
And so it was like wings Ned and Stacey.
It was all like sitcoms.
Ned and Stacey.
So that was a vehicle that was Tom.
Yeah, Thomas Hayden Church and Deborah Messing.
It went like two, two and a half seasons, and it was before
sideways and before Will and Grace.
But that was that was what I liked.
That was what I evolved from Muppet Babies Rewinds to watching that.
Did you watch USA up all night as well, Jason?
I don't remember USA up all night.
I really I would just turn on Comedy Central and watch whatever was on for hours.
So absolutely fabulous for many, many hours in a row.
That's what I remember.
And I didn't understand any of it.
I did not remember.
I did not understand the UCB show sitcom sketch show, the original one when it was on.
I did not understand Viva Variety.
It was all I got kids in the hall.
But like the others, I was just like, what's Viva Variety?
That was a bunch of the Reno 9-1-1 and state people.
Oh, OK.
Yeah, they did a lot of those, too.
I think they ran. There's more episodes of that than there is of the state.
I think that's right.
Exit 57 was the other one that was them, too, I think.
Can I say the strange fact also that Dabney Coleman's
Madman of the People was frequently directed by Monsters Inc.
actor John Ratzenberger?
No, that's right.
Who shows up in this ride?
There is a character from Monsters Inc.
The Yeti. Very fun little thing.
That's one of the that's a delightful little door that opens up.
And I guess that gets us out of the territory of Viva Variety.
I think that's a good point.
But Oscar, you're a star, just like the writers,
just like the guests at the end of Superstar limo.
So something comes back around.
Feel free to, you know, don't hold yourself back.
So Oscar, do you like Monsters Inc. the film?
You covered it, I'm sure, at this point on your show.
Yeah, I love Monsters Inc.
But I love Monsters University far more than I like Monsters Inc.
And that was that was an unexpected surprise for me
when I covered it on the podcast,
because prequels are always to me a bit of a miss,
because it's like, why do we have to do this?
Why do we have to go back?
Like, it doesn't make any sense.
But to me, it hit harder.
Monsters, especially with Mike Wazowski storyline.
And it's really have you guys seen Monsters University? Yeah.
I thought it was really charming. Yeah, it was great.
Yeah, it's very charming. Yeah.
But Monsters Inc. is great. Yeah.
So both your fans of both.
But the second one is your preference.
The second one is is a slapper, as they say.
Yes. I got to revisit the second one in the theme park world.
I think of the second one as like around the time it came out
and right after those Monsters you hats.
Yeah. Just became immediately best sellers.
Merch in all the theme parks. Right.
You know, the aesthetic, but no ride yet for Monsters.
No, I guess you had to know it into its own thing.
They should just open a Monsters, an actual university
in Disneyland Resort, like a full credit at school.
Yeah, sure. And it's like as expensive.
And they also have their own loan program.
So they already have it for the annual passes.
So they can do sort of like predatory loan
to people who just want to be in Disney.
This is a potential money.
Hey, listen, Disney, if you're listening, which I know you are.
Oh, yes.
This is potentially a money grabbing thing.
Literal Predator.
It was the predatory loans.
He's a monster. Yeah.
I mean, for a while in the 90s into the 2000s,
you could go to something called the Disney Institute at Walt Disney World.
And that was I mean, man, we have.
Oh, man, we should do a Disney Institute episode.
That thing was so you definitely should,
because it's it's a weird part of Disney history.
It is. Yeah, it's very strong.
I mean, Michael Eisner went to some adult retreat sort of thing.
And he's like, we got to make so we could make money on this.
We could do that.
Shitsy classes.
And that is pretty much long gone at this point.
I think there's still like, you know, business professional classes
and education workshops you can do.
Oscar, the fact that you know the superstar limo and the Disney Institute,
you're you know, some of the strangest, weirdest ends
of Disney lore.
I yeah, yeah.
Any other that you're you're fond of bizarre corners of the of the Disneyverse?
For me, I mean, it was what's the I don't see.
I'm not very familiar with Disney Walt Disney World, like Disney World.
I don't really know at all.
Disneyland is what I've been obsessed with.
And it started when I moved to California
because I was not really a Disney person at all when I lived in New York.
And when I moved to L.A., all these grown ass adults
were so obsessed with Disney and I was sort of weirded out by it.
I didn't get it. I was like, what?
It could be a lot.
It could be certainly a lot at first.
100. Yeah. At first, because listen, in New York, we're not close to the park.
So we don't have that sort of like, you know, foaming at the mouth,
passionate drive that these Disney adults have.
So I was very scared.
And also, I was
I was born and raised in Colombia.
So I was like kind of really unfamiliar with Disney movies and like
that whole thing. I like missed all of that.
So yeah, I was like, I don't I don't really get it.
And my friend, Claire and co-host of Inside the Disney Vault,
she was like, well, have you been to the parks?
And I'm like, no, no.
Isn't that for children?
And she's like, no, I'll take you.
So she took me and it it truly was a dive.
It was incredible. It was like, what?
I get I got it. I got it at that point.
I was like, oh, there's magic here.
There's like actual magic here.
And then I become obsessed in the 20s.
Is this like later for you a little bit?
This was five years ago. Oh, my God.
So this is possible to be a total late bloomer with all this stuff.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
I'm interested in your adult years.
What were the things that really made you go like, oh, wow, I get here.
This is the thing.
These are the things that people say they like.
Yeah. I mean, it was the like to me, the dark rides have always been
like for me, the reason to go to Disneyland.
You know, I'm not a roller coaster person or like a wild like six flags.
Hell no. I got nauseous at the freaking Wiley Coyote ride, the children's ride.
I was like, I ain't doing this shit no more. No.
And Disneyland had like just enough excitement for me
that made me feel like a sort of bad ass like Space Mountain is a child's ride.
But I feel like that's probably like the threshold for me as far as
thrills go, you know.
But it's aesthetically so thought out, incredibly well, like really, really.
Put together and the details, it's the little details
that I was super impressed with.
Yeah, that I was just like, oh, there's like so much history here
and there's so like I can keep coming back and discover new things.
You know, that's what I fell in love with.
Yeah, yeah, that makes sense.
That is beautiful to hear.
I mean, we talk about detail.
I would say this is a details oriented podcast.
I would I would I would say that.
So, yeah, that makes a lot of sense, whether it's the Pinocchio ride
or Madman of the People with Dabney Coleman.
It's the details that we.
But also the thing that I'll say to you about Disneyland
that I really like is how creepy it is, like specifically
when it comes to the dark rides. I mean,
mm hmm. Yeah, you go to you go to hell in, you know, Mr.
Chow. Yeah, like what if what if shot like what a surprise?
Like kids did that all the time and like didn't even blink an eye.
Like how creepy some of these rides are the Pinocchio ride.
Terrifying, terrifying.
There is. Yeah. And there is an aspect and I
there is an aspect to some of the rides where you do feel like
there's a little like hauntedness to them because there's an old
the smell that smells old.
It's some sort of building material that they don't use anymore.
So it smells like your grandmother's house, maybe.
And there are you can like feel like you can feel like the ghosts.
You can feel like a Waltz ghost just being like, hey, have fun out there.
I got to feel like that. Yeah.
And also something so like
popcorn and rainbows looking.
I mean, it's got to have a secret dark past.
You know what I mean?
There's got to be a lot of nasty underneath all that, like pretty paint.
You know, sure. Of course. I love it.
Yeah. If it's been around a long time. Yes, for sure.
So well, this is this attraction.
I think Monster's Inc is sort of like feels like kind of an advanced
version of the of the dark rides.
It like has some things in common with them, with the Fantasyland rides.
You know, specifically, there is the like
I've certainly seen it as like a complaint or criticism about it,
that the characters, they aren't full animatronics, their mouths don't move.
But it is in that sense a throwback to, you know, your Alice in Wonderland,
your Mr. Toads, you know, where there is a suspension of disbelief
and not every one of them is, you know, does the full thing.
But you're still I don't know, you can still get caught up in it.
Like it's not a requirement for me that they all have fun.
Yeah. And I think it honors the vibe of a dark ride
while adding a layer of polish to it.
You know what I mean? It's not like an insanely,
you know, still feels like a dark ride, you know, which I like.
I like I like the animatronic look to it.
But, you know, the the robots moves like smoother.
There's like it's like prettier, brighter, you know, but it's still still.
It still works. Yeah. Yeah.
It's it's yeah. Sorry. Go ahead, Jason.
Oh, I was going to say, yeah, it's got like, you know, mid 2000.
It's got a newer technological base early to that than like the base.
The original fantasy land rides have been kind of redone so many times.
This this has only been redone once.
I'm sure they've done basic maintenance to it, but it went from,
you know, Superstar Limbo, which barely lasted
a two years didn't even make it that long.
They wanted that.
They wanted the Yankee so fast.
If you want to like, you know, we we did a whole episode about it,
which you can listen to so not to read cover any of it,
but just to be to lay it all out.
When California Adventure opened, there was this one dark ride
that was like a current pop culture, snarky, holly, weird sort of vibe
that was just instantly greeted as the with with like the worst feedback
that any ride ever has gotten out of the gate, probably even more.
So this rides, I think people dislike more people.
This bad figment ride always comes up.
But like it wasn't that that was never reviewed by the newspaper.
Like, I feel like Superstar Limbo got in trouble because, wow,
Disneyland opened up a whole new park. What's it all about?
Oh, my God, it sucks.
Like this ride just like got all the stink of the early bad PR.
So they had to get it out of their base app, though.
Though Oscar, I'm sure you wish you could have experienced it.
Oh, God, yes.
But I will say even for 2001, the ride feels incredibly dated.
Like it just yeah, it expired the second it opened.
Do you know what I mean?
Like it's it's what who thought of this idea?
Who thought this was actually going to work?
I love it because it's campy and trash.
Like, that's why it's great.
It's fun to make fun of it. Yeah.
The force to genuinely be excited to get on that ride.
For real, real. I don't know.
I don't know if it has much like I don't know if there's a person.
Yeah, genuinely.
When when Monsters Inc. opened to there was also like a lack of that
classic Disney dark ride in California Adventure.
So like, yes, it it filled a purpose.
That movie was a big hit.
So we got that that those characters into this park.
And yeah, and it it I think it does a pretty good job of like using these.
Horrifying bones of superstar live, like using the taxis
with the little TV screen.
Yeah, you re blatantly reusing,
like putting a yellow jumpsuit on some animatronics. Yes.
Yeah, because as we discovered, I think,
or as we guessed during when we are our episode of Superstar Limo,
like some of the bodies and the heads are partially under there from the celebrities.
That's so crazy. Have you ever seen any of these side by side?
Have you seen the like explanation of here's the here was the Superstar Limo robot
and now here it is? Is it? I haven't.
No, I don't know what robot. I found a bigger.
We showed a couple of these in a slideshow at our live show, but I found
Jim Hill Media.
They did a pretty good breakdown with even more that I'd never seen.
So you can see poses side by side.
I didn't realize how many I thought there were only like two or three.
It's a ton of them.
Here's Jackie Chan. He's kicking and hanging off a wire.
And then here is a two eyed sort of two half heads.
Child Detecting Agency.
If you don't know, that's the the yellow jumpsuited characters
that wear hazmat suits because everybody's afraid of children in Monstropolis.
So, you know, you slap these suits on these these bones of bad wax figure.
Not even what no wax figures look good.
These are like, you know,
like the bad action figure, they're like low end action figure
versions of celebrities. Here's.
Yeah, it's like the time.
It's like the Times Square caricatures that you would get. Yeah. Yes.
Like that's that's whoever designed on proportions.
The resume was I made.
I made five dollar caricatures in Times Square.
It boils somebody down to one interest.
That may or may not be an interest of theirs, like in Drew Carey's case,
Maps to the Stars homes.
Why does it make sense?
So he pops out, Drew Carey would pop out and fan out all of these maps.
So they replace that with here's photos of Boo, the missing child.
So he has the same gag and he says in the ride,
here's the child we're looking for.
They really try to hammer home the justification.
Here's Cindy Crawford.
Who looks uber trashy in that original depiction?
I mean, I'm scared.
She's especially frightening.
And then there's just like kind of a big one big headed
spraying a bottle.
I don't know. It's a decontaminant spray, maybe.
Here's Tim Allen with a microphone at a stand up club.
That doesn't even look like Tim Allen at all.
No, it's like very Duracell man, like those weird.
Yeah.
So no longer a microphone, but now like a big sucking machine or something,
but still with weird crossed legs.
It's kind of this casual like men's model version of the hazmat suit.
But they had to break his hands.
The hands are at least tilted.
They had to break the animatronics hands and reset.
And on some of them, they clearly remove the head.
Oh, you're right. Yes.
Like when we go back up, the moth.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, absolutely.
Yeah. Replaced one head.
We had to carry doesn't have a head.
That's right. It's just a big back.
Drew Carey's head was removed.
So Drew Carey's body is under there in the suit, but his head is somewhere else.
It's missing in Imagineering somewhere.
That's frightening.
Do you think he's wearing a I assume this is an Aloha shirt.
Do you think he's still wearing this shirt underneath the contaminant suit?
I want to hope he is.
But if I had to guess, I don't think they took the shirt off and they're
it's sitting in a closet somewhere in Imagineering.
That's my guess.
But I'd like to think that under there is the clothes.
I am afraid still Drew Carey.
If you pry off the yellow, it'll just be big splotches of industrial glue.
Like on home renovation shows when they pull up carpet and it's like, wow,
look at this beautiful hardwood under all this rubber cement.
They had to pad out.
If you look at the yellow suit, they obviously had to pad out the legs and arms
because because, like, for instance, right, there were
on star tours now, there are the robots that check your luggage.
Do you know what I'm talking about?
That go like there's not your luggage.
They test luggage and they're like, yeah, whatever.
And they're like pointing at that.
That's a prerequisite to get on the ride.
You have to bring luggage.
Yeah, you have to you have to check a bag to do it.
But you can see the robot has a little tail and those are like
they were what geese on America Sings.
They were they originally like a bird, a robot bird.
So I'm guessing that these aren't just exoskeletons under here,
but it would be funny if it was just like,
you know, when the Terminator is burned and it's just a skeleton underneath
underneath the yellow suit.
It's possible it is. I don't know.
We got to get to the bones.
They're going to see what's down there.
If if that's the case, I mean, I will say it's incredibly impressive
that they were able to build a monster's ink ride, just like
put a monster's ink paint over this star, you know,
it's pretty clever because it's the right slaps, the monster's ink right.
Yeah, you know what I mean?
Yeah, definitely.
It makes sense.
Are you? Yeah.
Wow. This literal one to one ratio.
There's so many.
And apparently even it's not even all the hazmat suits.
They're apparently Regis Philbin turned into Randall.
The the chameleon Steve Buscemi.
Carrie, that one's really hard to parse.
He's got money in his hands in the Regis version.
And then it's just a weird clause.
Yeah, they did the most work with this.
Share that shares just another hazmat anyway.
Yeah. So bizarre to look at these.
Yeah, they did a really seamless job.
I was trying to think and I haven't been on every ride ever.
So I can't really make an official ruling.
But this is maybe like the number two redo behind.
Like there's a ride in Japan called Sinbad that I love.
That's amazing.
But it was a much different ride in its first version.
And if you go on it now, you wouldn't necessarily know
that it was in this strange.
I mean, you wouldn't know.
We didn't know there was a very strange version before.
And I think it's the same with this. Right.
If you go on Monster's Inc, you wouldn't be like, oh, this is clear.
Sinbad based on the adventure or the comedian?
Well, the adventure.
The adventure.
Comedian. It's not.
That's an idea. That's another million dollar.
It's not about Sinbad.
You watch him like you watch his experiences growing up,
what inspired his standup, the colorful characters in the neighborhood
that influenced his bits
and what he's doing in his golden years.
Yeah.
Now, believe me, I would have said that's one of the best rides ever, too,
if I had gone on.
Yeah, Sinbad's journey to comedy fame.
The now did you guys come across?
I don't think we talked about this with Superstar Limo before, but the whole.
So in the timeline of it, like within the first year of that ride being open,
it was like we have to do something.
We got to get people.
We got to get this ride out of here.
But there were other people saying we can't lose that capacity.
This ride does eat people even though and there's not a lot to do in this park.
So I don't know if it can go offline for that long.
Can we keep the bones and do something with it?
And Monsters Inc is what they landed on is that what Monsters Inc came out in,
what, 2003.
So they didn't have even have that option.
2001 to do a ride out of.
Oh, what's 2001? OK, sorry.
So they could have, but they didn't make it there for a little bit.
Do you guys know about what it almost was instead of Monsters Inc?
Oh, my gosh. Wait, was it a Chicken Little ride?
Oh, yeah. What?
I'll tell me it was Chicken Little.
Oh, I'm on the rain.
What? That is the I think that's the actually that's not the worst Disney
animated movie of all time. What's the worst?
It's dinosaur. Do you remember dinosaur?
You think dinosaurs are worse on this?
Well, now here's the question. You've seen dinosaur.
Do you remember when they obviously, you know, the main character, Aladar?
We all love Aladar, the primary dinosaur in dinosaur.
The iconic. Yeah, the iconic.
Remember when Aladar is a baby, he's just born and you see him
pee and fart.
Do you have any recollection about like how you felt about the baby version
of the character Aladar?
Off like off putting incredibly strange.
Oh, yeah. Oscar, look at Oscar.
Look at I hate it.
I hate this. Disgusting.
Why? Why bring this up?
A debate for what feels like a year.
I am apparently the only until now the only person
who didn't find that to be specifically cute.
The key, the word cute and in fact, very cute has been used by our
by people on the show, by much of our audience.
There's no way.
Thank you. Jason and I think that's cute.
He's cute. He's cute.
Cute little guy.
Explain to me why that is.
All right. Well, he's wiggling around.
Let me bring it back up.
No, Jason. No, Jason. I'm sorry.
Look at. OK, here's the baby.
Aladar is farting on the bottom here and he like lets out a tooth.
Look at his little like face like it's so maybe it's just
maybe I just need to have a baby.
Maybe that's what's ticking in my head.
But no, look, he looks like a baby that is like 10.
Your baby is a satiate, Scott.
Babe, I have one.
You don't need one.
Babies are cute. This is not.
I don't like this because it looks like it has real.
It looks too much like a human and it has that weird animatronic
uncanny valley vibe that I don't go senses being spoken on this podcast.
We've regained cheeks.
And he got your own pockets.
The dinosaurs don't have cheeks.
Yes, they do look as little cheeks kind of like he like
there's a little sneeze when he lets out his little fart.
Like it's so cute.
He's got the little he's got these little arms like his little like
that's very cute to the short arms with kind of the wide body.
Don't like this.
Every technological marvel.
OK, yes.
Humans have progressed.
Getting the beginning of the new century.
This was a technological marvel, a technical.
Logical Marvel was the flying whales in Fantasia 2000.
That was a technological marvel.
And then we didn't need dinosaur.
We didn't need this weird technological experiment that was.
I'm keeping this up.
We certainly didn't need chicken.
I'm just kind of forgot.
No, no, no.
I'm like conducting a little orchestra here, much like the evil Ivan Ooze.
I'm like, yes, finally.
Oh, yes, Oscar.
Keep complaining, Mike and Jason, defend yourselves.
I I'm happy to defend.
I'm happy to throw the topic out now and do another hour.
I can't believe that.
I'm baby.
Have you seen the movie, Mike?
Have you seen? No.
No, I haven't.
Wait, you haven't seen it.
No, I forgot about that.
Mike got a new phone last year and he's like, oh, guys, hey, check it out.
I got the new iPhone, like sent us a screenshot and baby.
Yeah, that's the man with the wall.
They always look at it.
He wants to look at every day.
I was crazy and had to photograph, had to get a second device
to photograph his phone to make sure we saw that that was the wallpaper.
Lindsay, Lindsay, my girlfriend, Oscar, you've done her podcast many times.
I texted her during that time and she said, yes, very cute.
She agreed with me.
No, I love Lindsay to death.
But this is where this is where both of you are incorrect.
Boy, this is well, I just want to tap out here.
I'm worried it's this is this is this episode is peak for me.
I just need to go like I feel like I've been to the spa because.
OK, Mike and Jason, do you find a lot of things cute?
That might be it.
Oh, if you think that they're the aladar is cute,
then you might think like everything is cute.
Well, I'm not a man who's afraid to call something cute.
Like I would call something cute.
So I am not opposed to the term.
I'm not a cute troller.
I believe I don't believe that I've been accused, I think, by Scott of trolling,
calling people cute just for troll purposes.
And I don't believe I do that because
there's been characters on the show and the Patreon, at least,
that we've discussed that I think are not cute.
And I'm not like Fuzzbucket is a movie that came out on the Disney Channel.
I know Fuzzbucket very well. Yes.
And I hate Fuzzbucket is a little turd and I hate him.
And you're just a hater, Mike.
OK, that's it. You're just a hater.
I get it. OK, that's fine.
But that's OK.
But Riff, the fourth Barney and Friends character,
which is he's an orange.
Turning away.
That was a big, that was a long take.
You you you might just like dinosaurs, I think, because there's.
Oh, yeah. I am a dinosaur fan.
I have a question for I have a question for all of y'all.
OK. Yeah. Who is cuter?
Baby Aladar or Boo from Monstersling Boo?
No, OK. All right.
OK, well, I'm going to wait in yet.
Let me take a look here.
No, remember, like, is really cute.
This is ridiculous.
The way she calls, she calls Sully Kitty and she calls Mike Mike Wasowski.
I mean, just to me, like, you know, thank you.
Oh, it's yeah.
Maybe one advocate.
Yeah, I'll say boo. I'll say.
All right. But grudgingly, but I don't even know.
You didn't want to say it.
If your heart couldn't. I don't want to say it.
I feel like it was sort of set up here in this question to make baby
all that I look bad, but I will admit I'm an honest.
I'm not a cute troller.
Nobody puts baby Aladar in a corner.
But you you think
Dinosaur is a worse movie than The Good Dinosaur.
Oh, my God.
That's a great question, because they were both atrocious films.
OK, so the only thing that saves the Good Dinosaur
is where they eat those berries that are hallucinogenic.
And there's not like weird trippy animation that was like too short,
way too short.
Yeah.
That's the reason why I would rank The Good Dinosaur higher than Dinosaur.
Dinosaur looked just like brown crap.
Yes.
Like cracked dirt is the.
Most of that movie.
You're just looking at like sad ground.
That's what it is.
It's like weird clay.
It's like someone tried to do a, you know, claymation project.
And just like didn't color any of the figures.
Good Dinosaur, though, I didn't see dinosaur in theaters
and I would have been a kid.
So it's not like I could have been like, let's walk out.
But like Good Dinosaur was the closest I've ever been.
I imagine baby Jason just that those are his first words.
That is something baby Jason would say.
But but seeing Good Dinosaur, I can picture sitting in the Arclight
Pasadena going like, what's that?
Policy of getting your money back?
Like, is it too far into the move?
Like and I knew I think it was probably not helped by like I knew going in.
They had like fired everyone from the good guy.
They fired the whole voice cast and they brought on new direct.
Like it was such a debacle.
It was a mess.
The trouble.
So probably feeding not even despite it being a hot mess.
It's not it doesn't compare to Dinosaur, which I think is a bigger mess.
I have not said it is.
I said it in my podcast.
I said it in inside the Disney of all I told listeners.
I was like, listen, if you if Dinosaur is your favorite Disney movie of all time,
let me know.
And I've had four people reach out for people thinking that dinosaur is the best
Disney animated movie, better than Aladdin, better than Lion King.
Yes, better than fucking Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs, better than those movies.
But did you serve when they saw it?
Because if you see a movie, any movie at the right range, like anything,
and I think, yeah, I think and that's it.
Yeah, they were like, I saw it at my formative years.
I was like, OK, well, yeah, there it is.
And that happens with theme park rides.
Yeah.
Yes.
Boy, there's boy, there's enough opinions out there for everyone to have,
I guess, like the most craziest opinion you can imagine.
Somebody has it.
Yeah.
I mean, if you put it out on the Internet, people will, I mean, love to engage.
Yeah, well, and more dinosaur discourse.
We stepped right in it like an Aladar poop.
So, oh, no, no.
Oh, I bet it's really like a real nice shape, a cute shape.
No.
Oh, boy.
OK, so to back up, because I think we left it hanging where it did sound like I was
saying that there was a home on the range ride proposed.
I don't think that's the case.
What they wanted to do, the quickest fix they could imagine for this ride was
we're not going to change the vehicles.
We're not even we're going to try to not change the settings if we don't have to.
But we got to get these creepy celebrity animatronics out of there.
But what do you replace them with?
You can't just have people go through cardboard flats.
Well, wait a minute.
We have just started.
It was 2001.
We have just started redoing all of the Disney stores in America.
We're starting to gapify them.
We're making them as boring as they can possibly be, just like a big swishy D
instead of like the fun characters up.
And because if you remember what Disney stores used to be like, and some of them
are like the whole second layer of the store, essentially are a bunch of characters
often filming a movie.
I think it depends store to store what it is they're doing and what characters are
up there. But they were starting to retire that theme and get rid of all of these,
not animatronics, but like maquettes, essentially of all the classic characters
that could turn and stuff.
They wanted to flood Superstar limo with yanked Disney store maquettes and call it
Goofy's Superstar limo.
This was a plan on the table for a long time.
And it got far enough that then head of the resort, Paul Pressler, was given an
after hours tour of the park.
At least they did part of the ride decked out with rejected characters that were
sitting in the Disney store warehouse.
They like decked it out for us.
So this ride did kind of exist.
That's audacious.
Isn't that bizarre? Like weird.
Could you imagine?
They buy up figures from malls in Ohio and Indiana and truck them out to Anaheim.
And that's your ride now.
What would be the storyline?
Goofy's, if it was Goofy's Superstar limo, is it so it must be all the same stuff.
Like it's you're on the way to a movie premiere for Goofy.
But then like the three little pigs are going to like give you a makeover.
Like is it that kind of thing?
Everyone's favorite Disney characters, the three little pigs.
You see them a lot.
You know, nobody really cares about them.
You know, Dumbo is going to read you the Hollywood Reporter on the way.
I don't I don't know.
Where where are Goofy's real friends at?
Where's Donald? Where's Mickey?
Where's Daisy? Maybe you got to save them because like
you can't use more than one unless we're going by Mickey verse multiverse rules.
You can't have like 20 Mickey's in the ride.
I don't know.
Mike, you never came across this odd.
This was like a Jim Hill discovery a long time ago.
No, I missed this. This is very strange.
Yeah, it feels like I mean, if you if you just think,
OK, take Superstar Limo and you just replace up replace, put Goofy on the ride.
It's still obviously a bad ride, but it's not.
Horrible, like whatever the the scale of the characters,
it must have all been so odd for them to go.
There's no way we can do this.
This looks so. Yeah, well, because they're small.
The yeah, right. The biggest issue.
With with the ride was that there was.
OK, the magic with the dark rides is that there is a storyline.
There's a narrative happening.
Yeah, the narrative of like going to a movie premiere is so loose, so flimsy.
There's nothing there for for them to just replace it with Goofy.
It's still going to suck because there's no story.
At least with Monsters Inc. There's a narrative.
They literally copy the plot of Monster's Inc.
But it's like, what can I attach myself to and Goofy's Superstar Limo?
No, I think you could force one in.
But it would be expensive.
And my pitch is that Goofy is trying to get to the premiere of the Goofy movie
and he's causing chaos in Los Angeles.
He's goofing everything up.
But then you got to get Max in there.
You got to get Roxanne in there.
You got to get Pete in there.
You know, you got to get all these guys and all these all these other characters.
But then there's power line in there.
You got to get power.
Yeah, he knocks.
He unplugs the power at a power line concert.
Oh, I like that.
They just go.
Why doesn't this power line concert the place they're going to?
Oh, that's good.
Oh, yeah, it doesn't even have to be.
He's in a limo to a concert.
VIP at the power line concert because he's trying to help.
It doesn't have to be a limo.
It could be his car, which is a reference to the Goofy.
Why isn't there just a Goofy movie ride?
Because then you can have like the you know, Disney loves these like drops.
You know what I mean?
And there was a waterfall scene in a Goofy movie.
You could incorporate that in the right.
It's yeah, that would be great.
I mean, it's timing timing wise.
Everything was falling apart when Goofy movie came out.
Sadly, that's true.
You feel like you're a Disney disaster.
Yeah, if I feel like if they announce that now we're doing a Goofy movie ride,
I feel like people would like the most ardent fans would be pretty fucking psyched.
Oh, yeah, because there is a huge fan base for that movie.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yes, it for sure.
Yeah, I they don't they're not like doing cool stuff like that.
And I know that sounds like that's one of the dorkiest thing to say.
They're not doing cool stuff like make a Goofy movie ride.
It's not really what I'm they're not doing like you mean it is an asterisk next to your cool.
Yeah. Yeah. Well, it's like when I it's like when I said that like a box lunch
at the mall has hip Disney merch like wristy cats merch.
I was like, all right.
Well, hip, I guess is not really.
Hey, kids, come on in.
Take a seat.
Let me tell you about the great mouse detective.
Yeah, that's a hip choice.
That's a for your Disney shirt.
Hey, kids, have you heard of fun and fancy free?
There you go.
It's what they called packaged film.
Very melody.
Hey, you know, Looney Tunes was a later.
Mary Melody's is what they used to call them back in my day.
Look, I wish you kids are all probably about the lunatics.
The extreme ass kicking Looney Tunes.
Yes. The managers like Greg were going to have to we're going to have to buy.
Voice uses you can't talk really off putting.
Mike, I'll give you credit, though.
I know what you mean.
You like they will they will invest in a number of few palettes of like power line
t-shirts and lapel pins, but I won't they won't like commit to a multimillion
dollar. No, it needs to be something they're confident in now.
They're going to make like three to six movies of sadly, like it doesn't feel like
unless it's like truly like Disney Vault classic, then like in Tokyo, they're
building a new right.
Are they building a new Peter Pan or in Tokyo?
That's right. Yeah, that's right.
Yeah. Yeah. So like something like that, maybe they'll build and they're building
they built the beauty and the beast ride there.
So unless it's one of their prestige things, it's only going to be new stuff.
I feel like and not cool, edgy Disney material like goofy movie like the black
cauldron or Oliver and Company, the cool ass shit that Disney used to make.
Huey Lewis, nothing cooler than Huey Huey Mike.
And for the listeners, Mike just put on a bolo tie.
Yeah, I'm cool now.
I'm changed. I'm cooler.
Yeah. So I wish I mean, I wish
as I think I've we've said on the show, I think I to I is the best Disney song ever made.
Maybe it's like part of your world and I to I is they're tied maybe.
Hmm.
Ty. Oh, wow. Yeah.
I yeah, I died as a slapper.
I have a weird bizarre favorite.
Go ahead. And it's from the 1977 movie The Rescuers.
Oh, I think I know.
And it is from it's called The Journey and it's
the very beginning intro song in the opening credits
where it's it's sung in the perspective of a message in a bottle
saying and it's it's in the sea.
It's in the ocean waves and it's a beautiful montage opening
credits where they're going on a journey.
Hence the song. And it's beautiful.
It's great. It's sort of like the Carpenter's except a little spooky,
a little bizarre. And I love it.
I think that's my favorite Disney song ever.
Oh, my God. I've certainly seen the movie, but I don't remember this.
Yeah, it's not stick.
It that does actually doesn't stick out because I haven't seen the movie in a long time.
That's I mean, it sounds great.
It sounds like that'll be so good.
That immediately will be back in our that'll be one of the hipper things we like.
Once you put it on a radar, I think that's what the song itself.
But yeah, the rescuers, the rescuers is already, of course, very hip
because it's a little more obscure, too.
But the song specifically.
Well, and right.
I remember watching the rescuers somehow as a kid.
But the VHS I had was rescuers down under, which is like the tonal op.
It's like the brightest movie I can remember from my childhood because it's an off trail.
It's just so much sunlight. Yes.
And that first rescuers is so dark, black, dim, green, dim and stuff.
That is such a such an interesting switch between those two.
What song was in the rescuers down under?
What was there like?
Is there one? I don't know the answer.
What was your song song years later, too?
That was like there was a pretty big gap between those movies.
I cannot recall. That's a lot.
I don't think there is a Oliver and Company was one of my first like in theater movies.
So I as a kid. Oh, yeah.
Oh, that's good. That has good music.
It does. Yeah. Should I?
Why should I worry?
That's a good song. And then Bette Midler has a song in there as well.
That's also the bond.
You know, maybe my favorite Disney song is the Huey Lewis.
Once upon a time in New York City, which I just learned was a Howard Ashman, actually, like a quieter.
Yeah, I even referenced in the documentary.
But Howard Ashman meets Huey Lewis, which is pretty cool.
That is a good that is good.
Interesting. One of the synthier Disney songs.
So that that adds up for me to go back to this this pre Monsters Inc.
history. There's one more thing I want to throw out.
This one seems like this. I don't know that this one got any got anywhere.
But also, Jim Hill claims that there was almost a they almost redid it quickly into Miss Piggy's Superstar limo.
All right. I was trying to throw them up.
They're really hung up on the superstar aspect of the ride.
Got to be a super star.
They love that name. Yeah.
Like Superstar wasn't a thing before.
I mean, I think it was a thing before.
You know, why are they so near this and limo too?
Because, you know, the cars don't look like limos.
No, they're I mean in the monsters, they're caps.
Yeah, it just changed.
They are. Can you imagine that being a limo?
Yeah, so oh, good.
I was going to say, sometimes you can't let go of an idea.
Yeah, yeah, it's hard to say goodbye to those scrunched little limos.
Yeah, but Monsters Inc.
They did the right thing.
You get in a taxi. They changed entirely.
The port authority. You get in a taxi.
And it's great because it's like you walk in and then, you know, you get a picture of the city of Monstropolis.
Like you get newspaper clippings, you know what's going on.
You get into the something that, you know, really isn't that explored in Monsters Inc.
But you explore the actual city, which is like, oh, that's fun.
I feel like I'm a monster in this ride.
It's very it does the job of making you feel like you are a citizen going on this journey.
So you sit in the car and it's great.
It's just it's fun. It's I think it's a well, I don't want to say a plus because it's not perfect, but it's an a ride for me.
Well, it's got a lot of tricks.
I like like the at the top of the ride where you you see the footage of the monster giving like the man on the street and he's doing the like the the you know,
Yokel had been abducted by aliens like talking about the child with the eyes and tentacles.
And you come around the corner of the ride and then you see the like statue maquette thing.
You see the interview happening in real life.
I think that's a nice trick.
The Randall, I mean a lot of the Randall tricks are very good.
Him swinging from the door color changing towards the end like Randall has sort of a similar.
I know I'm realizing I'm cursing Randall poor Randall, but Randall has a very similar Jack Sparrow in Pirates vibe on this ride in a better way.
He has more fun tricks of like, oh, there he is.
There he is.
And it feels like they put some more time or yes, they're better things than just like Jack Sparrow and the barrel and stuff.
Yeah, but I apologize to Randall for the association.
Well, Randall is a villain.
You wouldn't mind this this ride.
You know Randall's listening.
I don't offend him and he's very sensitive.
I know.
So that's what I was doing.
I mean this ride ate it by like, you know, the voices of like Steve Buscemi, Billy Crystal and John Goodman too.
Like right.
Then let's not forget Jennifer Tilly and Jennifer Tilly.
That's what I that was the last one.
I was trying to think of like who is Cecilia?
Oh God, it's the goddess Jennifer Tilly.
And also, I mean it also the ride also has my favorite scene, which is Harryhausen's the sushi restaurant, which is a nice nod to.
You know, the creator of all those stop motion movies from like the 50s, the 60s and 70s like Sinbad, those Sinbad movies.
And yeah, like I love all of that.
That chaotic scene in the restaurant was like so perfect.
God, I loved it.
Oh, I love that.
That scene is the best.
That's my favorite scene.
I think that's like that's not a that's a common opinion to have.
I assume that's not crazy is that that seems like a lot of people love the Roz at the end.
The doors are cool.
All that stuff is cool.
But yeah, that sushi that's yeah.
And the ginger, of course, the smell in there, which I think we determined is probably the only theme park ginger smell that exists.
I don't think we've found another example of them with fake smells.
We did a fake.
We did a fake smell final four last year.
Who broke down the best fake smells in theme parks and what's what was the best?
It was it.
I forget it.
ET.
The ET ride.
Oh, yeah.
Right. Of course, the forest.
Wait, what was the smell like a forest?
Wow.
And so, yeah, so I forest but it's you know, that doesn't sound so great.
But yeah, if you were there and if you go in Orlando, there's just a magic to it.
A musty magic is the right still.
Yeah, yeah.
Still going to Florida.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, really.
They took it out at Universal.
Yeah.
Gone in Hollywood.
Oh, wow.
Yeah, so that one.
But ginger was in the mix.
Didn't make it that far.
I will say this and I don't want to get us, we're being very positive and this will sound negative and I guess it's a little negative.
But I always forget about all this stuff because I don't go on this ride that often.
Mm-hmm.
Because the queue, the exterior of the queue, inside the queue is great.
I find it very kind of similar to like almost like Men in Black where I really appreciate how like mundane it feels.
It feels like it's part of the world.
Both of those movies have aspects where you have like very mundane officey type like things put on fantastical, I don't know, constructs.
I don't know what words I'm saying here, but you get what I'm saying.
It's very like office like and then it's a fantastic world.
Yeah, I think to add on to that, Mike, I think that there's when it comes to getting on the ride, the waiting is the waiting element of it either makes you
believe that you're like a stranger coming into this like strange land.
So it either impresses or it emerges you into that world, right?
And I think the Monsters Inc.
Ride does a really good job of making you feel like, oh, this is I impart.
This is like normal life for my character, the person that I am in this ride, you know,
whereas like the Hogwarts ride in Universal Studios is very much like look, be impressed by all this cool stuff.
Like, I don't think Monsters Inc.
Does right.
It's very much like this is your everyday life like.
Yeah, I mean, yeah, the fun of Monsters Inc.
is like the mundane this of it's putting on like just like making it making scaring kids,
not something that's mystical or fantastical.
It's just like a job.
It's a boring job.
And that's what's fun about it.
And then you get that vibe initially of like you're going to work, which is which is fun.
But I will say the exterior and the place this ride is located sucks.
Yeah, it's bad.
And it doesn't that we've I think we've found this on a lot of episodes
and we found this with the Soarin in Florida versus Soarin out here the Soarin in Florida.
I'm not happy with what's outside.
It's inside of a big building.
There's a lot of stuff.
It's kind of confusing and I don't really have any desire to go to it because of that, even though it's the same ride out here.
But the ride's version out here has a very cool hanger.
It's very inviting.
The location makes sense.
And it's so interesting how I really feel like that makes a huge difference on if I go to the ride a lot or not is like what it looks like
and what the area around it feels like and the place it's in in California Adventure is this just weird empty lot.
Now that's been used a lot for different like festivals, the glow fest festival, the mad tea party.
These are all things I like, by the way, Tron, the Tron, whatever it's electronica electronica.
But during the day, it's nothing.
And it's just this weird empty square.
And then the exterior of Monsters Inc is just like flats, just sort of boring, cheap looking flats.
And every time and I feel like maybe I go once or twice a year on Monsters Inc.
And every time I go on and I go, hey, these things are great.
Why didn't I? But I never want to go on the ride.
And I swear it's just because of its location and what's going on with like traffic flow out there.
I yeah, I 100 percent agree.
It is in a weird. It's also I believe the only dark ride in California Adventure.
Well, Little Mermaid now. Little Mermaid now.
Oh, Little Mermaid. Yes. But see, the Little Mermaid placement makes a lot of sense.
I mean, also it takes a lot of space for a not that impressive ride.
And you know, with Monsters Inc is just sort of like.
In the middle of nowhere, it just feels very tossed out, like just like an afterthought.
Yeah, you know, so I totally agree.
Of course, it's like a messy.
It's like the last part of the park that's sort of untouched
because, you know, they put all that money into it years ago now when Cars Land started.
And it feels like they've been like, we're we're getting to this.
We swear we're getting to this.
And then they like touched it with putting in Guardians ride.
And they're like, we swear we're going to do something soon.
But in the meantime, we're going to throw like chairs in the middle
and then we'll put like a Black Widow photo op or you can meet Black Panther
or Captain Marvel over here.
Yeah. But like by a soundstage.
And it's like, are they actors?
That doesn't make any sense. It's chaotic.
It's just chaotic.
It's a lot like there's a lot going on every time you go there.
Like when Jason and I were there for the Guardians opening, it was like
the summer of heroes.
And then it's like this really like militaristic music plays
and an SUV drives by with a Black Widow.
And we're like, we're supposed to like Black Widow after this, like show
of military strength.
Like, yeah, of course, she's not doing it.
Well, but I think the reason they haven't adjusted it in addition to cost is like
the both pro and con thing of like
back lot soundstage themed areas is its container.
You can put anything in the container like a movie's big hit.
You can get it in there.
Yeah. If we need we need something to distract people, we need something
that take people away
from the main part of the park.
Well, put something short run in the back lot area because it's like a movie studio.
You can put any movie, you can put any TV show back there.
I think the thing I like about the exterior is the
2D style of like the credits for Monsters Inc.
It's one of the movies where they do the credits kind of in like that 2D
throwback style.
And I would say the one thing I've always wanted to see from Pixar is a full length
2D animated film or like a 2D 3D combined like that paper man.
What are you, Jason? What are you saying?
What are you? Because Pixar has never done that.
I know that's what I'm saying.
I think that's crazy.
Oscar, that's part of that.
Disney's job.
That's my hot take.
You leave that to Disney.
Pixar does not do that.
But that but what if they they could some of those shorts, they get a little
animated, you know, shorts.
Paper man is not.
The shorts are a little different.
Yeah. But like that's that's that's dangerous talk, Jason.
You know, the way that's dangerous talk.
The wrong people hear that and you can be in serious trouble.
But you do see like what people, you know, international like Secret of Kells or triplets
of Belleville, like these very interesting 2D animated films.
And I think, you know, you're looking for more innovation.
Yes. Well, I'm just I'm thinking like, you know, you when you see like
Pixar artists like Doodle or like when they do shorts or they go off on produce
something on their own, it is often not like that CGI kind of style.
Right. And so I don't know.
I just think it would be interesting to know that is that's a good point
because like I do remember in the 70s with 100 and walled dimensions
being like a shining example of this is that a lot of their animations
were sort of shown as like rough drafts in the final animation.
You could see the line drawings in 101 Dalmatians.
Like it just it looked a little like the scratchy.
But it's yeah, the scratchiness.
And it was it added to the aesthetic of that movie.
And I want to see more of that.
I want to see more of like, yeah, show us a little of like a pared down Pixar film.
Because it's like every Pixar film is such a friggin like a bullhorn every year.
It's like I want to see like a quieter or like a I don't know, like a gentler.
One that doesn't have to be a tent so much.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yes. Not a temple understated exactly that.
Yeah. A little weirder. Give me an odd movie.
That isn't the good thing.
Well, I think baby elder should come back, quite frankly.
No!
In a new feature.
I was looking back through some rumors and for a while, I think before,
because like what probably will happen, I don't know what's going to be the final fate of Monster's Inc.
But it does feel like Marvel will keep swallowing this part of the park within the next 10 years.
I don't know if they'll probably get rid of Monster's Inc.
And maybe maybe they take the heads off other characters and put different Marvel heads on perhaps.
Like Drew Carey's body will still be there, but it'll be like Hawkeye's head now.
Onto Carey's body.
Just a weird Jeremy Renner like head.
With an...
Jeremy Renner head in the style of Superstar limo.
Oh, I got it. I got it. I got it.
It's Gambit's head.
Whoever they cast is Gambit because he has the four pamphlets and they turn them into playing cards.
That would be fan...
That's perfect.
Look at that. I'm saving money for the company right here.
So it's the X-Men Superstar limo.
X-Men Superstar limo.
It has to be Superstar limo again.
It has to be Superstar limo.
And Beast builds them all like they get rid of the Blackbird, the jet, and they still have a new limo that they ride around in.
Well, because you're a student.
You're a student at the Xavier Institute, you know?
Yes.
So you haven't gotten to the jet yet.
So you got to go on these like rinky-dink limos.
They're called.
But it stands for something, you know?
You got to drive them to make money to pay your way through school.
Yeah, for your predatory loan that Professor X loans you.
That is actually can...
Like I've been rereading the Chris Claremont, like the 70s and early 80s X-Men stuff, and they do have a long fancy car that like I guess it's like well, Professor X is a rich guy.
So he would have this.
But like when Cyclops needs to jaunt into that, they were going into the city to go to a nightclub.
He's like, well, let me just drive our big car.
See, so you can like you can weave that into the ride.
All of that.
You know what I mean?
All of that story.
Yeah.
That's look, these are great ideas.
But I hope that happens.
But there was a time, according to rumors and hearsay, that this section was just going to become monstropolis.
Whoa, really?
Wow.
Oh, yeah.
So they were going to add more stuff to that part of the park?
Yeah, build it out more, make it look better.
And then there would have been also, I believe, I believe I was reading correctly that there would have been an additional ride, which was the Monsters Inc, which I've seen this rumor.
And I'm sure this was for sure rumored for here and for Florida.
Monsters Inc door coaster.
Yeah.
It would have been a roller coaster, probably not a crazy one, but it would have been a roller coaster.
But it would have been a pretty fun little ride through like doors and through sort of the world, which seems great.
How would you be strapped into a door though?
Well, you're not in the door.
You'd probably be in some sort of, I'll say a limo.
Let's just say it's a fast limo.
You know.
Taxi cab, some sort of public transit to play up the sort of.
The door maintenance limo.
On the limo, it says this is a door painted on it.
Yes.
So that, so yeah, there was a, there was a time I believe when that could have happened.
I remember even people showing pictures of when they were going to demolish and now it's Mickey's Mickey and the magic.
What is no, not magical map.
Well, Philhar magic.
Geez.
Yeah.
They were going to demolish then the then Muppet Theater and they had the the balloons in the air, which they use in Imagineering to see how high things are.
Like if they would have to build, they use, they're not called trial balloons.
That's not right.
But that's a different thing.
They send the balloon boy up.
Yeah.
See if he gets high enough to get scared.
Right.
Falcon.
Let me down.
But I think on all four corners of the like existing building, they put a balloon up based on, okay, this ride will need to be this tall to see sight line wise, how it'll look from different parts of the park.
And to see what it would look like.
Yeah.
Just to sort of visualize what it would look like if they had to build a very tall structure right there.
So I believe they even got as far as maybe measuring stuff like that to do that here.
But I don't think it's going to happen.
I think it's going to be superstar limo with X.
No way.
That's kind of fascinating.
Are you seeing all of Hollywood?
Like if you just turn in that Hollywood area, is that Monstropolis from the get go?
I think it's just going to, the idea was maybe just those back lot, like the sound stages and that area they use for electronica and then with an additional ride and then maybe some eating thing or some restaurant.
That's cool.
Merch.
Harry houses.
Sure.
Harry has a good sushi place in the parks.
That'd be amazing.
They don't have a sushi place at Disneyland.
That would have been great.
Oh man.
So yeah, so I think that was, yeah, there was a time when that was very possible.
But we'll see.
Wow.
Now we're going to get a fantastic four sushi restaurant.
It would have been the exact same sushi though we know.
It would have been the same quality.
It would have been bad.
Yeah, it would have been bad sushi, but the one sushi is going to be real long.
One's going to be charred.
And one's going to be clear.
The wrapping is going to be like jellyfish clear.
And then the last one will just be on a rock plate.
Yeah, it's a valid cleanser.
Yeah.
Man, I mean, I want this expanded Monstropolis.
That sounds really good.
And because that, you know, when you're behind the flats and looking at that most usually empty stage where they don't do shows very often, that's one of my least favorite zones in a park.
Anywhere.
I really hate it.
And it's a boy.
It was so lame that around Christmas, that's one of the only things you could see.
Just really added to the depression of the Christmas festivities.
They have to blow that whole zone up.
Whatever happened.
I would love if Monsters Inc stayed as long as it could.
Yeah, oh yeah.
Yeah, right.
I think it does hurt and it puts you in like a weird bad mood when you're going on to the ride.
You think about not like, do I really want to walk over there?
Do I want to walk past all the scaffolding and the barely painted metal walls?
It's a bummer.
Yeah, the Monsters Inc ride is not a place you go first.
Technically, like usually, no one's like gunning for that ride.
You know what I mean?
No one's going to be like, I'm going to go to Disneyland to go to that ride and then go home.
No, that doesn't happen.
It's usually the last ride of the day.
You go to Disneyland and then you go to California Adventure, you know, and then you're tired at this point.
There's nothing.
There's nothing pretty to look at anymore.
You know, so like you're sort of in a bad mood going into it and that taints everything.
But I think there's a power to the ride where you come out of it feeling kind of renewed and feeling good.
It's a good one to like if you're bright and colorful and nice.
And well, and you see your friends, you see like the nice, you know, like Sully bonding with Boo, which is adorable.
I mean, any depiction of Sully anywhere, whether it's a walk around or on any ride, just
I don't know. It's nice to see Sully is very lovable.
Yeah. And then if you're wearing Mickey ears, the Roz animatronic calls it calls out the fact that you're wearing ears.
And it's very nice. That's one of the things Roz can refer to.
Yeah. So she'll say like, oh, the lady in the front, nice ears.
Are those yours? And it's like that only gets triggered if you are wearing a Mickey Mouse ears.
I did not. I do not know that.
Very cool.
Roz work. Is that like one of those situations where there's like a number of phrases and somebody has to be there activating them?
Yes. Yeah. Yeah. It's one of those like I don't know if the Mr. Potato Head works the same way.
I think there's an actual actor.
No, there's not. It's a it's a button thing, I think, because it's Don Rickles voice.
Oh, it's a button thing. But I think it's not a Don Rickles.
It's not like a 25 year old Don Rickles voice impressionist, because I think sometimes I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Take the magic away. Sorry to crush your dream.
I know you were angling for that when it reopened.
If you want to audition on the podcast right now, go ahead.
I mean, Disney listens.
Call us chowder heads. Yeah.
Whatever. Probably shouldn't use some of the material he used to use, I'll be honest, in 2021.
Yeah. Yeah.
It's not aged very well.
The explanation that like, you know, you're all big people.
You know, we're all big people here tonight.
You know, I don't pick that doesn't fly as quite as well nowadays.
I think you could do some ribbing and pull that off.
But yeah, some of that stuff.
Yeah. So, well, yeah, the potato.
I was going to say potato head. Yeah.
He just I remember there's been times when he like really can target people in the in the line.
And then sometimes he's just singing a song.
Yes. Yeah.
If the guy wants to take a lunch break.
I'll say this about Monsters Inc.
In terms of when I write it, I think Monsters Inc.
And Little Mermaid, I usually end up writing because there is if you spend a lot of a day at California Adventure,
let's assume at normal times, everything's operating.
There is a crush in the middle of the day at that park where the rides you really want to go on have super long waits.
All the restaurants are packed and you're like, I got to kill time for a fast pass or I got to kill time to like let the crowds die down a little at the restaurants or stores.
And that is usually Monsters Inc.
And Little Mermaid, just because they never stop loading.
That is when I find myself on one of those sorts of rides.
So it's like an afterthought. It's not even like you want to go there.
You don't like it's an afterthought. You hate the ride, Jason.
Well, OK, I'm not going that that I think I will admit it's my it's an afterthought for me.
And I'm saying it's not fair. It's fair that that's what happens.
I do think it's helping the Guardians now is something I love and go to.
So I'm more forced on the way in the flow of traffic.
Do you like the Guardians ride more than Tower of Terror?
The one that was there for sure the one that was there.
I like more. And I also I also though find now Tower of Terror in Florida a little lacking because of the drop sequences and as fun as the one.
But for sure, I like it better than what was there before the very because it's a it's a little better in Florida.
There's more theming and the one in Florida to the Tower of Terror.
But so I am going that way more often now, which leads me on there.
But I'm mad. But you don't go. You don't go for the monsters, right?
You go for Guardians of the Galaxy and then you make the stop.
Yes. And I don't I'm sorry to the right.
It's not fair because I said I go on it.
It's almost like because of where it's located, all it's all the good feelings I just had disappear so quickly because I'm in a really barren weird place again.
So it almost feels like a dream. It's like you're right.
And also you're right in terms of like tone as well.
Like you go to Guardians of the Galaxy, that area feels like very like adult to me.
Like it's not a place that like it doesn't have the whimsy or magic that I think like months that right should belong that that right belongs in Disneyland.
Number one and number two and like a more youthful area of the park.
Yeah, it's also I feel like maybe if they did like if they just built a really sort of I'm trying to think like an office like an office building that's a little stylized or something, something that like looks like a thing.
And that is, you know what?
It's you know, the thing is here's here's let's be quite honest.
This is an afterthought even for the people working at the parks.
Literally, it's an afterthought. It's not you know what I mean?
They didn't not mean to make monsters in the right.
And it shows it shows it shows in the park.
Yeah, it's like it's and that's and that's a shame.
It should be like the Dunder Mifflin office or something like they should give it.
I mean, look, the actual it's the most popular show of all time.
I get you may as well.
I know they don't own it, but give it an homage.
Maybe like there should be a little something there to sort of to sort of make me go, oh, I need to like the Haunted Mansion or whatever.
You see it and you go, oh, you get that good feeling from the Haunted Mansion.
I walk by Monsters Inc.
And I go, there's some paint is a flat piece of cardboard with the colors on the outside Monsters Inc.
Well, do you want it to look like the like where they work at like the factory?
Is that good?
I mean, probably better that than the Dunder Mifflin office.
I would know what.
No, I think it should be the actual Dunder Mifflin.
I think that's what.
All right, Scott, it's got to be something from the movie.
Whatever something that makes logical sense.
What a stickler.
Even for the container part of the part.
All right.
No, you're right.
Like, because they isn't it?
There is a better exterior in Tokyo in the Tokyo ride, which is a different ride called Ride and Seek.
And it is left over from the exterior that was there, but it lent itself more to that industrial, the grand building and the the the atrium that you walk into when you get into the ride.
You get in the line is like, you know, like the the monsters are very proud of where they work.
That's the thing you really feel in the movie.
They like they're so proud to be scarrers or makes a scare assistant or whatever.
The you know, they love this how these hallowed halls.
And yet I think you feel that when you go into the Tokyo one this year, you're in these narrow corridors and then the building itself still is sound stagey.
You want to feel Sully's pride when you walk into the thing.
It might help Sully's.
Well, he landed on the.
Yes, and everyone was that he made Sully made a miracle happen.
And do you still get on a cab in the Tokyo Disneyland ride with that vehicle is supposed to be this whole other.
Oh, but it is. Yeah.
And it's this premise where it is as opposed to this ride, which is kind of during the events of the movie.
This is post the movie where it is not screams the power of the city anymore.
It is laughs. So there is a fun game that is done now that is a hide and seek game with a flashlight.
So every so you get a flashlight.
It's basically like a Buzz Lightyear laser tag ride, but you point a flashlight instead of a gun.
So it's like a more family friendly.
But then boo gets loose again and you got to find boo and Randall still gets come up and he gets crushed into a cube in this really amazing.
Sequence. It is. It's extremely cool.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, it's it's interesting.
So I'm trying to I'll stop talking about the exterior because the ride itself is good, but it is funny.
Like thinking about like pirates in Florida doesn't have the queue that California does.
California has obviously that buildings exterior and it's a lot better.
The one in Florida doesn't even have like the you know how like there's the restaurant blue by your restaurant doesn't have that intro part to the ride.
It feels like the best rides like really easy in and out.
But also when you see the building of it, also it's like enticing you.
It's like the best rides have all of that in it.
Yeah, but also, I mean, we have to think think about the fact that the Monsters Inc.
Ride is a substitute ride.
You know, it replaced a as much as I love it, a shitty ride superstar limo tours.
It's it's just like it was never meant to be the star despite the name having superstar in the title.
This was an afterthought. This was like honestly a ride filler.
Let's be real. It was plugging a hole in a rowboat like that's exactly it.
The expectations are different when they start from a blank expansion pack.
Oh, yeah. Build fresh as opposed to like, yeah, reskinning.
We've got to get something in here. People say there's not enough characters in this park.
People say there's not enough family dark ride kind of things in this park.
So it kind of was a necessity being the mother of invention.
I need to cut it. Exactly. Yes. I need to be well, I need to be nicer.
Yeah, be yeah, be nicer. There's always room for improvement.
I mean, you know, here we've been trying to do our thing and get plus it up, keep it as is or burn it down for insurance money.
I think there are some options here and I'm not sure like in Mike's case, Mike is your version of this.
Make it a grander experience.
Fill in some of those things they couldn't do in the rush job of 2005.
And so Dunder Mifflin exterior like Scott character actor outside voice like actor inside talking like like.
There's a Michael Scott big head. Big, big.
That's good. Yeah. And then I mean, you could put as many as you want.
Dwight, we could have Dwight out there. So that would be my plus up.
Let's just get these office characters. But then it's the monsters in.
It's a monster sink. But people want to see the office characters.
I think this is perfect. Rendered like superstar limo looking like scary miniature dummies.
That'd be good. They're still under there. Turn Cindy Crawford into Pam.
All right. Yeah. And Melanie Griffith is Angela.
That's right. I think this makes Jackie Chan is Oscar. Yeah.
It makes sense. Your carries. Dwight, I guess. Yeah.
There's an equivalent. But Regis Philbin stays. Yes, yes. In honor.
All right. Does anybody else have strong feelings about what could happen?
I think I feel like I'm not in dire need to.
I think you got to plus up everything around the ride.
Just take that awful flat out of there.
But I think if with the right new ride, I wouldn't miss this.
Jason, what you said last time about Joe Rody's quote about like these things are like Broadway shows.
You get a run and that's a good run and then something else has to come in.
I think for the right replacement, I think I could say, hey, Monsters Inc was great, but let's do the next thing.
But it would have to be it have to be good. Can't be an afterthought.
And I will not keep it a limo if possible.
Yeah, I will see. Yeah, I feel like sadly I'm not going to be so upset if they get rid of it, but it's not fair.
I mean, it would be nice if they could move it and make it like a little grander somewhere else.
Like, I don't know. I mean, they do sometimes move stuff like this, but they probably won't.
But it would be fun if they like really massively built out Toontown or something and put this I guess this doesn't really make sense in Toontown.
But does it really make sense in Hollywood?
Certainly not. Yeah, where would it make sense? It doesn't really make sense.
Yeah, because it's like there's like California Venture is Pixar area.
Like I think they've supposedly I don't think they've said it said it unofficially, but like California Venture supposedly is Pixar, Marvel and Disneyland is Star Wars and then classic Disney.
Apparently they have some also in Disneyland.
But there's also a ton of Pixar because they didn't make that rule before. Yeah. Yeah.
It's from now on. Right. Yeah. So it's a hot mess.
Going forward, supposedly that's what it is until it changes tomorrow.
Jason or Oscar?
Oh, my God. Yeah, I was just going to say like if they fully build out like Marvel Comics in New York in this area, I will be in heaven if they do it right.
Like they're they're opening Avengers campus and I'm excited to go to it.
But it's like it looks like a college campus with a jet on the roof.
So I don't know, that's not quite that's not quite the excitement I had is reading the comics as a kid was like, oh, I want to go to college.
Like, and that's not even the X-Men's man.
The X-Men's mansion was like, I know the X-Men are in there.
It's like, oh, there's a building like learn from Hulk.
He'll teach me. Yeah, that feels weird.
Also, it's not canon and it's like, OK, I don't know.
I I could do without I like Spider-Man.
I like Spider-Man being in the Avengers.
Like I like him being worked into the universe.
But like the stuff that's coming with the ride, I'm sure I will enjoy the ride.
But like all this stuff about like, hey, stem, honk, it's don't you like step?
It's like, I don't know.
Can't kids do you got to do?
I don't push this.
Listen, if they're committing to a university put monsters university.
Hey, there we go.
And presumably there's some liberal arts at that Monsters University,
because, you know, we got to have liberal arts graduates.
We can't just have engineers and stuff.
Otherwise, you end up with all these Silicon Valley psychos.
And also, like in the in the case of like of what you were saying, Scott,
about keeping Monsters Inc. right, it's like, I don't mind it.
I don't mind them getting rid of it.
But if we get rid of it, as far as I know, that's the only Monsters
Inc. representation we see at the park.
And that's unfair.
That's unfair.
We got to have Monsters Inc.
somewhere in the park.
So we either like tear it down and rebuild another Monsters Inc.
thing or move Monsters Inc.
somewhere else in the park.
Well, there is one frozen treat.
The frozen treat stand in Pixar Pier.
Get out of here, Jason.
Get the fuck out of here.
No, that's not what I mean.
I know that's not what you mean.
But I do like that if you go by that door screen at the right time.
And I think this is a good use of screens.
Oh, yeah.
The doors to different places.
The Yeti offers you like a lemon ice, which you can then go by on Pixar Pier.
That's nice.
Why can't there be little doors like that, like just scattered throughout the park?
Yeah, that would be great.
You never know when someone will say hi.
Like doors that don't lead to anywhere.
They could be like storage spaces, but just like make a door on the outside
and it could lead.
Have those little interactive moments with like the Yeti or Cecilia, et cetera, et cetera.
I would be satisfied with that.
Where the front of the building.
You cover the front of the building and different doors at OE.
And then you can stand there and watch a little show between all the doors.
That's fantastic.
Like an updated Laugh-In.
Oh, yeah.
Yes.
Monster Laugh-In is pretty good.
That's a good show.
Billion dollar ideas left and right on this episode.
Could they turn the Hall of Presidents into Laugh-In maybe?
Maybe like with doors and like that, at least like you can get the like you won't be like
a serious political thing anymore where people boo the president.
It'll just be like Nixon and everybody opening up a door and saying socket to me.
Are people really booing presidents at the Hall of Presidents?
Well, I'm sure they do.
The last couple presidents certainly.
No one's booing Zachary Taylor.
I don't think so.
Interesting.
Not for a few decades.
It'd be great to see a Lincoln with like the Daniel Day Lewis like socket socket to me.
I don't know his voice.
No, no, no.
We're on the world stage now.
He did because they say Lincoln they think had a much higher register that he was portrayed
in like old fifties and sixties movies.
And so like, yeah, Daniel Day Lewis doing a very interesting voice in that movie.
Interesting.
But he's so tall.
That is weird.
Yeah.
Deep voices.
Yes.
They have a they have a plot of land, I think, back in Pixar Pier that could be developed on.
Yeah.
So that's where door laughing should have it in the rights.
Or laughing, cooking and will be sad.
And then the ride can then it'll become a literal afterthought.
I guess.
Yeah.
That's sad.
I'm trying to provoke Oscar with these divisive words, I think.
I mean, you're not the yes, I'm mad about it.
But listen, I can't be mad at the truth.
And that is the truth.
It's it's an afterthought ride pains me to say, but it is.
And I think as far as an afterthought ride, it's pretty dang good.
It's great.
It's true.
And it's great for what it is, what type of ride it is.
And I like it better than Little Mermaid.
Yeah.
100 percent.
And that was not an afterthought ride.
That was like a ride they wanted to make.
Huh?
So you might be disappointed.
I think we should we could bolster Monsters Inc.
Like the fan response, I think we should like the next thing they put on
like a meme kind of T-shirt is the guy with the photos of boo.
His line is I mean, part of the fun of those, you know, the yellow seat
decontamination guys is they you can have them say anything.
And his delivery when you go by him, he says, I have information on the girl.
Like he says the weirdest he says it the strangest way.
So if Disney I think will make big bucks if you start selling, I have
information dot dot dot on the girl on a T-shirt.
I catch that.
All right.
I love that.
Put it out there, Jason.
Yeah.
So hopefully they do it.
All right.
I think I'm just going to make the T-shirt.
Yeah, we might actually.
Yeah, we have a T-public.
Yeah, we should just go.
Now it's a race to the make it a race to the finish.
Whichever one of us does it first cashes in first.
So we're all going to make a dash to a T-public for now.
Oscar Montoya, you survived podcast the ride.
What a blast.
Thank you so much.
This was really fun.
This is so fun.
Thank you so much.
Let's exit through the gift shop.
Is there anything you would like to plug?
You can follow me on Instagram and Twitter at Ozzy Mo Ozzy ZYMO.
I also have a bunch of podcasts, one of them being a music video podcast called Podcast
Kill the Video Star, where we will we are on a quest.
Me and Mano Gappi are on a quest to find the top 100 definitive best music videos of all
time and then the listeners get to vote for which one makes it to the countdown.
I have Spanish I keep presented to the Latin X comedy podcast.
Listen to that wherever you listen to podcasts inside the Disney vault where I and Rachel
Chapman and Claire Logren watch every single Disney animated movie in chronological order.
We did that.
We watched every Pixar movie.
Now we're watching every D com in chronological order and that is a charade.
Wait, every one.
That's fun.
Every single D com Disney channel.
I didn't know that acronym.
Oh my God.
Wow.
Yeah.
They're all on Disney Plus.
This is a pretty like deep archive there.
Yeah.
So it's a fun little actually after Disney Plus we had a nice little boost because people
now could like watch them.
Watch along and like, you know, but yeah.
And other than that, you can watch me on a Fox show called Bless the Hearts is an animated
show every Sunday at 830 on Fox or wherever you watch that show.
Yeah.
And you did didn't like Fuzzbucket.
I love us.
You didn't like funny words in my mouth.
Yeah, that's true.
OK, I apologize.
You know, since we're going back to that conversation, I have a little addendum that appeared during
this recording.
This is about like about an hour ago.
I was trying to close out of some windows so that the Internet would be a little better.
And I clicked on my email and I had a new email that was updating me about an eBay order.
Let me explain.
I looked up the date on November 29th.
I purchased on eBay something for Mike Carlson for Christmas.
It gave me an estimated delivery date of December 18th.
December 18th rolled around.
No sign of anything.
I checked the listing and it was like, all right, so label printed and then nothing else
had occurred.
I'm like, OK, well, this thing isn't coming.
I use some taramana tequila to fill the Christmas order.
I mean, that's that's something in its own right.
But I was trying to do this thing.
And then somehow during this recording, I got an update about this.
And we're recording this on January 19th.
So this was supposed to come December 18th.
It is now January 19th.
And I get this email from an eBay seller.
I'm contacting you because as of the last month and a half, there's been a major backup and delay with USPS.
Packages have not scanned or delivered.
Please let me know if you've received this item.
If not, I'm sorry for wasting your time.
And I hope you understand the bother.
If you have not, please let me know so I can get the ball rolling and put a trace on this package.
Suddenly there is imperative.
Somebody really has the fire to get this thing out to me a month later.
What is this item?
You may ask.
The item is a baby.
I don't know.
Action.
No, what is what am I looking at?
Well, it's not what you're looking at.
The question really is, is this cute?
That doesn't quite look like the movie.
I wouldn't.
Let me see if I can get a bigger vintage Disney baby Aladar sound walking dino alive.
Aladar toy figure works.
And I don't know if I can see it any better than that.
It's a pretty small photo.
There we go.
Oh, my.
They have the merch.
There were baby.
Did you know this, Mike?
Did you ever checked in on this?
I think we looked on the episode a little bit.
I didn't see this one, though.
This might have been like part of another toy.
Like there might be like a bigger like mechanism that's supposed to be with it.
They broke this off.
But what would it be?
What could it be?
Possibly?
Oh, a adorable little turn.
No, think about it.
Imagine you're going to have to rig the turn yourself and imagine for yourself that you could make it out of Play-Doh, make it out of a little piece of chocolate.
Yeah.
Oh, fudgey.
I believe a listener emailed us that they had this toy and their family tried to get rid.
And it was like a haunted toy like for years, like with just the batteries never quite died.
So every now and then it would just make a horrific like sound.
And then every time they tried to get rid of it, it would end up back.
I have to go back and look through our emails.
Am I getting a cursed toy?
I think so.
So maybe you are getting it.
Maybe you are finally getting it.
That's why it couldn't get rid.
It disappeared.
But then we bring up Baby Aladar for the first time in months and suddenly it appears again.
They're absolutely a ghost thing.
You know what you did?
You secreted this shit right here.
I manifested it.
You manifested it.
It's going to end up in Scott's house.
I mean, it'll have to wait.
It's going to come to me to where I live, but maybe I won't bring it inside.
I think I have to leave it.
If it never actually enters my home, I think I'll feel more comfortable.
I'll leave it on the porch.
I'll let you know you can come get it on your own time.
What if yours?
I think your child has a new best friend.
Never.
No, I think no.
I think what's going to happen is you're going to pick up the package and you're going to open it up.
And then your son is going to go, brother.
No, my God.
Aladar, his first word.
Aladar.
He sounds like ET too.
Then he's in school one day and people are kids are talking about trying to see if they can figure out where babies come from.
And he says babies come from the mail.
That's where my bestest little brother came from.
eBay.
An angel named eBay.
Let's get this kid.
Let's teach him a lesson.
Oh, God.
When the other kids are mad about him.
Everybody knows it's from sex.
Let's beat him up.
Good boy, generation two doesn't know babies come from sex.
His dad does a theme park podcast still.
He's been doing it for 10 years.
Get him harder.
Get him harder than.
No, I will not send it to my child to this.
That's why we're getting out of here.
We're not we're not going to engage this fantasy anymore.
Go to our social medias and check us out there on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram.
And if you want three bonus episodes every month, go to podcast thread, the second gate at Patreon dot com slash podcast.
The ride there.
The buck stops here.
I say.
However, though, I would like to end the episode on it.
Just Jason, if you could do one clean what you imagine that that toy sounds like based on what the listener told you and we'll compare it eventually when it comes and Mike tested himself.
Did you do it like we didn't hear it?
Wait, I didn't hear it.
Oh, OK.
Ah, like a man, like someone choking in a restaurant.
All right, we will put the real and it probably it probably was supposed to say like, hurry, come on, everyone.
Stand together.
That's how it is.
Get your stand together.
Stand together.
Honestly, that sounds like a cute little noise.
Well, yeah, just record Jason doing that and put that in the toy.
So it sounds like that.
And then we'll start selling these.
We'll 3D print them.
We'll copy the mold.
Now I'm going to carry baby all around like he's Grogu and I'm mandalorian.
You have to protect him.
It's going to have a floating bassinet.
In a few years, we'll see like a post from like a Chris, Chris Evans or Chris Pine of like.
And by the way, the upcoming movie Aladar is not based on Disney's.
It's based on the dinosaur Aladar that exists that the movie was based on.
Why was it only Chris's Jason?
Huh?
Because I couldn't remember.
It's one Chris is playing Buzz Lightyear and I couldn't remember which of the Chris's.
I believe it is Evans.
Yeah, he's playing.
And also Chris is I'm not getting anywhere.
Only Chris is allowed to work.
You know, you can't do anything.
All right.
We will play.
We'll put this cursed item up to the microphone when it's in our possession.
But for now, thanks for listening.
Bye bye.
Bye.
Forever.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts.com and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.