Five, four, three, two, one.
Are we kicking off the second gate in 2021
with an episode about a failed children's hair salon?
You're damn right we are.
I'm Scott Gardner, welcome to podcast the ride the second gate.
I think Jason Sheridan's on board with this plan, this note.
I am 100% on board.
I think it's a perfectly insane topic
to start off the year with.
I would call it a hair raising experience.
I wouldn't go that far.
Oh, you got to, you got to use fun phrases like that.
You got to.
Mike Carlson, are you delighted
by the sheer insanity of today's topic?
Oh my gosh, now I'm feeling like such pressure
to do one of these.
Oh, okay.
Glad I thought of that, I would have been screwed.
Yeah, okay, well let's think.
What happens at a hair salon?
I don't know, like scissors?
Trim.
There's a big one, there's a big shiny one
waiting right for you.
Okay, wait, is it one of the two things I just said?
No.
Is it like, okay, what does that have to do with the chair,
the swinging around of the chair?
Barbasol, how about Barbasol?
Am I getting closer?
No, you know, while you're getting a little closer,
it's, you just have a little of them.
A little of them go a long way.
A little, okay, a little of them as far as hairs.
Yeah, a little.
Okay, oof, oof, neck, like trimming your neck hair?
Is that what we're talking about?
I'll go with it.
I'll toss it out there.
Hopefully this episode is a real highlight
of the Second Gate catalog.
Okay, all right.
Yeah, see?
Not sure I would have gotten there.
I only got there because of one specific thing
I found out about this place.
Oh, great, great.
Oh, interesting.
And we'll get around to that.
Oh, how about this?
I hope this one, this episode is enjoyable
and you don't drink a half a gallon of Barbasol
because you're so upset.
Pretty good.
You know, you aren't so mad about the wasted time
from this episode that you glug Barbasol.
We definitely hope that.
Yeah, so today's episode, as you see in your inbox,
is Six Flags Roller Coaster Cuts.
So this got on my radar,
as many great things get on my radar,
because of Eva Anderson.
She texted me the snippet from an article
that was going around Twitter,
and I was about to text it to you guys
when I had my phone out and was about to send it,
and then Jason sent it at that exact moment.
So we were completely simpatico here,
obsessed immediately with the phrase roller coaster cuts.
Had you guys come across this in any way before?
I had never come across this.
I mean, the article from Dave McKenna on Defector,
I like Defector a lot.
It's all the expats from Deadspin, writer and editor owned.
Shout out to them.
And I was so excited to read this
at like 8.39 in the morning.
I was too.
And I also want to shout out,
there's somebody on our Facebook group, Joe Spence,
who apparently was trying to get this on our radar way back,
might've emailed us in a mailbag or something too.
So apologies, we didn't see it
when Joe brought it to our attention.
But so, you know, there was like a tweet going around,
there was a snippet from this article.
The article is titled,
Let's Remember Dan Snyder's Six Flags Disaster.
The Dan Snyder presence kind of makes this a spiritual heir
to the episode we did over the summer about Mr. Six,
who is of course the Six Flags dancing old man.
We started with him and ended up in this whole run
about the Six Flags era during which they killed off
Mr. Six and eventually brought him back.
And I'm excited to go back to that era for this episode.
So knowing that it's about Dan Snyder,
when I saw Eva's text, I was like, roller coaster cuts.
What I jumped to was, is this some kind of like,
before I read it, I was like,
did he like institute a program
to like make cuts from roller coasters?
Like, was this about cutting back the budget
or like, do we have to repair them as much
or check them in a service way as much?
That was what I assumed at first.
Yeah, yes.
I also had that same confusion.
Is this what the, yeah, is it some sort of budget issue?
And then, yeah, and then when I finally was like,
okay, it has to do with haircuts,
I go, oh, it's like how they used to have maybe like
a barber on Main Street?
In the movie?
Good guess, absolutely.
Good guess, yep.
Okay, I go, okay, all right, huh.
That's a pretty good little slice to make there.
You're totally right, because you might see the title
and know that it's Arizona and think,
yeah, was there a barber shop in a Six Flags park?
Right, or it's like the Bibbidi Bobbidi Boutique.
That's obviously, there's precedent there for that,
even in today's world.
Yeah, there's a little salon on the Disney cruises,
but no, this is not that, this was off-site.
But before I get there, let me say some of the other things
in this article.
What I've realized now is that Dave McKenna,
is he's a Washington writer, and I think he was the source
of a lot of the things that we brought up the last time
all this came up.
I think he has been on a Dan Snyder tear
for the entire 15 years that this guy's been haunting.
Yeah.
I mean, I'm not sure when he took over
for the Washington football team,
but his Six Flags run ended in 2009, 2010.
Yeah, I found some of his posts
for the Washington City Paper in 2009,
where he also was doing the logic of,
okay, did Dan Snyder hear cuts from the accountants?
Because Six Flags was in massive debt.
We're talking billions of dollars of debt at the time.
Because of him.
Yeah, he was so bad.
And seen like financial malfeasance and like,
got the, Six Flags had an official mattress you could buy.
We talked about that.
We talked about the mattress.
You could buy a mattress in a Six Flags.
Yeah.
$1400.
Yes.
We did, we talked though.
And I'm, maybe I'm forgetting that he had,
he owned Johnny Rockets through a different company,
which is why you see such a strong Johnny Rockets presence
in the Six Flags.
No, we missed this one.
Yeah, I noted that.
I did not realize that.
Yeah, through some weird holdings group,
he already owned Johnny Rockets.
So when he took over Six Flags, he was like,
just put a Johnny Rockets in there
and get it as like, as close to the entrance as you can.
Just kind of right when you come in, Johnny Rockets.
Yeah, and Johnny Rockets has outlived Dan Snyder
as part of the Six Flags family.
That's true.
We saw a darkened one from our cars over the Christmas
in the highlight of our Christmas season.
I cited it as a highlight as my recollection
during that episode.
I go, I really want to see the closed down Johnny Rockets.
Unlit Johnny Rockets.
Unlit Johnny Rockets in a theme park while I'm driving by.
He did such a shitty job.
Some of this we talked about before,
but as a reminder, among the things he did
while driving Six Flags to bankruptcy,
he put Harvey Weinstein on the board of directors.
So in order to attain the extremely valuable characters
from the movie Hoodwinked,
okay, there was something that Jason brought up last time,
which was that when they retired Mr. Six,
they replaced him with an Asian man in a little bubble
who popped up and said something.
And I didn't really know the ad super well
when Jason brought them up and alerted me to that,
maybe it's kind of racist.
And like, oh yeah, probably that sounds right.
But then this article illuminated that the,
or some article somewhere illuminated that
the casting notice for that part said,
we want people to imitate Charlie Chan.
Oh my God.
Yeah, Jesus.
So you were on it at a time, Jason.
Did they have to explain to the actors like,
oh, by the way, Charlie Chan is like, come on.
Why would you, you peripherally hear the name Amos and Andy
as like a bad thing, but Charlie Chan does not come up
in culture rightfully so.
Yeah.
So that's crazy.
Yeah, there were a lot of Snyder things we,
I mean, maybe we said this before
and maybe it just stuck out to me for some reason
that he had taken control of Six Flags
during a stockholder coup.
A coup, huh?
That's what it said in the article.
Maybe that didn't stick out to me so strongly
six months ago, that's all.
Yes.
You forgot what, you hadn't realized in your lifetime
what coups feel like.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So I saw that, I was like, oh, interesting.
Last night I watched.
Oh yes.
Oh, sorry, I was gonna say, last night I watched
Death of Stalin, a perfect timed movie to watch,
a perfect comedy to watch during these trying times.
Dan Snyder would have put a lot of the Congress Stormers
on the Six Flags board.
You're all in.
Yeah, so bad stuff from him.
He's done a ton of bad stuff like since we did an episode
about this in the summer.
Like it was all, at the time he was fighting the name change
of the football team, and I no longer wanna say
what the name of the team was.
The team now is called Washington Football Team.
Because of his inaction, they have to play
under this bizarre Halloween costume knockoff name,
and with the logo that's just a W.
So they're playing all season with this terrible name.
Oh, and only not because he ever decided to change it
on principle, but because FedEx, Pepsi, Nike, and Amazon
all were threatening to end their partnerships
with the Washington Football Team.
Pretty big companies to tangle with.
Yeah, yeah, sure.
Yeah, he's...
I feel like this is, well, this is not the last time
we'll talk about him on the show.
I feel like they'll feel, I feel like we're missing
a lot still, just from looking, even when we looked
at like five to 10 articles about what we're talking
about today, I feel like he's gonna be around.
Yeah, yeah, I think it's safe to call him at this point
the anti-Eisner, like for everything that Eisner brought
to the Disney company in a short amount of time,
despite a less good second half.
Eisner brought so many gifts, and Snyder brought only
failure and despair, and continues to, wherever he goes.
It's like if Eisner was like, all right, when you go
to Disneyland, you can buy aluminum siding now
at a store off of Main Street, $1,200 for a whole side
of your house.
Do I just walk out of the park with it?
No, we ship it, and that costume, that's an extra 500.
Breck owns an aluminum siding company.
It's under his name for legal reasons.
He is 10.
We were gonna put, we thought about putting Mickey
on the aluminum siding, but the paint would corrode,
it would make the aluminum weaker, so it's plain
aluminum siding, but trust me, it's Mickey's favorite kind.
Yes, same issue with Disney Airlines, you know,
if a plane goes down in a cornfield, there's a smoking
Mickey Mouse, if there's a tornado, tears a house down,
there's a Mickey Mouse in the rubble.
You don't want, bad optics, bad optics.
If you have a barn collapse or such.
Yeah, also worth noting, only a couple months ago,
we found out about when he was still in charge of Six Flags,
he was accused of, this only recently did this come out,
that he paid off somebody who made sexual misconduct claims
against him, oh, by the way, entire culture
of sexual misconduct all over the Washington football team
with this guy at the top, and before all this,
when he was still in charge of Six Flags, he took a private
jet to the Academy of Country Music Awards,
which he owned, because he also owned
Dick Clark Productions, and something happened,
I don't know what, but he ended up paying the person
$1.6 million, and this was covered up until recently,
until after our episode, this guy is the worst,
is he the worst active businessman?
I don't know.
I mean, there's no way to know, they're also.
That's such a bar high, I mean, I would say there's
a businessman I know of that's worse off the top of my head.
Sure, currently.
But I think, you know, you could certainly put him
in the top 300.
Oh, God.
Yeah, I wish you could narrow it down more.
I top 10 for worst people in America, like pretty easy.
He's pretty bad.
You forget about him.
And I think they're all friends, too.
I think all of the top 10 all know each other very well.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, Hamptons.
They're like a sea, the society of explorers
and adventures, for sure.
The modern day version.
The dark sea.
Yeah, so, a bad guy.
So there's so much there and we might not even know
the full extent of it, but we, in talking about him
and, okay, just to remind you why any of this came up before,
his first act when he took over Six Flags in a Coup
was chasing Mr. Six out of town.
We don't want any more Mr. Six.
We don't want our brand associated
with the foolishness like this.
Apparently, something he did want his brand associated with
was children's haircuts.
I don't understand this whatsoever.
I can't begin to know, and no one ever explained why.
Why associate these things?
You know, and Mr. Six is around this haircuttery.
He is around and he looks like he's dying.
Like, he looks like this is killing him.
Yeah, by the end, I think 2006 or so, he took over.
By 2009, they're bleeding money and it becomes clear
that they have to get Mr. Six back in there
as quick as possible, and he's like the main attraction
by the time they open a regional children's hair salon.
I have a theory, and I couldn't find any confirmation
about this, but I was looking at the commercial
for this place, because that's like,
there's only one commercial online, I think, right?
There's a couple variants I found.
Yeah, okay, I think I watched it.
Versions are the same.
It looks a little bit like my memory
of what Club Libby Lou looked like.
Yes.
Club Libby Lou from Downtown Disney
in Eva's episode in the underworld.
Yeah. Exactly.
Jane clocked that too.
I showed her the commercial and she's like,
is this like Six Flags Club Libby Lou?
And it's like, well, you're not wrong.
Yeah.
But it opens just as all of the Club Libby Lou's are closing.
So Club Libby Lou, I think all of them close
or they're all done by 2009, which is when this opens.
So- Yeah, weird.
I either like, it's a complete direct connection of like,
oh, let's capture that part of the market
because this whole thing is failing,
or he's such a bad businessman.
He went, you know what we should invest heavily in?
Like a thing like Club Libby Lou,
look how well it's doing.
Cut to a year later, they're opening
as all the Club Libby Lou's are closing.
I like to think it's number two.
I like to think it's the second one
because it makes them look more idiotic.
I guess you also gotta include
the 2008 financial collapse in here.
Yes. Sure.
Now, if we place that, okay,
people are paring everything down to essentials
in their lives and cutting your hair
and your children's hair is essential,
even if you do it less.
Putting pink sparkles and crimps
and like action figures in your kid's hair.
Giving your son a green mohawk,
maybe not essential post 2008 collapse.
Maybe just a little trim.
Maybe not spending $50, which is what the cuts here cost.
Yeah, and it's also, okay, we'll get into the problems
with it, but it's like, if it was like Mickey's hair salon
and Mickey was there, you're like, okay,
I could see that kid would be like,
I'd like to go and see Mickey and get this hair thing done.
But what is really the draw for a kid
other than like video,
like you can play a video game in here.
Well, that's what I think.
It seems like someone half remember
with like a hangover headache,
remembering the nineties of like,
oh yeah, Disney tried,
like they can't go to theme parks every weekend,
but if they go to the mall a couple of times a month
and we do like Mickey's kitchen and Disney Quest,
DSPN, so like someone half remembers that.
And it's like, kids always need haircuts.
It feels like someone grasping for like the light switch
in the dark when you first walk into your home.
Yes, I totally know what you're saying.
I also do wonder if like, he just,
there's some like Intel or he was like,
there's a hole in the market right here,
or it's just some weird funneling scheme,
or there's some like controversy,
like how he was enriching himself with all these deals,
but like bleeding the companies dry.
Did he invest in barber chairs?
He had like 3000 barber chairs
sitting in a warehouse somewhere.
And he's like, we gotta figure out how to use this
so I can get paid and get make my money back.
He owned a fuchsia sparkles company
and needed to clear them out somehow.
Yeah.
Snyder opened, oh yeah.
He had a hundred thousand tons of sparkles.
Sitting in a warehouse.
Like a garbage dump.
Just like the wind blowing like sparkles
getting some of the maintenance guy's eyes.
Yeah.
This has gotta go.
They tried like using it to like celebrate a touchdown
for a little while and it got in the football player's eyes.
And he's like, we can't do this anymore.
This new artist, Katy Perry,
she might buy some tons of it for a concert tour.
She'll do some glitter blats at the end.
That's not gonna be enough though.
I need answers.
He's screaming at people on the board.
Gotta figure this out for me.
Like rats are burrowing into the sparkle pile
that they live there.
There's nests of rats who are all just permanently fuchsia
when they burst out of the pile.
Dan Snyder's sparkle warehouse.
It's like five miles long.
Before we get too far into this,
I guess we should say,
so the elevator pitch on this place
is that it was a kid's hair salon
where they could get their hair cut
while playing video games
or watching footage of roller coasters
on 2009 era flat screen TV.
So just before high def,
but everything is just kind of wide screen.
So you can watch that,
but it's also a toy store and it's also a candy store.
And also you can do kids parties there.
So a little unfocused, a little scatter shot.
This is the shows that your shark tanks
and your prophets would say,
pick a thing, pick a lane and stick with it.
God, there's even like,
there's some slogan somewhere in the store
that keeps going on and on and on.
It is like haircuts and thrills with characters
and photos and surprises plus games.
That's a literal thing.
It's like a six, this is run on sentence of what they do.
Pick one maybe.
This is reminding me, I had a job interview
10 years ago when I didn't have a job in LA.
And it was like, we're opening up a retail space.
That's also gonna be a performance space.
And we will also be making like short form video as well
that we will play in store.
And we need somebody to work in the stock room,
but also perform on the stage when we do show.
Like it was a laundry list.
And I met a woman in like a suite
at like a hotel on Sunset Boulevard by the comedy store.
Like somewhere along there.
And she was just like, you are perfect for this.
This is great.
She goes, all right, what I want you to do is email me
with how much you would need to make an hour.
And I go, oh, okay.
And then I think I asked for like some just insanely low,
like $15 an hour, please.
Never heard anything.
I don't know.
I'm assuming whatever this place was, it never opened.
But I was like, this isn't real.
This can't work.
It can't work.
It's too much stuff.
You were gonna perform?
I don't know.
I mean, I don't know.
Was it magic?
What was it?
I don't, I should see if I can find the email.
I think I found it on Craigslist.
Yeah, I don't know.
I really don't know.
But it was like a list of 10 things
that this retail store would now do
that was going to open on Sunset.
I think on Sunset Boulevard, but.
These pitches that all sound like the Garth Brooks video
of like, I just joined Facebook.
I wanna share real stuff, cool stuff.
Let the conversation begin.
And then he immediately bails less than a week later.
Did he not do that?
I don't think he lasted very long at all.
Let the conversation stop.
Yeah.
Weird.
Yeah, so, and then I think the big facts
that we're missing as Mike was alluding to
is that this is not a thing in Six Flags.
This was at malls, namely two malls.
Two, that's it.
That's all I got to.
Like Mickey's Kitchen.
Oh yeah, yeah.
Which was in the LA area somewhere and at Woodfield.
We got it all at Woodfield.
I didn't forget, never forget the song.
It was at a mall in Hartford, Connecticut
called Blueback Square.
It was a very clunky name
and I probably won't attempt to say it again.
And then at the King of Prussia Mall,
which is where in Pennsylvania?
Did you grow up with this at all, Jason,
or have you been there?
Oh yes, yeah, that was one of my old stomping grounds.
I've never been to West Hartford, Connecticut
and I have no idea what differentiates it
from Hartford, Connecticut.
But King of Prussia Mall was about an hour
from where I grew up and that was like a whole day event.
Well, we're not just going to the regular mall.
We're not going to Granite Run Mall.
We're not going to Axton Mall.
We're going to King of Prussia Mall.
This is the whole thing because King of Prussia Mall
is two malls next to each other with a walkway in between.
And this was in the court, not the plaza.
The court is smaller and in the past,
it used to be the fancier mall.
But when I looked up the listing recently
of the King of Prussia Mall, it's like,
well, the Louboutin store's in the plaza now
where the, like around the corner from the comic shop
and the old American apparel building
or the old American apparel store front.
So I guess it's been a little more distributed
but it gets a lot of traffic.
There's a lot of high-end stores
and like at some point in time, it was
and it might still be one of the largest shopping complexes
in America.
That's one of the mega huge ones.
Yeah, in my mall wanderings, I know that's one.
And what is, is the Canada one West Edmonton?
I think it's come up before,
when we were saying what are topics we should do in the year,
people have definitely brought up West Edmonton,
but that's, man, I want to go.
So many topics have people brought up.
I'm like, I gotta go before we talk about it.
Yeah.
Especially, particularly Dollywood.
That's definitely the...
Are we the only people in America
who will get the second shot of the vaccine
and like burst out?
We gotta get the pigeon forage.
Sounds good to me.
I'm pretty cooped up.
Yeah, no, I bet there's a lot of people waiting.
Although I think, you know what?
The people that want to go to pigeon forage
are better there already.
They are there as we speak.
Yeah.
I don't think it closed.
But Dollywood has seasons though.
Have they had to, I guess they've been open and pinned down.
I have no idea.
Yeah, yeah.
I shouldn't talk out of my ass about Dollywood.
I've done that before.
Not a dry county.
We've learned that.
Okay, so let's...
What are some other basics about this place?
Okay, here's some official...
Is this their official copy?
I think it might be.
Roller coaster cuts clients, kids only,
will be treated like royalty from the moment they enter
the brightly colored salon boutique.
This state of the art design features
a 22 inch flat panel TV, as Jason was alluding.
An okay TV.
About what I have in my bedroom.
It is eight years old.
Never have been able to quite get the settings right.
A TV that you've, the type of TV you would encourage
your parents to replace is in front of your child.
They are fully immersed into a Six Flags experience
by watching Six Flags TV, different thing,
or riding one of our virtual Six Flags roller coasters,
making it easy and fun for stylists
to work on children's hair.
So there's footage you could see if this were kids
to lay down to get their shampoo.
I'm, wait a minute, I'm sorry.
Don't wanna get ahead of myself, but it's not the shampoo,
but the shampoo-f.
I believe I saw the phrase shampoo,
the world's first shampoo theater.
Theater, what do you mean?
What?
No.
They don't know either.
So yeah, step one, you watch a small TV playing the POV
of a roller coaster while you get shampooed.
And it's in like the ceiling, it's like up above the child.
Yeah, like a dentist's office would have,
my guy go to a dentist that has,
that's playing like nature footage or something.
So there's that.
Again, don't wanna get off on too much of a tangent,
but I was like, what is Six Flags TV?
Cause Six Flags TV was also playing in the window,
like if you pass by it in the mall.
And Six Flags TV is very Disney World in Room video
where some agreeable, pleasant lady is showing you stuff.
But remember, this is the Dan Snyder era,
so there's bizarre tie-ins that this poor woman has to do.
So here's a quick clip of what Six Flags TV
was all about at the time.
Take it away, blandly pleasant lady.
Welcome back to Six Flags TV.
I'm your host, Kid Hoover, and I gotta tell ya,
I'm on a mission, cause something's up
with those Looney Tunes characters.
I mean, when you bump into them around this time every day,
they're kind of mellow, blissed out,
and I have a feeling something's going on right in here.
First of all, is she implying
that the Looney Tunes are getting high?
Yes, she is.
That is absolutely what I thought.
Around this time, and I don't know if that time is 4.20,
but if so, the Looney Tunes are getting mellow and blissed out.
Yeah, they are smoking up.
Yes, that's what she's saying.
That's what she thinks.
That's what Kit Hoover thinks.
That's Kit Hoover's official stance.
But you're going to find out it's not what you expected.
There's a different way they're getting loony.
Ah ha ha, I've been looking for them everywhere.
William, what is this place?
We're at AquaBeds, and this is where
our guests come to relax after walking
through the park for a long time.
You even let these critters in here?
Why not?
Looney Tunes?
Yeah.
I see you, Sylvester.
They even put that head down.
People are looking for you.
So the Looney Tunes.
This is like the water coffins that we
did during the City Walk saga, except there's no top.
It's an un-lidded water coffin.
It's an open casket.
The Aquabed challenge.
Yeah, yeah.
Where she has established the Looney Tunes are all hiding
so they don't have to see children.
This is something I feel like Disney would not
allude to, the Chip and Dale and Mickey and Minnie
don't want to see you today.
Yeah, because they might be high.
Yeah.
Well, they're covering their eyes in this shot.
Are they hiding that they're red?
Yeah, I think maybe.
I can't see them.
I can't deal with the kids.
They'll know.
This keeps going.
We might have hit the peak of it, but she.
Our high powered water jets.
And when you sit down on them, it
feels like three or four pairs of hands massaging you
all at the same time.
A little spa in the middle of Six Flags.
Exactly.
Who usually comes here?
Everyone.
No one.
Kids after a long walk through the park,
their kids like to come and relax.
It's just a nice way to chill for a little while.
Do you want to try, kid?
Should I kick Daffy off?
Daffy, come on.
Shake your tail feather.
Daffy, two minutes.
Two minutes.
Daffy is stomping.
Come on, Daffy.
He's angry that he's been forcibly removed
from his unsanctioned water massage.
Tweety bird, of course, looks very dirty.
And that guy's tie is very wide.
I will say that is one of the dirtiest
Tweety birds I've ever seen.
Just a filthy bird.
Not picture ready.
Lying in a Cleopatra, it's almost like a sultry stance
a little bit.
Yeah, Tweety also before this, I feel
like was lying on his stomach, which hot as exactly.
I don't want to cast anything.
But if you're lying on your front,
aren't you getting your genitals massaged?
And your tummy, your Tweety tummy.
Your dirty Tweety tummy is getting massaged?
Sylvester the cat is getting his weird cat penis rumbled.
Instead of doing his paid job of being nice to children.
Like, OK, wait a minute.
We were all in the water coffins.
Now, imagine you turn over and you're getting pummeled
with water in your dick.
Oh, yeah, we never flip.
Wait, wait, no, aren't we on our stomachs, though?
Which way were we?
We were on our stomachs, but because of the thing
on the top, that's where all the water,
that's where the massage was happening is on our backs.
Oh, you're right.
We were laying down just on a flat massage table.
Right.
This is a different deal.
The massaging is coming from underneath,
whereas the coffin is coming from on top.
So if you're on your stomach, you're
getting a massage on your chest, your stomach,
and your genitals.
That's just the fact.
Yeah, within fur, within...
If the person hired to be in the Sylvester costume is a furry,
today is their lucky day.
Six Flags was having people come in and use a sex machine,
essentially.
Yeah.
Did you also notice that earlier, there's
like some, when Daffy gets kicked out,
there's just like some guy sitting and watching
in the corner, just like a guy in a chair.
A couple of jackets next to him.
Uh-oh.
Little Alfred Molina and Boogie Nights vibes.
And then just this undressed set of stairs.
This is an unthemed room with black wood.
Could have done an episode about the AquaBeds episode
of Six Flags TV.
Are there any Six Flags with AquaBeds still inside?
Hmm.
That's a good question.
That might be worth...
Because you know they would be the exact same beds.
Did they convert these into coffins for the coffin
challenge during Fright Fest?
Yeah.
Scoop them out.
Scoop out the aqua-vart.
Scoop out the...
Get the water into the vlog flume.
We've reused these things for six different things.
They've been ride vehicles, they've been massage beds.
What if there's just a human being inside the bed rubbing?
He's just putting his hands up and touching
through the material and that's the massage.
It's just a teen, it's a bored teen,
massaging you through the AquaBed.
Possible.
Just got a hair spritzer in his hand.
Yeah.
Watching a three inch like iPod color,
like office on the iPod color.
This also brings up something that I had seen
in some of the videos of the Six Flags drive
through the park Christmas experience.
I don't think any of us, we were all complaining
because we didn't see the Looney Tunes,
but in the videos I saw where the Looney Tunes were out,
it was some very weird combinations.
It's like Bugs and Sylvester and it's like,
what, that's not a combo.
So this is like Daffy, Sylvester and Tweety.
And Sylvester and Tweety make sense to me,
but it's like, what is...
Is like Daffy is like a third.
That combo isn't when you see a lot.
They don't have the strict like character code
of a Disney either.
Mrs. Taz could hang out with Daffy
and they wouldn't give a shit.
Even though Mrs. Taz and Daffy never hung out
in the cartoon maybe.
Now somebody's really mad
because there's probably one cartoon from the 90s
where Mrs. Taz did hang out with Daffy.
So I apologize.
Send it to the gripes.
There probably is.
And that's like, Mike, you had sent me the,
JCPenney was selling Versace Popeye t-shirts
and then I found all the other,
they brought back all the other Looney Tunes
and baggy street wear t-shirts.
Yes.
Are very...
That's still around?
They call that a resurgence.
It's like retro merch now, I think.
So yeah, you can find,
I think at a lot of different stores,
like Bugs and Taz back to back
with baggy pants and shirts on.
Yeah, Taz.
That should have never gone away.
Back off.
Aggressive Taz.
Did we all have one of these at least?
I had like a Bugs shirt where he was like dressed cool
in the 90s.
But only one.
I might not have.
I guess now's my chance.
Jason, did you ever own a cool Looney Tunes merch?
Oh, yeah, I had like Taz in a backwards baseball cap
and like cargo shorts, I think.
That works.
That's part of it, yeah.
Maybe a Taz tearing through it.
Taz kind of sadly comes into play
and I found pictures of one of the roller coaster cuts,
I think the King of Pressure one, on a message board.
And Taz is just sort of like here.
He's just sort of placed in the front window
under a begrudgingly placed barbershop pole.
And if you look closely, Mr. Six is standing
facing away from the camera like the Blair Witch Project.
Boy, that's creepy as hell.
He's half shadowed.
Yeah.
Oh, God, that's unsettling.
Yeah, the theming for this place.
Yeah.
The logo is like old timey a little bit,
but then Taz is just in the window
like a little plastic Taz that is the same one they have,
I think, at all the Six Flags.
So I think I took a picture of Taz and Mrs. Taz
in that style on the way out of Fright Fest two years ago.
And boy, were the colors faded on those.
Well, and it looks like he was rescued
from the Warner Brothers store warehouse
and then just placed in like the glass storefront.
He kind of looks like he's in the Magneto prison
from X-Men.
The plastic prison. The plastic queue, yeah.
He's the only character because opposite him
is just like a fully white child mannequin.
Yeah.
So it's two, it's white children's mannequins
and then the Tasmanian devil.
Yes.
And was Taz that popular in 2009?
No, more hangover from the 90s.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, Taz's heyday was the mid 90s, right?
Mm-hmm.
I've read all about it.
There's this thing going on, Tasmania.
It's Tasmania out there.
Right, it was Tasmania.
We've got to get it into the mall.
People loved Taz in the 90s, but I feel like he's popular.
Why did he come to represent being a wild man?
That's interesting.
I think 90s, there was like a lot of,
I mean, now we're finally getting
the full Deadpool movie treatment,
because we've had a couple of Deadpool movies.
But like the 90s was very much like
about extreme characters.
They were like aggressive, and in comics for sure,
it was Deadpool, it was, I don't know, Cable.
Cable kind of, or Lobo.
Begun to kill, Lobo, oh.
Yeah.
Did Lobo start in the 1990s?
Was it the late 80s?
Maybe late 80s, early 90s.
But his heyday was the 90s, yes.
And Wolverine got caught up in this a little
when they did the Marvel versus DC crossover.
Wolverine fought Lobo.
Very strange combo.
Scott, do you know Lobo?
No, it's Lobo.
Just do a quick Google search of DC Comics Lobo.
And he was like an alien bounty hunter, bad guy,
who would like curse, and he was vulgar,
and I guess he was sexual.
Was Lobo sexual, Jason?
I think he was. I think he was horny.
I mean, it was one of those things where it's like,
oh, well, in Britain, DC had those weekly comics
like 2000 AD, and they had a lot more
like grungy space opera kind of like stuff.
So then they introduced a kind of one of those characters,
some of the writers who worked on those
would introduce Lobo, and Lobo was very extreme.
Yeah, he's got a cigar in the action figure
I'm looking at, and a flamethrower,
and then like a toxic symbol.
Yeah, he was created in 1983, but yeah,
my memory is, yeah, he had his big popularity surge
in the 90s.
They were pushing him then.
This is making me remember when I was working on a show
where there was a joke about Tasmanian devil tattoos,
and I don't remember the joke, but the implication
was the Tasmanian devil tattoos are not cool,
if you can imagine that, but they are a lame thing to have.
And it was an animated show, so things have to be gone
over and over and over and over again.
So in like the 10th time this comes up in the editing room,
the producer of the show lifts his arm and like,
well, I guess I get the message, and he has one,
and it's all stretched and faded weird, like, oh no.
You've had to hear this so many times.
There might be a listener.
I didn't write the joke, let me be clear.
I'll keep it nebulous, my feelings about Tasmanian devil
tattoos.
Yeah, plus it's coming back, it's back, you know?
It's back, yeah.
It's back, Tas is back.
You look on eBay, you have vintage clothes or Depop
or vintage stores, like Tas, big bucks.
Do you see this, do you see I pulled up here?
This is a cover of a Lobo comic.
It says first fraggin' issue, and it's an angle
from under him, and he's pointing at his dick,
and it says, I got your cover enhancement right here.
I'm into Lobo, I want the Lobo movie now.
Scott loves Lobo.
I got my in finally, get him in the justice,
get him in the DC verse, and now I'm paying attention.
They did a little of it on TV.
Oh, he showed up, yeah.
Yeah, they did a little of it on TV.
Yeah, but the show was canceled.
Okay, sorry Lobo.
Future guest of the show wrote on that.
Oh sure, okay.
Yeah, yeah.
He got to write some dick stuff.
We'll ask him all about the dick stuff.
So Lobo's dick.
Okay, where were we here?
Oh, you were talking about the bizarre,
the color scheme of the place.
I, here's another corporate little message.
Roller coaster cuts is a unique opportunity
to inject Six Flags into the everyday lives of children
while pursuing new non-traditional growth avenues
for the company.
So that kind of tells you what they were trying to do maybe
is like, as Jason was saying,
like okay, so there's the Disney store.
You can't always go to Disneyland,
but you can go to the Disney store
and then you see those characters
and then the branding is in your head
and that keeps the Disney spirit in your head
and then maybe you want to go to Disneyland more.
That's what they're trying to do with Six Flags.
So they are, I think they do successfully communicate
a lot about Six Flags.
That it's very busy graphics,
not well planned out,
incoherent color schemes,
the use of the Venga boys,
licensed characters who you don't quite recognize.
But, and so Mr. Six was there,
also in the commercial is wags the dog
and Henry the octopus, both from the Wiggles,
which were popular and I think remain popular,
like still do tours.
But I probably know who they were
if I were three years old when they were popular,
which I was not.
And I gotta say, I like Henry the octopus.
I like how all of his little limbs have like pant legs.
I think he's fun.
We came across Henry the octopus before
and I didn't know who he was at the time
because when we did that episode,
we did a tweet, which was Mark Shapiro,
who was the guy under Dan Snyder,
the president and CEO of Six Flags at the time.
He now runs the agency Endeavor.
And if you remember the last episode,
he is a personal enemy of Papa John.
Papa John thinks he should be in jail.
But during this time, he had to answer questions
live on television about a teenager
who got decapitated by one of their roller coasters.
He was not on, he snuck into the wrong area
and the roller coaster went by
and it was a very unfortunate accident.
This guy had to address it live on TV
and for some reason he did it in front of
all of the Wiggles characters dancing,
notably the octopus, which a couple people said,
hey, he has a name, damn it, it's Henry.
So I was delighted to see the ad and like,
oh wow, that's the decapitation distracting octopus.
Yeah, but he's just kind of like staring at a kid
getting their hair cut.
That's the funny thing.
Here, let me see if I have the right commercial.
I'll play one of these ads and you obviously can't see these,
but you can look them up, Six Flags roller coaster cuts.
Oh here, this one has it, I believe.
And I'm gonna turn the volume way down
because if you can imagine they are playing Venga Boys
extremely loud.
There we go.
Getting a haircut is way more fun
at Six Flags roller coaster cuts at Blue Bag Square.
It's where you'll find great haircuts
with all the thrills of Six Flags.
This place is awesome.
It's a full interactive experience.
You'll wish we'd have been around when you were a kid
or when you still had hair.
One back.
Visit us at rollercoastercuts.com
or come on in to roller coaster cuts at Blue Bag Square.
We're open every day.
Oh wait.
Warfags, warfum.
Yeah, okay.
That was Mr. Six earlier when they mentioned somebody,
when you had more hair, what the hell does he say here?
I was gonna ask that, I don't know.
I don't know.
I watched it six times.
I was like, oh, I guess they'll know.
I don't know, I can't tell.
Maybe the seventh is the charm.
Let's see, here we go.
Or when you still had hair.
One back.
Want back.
Want that?
Want that.
You like hair?
Womp womp?
Is it a womp womp like that?
No.
Hmm, one more.
One more, yeah.
See if you get it, listener.
One back.
I'm stumped.
No.
So, you see, can we take a screenshot of this,
of us right now, three of us with this face?
I'll do it, I got it.
Oh yeah, sure, yes please.
I don't know, I don't know.
Yeah, hmm, okay, so a commercial
with Loud Vankleboy's music,
a sound bite that we can't understand,
as Jason said, it cuts to, I like this kid.
Big flags.
This place is awesome.
It.
This place is awesome, and then it cuts to the octopus
with all of his arms shoved in front of his body,
just kind of like moping around,
interrupting the not, taking up a lot of the not very much
space that the hairstylist has,
blocking the view of the TV
that plays the roller coaster footage.
I'm realizing the one kid is like dead-eyed
playing PlayStation 2, like he's so focused,
and he just, he doesn't even seem like he knows
he's getting a haircut, and I guess that's the,
the idea, I guess that's, you know, to keep them wiggling.
To keep them from wiggling.
Then it cuts to, then it cuts to what he's playing,
and it says high score in the middle of the frame,
but then it's a roller coaster footage.
Is he playing a roller coaster game?
Hmm.
What's the game you're playing?
Attention to detail is not, you know, I don't.
In general, not Six Flags Forte.
Forte, yeah.
This is a variant of another one of their commercials.
What was different about this one?
I'm trying, oh, oh, this one kind of gives you
a broader overview of the activities,
so this might be helpful to look at.
This'll take us through the other.
Besides, once the haircut's done,
there's more fun in store.
Six Flags are fun.
Parties are way more fun at Six Flags Roller Coaster Cuts.
With party on, it's easy.
Just choose your theme, pick your fun,
then show up and we'll do the rest.
All right, I need to stop it already.
With party on, it's, and you don't know what that means.
With party on, I guess that's a program
that lets you book the parties.
There's several steps.
One is your theme.
These are seven little graphics in the corner.
Your theme, your fun, show up.
That's it.
Well, that was definitely an issue to the business.
People are not remembering step three.
People would book and then not come.
Who?
Who is this clown, by the way?
Oh, I don't know.
He's not a wiggle.
Oh my God, he's bearded.
He's a bearded clown.
He looks a lot like famous Bozo the Clown character Cookie.
He's got a very similar color scheme and a similar haircut,
but he is not Cookie.
He's a flashback to Bozo era in that he's a 60 year old man.
Yeah, he's drunk and he's 60.
The way clowns used to be.
Right.
Boy, yeah, he looks real haggard.
It looks like not a clown nose,
but a bulbous WC Fields nose.
It's his real nose.
Something's wrong.
That's why he was hired.
We can save money on the clown nose.
Just get a 1920s drunk in here, paint his face.
Wanted, drunk with permanent clown nose.
Wait, is he one of the, okay, I saw an article,
wait, there's a list of other characters.
You probably have this, right?
Maybe, yeah, here, I'll switch over.
I mean, I saw a list with the Wiggles characters,
but you might have something I don't have.
Hold on, let me find it.
Talk amongst yourselves.
Yeah.
Right here, go ahead.
Let me just say the digital artifacts of this.
It was very fun to remember the internet of 10 years ago
because you find a couple discoveries.
One, if you look up the Yelp and Foursquare pages
for this location, it categorizes them as toys.
So that's what I was alluding to when I was like,
well, they presented themselves as one thing,
but then landed on another.
The other thing you discover is there are snapshots
of the roller coaster kites website on the internet archive.
All the images are no longer there, though.
So you just find copy about haircuts with shampoos,
different options like divas delight, totally gross,
pirates rock, princess pampering party,
Mr., oh, and play fun stuff when you do,
when you have a birthday party here.
Birthday parties, by the way, $30 a head for each kid.
I don't know if that's comparable to like Chuck E. Cheese,
but like you can play Mr. Six's ball toss
or pin the bow tie on Mr. Six.
Was that just like a bozo buckets for Mr. Six,
his ball, Mr. Six's ball toss?
I guess so.
Gridiron challenge football toss.
Like this is the laziest mixed silly sand bath salt
or lotion in our liquid lab.
There's also not, there's no room in this place.
There's no room.
And you see the commercial and the kids are crammed
in between displays of merchandise.
Really packed, yeah.
There's not even like,
it doesn't appear to have like a party room.
Yeah, and they're still like having to squeeze in,
a red carpet.
I think they refer to a divas red carpet or something.
Yeah, you see, well, they have band jams too.
There's so much.
Let me find the red carpet.
Face painting, band jams, costumes and a runway walk.
Runway walk.
And then it cuts to a girl and a pink feather boa
and a bunch of miserable boys with guitar sunglasses.
And also like when you.
Like the characters from hackers.
Bunch of cyber punk kid, be a cyber punk kid.
Six Flags roller coaster kids.
This backdrop is not big enough to do a fun like photo op
to make it look like you're on a red carpet somewhere.
Like you would take that photo
and you'd easily see the merchandise to the left
and the kids waiting there.
Like if you wanted to be like.
Yeah, there's two velvet ropes on either side.
It's a length of two ropes.
Yeah, it's not even,
doesn't even look like a good photo op.
No.
I was wrong.
I got confused.
The names of the haircuts I thought were characters.
Well. Oh yeah.
I mean, we can't avoid those now, can we?
I mean, this was one of the things that jumped out
in the Twitter.
Would you care to do the honors, Mike?
Oh yes, sure.
All right, here we go.
I had something, it's in the Washington city paper
and they really editorialized here.
This is what they said.
Snyder's sub Mensa-esque brainchild,
the network of standalone kitty hair salons
known as Six Flags Rollercoaster Cuts
opened its first outlet in West Hartford, Connecticut
and started hawking costly coiff makeovers
with dumb ass names.
The Glammy, Zoink, Big Kapow and Blamma Jama.
All right, honey.
Do you want a Zoink or do you want a Big Kapow?
I want a.
You're not going to the liquid lab.
If you're not good, you're not going to the liquid lab.
I want to go to the liquid lab.
We'll do the divas red carpet dash,
but first you need to sit and get your Zoink.
The Zoink is what we're here to do.
And don't whine, sit down and Zoink.
And then the clown is like, yes, my name is Zoink.
No, no, we're not talking about you.
Oh no, we named the clown and the haircut the same thing.
Because Zoink seems like a clown name.
This is why I got.
It does.
Yeah.
Might've been, I don't know.
God damn it.
How much for a Glammy?
It's a $50 Glammy.
You can go to, the dad is arguing with the mom.
Like we could just go to God damn Fantastic Sam's.
It's on the other side of the God damn mall.
It's $20.
What are we doing?
They don't have feather boas there, Henry.
And an octopus won't stand in the corner
and stare at our son while he's getting his hair cut there.
He's gonna be screaming.
He's gonna be terrified of the razor
unless there's an octopus distracting him.
Now this brings up a good point that is something I had found.
So like a lot of hair salons, kids cuts,
back then you were looking at maybe like 10 to $15.
I think the roller coaster cuts,
you're looking like 16 to over $20.
I found a write up on classymommy.com.
And let me be clear.
I want no beef with the mommy bloggers.
There's a huge industry.
I'm fascinated by the Disney parents panel,
whatever they're calling it now.
But I want no beef with the mommy bloggers,
with fan fiction writers, with the K-Hive.
I want no beef with any of these subcultures.
But I did find a write up,
a glowing review of roller coaster cuts on classymommy.com.
Kyle loved every moment at roller coaster cuts
for his little haircut a few weeks ago.
No.
I dropped his big sister off at preschool
and the two of us took off for a special date
at the King of Prussia Mall for him to get a cut.
A date with my mom to get a little haircut.
This is, I'm reading this
because it sounds like something we would say.
The salon was fabulous and not crowded at all
since we went during quote school hours on a weekday.
The store was full of bright colors
and just about every tempting toy and candy imaginable.
And now this is where I have paused
because the prospect of a candy store
sharing space with a hair salon
is so off putting to me, a treat lover.
The blogger goes into detail of like,
and then Kyle of course,
he loved jumping into his big lollipop
while his cut was happening.
And I was like, whoa, whoa, whoa, no, no, no, no.
You enjoy your lollipop after the cut.
There is nothing, even as a kid I was like,
oh, I don't want hair on this lolly.
I want, when we get outside the door,
I will chow down on this.
But like, oh God, the sticky and hair like,
is making me feel.
The fragments just in the air,
like even like minutes later,
even after the kid left the chair.
Yeah.
Blows around, you blow it with a hairdryer.
It could like move over from the next station.
Hey, Jason, what was this blog called again?
It's called classymommy.com.
And again, I seen like a very popular,
it's right up with glowing of like Six Flags Rollercoaster.
Basically like, yeah, it's gonna be a few bucks more,
but the kids get to do more fun stuff.
The only issue I usually have with mommy blog
is when they go like,
Kyle usually hates getting his hair cut,
just like he hates the sting of a needle.
And what's in vaccines anyway?
That's when they start to lose.
Like I don't, I don't, don't cotton to that.
I don't cotton to that.
I tried to get, I tried to read a different mommy blog
called one not so bored mommy.
And I was, and because I found a tweet,
cause I just, I just Googled,
I just searched in Twitter this roller coaster cuts.
And I found like another, it says retweet,
what an incredible and blessed experience.
Thank you Six Flags Rollercoaster cuts.
And I clicked on the article and it was,
it says permission denied.
It doesn't look like you have been invited
to read this blog.
If you think this is a mistake.
I got there.
I got to one board.
Okay, so I think this is rebranded at some point.
Well, here's the thing.
I think at one point in time, it was one bored mommy.
And then, cause once I went, once I way back machined it,
it was one bored mommy and then became one not so bored
mommy, like maybe she did a little like positive spit
or found so much stuff to do that she became
a not so bored mommy.
So there was a rebranding and I'm so glad I got through
and I could fill in the gaps for you because
also some fun details on one bored mommy.
Classy mommy is not the only fun writer.
We spent two fun and very exciting hours playing
in the store with their fun staff,
getting the kids hair decorated,
their nails painted, doing the limbo,
walking the red carpet and sucking in what it felt like
to live the glamorous life through a child's eyes.
It's a glamorous life.
Excuse me?
Suck in the glamorous life.
Tell your kids to suck in the glamor.
Huh?
Suck in glamor kids as you get a big lollipop
with your little haircut on your special day date
with your classy mommy.
Who's not bored.
Who was not so bored.
Was bored at the time.
Was bored but not so much.
Not bored anymore.
Now that I'm doing the limbo and sucking in glamor.
Oh, I love to do the limbo, lose my footing,
put my hand on the ground and come up covered in hair.
And then immediately reach for a lollipop.
Reach for a big sticky lolly.
Thanks, oh and Mr. Six is handing it to me
and you know his white hands are covered in hair.
His white gloves are just.
I'm stuck to Mr. Six now.
I'm fused to Mr. Six.
Somebody needs to get a little blowtorch.
Uh oh, Zoink the clown fell over again.
Mr. Six is helping up Zoink.
He didn't get enough sleep last night.
Uh oh.
How did you, Scott, how did you get to gain access
to this blog?
Why am I getting kicked out of this blog?
Through the way back machine, through web.archive.org.
One of the best tools when you're looking for inaneity
that nobody bothered to keep around.
Huh.
I was thinking maybe it's because of the three of us
you're the only authentic Disney daddy.
Oh you're right.
Hey, well thanks for the notice.
I'm glad that I, I don't say it enough
that I'm a Disney daddy, a classy Disney daddy.
And I, yeah, yeah, no I didn't,
there was no point where I had to scan my son's eyes
to prove that, show us the baby pupils
or else you're not getting into one not support mommy.
Yeah.
Internet Archive and Reader View are very helpful
with these sorts of things.
I don't know whether to say because the defector site is,
I think it was Paywold on my phone
but OK on my laptop browser.
I'm gonna sign up anyway because it's a great site.
It's worth it for David Roth's articles alone.
One of the only writers who understands the Trump era.
But certainly looking up ancient Six Flags rollercoaster cuts
the Internet Archive was a godsend.
Oh and I should say though, Scott,
you found a Twitter account
for one of the rollercoaster cuts locations.
Oh yeah, that's right.
There wasn't a lot of tweets so I read all of them.
And you can kind of see, I mean once they get to like,
show this tweet for a discount
which was harder to show a tweet in 2010.
70% off summer styles.
You never wanna see that
and they're mostly plugging the toys anyway.
But the best tweet hands down just said,
coming soon to Six Flags rollercoaster cuts, highlights.
Coming soon.
Didn't have them.
Maybe wouldn't that be a day one option, highlights?
You would think.
My favorite tweet and if you wanna read
any of these read the history of tweets yourself,
it's at Coaster Cuts.
And they have not been very active since 2010.
So my favorite one, children and parents alike love reading.
Every Tuesday from 10.30 to 11.30,
story time with poor Fessor Curly Q.
Just flip the R and the O.
Poor Fessor.
So it's not just Taz, Mr. Six,
and the Wiggles characters and Zoinks the clown.
So they also, some time for an hour a week,
you get poor Fessor Curly Q.
Yeah, you said it's at Coaster Cuts, right?
Yeah.
I like how you can clearly see the downfall of the store,
but it's not said that that's happening.
It's not said that that's happening.
Oh yeah.
You're gonna be like, 50% off all merchandise.
Next tweet is 70% off all merchandise.
And then that's the last tweet.
Yeah.
They also, they advertise something called,
it's also very bluntly, Silly Bands with an E, not a Y,
and a Z, not an S.
Those were hugely popular.
I don't know if they still are,
but I believe they were a big short-lived trend,
maybe long-lived trend,
but I think kids liked Silly Bands.
Silly, Silly Bands.
We just got another shipment.
We got the crates in, crates here.
Dan Snyder has more Silly Bands for us to clear out.
Put it next to the all things must go side.
What have we not talked about?
Well, there's other things you could get there
that I wanna shout out.
We mentioned shampoos, haircuts with a Z with shampoos,
blow blasts, or a separate item,
and I don't know what blow blasts are.
That could just be getting your hair dried.
I'm not sure.
Blow blasts, mini mannies, girly updos,
peekaboo highlights,
and then they were offering a good deal
at one point in time, special scissor savings,
two shampoos and haircuts for $30 on Tuesdays
and Wednesdays only, special excludes blow blast.
Can we go to Six Flags roller coaster cuts today?
No, we can't.
I told you, we have to wait until Tuesday.
Why?
Because you and your brother can both get shampoos
and haircuts for only $30.
Can we get a blow blast too this time?
Absolutely not.
Are we? $30 is plenty.
Are we poor?
Daddy has just been,
there's been some bad things in the economy,
and daddy can't afford as many shampoos
as he used to be able to.
And don't even think about asking about peekaboo highlights.
Not today.
Until daddy figures out his mortgage, refinances.
So I guess having a zoink is out of the question.
Oh no, no, no.
Let's not go basic, just a basic shampoo.
You can get it, when you get a job,
then you can get a zoink.
How much did the clown charge for the balloons?
Why?
Well, we probably should make the leap
that they're called baloofs or something.
So, and then you get this,
an upcharge for the custom name.
So yeah, every baloof is 25 bucks.
Oh man.
This is actually all pure comedy,
because I guarantee none of this ever happened.
There was never a child demanding to go back here.
Look, kids are smarter than Dan Snyder
when it comes to shit like this.
Like I can tell exactly how we would have felt
about this place as a kid.
I'd have been like, oh, it's cool to play a video game
while I'm getting my hair cut.
And that's about it.
We have a Warner Brothers store, much better themed.
I could see all the characters in there.
Or at least at the time, I guess they didn't overlap.
But if I was a kid and this existed
in the same time I was a kid,
and I would have been like,
I'm not getting my hair colored.
I want to have a birthday at Chuck E. Cheese,
or even a McDonald's with a Play Place.
Yeah.
There's no.
Let's just go to Supricots
and then we'll go to the One Burger King
where there's like an N64 with a CRT TV.
Yeah.
Let me climb around an Officer Big Mac's mouth.
That's what I want to do.
I want to get my hair cut quick out of the way.
Let me play with my McDonald's.
I wouldn't think so.
But then that's where the zoinks and the gaffoos come in.
Like they're fun.
It's fun haircuts.
So that's something you want to do with friends, right?
You all want to glam out.
You and your boyfriend, you and your male friends
all want to glam out like rock stars.
You want to have dyed hair.
What band at this time still had dyed hair?
Fallout Boy.
Like what's a cool band?
In 2009?
Good Charlotte.
Yeah.
Huh.
When does the black parade come out?
From like the romance.
Oh, right.
Yeah, I don't know.
Or maybe Billy Joe still dying his hair color.
If you're an eight year old boy and your friends,
you all want to look like Billy Joe.
Also, how many kids came home
and their parents screamed at them from a party?
I'm like, what did you do?
That's literally not allowed at your Catholic school.
You can't go in the door on Monday.
Scott, imagine you came home as a little boy.
Oh God.
Big purple, like big purple streak in your hair.
My parents had problems when I started wearing sandals
at 21, much less dying my.
Which is funny because I know a certain carpenter
who wore sandals all the time.
Yeah, that's right.
Up and through his 30s when he was crucified
for his own orthodox beliefs, like sandal wearing.
I think I wore white sunglasses when I was 26
and my parents were like, huh, what?
Look at this.
And some ideas in LA, are you?
What is this?
Hollywood Michael. Mr. Hollywood.
I don't know, they're white?
The color is white instead of black?
They weren't like Elton John glasses or anything.
They were just white.
The frames were white.
Anyway.
I have some insight, I think,
onto the Six Flags perspective about children's haircuts
because I found the Blue Loop,
one of the trade group articles about it opening.
Here is a quote.
Roller coaster cuts is redefining the Six Flags experience,
said Mike Ant and Tenoro,
executive vice president, entertainment and marketing.
What can sometimes be a dreaded,
yes, necessary obligation for kids
turns into an environment of fun, thrills and excitement
that is the Six Flags brand.
And I don't know, should we take that phrase,
like podcast the ride, a dreaded but necessary obligation?
Like, I wasn't thrilled about getting my hair cut.
I found it a little annoying.
Like, I don't, I like having-
The three childless men in their 30s with a dreaded,
a dreaded but necessary obligation?
Yeah.
Or at least put it on a shirt.
I don't know that phrase to describe haircuts.
Like, yeah, I wasn't wild about them,
but that's a little heavy.
Saying that that's still in their description
of what the service they're offering.
We're a place that fulfills dreaded
but necessary obligations.
It's like Six Flags also describing
like when a child does its appendix out or something.
That was the next step they were gonna offer.
Six Flags surgical.
Tonsils.
Yeah, tonsils.
Appendix.
Yeah, anything that would happen as a kid.
I guess wisdom teeth for the tweens and teens.
They would explain to you why they can't,
why you can't see grandma anymore.
Yeah.
They would do all the tough talks
and then incorporate it into a diva dance party.
I danced Snyder.
I wouldn't put it past them if this was like a mild success
to try to spin it off into other avenues
of unpleasant things kids have to do.
Oh yeah.
Six Flags branded chore wheels.
What's that?
Chore wheels.
Six Flags branded chore wheels.
All right, you're washing the dishes this week, Tommy.
How many chores, how many more chores you have to do
before you get to go to Six Flags.
More chores, more fun.
Okay, Tommy has figured out how to rig the chore wheels
so it always lands on go to Six Flags great adventure.
No.
He waited it.
Tommy's cheating.
I guess Six Flags like homework centers
is where you would go to the mall to do homework.
Oh yeah, one of those sinister divorce education
like Khan Academy nonsense things.
It's like just slowly destroying unions across America
but like, oh, roller coaster at lunch.
And octopus will stare at you while you do your homework.
He's your SAT.
You get a high five for each page that you finish.
He'll high five you with a different tentacle.
That actually sounds pretty good.
Yeah.
Maybe I would have wanted to do that one.
I mean, we might, if this had been allowed to breathe,
they might've redefined the Six Flags brand.
It might've been like Six Flags is your source
for holding your child's hand through unnecessary
or through necessary obligations of life
and then giving them a little dose of fun at the end.
Yeah, I mean, that could have really influenced
the whole thing.
Like the theme park itself then more becomes
about grooming children and not in the grooming.
You grow grooming children.
Careful, careful.
I am being careful.
Cutting their hair.
And maybe that would be more Six Flags' identity
at this point.
And I know Dan was confused.
I mean, he wanted the identity to be mattresses
and to a water massage.
He should have picked one, I think.
And it would have stuck maybe better.
As children, what place did you guys go
to get your hair cut?
I was recalling that I did go to like a fun place
a little bit.
That there was, it was fun, I think,
because you got candy while you were waiting.
You could play on a Pac-Man machine.
And there was a poster of the 1976 King Kong,
the one with the Twin Towers in it.
Sure.
And I remember it so strongly.
I'm not sure why.
King Kong, I think I'd never heard of it.
And I would just stare at it every time I got a haircut.
So it left an impression.
Yeah.
Jason?
We were a super cuts family.
Or occasionally there would be a mom and pop place
that at best had one chair that was an airplane or a car.
And then a few times we went to one of our friends' house
because his mom was a hairdresser
and she had a chair set up in the basement.
And she would charge a little less
than whatever salon she was employed at.
But she kept everything.
She got to keep everything.
Interesting.
You know what?
Moms in basements doing business, I feel like, is common.
I remember there was a mom in a basement
who did that in our town.
But then there was also a mom in a basement
who sold shoes out of her house.
My mom bought my sister's orthopedic little shoes
because her feet had to go a certain way.
And we bought them from a woman in the basement
of a house.
And I remember being like,
this is the strangest thing I've ever seen.
Like a five-year-old.
It's like, she has a store in her house?
A basement.
For sale, baby shoes never worn in my basement.
I went to...
Yeah, go ahead.
No, no, no, no, go ahead.
I was just gonna say, I went to a place called Fantastic Sams
which was basically standard,
except they had a little TV plant,
like a little box with a TV.
And then there was a door.
And after you were done, you would knock on the door
and then they would like put a sucker in,
like a ring, a spider ring.
And then you'd open the door and it would appear
and you'd take it.
So you got a little treat at the end.
Weird little box.
That's strange.
Yeah, it was like a,
it was kind of like a big cabinet with a TV.
And I can't remember if like the trick was like,
they would say, open it and there would be nothing in it.
You would close it and then you would knock.
But then when you got like to be six or seven,
you'd notice that the person was just clearly dropping it
on the side so it would fall down and you'd open it.
You'd get like a sucker.
And then if we were lucky, we would get a slush puppy
from the convenience, the white hen
or whatever convenience store was next door.
That was rare.
That sounds pretty good.
All right, well, that's what RollerCoasterCuts
is trying to do is cut out the middle man.
Now you don't have to walk somewhere else.
You can get your slushy with only a few small hair follicles
as an unwanted topping.
Yeah, that's a small price to pay for treats.
You know, one stop shop.
This was, it's so weird.
I guess I'll find out as this kid grows up that like,
oh yeah, I guess I forgot the whole component
of haircuts being unpleasant and like why many parents
have to do them themselves.
But I'm also like, you know, I'm adding up like,
I'm remembering the things I have to do as a dad
or that Aaron has to do.
And like, if you had like green sparkly hair,
like you have to clean that out.
Like this is your, and it's probably hard as hell
and toxic, it probably stinks.
Like this is like really saddling the parents after the fact.
Yeah, cause like, yeah, there's no way they were using like
real legit permanent hair dye.
Cause if you're dying someone, especially dark hair,
if you're dying it purple,
I believe you need to bleach it first.
You need to bleach the hair, that takes a while.
Then you need to put the purple dye in it.
Cause if you just put purple dye in dark hair,
it won't show up very well.
I am confident they were not like bleaching
the kid's hair first, then putting pink and purple in.
They were probably putting some sort of temporary color on
that for sure was coming out all over the pillow that night.
Like there was no way that was like permanent hair color
and was just like ruining kids bedspreads
every single night.
Six Flags pillow stainers.
Oh, oh wait.
Okay, I got it.
I figured it out.
I figured out the whole scheme.
Dan Snyder wanted to sell more mattresses
in Six Flags parks.
So he wanted to ruin kids mattresses at home
and then they'd have no choice,
but to go to a Six Flags to buy a new mattress.
This is it.
This is what he was coming up with there.
He had also bought a toxic paint company at some point.
And that was, he thought he was gonna have to sell it
because it was toxic.
But then he realized, wait a minute,
I have use for paint that never goes anywhere.
Ace Chemicals purchased by Dan Snyder from Batman.
Ace Chemicals, same thing that scarred the Joker.
Yeah, man.
This is a good new Joker origin story
that he went to a roller coaster cuts
and it's when he got a glammy
that didn't go how he wanted it.
And then he's asking for the mirror
and the octopus is reluctant to give it to him
when they show them what they've done to him.
Henry, give it to me.
And then he kills Mr. Six with like a joy,
but the buzzer in his hand.
One of the grimmer parts of researching this episode
was if you Google the phrase Six Flags roller coaster cuts,
you get the commercials first and second for results.
And then you start getting news stories
of roller coaster cuts off or drop tower cuts.
And you're like, oh, the Vangabas is not coming.
That's my other theory is that this was all an attempt
to shift the Google results.
Like we got too many results
for six flags roller coaster cuts.
How do we skip ahead in this line?
People are getting caught on these coasters so often.
Our coasters are cutting everybody.
What are we gonna do?
Wait, Jason, did you get cut in Six Flags?
No, I got cut at King's Dominion.
Oh, that's right.
Jagged chain like chest.
I got cut, yeah, I got cut very,
it looked like it was very minor cut,
but it did leave a scar and it just,
it cut in a spot where it just would not stop bleeding.
Like a very fine layer of blood on my belly.
And yes, that is true.
That was at King's Dominion though.
Water play area.
So after getting cut, I was then blasted with chlorine water
and Nickelodeon logos as I attempted to get out
of the water play area to go, hey, can we go to first aid?
So they should have used the catchphrase.
I got cut at Six Flags.
Yeah.
They really actually used, oh no good.
Sorry, they need to figure out a way
to flip the Google results from people
that are getting their genitals crushed on roller coasters.
And call it like Six Flags crush in the mall.
Maybe they sell like different versions of the soda.
It's like a soda bar or something.
Or like, is it a, it's a preteen dating surface.
Oh, that's good.
That's much better, yeah.
It's like a speed skate.
What better place to take your crush than a Six Flags?
Come in, make a dating video.
Say all of your likes and dislikes
and we'll pair you with the cutest,
yeah, the cutest fellow preteen in town.
Preteen dating surface.
Yeah, that's a good business end up.
I believe Dan Snyder would have invested in that.
Yeah, I think so.
He was just bored.
He was like, like, didn't like the idea of theme parks,
I think, and just went, no.
Anything else we can stamp this name on.
Man.
Really quick also, that they, that the sub,
the little like subtitle of it is a hair raising experience.
That's one of those, I hate puns where it's not a word
that you use in day to day life.
Like nobody's ever said I'm getting my hair raised.
So it just like, I have this issue
with like popsicle stick jokes.
Usually the puns are resting on the back of a phrase
that nobody would ever say.
Yeah, it's like hair raising is only used in jokes.
Yeah, yes.
I think they made it up.
I think this was made up by the popsicle stick industry
so that they would have an easier.
Yeah, unless it was like a hundred years ago,
somebody would say, oh, I heard you were stuck
in the wilderness for two weeks, how was it?
And they were like, well, it was very hair raising.
Maybe people used to use it?
I don't know, I've never heard anyone use it.
Well, I mean, that definition, hair raising I get,
but cutting being raising, like who's ever said that
in the last century?
Yeah, I don't know, no one.
No one.
Update your, this is a, your catchphrase
is from the 1800s.
That's problem number one.
Problem number two, you offer services called
Big Kapow and Blamajama.
Problem number three, your mascot is an old man
who hangs around next to an old drunk clown.
And he looks like, again, I cannot emphasize enough,
the Mr. Six costumes they gave to this hair salon,
all the pictures and video look bad, you know?
It's not like a film set, makeup artist quality.
It looks like, it looks like in a movie,
like Point Break or something,
where they have the old president with the masks on.
Yes, it does look like that.
And I also, I know I was surprised by how many people
love Mr. Six.
I would like, it was like, what, 65%, 70% almost.
But I still think it's also as a kid though.
I think kids, Jason, you liked him as a kid, right?
Yeah, I mean, I was hitting like pre-teen teen years,
I think when he was rolled out, right?
You know?
Right, but like an eight year,
I bet if we polled eight year olds,
do you like Mr. Six?
The number would be lower.
Now my point is like, I don't know that he's the best mascot
for getting like kids under 10,
some creepy old man who like dances in a strange way.
You were, okay, so you're scared
of getting your haircut, huh?
How would you like, would you be more willing
to get your haircut if this old man stared at you?
Yeah, and he like, and he's gonna like,
he's gonna bother you.
He will pester you.
You'll have to deal with him.
The place is too small for him not to bother you
at some point.
And you'll have to-
There's not gonna be enough people in there.
You will for sure interact with this old man.
If you have sunglasses on, he's gonna take them.
He's gonna like point at anything unusual on your person.
Right.
You're gonna be like, as a kid, you're gonna be like,
I know he's not old, but maybe he is.
And I know that I'm not supposed to like
talk to strangers like this,
but like it's gonna be so confusing for you.
And he's the mascot.
Why not just put a Taz outfit?
Like a guy in a Taz outfit.
Yeah.
If they have Taz, if they're using, yeah.
And why are they even using Wiggles characters
who older kids are less likely to know?
We fucking Taz-ed.
Well, look, Mr. Six was the compromise.
All of Dan Snyder's other pitches
were the most racist things you could imagine.
And they're like, just tell him we already bought
Mr. Six costume, we gotta stop him from saying this stuff.
Dan Snyder sent us 10 ideas,
and I took the liberty of shredding the document
before sharing it with anyone else.
I reported him to HR,
but they were all in the process of resigning anyway.
So I don't know that anything is going to happen.
He dissolved the HR department.
There could be no more complaints.
I missed a thing about Dan Snyder also earlier
that this is, I think also in the reporting
of Dave McKenna.
He got a quote from somebody who,
I think we said this in the last episode
that Bill Gates invested over $100 million
into Six Flags around this time,
and he lost all of it.
Just totally toast investment.
Same with Dan Snyder.
All the money he put in to doing the coup,
he lost every cent.
This guy, this is a fellow Six Flags investor.
Bill Gates gives away more money than anybody,
and his main cause is malaria,
says this guy who also is a person who fights malaria
through a group called Hedge Funds versus Malaria.
That's strange.
Anyway, quote this guy,
that was money that could have gone
to save kids from malaria.
So by looping in Bill Gates,
Dan Snyder kept the malaria problem going full speed.
He's, his primary children's issue is making it more fun
to get their hair cut, and in the process,
he gave thousands of children malaria.
I wish that all, anytime like a billionaire wastes money
on the news or whatever, and then at a total,
like somebody, after they've explained what the story was
and how the money was lost, they go,
and that money could have gone to curing malaria.
Like Mike Bloomberg has dropped out of his presidential bid
after spending $750 million.
That money could have gone to curing malaria.
Just to give us perspective,
because I think people need to know we could cure malaria
with all this wasted money.
I think it's smart.
Elon Musk, Elon Musk smoked a thousand dollar bill
like a cigar with Joe Rogan.
That money could have gone to fighting malaria.
Yeah, do it with any of your favorite
rich maniac wasting money stories.
If we're winding down here,
and feel free to throw in any last things,
but I just have a little assignment
that I think would be good.
Just a little bit of social media fun,
because you know what, honestly, boy, you know,
in this particular week in 2021,
things could not be uglier and crazier on social media.
And isn't it fun to go back to 2010,
and just see innocent tweets about shampoos
and silly bands and poor fessers.
We all remember how kind of fun and novelty
Twitter was at the time.
So I would encourage everybody to take that trip,
and go to at CoasterCuts,
which currently has, as it stands as we record this,
it has nine followers.
It never got two out there.
There weren't a lot of likes in general.
You'll be confused when you look it up,
because it's at CoasterCuts,
but the username is Darlene Reese.
Now again, more branding issues.
But I have a couple proposals
for our followers to do on Twitter.
I think if you follow at CoasterCuts,
everyone listening to this, go follow at CoasterCuts,
and let's see what happens to the numbers.
Starting at nine, where is it gonna go?
And I have another fun idea, I think, within this.
Another favorite of my tweets that I found,
let me read it.
Fall is coming.
Rock out your piggies while you still can
with our new piggy paints.
Try colors like solar power or radioactive.
And that's a lot of fun.
And I'm gonna propose doing something,
the rarely, maybe never done reverse ratio,
a good ratio.
Ratios are where there's not a lot of likes,
but there's so many comments that imply
that there's something problematic about what you said
or something that has to get RU.
You don't wanna get ratioed on Twitter.
But why do those YFs always have to be bad?
Why can't they be good?
I think we should good ratio this tweet.
You know, just say, let's say you're also looking forward
to fall.
Talk about which of your piggies you want to rock out.
The big one, the one you wanna give the little one some love,
or how about the middle?
The middle gets forgotten.
Suggest different colors of piggy paints
that you might be thinking about.
Or something unrelated, just say you're looking forward
to having a great diva jam with Mr. Six this weekend.
Just transport to 2010.
Yeah, ask what hours the clown is in.
Ask if you just make sure that he's there.
What's the asking price for Baloofs right now?
Right.
I like this, yeah, this is good.
Can you, will the clown or the octopus
give me a Tasmanian devil temp tattoo?
Or a permanent one?
Will it almost lose my hair before dying it purple?
A couple of people have sent us this over the months
of the CityWalk Hollywood account is locked now.
And I don't think there's anything sinister behind it.
I think they just was like,
oh, we're just gonna announce everything
on the Universal Hollywood account.
So we're not gonna use this one anymore.
But it's still up.
So do you think Universal Hollywood knew we would come
for that account eventually with something like this?
They're like, lock it down, lock it down.
Guys are paying too much attention.
My guess is that Trump tried to seize the CityWalk account
to tweet from music and bloggers.
That was my guess.
Oh man, are we gonna call attention to it?
And before you know it,
Darlene Reese is calling for uprisings.
I don't know, you might hopefully not.
No, we're gonna use this for fun.
So go follow at CoasterCuts.
Let's see what happens to the numbers.
Let's bump it up from nine.
Let's go have some fun.
Cause it was a tough run for this place.
I should mention the first one of these opened in March 2009
and in June 2009, Six Flags filed for bankruptcy.
So this wasn't, hey, this was a hair raising experience
for them in the wrong way.
So let's give some positivity to this social media.
Yeah.
I think on the show, I think that's great.
I think on the show we've called for us
to be put in charge of Six Flags in general.
And I think if that ever happens,
project number one is putting these back
in malls across America.
Yeah, yeah, that's right.
Well, yeah, malls are dying.
You gotta get people in there
and you gotta do experiences,
which I think people will be dying for
after being cooped up for so long.
What didn't sound so fun in 2009,
I think would be a blast in 20.
I've like, we've just been stuck inside for so long.
I would love to go have a rock the plank
pirates rock birthday party with you guys.
I'd gladly go pirate up all of our hair together.
Yes, I would love, yes, to pirate up our hair together.
Go see Doolittle and IMAX again.
Can I read this tweet?
Get it while it's hot, $15 buzz cuts.
I would, it's hard to get your hair cut also, you know?
I haven't done it in a while.
Man, at this time they were just plentiful.
$15 buzz cuts and it wasn't even a thing.
It wasn't even a TV special to watch people
get their hair cut.
It was nothing back then.
No longer a dreaded but necessary obligation,
a blessed gift in our modern times.
Yeah.
Man, you know what?
You know, there's that place,
I think we mentioned it,
that was open right before the pandemic, round one,
that is open already in some other places
with arcade games, it has a bowling alley
and it has karaoke rooms.
We were very excited about it.
I think let's add haircuts to that too.
Let's just get another thing in there
and let's get, yeah, let's get a pirate plank birthday
going for me.
Maybe not this year, but maybe next year.
Wow, Mike, I'm having such a great time.
I've been limbo for an hour.
Oh my gosh, I'm so tired, but it was so worth it.
And I gotta say, your big kapow looks totally awesome.
Wow, thanks, this is the best 40th birthday ever.
I assume that's when we'll be able to have a party.
Yeah, at least get it a karaoke room.
Yeah.
Oh no, Jason was just trying to get a blamma jamma
and they cut him.
Just like in his dominion in the 90s.
They cut his belly, they cut Jason's belly again.
His hairy belly, I believe as you referred to it
on the episode. Yes, that's right.
The octopus couldn't see and he cut Jason's hairy belly.
Well, that's what happens when you have eight blades,
one in each of your tentacles.
You can't keep track of them all.
Swinging them around.
I'm realizing now a dreaded but necessary obligation
is probably what my family called it
if we accidentally went to Six Flags Great Adventure
on like a muggy holiday weekend
in the middle of the summer.
Well, geez, you know, I better get back out there
and make sure that my wife is not one bored mommy right now.
I'll help her not be one not so bored mommy.
And she's always a classy mommy.
Let me be clear about that.
On that note, use your phone.
You can play the Vanga Boys when you put a bowl
on your child's head and just cut around.
And give him a picture of Mr. Six and a bow tie
and tell him to pin it.
Yeah.
Go ahead, pin the bow tie.
Yeah, well, we do what we can.
We do virtual Six Flags roller coaster cuts
and we try to make it fun.
You survived podcast the ride.
What a way to kick off the second gate for the year.
I think all of 2021 on the second gate
is gonna be a real, to keep consulting the list.
I think, boy, this year is gonna be a real zoink,
don't you think?
A real, I agree, a real zoink.
Real zoink.
Yeah.
Real blamma jamma hours.
We're gonna, we have so many blamma jamas planned
and every episode for the year is gonna be more fun
than a little date with your classy mommy.
All right, gang, we'll see you next time with more stuff.
Our Venga bus is leaving, gotta go.
Bye bye.
Bye.