Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast contains an ice cream train, seed talk, a horrific batch
of fonts, and spin city era Richard Kind, all part of the troubled stew that was Disney's
California Adventure 1.0.
Come reminisce with us today on Podcast The Ride.
Greetings from California.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the show where we love to San Diego to theme parks and spill
the Yosemite about our favorite rides.
I'm Scott Golden Gatener, and here's a guy who Fres knows his stuff about theme parks,
and you can take that to the Burbank.
It's Mike Carlsbadson.
Hi there.
My name is Mike Carlsbadson.
I am thrilled today to be joined by my two best sacram-bud- sacrament-buddies.
Sacramento buddies.
Right?
Yeah, that works, but it makes me have to change my next one.
Oh, sorry, sorry, sorry.
Because I Hollywood like to introduce the other host of the show.
His favorite movie is Mr. Mulholland's Opus.
Jason Sand Louis Abispeden.
That's right.
Also, would have taken Mulholland Drive.
Wait a minute.
Cleaner, smoother, yes.
That's better.
You punched it up.
How about sacrament bros?
My sacrament, yeah.
We're the three sacrament bros.
Yeah, that's good.
That makes sense.
Could also be San Louis Abis-bros.
You could really change.
That's true.
You could interchange all of the Sans.
If you don't know why I did all that, it still might not add up.
But if you don't know why all this is happening, then you didn't get to experience the original
Disney's California Adventure, which I feel was like walking around what I just did.
Yes.
Is that accurate?
You mean the most jam-packed theme park ever, right?
As the LA Times was hyping it up.
They said that then?
That is the headline to the soft opening roundup article of January 14th, 2001.
The most jam-packed theme park on earth?
What?
What do you mean?
Oh wait, maybe DisneySea wasn't open yet.
When did DisneySea open?
Because if it was open.
DisneySea opened later in 2001, didn't it?
I believe.
Well, then that's the problem.
But the reason they described it that way is because the contents of this article is
all about how we are expecting folks come early in the morning or late at night, because
we're going to be turning people away from this place.
We're expecting 7 million people opening year.
And that did not happen.
Do you have any idea where it ended up?
I'm going to put you on the fact spot.
I saw some numbers that were not good.
I just don't remember them.
They were expecting.
So for they were expecting for the original for Classic Disneyland Park, they were expecting
13.3 million.
And at DCA, they're expecting 7 million.
What they got was 12.3 million and 5 million.
Oh, man.
Wow.
Well, yeah, and in general, just like the day to day crowds were not what they thought
they would.
It was like they thought they were going to like they kind of scared everybody away with
the high, which is similar to what happened a little bit with various points of this of
the Star Wars.
I mean, I mean, Star Wars is always pretty jammed.
But like, I mean, remember the rest of that day of Galaxy's Edge opening were just like
everywhere else at Disneyland as a ghost town.
It was so nuts.
Yes. And we thought we were like going to get tasered if we didn't immediately like
run out.
Yes. Oh, yes. Yes.
I was very worried. I was like, oh, well, they told us we have to leave by two o'clock
and if we don't or noon and if we don't get out by noon, you know what happens?
Jail is 12.03.
We're standing on an largely empty wooded pathway at the other end.
It can't be in this park anymore.
Yeah. If we had if we hadn't gotten out in time, we all would have been dead.
We would have been put into slave Leia costumes.
That's yeah, that's right.
Shamed up and been on Chepex barge and put on Chepex barge.
We're going out into the desert.
You mean Chepex actually, two tons.
They just they Photoshop him to look like that.
He's actually a hulking worm monster.
Chepex is the hut.
Chepex is a hut.
That's our real Chepex the hut.
That's why they they cut the banter ride is they had to pay for his barge.
That that is some lame joke
that's been made by some theme park account, right, or some theme park
like not journals, but commentator.
That's one. Oh, this one.
Sorry, the current one talking.
Yeah, I really we really need to check, check ourselves when we act like
we're so much cooler than the other theme park media.
To to give you an idea of that.
That so these numbers and again, you can find this L.A.
Times article, they are it's the most big dick energy you've ever.
They're like walking around on top of the world.
The park is not opened yet, but they're like, get ready, get ready for this.
So in 2019, the rough attendance numbers and this is all coming from like L.A.
Times and Orange County Register, Disneyland, 18.7 million,
DCA, nine point nine million.
And that year they were like, the numbers are kind of plateauing,
even with Galaxy's Edge.
But in theory, that's a decent year.
Like that's that's a much higher increase like than 18 years ago.
And it's just over half at the second park on a good year.
It's just over half as many people.
Right now, which especially they were like framing the park initially.
Also, like still they wanted those numbers to be as high, but they were also saying
it's maybe, you know, it's not as much as Disneyland.
Like they still would kind of like hedge their bets.
Like, you know, it's it's a 75 percent Disneyland, but that's good.
Right. You're OK with that. Right.
And no one was OK with that.
We're talking here about the episode.
It's called DCA one point.
And we're doing this because this very week,
California Adventure will be celebrating its 20th anniversary.
February 8th, to be exact, is when the park opened.
So so 20 years of California Adventure.
And could we celebrate the the the the wonderful part,
the many great things that there are to do there now or not now,
but were to do when it was open, you know, that the incredible park
it's become. We could do that or we could flash back to the bizarre,
spare, annoying version
that we got some some 20 years ago.
What does it sound like listeners we would do?
You know us. What do you think it sounds like?
You had to guess.
Well, yeah, I think it's I think it's clear what we're going to do.
And I think I think it's a good
it's a good area for us and a good like what I'm excited about here
is that so many of our episodes are about a specific
ride or or place or or area of a park.
And this, I feel like and I, you know,
this is one of those titles that's open to interpretation DCA one point.
But to me, it's about a vibe.
This is like it's like a general
just like aesthetic and a thing in the aesthetic that manifests in
in signs and fonts and odd architecture and
very limited music
collection that was played in this place.
I'm just I'm excited to swim in the vibe of DCA one point.
Oh, and to that end, I think maybe a good thing to talk about is that
in one of our very first episodes, we were talking about like
maybe controversial theme park opinions that we have.
And Jason's was that he he kind of liked the vibe
that you do in some ways miss
what California was like in the very beginning.
Well, you know, I was talking to my dad about this the other day
because I told him we were doing this episode and he's like, you know,
and let me be clear that the first time
I went there was like 2006.
So some adjustments had already been made,
but a lot of it had not been changed yet.
The first time he would have seen, I think, would have been like 2007, 2008.
So, again, even more adjustments.
I think he first came out and saw that park
maybe 2008 right before like Toy Story Midway Mania.
So but there was still a lot of it hanging on.
And I think the thing, one of the things we liked
was, you know, Disneyland's really jam packed with stuff to do.
But DCA, even in its transitional, like years in between the like
very original and then the gradual changes in the mid to late 2000s, early 2010s,
I it was kind of like nice that you didn't have like there were less attraction.
Like you could go a little slower.
You could have a beer.
You know, it was a little like leisurely pace.
We liked, you know, the Grizzly Peak recreation area.
You know, we like the Fisherman's Wharf, the bread tour,
the tortilla factories and some kind of different stuff.
But you could still have a slow day, even if there was more to do.
You know, you can have a slow day now and a beer now.
It would prevent you from.
I mean, that's true.
Now I think it does occasionally suffer from the problem
they were concerned about early on of like with less attractions.
If one or two goes down or one or two are just really backed up,
you can get in that like, oh, what do we do?
Like, where do we go?
Here's my.
It's like blockbuster driven.
Yeah, yeah.
I was just going to here's my theory for what you're actually is going on in your brain.
And I have some of it.
I believe that just because it was 10 years ago, we're all nostalgic for being younger
and being in the past when we had less troubles and less cares.
And now you have that annoying Calliope music with
with the like sparse California adventure, like
theming and the sort of genericness of it.
So now it's associated, you know, 10 years ago,
you were a carefree man in his 20s.
You were a childless man in his 20s.
You know, I, you know, that that's not wrong.
I do very much remember the first day I went in college with my roommate, Jack.
And we got there bright and early at 8 a.m.
because we were going to try to do both parks in one day.
And we did pretty much all of California adventure by noon.
Yeah. And we're like, well, guess we're going back to Disneyland.
Yeah. So because like it could have been Disney, like Disney in 2001
opened up Disney's Toilet Park and it's a toilet themed theme park.
And there are no rides.
It's just a series of bathrooms.
And even though you knew at the time it was bad, I think 10 years later,
you'd be like, you know what? Toilet Park wasn't all bad.
There was some interesting stuff at Toilet Park.
Well, but then there's also some fun to be had for making fun of Toilet Park.
We're going and going and of course, a little on on parts of it.
And, you know, I, I, I do think a lot of stuff I like in California design.
There's a lot of good California kitsch.
So and I can see them like with a limited budget or a budget
that was like, you know, kept getting scaled back.
It seems like there were some stuff they tried to do kitsch.
And some more successful than others and some just outright horror shows.
Yeah. That line of kitsch and cheap is just you got to be you got to be careful.
You have to be so careful or else you end up with the SS Rustworthy.
Oh, boy. Oh, we're going to have some fun here.
Yeah. I think if California Adventure, the original and I yeah, there's obviously,
you know, there's there's Soarin, which is a great ride and it's lasted.
And there's other stuff we like, obviously.
But but California Adventure 1.0
feels like it's the aesthetic of that City Walk gift shop
that sells the fake celebrity IDs.
It's like just it's like as gaudy in places as the sock market
or like any of those other like in your face retail store, like retail shops.
And with that air of like, because we're a little funky here.
Well, welcome, visitor from California.
We do it a little different.
You might have just a plain box and one font,
but we have nine fonts and they are all spinning and yelling at each other.
Yeah. And what you said about the vibe, like the vibe of it is actually,
I think the issue, because I was thinking earlier, I was like, all right,
if you really look at the opening day rides for all the parks, like,
you know, Animal Kingdom, MGM Studios, Epcot,
it's not that there's a lack of like five e-ticket rides,
because that isn't often what happens when a theme park opens.
They have like maybe one like MGM Studios opens and it's got.
Great movie ride. That's like the big showstopper.
And that's a catastrophe canyon in the tour that they have a tram.
Right. Ready to go.
But that's obviously there's precedent for a tram tour,
and I'm not saying they didn't do a good job. They did.
But it's like it just why was an MGM Studios considered a flop
if they only had a couple big new things.
It's like Soren's a great ride and the other rides are fun.
It's what you're saying is what I'm saying.
You're you've got to the point.
I think it's it's the vibe and it's the aesthetic that made people go,
this isn't this isn't worthy.
Well, yeah, but also like, yeah, you're right.
I was younger and like I had less, you know, worries and stuff.
And I was there with my friends or college classmates and family.
And we were having a nice time.
It's why you look back on like movies and you're like, yeah, I don't know if that
I need to rewatch that movie ever.
But like I had a nice time when like XYZ Blockbuster came out
and went with my family and we all went out to dinner.
Of course. You know, of course.
There's no shame in that, by the way.
I'm not trying to shame you for that.
But I think you might be doing some historical revisionism because MGM 1.0.
I think a lot of people forget that it was the great movie ride
at a two hour tram tour.
And that was it.
Yeah. Right. But it was but it was, I think, well received.
I think that was the difference.
But I think that people did like it and were just like thirsting for more.
California Adventure felt to me like we do not want more.
You do do a lot more or I'm never coming back.
Yeah. That I think was the feel.
That is true.
I mean, I think it had a lot riding against it, which is too.
I mean, in the previous years, you had seen Animal Kingdom open
and Islands of Adventure open.
And both pretty well received.
Alamo Kingdom kind of doing a different vibe, a different, different stuff.
A little light on attractions in the early days.
I think very light. I think very light.
Yeah, very light, but very beautiful.
Of course, to counteract.
It's all about the adventure.
Yeah, it's all about the vibe.
Islands of Adventure packed with big roller coasters and very popular
like e-tickets right out the gate.
And then the other thing that was riding against it was the unbuilt
parks, the Westcott and then the Disney Sea that would have gone in Long Beach.
Yes. Yeah, much better sounding.
Definitely. Yeah.
Yeah. And after all that, like if you got any taste of Westcott
and there was enough like I certainly was not like,
you know, I'm in middle school is all this is playing out.
But I still like I remember looking in the newspaper and seeing a
seeing concept art of Westcott and it just looks grand.
It like it looked pretty epic and you knew they were going to
pull it off in a very stately way. Yeah.
I did, though, like concept art of this, too.
I think there was an early California adventure
that would have been better than what they did.
And clearly they just like winded it down and winded it down.
Yeah. And I was, you know, as a younger, I was not aware of the history
of Westcott and the Disney Sea in Long Beach.
And I would assume what?
Ninety eight percent of guests were not aware of any of that.
That's got it right. Yeah. Maybe less. Ninety nine.
It depends. Yeah.
It depends on how local they were.
And I think if they read the newspapers a lot,
because my parents were very aware of like Disney's America and
the Disney Quest in Philadelphia projects, just because that's true.
It's got like a lot of play in the local paper. Right.
But I think you're right, though, Mike, that it's like the average person
is just like, oh, Disneyland. I like Disneyland.
Oh, there's a new Disneyland. I don't like this Disneyland.
Yeah. What is that?
I'd say a degree of knowledge there.
Yeah. It's more of just like initial. This doesn't feel good.
I don't like this feeling like that's what it is.
It's like this feels this feels different.
This feels like this feels, yeah, tacky.
Disney doesn't like if you think about
like a second gate, which we which we call our Patreon.
You know, there weren't that many of them by this point.
Like if you think about, I mean, there were now like several parks at
Disney World, but like there's a lot of pressure on number two.
In a way, almost there isn't as much on number three or four.
And like, what's OK?
Animal Kingdom didn't have as much to do.
Like we know how this goes. They're going to get it there.
But being sort of having to be Disneyland to whether or not that's what they're
whether or not that's fair.
Like when you think about what's the first second gate, it's Epcot Center.
And that's massive.
That opens massive and with extremely ambitious things.
And then Islands of Adventure.
And yeah, that's like completely different vibe than Universal Florida.
And so much to do and really grand stuff also.
Both Epcot and and Islands of Adventure, you have like
technology you can't figure out.
Like they like stepped up.
They they like stepped up a game, essentially,
somewhere in the course of the park.
And then you get what's Disneyland to its
bunch of like sunglasses puns.
It's puns. It's a lot of puns.
A lot of puns.
It's a lot of like postcard humor.
You know what, though, I this wasn't a thing that really dawned on me
until very recently, but.
I think in current DCA,
it would be awesome to just walk over and get a Big Mac.
You cannot undersell how good a Big Mac hamburger is.
And the building looks like shit.
Oh, my God. Oh, the building.
I'm curious what everybody's like least favorite, which that's a candidate for me.
But yeah, like we start getting into specifics here because
there's so much to tribute.
There's so many odds and ends to call out.
It's something that I want to say at the top, just to acquaint
the listener who doesn't totally know.
So, yeah, but you probably know to some extent that California Adventure
opened a little disappointing and there wasn't a lot to do.
And that major things have been added.
The big things being turning the entrance area into Buena Vista Street
with the very the classy Carthay Circle restaurant,
not only as a cool restaurant at the end of the street, but as kind of
the castle that they didn't have before.
So that was a lot of that was one of the big renovations was making that
that street really nice and like the, you know, the
not the I guess the is it 20s or 30s like the Hollywood that Walt landed in
and and Cars Land, obviously, is the huge one.
But that got added.
But besides that, just to acquaint you that in 2001,
what did they not have at California Adventure?
They did not have the Tower of Terror, probably the big
the biggest, quickest save that they were able to do.
They did not have a Bugs Land,
which is now they don't have any more and it's becoming Marvel.
But just all that was, you know, less.
And we'll talk about that.
No Cars Land, no, no Little Mermaid.
There was the Pier area and California Scream and the roller coaster.
But there was not Toy Story Midway Mania.
So you're now you're talking like so many of the what are now
kind of the tent poles of the park are not there.
And obviously, we've talked about this plenty and we just talked about it.
But what is now the Monsters Inc ride was Superstar Limo,
considered the worst attraction.
And and really, we got we've we've covered that plenty.
But Superstar Limo, I feel like jumped out.
I think you didn't have to be a theme park nerd to know about Superstar Limo
and be like, yeah, that sounds awful, because like newspaper articles
would call it out and say, are you wondering what that second Disneyland is?
It's got this. Yeah. Maybe reconsider.
Well, you even compare that to just what a great movie ride,
which I some I've heard critic good, like legit criticisms of great movie.
Great movie, right?
Has tons of show scenes, tons of robots.
You're on a car. They're impressive robots.
They're human size.
And then you just like years later, it's just like tiny little creep robot,
like not even robots.
And it's like, yeah, if you heard about it, you go, oh, that sucks.
But if it was like, I guess there's a version of Superstar Limo
where it's like on the scale of great movie ride, where you maybe go,
oh, well, that was like a big show scene where you saw Drew Carey holding tickets
or whatever. It was a better robot of Drew Carey.
And like even the concepts in that ride could be done better. Right.
You know, I almost said and then and then did not.
When we were talking to Oscar about Monsters Inc.
that I was something occurred to me about that.
I think the I think the vibe, the aesthetic of Superstar Limo
is like the animated intro to the Anna Nicole Smith reality show.
Oh, man.
You are in a ride that looks like that.
We know exactly what you're talking about. Yes.
That is like almost like the nanny.
I don't want to.
I don't I don't dislike the nanny opening as much, but right.
I don't know that I want to go into a ride that looks like the nanny intro.
I think it's using the nannies intro style
as an excuse for a lack of budget.
I think you're you're using that to try to hide and go, well, that's just
there, the aesthetic of it as opposed to like, we don't have that much money.
This is what we got approved.
We're sorry.
Like we did our best. Yeah.
But if if they had like you're saying, Scott, if they had made like
Drew Carey's superstar, like Superstar Limo starring Drew Carey
and it's Drew Carey picking you up at the airport and showing you Hollywood.
Yeah, that could be something. Sure.
Had a popular show on the air.
They could have done like the ball. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. If it's like the scale, like closer to the scale and scope of
great movie ride, yeah, like why like you go, that's kind of odd.
But all right. Like I like that.
I like this scene.
Like as we've said before, like IP and stuff
and even sometimes concept doesn't really matter.
It really just it's like execution and and I would of course say intimacy,
but that's not what everyone would say if you if you wish.
I mean, like, well, now now imagine the exact same series of events
of Rise of the Resistance, but do them as squiggle drawings like Superstar Limo
and like animatronics that are like, is that Kylo Ren?
Yeah. I don't know if is that like John Boyega?
They all look like slightly larger ventriloquist dummies
or like like puppets, like lonely goat herds,
sound of music puppets with like Kylo Ren.
And he's he's like two feet tall and like his arms are just moving up and down.
Floppy mouth. Yeah.
And then the 80 80s are like flat cardboard cutouts
and they're five feet tall.
And then and it's not John Boyega taking you through it or Lieutenant Beck.
It's like, there they are, everyone, the famous.
Take a picture. Smile.
Yeah, I can't imagine that.
It's interesting if stuff had worked out, there might be a version.
If Lucas had sold, say, Lucas decided not to make the prequels
he sold to Disney back then,
maybe because of the budget and the situation at the time,
that would have been the big new Star Wars ride.
You know, I know that, like, of course, we're landing in this
this kind of general opinion of that the the prequels were underrated.
And but like I was always and I like Star Wars too.
I like Star Wars Adventures Continue.
But I remember how like when you were here and they were going to try to do that
in like 2000, like, thank God it took a little longer.
Like, think about how bad those graphics would be.
And they would not have changed it.
I mean, it'd be fascinating if there was like a sub prequel
because it wouldn't have looked as good as the movies even.
It would have been like a lesser version of the pod race that's still there.
Like they certainly would not have changed it in 20 years.
Yeah, because some of the I mean, the prequels still look pretty good.
And he's touched.
George has touched up a lot, had touched up a lot.
And maybe that will continue.
But yeah, I can imagine that the theme park tech version of that
in 2000 would have been bad, coupled with the fact that they weren't spending.
They weren't in a good spending mode.
You could imagine what that would look like.
The first thing I thought of was because for whatever reason,
Instagram suggested I watch a clip and a clip of the red chili peppers
Californication video, which is like sub crazy video game.
Yes. Sub crazy taxi graphics.
Well, that's kind of the idea.
I don't think they meant for that to be photorealistic.
Yeah, no, but it looks awful.
It looks really bad, like much worse than I remember it looking.
And maybe crazy taxi looks that bad, too.
And I'm forgetting.
But that's my first thought is how a star tours would have looked.
Is that level? But that was yeah, that was that was 99, I believe.
Ninety nine or 2000 is when that video came out.
Something like that. Yeah.
I mean, you're you're again.
These are all things, like I said earlier, that I have such
fond memories of warm feelings at the time.
It is hard to divorce myself
from like, I mean, I think I told I told the story about Mike
and me like hanging out with people and putting
Phantom Menace on on a giant TV.
And maybe it had motion smoothing on and that was part of it.
But it looked like like a Windows 2000 screensaver
kind of playing in the background.
But I like a lot of those actors, you know, from the prequels.
And I like a lot of the actors and the new ones, you know, so you
it's it's you have more.
And again, you go see it with people you like.
And so it can be hard to divorce from the quality of something.
I would have replaced Rex in start in Star Tours 2000.
That's a good question.
I mean, yeah, so Phantom Menace is just coming out.
I mean, is it does Jar Jar go in there?
It's got to be Jar Jar.
George definitely was like,
Jar Jar is going to be the biggest character of all time.
Like he was he told Ahmed best that he was not anticipating any
any sort of backlash.
So I could see George being like, well, you know, we're going to want to have Jar Jar
because everyone's going to want to come see him.
We my brother and I had T-shirts had toys before the movie came out.
And Jar Jar was front and center of those shirts.
Yeah, yeah. So excited.
We were I had all the I had all the toys from Phantom Menace.
They are this is how sick I am and how sick the collector community is.
They are just releasing bigger versions on the car
on the same Phantom Menace card and their best, which means that backing of a figure.
So it basically looks exactly like the toys you're talking about.
Phantom Menace, that red card and only it's like, you know, six inch, six inch
figures now, not like the shorter ones we bought.
And I want them. I want the Mace Windu.
I want the Jar Jar. I want I've bought many of these different retro toys this year
that have the same backing card as I had when I was a child.
So, yeah, I we were all hyped for all of those.
And Jar Jar was definitely part of it.
And so maybe it's maybe it's Jar Jar or is it a
is it little Anakin, but rendered at the time in Superstar Limo quality?
I'm going to fly it. I'm the pilot.
So like a little ventriloquist dummy of Anakin Skywalker,
essentially like that quality, big wide mouth and very dead eyes.
Yes, you could like you wouldn't have.
It would have made complete sense to like just replace Pinocchio with him
on the Pinocchio ride, and no one would have even noticed.
They'd be like, oh, yeah, the top on Pinocchio got a new haircut
and he's wearing like a robe now. OK.
Yeah, that's an interesting.
Yeah, I think we would have had a lot more boss Nass.
On on it. I wish there was more boss Nass now.
I love almost all the prequel characters and it's turned.
It's not even ironic anymore, I will say.
But I am fast.
I would have loved it if that had happened.
And then we've got an updated version.
But as you're saying, you're correct.
It would not have happened if it was.
Yes. Although some people would be ardently arguing
and that it's the best ride in history.
There would certainly be that.
Yes, that is true.
That is true. Yes.
Darth Plague is the ride.
Uh, I'll bring it back to California Adventure.
So the one phrase I kept seeing come up and I didn't quite do the math on.
I think it's about right, but it depends on what you consider an attraction.
When California Adventure opened, it had the same number of attractions
as Disneyland did in 1955. Yes.
Did anyone else come across that?
Yes, because I watched the opening day special
hosted by Richard Kind, Barry Bostwick,
Colin Mockery, like a lot of different people.
And they say Brad Sherwood.
Thank you.
Or Burton in there.
And of course, Eisner at the end.
But they say that early on, and that's they're very proud of that.
Yes. As if that means that's not acceptable.
Yeah, that's bad. That's not good.
Yeah, our standards have it's kind of similar to how like sometimes somebody will.
You'll you'll see a comforting stats.
What's supposed to be a comforting stat about how actually the pandemic is playing
just about just like the Spanish flu.
Like, oh, and these things happen, these things happen.
So this is kind of how this thing is supposed to go.
You're like, no, it's not. That was 100 years ago.
Yeah. Yeah. Should be way better than it's something 100 years ago.
It's it really feels like that Disneyland stat is an excuse.
It feels like they're already hedging a little bit and go, well,
it's the same as the original.
So I don't know what you're complaining about.
And you're like, I didn't complain yet. I don't know.
Why are you so defensive?
Why are you arguing with me in this special?
It's like when they did the Hong Kong Castle exactly like the Disneyland Castle.
That's like a trap.
Like, yes, instead of doing a giant ornate castle,
which now they're having to go back and do, they did exactly a Disneyland castle.
And they're like, well, that's not good enough for you.
You seem to like it at Disneyland.
Why don't you like it here?
Because we our expectations are higher now.
Yeah, you clearly you just did it because it's cheaper to build this
and you have the design.
So that's what you're doing.
You're pretending it's like some sort of homage
when it's not because I looked at the Disneyland stat and then I looked at
I go, OK, what was open Disney Disneyland opening day?
It's like, first of all, you have to put yourself in a different context.
This type of crazy theme park did not exist yet.
Yeah, it is inventing a thing.
It's inventing a thing.
But there's a number of mule based attraction.
There's a lot of mules.
There were no mules in DCA.
Mules, multiple trains, you know, trains, mules,
and then a couple of dark rides, which were very ambitious for the time.
And then the theming, of course, which.
Almost all of it. Yeah.
If you were to if I'm trying to think, what would you describe it?
Is it like inflation, like themed inflation?
We're like, you know, that and, you know, when Disneyland opened,
that was worth three animal kingdoms at the time.
But now we're sure that's what I'm trying to figure out how to explain that.
Like, just that they like had a flag.
Like, here's a medieval flag.
Well, it's just like it would look in the movie.
And now you're you kind of expect because they stepped up their game.
You have to judge people by post 1955 standards.
Yeah, I mean, people probably like saw the car,
the Snow White and the Seven Dwarf cars that had the name of the dwarves on it.
And they were like, holy shit, those are the characters from the movie we like.
Oh, my. They were getting so excited about it like that.
That made so much like that was so much of a bigger impact,
probably on those guests than. Yeah.
Then then.
Honey, give me a Benzo and a cigarette.
I need to calm down.
Hold on. I'm getting harassed by Bob Cummings.
I have to. Yeah.
Hold on. Help. I need I need to get away from this crazed man.
There are so many mules and you could make out with a big star from TV
who's hopped up on sheep's sperm.
There's so much to do here.
Yeah. Oh, Jason, go ahead.
Oh, I was going to say, meanwhile,
here's another thing from that L.A. Times article.
They quote Barry Braverman,
Disney's chief creative supervisor of the project.
And the setup is that, you know, well, there's less rides.
So a couple go down, you know, that could be dicey.
And his response is, quote,
we'll just have to count on the live entertainment being good.
And I think we it wasn't right.
I don't have a lot about all of this stuff, but I have these phrases in my head
like Eureka!
Or there'd be, I don't know, like people banging on trash cans.
What was the live entertainment?
There was a bad show called Steps in Time.
I don't remember much about Steps in Time.
That was kind of like a not a jukebox musical, like a variety of review.
I think was big songs from the movies and stuff.
OK. And that was eventually replaced by the trash can thing.
Eureka! was the California parade, right?
Yeah, that's right. Right.
Yeah. Do we know what Eureka! was like?
I did not go down the Eureka! rabbit hole.
Some of this, you know, we got it.
We've got a three hour Bountiful Valley Farm episode.
We got a Eureka! episode.
You know, the bigger bigger fish to fry the opening special alone.
Yeah, we're going to plant seeds for future things.
Oh, like the seeds you would find at Santa Rosa seed and supply.
Roses. That was something in the park.
Santa Rosa seed and supply.
Yeah, it was by San Andreas Shakes and Bountiful Valley Farmers Market.
Oh, and the Bountiful Valley Farm. Yeah.
Oh, boy. Well, we got so much.
This is going to be a two parter.
Here, I just want to show you what I found just googling the parade.
Oh, yeah. This is terrible.
So Disney's Eureka! California Adventure Parade had a guy dressed as a fortune
cookie and somebody dressed as a box of noodles.
And his legs are bamboo and his legs are still legs are big bamboo shoots.
That's the big float.
Oh, God. The stilt walkers is the Golden Gate Bridge is horrified.
So there's two guys dressed as the Golden Gate Bridge.
Yeah, here's just like
just an ugly version of the entrance and the sun.
No, that's a that's Pixar Play Parade.
That is not that there's that woman like the spirit of California.
I don't know. There's a lot of like generic mystical element,
like spirit of California and and some questionable indigenous representation.
Like, it's just.
I don't quite know what it I don't even know how to describe it.
Well, we'll be doing that eventually.
Yeah, there's yeah.
The the I'll pull up a video that is the
did you guys watch the opening ceremony?
The like the little like play that happened out in front.
We're way Disney talked and Eisner talked.
I mean, we I think we have to do an episode all about
opening ceremonies at some point, as we've talked about.
Yeah, we're like that.
They make Benicio del Toro do it with a little skit.
I mean, these things are great.
This is definitely its own thing.
But let me try to find this part, because this is kind of the vibe that
you were showing with like vaguely mystical elements,
as Jason was saying.
And this is what I so they put up a bunch of like
blue tarps in front of the park.
There's an audience of seated guests.
There's this I don't know what character this is.
If this is like a something related to Khalifa or Khalifa,
the whoopie Goldberg character, and we'll deal with that later.
But the, you know, there's some kind of California Queen comes out.
And it seems like it's all these dreamers essentially like here's gold people
and blue people, and they're all chasing something with streamers.
They're dreamers with streamers.
But what is it? What do they want?
Oh, a big golden California.
There she blows.
And then the guy waves it in front of them like here.
Isn't this what you were dreaming of?
And then a banner goes by that says, imagine.
And one says culture and most you can't read because they aren't angled
to face the audience.
I like this is chaos.
And also, what is this like?
All right. The things you can do in California, that there's beauty
and there's Hollywood, I get all that.
But like who cares about the shape?
Like as if the shape came to you in a flux capacitor dream.
There's a place and it looks like this.
It's straight at the top and then it squiggles down to the right.
It haunts me each night.
Well, you make fun of it, but you had the video muted.
You couldn't hear the assembled crowd going shape, shape, shape.
Best state shape.
That looks like other than the size, that looks like a thing I made
in elementary school for like a project, like a home project
that I put off until like nine p.m.
Nine p.m. the night before the night before,
which is how I usually did my projects.
And it would just be like, well, I don't my mom.
I don't know. We have cardboard.
You could there's a goal.
We have a gold pen.
And I'd be like, oh, yeah, OK.
So we'll like just cut out California and pan like draw gold on it.
It looks I mean, I'm sure it's not paper, but it looks like shit.
It looks awful. Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, it's big.
That's the only thing is that the only thing I could give this
to them over you and your mom is that maybe you couldn't have fit this
in your house. No.
Besides that, the quality is exactly
exactly the school project.
Give it some shading or something so the audience can see it a little more.
Something suggesting dimension, perhaps.
It just yeah, it looks it looks bad.
The whole thing is rough.
And, you know, yeah, we'll deal with this in an opening ceremony thing.
But, you know, Mickey comes out and Eisner sort of justifies the the premise.
This is a whole I don't know that we super need to go into this.
And it's covered in the various documentaries and such.
But, you know, there was a retreat in Aspen where they got everybody together to
let's crack that idea, that second park.
What's something we can do?
And they put a lot of ideas up on the board.
And it sort of was like cherry picking a few.
And the idea was like, if you were being not cynical, you would say, well,
these are themes we've always wanted to tackle, like the charming seaside
amusement park or the nature of Yosemite and that kind of thing.
And of course, you're doing a new Disney MGM studios would make sense.
But if you're being cynical about it, it's like, well, what are our main
travel tourism competitors?
Like, all right, people, what do people do instead of Disneyland?
They go to nature and they go to Hollywood and they go to,
I don't know, Santa Cruz, the boardwalk there.
How do we let's do a fake one of all those and then we'll cut in all their money.
That is, I mean, I guess, yeah, now that you say that, it's like that was sort of
a very strong Eisner philosophy.
MGM studios is that.
Animal Kingdom is like, well, let's make a better zoo than the zoo.
Let's put Busch Gardens out of business.
Yeah, right.
So it's like we can do everything better.
So like, it does seem like that is a big part of him, even in the parks that we
like and were more successful from the get go was, yeah.
I think it's that he could like that sort of cynicism mixed with a ton of money
could sometimes produce some great results.
But then here you didn't have the ton of money.
Well, but what you said, something that runs me the wrong way, I was like,
wait a minute, why did they transport all these people to Aspen, Colorado
to figure this out?
I mean, if you wanted to get everyone out of town, like Santa
Barbara's two hours up the road, like, well, they maybe didn't have
their California idea yet.
Yeah, right. Maybe the thoughts.
Yeah, they maybe it could have been a totally other idea.
No, no, I don't even mean like the transporting the park.
I mean, like for corporate responsibility, it's like,
oh, it seems like you put more thought into the this retreats
vacation aspect than you did the actual work, you know, potentially.
It's that maybe where they their head was at.
Yes. What's a nice trip we can do.
Do you think if Eisner was still in charge, we would have like some sort of
Lego type land in one of the parks to make sure people like kids
didn't go to Lego land.
I don't know if he would have like block partnered with block place or something
like block. Yeah.
California Adventure would have a block place where you would play with connects.
Connects. Yeah. Is that Lego Lego owned?
I forget. Oh, as it might be Playmobil.
He's just like looking for, yeah, adjacent properties.
Or they just make their own.
They just make their own Disney Mickey Mortars.
They build a building with Mickey Mortar. Mortars.
Yeah, like like what you.
Oh, yeah. Oh, right. Yeah, yeah, yeah, of course.
Not the yeah, that's the bomb.
The projectile. Yeah, you're right.
That's what my brain went to is like, we're making Bob.
We're making bombs now.
That's that's for dismal land.
That's for Banksy's dismal land.
Yeah. Oh, Disneyland. Yeah.
I maybe to start stepping into some specific things.
And some of the big stuff that I'm sure we want to talk about is right at the front.
So why don't we do kind of let's let's head into the park.
Let's imagine that those blue walls at the opening ceremony went down,
because that's what happens after they find California.
Thanks to the sun goddess or whatever.
Then one layer comes down and you see those big California letters.
There you I think people probably remember this.
This was still there up until fairly recently.
Big letter spelling out California.
I think this is among the less egregious things that they they did initially.
Yeah, I think it's a clever idea.
I don't know that a lot of this park, it's like, oh, I can kind of see
the kernel of a clever idea.
The execution or the like the reach was not necessarily there.
But yeah, this is this is less egregious. Yeah.
And I think this is a food. I will give this credit.
This is a these are letters that were taken like photos in front of a lot.
I believe everyone, everybody has photos of these.
So like pre Instagram, they had made like a very Instagramable thing.
And like, I believe, I don't know, I'm using a newer way,
a newer philosophy to think about success here.
But I think that you could say, well, that was fun.
I liked taking it. I like going up in front of that sea.
Now, the problem may have been a lot of people did the photo
and then walked away from this.
Is it to Disneyland?
Yes, to Disneyland or to the pizza restaurant.
Yeah, yeah. That'd be fair.
Yeah, you know, I liked I think the letters ended up looking nice
when they did like they made it look like the world of color.
And there's a slow gradient to the letters.
They look nice in the holidays.
Like they were able to like on DCA 1.0 these that like they
they didn't look like trash. And then the font is good.
I'll give it up for the font because I have a lot of font problems in this park.
They eventually got rid of these.
Though they lasted a while longer.
They now it all got moved up to Sacramento
to a place called Cal Expo, which is where they do the California State Fair.
So it's cool that they found another home.
Gavin Newsom has given some very stressful press conferences
in front of these letters and which I remember like infuriating.
I think he like announced restrictions on theme parks
or failed to address theme parks or something in front of the letters.
And people were like, but he's right in front of the letters
and he's making theme parks suffer.
So a dark use of the letters.
And then, by the way, now that thing Cal Expo,
because the state fair sites just kind of sit dormant most of the year
and all year in this case, because there's no state fair,
it has become a mega vaccine site.
And it is apparently doing among the worst of any of the mega vaccine sites.
Disneyland is which has a vaccine site now is up and running
and doing way better than the place it gave the letters to.
Toy Story lot is where that vaccine center is.
Yeah, which, you know, there I was I was going to tweet about this,
but maybe this is it.
Do we do the three of us and therefore
parking garage expert Nick Weiger, do we have to wait to get the vaccine
and apply to do it in a different county so that we can do it
in the Toy Story lot so far unaddressed on podcast?
Well, that's a very good question.
I have thought about that question.
Yeah. But then also apparently Six Flags is a vaccination site as well.
Yes. Closer is L.A. County.
Yeah. And we apply for we are we qualify for that one.
But yeah.
So here's the thing.
This is a great idea for a bit.
But the reality is we should probably all get a vaccine
as soon as we can and maybe not hold out for a bit.
But the reality is if someone broke into my home
and was screaming that a needle that they have out is the vaccine,
I might let them stick it in me just in case.
I'll take anything resembling a vaccine.
It's worth the risk.
So if it if it happens, if there's some sort of serendipity
where we can do it in one of these places, I would love it.
But yes, I agree with you.
If like the mailman goes, hey, you know, I have an extra vaccine.
You want to take it? I would say, oh, yeah, sure. OK.
I would probably do it.
So it's a great idea, though.
I mean, we would get a great three hour episode out of waiting in the vaccine
line and say, like, how did they you know, how's the theming for the vaccine line?
And we've gotten we've talked about so much less with the parking garages.
And now we could go get cured of the disease of the century in the parking lot.
That's probably that's so much more dramatic than anything
we ever thought would happen in the Disneyland parking lots,
especially the one that is nothing that is just a pavement.
Could we get the first dose in Toy Story and the second dose at Six Flags?
If we're doing Moderna or Pfizer,
just so we can get this whole spread.
I don't think City Walk is out.
Yeah, I don't think City Walk is doing it.
Because it's too confusing.
Yeah, yeah.
People, they'd waste vile after vile
because of the confusing universal parking garages.
Where's King Kong? Yeah.
Oh, no. I got the disease now.
I died.
And Mike would end up with a comically large thing of vaccine juice
that he's like, I don't want to drink that.
I got to go.
I don't want to throw it out.
Just dump it in a bush.
You don't want to dump it in a bush.
Yeah, yeah. I guess that makes sense.
It would want to do that at City Walk.
Well, so that's I don't know.
Let us know what you think.
If you really want us to do it and if you work in the medical community
and can help us do it.
Oh, yeah, we're willing to cut.
We're willing to cut a line in front of people that need it more.
I will start doing spin kicks on strangers.
Yeah. And why is for sure in?
I mean, oh, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, we'll just assume for him.
Right. Definitely.
He'll hear. Yeah.
OK, so we keep moving past the letters and the letters are part of a greater
tableau, and that is the postcard
introduction to the park.
The is it was it just called?
Is it called anything?
Is it called sort of greetings from California or something?
You mean is it like that's called the world's largest ceramic mural is what it is.
It's the largest at the time was the largest ceramic mural in the world.
That's cool. That is cool.
The postcard.
Yeah, the postcard didn't go anywhere, right?
I didn't see anything about that.
Do like, did it move the mural?
Yeah, I'm not sure.
I feel like I might have.
Maybe they did try to take it somewhere, but I don't really know.
But this whole idea, I don't think that I knew exactly that this
that was the idea.
It just kind of looks
chintzy, despite being like, it's certainly amazing ceramic work.
If you're just judging it on the the ceramic quality, but the
that you're in a postcard, I don't think I got it.
Yeah, I guess I didn't get that either, really.
I guess that doesn't really play so strongly.
This is also another thing about and I should as we criticize
some things about California Adventure 1.0, if you look at something,
you might actually go, well, that looks like it took a lot of time
and artistry to make it.
I just don't find it pleasant.
Mm hmm. Yeah, yeah.
Totally. It's like that sort of.
Yeah, you can actually appreciate sometimes where you go, man,
a lot of work went into that thing that I go, oh,
just show. Well, how about just how do you guys feel about the
Golden Gateway, which is what I believe what they call the Golden Gate Bridge?
You know, the miniature Golden Gate that the monorail goes over,
because that's still a bridge.
They made it that bridge and that water village that you take
if you're going to Dunkin Donuts.
I think like a bridge we use.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think that's I honestly I think that's OK.
I don't find that so egregious.
Yeah, it makes sense.
It's a pretty what are the more recognizable,
you know, things I think they reproduce?
I liked the idea.
But yeah, I think it's chintzy.
They hit it in that they're just saying it in the Imagineering Story
documentary, and I was like, good. Yeah, let's and I can't tell you why exactly.
The idea I remember thinking, oh, and the monorail goes over the Golden Gate
Bridge, that's pretty neat.
And then it just what is wrong with the bridge?
Is it is it the wrong shade?
Is it too small? It does.
It looks legolandy to me.
Yeah, I think it's a little cartoony.
And then and then shortly thereafter that you hit this ornate Grand Hotel,
which is very detailed.
Of course, you do not stop at it.
No, no, you can't get off her on there.
No, no. So, yeah.
I think it's I think that if the if it wasn't just like flats
with mountains around it when you're looking at those Golden Gate Bridge
things, I think it would have looked better.
I think just the nature of it, it does it like when those things juxtaposed,
it just gives you a sense of cheap, like cheap.
It just doesn't feel grand.
And I think you could probably keep the bridge things the same.
And if just the stuff around it was better,
you might actually go, oh, yeah, well, it looks cool.
That's pretty cool. Yeah, yeah.
There's so many rivets.
It was just like so studded.
I felt like it seemed like too many.
Maybe they maybe they bought me.
That's what made it look like Legos to me.
I this this might be a good
because this is this is how I found this this little rabbit hole.
I you know, if you want to see pictures of early California adventure,
it is so well archived on the site.
Yes, your land that does a great job of.
Yeah, just keeping track of things that used to be there.
And they're a California side of the site is just packed.
There's so much.
And they were talking about things about this Golden Gate Bridge.
And well, you know, one thing about it is it was a great place to hang
banners and to advertise events that were coming up at the park,
because they were they one thing about early California adventure.
They tried to do a lot of odds and ends events.
They had the X games come in, which led to some very ugly artwork.
They had a concert series in the first band ever to play it.
Of course, America's band, the Beach Boys with Mike Love
and Bruce Johnston and no one else who matters.
So there was lots of garbage like that.
And they did a thing called and there's a big banner hanging off
the Golden Gate Bridge advertising ABC Primetime preview weekend in 2004.
So I wondered what that was.
And it seems like it was basically an up front.
And if you don't know the up front, it's where a network trots out
all their new shows to show to advertisers.
And wouldn't you, a regular person who paid to go on some rides,
love to be advertised to about, you know, hope and faith
or and or eight rules for dating my teenage daughter
or whatever shows were on ABC at the time.
Is this thing? Oh, yes, I was just going to say, is that the same event
where Jim Belushi played blues on stage?
You are correct, sir.
I'm sorry, I probably I jumped the gun.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. No, no, no, no, no.
No, this is because this is great.
Yes. Among the like you're looking at a list.
I mean, there's great stuff all over the list.
You know, there's going to be a reunion of growing pains with Kirk Cameron
with a new some defying
Christmas spirit carrier and covid carrier Kirk Cameron.
Uh, so a lot of lots of dumb stuff.
And then it all culminates.
That seems like the peak of this event was a live Saturday evening performance
by Jim Belushi and the Sacred Hearts introduced by Jimmy Kimmel.
Jimmy Kimmel, eventual host of the Oscars, kind of America's host
at this point, was just the opening act for Jim Belushi.
I feel like this restaurant tour, this guy's got a barbecue place down the block.
Oh, does it? I haven't been.
Oh, what's that?
You're. Wait, wait, wait, wait, hang on.
Who's who's a restaurateur?
Yeah, Belushi.
Yes, a barbecue.
Isn't he part of House of Blues?
House of Blues was.
He's not part of House of Blues.
He would certainly play at it, but he was not.
I don't believe was a like at least like not a major partner.
He might maybe that maybe he got in there as an investor or something,
but I don't think he was like one of the mains.
I see. OK.
I don't. You guys are the Belushi experts.
I got to leave it.
Proudly so.
Yeah.
But should you discover anything I don't know about this?
How this sacred performance?
No, and I'm trying to remember which episode we talked about this before.
It's been like two years, but there were two.
We did talk about it. We did.
There were two years in a row that Jim Belushi and the Sacred Hearts played,
and I was looking desperately for footage, but I could not find any.
I just found some pictures of him with like the DCA backdrop.
And I want to say he was playing like a harmonica, but.
Sounds right. Yeah.
So, yeah, there's no I mean, if somebody in the audience has video of Jim Belushi,
please send it to to us or point us in the right direction.
If it's your private video, even please
up raise or capture it and send it our way,
because I would like to see this.
Mm hmm. But yeah, I don't know.
Look, I'd love to see Jim Belushi perform at Disney's California Adventure now.
I think that that should still happen.
I think it could happen.
It would have been great if he like did a guest spot at the Mad Tea Party
where like he just kind of spinning.
Yeah, he could have dressed up like one of the Alice characters or not.
It doesn't matter.
Some like and now the Cheshire cat, Mr.
Jim Belushi to play Cheshire blues cat.
Yeah, he's a cool cat. We know that.
I like Jim Belushi, by the way, on Twitter lately has been killing it.
I will give him that. You know, he gets he's got.
Yeah, you're kind of funny in his like weed guy.
Yeah, he's got a lot of shit over the years, but it feels like he's in a nice,
comfortable place where he's just growing weed and like being nice to people on Twitter.
Hmm. I tried to get us some, but it's only being sold, I think,
at the Pacific Northwest right now due to licensing and interstate trade.
Oh, man.
Is Jim Belushi's weed farm themed enough for us to do an episode on podcast?
I think the strains are Blues Brothers oriented,
so there is theming in the weed itself.
God, yes, we have to.
We really should do that.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, boy. Yeah.
What is this? It's just Belushi farms.
What is he? Because I it's like I think it is just like it's not even clever.
It is like Blues Brothers weed.
Oh, yeah, it's just the Blues Brothers.
And then Belushi's secret stash.
Wow. So do you think Danny Danny Ackroyd gets a cut?
Do you or he just kind of gave him his blessing to make it?
Because obviously weed is a big business.
And I think like Danny, Danny's a big business man, as we know.
I wonder. I'm interested.
Was it was he cut out as revenge for not being part of the House of Blues?
That's a good question.
Or not being featured prominently in Blues Brothers 2000.
Or is he in it at all?
Doesn't make an appearance or my crazy.
I'm just thinking, I don't know if he's in it at all.
He just shows he sometimes plays as the Blues Brothers on tour with Dan Ackroyd.
I just found an old performance.
I was thinking about the especially the area where there were three of them,
where it was Ackroyd and John Goodman and Jim Belushi.
And I saw a performance from the House of Blues where they have the actual of Sam
and Dave. Sam is performing Soulman with them
uncoordinated dancing in the background, like not synced up.
And he does the first verse of Soulman, he being a
African-American performer.
And then for the second verse, Jim Belushi, a white man,
grabs the mic forcefully and takes it over to sing Soulman.
And just like the hearing.
All right. Here's the original.
And now Jim Belushi, who seems to do his choices to scream it.
That's his take on the blues is screaming.
I'm not sure any of those three men, Dan, Jim or John,
are the greatest singers in the world.
That's not what I would say.
No, Sam and Dave great, like fantastic singers from
you know, Sam's there. Maybe you let Sam do it.
Is Belushi the one that we talk about the story about the DVDs?
The Christmas gifts and the car? I'm not sure.
I'm not sure where I heard this. I think it's Belushi, but.
It it was Christmas time
and the show was taken, whatever it would have been, according to Jim,
was his show, right? Mm hmm.
And usually when you're working on a long run TV show like that
and it gets, you know, everyone gets very close
and either the production company or the studio gives out Christmas gifts.
And sometimes like I've had friends get like bikes like for the Christmas gift.
The Christmas gift on that show was the season, the previous season on DVD.
And I believe the story goes that Belushi had, you know, he had the
primo parking spot right by the soundstage.
But his window was like left cracked just a little.
And he came out at the end of the night and the car had just been filled
of the DVDs, like people just shut the boxes through the window and filled the car up.
Wow. I've never heard this. Is this a secret story?
I don't know. Wow. I don't know.
I have no idea where the bridge is being burned.
Is it our bridge to go to Belushi farms? Yeah.
Yeah. We'll have to figure it out if we have to leave this in, you know. Yeah.
Hmm. Yeah. How bad too much do we because it is a themed environment.
Or are you thinking like this happened to Kevin James?
Like, you know, is there another? Oh, yes.
It also could. Yeah, it could have.
Now that you say that, it could have been Kevin James.
It did it. I like the story.
It's a great story. Yeah. The source of it.
I also just want to say really fast that I'm on Belushi's farm dot com.
And there's like a big I almost feel like acroids involved because the
the the text and specifics could not be thicker than the copy
that I am reading about these marijuana strands.
And listen to this.
As with music, we are naturally wired and set up with tetrahedronal shaped
endocannabinoid receptors that are organic to all of us.
Jeff Sessions included.
God, if whenever you have that set case closed,
that's a that sounds like a real acroid.
Yeah, yeah. Maybe he maybe he helped.
He punched it up.
And then we'll topical bunch up several Trump,
several generations of Trump villain ago.
And which sort of brings me to
the second thing I was going to say about this event,
about prime time preview weekend 2004.
There was also among the many things, come see the stars of the show.
And you can also see a little preview and meet the star of the show.
The benefactor.
Do you guys have any idea what the benefactor was?
Show in 2004, was it their version of the apprentice?
It was their version of the apprentice and it was starring this beefcake.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Do you even recognize him as young, hunky Mark Cuban?
This is like what who is he trying to look like?
He's like trying to he thinks he's Freddie Prinze Jr. or something.
Chris Klein early to. Yeah, yeah, totally.
The CW's Frankenstein.
He's in a bright blue shirt.
They didn't shop out his nipple.
It's poking through and also in front of a blue background.
They got Cubans look.
They engineered it a little better on a ventral shark tank and shark tank,
obviously much more successful than the benefactor.
The benefactor did not do so well.
And in the wake of the show going away, Mr.
Cuban received a letter.
And I'd like you to guess during this letter who wrote the letter.
Oh, dear Mark, if you have any suspicions.
I might know.
Bet a lot of money on your opinion on this.
Dear Mark, I am truly sorry to hear that your show has been canceled
for lack of ratings when I initially called you to congratulate you on the benefactor.
Little did you or I realize how disastrous and embarrassing
it would turn out to be for you.
If you ever decide to do another show, please call me and I will be happy
to lend a helping hand with best wishes.
And then I'll narrow it down.
The writer of this letter is a future president of the United States.
So that gets you down to three and you can guess which one.
Ron Paul. Yeah.
We don't need to say it.
That's yeah, that's right.
That makes sense. That makes a lot of sense.
It's on gold letterhead that might have helped you figure it out.
This this is what this guy's doing in 2004.
And we we must elect him to the highest of this guy has to take control of the world.
Yeah, no, that may it makes after having seen it for four years,
it makes total sense that this it all makes sense.
It had to happen. It was great that it happened.
We all the America was made great again.
So that's that's all my thoughts about this is how this is.
This is quickly becoming that we're just going to have to do a part two of this
because boy, oh boy, yeah, we're just going to have to do like land by land.
This is only the street.
Right. And then we'll do Paradise Pier 1.0.
And maybe genuinely a solution because man, we're there.
We got a lot here.
Well, and we haven't even talked about my favorite part of Sunshine Plaza.
Yeah, yes.
I'm talking about Burbank Ice Cream.
Maybe you threw me.
I thought you were going to go for the sun.
The sun's fear.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, I think about Burbank Ice Cream, please.
So Burbank Ice Cream was the like, you know, the the Sunshine Plaza.
This is the equivalent of Main Street.
So it's got to have an ice cream parlor to get people coming in
or going out of the park at the end of the night.
And it you entered through a California Zephyr like train car.
And it's a it's a real like, you know, two sides of the train.
I just think it looks great.
It's a shiny like restored train car.
And you went in and you got any any number of Disney's six ice cream flavors.
They have not updated in, I don't know, decades.
Like whatever the dryers relationship.
I think when when Disney when when Disneyland opens back up,
we need more ice cream flavors.
It's it's the same flavor, the same seven or eight flavors.
I know I I I wouldn't mind more flavors,
but I do find the dryers flavors comforting that they don't change ever.
There's something I like about the stability.
And maybe I'm being a hypocrite when other things that I say.
But I I'm not saying take any way.
I'm saying, like, let's get it.
Disneyland, it's supposed to be.
Yeah, it's expand.
And like, especially back then, they had four Sundays.
Like, I don't know.
It just seems like kind of all of the ice cream,
except the ice cream at Paradise Pier, where you would pick a flavor ripple.
Yeah, like everything is just chocolate vanilla in this part.
Everything's what are you looking for?
Yeah, like Blue Sky real quick here.
Five, five to ten more flavors that they need to have.
OK, well, I I think mocha almond fudge is an interesting flavor,
but I found the almond overwhelming.
I think they need a simple coffee flavor.
OK, I think they need a rocky road.
OK, OK, they have chocolate chip, which I think people think is crazy.
A crazy like I love chocolate chip because you get the creaminess of vanilla,
but then actual crispy chocolate. Right.
Let me see some sort of caramel.
OK, some sort of caramel.
What else we get on the fruitier side or getting towards the gelato territory?
Yeah, maybe a raspberry sorbet or a you get a sherbet.
Mike, you get a I am.
I got a sherbet, a rainbow sherbet,
and I often get a double scoop with a cookie dough as well.
That's good. They do a good cookie dough.
And is cookies and cream on this list?
They have cookies and cream, right?
I guess they have cookies and cream.
There's there's a big one that I feel like it's some sort of peanut butter thing.
OK, yeah, that's good. I hear you.
I think I just think more variety.
I mean, I looked up the menu of San Andreas Shakes, too,
which is a different part of the park.
That was pretty much just like two kinds of blizzards
and two kinds of milkshakes, chocolate or vanilla.
Yeah, like that's that's kind of boring.
Well, you can get date shakes there, I thought, like all on the way to Palm Springs.
I forget the name of that date shake place, but I definitely at some point
in time had a date shake in California Adventure.
See now that I like I must have been looking at a newer menu where they scaled back.
But I think like, yeah, date shakes. That's fun.
Yeah, for sure.
I don't know if it was there, but I definitely had one in the park.
Does Ghirardelli do anything for you or do you want to do your land?
OK, because we always go to Ghirardelli in California Adventure.
Now, do they have enough? They're right.
Does Ghirardelli have enough?
Yeah, they have a lot of varieties of like parfaits and sundaes
and maybe just one or two more ice cream flip.
But they have they just have a lot and they have a lot of mix ins
and they have a lot of toppings.
So you want to just a little more convenience, essentially,
because if they have it in California Adventure, you will.
You just want something else on Main Street switched up.
Yeah, I guess I guess on.
Yeah, I don't I don't need it in California Adventure because there is Ghirardelli.
But yes, at Main Street and at California Adventure now,
they have the hand dipped ice cream bars, which that's fun.
That's very nice. I like that.
That's that's a huge two.
I agree with you. Burbank, the Burbank.
What is what is called Burbank ice cream? What was it called?
Like so Burbank, Burbank ice cream.
Burbank ice cream. The train cars were cool.
I do miss getting ice cream in the train cars for by like that.
But that area is, I think, the thing I miss the most of all.
I think they pulled that off.
If you're going to keep anything from this opening zone. Yeah.
I remember being on the train.
Yeah. A little disappointed when I went the first.
I was like, oh, they got rid of the train cars. Oh, oh.
Yeah. And that seems like something they easily could have moved
to the Hollywood backlot area. Yeah.
But yeah, I assume they were still.
I think that the Hollywood backlot, yeah, they we've talked about it before.
Like it's obviously going to be changed eventually.
And I think they were probably assuming they would do something sooner
rather than later.
And they probably didn't see a pandemic slowing everything down either.
Yeah. Yeah. Yes. We're stuck.
We're stuck with it.
I well, OK, you want to talk about, by the way,
Disney's got to hire you for to be an ice cream consultant.
Of course. That was so concise.
Like great ideas. Just flying.
You didn't even prep that. That's just off the dome. Yeah. Sure.
Just walk around. Yeah.
Like walk around like you would walk around with a team of people at Disney.
And you would just sort of be giving your thoughts like very free.
They'd be like kind of all have a notepad and they'd be hanging on every word.
And you would just be shouting flavors, flavor every every different food
stand in a restaurant.
I think you would just shout things out and they would write it down
and that you could fix a lot of problems that way.
I feel like I was shouting a lot like looking at the map,
like looking at the original DCA maps.
And I was just then I would go look up what they had.
And and I was just like, OK, the the will was not the thought was there.
The will was not there.
It's like like we want this to be a park for adults.
We want then don't serve like dog food, like
college, like food you would have thrown together in college.
You know, food wasn't good there, was it?
For like you think that's one of the main things and probably why I'm so
for why I consider it like the park of my the park of my 20s
in my early 30s is like you go there for good food and good beverage.
Yeah, I don't. Yeah, it was kind of junky to begin with.
I think Pacific Wharf was always interesting.
It always had a variety of stuff.
It was bread and it had some freshly made stuff.
And then I I honestly have never eaten at that.
Winery restaurant.
The sit down restaurant, I don't recall loving.
I'm I love the terrace and I love the walk of the walk away wine bar.
But the yeah, it's kind of like generic Italian, I feel like.
OK, she can get in a lot of place.
I could be wrong if I'm if I'm way off on that place.
I was just disappointed the one time I did it.
I'm sure it's changed the menu like a million times at this point.
So who knows? Yeah, yeah.
Rough food, seemingly.
The also the shout out to the restaurant was called Chips.
It's strips, dips and chips.
Yeah, strips, dips or chips.
No one rides for free.
That kind of the fried mozzarella and the chicken strips and fish fillet.
So, you know, you know, it's I think, yeah, the train is good,
but you know, it's egregious and I'll share the screen so we can be reminded.
Engine ears, toys, city walk, real gaudy logo.
Yeah, yes. Yeah, extremely city walky, extremely sock market sock market.
You know, I think extremely build a bear and the bear went in
not too long before this.
And you can have that outside a theme park, but, you know, you need something.
You know what else is this a lot like with that, like brightly painted
corrugated metal this and forgive me for the local reference,
but this is the Burbank Empire Center Big Time.
Oh, yeah. Good functional place because they have a target and things.
You need an REI and the sharkies, which I'm fine with, but ugly to look at
and kind of gaudy off the five freeway.
It's like at the most like like that's just a junkie.
That's the most like kind of outlet mall.
All right. Let's put up five tiny planes and that's enough. Right.
And then this like real bright, like metal painted.
Yeah, I don't like it.
The only thing that caught me off after this Empire Center talk,
the only thing I kind of like about the Empire Center is the light.
Some decent lighting at night.
Does it really? I'm rarely there at night, so I might not know this.
Jason, you know what I'm talking about?
I do know what you're talking about, and I think there are touches.
They've they've painted over the the because that's where
the Howard was it Lockheed Martin or Howard Hughes's aircraft factory was?
So there's little touches of like this of like air airplane,
airplane specifics, you know, the history of Burbank.
But it's also it all sun faded over the years.
It's so hard to tell.
And then they just painted everything gray.
So you can't really see anything now.
That's their DCA two point.
It's Empire Center to point out.
Yeah. If you want us to cover this entire mall, let us know.
Yes, we're fairly willing.
Who are these? This place, we go back up.
Who are those characters?
They're not that they're generic toy.
Like if you look up toy and like a visual dictionary, you see that.
Right. There's a blue deer and not Raggedy Andy, a different
red hair and not raggedy.
Oh, it's a boy.
Maybe a very generic just overalls that could be either way.
A little like red dot cheeked
top hat. No, it's a conductor bear.
I don't like any of these guys.
It is original theme park IP, I suppose, but I'm not not fond of them.
I don't want to dig deeper.
I well, if anybody knows if the engineer toys have names, please let us know.
I am interested to know.
It could say further in this article, I don't know.
And then inside is just like this is what they had to do.
They had to do the state like the classy 30s vibe on the way in
because it just like, I don't know, it's like now it's like a beautiful overture
before the film starts.
And this is like a like the fourth generation AMC
candy band where the graphics are getting actually worse with time.
And they're they're more annoying.
The little pre movie little little feature ads.
Yeah, gross, right?
Oh, and there's there's puns in here.
El there's a clock.
And when it's noon, it's not just noon, it's El Nuneo
referencing the killer storm that this palm swings for some reason.
Why swings? What's that?
Rancho choo choo manga.
This is where now we're getting into pun worlds.
This really big bear lake.
The lake looks like a bear.
I mean, that's kind of cute.
Some of these things, though,
there's a lot of cute puns everywhere in every theme park.
But it also often comes down to just what does the presentation look like?
Like if this map was subtle
and you really had to like look at it for like 15 seconds and go,
oh, there's some funny things written on here.
I don't think it's nearly as offensive as looking at this
like barely graphic designed train map
and seeing these like aggressive puns,
seeing these aggressive, like lame jokes.
Bad font. That's a stock font.
That's maybe a copperfield black.
No good.
Now, I want luxury fonts when I go to my Disney parks.
Yes, I agree.
Blue ceiling. Look at this.
I mean, this is just the ceiling here.
They just painted all of the pipes and vents and everything bright blue.
This absolutely is the Walmart in the Empire Center.
Yeah. Yeah.
Demand better out of your your Disney parks.
Mm hmm.
Now, I pulled up that website too, and it does not have one thing that I do like
from DCA 1.0, which is they made replica little miniature toys
of some of the, you know, simple attractions.
And these toys in box still go for like two hundred or a hundred dollars on eBay,
because I don't think a lot of people bought them.
I would get one of these.
I can see having a little orange stinger, the hollowed out orange ride.
Maybe I'd buy this. I don't know.
They're like a hundred bucks.
Hmm. That's not crazy.
I found one that I well, I was going to get it.
And then it said like broken does not work.
Parts may fall off.
And I was like, OK, well, if you glue it, if it's cheap and you can glue it.
I guess so. I'll see if it's still up for sale.
Yeah. You want to talk about the sun?
Not the sun wheel.
The Ferris wheel used to have a big scary sun on it, not Mickey. Right.
And that was the sun wheel.
But when you come into the park and Sunshine Plaza is the sun icon.
The creatively you've got the Sleeping Beauty's castle,
you get Spaceship Earth and you've got the sun icon.
And this was intended to be there.
Here is the big landmark.
When you go into that opening street and what is it at the end of the road for you?
It's a big tin sun.
This is where they really, really messed up bad.
Yeah, it's it's just not I would even say it's not memorable.
I like I'm sure the first five, ten times I went.
I might not have even like go, well, what was the icon you saw?
And I go, oh, I'm not sure.
Didn't do one. I think they didn't do.
And yeah, they didn't do that.
Must be. They didn't do well, isn't.
But they had the sun thing and then the wolf like the big stone.
Like they kind of had two icons. They got to split the difference.
It's not a we've been.
Yeah, it's not a wolf. Oh, it's a bear.
It's a grizzly. I had a thought I had it reversed.
I was like, and remember, Jason, it's not the thing you think it is.
Not a bear. It's a wolf.
I was like, was there a stone wolf
bear howling at the sun under it?
And I was like, maybe there was.
And I like scrambling the look, I go, oh, shit, I forgot.
There was a stone wolf that was like, I always thought it was a wolf.
I thought the squint to see the bear.
Well, yeah, we we are the grizzly river rapids episode.
We all there was some confusion about what it looks like.
Yeah, which is a price that was also supposed to be kind of their icon.
And you're not sure what it is.
Yeah, it was kind of painted worse when it opened to.
I feel like, yeah, this is a mess.
But the sun icon clearly could not have been the the the
main thing that you draw from the park.
Here's the big thing you see when you come in the park.
It doesn't work.
Also, the whole idea is that it was going to reflect the light of the sun
and make it nice and warm and glowy in this area.
Through all through Sunshine Plaza.
I don't remember any of this that but they they it was painted.
There was pointed the wrong way, like to where it wouldn't get the sun
where how it was supposed to to make it glow.
So they had to use big reflector machines
that were up on poles to hopefully bounce the sunlight off of the it.
It bounces off of that and bounces on to the sun, which it did not do.
This never worked.
So it just kind of looked flat and bad here all the time.
Yeah, I did not know that's what they were trying to do.
That didn't I see now those the things I think the things that was trying to reflect.
Yeah, no, that never read to me at all.
This thing isn't also for all the other icons of Disney parks.
This isn't even that big.
It's really small.
Yeah, at least do something big like if it was, you know,
you know what the story there is, is this this is from this is a Westcott
holdover that they were not going to do Spaceship Earth again.
They were going to do a big golden spire, and that was going to be extremely tall,
probably as tall as the Tower of Terror.
Guardians is now, but because it was going to be really bright.
And I think maybe the relationship with Anaheim was just not good at the time.
And the neighbors were like, no, no, no, we're not going to have a big pointy light.
That sounds terrible.
So they're like, all right, well, we got to do something small then,
because that was even that was going to be in Westcott
and it was going to be in California Adventure.
Like the big point, the golden point was still part of the plan.
Right. And instead it became what a lot of people called the hubcap.
It was a cool little hubcap.
Yeah, it's it's yeah, it's just
I'm trying to think like, say it was say it was the exact same design,
but it was five times the size.
I think at the very least, I think we would all be saying
if it would have been gone away by now.
Well, you know, it was kind of cool because how big it was.
I think we would have given it that praise.
Like, oh, well, you know, it was impressive that this giant sort of sun thing.
It's not aesthetically pleasing to me, but at the very least, like, wow,
it really impressed me when I'd walk in and go, wow, that is that's huge. Wow.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
Just make it big. What are you doing?
Yeah, this is all what really it's just like a really tepid, flaccid way
to start your day in the in the park.
And I will also add, because I'm seeing this in the photos of sunshine
Plaza that you also then are.
So you can turn to the left and go over to the Hollywood area.
And at that time, it said Hollywood really big at the top.
And then there were these big elephants.
And the elephants are there because you're like,
why giant elephants on top of pedestals?
Well, that, of course, is a reference to D.W.
Griffith's film, Intolerance. Yes.
What? Why? Why?
And of course, those elephants also appear at, let's all say it together.
The Hollywood and Highland Shopping Complex.
Yes. Which will open, I think.
Well, was it before this or after?
I was right around the same time.
So you're like, why are there two two things felt the need
to tribute D.W. Griffith's Intolerance?
I want to say Hollywood Pictures.
So not Disney Studio.
This is a fake back lot called Hollywood Pictures.
Hollywood Pictures back lot.
Yes. Which seems like something you would get on a T-shirt
at Hollywood and Highland for like three T-shirts for twenty dollars.
That's truly the tribute.
The tribute is gift shop at Hollywood and Highland at City Walk
on Hollywood Boulevard.
That's really the true inspiration for California Adventure.
Is that tacky tourist trap garbage?
Yeah, yeah.
I think that whole I mean, you know, Hollywood is sort of its own thing.
You could almost devote a whole episode to, but that then you just
you just keep staring down that way.
And I boy, I've always hated that fake sky backdrop
with the forced perspective where the city gets smaller and smaller,
which is weird because I really liked it in MGM Studios.
I remember thinking that was so neat as a kid.
Oh, you mean so they all like to make a street look really long.
They'll make the buildings get smaller and smaller.
And I wanted pictures in front of it.
I thought it was so cool. This one's worse.
Why is it where it's still to this day, I think, is just too
executed and too tacky of a way.
Yeah, it just stands out.
It's like almost it just stands out more.
I think I really like it's I'm trying to think the MGM one isn't so.
I don't know. This one's just in your face.
The one in California is just in your face and your brain doesn't get
tricked at all ever.
No, no, no, no.
Yeah, there's never a second where you go.
That's sky. That's real.
Like it never happens. Yeah. Yeah.
So it's just odd. It just looks odd.
You also in in this neck of the woods, this is pun central,
and it still kind of is this way.
There still is a lot of this isn't like is schmooze is still there.
Yes. Oh, yes, it is.
Exist. Yeah, okay.
Yeah. War.
War. Winners certainly.
Where do we go there? Yes.
Yeah. But there's other stuff they got rid of because I think there I think
there were like 10 times the puns.
Yeah. In this neck of the woods, if anybody has any of them.
The thing that they got a lot of trouble with was there was a sign of like
about like a casting couch joke.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
2000. What are like?
What are you doing?
I missed this 100 percent when it happened.
I found out about this today.
Philip, a couch casting agency.
It is a casting couch reference and it is on a sign that looks like a penis.
It is. Oh, yeah.
Do you guys do you remember that?
I don't know. That's intentional.
I remember that I remembered.
Oh, my God. You're right.
Yep. There's a little tip at the bottom and there's two little swirly's up at the top.
Damn. Yeah. Yes.
That is not a stretch at all, by the way.
Sometimes you see the Disney's phallic imagery and you go, well, kind of.
That one, there's no mistaking it.
That is a dick sign.
Yeah. About a casting and then this was they put this in in the era
where they owned Miramax and worked closely with Harvey Weinstein.
Yeah. There's so much stuff as you go through, like old clips of late
night talk shows and stand up monologues and stuff where people are making jokes,
stuff like that. And then if you really like analyze it, you go, hey, that's fucked up.
I don't know why we were all just like, oh, the casting couch.
Oh, we all know it exists like that was.
I might have been kind of conditioned by seeing like Oscar monologue jokes like that.
And I think as a like ignorant 15 year old, I'm like, oh, that's where the producer
wants to give you a smooch. And then you get I don't I really don't think I was aware
of like what that actually means.
And I don't know.
You know, I don't think anyone knew the truly the extent of it until.
I mean, obviously, it's it's so crazy and horrible.
But yeah, how insane that that was like cutified for so many years.
And it's not even like hidden.
I would I would actually give it like I would give like the Imagineers like credit
for like really sneaking one in if I go, oh, I see if you combine the last letters
of each word, then it forms casting.
I go, well, they really snuck it in there.
So there's no way you like you would know if you just walked by it.
Not this sign.
This sign is just casting advertising a penis.
It's wild. So crazy.
Yeah, this is kind of underratedly one of the craziest things
it's ever been in a in a park and the even if it was different words,
the very blatant penis shape.
Yeah, yeah, really. Yeah.
It should be award winners. Let's be honest.
It should be right.
If that was a penis shape, I don't think that would.
Oh, my God. I would love it.
I go, you know, the award winners, we can get a hot dog.
The sign is shaped like a giant dick.
And I'd be like, that's funny. That's good.
I like that.
Good work, Imagineers.
Is there anything else worth calling out in this neck of the woods
in terms of the puns?
Yeah. Dial M for muscle.
Ben hair.
I do. I've said this maybe three times now on the show, but
I do maintain if the place looked less tacky,
those puns would be less egregious.
This is one of the tackiest looking places it still is.
A lot of the fonts are bad. It's very dated.
I mean, you go around Tokyo, Disney Sea and Tokyo,
Disney Sea is so much subtlety in their theming and jokes and puns.
Like there are just dense paragraphs full of jokes
on the side of like the where you pick up the train to go around the park
and even in the different eateries.
Like we were finding just so much information
that was just all jokes about where we were.
But it's so subtle and it was not and it was, as you're saying, a classy font.
And really like just fully developed immersive environments.
Yeah, you'll go to Jungle Cruise in general.
You will go with grown worthy stuff. Right.
And if you.
Hey, everything is context, you know, jokes don't need to be so clever.
It just needs to be in the right context.
That's my comedy lesson.
Yeah, you're welcome, everyone.
Pretend you're in the car next to Jerry.
Yes, yes, he would.
And that's the West End.
Yes, make fun of waitresses more.
It's interesting the way this area is presented on the map.
It's like one of the attractions and ventures.
It just says Hyperion Theater, Magnificent 2000 seat theater.
That's it.
Like, what's in it?
Yeah, that's good for you guys for building a place
where you can do corporate events that no one will ever see.
Where you can make a confusingly cut out front of a stage
that Kelsey Grammer can very easily fall into.
That's right. Yeah.
It was waiting to happen.
It's not Kelsey's fault.
No, at all. No, no.
It was a very specific, specifically designed stage.
They did have the Muppets back here.
And I used to really like that kiosk outside of it
that had a ton of Muppets stuff.
And I was just kind of like swing merchant, like whatever merchandise
they want to shove in there.
Yeah. Oh, and this Christmas thing, it's so many spider bots
that nobody's fighting on. Oh, no.
Just tons of spider.
They better hope we fall in love with the spider bots when that ride opens.
Because they, I bet there's like the ninety nine cent stores
have spider bots at this point.
They made so many.
They're just selling them to any different store.
As legacy pass holders, are we gifted a complimentary spider bot?
Thirty percent off.
Thirty percent off Monday through Thursday, Monday through Thursday.
Not every day.
Parking is not included on the high end passes anymore.
It's it's a hundred dollars each time you come.
But you get a 30 percent off spider bot.
Yes. Thank you, sir.
May I have another shape and shape back the hut?
I have a general pitch for what we do here and now.
And it is this.
I think I have a plan because this episode could go for
the full amount of time that we've already done.
What if maybe the way that we section off, what if we what if there's
a an episode that is about you call it DCA 1.0 to Paradise Pier?
We leave Paradise Pier.
That's our general tribute to what Paradise Pier used to be,
because there's so many rides over there.
Yes. Yes. I think there might be enough.
So maybe that's where we that's the cutoff.
But we try to, you know, let's cover Hollywood and then let's.
I mean, what a beautiful.
What more beautiful ending than Bountiful Valley Farm?
Of course.
So so for this episode, we will try to conquer.
Let me if I have this correct.
Not Paradise Pier, Golden State.
I suppose. Well, is Golden State where what's Golden State?
OK, Golden State is one of four districts.
That's how the Anaheim Tourism Board described it in the early days.
It's not lands, it's districts.
But it's a district, but it's got six different areas.
What's the difference between a district and an area?
So Bountiful Valley Farms,
Pacific Wharf, Golden Vine Winery, Condor Flats,
the Bay Area and Grizzly Peak Recreation Area.
So that's a lot to explain to someone, I feel like.
I agree. Yeah, very complicated.
And a lot of those things you just described are like, you know, 20 feet wide.
Those aren't that's not big enough to be an area.
Yeah. So yes. All right.
So what are we doing?
So, yeah, I don't know where we're going now.
We're as confused as if we're looking on an original map.
I don't know what's going on.
I think.
Wait, is this is this behind the scenes or is this?
No, I think this is on.
Oh, we're on the air. We're on the air.
We're live. We're live.
This is live. Oh, no. Yeah.
I think I'm getting in a Bountiful Valley Farms tractor and getting the F out of here.
I mean, maybe it's that maybe because there's so like so many of the puns remain,
I feel like in in the you know, I think we have to leave Route 66 out,
which is a shame because that's where so much the rust with the SS
rust worthy burger invasion.
But that's that's good.
You know, those are good.
We need to lead you into the next episode.
Are we done or are we do have more?
I'm good. No, no, no. I think we do Bountiful Valley.
Oh, OK.
Bountiful Valley Farm. And then we're done. Got it.
I think so.
How long have we been going?
I think I'm going to collapse if we don't.
Yeah, yeah, I'm good with that. OK.
I'm good to be there. I don't care.
Well, we'll do DCA one point
oh dot two like a software update.
Yes, yes.
Like a software update that a great California visionary like Steve Jobs
would give you covering much of Golden State and Paradise Pier.
But yeah, that's a good way to do it.
OK, OK. Good.
And so but yeah, let's talk about Bountiful Valley Farm.
Oh, yeah, we got if you go if you go past
the sun item.
This is the first thing you see on your left is Bountiful Valley Farm.
And now this yeah, and this really tripped me out when I was watching the
in general, very difficult to watch opening special with Richard
Kind and Barry Bostwick right around the same stretch of time.
I for the first time, embarrassingly, had not seen before this
a serious man, the very good. Oh, yeah.
Like one of my favorites. Yes.
Really, really liked it. Yeah.
And then and so going the whiplash of wow, Richard Kind is wonderful in this.
And then he's also in like a bright yellow Hawaiian shirt
bumbling around with Barry Bostwick and convincing us that the amount of rides
is fine and the Bountiful Valley Farm is good enough to be an area.
But I think of all the things
like some things are burning in my memory.
Of course, I know there was a big orange.
Of course, I knew there was a big, scary sun face.
But when they are walking through this farm zone and I'm like,
oh, my God, no, Bugsland.
I did not like because then there was kind of an in-between.
There was there was some farm and then Bugsland.
But oh, my God, when there was no Bugsland, what was even happening?
What was this park? Yeah, I thought Bugsland was opening day.
I if you would have if you would have asked me like five days ago,
I would have said, oh, yeah, Bugsland open opening day. Right.
But no, like a long time ago.
And it felt like still for being an addition,
chintzy enough that they had to take it out eventually.
Like it felt like temp or expendable or something.
This is like as good as like all the stuff in here is like as good as like
this place, Gobert's Pumpkin Farm that I used to go to as a child.
And that's a good point, because I was going to say as a child,
I love trucks and tractors and trail like I loved all that stuff.
So getting to climb on one of those again, the instinct is correct.
Children like climbing on construction. Right. Sure. Yeah. Yeah.
But it's it's not enough. It's just not enough. What is it?
Yeah. What is it doing here? Why was it here before?
And they built around it like that's the way it feels to me
when I look at these pictures like there was a farm.
They bought up all the land.
But there was just this one miniature farm where they like wouldn't really.
So like you have to still let us raise some crops.
That's the only way we're going to kind of give you the rest of this.
Like living with the land in Epcot, there's crops, but it's, you know,
we're in a facility of some kind and there's windows and there's, you know,
experiments going on and you're in a boat. It's themed.
This is truly like they built an OK theme park around a little plot of land
where they're growing lemons.
Yeah. What are the crops?
Let's I see some some Valencia oranges.
Those look nice. Some nice, beautiful flowers.
There is they don't there are no cattle there, but there's some plastic
cows. Maybe be helpful to just maybe we'll all screen share this yesterlain
page. You know, it's extremely it's a
state fair display and you would love to see it there, but in a theme park.
What do you mean? It's so strange.
Yeah. And it's like they had, you know, when they had the pettings,
they have a petting zoo at this point in Disneyland.
They have a petting zoo.
They have real animals in the back of Disneyland.
So like you come over here and you go, oh, there's some shitty plastic cows.
There's two shitty plastic cows. I just saw a goat. I just saw.
I saw a horse. I just saw what's the they would.
They have a cow as well. Or what was the big?
Sometimes there'd be a cow.
Yeah. I'll lift my hand once. Yeah.
A cow like Jason's hand.
You can't get that over here with these plastic cows.
But what you can get is the Bountiful Valley Farmers Market.
And you know what they have?
Healthy wraps, the healthiest food of the 1990s.
Wraps. Yeah.
We get convinced on wraps.
And why did they why did everybody pretend they were OK to eat,
that they had any taste?
I haven't had a wrap in so long, and it makes me feel great.
Yeah, I I liked like buffalo chicken wraps if they were freshly made,
because if you wrap a wrap up and put it in like an airport
refrigerated cooler thing, nothing congeals faster than a wrap.
That's it. It's like a it's a mayonnaise trap.
It like it's a way to like hide it and condense it.
So then once you bite into that reserve, that spoiled reserve, everything,
everything switches texture like 10.
Everything's entropy is reverse.
It's just like, oh, no, it's transforming.
No, I feel like this is another one of the things where I've talked about
a vitamin water trick to me, like a number of things trick to me.
And like wraps, I go to Togo's and get like what Jason said,
some buffalo chicken wrap and I go, this is healthier.
I'm eating pretty healthier.
If you really looked, it was like the wrap was like 70 less calories
than the bread.
Yeah, exactly. So fine.
Less carbs.
We were all tricked by whole wheat.
They're right. Oh, I never went all in.
I did. I was wheat for years.
You did. I was.
You gave me for buying white bread and sourdough bread.
I'm so sorry. I was wrong.
Wheat is bad. I didn't know.
It was like that was something I would get wheat
and I would get a little spring in my step and be like, well, healthy boy.
Look what you did today.
And they're just shoving molasses or corn syrup in there to make it like.
Monsanto is killing us slowly with their wheat.
Got it. Unbelievable.
We all know we look we all watched Super Size Me 2, Holy Chicken.
Of course we know what the industry is doing.
A DCA exclusive.
It could have been that could have been a theme for film. Yes.
But, you know, they don't forsake that you can go, as you said,
you go get on a tractor.
They did work with they got Caterpillar
tractors involved in.
You learn about in signs about
tractor makers, Benjamin Holt and Daniel Best.
Mommy, I learned about Daniel Best today.
I don't can you get on the track now?
I'm questioning this.
I don't see any pictures of kids in a tractor.
Yeah, I swear you could at least get in the cab, but maybe.
I'm misremembering or maybe that was all they would let me do.
Because I'm a 20 year old college student.
You're young enough. We'll let you do it. Yeah.
No, no, no. Wait, wait. Climb into the cab. OK. Yeah.
Yeah. Like Trump in the big, big.
You know, lots of unhappy memories, but, you know, it's nice to think about
the trend, the truck part.
The one nice day.
Boundable Valley, it was the home of San Andreas Shakes.
And that is another thing.
I think it is sometimes hard in theme parks, not at this one,
because a Ghirardelli, you can get them.
But every now and then I'm like, I want a milkshake.
And it's not as easy to like dig one up as you think.
And if you. Yeah. Yeah.
Because you can eat, you can just drink it, drink it and walk.
But I think I was there in like 2015 or 2016.
And I was like, is San Andreas Shakes still around?
And I'm like, no, what are you talking about?
Like, what is the mountain now?
I've had the same.
I too recently have thought those were there.
And you're right. They were good.
And I looked it up and it is date was like a topping.
OK. You know, of course, it's the oh, you know what?
It's in its Sam Andreas because it's a guy or at least the sign says.
Yeah. So we're even deeper into pun.
The pun extends deeper than we thought.
And they're called shakers.
And then there's.
Wait, this is Tim Blore talk.
Oh, well, Tim Blore, that was their blizzard.
That was their version of a blizzard.
Not tremble or Tim Blore.
I don't quite understand that pun.
I think it's wordplay and it's just missing the mark.
Yeah, I can't even just misspell it.
That would be funny if they misspelled it.
I got to give it a guy, Selga, in his like recap.
I think he was the one who posted like the very old map on touring plans
a blog referred to this area as the worst land Disney has ever done.
I mean, yeah, but now I'm worried somebody out there is going to be like,
wait, I love Bountiful Valley Farm.
I like watching the crops grow out there.
You I'm so like shy to be insulting to crops at this point that I.
Oh, yeah. I don't want to step in it again.
Well, let's see.
If you're a big stand for this part of the park, please let us know.
And you know what?
Don't tag our show account, tag Scott's Twitter account.
We don't need to see it.
Just send it to Scott.
Look, I became I'm no longer Scott Gardner anyway.
I'm Mr. Viral Questions.
My account is devoted to asking the questions
that the most burning questions that go the most viral.
So I can't even respond.
That's not what my account does anymore.
OK, so you won't get nothing out of me.
I'm not afraid of you.
I'm Mr. Viral Questions now.
OK. So, yeah, just I'll
DM me, I'll send you Scott's physical address.
Shit. No, no, fine.
All right. Do whatever you got to do.
Mike's going to do it, I swear.
We'll do it. Yeah.
I yeah, this is bad.
You know, and then they kind of tied it into Bugsland and made it
like they put Heimlich run around.
And then there's kind of a slow gradient into Bugsland.
And that was better, but still weird.
I now I want to I didn't look at the yesterlain page for Santa Rosa
seed and supply.
This is did you look into this before?
Do we have to discover Santa Rosa?
I knew you get like seeds and stuff, right?
You could buy seeds in the theme park.
I think so. I think you can still get seeds at a grizzly peak at that.
Can you still buy seeds?
I think that like one one of their displays, like a couple of years ago or so,
when they were leaning into the national park motif.
No, I will give them credit.
Buying seeds in the park is cool, I think.
That's the only one of those 1955.
Yeah. Yeah.
Something you shouldn't need to buy at a park or like there's no reason for it.
I like it when they sell it in a park and in only maybe one or two areas,
especially if it's high, like specialized to one theme from theme gift shop.
See, I can always use seeds.
I've mostly just been planting those seeds that showed up in an Amazon box
a couple of times and I just played at those all over California.
Wait, what is that?
Oh, that was the there was an oddly enough news story a while back,
I think last year that like people who had placed Amazon orders,
it was like some sort of drop shipping bullshit mix up.
We're just getting like there would be a bag of seeds in with their like
Oh, yeah.
What are the seeds?
Stay away from the seeds.
God, that was feels like forever ago.
Yeah. And the FDA was or whoever regulates that was just like,
do not plant the seeds, please.
Did I?
We really were too late.
But have I told the Neil Young story about the concert with the seeds before?
I feel you might have.
I'm worried. It sounds familiar.
But maybe it was it on air or other.
I can't remember. Real quick.
I saw Neil Young. He played at the forum.
The first four songs he plays like after the gold rush, Old Man.
He sounds fantastic.
These songs are like you're getting chills are so good.
And then all of a sudden, after four songs, he has people in hazmat suits
come out and like spray down the stage.
And then it's like he brings out Willie Nelson's sons who he was playing with.
And they're like great players and they're playing new stuff.
And then Neil hands out like seeds to the audience
because he's trying to make an environmental message.
And the rest of the show had like a theme.
And you were like, man, I appreciate what you're doing, Neil.
But God, this is lame.
We are the seed man.
Yeah. It's like the first four.
All bow to the seed man.
Like just Neil on the piano after the gold rush, which is one of my favorite songs
ever. And it's like, oh, this is incredible.
And then it's like a themed experience about seeds.
It's like women with like baskets handing out seeds like, you know,
there's a law against seeds now and we're trying to circumvent.
And I'm like, this is great, Neil.
Give me a pamphlet. I'll look into it and I support what you're doing.
But back to the good stuff.
And the women for like grabbed you by the hand, forced your hand open,
shoved the seeds in your hand, made you hold them.
Yeah. And they checked on the way out to make sure you didn't throw them away.
They kept calling and saying, did you plant them?
Checking. Hey, it's Neil's the seed girl.
This is Cynthia from the Seed Girls.
Just if you had a chance to plant those seeds yet, Neil was asking about you
specifically. Oh, wait. Oh, Neil, you want to talk to him?
Yeah. Did you plant the seeds?
I got to sing my Starbucks song and I needed I was going to Skype you in,
see how the seeds were coming.
Do you want to buy a po? Do you want to buy a Pono?
Don't make me write a mean song about you like George W.
Bush. All right. I'll say let's impeach Mike Carlson.
OK, Neil, I plan it on my swear.
Planted a photographic proof, please.
Have you been to DCA?
Have you been to California Adventure?
It's a good theme park.
I don't like that sound.
What they're going to they're going to add a Cars Land.
I like the taking out the seeds, taking out the seeds.
Crest commercialism. I was fine with it before, but
you would have been OK if Cars Land was more like electric cars, I think.
Yeah. Oh, sure. Yeah.
Aren't they? Well, I guess you're right.
The cars in the Cars Land, they have like hearts and lungs, right?
Cars in the movie. Oh, yeah. They're just alive.
Yeah. So yeah, he's fine with cars.
Yeah. Take the joke back. Anyway, what would happen to all this?
Is this just like the entrance of Cars Land now?
What where are we geographically when we're at Santa Rosa seed and supply?
I think we're looking at Cars Land and soon to be like Marvel.
I think that's the real sort of in the in between.
Oh, and you know what?
Before we wrap up the thing we haven't said, you know, part of
apparently the lore and I was trying to find a quote on this.
And maybe I'll try to have something for part two for one point to when we do it.
Supposedly the biggest fan of Bountiful Valley Farm was not a visitor,
but Michael Eisner, I was trying to buy that love.
I loved the heart and soul.
I feel like he described it that like he was all in on Bountiful Valley Farm.
Wow. Wow.
There was some other quote where he said, like, all right,
you know, everything I said about the Aspen retreat, like,
what do we want to represent about California?
Well, you know, there's the hot there's Hollywood and there's,
you know, nature and tourism and there's industry.
There's the workplace.
I think he said the workplace that sucks workplace.
Yeah, it sucks.
I don't want any workplace to be represented.
And what about like, workplaces are gone.
Nobody has workplaces anymore now.
I don't want us to go to a theme park and see.
Maybe I do miss them.
Well, I'll just go walk around an office.
What about like if they represented like a Dunder Mifflin
somewhere in California, venture?
Oh, of course.
The ultimate workplace.
Well, that's going to have to be universal, though.
That's all right. You're right.
They have it back on Peacock and.
Yeah, the that seems like a will.
Like they, you know, if they did like a store that was exactly
the layout of the office office, I couldn't aid on that.
That's something.
I think they should do a superstar limo style office, right?
I mean, that's what we were getting at on the Monsters Inc.
Right. But I think that universal at this point, it's probably
it's like the most popular show on all the streaming services.
So like, let's you got they got to do something with it.
They got to expand.
That's what she said.
Yeah, yeah, for sure.
Uh, or it's just like Office Live and they have they recast the characters
and you get to watch like a little play, a little office play every every day.
Well, Office, Office, the musical.
OK, the way that, you know, like finding Nemo, the musical where there wasn't
it wasn't a musical before, but why not do it now?
And then they can get like during Halloween time, they can get rowdy.
They can get bawdy.
Like Slaughter World.
Yeah, like Slaughter World. Yeah.
But like it's and it's called the off fix with three X's at the end.
Yeah, that's good.
How have we not been we done done this show now for three years.
We haven't been hired yet. It's unbelievable.
I know great ideas left and right.
This was just a con.
This whole thing was just a con to get hired in one of these companies
and it hasn't worked.
Unbelievable. It's time to it's time to admit.
What we're doing.
This is all it's been about.
So, yeah, if you work at Universal Studios, just let us just let us.
You've been listening to all of them.
We know you're looking for pun writers.
We know puns are coming back around 20 years later.
What do you want?
Thing I did at the beginning, there were so many puns.
Yeah. What else do we have to do?
Cry on the air if you want.
We'll beg. Cry.
And it's OK to cry.
As Judge Gad said nearly a year ago, it's OK to cry.
Yeah. Oh, that actually might make me cry if I examine that statement.
That it was almost. Oh, yeah.
Yeah. No kidding. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep.
Woof. Anyway, my therapist, my therapist says it's OK.
OK, he emphasized it's OK to cry.
He's like, sometimes if you need to prime yourself, he's like,
if you need to like watch Rocky or something, because you know, it'll make you cry.
And like, well, guess now I'm thinking,
maybe I just need to watch Gad.
You didn't it didn't make you cry when it was only a day old.
But once it's a year old, imagine no possessions.
That's we're going to get to so many year anniversaries.
Remember?
Then there was the other different one where Aaron Paul was yelling, boy,
what a great work is it a year already?
Happy birthday.
They've done enough.
They've done enough celebrity boxings.
They don't remember that's been a year.
So who wait?
Who has done celebrity?
The Paul brothers.
They just know Aaron Paul from from.
Oh, yeah. No, Aaron Paul.
No, no, no.
Not Logan Paul and not what's the brother?
Jake, I would certainly.
Jake, that's what I'm OK.
I would buy that Aaron Paul has a brother and that they're into boxing together.
That's not such a stretch.
Yeah, that's that's not where it would be funny if it was suddenly revealed
that Aaron Paul is the third after Jake and Logan.
I was like, I was.
Yeah, I was like, did Aaron Paul have like a celebrity
boxing match against like the bagel boss or something?
They fight it like it's a right.
It was well right before the pandemic.
So like, I kind of forget a lot of stuff.
So, yeah. OK.
We're announcing a new enterprise boxing bitch.
A whole new way to fight.
Universal involved in the fighting yourself.
Universal, hire us so we can we can book celebrity boxing matches at the park.
Yeah, get us.
We just need the three of us and Aaron Paul and we will bring boxing
bitch to your park.
We have access.
You know, the celebrities we've had.
Do you want Evan Susser to box?
Nick Weigar at Universal?
Of course you do.
We can make that happen for you.
So hire us, please.
Or do you want Evan Susser to fight the bagel boss?
We can make that happen.
We should do it. We can book.
You know him. He did something with the minions once.
Do you want someone who did something with the minions once to box Aaron Paul?
That's right. That's what we're proposing.
I don't know. I'm so so much.
Whereas again, we're lost.
We're lost in the middle of confusing the middle.
DCA. And what we've determined is that we have to step down
like DCA, stop and talk about it and do a refurbish and we'll come back.
We'll have to figure out the plan.
We'll have to figure out the timing on this.
Yeah, but yeah, do it.
It will be sooner in a year.
I don't know. Yes.
Good question. Because we've got more.
There's more DCA coming to the second gate.
There's more. But do we do this?
Well, I guess that's the off air conversation.
Either way, there's more off air, I think. Yeah.
Yeah, because this is this is DCA 20 years.
We got to celebrate it in a big way.
It's got to we got to end.
And it's the second gate.
We have to celebrate the second gate on the second gate.
So there's more coming.
So don't worry about that. Right.
For now, you survived.
I can't believe we even thought we would get further than this.
But you survived part one.
You survived DCA one point.
Oh, point one. Oh, oh, oh.
Actually, yeah, one point.
Oh, point one would be the first update.
I think it well.
But then you want to get two in the title when we do it.
Yeah. For cleanliness sake, we'll call it the next installment.
One point, oh point two.
Yes, it's extremely cleanly.
The this way, this was great.
So we're going to figure it out.
It's a big week.
We will there will be more DCA content over on the second gate.
And there's always great stuff happening over there,
which hopefully, as you know, is Patreon.com
slash podcast, the ride and follow us on all the other social media.
We'll we'll be posting great photos of I mean, we got to post all our favorites.
We for sure have to show some of that parade.
Oh, my God. The chow main man and the Golden Gate Bridge boys.
That was that's a hell of a parade.
I love Eureka. Yeah.
Well, yeah, we'll we'll get deep into Eureka.
Also, right on our way out, I'll drop the new story that Evermore Park
is suing Taylor Swift for naming her album Evermore.
Hell yes. Let's go.
That's what you teased. Whoa.
You told us he had a good one.
A good topical. Oh, man.
They got to pay those contractors somehow.
Evermore. Yeah.
No one's ever used Evermore before Evermore Park.
Good. Nice. Nice try, I think.
Yeah. Yeah.
What are you going to try to sue Edgar Allen Poe now?
Yeah. Nevermore is too close.
Poe had a Poe had a time machine is what it alleged.
They allege went into the future.
So anybody would come on.
He had a steampunk time machine.
Of course he did. He stole our name.
So yeah.
So anyway, let's see if Taylor can get out of this one.
I have not listened to Evermore nearly as much as Folklore,
and Folklore is fantastic, I will say.
But Evermore is good.
OK, yeah. Well, so check those out.
Check out those albums streaming.
Plug Taylor Swift, help her out during this lawsuit from the Evermore theme park.
It's going to be a tough time for her, clearly.
And we will come back.
You will hear more from us and we'll get to all your...
We'll get to Burger Invasion.
We'll get to Orange Stinger.
We'll get to Pizza Um, Mau Mau.
You're going to hear it all.
That's right.
Yeah. Mela-bur-ito.
If that doesn't entice you.
So hold on tight.
Happy birthday, California Adventure.
And we'll talk to you all soon.
ForeverDog News by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at ForeverDogTeam and liking our page on Facebook.