Five, four, three, two, one.
Three, two, fire one.
On Podcast The Ride, the Second Gate Casino Implosions!
Exclamation point, this should be a dynamic episode,
a dynamite episode, if you will,
and we've got round the clock coverage
from going from all around the Valley Burbank area.
I'm Scott Gardner, and joined by,
I mean, everybody's a sudden implosion expert, I think,
in preparation for this.
So yeah, sure, implosion expert Mike Carlson.
Yes, I am here.
I'd also like to say I am an emotional implosion expert.
Sometimes my self-confidence can just be destroyed
within a matter of moments.
It depends, you know, I can def-
I am self-defeating as well.
So I can analyze from a different,
a variety of ways is what I'm saying.
And potentially an expert in all the kinds of implosions
we're talking about and more, Jason Sheridan.
Just keep tamping it down, like gunpowder
and explosive too, you know,
for a beautiful fireworks display.
That's right.
What an exciting episode today.
I was saying before the show,
just a wonderful parade of scum bags
and beautiful human, human just, yeah, implosions,
explosions, fireworks, fireballs.
People who should be caught in implosion,
who like should be in the building as it is imploded,
if there was any justice.
Yeah.
If you were, yes, if you were Judge Dredd,
you would say, you would sentence them
to be imploded in their own building.
In their own building,
if you were doing ironic sentencing, yeah.
Yeah.
It's implosions, it's casino implosions mainly
is the way we're tying it together.
You know, buildings implode all the time.
This happens, this is a fact of life.
It's always impressive.
It's always a big show of the might of man.
So they're never not impressive,
but why do it on this theme park podcast?
Well, I think mainly because in the 90s and 2000s,
Las Vegas began this trend of imploding buildings,
not just quietly in the middle of the night,
but in a big, stupid theme parky way
with a huge spectacle and fireworks and lasers
and projections on buildings sometimes
and music and celebrities and actors
and maybe a movie being filmed is part of it.
It's just, I'm not even sure how many of these
there have been all told, but you know,
a handful, like at least 10 or so.
And some of the details and culture surrounding these things
are just so silly and so fun.
And it is such a like a satisfying story
line of like New Vegas, theme park Vegas,
killing old Vegas, killing mafia Vegas,
like in giant, giant explosions, like giant fireballs.
And then eventually in a sadder turn of events,
theme park Vegas just kind of collapses in on itself.
In slow motion, yes.
In not an exciting way.
Yes, not in an exciting way at all
because none of these attractions,
which there is so many wonderful theme parky Vegas
sort of stuff, most of which isn't around anymore,
but they were not in it for the long haul.
They were not in it for like,
you have to give this 10 years to pick up some steam.
They were like, as soon as it opened,
some of that stuff was just like, oh, we're done with you.
Yeah, there is a chance.
I mean, we've talked about this on the show before.
They were going to build a replica, an accurate,
Star Trek Starship Enterprise in Vegas as a hotel casino.
There's a chance they would have imploded it by now
that there would have been on TV and X enterprise exploding
because it was unprofitable.
If they made it either, okay, you could do it in universe
and like a Klingon ship blows it up
or just like a different pop culture IP entirely.
I don't know, like the blue man group bangs a drum
and then the enterprise goes down.
They've blown up the enterprise a few times in the movies.
They're different enterprises.
They enterprise the original, then the enterprise A,
and it goes through whatever it is at this point.
But Kirk blows up the ship at the end of Star Trek III,
which he's battling, forgive me, I think Klingons.
So you could have William Shatner come back to the hotel
and just lazily run through the scenes
where he starts like the self-destruct on the ship.
And then like you see William Shatner have to like run away
from the hotel before it falls and collapses in on itself.
That sounds so cool.
If only Star Trek III live broadcast live on TV.
Oh man.
I mean, nothing that silly happened, I guess,
but there's some pretty silly stuff.
Oh yeah.
Actors involved, movies involved,
and maybe the thing to say at the top,
and we'll kind of culminate in this
and revisit this at the end,
but this is something that's been on our list of stuff
to talk about for a while,
but it's been made newly relevant because this very week,
I think a week ago as this is coming out,
there was a big implosion of a Trump property in Atlantic City,
Trump Plaza, which has been decaying for,
I mean, since it was built basically,
but it's been completely unoccupied for I think five years
and was considered an eyesore and debris
was hurting people and businesses.
So they blew up a Trump building this week if you didn't see it.
And so we were like, okay,
we can't do implosions until that happens so we can,
you know, see what a 2021 implosion looks like.
Yes.
And the answer is less good than others.
But surprisingly beautiful.
Like very like, oh, a little elegant almost.
Just like...
Well, there is something interesting and, I don't know,
beautiful, artistic about a nice implosion.
Yeah.
If we're really judging them aesthetically,
if we're really trying to judge, like put on our theme park hats
as far as what an experience is like and what it makes us feel,
I do agree.
There is, you could find something nice in any implosion.
I will agree with you there.
It was also nice at the Sheridan household to like see Atlantic City
and the big, in the news, you know,
there are a lot of Sheridan ties back to the city.
And just growing up,
growing up, spending time down the shore,
having relatives like right outside the city.
As a young boy, I ended up with a lot of detritus from these casinos.
Like the big cups, if you remember slot machines
when they used to spit out tokens, there'd be big plastic cups everywhere.
Oh, right.
And those were fun, free marketing if you just took them out with you.
But at the beach, they were great for building sandcastles.
So I feel like I had those,
I had a lot of dirty, like one cent slot machine tokens.
And then we always had like dead decks of cards.
If you know a dead deck or a canceled deck,
it has a hole punched in the middle of it.
If you've ever seen that.
Casinos usually give those away or sell them for free in the gift shop
or give them away for free.
Right. So do you think maybe,
obviously it didn't happen here,
but do you think because like if any of these implosions happen in the future
around where you grew up,
you should be the one to push down on that TNT box on the classic Wile E. Coyote implosion?
Like that would be an honor to do,
but also it feels like, you know,
it's a personal relationship you have with these places.
Well, sure. And that we'll get to that because there is a Trump Plaza specific
about pushing the button that was like very exciting and then kind of,
you know, kind of not as exciting.
Brought into realistic terms.
Yeah.
I don't want to get us completely off tangent here,
but if there is a building that you guys feel you are the most like,
what's the building in your life you feel like you have the most ownership over
that you feel like it would be best if I was the one to blow it up?
That's a tough question because I would hate,
it would have to be like there is no other choice but to blow this up.
And that's the scenario. That's the hypothetical, I think.
Because I flash to two, the Burbank Holiday Inn,
which could be a candidate for all of this potentially.
And then the Weston Bonaventure,
which I'm looking at a mug of,
which is the like future pod hotel in downtown LA.
But geez, I would feel it would wreck me legitimately to see it come down.
I don't know if I could.
It's almost like it has to be one that's more of a novelty, right?
Like, yeah, it's fine.
I don't know if I could blow up a building I love.
Interesting.
I mean, I think I consider it's like sort of an oldie-eller situation,
you know, where you would, it should be you to do it.
I would say, and they didn't actually blow this building up,
but the Toys R Us on Gulf Road in Chambers, Illinois,
I do believe if they were going to implode it,
I should be the one to hit the TNT box.
If they do, I mean, it's been replaced at this point,
so it's not going to happen, but I'll blow up whatever's there.
Yeah.
I'm willing to do it.
Jason, do you have one?
Well, I think it already got blown up
and was supposed to be blown up in a grander fashion,
but I was going to say the Granite Run Mall in Media, Pennsylvania,
which was my childhood mall,
and slowly, you know, as malls started to fall on tough times,
a lot of the stores closed,
and it is still like there's a plan to build a more Americana thing.
I think they kept a couple of the department stores,
and then in between they sort of built up a more shopping center,
put a Chipotle or a World Home Goods or a World Market sort of thing,
but it does not look like the classic indoor fountain mall anymore,
but that was supposed to be blown up by one Mr. Kevin Smith in his mall.
Oh, interesting.
Mall Rats sequel slash thing,
and then the Exton Mall, which is still an operating mall in Pennsylvania,
was where they were going to shoot.
They were like, okay, well, we're not going to be able to do it in time,
so they have to bulldoze the Granite Run Mall.
And the Exton Mall has some empty wings,
and they were going to shoot there, and they weren't going to blow that up,
but I have less affection for that one.
So probably the Granite Run Mall I would have liked to have.
Interesting.
I mean, I was going to say, let's throw it out to the listeners,
but I don't know that we want on our Twitter,
which building do you want to blow up?
I think maybe that's out of context, that might seem odd.
It's an edgy time.
Yeah.
Well, you're the edge.
You're the edge lord.
Oh, hey, but it's the edge lord.
I can activate every now suddenly everybody's an edge lord.
Yeah.
You get what you fucking deserve.
You know, that is such a funny one.
Words have lost so much of their meaning on the internet,
and that's such a silly one to re-click.
It's just like, it doesn't mean anything anymore.
So yeah, Scott the edge lord is so funny.
Yeah, I've been loving it.
I've been basking in it now that this new identity is out.
I'm thrilled.
Let's talk about these actual things.
I mean, we could go in chronological order,
but I feel like we almost have to build to the one that started at all,
which is kind of the craziest one.
So maybe we save it, and we don't even have to do so chronologically.
You know, we could jump around, but there's, you know,
yeah, like Jason said, in the nineties, it was a real turnover in Las Vegas.
We're going from mob run Vegas to a new nineties era of scumbag.
Yes.
Which in many cases is Steve Wynn.
I feel like a number of these are, end up being Steve Wynn properties,
and he'll factor into the episode.
Yeah. And again, I cannot stress so many of these men.
It's like the league.
It's like Kevin Spacey assembled the League of Extraordinary Gentlemen.
It's like so sleazy.
Yeah.
Every owner has had a feud with Girls Gone Wild mogul Joe Francis.
I'm assuming.
Yeah.
They despise the labor unions that keep their casinos running.
Most of them have sexual misconduct allegations.
One that is only kind of tangentially related, funneled 500 million over 10 years into the Republican Party.
That's the 2010 to 2020 Republican Party.
So super villain level.
Yeah.
That's the worst thing to funnel money into. Sure.
Yeah. And then one was the former president of the United States.
And we all saw how that went.
He had to have had a tussle with Joe Francis at some point.
We have to look into that.
There had to have been like some angry phone call on some radio show in the 90s.
The girls are good.
The girls don't even go wild.
I don't know what this tape is.
He's calling them wild.
They got to take the word off.
I'm buying the word wild so they can't use it anymore.
They lost the right.
A tape.
I mean, Trump is such a scumbag.
I'm surprised he didn't market his own tape where women that were drunk and 18 took off their shirts.
That feels right, doesn't it?
That feels like a market he would have gotten into maybe at a certain point.
Yeah.
Yeah. Unless, well, he doesn't drink though.
Maybe that's where he draws the line.
You're right. That's a good point.
He's offended on that level.
Like, yeah, underage boobs, no problem.
But yeah.
Yeah.
There's one that is maybe one of my favorites that I think was like the second big one.
And I don't, Jason, you can correct me.
I don't see the scumbagginess in this, but I might be missing one.
I'm not sure.
But so, yeah, we start blowing stuff up.
And I think 93 is the first one, which we'll come back to.
1995 is a really cool one.
They blew up a hotel called The Landmark.
And this was this.
Now, if you watch a compilation, and you should, I mean, we'll recommend a lot of videos in this episode.
But if you watch a compilation of Vegas implosions, this is the one that looks like a mini space needle.
It's kind of a 60s sci-fi.
So I love the build.
This is certainly one that I would love to blow up.
But yeah, it's sort of like I saw it described as having a Jetsons vibe.
And I like any building like that where it's narrow and then the big thing up at the top.
And I forget what's here now.
I think it's just a parking lot for the convention center.
This one wasn't replaced by anything too cool.
I guess you got one scumbag.
I think this was a Howard Hughes property.
It's weird to lump him.
I mean, you'd call him that, but he's a different.
He's more fascinating.
Too fascinating to call him a scumbag, I guess.
Yeah, I don't think you can.
I think he's too complicated.
He's not like an Iken or a Wynn or a Trump or an Adelson.
I don't know.
I guess we'll get to that.
Oh, you will.
You will.
This landmark, this might be my favorite, honestly.
Yeah.
I think it is the actual implosion.
I think it is my favorite because they're all done in different ways.
It really depends on the architecture of the building.
Most of these are done by a company called Controlled Demolition, and they're true geniuses.
I mean, the one that just to the Trump one was done by the same company that did these 90s ones.
And in all cases, just knowing the pressure points and being able to make these things happen in just a matter of seconds.
And often, as we said, the shape can be very beautiful.
But this one, I think, is really cool because it splits down the middle.
It's such a strange, striking...
I don't know what made them determine that it had to be done that way, but there's this odd...
It takes longer than other ones, I feel like, where it is up in the air for a while, and one side goes down,
and the other one's going slower, and then finally it all implodes in on itself.
Was that an accident?
Maybe.
It does look a little wonky, right?
It's not symmetrical.
The timing is off.
Yeah.
So I don't know.
I'm not actually sure.
This is Mars Attacks, right?
This is the Mars Attacks one, which I think is one of the coolest things.
So there's a number of implosions that happened in real life, ended up in movies.
And I'm sure things have been used as like stock footage, but this one's so recognizable, the 60s sci-fi vibe,
which is the vibe of Mars Attacks.
And it was certainly not an accident.
Let's just go film anything that's imploding.
Tim Burton loved this building.
He was really obsessed with this hotel, stayed in it several times.
When he heard they were tearing it down, he was really upset.
And there's quotes from him saying, like, there's got to be a way we can restore these things
and not just tear them to the ground, because this is like architecture history.
This is an icon to me.
But if they're going to do something with it, I want it to be in my movie.
Right.
Yeah.
And yes, it's perfect for the movie.
Did Tim pay off some of the explosive guys and be like, make it look a little cooler than the average one?
Possibly.
I mean, one thing that did happen for sure that I think is cool,
I love that the city has to coordinate with the old owner and the new owner or whoever it is.
There's so much involved.
And the demolition company, there's so much logistics involved.
In this case, Tim Burton is dictating terms of it a little bit, and they pushed it.
They made it happen later in the day so that it could happen kind of at magic hour.
He was trying to make it happen at sunset.
And it's like even the like disaffected, like the not filmy news camera version of it looks amazing.
There's this purple desert hue.
I think this is the most beautiful implosion easily.
Yeah, I completely agree.
And it's the coolest building of all the buildings.
The smoke is good.
I mean, if we're judging the like as far as like the smoke looks cool, I don't know.
I totally agree.
Yeah, it like runs off in a fun way.
If you watch it in the in sequence in Mars Attacks, which I really love in general, Mars Attacks is so great.
It's like Jack Nicholson.
It's his hotel.
It's the second character he plays, the crazier character.
And he's up in whatever like lounges up in the top of the thing.
And they like they made all this other stuff happen, like a big globe dislodges and falls out and they added that and CG.
But yeah, like a UFO blows it up from the center, fires lasers at it, and then they send people running after like they involve it in the scene really organically and wonderfully.
And I think they account for the weird split in half.
I think they have the aliens fire a second round because there was the weird lag.
Right.
That works.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It just ties into the narrative.
Great.
You know, one thing that I think is interesting to me about 90s Vegas is the transitional phase.
Like even the first time I went to Vegas and like the mid 2000s, there's sections of the strip that are just empty lots or like just a McDonald's and a Ross or something, which now it's kind of you mentioned Star Trek earlier.
It's kind of like the Borg.
It's just the strip.
It's just one long thing.
One building blends into the other.
None of it architecturally.
None of it makes sense, but it's the excess is certainly there.
But there's some great footage on YouTube called like driving around the Vegas strip 1994.
And it is very fascinating to see the old Vegas next to the what are they called the mega resorts, your Mirage, your MGM Grand.
And then there's just a McDonald's and that that it's just it's very interesting to me because now even a McDonald's would be elevated.
It would be like a big crazy neon McDonald's.
But yeah, back then they didn't necessarily fancy it all up.
No.
Yeah, and there's those you can still like there's this little pieces of the strip left for like stores that are holding out.
And I don't know that like, you know, there's like a weird t-shirt store on the strip still.
Yeah.
And that like these like out these like strip malls that still exist in between some of the casinos.
But most of the real estate, as you're saying, is like turned into the gaudiest, most eye catching anything, whether it's the Taco Bell or it's, you know, the Toby Keith.
I love this bar.
Is that on the strip?
I forget.
Yeah, yeah.
Or it was.
It's down a ways.
That closed.
I think it used to be by the senior frogs and they might have been cutting into each other's bottom line and one of them had to close.
Sure.
The Cabo Wabo is at the Planet Hollywood or something like that's all.
The last resort is at Excalibur.
So there's plenty of room between the crude body.
They'll make fun of you.
The waitress might have cleavage kind of.
Yes, and there's twin peaks over by the Taco Bell.
Oh, right.
A different restaurant.
That's in that one where it's like a hard rock and a Bubba Gump and a rain.
I forget what they're all stacked on top of each other.
It's just a big stack of shit.
And you can climb.
You can you can battle a waitress and on a climbing wall in that restaurant.
A twin.
Really?
Yes.
My friends wanted to go.
I swear I'm not a little.
We went.
It's not it's nothing obviously like any of those restaurants.
But then I was like, all right, I guess I'll try to climb the wall.
And I was just humiliated.
I could not do it.
Yeah, I got up.
I got up like three things because they're doing it all the time.
Well, right.
I'm just saying I'm not even saying of course I expect them to be good at it because they've done it a lot.
I was so bad at it.
I was shocked.
I was just I was like, well, maybe I'll get up like halfway and then I'll kind of fall.
No, I could I couldn't get up.
I couldn't get five feet off the ground.
It was humiliating.
Wow. I didn't know about this one.
Yes. Yeah.
Climbing spreader got to be a lot harder than it looks.
I would imagine.
And I didn't I didn't want to do it.
But I was like, well, you know, I don't want to do it.
But I'm going to really I'm going to get up there and they're going to be like, wow, look at this guy.
How did he climb so well for being a first timer?
But no, no, I was a pathetic.
And this is like years.
I mean, even I'm in at least my like early 30s in this story.
Well, 3030, why?
I'm for God's sake.
Prime climb time.
Yeah, that's the perfect time to climb.
Taco Bell Cantina drinks Baja Blast with a shot of Stoli coursing through your veins, which we did.
I did go we did go to the Taco Bell Cantina.
This comes out like on the one year anniversary of when I was last in Vegas.
And I think the thing that I missed that I was like, I can't believe I can't believe I was there.
I didn't do it was the Twilight Zone mini golf.
I think I was.
Yeah, I did.
I buy a good.
Yeah, it's really fun.
Yeah.
And the other one there with the kiss one, I forget if it's still there, if it moved or something.
But it's coming.
It's great.
I think that's at the Rio now, which is the OK, one of the ones.
You know what I think might still be a holdover from old Vegas is the circus circus block.
I haven't been down there and I have a feeling it kind of falls apart around there.
It gets shadier circus circus is kind of scary in general.
They've got this.
Has anybody been to the pepper mill?
The diner that no, no, no, I hear that's fun, though.
It's like my wet dream.
It's like perverse how perfect the pepper mill looks.
It's just like bright neon purple pink brass like indoor like mini golf fountains indoors.
Pepper mill is beautiful.
Maybe I'd want to blow up the pepper mill if but I oh, God, I hope nothing ever happens to it.
I believe Penn Jillette has a mini pepper mill inside his house is what I read.
Oh, wow. Yeah, yeah.
Which is certainly what I would do if I had Penn Jillette money.
Yeah.
So yeah, it gets weird and sloppy down there, though.
And there's a big blank area like where nothing has been built.
And is that oh, no, it's not the next.
That's well, you know, I might as well say we're going a little out of order.
I don't have a lot to say about this one in 2007, the Stardust, but that's like that's been blank for a long time,
even though they blew up the Stardust, which is like an iconic original Vegas one.
But I learned this morning that friend of the show, Matt Mazzani was there for the implosion.
He was just passing through Vegas and it happened to be that day.
And he watched it happen. He said it was spectacular and that there was essentially like a tailgate going on,
like so many people were there and partying and just passing beer around.
So he just got free beer in general from the crowd as everybody cheered a building imploding.
So I'm very jealous of Matt that he got to experience one of these in person because I have not.
But I bring some of that up to say because that is the area we're talking about.
It's right next to Circus Circus and the Riviera, which is recently blown up.
And that for so long has just been a blank zone where they're supposed to be building something called Resorts World.
And Resorts World is part of Genting Group. Genting, which came up a long time ago with Fox Studios Malaysia.
And one of your favorite so many nefarious characters are coming back.
One of yours, Jason's favorite guy, Mercurial Casino Chairman Lim Cock Thay.
Lim Cock Thay. One of these now imploded sites.
I don't know. I don't know what sort of sinister shit casino magnets across the world get into.
But compared to the American, I don't know, maybe Lim Cock Thay is a saint.
Who knows? He's Mercurial. He's a mystery.
Mercurial doesn't mean you're bad. It could mean you're good and you're embarrassed how good you are.
Yeah. Right. So I thought I was going to be embarrassed how good I was at rock climbing against a waitress.
Yeah. I was not.
The Resorts World project is fascinating.
It's so many of these Vegas things just take years and years and there's bankruptcies and economic downturns, the pandemic now.
So much goes on to actually get these massive mega resorts open.
I think that's pretty far along at this point, but it's still taking years and years.
There's one of the first major implosion was in order to build the Bellagio.
And that was four years, all told, which is like, I think that's gunning it.
And especially for such a giant and impressive casino.
I think you're not usually that lucky to just have it done in four.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's like Universal Studios building.
Oh, yeah.
Or they just crank their crank and stuff out at this point.
Crank to get that Cinderella Man screen ride open.
You know, they're grinding, you know, right on time.
Yes.
They got to get it open for the canceled Cinderella Man 2. Back to the ball.
What do you like? Do you punch along with him like the Spider-Man ride? Like it tracks your fists.
Well, that went away after much like a Vegas amusement attraction that within a month, they're like, all right, we're taking this out.
The punching along stopped being interactive after about three weeks because it was just too hard to work.
The whole land teaches you, like it trains you to be a boxer. You are the boxer.
Yes.
You know, that's what it's about.
Yeah, yeah.
You're certified by the end.
Right.
I pulled up the Stardust Implosion and this, I think, is the first one.
Maybe I just saw an abbreviated landmark one, but this one especially, the theme park connection that struck me the most in a lot of these is there is a grand nighttime spectacular of coordinated multicolored fireworks before the controlled demolition.
And that if that isn't theme park, I don't know what is, you know?
Yeah, there's like long fireworks shows before some of these.
Yes. Yeah.
And this one, I'm losing track of my.
Yeah, this one has the numbers, of course, the countdown.
Oh, that's really cool.
Yes. Like flames go off in the windows that take so many to take you all the way from 10 to one.
Yeah. So like the whole front of the building has big like old school alarm clock digital letters, essentially.
Like that's how they they're not like nice, cool cursive or anything.
It's just like these straight lines.
They did their best that time. I'm not. I sounds like I'm shitting on them. But yes, I like.
It's cool as hell. It's great.
Yeah, it's weird. It's cool and weird. It's I don't know. It's like.
Yeah, you turned. It's like I'm trying to think it's like you turned.
It's like if it's like the early version of maybe how Disney does like mapping park mapping now, how you can put different textures on the front of the castle or the Tower of Terror.
But this one is just like, well, we'll turn we'll get some of the lights on and there'll be some straight lines and we'll do our best.
And you got to admire it. You got to love it.
Yeah, there's not so many that you can.
There's not so many options in terms of decorating the building, so you got to be impressed when they they can figure something out.
Another one I don't have a lot to say about it.
I don't even know the year, but there's there's one the frontier and that one has a three, two, one.
And then also the detonator machine, also the loony tunes.
They make the box and the lever and it goes down and then the building goes down.
So that's pretty I shouldn't throw the frontier under the bus because having the living detonator is pretty great.
Yeah, I mean, you can you can find something.
I like how everybody wants. They're like, let's make this implosion our own.
Let's let's give a little something unique in each one.
And the in the box is a very nice touch because you wouldn't know they're not.
It's not like you get a program when you go to an implosion and says, OK, well, the first will be the fireworks show, then the countdown.
And then you'll see the box and the box will go down.
So I feel like you would be a nice surprise if you were waiting there all day tailgating and you get to yeah, you get to have fun with that little Easter egg.
That's like the Tupac hologram coming out at least weekend one where they didn't know it was going to happen.
Right. At this point, there should be like a hologram for these implosions.
I mean, I think I'm sure we'll sum up at the end, but like I want to get to a place back where we're thinking ambitious again.
Vaccines are out. The world has opened up again.
Let's think about getting ambitious with these with these implosions.
Yeah, they got to get stupid again, because I do think we lost our way a little bit.
So if we're if we're back in the chronological order, the next big one that I have is the Sands, which was in 1996.
It is this is the spot that is now the Venetian.
This is a bit of a big rat pack kind of spot to get for the old generation of scumbags giving way to the new.
The this one, there's no movie involved in the making of this one.
But really recently, I think when maybe in the time that the Sands have been closed, they did shoot the finale of Con Air in front of this.
Well, like the Con Air plane screeches to a halt in the lobby of like where the cars park basically.
And then the news footage that I saw like shows that practically happening.
The movie I don't think was out yet.
And everybody's a lot of anticipation for Con Air.
They were right. Con Air is pretty pretty dumb and fun.
Yeah, yeah, for sure.
Yeah, this one is this one's good.
It's kind of like just like a little cake collapsing.
It's just like like somebody put a big straw in a cake and sucked out all the insides from the cake and then the cake just sort of collapsed in on itself.
It's nice, it's simple.
Well, yeah, you know, the actual implosion itself, there's not a lot to write home about.
But here's what I like about this one.
This is where we start getting into.
This is the after I think the success of the first of the dunes in 93, which we'll get to the.
Local news starts realizing that this can be a thing.
We can squeeze a lot of juice out of an implosion happening live on TV.
And especially the mother might have been multiple channels, but the one that jumps out and that is archived really nicely on YouTube is News 13.
And the good people at News 13 put on such a good show every year.
Every year. This is kind of why I've been obsessed with this for a little while, because a YouTube user named access Vegas dot com.
And I will give him credit because it's amazing they post all this great Vegas nonsense.
They they're just there's these full hour long specials showing an implosion happening live that are such wonderful exercises in time killing.
Just like how much for something that unfolds in a matter of 10 seconds, basically, how much other crap can we put at the beginning and the end?
How many reporters can we have down there?
How many cameras can we set up?
And I'll play a little clip here that kind of illustrates the vibe that I like about this.
Here is a little bit of News 13's coverage of the implosion of the sands.
I'm Steve Kruppi. We're getting ready for another heavyweight knockdown in Las Vegas.
You'll see all the angles right here.
I'm Mark Martinez, soaring above the sands in live Chopper 13 where the view of the implosion promises to be spectacular.
I'm Mark Sayer inside the blast zone. We are as close as any human is going to get to this.
We're expecting a huge dust cloud. We're ready for it.
And we'll have the play by play.
I'm Robin Berg, three stories up, giving you yet another view of 18 stories.
Yet another. And I'm Michael Gieser, street side.
This is where the public will gather to witness history.
This is a News 13 special report.
Love it so much. Love the music. Love the names.
Michael Gieser. These people are all awesome. They did such great work.
And that's not at first. I thought they were like actually winking a little bit.
And then I realized, no, they're not.
Yeah, no, I don't think so. I think they're all in.
I think they're there. It's the celebrity that you have.
If you're a local news anchor, especially at this time with less channels and everything, this is this is prime time for them.
This is everybody's chance to shine. And they're they're psyched.
I like that he says play by play as if he's going to be like counting down the room numbers as the each room collapses, like as if there's time for any sort of play by play.
Like the gym, the hotel gym has collapsed.
The the free weights have disintegrated into dust.
They left them in there for some reason. I'm not sure why.
There goes the meeting rooms on floor three.
A salesman who went to an expo there. You won't again.
Yeah, there's no time play by play.
Is he talking about? Yeah, what what they do instead is just kill a lot of time with like setting up all of the cameras that are going to be there.
And this is the one where I think it really gets going. I wrote down a bunch.
They just like there's people in the studio and then some of the reporters are with the cameras, but some of the cameras nobody is with because it's going to be right in the blast zone.
Like something bad is going to happen to the cameras is the only way to get this perspective.
So they introduce all the cameras one by one.
You got the balcony cam and that's like out on that's like up on one of the top penthouses.
And something they say with that a lot is like we're going to write it down.
We're going to ride the building all the way to the ground and then the zoom cam and the hallway cam and the roof cam and the the I don't even capture cam.
That can't be right. I must have written the wrong word.
Copter is probably what it's probably open.
Or the collapse cam or the blast cam and the blast cam is the best one because this keeps factoring into them where this now is a veteran.
We've used this in implosion after implosion and that's set up so that the building falls right on it.
It's right in the path. We've tried to kill it in the past and it didn't go down and we're going to try to kill it again tonight.
Let's see if the blast cam survives.
So are they getting a feed off that or they're then like they have to go retrieve it later on.
It's got to be a feed. Yeah, it's got to be a feed.
They were thinking they would be blown up. It had to be a live feed.
Yeah, because there's no way if they said it didn't get killed last like they must just be like let's punish this camera.
And it's just on a long rope that they just like once the implosion is done, they just got to pull it out from the rubble.
All right, buddy. Yank you back in. Thanks again.
Yeah, I think so because they get the footage back real fast.
And then of course, the second half of the broadcast is just let's see that again.
Now let's see it again from the roof cam.
Now let's see it again from the balcony cam.
And it turns out the blast cam made it and I even hear some of the spectators are pointing at the camera and saying how did the camera make it?
Well, it just because it has stamina. It's the blast cam and it's a veteran of many implosions.
Wow, many.
Yeah, this is the blast cam made it through like six or something.
It is pretty amazing. That's a feat.
Wow, this is like the toughest camera that's ever been invented.
Why don't they know if it ever went down the whole plane out of the blast cam?
Yeah, I will. This blast cam.
Is it in a museum? It should be in a museum somewhere at this point.
And then people should be able to pay and take to take shots at it to see if they can take it down.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Can you climb up with the blast cam to the top of rock climbing wall and throw it with all your might?
And can you break it? Oh, yeah.
Where the waitress does or Vegas has those firing ranges where you can fire a fully automatic like machine gun.
If you could just open up like on the blast cam, the blast cam, the standard definition.
The standard footage, you know that there's no HD cameras are to set like to they're not made sturdy enough.
You know, they're not going to survive like the blast cam did.
Yeah, these are tanks. Absolutely.
Yeah, but also the blast cam. If you sign the waiver, it can take a shot at you. So be careful.
I'd be honored to get clipped by the blast cam.
I lost a toe to the blast cam.
Yeah, Jason, Jason, you realize Jason Sheridan gunned down by the blast cam in the desert of Vegas.
Throw my corpse off the top of the stratosphere.
He always loved. He always loved heights.
It's a shame he could not ride the was it the high roller was that the roller coaster they tore down piece by piece in the elevator.
Oh, I got to really like take it out piece by piece.
You know what? I don't want to spoil it forever. Go to there's a playlist expedition theme park.
I'm sure people are familiar with these videos.
They have a playlist of how the like a lot of the 90s Vegas attractions and the roller coaster that used to circle the top of the stratosphere has a really good one.
That and the Prim attractions and the the MGM, which is that's a big one we haven't done yet is the MGM.
Oh, yeah. Park that they really see it like they cut the ribbon and they were like, oh, we hate this.
We were going to let this rot.
We want pool parties here. We want gross pool parties as fast as they could possibly have.
Yeah, yeah.
There's like I feel like there's a year of podcasts, the ride content from Vegas.
We've done it slowly. I feel like how many Vegas related episodes have we done?
Is this the fourth? I don't know.
Something like, yeah, not too many.
There's a lot. There's so much more.
And it's like all from the 90s. Also, it was all that this one big explosion that required lots of implosions.
I think we were I tossed out the there's the special about the Luxor, the interconnected Luxor attractions.
And then every I think it got I totally forgot about it because everything went into quarantine.
But like right around the start of that, I saw the Luxors.
But I was like, I can't believe they attempted this like no Disney or Universal would have kept that going.
Like it was so complicated.
It's three attractions that are all kind of of the same world and plot line.
But one's a Back to the Future ride type thing made by that director, Doug Trumbull.
And another is like a talk show.
You're watching a live talk show happen that involves the events of the simulator ride.
I think I'm not making this up.
No, you're not. And the actors, you would need the actors like it's basically like a residency
or like a Broadway show run where it's like, oh, the actors in this are the actors in the talk show.
And that's wild. Wow.
Yeah, I say I don't know how to parse out Vegas if you do a theme month or do you just like spread it through the show?
Because we have to do one once a month to keep up pace.
There's so much Vegas nonsense. I mean, maybe a Vegas month in the future is a good idea to get a bunch of some of the big stuff out of the way.
And then we can keep. Yeah.
I mean, obviously we have to return to the David Copperfield theater also and see how the show is doing and how they've updated it.
They've updated it. Tickets on sale March 15th. Who knows what they're going up.
I wouldn't say go yet, but yeah, eventually when it's good, when you're good.
You know, since we're jumping around a little along with the main timeline,
friend of the show, Andrew Grissom reminded me that David Copperfield did an illusion involving a building implosion.
Does anyone remember this? Have you seen this? I have seen this, but I did not refresh myself before this episode.
It's you know, it's just a really good one. I can't even exactly.
There's nothing like blue to snark on. It just is great.
He he gets locked in a safe in a building that's getting imploded in Charlotte, North Carolina,
and he has two and a half minutes to get out.
And one camera follows like the police officers who handcuff him and then all of the safety workers who all run out together
and another camera stays trained on the lock to see if it moves or if anything happens.
And I don't want to give it away, but it's it's just great.
You've like, boy, he was good at that. Those 90s specials are fantastic.
Yeah. Oh, yeah, I got it. I'll check. I'll check back in on that.
Well, we can we can revisit it when we go back to the Copperfield Theatre to see how the show is doing.
We could just watch a bunch of those old one. I mean, yeah, there's a ton there.
But isn't it what is it? What is it with this episode where so many of our favorite characters are returning?
We've had the Mercurial Chairman, we've had Copperfield, Steve Winfrey,
Steve Wynn comes in and out. It's like we just did an episode about Mickey's house and Toontown.
And it is like Vegas is Toontown for some of our favorite characters.
You know, they live in these places, stuff we people Steve Wynn, David Copperfield, Jimmy Buffett, Margaritaville.
I mean, there's so many Sammy Hagar Hagar there who I just learned wrote the I thought Rick Springfield wrote the song.
I would do anything. I've done everything for you.
But Sammy Hagar wrote that song. How about that?
Who does the song? Who's the singer of it?
Rick Springfield's like, I've done everything for you.
You've done nothing for me. I thought it was Rick Springfield written song.
It's not. It's Sammy Hagar, the man himself.
Wow. The legend. Shocked. He stumped me though. I don't know that song.
I think you've heard it. It's in a movie. Is it in Wet Hot American Summer?
No, that's Love Is Alright Tonight.
That's Love Is Alright Tonight. It's something else then. Sorry.
Wonderful song. Great song.
The OK, so you're getting back on the trajectory.
Oh, and actually, because here's what I'm starting to as I'm going through these specials and I've been like, this has been a great excuse to why I've watched these years ago.
But Aaron and I have been watching them together again.
We spent Valentine's Day watching an implosion special with a bottle of wine.
And I regret nothing. In quarantine times, that's about as great of a Valentine's Day as you're going to get.
So revisiting all these, especially via the News 13 coverage, I'm starting to fall in love with these people.
I think all of these anchors are great. And then you see kind of some push and pull.
Like people rise up in the ranks. There's somebody who's like, you know, I've been stuck in the studio for the implosions most years.
This is actually the first one that I've seen in person and I have to say in person, it's amazing.
You really feel the rumble. It's just, you know, nothing can describe it.
Then another guy will say, oh, this is actually my sixth.
So when you make it up to six, you'll really know the ins and outs.
Like they're kind of like one upping each other in terms of implosion counts.
I love it. These people, like I want to I want to hang out with the News 13 gang.
I want to I would love to I was thinking how I would like to moderate a panel reuniting the many years running implosion crew
and just like see if they've kept up and perspective they have on implosions that they didn't 25 years ago.
I mean, this is this is one of those hypothetical projects that would be really great if you spent a ton of time on it.
Yeah, yeah. If I just like poured lots and lots of all the time that I have,
if I if I stunted my own career that I'm trying to keep vaguely on track, if I just.
All right. Screw all that. Let's implode it.
And instead, let's go talk to let's go see if I can track down Steve Kruppi.
Let's get the reunion zoom going.
Well, Robin Burke said yes, we got Rob.
Then you're filming a documentary about the making of the documentary where like she says yes.
Yes, we got Robin Burke. There's a big celebration and champagne.
We got Robin. We got Robin.
I as I put down the phone, there's no one else in the room.
There's just a mirror, a dirty mirror that you're looking at.
Dirty from kisses like you got Michael Gieser, you sharp son of a bitch.
I believe in you and I always have.
And then like it cuts to the mirror and it's you.
But in a different like you've lost your mind and you're like, have you been it's the last time you saw your son?
This documentary is your son now, isn't it? Yes.
And what's wrong with that? What's wrong with that? Me?
I'm the edge lord now. I don't need you.
I mean, I've punched the mirror.
I slice myself with one of the shards in the face.
Now I have a cool scar. I live here.
I live here in the Riviera stripped, stripped everything sold every item liquidated.
But still it has the aura of cigarette smoke and the grease, everything covered as if it was rubbed with ham.
So I'm living in the like the remains of the Riviera, just like finding expired Wendy's patties that were somewhere in the fire.
I have a summer home. I have a summer home in the remains of Speed the Ride sitting unattended in an empty lot by Bandolier Bay.
If if if Covid were to stretch into 2022, I don't think this scenario is unlikely.
No, we've all just made mine for all for all for all of us.
For all of us. We've all made mind palaces of extinct, disgusting casinos.
My version, my version is like I look at the mirror and I'm like, have you gotten all four punk frog side characters from the new Ninja Turtle neck a line?
No, you haven't found them. Why not?
It's like, well, when was the last time you talked to your parents?
A year, but it doesn't matter because I need to get Rasputin the Mad Frog, my favorite of the four frog friends.
If I'd been raised by Rasputin, none of this would have happened.
I need to start dressing like him with his Hawaiian shirt and his little shorts.
I am that Rasputin now.
I've built little beds for all four of them. All they need to do is arrive at my door.
They look like lily pads. They sleep on lily pads made out of napkins.
I've tracked the ley lines of Las Vegas with the Krispy Kreme donut locations.
They seem to be everywhere. People want excess. People want indulgences.
And I think Anton Levese's works probably have something to say about this.
Jason is like, if I build the world's largest glass, I can dunk myself in.
I will become the cookie.
Yeah, the Church of Satan, you know, the rules do no harm, but do what thou wilt.
So, you know, that's the first part of the saying.
Jason Sheridan died today, drowned in a giant glass of milk.
Requested that his doomsday say, Jason Sheridan, a great cookie.
If it goes longer, that's where we're at.
Yeah, maybe like end of April.
We know it's going to be going then. Just how mad will we be?
Yeah, also, by the way, the right amount.
Mine was, by the way, the closest to actually what's happening.
Oh, yeah.
I have a dry one with a little bit of a dry one.
This is sort of will be good for content, but I'm surrounded by so many books written by Martin Pegler that are all like just like this one's called storefronts and facades.
I've been collecting these during the pandemic.
It'll just be like photos of the front of, you know, a Dave and Buster's or a Planet Hollywood retail store.
It is the I mean, we'll get content out of this for sure.
But like, here's like really artful photos of like a footlocker, like a really fancy footlocker.
There actually is good stuff in it.
Did you know, Mike, that there was a not a Planet Hollywood in the Schomburg Mall, but just a Planet Hollywood store?
They were trying to do stores without the restaurant.
Oh, that is familiar.
I would not. I don't know.
Do you know how when it was there?
I'd have to study my Martin Pegler books a little more.
I'm not sure if it's in storefronts and facades or retail experiences.
Number three.
I feel like it was brief.
Because you know, there's that period where I did not go to Mars and Woodfield.
So there was a period where I was apparently not enjoying garbage, like garbage, kitschy bullshit.
Man. Yeah.
Well, we all have that dark period in our lives.
Mine was college.
I was trying to, you know, expand my horizons and date.
What a fool I was.
Now I'm back on track.
Yuck is all I can say.
The most famous in the theme park world, free standing Planet Hollywood store at Disney MGM Studios, right on the Sunset Boulevard extension.
There was just.
Oh, it was its own? Really?
Yep. Right in the middle on the way to Tarotary.
You pop in.
You look at Planet Hollywood shirts.
You know, you've already looked at them at downtown Disney.
You know, that's bizarre.
Another one of these I have in front of me is just called streetscapes.
And this is like a nice coffee table book that's just a photo of City Walk on the front.
Perfect.
There's Crab Tree in Evelyn.
There's the Nature Company.
Wow.
So I don't I don't I guess I can't say I have any regrets.
No.
Yeah. Well, content will be coming your way from streetscapes.
Is there.
Back to the madness at hand.
Yeah.
I think what I was trying to say about these anchors, here's just a quick clip of which which guy is this?
I think this is Mark Sayers.
He's kind of the one who's the most braggy about how many he's been part of.
And this is just an example of the great like, all right, I am surrounded by smoke.
And how can I kill time on camera for six straight minutes?
And he ended up just rambling to eat till you get to this.
I hope you I hope you can see this in front of me.
We literally have just turned in, turned night into additional night to more night to additional blackness.
It is really quite an experience.
Just now the night has become more night.
It is almost double night.
It's I did not know night could be so nighty.
But that is what implosions have taught us.
And that's why it's important to see them and support them.
He that is off.
He does not report on levels of darkness very often.
I can tell that is not something that he has in his in his brain.
I will also say it really made me uncomfortable because he was not wearing an N95.
He was wearing a really flimsy mask that you might wear when you're like doing some woodwork or something.
Yeah, no goggles, no safety glasses.
He had his goggles off too.
So I was like, oh, he's breathing in some bad crap.
Yeah, we're so mask conscious at this point.
It is funny what like that they go out of their way to say, and I even brought a mask.
It's like very chilling to watch in our current environment.
And yeah, knowing that like, yeah, that's not going to do anything for he's talking about like I can really smell that acrid smell.
Oh, no way.
Then this is one thing that has come up as Aaron and I've been watching these.
I said, like, God, I really, man, I want to go to an implosion one day.
And she's like, yeah, you want to go like breathe in just like concentrated asbestos?
Yeah, it was like, how much can I have in one sitting?
Now, there's a good point.
Yeah, there's a short documentary I watched a while back and I think it was I don't know if then this is later chronologically, but the Riviera, there was concern when that was coming down to there was a bunch of asbestos in it.
They're like, we think we got it all out and they imploded part of it and immediately they discovered it's like we have set asbestos particles into the air.
No. Yeah.
And so like, you know, this is the one thing we didn't want to happen immediately happened like, yeah.
Yes.
There's a process in all these, I think, where I like Aaron about the dunes one that before any of it, they had to go.
It cost $800,000 to do asbestos removal.
So that's a whole step and you try to get it out before you blow it into the air.
Yeah, but they can't get all of it.
They can't get all the way or they think they got all of it.
And it's like, oh, we forgot that floor.
So I whoopsie whoopsie whoops whoops again.
The quoting last episode, the yeah, these that's one funny thing about these like and there goes smoke just all over.
I've been watching the Trump one was funny with that, too.
I like yeah, it can't be good to be in the vicinity of these.
It can't be good for that.
I don't know what else you do.
I don't know how you take these down otherwise.
But but yeah, maybe don't be close, close by.
Yeah.
Maybe get far away for a while.
Yeah, that would be my unless you like.
I don't think you can't tent it or anything.
You can't tent it, then blow it up.
There's one that I watched.
I think the Aladdin that had VIP tent and the reporter was saying how this is as close to the blast zone as you could be.
But you also know that that tense just going to just be like poof.
And then it's just covered in dust and you can't see it anymore.
At the very least to N95 if you're going to do it.
That's what I would say.
Yeah.
There are plenty of those around this time in the 2021 implosion.
I guess here we keep moving to the this was just an implosion horrific time in Vegas because right after the sands just a few months later, they blew up one called the Hacienda and the Hacienda.
They made this happen on New Year's Eve 1996.
Big old fireworks show.
They seem to be playing the Mission Impossible theme along with it, which is really good.
Perfect.
And I didn't have a lot of info about this one.
I couldn't even find the local news coverage.
I'm like, was this kind of a quieter one?
I guess maybe this and then late breaking right before we started recording, I found that I think maybe maybe the networks saw News 13 and Steve Kruppie and all their great work.
And they're like, we need a piece of this action.
We got to bring this to the big leagues.
So Fox in 1996 for their New Year's Eve coverage not only covered the implosion live, but made it the centerpiece of their entire thing because there's Dick Clark's Rockin' Eve.
And that's still what they do.
But they wanted to start a new New Year's franchise.
And here I'll reveal this title within the clip itself.
Hell yes.
The best graphics I've ever seen.
Starring the Doobie Brothers.
Coo-dee-la-maw Fish.
Salt and Pepper.
Siegfried and Roy.
The Treasure Island.
Buckethead Bay Pirates.
Cirque du Soleil.
And the live implosion of the Hacienda Hotel.
And then Sinbad does stand up and he makes fun of people's yard drinks.
It's just a great block of television.
It's so fun.
It rules.
Yeah, Jason, as you said, amazing graphics.
It's like clock spinning and unreadable fonts and unnecessary capitalizations.
They do the N and the B in Sinbad.
That doesn't make sense.
No, it doesn't.
Hootie and the Blowfish and Cirque du Soleil and Doobie Brothers.
I mean, we might have to put that on one of the Ampersand shirts.
We might have to sell that one.
The greatest group ever and the Hacienda explosion.
And there's one celebrity that I have not mentioned.
They got a celebrity involved in the implosion part itself.
I don't have the time code.
I don't want to spoil it.
Robert Blake.
This might be like the best.
This might be the pull quote of all pull quotes.
And now you guys are seeing them.
Let me find the moment.
And I might not have it timed out right.
There might be a little extra lead time.
But this might be the best thing ever said during implosion coverage.
By 96.
Welcome 97.
Let's get ready to crumble.
Did you know where it was going?
Is anybody like I'm ahead of it?
I know what it's going to be instead of rumble.
Or did you think it was just going to be rumble?
You know, I didn't even think that far ahead.
I guess I assumed it would be rumble or rubble.
Rubble would be good.
Yeah, pretty good.
Get ready for rubble.
Let's get ready for rubble.
Yeah, that would be good.
I feel stupid.
Was that Vince?
Who was that?
That's Michael Buffer.
Michael Buffer.
Okay, I could not place his name.
You thought it was Vince McMahon?
Well, young Vince, I keep watching older WWE stuff.
And it is crazy what Vince McMahon looks like now compared to...
He wasn't that young in the 90s.
But I was like 50.
Yeah.
I mean, there's a similar vibe.
There's a little, yeah.
The pompadour, the poof, I think, was doing a lot of work when I was looking at...
Big meaty cheekbones.
Vince wasn't white haired though back then.
Yes, that's true.
Yeah, that's the only difference.
They really should have...
Like some wrestling interaction with implosion.
I mean, that'd be a good way to...
Just like, I don't know, having one of them do it or like a fight is happening in the minutes before...
Like they got to wrap it up before the countdown starts.
They really should have done something.
You mean like two guys are battling in a building that's about to be imploded?
Yes. Yeah. Yeah.
And they have to get to some resolution here or they both die.
Mm-hmm. That's pretty good.
Yeah.
That's shocking that didn't happen in the 90s.
Like some of those 90s that...
I was watching like the 98 or 99 Royal Rumble and just immediately share shots to the head within minutes.
And it's just like, oh no. Oh no.
Oh yeah, yeah.
You're saying that shocked you as much as a match about guys getting blown up.
Vince got blown up in a limo.
Well, I remember the limo. Yes.
Our ex-president thought it was real.
Yes.
Oh, he called him to check in.
He called him to check in.
Yeah.
Trump saw Vince's limo blow up on Monday Night Raw and called to make sure Vince was okay.
You know what's a trip to watch that I caught?
A couple of them recently is the Rock hosting in 2000 and 2002, his monologues and like just what was going on in the world in 2002.
The first two sketches are about a rash of suicide bombings in the Middle East.
And you're like, wow.
With the SNLs?
Yeah, the SNLs. It's like, wow, coming out swinging.
Wait, I guess that's... Yeah, wait. Did he host sort of soon after 9-11? Was it...
Yeah, I think it was 2002, but there wasn't a lot of 9-11 stuff in that one.
But in 2000, that was the one where Vince is backstage with Lorne, big show, Triple H, Foley and the audience coming down.
They jumped down from the bleachers and it's the best.
And just in the sleaziest leather jackets, the grungiest looking hair. And it's just like, oh yeah, wow, wow, wow.
Vince did a really good live from...
And you know he can't let people down. He's got to do that great.
He might be one of the best ever. Just how much did he bring to that phrase that's been said so many times?
Yeah.
Vince and Lorne together.
Yeah, I know, just that. I want to see them again. He's got to come back.
Oh yeah, I'd like to see several episodes.
Lorne is like playing along with the character. He's like, your men better behave themselves, McMahon.
Your boys. Your boys aren't going to... It's so good.
It's great.
Written by Tommy Blacha, my showrunner.
Oh yeah.
Because he was a wrestling writer, so he did the like, stitched together the story with the... And let's make it comedy as well.
Wow.
That's great.
Also, with Moonbeam City, so much of I loved Implosions that in season two of Moonbeam City, there was going to be an episode that all took place during a live Implosion special being covered on the local news.
So yeah, this has been a long running... I was going to use all the cams. Like, can we like... And like all the scenes happen via balcony cams, hallway cams, all that shit.
If only. We would have had fun. Until the show, until the Comedy Central imploded the show.
Without warning.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. No, we didn't have time to get out.
Yeah.
The Aladdin in 1998. I don't have a lot about this one. It's just another solid... Like, the news crew again, they are just firing on all cylinders. They're so great.
The blast cam is back. They're going to try to kill it again, but it doesn't die. Never does. It's becoming a family at this point. They have 22 cameras to cover.
And that keeps... We have all the angles and the angles you're only going to see on News 13. Like, I think they really had to muscle out. Maybe they were still working with the mafia.
Like, we got to make sure no other news station is anywhere close. They get one camera tops.
Yeah. It's... Aladdin is fine. It's a fine implosion.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It's a great special. I recommend all the specials and we'll post clips of all this stuff.
We can make it over to the first one, but I want to name check a couple other. Because as I said, like, if movies can be involved in implosions, now we're really tied. This is the best that these things can be.
Did you guys find anything about the lethal weapon implosion?
No.
Oh, wow.
Never heard about this. Number of good implosions in Orlando. Amway Arena blew up and that's just like, that's so much there to like cave in on it. So that's a really cool one to watch.
But they blew up a city hall and what happened was they started building the new city hall behind the old city hall and like, like feed away, like as close as a house is to its next door neighbor.
So and I don't think they necessarily, it's not that they didn't have a plan. It was like, this has to be the most top of the line implosion or else like the mayor is going to be in trouble.
The mayor is like, if there's any debris and I mess up both buildings and we have nowhere to work, we spent all this money on it. I'm screwed.
So they didn't have the money to do the implosion right? And they started realizing what if we had, what if we auction off the rights to a movie? Could we sell the movie rights to an implosion?
And they reached out to Joel Silver, Hollywood mega producer Joel Silver, who ended up paying $50,000 to use this implosion in lethal weapon three.
And and there's great footage you can watch of this of they don't run out before the actual building implodes.
There's kind of like a pre step or they do like fire off a bunch of explosions as they're running out and then they went and did the real thing.
But Mel Gibson and Danny Glover went down to do it. So they run out of a building that's going to be imploded real soon.
And then the mayor of Orlando was awarded with a rewarded with a movie role. He's in the movie.
He has one line and I'll tell you it it blows all of fucking Garcetti's cameos out of the water.
That's a that's a movie cameo that you earned by engineering a great masterpiece of implosion.
So that that's all really cool. That's a good one.
And then you got to bring up the Dark Knight.
Dark Knight was a great movie implosion where it was a candy factory.
It was an abandoned candy factory. The Brock's the Brock's administration building.
Oh, it wasn't a factory. It was just where they worked.
I'm actually not sure if they actually did any fact. I just know that it was called where I have it here.
Yeah, it's sorry. Sorry.
I'm looking through. Yeah, Brock's. Can you spell that?
They call they say Brock's candy. B R A C C H. Isn't that a brax? Is it Brock's?
I don't know. I figured this would come up. Right. Yeah. Yeah.
I believe it's Brock's. That's all I've always. I mean, I could be wrong.
Well, they make a quality product. It's called. Yeah, it's called Brock's administration building.
But I think it might be also the factory. OK.
But they dressed it as Gotham Hospital and the Joker blows it up.
And that's funny. That's another one. You know what I love in all of these things?
I mean, this is true with a lot of stuff in Dark Knight where you know it's going to look cool in the movie.
But when people just go film it from wherever vantage point they can get to and it looks cool before it's even in a movie,
you know, it's going to be a great scene. That that sequence is so awesome.
I mean, of course, I love it because I'm an edge lord, but for us and he's your guy, your guys in the scene.
Yeah, yeah. All the jokers are my guys. That's right.
You have that. You have one of those T-shirts where they're all playing poker, you know. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I have a number. They all have. I have different ones where they're all in different positions like. Yeah.
Who is winning? Who didn't get to sit because it was too crowded.
Yeah, it's really good. The Dark Knight is so good and is is stupid that there's so much garbage culture around that movie.
Doesn't it feel lame to say you like the Dark Knight now?
Well, it happens with all the things that are end up being like cultural phenomenon.
Nominance. So, yeah, I hear. I mean, yeah, there's plenty of stuff where you go.
It feels lame to like this now, but it is good. And Dark Knight certainly falls into that category.
Why so serious? That feels like now it's just on like shirts at the boardwalk.
Yeah, but I mean, the performance on its own.
I mean, some of the surveillance storyline stuff with the cell phones making the radar like that is such a thing of its time.
But it's like, yeah, you kind of you can't beat Christian Bale or Christian Bale.
He's a ledger. I like Christian Nolan.
There's some Nolan. There's some Nolan bullshit in those movies.
But ultimately, you just say you want to see him kill that guy with a pencil. Yeah. Yeah. That's cool.
And so good. And also really tying it together, the finale of that movie and the Joker hanging from the side of the that is filmed in Chicago in an under the opposite, an under construction Trump Tower.
They were still. Yeah, that's a Trump building. I forgot about that.
The they call the the Brock's administration implosion, the implosion slash explosion because it does have exterior blasts as well to make it more spectacular.
Yeah. And then it's a little CGI a fight in the mood like they add.
If they add some extra extra oomph to the explosion.
So is it a true implosion? I think maybe it's both. It's half and half.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. Little mix.
Do we miss any other good ones before we take it to the high seas?
Yeah, I mean, well, that one that one is is such a behemoth.
And that one I was watching, I felt very silly. I was like the one we're about to talk about.
I was like, man, this looks cinematic. Were those fireballs?
And there was good reason because it was purposely cinematic because they used it in a movie, TV.
Yeah, yes. And I this must be why any of this came up before, because the big one, the one that started it all, the dunes in 1993.
And this, I believe, is one of the greatest events in the history of mankind.
I think this rules so much because this so it's the site where they were going to build the Bellagio.
And right next door to that is the newly opened Treasure Island.
I found out that it opened on the day that the implosion happens.
This is the first day ever of operation of Treasure Island and Treasure Island, I think, still does this pirate show outside with a big pirate ship.
And if you're going to have an implosion, why not tie it all together and have the pirates blow up the building with a cannon?
I remember I remember the room I was in when my dad with something of this was on TV and my dad explaining to me, oh, yeah, they did this thing where the pirates blew up the casino.
And I was just never stopped thinking about I thought that was the coolest thing I'd ever heard.
I think I was eight at the time.
And it's never the feeling is not diminished.
I wouldn't say so. No, I'm still just as excited about it.
It rules. It's so great to talk about some of what Jason was saying.
This is like really the big one.
I think I didn't know any of the context of this where the dunes was a super mafia hotel.
So blowing up the dunes is completely we're saying goodbye to that era and to the end of mafia control of Las Vegas.
It's the end of an era and to help celebrate it, pirates are there.
No, goodbye, mafia. Hello, pirates.
The pirates are commanded to buy sea wood.
I have the clip.
Please do.
The clip is so good.
Please.
All right.
And here's Mr.
When the captain of the Britannia, are you ready, sir?
Prepare.
Ready.
Fire.
And then they're just watching the listener can't see this.
But holy shit, this is it's fireballs.
They don't need to do any of this.
Yes.
None of this is helping the building.
Exterior fire.
The sign is lit up.
It says no vacancy.
All right.
Oh, good detail.
Yeah.
The sign.
They blow up the sign.
And then just a massive fireball.
And then it's just on fire for a while before it goes down.
Oh, my God.
It looks like hell.
It looks like hell has opened up and swallows the building whole.
It is so scary looking because of the fact that it's on fire and then it falls down.
I mean, it has to be so much worse for the air than even a normal implosion to do all that.
Yeah.
I think to me, that is some of the joy of these things in general.
When you think about other scenarios where buildings collapse, I mean, there's just there's
you really think of a big one.
Obviously, September 11th.
Horrible, horrible.
We're all scarred from it forever.
So, like the idea of that, like, oh, my God, that building is on fire and then you watch it fall.
Like, what gives you a pit in your stomach?
What's scarier than that?
So, to have all these things where we did it on purpose and pirates did it and it's fun
and we're harnessing this power for good and for change and kids are going to laugh about it
and people are going to tailgate with it.
It's so silly to me, like making a building falling down the funnest thing ever.
Yeah.
That's what Jane was like.
Isn't it weird?
They made these exploding buildings into entertainment and I'm like, yeah, 100%.
It's weird.
But casinos are weird.
It's like luxury, like nice hotel rooms, spas, fine dining next to gamble and next to abject
human misery.
Just so much money changing hands.
Like, and just people leaving fortunes up to fate.
It's absurd.
We should blow up a monument every year on like 4th of July.
We should just blow up the Statue of Liberty or the Washington Monument.
I think that would be so exciting.
It's fun to see big things as long as it's obviously not in some horrible, as long as people aren't dying.
It is fun and it's strange to see something so large blow up.
We haven't talked about like the Disney context of that.
Like, would you, if there was like an idea to, we're going to build Cinderella's castle bigger and better,
and then we're going to blow up the current Cinderella castle, would you like that or would that be bizarre and like scary?
Well, we've talked about dystopian Disneyland and Disney World seems very scary.
There's, if you could find those videos of the knockoff theme parks overseas that are abandoned and you can get a taste of what it would be like.
And it is like, it is a nightmare.
It is a huge nightmare.
So I imagine if seeing like one of the castles implode would be a little traumatizing.
I would, I would guess.
Yeah.
But if they made it fun and Mickey detonated it.
Or like Goofy sat on the wrong lever or something.
Oh, that's good.
You can screw it up.
Now they do, you know what they do in that, in that Hogwarts show they had been doing.
They do have projection to make Hogwarts castle fall apart, which is cool.
Oh yeah.
That's true.
So like you can see it gets like pieces fall off.
It's exposed.
You can see inside of it.
And then obviously they fix it or Dumbledore fixes it at the end.
So you could do like a cute version like that as opposed to actually putting dynamite into
Sleeping Beauty's castle.
I'll tell you what they should have blown up.
They should have blown up the not that it's good.
I mean, it's sad that it closed, but horizons, the closure of horizons was so painfully stretched out and anticlimactic.
But if every, if they had been like the future begins January 1st, 2000 and it blown up that build it like
That is sad, but also kind of awesome.
Robot butler's head lands in somebody's lap.
Yes.
I should say Scott, because you mentioned the yeah, treasure island was newly opened and that was a real new Vegas conquering old Vegas with the dunes being exploded.
I know the strip was less built up at the time, but if you look at a map of the strip, you can see that they're not exactly close.
Here's treasure island.
And then here is the Bellagio and there is Caesar's palace in between.
Oh, I thought they were next door.
I thought that's why it happened.
Wow.
That's yeah, that's nowhere close.
That's a lot in between.
And I think, well, I, I, the, the ownership is, I think it is.
Like, because when sold off the Mirage casinos to before he well before he built the win in the encore, he sold off the Mirage and treasure, not treasure island.
Or did he sell off treasure island?
Treasure island, I don't think it's part of MGM now, but he sold off a grip of them to MGM.
Resort.
Which I believe the Mirage owns now.
And that's how you end up with like monorails connecting a lot of just the ones that are in the back.
Oh, just the ones that are in that system.
That map you were just showing also right next to that is the fashion show mall, which had a dive restaurant, the submarine restaurant.
The submarine restaurant was right next to the pirate show.
This is just such a good time.
It all makes me wish I grew up in Las Vegas, although maybe not because maybe there's weirdness to that too.
But I, or I just that I'd visited, you know, several times a year.
You would be like the guy who you wouldn't have a this career you would have be the guy who controls Blue's mouth at the Copperfield show.
And I pick which Rob Paulson clips to play.
Well, David will scream at you after each show.
But yes, you can make one error.
Yeah, right.
But I get but at least I get to like walk around with like my children from a book, a bunch of marriages.
And I get them all together and say like there used to be a submarine in there and they'll say, shut up.
Take us to that one little lettuce drink.
But you're twelve.
Shut up.
I'm part of shut up.
Did you not get dad?
I mean, I don't know.
There's probably some joy in that life.
I think so.
I believe suburban, you know, Vegas Vegas, suburban Vegas, one of the most quickest expanding residential areas in the world.
Yeah, that's what I understand.
Yeah, because I think it's affordable to live.
There's no income tax.
There's some something like that.
So what Jason is saying, Scott, is it's not too late.
It's not too late.
Yeah.
And then you just have to deal with that for a while every year.
It is one hundred and fifty degrees.
That's right.
As long as you can make it through that part.
But you can go to like the rehab pool party on Sunday.
On Sundays and listen to loud music and be with a bunch of people and then you can cool off and you can hit up.
I'm realizing in this version.
What's that?
Well, you can add up the locals casinos like Sam's town.
Well, that's what I'm what I'm realizing is I think in this version, like this version of Scott ends up I'm acting in the movie Billy Toppet alongside Lance Burton.
I have I have dyed hair for some reason, even though I'm not gray yet, I still just go overboard.
I have jet black hair.
I'm considered the young gun of the magician crew at 32.
I'm the youngest person they know.
You are padlocking him into the desperado track.
Into the wait.
The roller coaster.
You are padlocking him.
Oh, and he's strapped to the roller coaster.
Right.
So I'm Lance Burton's assistant in this world.
I've been married four times.
Yeah.
He keeps saying like, well, I'll give you an opening spot.
I'll give you an opening spot and just string in your ass at log.
Lance says one day now I know Lance isn't playing anywhere right now.
They've blown up.
They've imploded several of the places where he did residencies.
But if he finds another one, I could be hitting up Sam's land.
What was the one?
Sam's town.
The one that the killer's album was named after.
Yeah, that's right.
And then like tape face comes to town and Scott gets so mad because he like,
he was up for that slot and tape face got it.
I didn't get blue man.
I didn't get puppetry of the penis.
They aren't letting me in anything.
Tony and Tina's wedding.
Yeah.
Couldn't even get a slot.
I passed that audition with flying colors.
Couldn't even get a slot at the dollar hot dog one at the best Western with the
casino with the cheapest with $5 blackjack buy in.
Scott can't even get a dish watching job at twin peaks.
So sad.
You can't climb the rock wall at all.
That's the so you want to wash dishes here, huh?
Why don't you try climbing that wall?
I got it.
No problem.
Oh man, I fell off.
I fell off three feet in and all my children laughed at me.
The okay, so we're missing one big component of this.
So the the the pirates of Buccaneer Bay and we'll we will cover all this someday
down the line.
I just love that this thing happens.
They shooting a cannon at a I like thinking that that happened that like a
cannon fires one ball and then an entire building goes down.
It's like the death.
So we lit on fire.
Oh, yeah.
You know, a ragtag group, an unlikely group, right, brings down the great
evil.
And this is cool.
It's cool.
It's cool to watch it on the news.
I love that it happened.
But then what I didn't know until a couple of years ago, and I think a fan of the
show mentioned this, that this was all filmed for a movie for a feature film for
the now classic Treasure Island.
The adventure begins.
They film starring Steve Wynn as Steve Wynn that aired on NBC and then just was
shown in the Treasure Island Hotel on a loop all day every day.
Yeah.
And that's we can't we'll get to it.
Yes.
This it is.
It is.
It is as wild as it sounds.
It's as weird as it sounds.
It's I don't know.
There's more.
There's definitely some big movies made as marketing devices.
But this one, like a movie to commemorate the opening of a new casino that aired on
TV, it's like 45 minutes long without commercials.
So with commercials, I guess it's probably like 90 minutes.
It's like prime time.
It was.
It was prime time.
And I found out a little bit about the airing of it from a newspaper article.
It was in like the Washington Post.
It was like, what the fuck was this?
This is the worst thing I've ever seen on TV.
And it turned it was aired.
Yeah.
In prime time, it was one of the lowest rated things of the week easily.
And the person who greenlit it and said, yeah, let's do it, was an NBC executive
named Don Ohlmeyer, perhaps best known for firing Norm McDonald from Weekend
Update, one of the great boneheads in executive history.
Good personal friend of OJ Simpson, fire of Norm McDonald and green lighter of
Treasure Island.
The adventure begins.
We need to get there.
He's on some specials from SNL specials, but I would love to really know exactly
the making of this.
This is more interesting.
I want to know everything.
Yeah.
And when you think about the coordination, because I mean, in general, anything that's
like we're filming this for multiple different things, but I just love that.
So what we just saw where Steve Wynn says, captain of the Britannia, then right after
this, he had to move positions and go like arm and arm with a fake family with an actor
family, because that's how you see it in the movie.
The camera swoops up behind them and he's like you do how you go on a vacation with
your family and then end up with the owner of the casino, like hugging him.
They're all arm and arm watching the beautiful implosion again.
I believe the kid was like he was in the building.
Yes.
Blackbeard or something with a count with pirates with a countdown going because, you
know, the family has just come to Vegas to see all that the Treasure Island, you know,
the brand new Treasure Island casino has to offer, you know, the amenities, all the cool
features and so many stores.
Mom loves those, you know, as in 90 percent of movies in the 90s.
Everyday life gets a little bit more interesting when you get scooped up into the arms of
Lady Adventure, you know.
I do know.
That's Robert McKee.
So make sure that your story has Lady Adventure in it.
Yes.
Answer Lady Adventure's call by the end of the first act.
Are you stuck?
Thrust your characters into the arms of Lady Adventure.
Lady Adventure.
You know, it's not enough to just have dinosaurs back in Central Park.
You know, you have to have more.
Of course.
Yeah. Wait, did he write We're Back a Dinosaur story?
No, I was just thinking what is the most 90s movie besides this movie?
What else is very 90s and we're back.
Yeah.
I was just hoping like because I like I love when there's some like snooty screenwriter
guy and then what's the credit like how there's a book called Screenwriting for Dummies and
it's written by the guy who wrote the movie Miss Castaway, which is a parody of Miss
Congeniality and Castaway starring Michael Jackson.
Mm hmm.
Ah, yeah, you know that.
I'm not saying I'm not saying he doesn't know.
Maybe he's good.
He's never got anything made.
I'm not saying this isn't about him what I'm about to say, but it's almost as if you
could teach classes on things and not be very good at them.
I bet can't be true.
There's a program that I've I've paid for many of these.
There's a program called Master Class and all of those are with the top, very top person
in their field.
Any number of people on the flight logs of those master classes.
They shot them on Little St. James from what I understand.
There's a studio there.
Oh, that's where the class is.
Yeah.
I am listening to the audio book of David Lynch's memoir and he was in the first like
graduating class or first class of like fellows at AFI and offhandedly they mentioned one
of the faculty members who taught like Lynch and Terrence Malick and stuff had a screenwriting
technique and I wrote it down because I forget what it's called.
I don't have the paper in front of me.
That involves writing down 70 elements of a screen of let's story onto index cards and
then you turn that into a screenplay and I'm like I have never heard of this technique
before.
I have to know everything about this 70 items.
70 items.
I don't know anything about the 70 items.
And then but unless one of them is Lady Adventure and then it's not going to work.
I'm really enjoying the book but I did get very excited for show reasons because they
said and then Lynch was able to get with Mel Brooks attached as producer.
The elephant man was picked up by Paramount where Michael Eisner and Jeffrey Katzenberg
were running the studio and I was like and.
Yes.
Mel it seemed like the long and short of it was Mel Brooks ran was so confident in him
and ran so much interference he didn't have a lot of notes from the studio and the outfit
man was nominated for eight Oscars but I was like oh my god is this about to be a Katzenberg
Eisner thing and like no it just had happy ending that the movie did very well and put
him on the map.
Okay.
Oh man.
Almost.
And no ride ever made out of the elephant man.
No no heartwarming tale of a Victorian doctor.
If only.
Yeah.
I mean yeah.
Trails Around the Adventures begins a an amazing film one of the great films from the
director of Totally Mini by the way.
So we got a.
Wow.
We'll cover this.
This is I'm excited to watch this.
Probably his whole filmography we got to do.
I don't know.
I mean that taps me out in terms of what to say about the dunes.
I just I love it.
It's so cool.
What a good idea.
Steve Wynn is clearly a bad man but you know what a what a good idea.
A bad man with a good idea.
Him realizing he could coordinate all this and make pirates blow up a building.
I would like boy we need something this cool to happen in this in this bad year in this
bad stretch that would unite everybody if something this stupid happened.
I was trying to think of like how you could top it and it's like is there a way like
Godzilla versus Kong is coming out.
I guess you'd have to do CGI but I mean I guess you could do it if you map CGI over
a building and make it look like maybe Godzilla had destroyed a building and it was a controlled
demolition like something along these lines.
I like it practical of course but I'm just trying to innovate in the space.
I think there's a way to do it you know that can bring new excitement to watching a building
fall down.
Well.
It's cool.
What you do is you finally figure out the physics of the one of the best unbuilt Vegas
attractions the full sized King Kong that you would ride in that was going to climb
the stratosphere every day.
What.
Yeah.
Whoa.
That one's news to me.
I'll send you I'll send you a video.
It's in the right.
It's stratosphere Expedition theme park and it's like you would enter you would enter
where on you would sit in his chest and it could go down the building.
You know I was hoping you would climb into his urethra.
I don't know how you enter.
I don't maybe climb in the very spacious plenty of rooms.
Yeah.
Well where else.
What other hole is there.
It'd be.
Than his butt.
I mean that's why if it folded down a stairway up from his butt.
But like I guess his anus.
Yeah.
Would be bigger.
I think what kind of like giggles when you got in.
Yeah.
I think what happened was they found out this would be mechanically impossible to create
and build to run every day.
Oh that's quitter talk.
Yeah.
Man that's so cool.
Oh God.
I want to know everything about that.
I can't wait to watch that video.
You know you should have gotten into he should have been wearing like a little barrel around
his neck like a Saint Bernard saving people in like the Arctic.
And then you got into the barrel and you could see there's like a window in the barrel.
The post being inside here in his body.
Yeah.
It's like crazy.
Why does he have a weird like a window on his chest.
Yeah.
There's no real justification of a translucent part of your chest.
No one should have that.
Right.
So we'll look into this more.
I'm obsessed with the movie where King Kong gets a heart transplant.
So if you were inside his mechanical heart which is shoved into his chest.
Oh yeah.
I would allow.
You could help beat like make it beat.
Oh yeah.
Oh you have to like operate.
You got to like pull levers and yeah.
Pedal a bicycle.
That's your keeping key.
You're keeping King Kong alive.
That would be the most stressful thing for me as a kid.
He's going to die.
My God.
Dad you're not doing it.
You're not doing it enough.
You're killing him.
Daddy.
Blood is on your hands.
Well if you want to kill the beast.
If he wanted to be faithful you'd have to have him get to the top and then like a plane
or a helicopter on a pole would have to come around shoot him and have him fall off the
stratosphere like a drop ride and that's how you get back to the ground.
But then.
Sure.
That would be true to the films but then you would be getting off a dead King Kong.
The greatest thing ever.
Oh my God.
I have any version of this.
Yeah.
And so bad.
We just wind it down because we still haven't even talked about the one that just happened.
Yes.
And it says you know it's an unfair comparison to go from but maybe not unfair because this
should have been cooler I think.
To go from the best one the pirate one to the one that just happened Trump Plaza in Atlantic
City.
Jason I know both woke up to to watch it.
Which was nice and fun but you know there were there wasn't the spectacle.
It was a very good implosion.
I'm not arguing that.
Yes.
Yeah this was I mean it was built in the mid 80s Trump Plaza.
They marketed it as Atlantic City centerpiece which is kind of a trick because they're trying
to you know like centerpiece beautiful elegant luxurious in-ringed and it's a very cool
luxurious in reality it is kind of smack in the center of the boardwalk.
It's smack in the center of the of the city.
So that is both literal and metaphorical the centerpiece thing and it it was sold like
Trump ate it in Atlantic City in the 2000s Trump Plaza Trump Toshima Hall Trump Marina
all closed.
Carl I can the Raider capitalist bought it and just shut it down like he didn't redo
it he didn't keep it going it was just empty for years and pieces started to fall off it
onto the historical Atlantic City boardwalk.
God did anyone get hurt by the building.
I think people were OK but they're like we got to do something about this and should
say this was this was the main tower of it is not the whole there's still pieces like
for example the smaller building that the Rainforest Cafe that consistently survives
the financial difficulties of Trump Plaza still going strong.
They like sued their way into being able to still operate because I didn't understand
the I was picturing like it's in the basement of a collapsing building.
Why would you keep this going but now that I've seen now I've seen the geography and
it's really removed it is next to that bad other building with like a like this like
red triangle that's just been rusting away since Trump got out of there.
But yeah it's very distant of course it could keep operating but it's it's close on one
side to Caesar's Palace which is not as massive as the Vegas one but significantly large and
that's where a lot of the press watch the implosion.
You could pay ten dollars to park and watch from your car in a safe distance away in a
parking lot due to city ordinances that say all city events have to charge ten dollars
for parking which I thought was very funny.
The other side of Trump Plaza is the historic now called Boardwalk Hall which used to be
called the Atlantic City Convention Center.
And that was notable for holding the Miss America pageant for decades and decades.
Where all the villains hung out.
Yes and more and of course WrestleMania 4 and 5.
Yes I believe that's right.
Sponsored by Trump Plaza.
So in the broadcast it's announced as coming to you from Trump Plaza.
But it's not.
It's yet another one of those little lies.
It's technically next door.
Yes.
That's right.
So that is a historical landmark that they had to make sure was not damaged by a massive
implosion.
Oh that's right there.
Yeah.
That was also that I believe that that was the venue for I mean a couple of big boxing
matches but Mike Tyson fight where this group hung out.
Look at this photo.
Let's go down the line.
Nicholson, Beatty, Larry King, Donald Trump deep in conversation with or perhaps Paul
Simon all at the same table and just off running around somewhere with his little growth to
to gross toothy mouth is old Donald Trump Jr.
Yeah it's what a what a array of idiots.
I mean some of these people are cool.
I like a couple of them but RIP Larry.
But what a lineup like the history of this place.
I also didn't just to throw in another Trump Plaza thing.
I didn't know that it whenever it opened up it opened up at 2 p.m.
on a certain day and at 2 40 an alarm went off and the building had to be evacuated.
So it survived 40 minutes of operation.
And just the beginning of a long bizarre legacy.
Yeah there's a crazy story about like a professional gambler who took them for a ride like who
was just playing like he was just racking up the winds at Trump Plaza and they were
like we got to do something about this guy.
And it's so funny it happened early on because there was a lot of pop in circumstance when
this this one opened it was pretty sizable.
Again it's very centrally located.
If you if you come in through one bridge of Atlantic City you pretty much go smack into
like Caesars and Trump Plaza area and it was just a high sore for years and years and
yes started crumbling.
So there I was to say Jason you have your personal relationship with this place at
anything you have anything.
I I don't have a lot.
I've been to a lot of places.
I don't have a lot.
I've been to that rainforest cafe for sure.
I know that we were more of a Caesars family because that's where Plan Hollywood was and
we like to go there.
What a place man.
Occasionally we would check down to the Trump Taj Mahal which even as a preteen I knew I
was like I don't know are you so this is uncomfortable.
It was like gross right.
Yeah it looks like shit like Donald Trump like the Golden Toilet.
Like trying to replicate Indian design and culture and like a massive land world landmark.
But with the Trump aesthetic and then you have to walk through this to get to the Hardrock
Cafe on the word.
The Trump Taj Mahal was taken over by the Hardrock people.
That is like the newest casino in the land city the Hardrock casino.
And I didn't know.
All right here comes just a big like here comes the Expendables.
I didn't know the history of what started as Trump Castle one of the stupidest names ever
then became Trump Marina and then it just you know languished for a while as all of them
did and then it was almost bought by Hardrock then almost bought by Buffett almost made
into a Margaritaville hotel but eventually finally turned into a Golden Nugget after
it was bought by Landry's and our friend Mr. Boot in the Ass himself Tillman Fertitta.
All of everybody every character from the show comes to play when it's implosion time.
And that I have characters I've been to Trump Marina now Golden Nugget that is on the that
is on the Bay that is by.
That's removed.
Yeah that's removed.
That's by the Borgata which is like the nicest casino which is an MGM casino.
Steve Wynn tried to get a Le Jardin I think was called he tried to get a different project
off the ground convinced the city to build like a road going to it and then backed out
of it eventually MGM would come in and build the Borgata which is very nice.
And then the Golden Nugget is kind of it is smaller but I think I ate at the the Chart
House at the Golden Nugget and there's another there's a Landry's restaurant another land
restaurant and there's like a an Italian place in there I ate there like right before we
started doing the show or like right after we had started doing the show before we discovered
all these characters.
Wow knowing that we cared about Landry's yeah I think we found it all together.
But I know you guys you've never been to Atlantic City of course right.
No no I want to now.
I didn't I when I dropped off your Christmas gifts I dropped off some envelopes for you
to open.
Oh yes oh my god yeah.
So there's been an envelope sitting in front of Mike and I this whole time.
If you want to open it to give you the full experience.
Oh boy.
All right I'm gonna make I'm gonna let everyone hear it yeah yeah.
This is binaural audio.
Creepy.
It's relaxing like ASMR.
That's right.
It you know I didn't want it to be the only remnant of the building to just be an eight
story pile of rubble that it will take June to clear take until June to clear out.
So I went digging and found there's a large market of casino detritus on eBay.
Ah we got some the aforementioned what's the variety what do they call the cards.
The cancel deck.
Cancel deck we have a Trump plot.
Oh my god.
I mean Jason I this is so thoughtful thank you.
Have you just put a curse on Scott and I's apartment.
But no that's okay.
I've got one too.
Okay all three of us.
Anything that says Trump in it.
I you have Trump Plaza canceled decks and it came in a pack and I have one too.
And and postcards.
Mike.
Wow it's an old school postcard too.
Yeah and Mike your postcard I believe is just the you can just see the how gray much of Trump Plaza was.
But Scott yours has the Trump Plaza and the Trump Taj Mahal in early 90s Photoshop.
It's just laid on top of each other.
Those buildings could not come together in an impossible way in an impossible way and those buildings could not be farther apart.
So they are nowhere near each other.
Wow.
There's also an ad for a draping down the side for Cirque du Soleil show called Cirque Dreams Jungle Fantasy.
That's DCA level fonts.
Boy that is hideous.
This is a really big elephant.
This is just a terrible item.
I'm very happy to have it.
Yeah.
Wow thank you Jason.
Cursed objects for everyone.
Yeah.
Geez.
Piece of history now.
It's now ash as the news anchors would say.
I.
Yeah.
This seems like a garbage place like this.
This must have been a bummer to be in here.
I'd imagine even when it was at its height.
Yeah.
Are you saying the guy whose name on the building maybe didn't pay any attention to something after he built it or take care of it or let it decay.
Is that what you're insinuating.
Wanted to make a big PR splash and then not really have to deal with any of the problems that happen.
I have the stamina for anything.
Well he did go out of his way to sue an old lady to get her out of her house because this is an up esc scenario where there's a woman who had like a three story building that's been that had been there since before the 50s and she had to go to the
And Trump was trying to get this he was claiming was dilapidated and you look at it and like it's fine.
It's like old but who cares.
And he was trying to sue so that he could demolish it and build a parking lot for limousines.
What an idiot.
There's not one story about this man that isn't annoying.
And then there's you can watch a lot of the stuff that's going on in the back of the car.
There's a story about this man that isn't annoying.
And then there's a you can watch an old news report where he's actually being challenged on this a little bit like well why you know she has the right to be there.
You can't just have people come in and say you have to leave your and he's going on about like what Jason said there's a road there's a road that takes you right into the heart of Atlantic City and they drive in and they see this ugly buildings hideous building when they could instead be seeing a beautiful fountain or beautiful.
Other things which would be good.
This is a quote from the man who would be president.
I don't believe it doesn't sound like him.
Beautiful other things that would be good.
Well, he's more.
Yeah, he got way more.
Yeah, well, I'll tell you.
Orator.
I went looking for this because it's headed unfortunately sold.
I'll tell you what you see.
You see a giant emblem.
This Trump Plaza this ugly stamp like it's a fake.
Royal stamp you would see a fake presidential seal now that he sent the tag letter on that's like a made up that's nothing.
Yeah, you would see that three stories high on the side of this gray building.
That said, I'm sure if you saw Liza the one and only I'm sure this residency was good because she was.
I would love I would love to see Liza the one and only I've been in a big Liza phase lately.
Very much love to also.
I think listeners you will be heartened to know that a lot of the casino detritus online buttons postcards decks.
Don't worry.
The Trump stuff did not go up in value.
It's good news.
Good.
Well, that's it's going to go way down when I go through every single one of these cards and on the four mentions of Trump Trump's name on each one.
I put an asterisk instead of the you.
Well, you know, show him.
I understand why people are doing this.
I don't even say I don't even say his name.
I usually just say 45 and I think that's pretty cool.
Good for you.
You know what?
For me.
This, you know, if you are looking for Trump revenge in some mild way, I mean, this is pretty great.
Like if this is like if you're mad at him, then seeing like this this albatross of a bad hotel he built go down and smoke.
It's pretty great.
I don't you know, I mean, it's hollow.
I don't know if he cares.
Although maybe he probably was watching this live and grumbling at it.
And, you know, we know he's up early.
First of all, yeah, this guy doesn't sleep.
So he probably did watch it and was mad.
I shouldn't discount that.
He's very petty.
Not well liked in Atlantic City, not well liked by the hundreds, if not thousands who were employed at these casinos that all suddenly closed during the economic downturn.
I should add or right afterwards.
And Carl Icahn, of course, did not keep them employed or did not take care of them.
I believe just canceled union contracts outright.
Real shady stuff.
I don't know how this all I'm not a smart person.
But I is generally the story that he put his own personal debts onto the casinos, which made them fail.
But his brand was able to like narrowly escape out of the rubble.
Like Donald Trump never went bankrupt, but Trump, the organization did.
So he technically could say I didn't go bankrupt.
It's it's something like that.
Like he put too much.
He made the casinos fail, basically.
I believe that's correct.
Yeah, it's that thing where it's like people buy debt and somehow make money.
And like I don't I for one don't understand it, but it seems insane.
Shell shell game, big shell game.
Yeah.
No one suffers any consequences for anything.
They lose 400 million dollars.
It doesn't matter.
But I don't care.
I remember meeting a waiter.
I think I was at Harrah.
I think I was at the Guy Fieri steakhouse at Harrah and just hearing this like it is a company town.
It's like an entertainment town like Orlando or Vega.
And he had just worked.
Oh, I was a cater waiter.
I was a room service waiter.
It's just all over the island at all the different casinos and like really hit hard when like a third of the casinos closed and the Trump ones kind of were around then or followed then.
Was he had so many that he would be if all of those go down and every like the whole thing.
And oh my God, he had all his other like failed shit.
I didn't know any of this that he he owned the pier at one point in time and he let's keep bringing in things we like.
There was a point in time where he claimed he'd made a deal with Six Flags and that they were going to do a little mini Six Flags on the pier.
Trump Six Flags over Trump Pier.
I don't know if that was going to be the name, but maybe.
And then he claimed Sega was going to do something and none of it happened.
So yeah, casinos fail.
Pier project still is.
It's not really anything there, right?
Well, anything on the Six Flags.
The Six Flags deal fell apart because he wanted all six to be Confederate flags.
I believe that the pier in question, the one you can look out and look, you could stand on the third floor.
It's a they turn it into an upscale mall.
If we're talking about the same pier.
And you could stand on the third floor and look down at the Rainforest Cafe, which I believe I did explaining like, yeah, so Trump Plaza closed, but this Rainforest Cafe got a contract to get their own utility line so they could stay open.
That is owned by Caesars.
I think Caesars owned it, sold it.
It was like a dirt mall for years.
It was like a just a mall of like beach supplies and like newspapers, newspapers, cigarettes, books, paperback books, newspapers.
And then eventually it tried to go upscale.
It got a Apple Store.
I believe that is the first it sugar in that location.
Oh, that was the flagship.
Yeah.
So but it fell on hard times, too.
They tried to turn it into like Pleasure Island, like a bunch of little bars with different themes and they'd all be fun.
And I went the opening summer, my family went and we're like, no one's here.
It's it's it's like 8 p.m. on a Thursday night in July.
This place should be packed and no one was there.
Man.
Yikes. Tragic.
Yeah.
He just blew up the whole thing.
And if it is considered the center of Atlantic City and the center goes down, then yeah, what do you what do you have?
So it seems like to take this place out, it like I read that the mayor, the guy who is now the mayor made it one of his promises.
We will implode this building, which just signifies because we could put so they don't know what they're putting there yet.
But we can put something that serves as like a beacon for what will come in Atlantic City instead of this rotting.
Yeah.
Remember a thing from the past?
He was I believe he was putting up like images on social media of like a movie poster for this Trump Plaza Plaza explosion.
I like that.
That's spectacle.
And I could not find them.
I'll try to locate see if we can locate them.
But yeah, I mean, it's a resilience and it's had a lot of different transformations.
Like my parents, my grandparents on my mom's side had their honeymoon in Atlantic City in the 40s when he was on leave from the war.
And and so it's had a lot of transformations from like the Victorian seaside kind of town to the gambling comes in in the 70s and stuff and has its ups and downs and was on an upswing.
That hard rock was a big deal.
And then coronavirus, I'm sure, is not helping matters for the city.
But yeah, can I propose let's build the Starship Enterprise there?
But King Kong is sleeping on top of it.
Oh, and you get to climb in his asshole and shockingly brazen for you, Mike.
Mike, I love it.
Hey, I said after 90 minutes on these, I get punchy.
Yeah.
You know what? Right past the end of the one end of the boardwalk, there is a huge plot of seaside land that would be perfect for it.
You just got have to get it out of the hands of its owner, which checking my notes is Jared Kushner.
OK, great.
No, no, no.
Here's the deal. I could sell Jared Kushner on people climbing into King Kong's asshole in 10 minutes.
Give me 10 minutes with Kushner and I could sell him on this idea.
Starship Enterprise, King Kong, put them together.
Wait, so he's sleeping on it so you don't go into the enterprise.
Maybe you can go into both.
I can go into both.
It's probably you have to walk.
You have to get to the bridge on the Enterprise and then there's some way out the top of the Enterprise and that's where Kong is.
You can slide out of his drool down into the cockpit.
That's good too.
I mean, there's multiple ways in, I think.
You can go in his nostrils.
You can go in his urethra.
There's plenty of ways. Ears.
This is the future. This is where Atlantis, yeah, no more of this disgusting building.
Let's put in something with class.
Something with class and revisit a couple old ideas and we can freshen them both up and add them.
That's what I think is good.
This sounds great. This sounds really good.
What do we think of the implosion in general?
I think we're all agreed that we just don't...
There wasn't even, I don't think, the news 13 level of...
I woke up early thinking I'd find some news anchors having fun or maybe my old friends, Steve Krupke or whatever.
It was just a bunch of silent cameras.
Well, I found...
It's back to basics.
NBC 10, the Philadelphia affiliate, had a helicopter over the water, over the ocean, and they caught it from a certain angle.
I think there's a roundup of that.
I did catch the tail end of it.
I was trying to video capture it and then the broadcast ended.
But there was one news anchor and I didn't get her exact wording, but what she said was something like,
You know, I'm just a lay person, but that looked great.
I like that. Yeah.
And I agree. It was awesome.
It kind of did this little swirl as it went down.
It was very fast. It felt faster than any of these.
They did an amazing job.
Yeah.
It's like back... Here's what I think.
It's back to basics.
It's like YouTube, beautiful day, back to what started this whole thing.
And then now we can go forward to try it.
YouTube's a bad comparison because they never went forward.
They just kept trying to do the same thing.
But back to basics, then we can sort of now innovate.
So it's like it's a good fun thing to watch.
But yes, after we're doing some research on these other ones, how can you even...
How can you be satisfied after a pirate was involved?
Yeah. I mean, they did it at 9.07 in the morning East Coast time.
Yeah.
Morning time, tougher for the West Coast.
Yeah. But granted...
With all of the...
It was 27 degrees outside.
So I don't know if they could have gotten as much as the Vegas crowds,
a more temperate climate Vegas.
Right. Oof.
You know, with so much Trump animosity also, you'd think that there would be like...
They didn't want to make it political, but you can't help but feel that way.
And it's a metaphor for the crumbling of the empire.
Just as his building crumbles, so does his presidency.
Cut to him winning in 2024 easily.
We're all fucking under his thumb again.
But I don't know. It did feel good in that moment.
Like it is symbolic.
So like what could they have done that would have been satisfying to like...
To what we're all kind of feeling about him in the end of the run?
Or just something cool that doesn't have anything to do with Donald Trump?
Well, there's some real dark things I could think of that I don't even want to say out loud.
And I won't say it, but let's think of some more...
King Kong takes a big dump, like a really fast dump that shoots out and hits the building in the base.
King Kong takes Donald Trump and shoves him inside of his butt.
And then farts him out?
And farts Trump out at the building, knocking the building down.
Yes, perfect.
Man, Ben Shapiro would really hate our podcast if he's been a fan of it up until now.
Oh, sorry, Ben.
We're not getting him.
That was too lewd.
He liked how good we were on the main feed and now he's not liking me.
He loves seat. Ben Shapiro says the word seat all the time.
I think like the end of Dark Knight, you let him fall a little much like the Joker, but then you throw a batarang.
Like someone catches you, because you're better than him.
Justice was done correctly.
Because you need to think about what you've done.
It's too easy to just let you fall.
I think it would be good if they had projected all the famous people that he was like casually acquainted with that he thought he was good friends with on the building saying they hate him.
Because those are the people he cares about the most, are like famous people.
He's so mad at Hollywood because he's like desperate for like their attention and their love, which he can truly not get now.
Nicholson Beatty, everyone in that photo.
Larry King, one of the last pieces of footage of Larry King.
Fuck you, Donald.
Yeah, if you get like people like that.
I mean, it's probably like Nicholson.
He probably had never seen a Jack Nicholson movie.
Let's be honest.
He just Trump like Stephen Seagal movies and that's about the top.
That's about as sophisticated as he gets.
But like even if you do, are you an actor?
Stephen Seagal, I'm sure still supported him.
But if you just paid Stephen Seagal, say like a hundred bucks, he would be like, you just say like, fuck you, Trump.
You're dead to me.
And then like projected on the building and then you get like 50 of them and then you take the thing down.
Well, I think you do get some justice for Atlantic City as an option.
And as I described that pier with them all, the pier he might have owned might have been I think what is now Steel Pier.
There's a pier right by what was Trump Taj Mahal with amusement attractions.
And I could see him lying his way of like these old roller coasters, these old shitty rides.
You know, yes, six flags will come in and fix these right up.
But I believe on one of those peers or maybe one that's been since demolished, the original Steel Pier had a high diving course,
which would was a horse that would climb a ladder to a high dive board and dive into a pool.
And so I think you make him climb the ladder.
You rebuild this platform in the pool and you let the residents throw some Jersey fresh tomatoes up until he goes off the end of the high dive into the horse pool.
Trump in the horse pool is pretty good. Yeah.
Wait, does that trigger the explosion somehow?
Like is there is that like then a mousetrap situation where like then the water from the pool, the tank runs a lot like hits a wire and then.
Oh, yeah, I guess that should probably explode something.
Well, I think there's another Trump Plaza tower where there's another building.
You know, there's still some ancillary buildings.
I'm like almost going backwards.
Like if they would, you're right, there will be other ones to blow up.
Yeah, I'm just saying what they could have done to this one.
Oh, to this one. Yeah.
And that triggers the explosion.
And you just you don't tell that that they're actually very far apart.
You cheat it like the magic of, you know, the Treasure Island cannonballs, the postcard.
Well, maybe I kind of want to flash back to the to the Treasure Island implosion.
Steve Wynn, an enemy of Trump's.
So for him to be proven the winner, Steve, Steve, you win everything.
You're great. Nothing to worry about here.
So you let Steve come back in with a pirate ship is it's all along the water is all on the beach.
So he pulls up and then he nods to somebody in a pirate hat and he announces with a bullhorn
Captain of Captain of the Clintonia.
Are you ready, ma'am?
And then it's Hillary and Hillary fires the cannon.
And was there was there a good Hillary fray?
Nevertheless, I resisted.
And then what is there?
What was her friend?
What's a good Hillary phrase to?
Well, oh, shoot.
What was the I'm just chilling on the Britannia.
Stronger together, stronger together.
Pokemon go into the building.
Yeah, that's good.
I mean, if the Pots of America guys could be involved to to help with all that stuff, I think that's a great.
They're going to write.
Oh, yeah. Great zingers.
Make more money than we've ever seen in our lives.
Yeah, I this the win connection would be fitting because the you know, the war for the shore, I think it's the book is called Trump brand.
Steve pretty much ran Trump won Trump ran Steve went out of town basically, you know, in the casino wars of the 70s and 80s.
Wow. So he comes back on the boat, one of his rivals, maybe everybody who kind of feuded with Kathy Griffin.
It's not there. OK, great, great. Yeah.
Who was who did Trump make an enemy of General Mattis, General Mattis, Matt Dogg Mattis, Kristen Stewart's on there.
Oh, you're right. Yes.
Oh, that middler, that middler, John Bolton, you know, all the enemies.
Yeah. Scaramouche.
That's great. Oh, yeah.
Dancing the dancing potato.
What was that idiot's name? The one on Dancing with the Stars is just like on Spicer Spicer.
Yes. I was pretty sure there was maybe like a potato spokesman I had forgotten about in the four years when you said that.
I mean, he could have taken some shots at like an Uraida mascot or like Mr. Mr. Peanut.
There's a windmill. There's a dancing windmill that comes on because he hates windmills.
So just a I think a pirate ship of his enemies blowing up the boat. How did they miss this?
This should have been done. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. If only I think but I think also I think just do all of them.
I think I'll then also have the horse falling and then of course replace it with King Kong sleeping on Enterprise.
Yeah, I think that's great.
Put your makeup on, fix your hair up pretty and meet me tonight at the Trump Plaza of Explosion Viewing Area.
Well, that's been the commercial. Yeah, that should have been a Jeep commercial.
And this should. Yeah, true. With that song at the beginning with Sinbad hosting and with appearances from my favorite news crew,
Mark Sayers and Steve Kruppi and Ted Tester and Michael Gieser.
And they all we all blow this up. We blow this up for them.
This should have been and it should have they should have done this instead of that inauguration with Tom Hanks and Katy Perry.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. The inauguration should have been.
Wait, what is this? What do you know?
You know, they did the inauguration special with Katy Perry and Biden.
Yeah, Biden. Yeah, Biden and an empty Lincoln Memorial and the new radicals.
I didn't know the new radical. I knew about the new radicals. Yeah.
Mm hmm. Yeah. Well, yes, everybody did. So, yeah, this should have been it.
We could have planned this thing, taken everything back to its 90s roots.
Next time, let us Biden. If you get reelected, blow up another Trump building of your choice and bring us on to do it.
Yeah, we're ready. We're ready.
That just like the captain of the Britannia.
And well, that was wonderful. We survived podcast, the ride casino implosions.
Boy, oh, boy. So nice to see so many great old friends and enemies again.
A topic with so much that we actually went as long as we used to have the energy to in person.
That's right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
But we go along because we love you implosions. Thanks for everything. We hope you maintain through the next century.
And when the podcast is done, when we decide that we're done, we should build the thing in our logo as a literal item, like 3D printed.
And we should implode it. And that's how I guess the ride ends.
And it'll be a whole celebration. Yeah, I have a feeling King Kong will be involved.
You sure will. Well, whenever that happens, let's get ready to crumble.
And you please let's get ready to stay subscribed for more stuff like this coming next month. So long, everybody. Bye bye.