Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to what is now the most important election
of our lifetimes.
Today on Podcast The Ride, we will be determining
once and for all what is the greatest music video
filmed at Universal Studios Florida.
I'm Scott Gardner, joined for this momentous occasion
by Mike Carlson.
I am here and I am in a very serious mood.
And I'm also in a philosophical mood
because of what I'll be discussing today
because there's so much wisdom also
in what I will be talking about.
Yeah, I'd say so.
That's a song that goes there that addresses a lot.
Boy, boy does it.
We'll save it.
Jason Sheridan also here for this weighty occasion.
Yes, thank you so much, Scott.
And I just wanna say hello again to my fellow hosts
and our second gate listeners,
our wonderful second gate listeners.
But most importantly, say hello to myself.
Because that's what I'm gonna be talking about a lot today.
Okay, very good vague hints.
Yeah.
That's so vague.
Now, we may have given away some of what these music videos
are in a tweet or something or other,
but if you don't know, we'll splay them out slowly.
But I thought this would be a fun topic.
Many things have been filmed at Universal Studios Florida,
many feature films, many wrestling events,
maybe many bizarre Crayola-sponsored VHSs,
if you know that one.
Lots of great film productions.
But I think three of the greatest are for music videos
that happen to be for,
I think three of the greatest songs ever made.
I think, yeah, indisputably.
I think all three of the things that we're gonna talk about
reflect the Orlando culture in specific ways.
So they're all representative of different Orlando facets,
which I think is great.
They aren't just random.
And I can't wait to talk about them.
Yeah, we're gonna, there's definitely, of course,
overlap in all of the videos.
I mean, I guess you're always gonna find overlap
in popular music.
But I think that you're dealing with three
stylistically different pieces here, musically and visually.
Yeah, yeah, indeed.
But now there's something that I don't think
you guys know about, which is that I did like a little,
I did a little switch out of mine.
Maybe I didn't address this with you guys
because this episode idea was inspired by
a 90s Beach Boys video that I saw,
that I saw, I mean, look, I know it.
I just re-saw it for the song Hot Fun in the Summertime.
It re-imagines the Sly and the Family Stone,
Hot Fun in the Summertime, but with a twist.
What if it was done by very white people?
It's a fun video.
The Beach Boys jam out with child versions of themselves,
and I recommend to anyone to watch it.
But I was thinking like, oh, it reminded me
of these other music videos and like,
what about Universal Studios thing?
But technically that one is Universal Hollywood.
So I think it does not count.
So I had to think of a new music video
from Universal Florida.
And luckily there was one, which I can reveal to you now.
If you don't mind me kicking it off.
Go ahead, yes, please.
We're all kind of representing one.
Yeah, if you go first, I'll go second,
and we'll end on Mike.
Cause I know once we get to Mike,
we're not gonna be able to,
once that ball starts rolling downhill,
it's not gonna be able to stop.
Right, it's not gonna be possible.
I will say, I'm glad you actually
thrown that Beach Boys video out
because I found it a bit racy.
Well, now remind me why.
I know that this is a video, again,
to take a black art and do it very white.
It was like the vibe of do the right thing a little bit
where it's a sweltering day on the street corner.
And we're letting the fire hydrants loose and all that.
And does that end up where like hosing girls down?
Is that what goes on?
I mean, Mike Love is not hosing girls down directly,
but there's a lot of long like male gaze woman
taking her shirt off close up on her body,
like very long closeups on it.
Which for a Beach Boys video,
I go, that's a little too much.
Sure.
And then there's a lot,
and then you of course cut back to a bunch of 60 year olds.
Yeah, then in the 90s.
And you're like, that's a little,
and look, my video has women in bathing suits,
but they're much, it's quicker shots.
They're much more tasteful, I believe.
So thank you, Scott, for taking care of the problem
I already had with the potential video.
Not forcing you to go down this avenue.
Yeah, there's a whiplash that comes from the combo
of bikini babes and very old men in neon hats
that cover that they are very much bald.
Right.
I'm disappointed to not talk about it,
but I'm also, I'm happy to talk about this other one.
There's this music video that's been burned in my brain
for a long time.
When I say that the three videos
we're gonna talk about today reflect the Orlando culture.
Well, when you think of Orlando and you think about music,
you of course think about the big trend
that came from Orlando, it was born in Orlando,
and that's boy bands.
Orlando's the home of the Backstreet Boys in sync.
And of course, we all know it,
the most popular best boy band of all.
Everybody say it with me, Natural.
You know, Natural, right?
Of course.
Natural.
Natural was the final boy band attempted by Lou Pearlman.
And you know, last time's the charm.
I think he hit it out of the park with this one.
Natural put out an album in 2002 called Keep It Natural.
And why the name Natural?
Well, because the gimmick of Natural
is that they also played their own instruments.
They don't just dance.
By this point, it had been, you know,
the prefab nature of the boy bands had been called out.
We want people who actually have some musical talent.
So that's why these guys actually played their instruments.
Let me familiarize you guys with Natural a little bit.
So here is the gang.
Let me share the screen.
I mean, you know I'm just reacquainting you,
but hey, here they are, the five guys.
All with varying degrees of spiky, Dane Cook-esque hair.
And of course, in the middle is Big Papa himself, Lou,
in just like a blue collared businessman shirt,
just like dressed for his banker job
around all these leopard print bowling shirt guys.
It's like they're all smiling
because they're about to like handcuff him and arrest him.
Citizens arrest.
It looks like five people are holding back this monster.
If they weren't, yeah, if they weren't smiling,
you would think, oh, they're trying to detain this man.
This is finally, we're putting him away.
We're reading him his race.
It's funny that you mentioned that
because in looking for this photo,
I found another picture of Lou Perlman
and this one's with Joey Fatone, I believe,
and it's Lou smiling just this big
and he's putting handcuffs on Joey Fatone.
Oh my God.
It's a very disturbing photograph,
I believe taken at one of his NYPD themed pizza parlors.
Was there a conversation with all the boy bands
where they went, all right, we need to get handcuffs.
Let's just try to get, like, let's just try to arrest him,
do a citizens arrest.
And they're like, I don't know, is it gonna work?
All right, we know he has this pizza place.
There's probably some handcuffs hanging around.
If we can just do a little flip on him, then that's it.
This goes away.
Would have been a good plan.
Maybe they're trying it.
One of these guys might have handcuffs right now,
but it's not working.
These are especially disturbing photos
in social distancing time, watching these boys
forced hanging out with Lou.
Here they are on a staircase.
Why is he in all these photos?
I mean, don't answer the question.
I mean, I don't have an answer.
Honestly, it was hard to find a photo of them without Lou.
Was he in the band?
Did Lou put himself in this one?
I mean, technically, I mean, his contract within Sync
was that he is the sixth member,
something that he neglected to tell them
until deep into the process,
that he was when the money was doled out every month,
that he would, he'd take money off the top
and then get paid as member number six.
Jesus Christ.
Wow.
Crazy guy.
Crazy man.
No longer with us.
He also, by the way, wrote a song on this band's album.
I believe the first ever songwriting credit
attributed to Lou Pearlman.
I need to hear that.
Just imagine the boring song you've ever heard.
Imagine a song you would have written
when you learned your first two guitar chords.
You know, for a girlfriend who you didn't do anything with.
Okay, got it.
And here he is, a planet Hollywood with the guys.
So Lou, Lou constantly around.
The guys, by the way, let's just call them out by name.
Hey, Ben, Mark, Michael, other Michael and Patrick.
So that's natural.
And they, like I said, they shot a video at Universal Florida.
Why do I know any of this?
Because I was studying abroad in Germany in 2005
and watching whatever MTV equivalent out there.
And at some point this music video came on
and it caught my eye because it was clearly
Universal Florida and it made me homesick for America
and the best place in America, Universal Florida.
And mainly I was like, wait, still boy bands in 2005.
I guess in Germany it's still passed, I don't know.
But let's just skim through this video a little bit.
And I guess, okay, so I don't know what our criteria are
other than just like general quality and is it a good song?
But I guess like, do we think like back lot coverage
or like creativity of reappropriation
of universal environments?
I, yes, I completely, that was gonna be one of my criteria
because Beach Boys Hot Fun in the summertime
is very limited in its scope of what it's showing
of the actual park.
And I was gonna dock at points for that
because my video is a lot more of the actual area
and I think that's good.
We wanna see more of Universal Florida.
Yours is kind of one to beat, I would say in that area.
It definitely makes its way around
and uses a lot of the themed environments creatively.
But here, let me show you around the natural song,
Put Your Arms Around Me.
We're in the entrance plaza a lot.
We're hanging out by the dock.
I think we're in sort of like the Jaws zone.
Here's the boys and they are practicing instruments
a little bit and banging on the dock, but maybe they work.
Maybe they're like boatsmen, I'm not sure,
dreaming of musical stardom.
They see some girls.
Maybe a way to get the girls' attention
is a battle of the bands, which is,
wait, they're already on the flyer though,
so I guess this isn't them hearing about the battle
of the bands for the first time.
Does that say they're playing at Ugly Burger?
Yeah, or is that a band?
Is that another band that they're playing against?
Perhaps, yeah.
Fictitious Chickens is one.
Right, yeah, you're right, that might be another band.
Great fonts all around on here.
So we cover Jaws zone, like Cape Cod zone.
It's nice to see that.
Mainly we're in this entrance plaza,
which I remember was the thing that I liked
when I saw it many years ago.
I really like that entrance plaza.
It's kind of like, I don't know why to explain
to you anything that's good about it,
but that big gate, just any time I'm in there,
I have so much anticipation for the day
and the adventures I'll be going on
and the friends I'll be seeing.
So it's nice to be in there.
So you know, there's shirtless and stuff.
Let me try to find the chorus
and give you a taste of what natural's all about.
I'm standing still.
Come back and say that you will.
Put your arms around me.
You're the one and only.
I'll be here if you let your heart show the way.
Always be beside me.
Put your arms around me.
I'll be here when the dawn is the same.
You tell me.
How you feel about that?
This guy has a shirt that looks like a Pope caught,
like a Catholic priest collar.
Yeah, you see tuxedo t-shirts,
but you don't usually see a Catholic priest garb as shirts.
This sounds like a B-side of the fray or something.
That's a good band to call.
I was thinking about,
I don't really know what this band is too much,
but the calling, is this what the calling is like?
Yeah, what does the calling do?
I know the calling.
I don't know.
I just know the name and that they're pretty, right?
Is the calling pretty?
The calling does, oh yeah, wherever you will go,
but I could, if I would, I'll go wherever you will go.
Way up high, I can keep going.
Or down low.
Jason and I know it.
These songs just remind me of being worried
that if I started dating somebody and that's what they liked
that I would have to pretend to like it.
You mean then or now?
It doesn't seem likely now so much.
Could there be anyone who loves,
their favorite music is still the calling,
Lifehouse, the fray, and natural.
My girlfriend at the time was a big Lifehouse
and Vertical Horizon.
Oh, Vertical, right, yeah, yeah.
Lifehouse has Hanging By A Moment, which I like,
but is in this genre, I feel.
Unlike Lifehouse, Natural was not played every other
song block on top 40 stations.
Oh God.
Yeah, they wore that one out.
Vertical Horizon, there's like three hits from them
that just feel like they've been lost to time.
You pretty never hear those songs again.
Yeah, there's no radio station that is like,
only 2000s spiked collar, hookah shell kind of bands.
Yeah.
Is Fuel in this category or they're a little harder,
I guess.
I think they're a little harder.
They're a little harder, but it is around
a couple years prior to this.
Yellow Card.
That's more punk, that's more a little SoCal punk though.
Yeah, I think so.
Yeah, this song has no genre, pretty much.
It's not hard enough in any rock category
to force it to be a genre.
10 Half-Lifes after Matchbox 20.
There's nothing even resembling the goodness
of Matchbox 20 left.
Yes, the spark, the hard thrust of Matchbox 20.
Yeah, Natural does not hold a candle to Bent.
No, oh my God, Bent is a masterpiece compared to this.
Yeah, I will say though, this video,
this shot in the entryway, this kind of bluish gray,
if you read about early 2000s design choices,
this and the era of Blobjects,
I think we've talked about before,
the kind of liquidy metal, the plastic,
the blue and gray color schemes like this
come up a lot in design histories.
Well, music videos around this time were so tinty.
Let's just make the colors really crazy
and this will come up again, I think, with Jason,
the one that Jason was forced to associate with,
which all these videos were shot on film,
but then down-res for TV and there's no way
to get them back.
So they just, the quality is such garbage.
Right.
Also just the jib on this thing is too steep.
It makes me dizzy as if I'm going on Hollywood
rip ride rocket soon to be built just feet
from this location.
Forgive me, what is the name of the song?
Oh, Put Your Arms Around Me.
I'm just gonna put it into Apple Music
and see what it says is around that time.
And it appears natural is not in Apple Music.
Not even in it at all?
The US Marshalls still have the masters impounded.
It's evidence, yes.
At this point, they have like everything on here.
Yeah, I know it's weird when music slips through the crowd,
when there's an album that is not on Spotify
or any of them, it's very bizarre.
I would say skip past natural entirely
and go to another pseudo boy band
that also played instruments called Soul Decision.
I don't know if you remember Soul Decision.
I'm a big, I stand for Soul Decision.
The song faded.
Kinda faded, but I feel all right.
Think about making my move tonight.
It's a good one.
I remember that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's a catchy one, that one holds up.
Anyway, see we go through carnival games.
We're in that Jaws zone now.
We're still in entrance plaza.
We got a purple hair goatee guy.
I think really the thing that you have to dock this video
points for is that its best sequence
happens not in the parks.
Clearly the best part of the video,
which I'll play for you now.
Ah, would you come to round me?
Whoa.
Now, this seems to reference a film
and I don't know if you know the film,
but there's a, the filmmakers are the Wachowskis.
It's called The Matrix.
I think that's what it's nodding to.
It's an obscure film from the era.
They're like in a canyon environment.
There's lightning, digital lightning.
They're doing, there is the matrix effect.
They're in trench coats.
Maybe it's, yeah.
Or it's like an unsalvageable earth is where they are.
Or it's where Christopher Lambert takes some of the
combatants in Mortal Kombat, maybe.
Yeah, it's a Mortal Kombat level.
It's like a Mortal Kombat world.
The freeze jump.
Yeah.
Wow, this was good.
This is good, I like this part.
This is pretty good.
I think that the verses are pretty toothless
and I like this kind of more like
in sync breakdown-ish part.
I think maybe they should have leaned into Boy Band more.
But we come out of here and then here's where,
I think the only, I don't think Natural has a shot
at winning the tournament, but the only thing going for it
is that they are, they finished the thing at City Walk.
The big battle of the bands, I'll play it quietly.
Remember that big fountain?
I love that weird fountain.
It's kind of this double decker area.
All the Natural fans have gathered.
The steep jib continues.
So just nice to see City Walk at such a peak.
I mean, it's pretty new still at that point.
This is still City Walk Orlando Prime.
Not that it ever isn't, but you know what I mean.
Yeah, I like that it's at City Walk.
That's great.
Yeah, because it's, when did City Walk open in Orlando?
Do we know the date?
Yes, around 1999, same year as, I think end of 98 maybe?
They were projected early 99 at the latest
because then Islands of Adventure opens
at the start of the summer.
Well, I'll have to know it when we do it.
When we do the East Coast Saga.
Just say it, do it, yeah, do it.
I'll say it, okay, okay, I'll say no more.
Anyway, I mean, that gives you the gist of it.
There's not too much to speak of there,
but I just wanted to shout out Natural
for giving me a little shot of Orlando comfort.
I'd also like to say that them being a,
let's prove that we're not prefabricated band,
they were paired up with the original one of those,
The Monkeys.
They were the touring opener for The Monkeys
on a 2001 tour, which ended with Peter Tork being fired
due to excessive alcohol use.
Oh no, Peter.
We ended that tour with only two monkeys.
Replay, The Monkeys, there was that,
well, no, they didn't.
The Monkeys, the whole thing,
because they, Mike Nesmith would not tour with them
for the longest time.
And then he agreed to tour with them.
And then Peter Tork was back in the band.
And then Davey just dropped dead.
Oh, so they were finally together all again.
And then, hmm.
Yes, so then, yeah, so then it was just the three monkeys
without Davey Jones.
And then now it's weird,
like Mickey Dolan's and Mike Nesmith's monkey shows together.
It's very strange, like the configuration.
They apparently, in this time, went into the studio
and re-recorded the three big songs with Natural.
They were tricked into thinking
that Natural was gonna be something.
Wow.
I have to hear this.
Well, you can't, it was never released.
They recorded it, but never did anything with it.
Not like the, oh, sorry, go ahead.
I was just gonna, I know someone
who might be able to get their hands on this.
I knew, has the keys to Michael Nesmith's vault.
Yes, actually, yes.
Oh, hmm, friends in high places.
Yeah, yes.
Not like the album, Keep It Natural,
which was, while it did not chart in America,
it still did get around,
because it was a giveaway if you bought more than $12
worth of jewelry at Claire's.
So there might be some girls who were, you know,
buying some charms or something,
and ended up accidentally with a Natural in their bag.
Wow.
That's difficult.
That's like a garbage bag worth of jewelry from Claire's,
if memory serves their price points.
Oh, that's true, yes.
You're spending a lot of like 79 cent items.
Yeah, a lot of, I mean, and the person piercing your ears
is only gonna be a year or two older than you.
Like, you're really, really rolling the dice, Claire's.
So that's Natural, but I know it probably doesn't have
what it takes to go all the way,
but the next one very well might,
and I thank Jason for taking the lead on it.
Tell us about it.
Sure, well, you know, the Natural album, like you said,
didn't really chart, but let's go in the other direction
to with a song that came from an album at the time
viewed as kind of a dud,
because it only sold 6 million copies,
as opposed to the previous record by this band,
which sold 12 million copies.
And folks, you probably already know
who I'm talking about.
I'm talking about Creed and the music video
for My Sacrifice.
Now- Yeah, man, big song.
As opposed to Natural, a quiet one,
people don't really know that one.
My Sacrifice, major hit.
You could not, when you think about like Top 40 radio
in the early 2000s, like if you turned on a Top 40 station,
you were probably hearing this song or With Arms Wide Open,
you're probably hearing some Creed.
Unavoidable. Yes.
Yeah, and, you know, mixed feelings,
mixed feelings on Creed, because at the time,
I think we all kind of were like,
well, these songs are kind of earworms
and that's complicated because they suck.
Like this sucks, I hate this, but I can't avoid it.
And I somehow have learned all the words
because I have heard it so many times.
But I feel bad- I know the words,
but I also will fudge it because the way he sings is like,
yes.
Hello, my friend, meet you there.
A tale of bitter, silly, bitterly.
Like that's, as far as I know, that's what it is.
Yes. Yeah.
And I feel kind of bad for dumping on Creed
so much in the early 2000s,
because the more I read about poor Scott Stapp,
the man had a lot of substance abuse issues
was eventually diagnosed bipolar, thank God,
because yeah, he tried to kill himself in some crazy ways.
So that said, this music video-
Well, let's pin it on the other guys then
so we can make fun of them,
because this band sucks.
And I also just, right before you get into it,
what you brought up the album,
the album is called Weathered.
Yes, Weathered, that's correct.
Yeah, Weathered, the album Weathered.
And yeah, 6 million people own Weathered,
and this is the cover of Weathered.
This is this album 6 million people bought,
and this is the cover.
You can barely read the word weathered
with its pale spaced out font.
There's like an asymmetrical tree,
like it can't decide if it's all the way on the left
or in the middle,
and a man is chiseling the faces of the members into it,
but then it's just like the crappiest
Photoshop overlay you've ever-
Like, I don't-
If your younger cousin's band had this as the cover,
you'd find it hard to compliment,
like let alone the biggest band in America.
And what is the sun here?
The sun is like-
Sun's peeking out.
It's a blood orange.
Yeah.
Very strange.
It is some of the worst graphic design of all time.
I guess there's, it does kind of look like it's of its time,
but it looks like it's a bad version of it for its time too.
Yeah, there's better graphic design than this.
There's better awful graphic design
from the late 90s, early 2000s for sure.
I'd much rather look at any of the No Limit album covers.
I mean, that's bad graphic design,
but in the most delightful loopy way,
this is just-
It's so serious.
Yeah.
I look here, I have a, just real quick,
my, I didn't get a taste of music snobbishness until college.
So when Hire came out,
which sounds a lot like my sacrifice.
Yes.
Which do you think is better though?
Cause I'm torn on this.
I know, I know I have an answer.
It's my sacrifice.
Yeah, I think so.
And I also have, there's a reason,
there's also a special reason I feel like that as well.
But Hire came out and I was like, oh, okay.
And then I think it was like a couple of months,
and this is the same, my same relationship with Nickelback
when How You Remind Me came out,
where you're like, yeah, rock and roll man.
And then after a couple of months,
you're like, maybe this is bad, huh?
And then I was like, I don't know if I would've said
like it was bad, but then like a year or two later,
I was probably like, this sucks.
But then my sacrifice came out and I was like,
I think Creed was already like, ah, Creed.
But then the WWE used my sacrifice
on one of the greatest promo packages of all time.
And then on top of that, my friend Luke edited
a highlight reel of our backyard wrestling set
to my sacrifice.
Ah!
Perfect.
Which I know I needed to have today, but I will produce it
and we will look at it.
Yeah, please do.
What age are you?
17, 16, 17, 18.
Were there graphic design,
was there graphic design or like filters along with it?
Yeah, whatever the video editing software of the day was.
Would it cut to like, now it looks,
now it's like black and white and all shaky sometimes?
I don't think like, maybe black and white for sure,
I think, unless I'm misremembering,
but whatever effect you could do, I think is in the video.
Wow.
Set to my sacrifice.
So I do have an affection for my sacrifice
that I don't for hire or Arms Wide Open or anything else.
And I never owned the albums,
but I won't act like I was always above it
because I liked a lot of normie garbage in high school.
Well, and I think one of the reasons why this song
in particular, I need to contextualize this in its time
because my sacrifice, the single was released
in October of 2001.
So that's where we're at.
That's where everyone's head's at.
I feel like you're always contextualizing things
having to do with late 2001 for some reason.
This is true.
It's happened at least 10 times.
If a listener knows better,
how many times has Jason contextualized something
post 9-11?
I was like, by the way, guess when this one came out?
Yeah.
Well, it did cause this to get swept up into the tide of,
this was not written about 9-11
and Ricky Iglesias hero was not written about 9-11,
but they got to be the YouTube song,
all the YouTube songs of that.
It all got swallowed by 9-11.
Oh yeah.
And I know there was some NFL promos with my sacrifice.
I'm sure there was some troop promos,
some troop commercials with my sacrifice.
So my sacrifice, I think mine is the only one
that has an MTV making the video about it.
So I learned a lot about my sacrifice.
For example, it was shot over the days of October 23rd
through October 25th, 2001.
And boy, they really use a lot of Universal Studios Florida.
And I wondered, how did they,
like one of the things about your guys' videos
is you can kind of tell that the sun is very high in the sky
as if they're like, all right,
let's try and wrap this up by 10 a.m.
Let's wrap up this filming by 10 a.m.
Kind of less so,
hard to tell with the Creed video itself,
but you can tell in the making the video
because they timestamp like, all right, it's like 1 p.m.
and I'm getting in a rowboat next to a tiger.
And I was wondering,
how did they shut down a large part of the park to do this?
And then I learned that it was filmed again, October 2001,
tourism way in the toilet in Orlando at the time,
probably got the location fee for a steal.
I believe Universal Music,
hard to tell Creed has a lot of music companies,
like annotate it in the notes for these videos.
Everybody wanted a piece of Creed.
Oh yeah.
We gotta get in on this.
This big rule. They were big business.
That's why it's so weird that cover is so bad.
Like they had the money.
And they'd already made,
this wasn't even their first album.
You could like,
if like if they didn't know they were gonna be so big
and they had a weird crappy cover,
but well, yeah, money was spent on this.
Cover probably cost like a half a million dollars.
Yes. That was what I was about to say.
I would love to know how much they paid the graphic designer
and I bet we would faint.
Yeah.
I've looked through that making the video
and what you're saying about the time makes sense
because my takeaway from it was like,
God, this shoot seems miserable.
Just when you're, when you have to think,
like you're thinking about like blasting water and trash
in the face of this anonymous guitarist
and all the PAs who were sweating it
and being treated mean by everybody.
Well, and that's a strike against this,
but in my favor,
it seems like mine was a lot of fun for everyone involved.
Well, yours seems like a lot of fun,
but I mean, I wrote down a number of quotes from this,
making the video and probably the best is
when the guitarist, bass guitar,
I think he took over after the bassist left,
he also started playing bass guitar.
He says literally, videos so far have been pretty tedious.
And you know what?
That's a fair assessment of shooting anything.
But what are some other great quotes?
Creed videos aim to have more substance.
If you listen to the words,
it's like Scott is reuniting with himself,
Scott's staff, not Scott character.
But I'm sure Scott, you've had moments where you,
you imagine yourself an old man
and you zoom into your own CGI brain
and you can see a metaphorical representation
of a flooded town.
Right.
Absolutely.
When I look at my son, this is what happened.
My son who has my exact same eyes.
So if you did a zoom and then a zoom into me
and then out of him, it would be seamless.
And you gotta be careful,
cause your son could go blind,
but you could get your vision back as an old man,
which happens in this video.
Thank God there's hope.
And also, I mean, so many in this stressful year
of the pandemic and child rearing,
I've often felt as though I am drowning
and imagining if only I had a lifeboat
with which to pick up myself,
a second version of myself and save him.
Yes, as if you were reuniting with yourself.
And I mean, I'm burying the lead here.
The big set piece of this video
is they flooded the New York streets over by like Kong,
Kong mummy area.
And Scott's staff's in a rowboat.
The other two band members are playing guitar
and drums in waist deep water.
I will, actually here, I will,
can one of you, I texted you the video,
can one of you play it who records sound?
Yeah, I have them all pulled.
Would you like to go to a specific part or just?
Yeah, go, share the screen,
go to like two minutes, five seconds.
I think that's kind of the best representation.
I mean, it's nice to,
there's so much that's nice to see here.
There's a tiger, there's a baseball being thrown.
There's kids, you know, it's really.
Flying over a rowboat.
Digital baseball.
Digital sky.
Is this around where you want me to play?
Where was it again?
Yeah, yeah, this is good.
Okay, American flag, just a game of stick ball,
but the streets are flooded.
There's a lot of powerful imagery here.
Okay, I'm gonna keep it a little quiet so it doesn't blast.
Oh yeah.
Because when you are with me
I'm afraid
I'm careless
I believe
Okay, you can cut it, you can cut it.
That's enough, okay?
That's enough.
This one is successful enough.
I don't want to get DMC.
So you can see.
Oh sorry, go ahead, go ahead.
Well, you can see like Scott and the Rowboat,
you can see the other band members.
Playing instruments.
And it, yeah.
And it's good filmmaking impossible architecture
because Scott is clearly on the main drag
and the other guys. Scott.
Scott Stapp, yeah, is on the main drag.
And then the drummer and the guitarist,
there's a video on YouTube where a guy goes,
and I'll pull up the name in a second,
but a guy goes to the park.
It's the world of Micah.
He goes to the park and he goes like,
okay, so they would have been shooting here for Scott Stapp
and then the drummer was here across from the Irish store
and the guitarist was next to the Irish store
and you can see, because the plaque is,
the arcade movie theater plaque is still on the wall.
And that was pretty neat.
So, and then when you watch them making the video,
it's like, okay, they did this set up
and then they did this set up.
Then they broke the window at Mel's diner the next day.
This is a very complicated shoot.
Boy, the magic of the movies, huh?
Yeah.
Do we know how much this cost?
It seems very expensive.
I guess what, $10 million?
Something like that,
because that's a real tiger too.
They walk through dealing with the tiger.
In the water, the tiger is in the water?
The tiger is in the water.
They talk about how tigers like to swim.
What?
Oh, sure they do.
So says the tiger guy.
The shoot appeared to be momentarily delayed
because the tiger was not cooperating with the swimming.
The tiger got loose in ET.
Yeah.
So, but this is a big part of the park to take over
and fill with water, you know?
That is insane.
I mean, like, when I was looking at it,
I was actually trying to figure out
if some of it was digital effects with the wall.
I was looking at it, trying to figure out,
because it is incredibly impressive
that they would do something like that.
Covers a lot of space.
That plane cut, you can see they go from the drummer
and then a tiny airplane flies by.
And this is like a episode, a prequel edit
where like the plane flies by and that cuts to,
that's right, a school bus full of candles,
wipes to candle bus.
School bus full of candles.
Candle bus, another big band of the time.
Candle bus.
And this shot is funny because Scott Stapp's
in the very back singing, the guitarist is playing the guitar
and the drummer's just kind of twirling his stick
sitting on the bus.
That's a prod, that happened with Natural too.
What do you do when you're a drummer who can't,
where they won't bring the full drum kit to the set?
Yeah, you can like have a tambourine.
You can kind of have one of those like boxes,
one of those wooden boxes you hit.
Just kind of bang your hands on your knees, I guess.
It's awkward.
Poor drummers.
Poor guitarist who had to get pelted with garbage
in front of Mel's drive-in.
Yeah, he was not happy about that.
And again, we could probably do a whole episode
about this making the video episode
because it's just, I don't know, it's very funny.
The color aesthetic too feels very like
in the wake of the, not wake of the,
when the Matrix 99, first Matrix 99.
Yeah, yeah.
Still hanging on.
It does look like, I don't know if a Matrix starts
this like color aesthetic, this dreary thing.
But it's of its time.
Fake letterboxing, why this,
like this is only gonna be on four by three TV.
Why do we put the bars in?
Which again, you can only find it in the worst,
the lowest res, this $10 million video.
Yes.
And then there's a, oh, we mentioned the mailman earlier.
I mean, there's all sorts of people in the water.
There's a beautiful woman in the water,
kids from the old neighborhood,
bunch of monks, some lizard people.
Stan here.
Yeah, Stan.
There's still a bunch of Stans.
Many Stans.
The mailman, they make a point to point out like,
and then we thought like the mail, mail in the water,
cause even if the world floods, you know,
the mail will still go on.
And of course the America,
the American flags were already there.
And of course America standing tall.
You could tell Scott's that trying out like,
and of course, you know, we're all in this together,
America right now.
What's the story of the video?
Has there been an apocalypse?
Is this a global warm?
Is this a flooding of a city?
Do they, do we even know?
Have terrorists attacked us with water?
I think they really go into like, you know,
Scott is very, he's had some troubles
and this is really, you know,
it's really him reuniting, finding himself again,
getting back on level.
So they don't know, they have no idea.
They kind of, they don't know.
But in terms of Bonafides,
the director, David Myers, would go on to direct
just an insane amount of music videos
and like big music videos.
Yeah, we all know C. Eliot's.
Yeah, Pass That Dutch, Bombs Over Baghdad,
more recently, Katy Perry's Firework
and Ariana Grande's Positions.
It's crazy.
Oh, the Sicko Mode music video,
which you know I love that Sicko Mode.
That's a very funny music video
because it starts with a bunch of shots
of children running in terror and like hiding in houses.
And then it cuts to a hard, hard cut to a shot of Drake.
And you know, I don't know,
maybe that was a wording, you know.
Oh, right.
Knowing what we know.
Yeah, you know, Dave Myers was a graduate
of my film school, Loyola Marymount,
and he came and spoke one time,
but he was only there for like 10 minutes.
And I swear he like walked on stage,
finishing up a cell phone call,
then got to the mic and like,
yeah, sorry, I can't stay for long
because I'm doing a bust of video in the morning.
So I just gonna take like three questions, okay.
And then like, okay, I gotta go.
And then immediately got back on the phone and walked away.
But when you, if you look at, I mean, this wasn't 2001,
but like in 2001, he seems to have directed
like 70 music videos and you've heard of all of them.
So I guess it adds up that he was so busy.
I wish he had more time for questions
so you could have asked him what was the meaning of this.
What was it like to flood the iconic New York sets
of Universal Orlando?
This music video would be great for like an eighth grade
or ninth grade English class to go like,
all right, let's talk about symbolism.
Let's talk about metaphors, right?
So the old man was Scott Stapp
and the young boy was also Scott, okay.
And don't know what the fish lizard people represent.
The song itself is about Jesus, right?
My sacrifice.
You should be able to interpret this
because you had more religious schooling than we did.
Religious, yeah.
When you were with me, I'm free.
Yeah, is it about, is this Jesus's feelings
about Mary Magdalene?
Okay, that seems like it could be right.
Could be, or it's the sacrifice of today's Christ,
Scott Stapp.
That's sort of a funny thing about him
is the Jesus-y nature of him and his hair
that was off putting.
Creed pushed back against the Christian rock
labeled more than say POD, payable on death.
They were a little more obvious.
Mm-hmm, yeah, they were, yeah, they were a Christian rock.
I remember, I mean, this, my sacrifice,
this is very Jesus-y.
So I don't know if they were just trying to like
make sure people didn't like pigeonhole them.
Yeah, and I mean, if you have a metal bracelet
like he's wearing, you probably got some thoughts
on Jesus in 2001, you know?
Mm-hmm.
We just got to, oh, no, go ahead, Mike.
I'm trying to think, wasn't there like a voltage
I'm trying to think, wasn't there like a vertical
Ryzen song called You're a God?
Mm-hmm.
I'm not sure.
Yes, the answer is yes.
I guess if you felt it.
You're a God and I am God
and I just want to let you know, I believe.
I think my parents would have found that pretty sacrilegious.
Yeah, so they don't like Kanye's I am a God from Yeezus,
I bet.
I wouldn't imagine, probably just Yeezus would be too,
like he, he thought of a name for himself
that rhymes with Jesus, very disrespectful.
Mm, that's a good point.
But then they'd like his political leanings.
Yeah.
Let's just watch without sound the end of this scenario.
Well, we see, we've alluded to it a little bit,
but that like he, yeah, we saw an old man at the beginning
and then Scott survives the onslaught of trash
at Mel's drive-in and then hugs an overhauled boy
who turns to us and his eyes glow white.
Like, is he the devil?
No, wait, that indicates that he's blind
and then Scott's to have morphs, he grows a digital beard
and turns into the old man at the beginning.
The old man from the beginning.
Moses, he turns into Moses.
Moses, but we'll pay attention, this classic end,
he's got a leather duster on, also Matrix,
CGI pigeon coming right at you.
The religion from the John Woo of the day.
The John Woo move of the day.
This is our second big trench coat appearance
in one of the, I mean, when you get two music videos
from 2001, you end up with big black trench coats.
Trench coat Moses.
Another band I loved at the time.
Yeah.
I got the lyrics to, I got the lyrics wrong, by the way,
to Vertical Horizons, You're a God, I apologize.
It's You're a God and I am not.
Okay.
So my parents are a little more on board then,
so they like Vertical Horizons.
So we think maybe this thing gets points
because it is a very creative use of the backlight.
It really takes it over more.
You're not just looking at empty backlight streets.
We've populated it with monks and sheds and flooded it.
I mean, this is a very ambitious use of the hallowed area
in front of confrontation.
And they're using, they shoot at Mel's diner,
they shoot outside of that,
they shoot under the pavilion next to Mel's diner.
This is like three day, four day shoot, 12 hour date.
Like they were there all day.
And like, I'm assuming the park was open.
I'm assuming they were just working around it.
We should also say that this is the, according to Wikipedia,
this was the first video over which Creed
had complete creative control.
Yes, thank you.
I forgot to mention that.
I had that note.
So all of these metaphor and the,
and Stapp morphing into trench coat Moses,
every bit of it Stapp's idea.
Yeah, it is, look, there's a lot,
there is a lot to like about this video.
There certainly is.
And I have some affection for the song as well.
So I'm not trying to put this down.
It's coming in pretty hot.
And I think we're moving on to the next one,
but I can't allow Creed to come up
without bringing up one of my favorite things in the world.
Well, there's two things and I won't show the clip,
but this was going around Twitter recently.
And it was nice to say I had a vague memory of it.
But I don't know if you guys saw this going around,
that they played at some football halftime show
where they did hire and then right on hire.
He's, first of all, he's in a football jersey
that says Stapp.
And then right as the chorus kicks in,
like a shirtless Adonis with a big drape on him,
like flies up into the air,
much like what we saw at the Pirates Dinner Adventure.
Maybe you do just need to see a quick taste of this.
Hang on. Yeah, please.
This is so great.
Two great correlations of Creed and sports.
Let me get to this.
But there's a ton of like bright red,
unitarded dancers. Devils?
Yeah, where maybe they're being fought.
They're fighting off the temptations of these she devils.
And then, and forgive the bad quality,
but let's see if we can get it here.
["She Devils"]
So we got shirtless acrobat.
Wait, but let me get to the chorus
because it's the takeoff that's the funniest thing.
Oh wait, that was my sacrifice, wasn't it?
Yeah, yeah. That was my sacrifice.
Also, it should be pointed out, Scott Stapp is like,
he's not in like Jersey and cool rock pit.
He looks like he's in like business casual Friday
and it's Jersey Day,
so you can wear your team's jersey in the office.
It's not fitted. Yeah, it's a bizarre size.
Meant to be worn at home on the couch only.
All right, here's the takeoff.
["She Devils"]
Whoa!
Old shirtless drape flyer.
They're really getting air too.
He spins around to readjust the drapes.
I mean, this is inspiring stuff.
Wow, he's like a ribbon, not a ribbon dancer,
but like what do you call those?
The ribbon answering is like, yeah,
but the people that like get tangled up
in the long piece of cloth that hangs from the ceiling.
Yeah, yeah.
The drape acrobat, Imhotep lives, that's what I'll say.
It's very Imhotep-y, yes.
He's very, yeah.
The other one, and do you guys both know this offhand
and I don't know, is this the most obvious thing
I'm bringing up or do people not know this?
The song that Scott Stapp, an Orlando native by the way,
did for his beloved sports team, the Florida Marlins.
Oh, I don't think I know this.
Oh, sweet, okay.
This is so good.
This is an unbelievable song.
He just voluntarily made a song for the Florida Marlins,
the baseball team, and the lyrics are pretty baseball forward.
I'll just let it speak for itself.
["She Devils"]
Let's play ball, it's game day
We want strikeouts, base hits, double plays
Take the field, hear the roar of the crowd
Come on Marlins, make your frown
Keep hoping and dreaming and you will soar
The song is called Marlins Will Soar,
which itself to say that a fish will soar.
And then also, like a lot of sports,
you could talk about flying.
You could talk about Michael Jordan's soaring,
but baseball, I don't really think of soaring
as part of the activities.
The ball soars.
Yeah.
Yes, that counts, sure, sure.
The Marlins keep hoping and dreaming the ball will soar.
Just a quick head of the second verse too,
which is where like I'm, all right,
I'm wavering a little.
The fact that they use a baseball hit
as a percussive element, but then here is,
here's the zone where I started thinking perhaps
Marlins Will Soar is the worst song ever made.
A perfect game, a triple play,
another play of rage, yes.
Well, series champs will
bang!
Keep hoping and dreaming and
Series champs!
Chimps!
Just the ultra serious, like I'd say
the biggest baseball song up until this point
has been Take Me Out to the Ball Game,
which is a pretty good natured song.
So now to hear such a humorless triple play.
I like that he's trying to get as many baseball things,
like terms in there as possible.
Triple double,
ground rule double.
Bounces off the outfield into the stands.
We'll pause the game if there is rain.
Extra innings we will queue.
I, what a song.
I just couldn't let this moment pass.
Wow, I did not know, thank you.
Yeah, I did not know that.
That one's pretty good.
Marlins Will Soar, I need to listen to Marlins Will Soar
every six months at least.
Sure, do you think there are other members of Creed
who famously when Creed broke up
and then they've gotten back together once or twice,
but like, Stapp did solo records
but the other members of Creed formed a band
with another guy called Altered Bridge?
Alter Bridge.
Alter Bridge?
See, I didn't sound right in my head.
Okay, Alter Bridge.
Alter, like at the altar.
Okay, here we go now.
Wait, but I would also buy a band at this time
being called Altered Bridge.
I mean, that's stupid.
I know Alter Bridge so well.
Well, sure.
And why I jumped in.
But do you think they were-
I don't know if it's spelled Alter though.
It might be spelled,
Alter is spelled, the religious one is with a two A's, right?
It is Alter Bridge, but I would certainly buy,
of course, their album,
their album, Walk the Sky just came out.
Oh, we've all been jamming on Walk the Sky all year.
Yeah.
Do you think they were all on their Alter Bridge bus
and were like, did you hear Stapp's Marlin song?
We fucked up.
We blew it.
He's putting out gold for baseball teams.
What are we doing?
I think that's, yeah, that happened.
Yeah.
Stapp is gonna help those guys ride all the way
to the World Series title.
And who are we helping?
God.
I guess that, yeah.
Well, even if they do win, really it was God's doing.
So Scott didn't do shit.
Hey, the Marlins did win World Series in 97 in 2003.
So I don't know if it was buoyed by that Scott Stapp song
or if it came later,
he's trying to get him back in contention.
I don't know when he did Marlins will sort.
I think 2010, 11.
So do they play it also?
Like, do they use it at the games?
That's a good question.
Did he do it on spec?
That's my guess for some reason.
That's based on nothing.
Maybe they paid him a handsome amount.
Do they no longer play Take Me Out to the Ball Game?
They fired the organist.
Don't need you anymore.
And Scott plays it from the booth every single game.
Here we go, everyone.
Sing along.
There's like some Eddie Vedder baseball song too, right?
And Eddie Vedder, I know Scott Stapp got compared
to Eddie Vedder a lot with the voice.
Which I haven't, no offense to anyone who likes them.
I've never really understood.
I don't really like Pearl Jam or Eddie Vedder.
Just not my thing.
So imagine me with, if I don't like the real deal,
then like imagine me hearing,
Dab a dog a loo.
Yikes.
I'm trying to think.
Oh yeah, all the way he did a Cubs tribute.
Oh, really?
Did that give him the idea?
Did he steal this idea?
That's what I'm wondering if Scott Stapp stole his voice
from Eddie Vedder and then stole the baseball song idea
from him.
It's possible.
Ah, someone needs to look into this.
We're gonna investigate this.
Giuliani's on it.
Yeah.
All right, well, if that closes out the Creed chapter,
then that brings us to number three.
And what can I say?
This is, it's coming in heavy, it's coming in hot.
It's the one to beat, certainly.
Yes, okay.
So most people probably know this already.
With all the teases, but this last one is the video
for the song by Mr. Jimmy Buffett.
And the song is called Fruit Cakes.
And I think I've said on the show before,
maybe I've said it in real life,
I kind of feel like Fruit Cakes is the perfect encapsulation
of Jimmy Buffett.
It's kind of his best song.
People say Margaritaville is his best song,
and I get it, because it's the catchiest one,
and most people know it.
But Fruit Cakes, I feel like you get the whole picture
of the man's philosophy, his unified philosophy
about everything.
Musically, it's all in there.
It's the conga, not conga, it's the steel drums.
It's the calypso rhythms.
It's the very like, kind of like,
it kind of limps around for eight minutes.
It's like energetic, kind of, but not so energetic.
You wouldn't call it rockin', you wouldn't call it a jam.
Yeah, but he talks things in it a lot,
so you get his voice.
You get like a little hint of like his banter at concerts.
It's like you kind of can just listen to this song,
and you know all you need to know about him.
As a person, as a businessman, as a philosopher king,
all of it is in Jimmy Buffett's Fruit Cakes.
It's a long song, it's like eight minutes.
This one was, I think, the biggest culture shock to me
as you were acquainting me with the Buffett body of work,
the rabbit hole that you had gone down.
Being that it is a 90s one, it's like 93 or 94.
Yes, I think he's like 49 here.
Okay, okay.
It's shot in 94, came out in 94.
Cause, you know, my Buffett awareness
is pretty like on the sidelines, right?
Like I guess I knew there was this guy,
and he sort of has his roots
in kind of legit eagle style country rock,
and then got sort of goofy,
and everybody wears bright colors to his concerts.
But I don't think I knew the vibe of the music
he was continuing to make for so many years.
And yeah, this one does encapsulate it.
It is like tropical, but also not genuinely the genre.
Yeah, it's like fake, it's all a little fake.
It's like fake music, kind of.
The way that, you know, like guys of his era and age
would still put out albums, and like Marin would go,
man, that guy can play, you know, that, yeah, god.
He's the hell of a player.
No one says that about anything on Buffett's album.
There's no like outstanding musicianship,
I wouldn't say anywhere.
No, there's great, there's a guy who's played in his band
for a long time, Mack McAnally, who has own songwriter,
who I do think is a really good musician.
I think a lot, there are really good musicians,
but Jimmy Buffett never calls upon them to do anything
to really showcase their actual chops as far as musicians.
I'm sure there's a couple examples people would cite,
but in general, it's much more about the lyrics,
it's about the vibe, it's about the lifestyle.
Yes, Jason.
Well, when we saw him live though,
when Jimmy wanted to take a break, he had a glass of wine,
he let Mack on stage, and Mack played
some very impressive music.
Mack did a lot of, yeah, Jimmy had like a five minute break,
and he's like, all right, Mack, you go do whatever you want.
Like Mack played a very impressive little piece
where he like showed off that he knows his scales real well,
and that diminishes it,
but it was a very impressive like guitar piece.
Mack wrote Back Where I Come From,
which was a big hit country song.
Yeah.
Jason loves Back Where I Come From.
I do like it, but they, you know what they would do
when they play it at the concerts,
they have a video package that's different in every city,
and I don't know, some of the ones in some parts
of the country, there's some imagery that you're like,
oh, I don't know if you wanna put that flag up there.
I don't know what you're talking about.
What was it in the LA one?
Was it like a picture of like Spielberg making ET?
Hollywood.
We went to, I wanna just real fill the listener in,
we went to a Jimmy Buffa concert,
is it five years ago already?
Yeah. Yes.
With a couple, Weiger was there, Nick Weiger was there.
Stone face sitting, staring intently ahead,
no smile on his face the entire time.
I think he was watching it very seriously
to where you're thinking, is he enjoying this at all?
And then at the end of the night,
he's like, this is the best night of my life.
Yeah, I think I slid over and I was like,
hey, you enjoying this?
Yeah, best night of my fucking life.
Anthony Gio also at this concert as well.
Yeah.
Who should become a better, a more frequent guest?
A better guest, I'm calling him on to be better.
Oh.
He's done a bad job.
A better man.
A better man like Pearl Jam.
You know that song?
You know that song.
Can't find a better man.
I'm singing a lot today.
Now do it as Buffa.
Can't find a better man.
He toxin's it.
Yeah, so we went to the concert and I thought it was funny.
I don't remember those video packages,
but I did think it was funny
because he would say stuff like,
for no reason during the concert,
he would be playing one of his regular songs
and then he would just yell like,
In-N-Out Burger.
He would shout references to Los Angeles
that didn't really see,
maybe he said that in Cheeseburger Paradise,
that which would make sense,
but I swear he would be like,
he would do like a Brody Stevens,
like 405 Freeway.
Supreme store.
Yeah.
So I enjoyed that a lot.
Shitty mayor.
Bad mayor.
Confusing.
Crossroads of the world.
What is that little strip ball?
Can't decide what you,
there's no genuine attractions.
UCB Franklin.
Asscat, Matt Besser.
Unbuilt target.
Everyone nodded.
We all melted down for that.
So I don't know,
I've lost my train of thought already.
I'm in Buffett.
Talking about the concert.
I mean that.
But now he didn't play Fruit Cakes,
I believe.
Did not do Fruit Cakes and did not do,
and Lindsay pointed this out to me not long ago.
The last concert we saw was Jimmy Buffett
before this all went to hell.
Perfect.
We went to see him in Anaheim
and I had a really good time at the Hollywood Bowl.
I had a great time in Anaheim seeing him.
And Lindsay who is very much more like,
oh God,
has still,
had to give it up like,
yeah this is fun.
We're having a fun time.
Well you guys ended up on the Jumbotron.
Yes we did.
And there's footage,
there's viewable footage of that.
Yes.
And yeah, Lindsay's very genuinely into it.
Yeah.
There's documented proof.
So,
right,
so yeah,
and he did not do Fruit Cakes there,
which I obviously,
that's what I wanted him to play.
I also want,
I have yet to,
I've only seen him a couple times at this point,
but there's songs I want him to play,
I wish lunch would last forever.
And of course the song Math Sucks.
This is the song I want him to play more than anything.
But Math Sucks certainly has his like,
lazy wisdom in it as well.
But Fruit Cakes has a more wide range picture
about the top,
his philosophy on different topics.
Not just math.
Not just lunch lasting forever.
Explain the thesis of the song Fruit Cakes.
If I had to sum it up,
now I believe he's using the term Fruit Cakes to mean crazy,
silly,
like unusual person.
I don't think he's using it in the term,
like as a slur against gay people.
Oh, no, no,
I don't take it like that at all.
Yeah.
But I mean,
I think you could ensure that's what some people
would use that.
So he's using Fruit Cakes as a term,
I think to say.
And also not as a mentally ill slam,
but rather a,
to summarize the people who just have a screw loose
and we love them for it.
Right.
And we're all Fruit Cakes is what,
also what he's saying too.
There's a little bit of Fruit Cake in every one of us,
he says,
like we're all a little crazy.
But if I had to sum it up,
I would say,
everything's crazy.
We're all crazy,
would be the sum up of it.
We're all crazy.
Life's crazy.
We're just,
you know, there's problems,
but we're just all on the ride.
This crazy journey called life.
Maybe it's just like buckle up.
Buckle up.
Street,
street preachers,
your create your coworker who believes
in conspiracy theories.
We're all in it together.
Well,
he has done Fruit Cakes with updated lyrics
in the last decade,
but not recently.
Cause I always,
I was looking.
Like,
QAnon.
Stephen Miller.
Stephen Miller is just a Fruit Cake.
Audit the vote.
It's the lefty and you.
It's the Q and me.
It's the centrist in him.
Maybe he needs to update this.
Maybe an updated Fruit Cakes is what it will take
to unite this divided nation.
I will say,
to Buffett's credit,
he is not a Trump guy.
Unlike your beloved Mike Love.
Well, my beloved,
there's some levels to the belovedness.
Okay, fair enough.
Fair enough.
You know, it'll get more genuine when I'm in the band,
you know,
when I'm talking to him on the daily
and complimenting him.
Boy, you really nailed this top of be true
to your school tonight, Mike.
And he just like kind of goes,
oh, thank you.
Cause he's 90 years old and you know,
still a good vibrations.
Still, you know,
started in harmonizing with my brothers
and still doing it.
Anytime he talks to anybody,
he tells that story.
He hasn't had a new story since 1969.
So look,
I could talk about that stuff forever.
We're here to talk about the video.
And we are.
Well, you know what might be worth,
and this might dovetail into the video,
but when you talk about how he's updated it
for modern times,
the reason that's important is that this song
has these stretches that feel very topic,
like especially the zone about going to LA
or being out in California.
That's really the part that feels like,
this is like the 94 perspective
because everything was going mad in LA.
There's earthquakes and there's Menendez's
and OJ's and riots.
And so there's this odd verse
that says all that stuff.
Right.
And you know,
feel free to play the man himself.
Yeah, let me just,
and we don't have to play the whole thing
because this is the full fruitcake song,
as I said, like eight minutes or seven minutes
or something.
This is obviously shorter,
but I'm gonna just give like,
play a little of this start,
just so you know while we're talking
what the vibe is in case you don't know the song.
So here he's-
In case.
In case, yeah.
Yeah.
["In Case"]
You know, I was talking to my friend, Des Demolter.
The other day she runs the space station
and bake shop down near Boone Town.
She told me that human beings are flawed individuals.
But the cosmic bakers took us out of the oven
a little too early.
And that's the reason we're as crazy as we are.
And I believe it.
["In Case"]
Fruitcakes in the kitchen.
All right, so that's, yeah,
that gives you an idea sort of,
is talk singing or talking really.
And then a little bit of the musical vibe there.
You can get anything you wanted, Alice's Restaurant.
Yeah, so it's a very, you know,
it's homespun wisdom, some philosophy.
The line there, you know,
I was talking to my friend Des Demona.
Which is like a person he references
in other songs as well.
She's in the, Des Demona is in the Buffett verse.
There is a Buffett verse that contains
from characters from his books, like Tully Mars.
Who's also in the Escape to Margaritaville musical.
Which.
Which was one of the other last things we did.
That's the very last thing we did.
The very last thing we did.
We went to Escape to Margaritaville.
It's crazy we haven't actually done a full episode.
We went with Eva too.
Yeah.
So that is kind of got,
I think because of the craziness of that time,
we neglected to talk about it,
but we saw it.
The biggest tragedy of the era.
So yeah, so anyway, there's so much,
I can be derailed very easily during this.
So.
Well, I kind of want to hear the LA or the California.
Yeah, let's go to that.
And that is, hold on.
Paradise.
The hair is really something.
So yeah, let's say, let's set up a little bit of a look.
So Jimmy has on his like his white sport coat,
which is a reference I think to,
well, it's a sport coat pink,
white sport coat pink crustacean, which is an album.
So he's wearing white pants.
God.
White sport coat pink crustacean.
You've not heard of that one, Scott?
No, no.
He put the white.
How many albums does he have?
150.
He just released a new one this year.
Yes.
Songs you don't know by heart.
Okay.
Well, actually that's a,
he's released like a couple of compilations.
He's released a full new album though, this year,
which has a song on it called Cussin Island,
which is maybe my favorite of all the new ones.
But the first song was down at the La-Di-Da,
which is about drinking a margarita
at a bar near the water.
Yeah.
You guys have covered that already?
He had a few more.
It's a different bar, Scott.
This bar is called the La-Di-Da.
It's a different, it's a new bar he made up
in the Buffett verse.
I can respect that.
I think we were talking about that with Eva
around the time of the musical.
And she was like, yes, we're all kind of like, it's okay.
And she's like, it feels like Margaritaville
without any teeth.
I believe it's our salvation.
It looks like.
I really should have the marker down
for where the California.
It's before this, right?
Yeah, cause yeah, you're in religion.
Each verse kind of covers a different thing
that's crazy about our world.
This one seems to be about out of the kooky lifestyle
we live in California.
There's a stint about religion and then, oh boy,
relationships buckle up, ladies and fellas.
All right, so this.
In the middle of the week, I've been.
Oh, I'm in a bad spot.
It's fine, it's fine.
I don't want to edit it cause it's so good, you know.
You can just play it.
Fruitcake left in every one of us.
Religion.
Way knows religion.
All over the place.
This is religion.
That's it, that's it.
It's a Hollywood.
Cause it uses the fake Pantages Theater
at Universal Florida with the weird.
There was a photo op where you could like take a picture
and then it looks like the Hollywood Hills
are matted into a photo that you could take,
which is like a thing.
Like put your camera here
and then it'll look like the Hollywood Hills are up.
And they did that effect in this video.
This might be the only thing that did this little
like fun photo op that was available at Universal Florida.
Let's try again.
I'm also, I realized I'm looking at the lyrics
for the full version, which has an extra chunk of dialogue
at the start about paying for junior mints
and large sodas at the movie theater
that is not included.
Which is, it's demented.
He's screaming.
He gets hysterical.
He's like, I want my junior mints.
And then he said like,
I don't want to pay for this much organization.
It doesn't make any sense.
You're going to hear this so many times.
You're welcome by the way.
I mean, look, that's what I, they got a bunch of serious things.
They got sushi in the malls.
Which I guess in 93.
This is before sushi at gas stations kind of time.
So what is this?
I mean, this was just a lot of info for me to get this video
whenever I first saw it.
And maybe we can start talking about what's happening in it,
which is he's in that intro that we played about Des Damona.
He's driving his car around in which we get, you know,
we cover so much ground of the universal lagoon.
And then he ends up almost crashing his car into a young skateboarding
jean shorted woman.
And we don't see the collision.
It just cuts to a fire hydrant spraying water.
And then this music video starts in earnest
where he's joined by just a parade of colorful folks.
Would you call them like Zydeco dancers
and then just like regular people who work in the building and then,
you know, hunks, you don't just got fruitcakes, you got beefcakes.
And then, of course, a big line of actual suits of of fruitcakes.
There's like at least four of them, maybe more.
You know, they look like, you know, what would be dancers
in a sponsored portion of a 1950s live broadcast
where it's just the legs sticking out.
It's hard to convey what a fruitcake is.
It's just kind of a big brown mass with weird, little sticky items poking out.
Yeah, it looks like a big piece of shit.
Yeah, I would think pretty much.
Yeah, a slightly molded piece of shit with like stuff in it that didn't get digested.
Mm hmm. But now we're you know, we're marching down Hollywood Boulevard here,
you know, by Schwab's and the palm lined streets.
I mean, so many people have joined to be in a party like this.
This is what I hope it will be like when the vaccines get out,
that we're just dancing down the street with the side of people and people from all walks of life.
I mean, this party, this is this is a blast.
He yeah, he first of all, he's got like kind of a striped shirt on.
Jimmy does. There's an older man move, which I like is a tucked in shirt
with a bit of a belly going on that I think is we guess we know what you'll look like at 49.
Oh, I'm I'm working on it now.
And he's got like crazy.
He's he's he's a bald gentleman, but he's got like crazy hair in the back.
And this is just this look is I feel like maybe the best Buffett look
other than maybe when he was young and had like the big mustache and stuff.
It's the most, you know, a a bald guy with crazy scraggly hair
who has ideas that are a little unorthodox, you know, I guess in that way, Mr.
Buffett reminds us of Senator Bernie Sanders.
Could Buffett have taken it all the way is Buffett electable?
I say yes.
Buffett would have definitely been hit by that tax.
We'll say that.
Yeah, they'd be I don't like he's not a Trumper,
but I don't know if he'd get along with Bernie.
Oh, no. Yeah, no.
He seems like nice guy, but I don't know about those cookie ideas.
Health care for everyone.
Huh? This is a fruitcake I can't get behind. Yeah.
My my I see you can buy a Walmart that's mostly cord syrup
has been labeled a carcinogen.
Can't have him looking into that.
So I don't know. I'm sure.
Yeah. Looks what look wise, they they they share a lot.
Mm hmm. But then we get joined by some of the most colorful
the costumes of the you know, you think they've shown all their cards,
that it's all these Key West partiers.
But then he's got a couple of thoughts about the crazy world of religion.
And I like the big wind up here, which is very it's like how a stand up
would do it like, OK, folks, stay in your seats, remain calm.
We're going to go there.
And I just want to point out equal opportunity skin showing here.
I mean, there's three women, but there's, you know, topless men.
There's women in bathing suits.
Not like that.
Hopless men on rollerblades that hedonistic Beach Boys video.
I agree. That's a very that's that should be rated X.
That's inappropriate.
I bet that's why they never played it on MTV.
The only reason has to be the reason.
OK, give us a little taste of religion.
Oh, there's a thin line between Saturday night and Sunday morning.
Amen, brother.
Here we go now.
Mayor, mayor, mayor, mayor, Maxima, mayor, mayor, mayor, mayor, Maxima.
Where is the church who took the secret religions
in the hands of some crazy ass people, television preachers with bad hair
and dimples, the god's honest truth is it's not that simple.
It's the Buddhist in you.
It's the pagan in me.
It's the Muslim in him.
She's Catholic.
It's that born again.
Look, it's the wife with the Jews.
Tell me what's going on.
I ain't got a clue.
I mean, what what isn't he saying there?
What is he not trying to make a point about?
Like, OK, buckle up.
We're going to talk about religion, folks.
So here's here's how I see it.
You got all these different things.
What are we going to do about it?
I'll find out.
That that that that that that.
All right. You're twisted.
And every by the way, in those in those lyrics,
everything that he referenced was cut to.
We cut to a televangelist with fake hair.
We cut to a sexy Catholic schoolgirl.
He says, Wasp and the Jew.
And then it cuts to a rabbi going like, yeah, I don't know.
Yeah. What could I tell you?
His yeah, if you could sum up what he what his view on religion is,
what would you say?
90s HBO stand up half hour.
I think too many words.
I think it's like, I don't know.
Yeah, it's weird.
Go go fish.
Rather be fishing.
Dave Barry book.
Yeah, he's he's got he's got nothing to say.
Nothing to say, but a lot of costumes.
And then you see him in like a in like a choir uniform
with a bunch of altar boys, not altered, not alter.
What was the bridge?
But then we are on the street.
We are on the street, you know.
Yes. Yeah, we're covering kind of the same neck of the woods.
We're hovering around a confrontation.
And what's the other?
What else are we near?
I mean, mainly that.
Yeah, it's a lot of the New York neck of the woods.
Transformers.
Yeah, Transformers down the line.
But we covered some Hollywood, too.
And, you know, and as I said, we're all around that lagoon.
So in terms of full just universal coverage, we're getting it.
There's a big there's a big bus and there's fruitcakes dancing on top of it.
I mean, they're really taking us.
They're taking us on a tour of the lot.
And for me, not having been able to go there recently, you know,
it's it's it's making me homesick.
It's nice to see all these places in their 94 prime.
Yes, there's also I also watched Jason reference the YouTube channel
called the World of Micah.
Yeah, which I also watched because he did the same thing for the fruitcake.
I also watched because he did the same thing for the fruitcakes video
that he did for my sacrifice.
He also has a video, which I really like, where he goes and sees
what's left of a closed down shownies.
World of Micah really doing it, really living his best life.
There's a there's one there's also one where he does a Kokomo video
at the Grand Floridian.
Oh, no kidding.
So he shows all of the angles.
Right. Wow. Wow.
He also like kind of gets into a weird space where he's trying
to like starting to like hypothesize how much fun it would have been
to party with the Beach Boys and like the cheerleaders at the Grand Floridian.
What's wrong with that?
Because he's right. The answer is very much fun.
It's not going to be the same cheerleaders, obviously.
But when I'm with the band, I'm going to find out how fun it is.
We're we're all hanging at Mike's pad in Lake Tahoe.
I'm going to be in the jacuzzi.
I really want to earnestly work on this.
Getting you. Yeah, I'm not really.
I'm not sure the in can you tweet your way into a band?
I don't know. It seems like a tall order. Yeah.
We just need to get you like some fake credentials
and get you on stage in the right outfit.
And then you just sort of go city to city and no one notices.
I'm just there. Well, it's you know, the way that in lots of great movies that
if characters are trying to hide from mobsters
or somebody wants to kill them, that they end up on stage
dressed as showgirls or something like that.
Like I'll just put on the headdress and then this happens in the
Saved by the Bell, the wedding movie and many other great films.
I think that's that kind of thing.
Like that nobody the other showgirls don't question it because they don't have time.
They're getting ready for the show.
And there's about as many beach boys as there are showgirls in a typical
showgirl show.
So I think if I just sneak in as if I'm avoiding the mob, right,
then I'll probably just end up doing the show and end up on the bus. Yeah.
I think we are as soon as as soon as Covid is over.
Oh, did the beach boys play that that parking show, the parking lot show?
Yeah, I've heard audio of it.
It's something else.
They they do their 20 20 song about being socially distant.
It's called The This Too Shall Pass.
And I heard a recording where because it's a song that is newer than 1972
and Mike doesn't have it as sense memory for many decades in his brain,
he blows the song so hard.
He just like and you hear band members go, no, it and they do the part for him.
Oh, no. This is cues.
Now I forget the lyrics.
If you haven't heard this song, you heard the social distance.
Oh, yeah.
Like, do what the CDC says.
And this do this will be over before we know it.
I'd like to hear the song you would write now about it.
All right. It's
where we're catching a third wave, but that's OK.
Keep the businesses open, man.
Was the Chinese government that made it this way?
Then we're now we're getting into Clapton and Morrison territory.
That's true, too.
They should all team up.
That's how bad Mike Love has it.
He didn't even get invited to be part of that.
Oh, Mike Love's calling.
Don't pick up.
That guy's crazy.
A reference.
Well, on the Dick Tracy episode, we were talking a lot about.
Eva was talking about how it seemed like the creator of Dick Tracy
had it in for NASA.
But Jimmy Buffett in not in the music video, in the song,
the long song fruitcakes seems to have some gripes with the space program.
Hmm.
Ah, and this this actually to me seems like its most coherent thought.
Yeah, he the lyrics are we lost our Martian rocket ship,
the high paid spokesman said, looks like that silly rocket ship
has lost its cone shaped head.
We spent 90 jillion dollars trying to get a look at Mars.
I hear universal laughter ringing out among the stars.
That's the most like I understand what he thinks.
That's dumb. That's a waste of money.
But that's the closest thing to any thought.
That's the closest thing to a maybe the space program.
Yeah. Yeah.
He wouldn't be into Space Force. Right.
And then he's then the quote, there's a chorus that's specific
to that version as well. That's fruitcakes in the galaxy.
So instead of fruitcakes.
Well, now I wish they'd done that.
They'd film that verse and they could have gone and filmed it in the E.T. ride.
Yeah, that's the only way to make this better.
And he's like playing percussion on the shells or whatever,
on the magic mushrooms with with E.T. in the gang.
I mean, God, that would be next level.
We haven't even gotten to the part yet where he's like, my old lady's mad at me.
Oh, well, that's that's coming now, right?
He's got it right.
Yeah, I think it's I mean, this is yeah, it's right here.
He's hanging out in the front yard. Right.
So it's yeah, there's another big wind up here.
Let's see if I can catch it in the right spot
where he goes like, here comes the big ones.
Relationships.
Another one like, I'm going there.
Ah, here comes the big ones.
Relationships.
We all got them.
We all want them.
What do we do with them?
Here we go, I'll tell you.
Sounds like a box worthy.
She said you've got to do your fair share.
Now, on top of Hathoran,
I treat my body like a temple.
You treat yours like a tent.
But the right word at the right time.
His wife is beautiful, dressed in 90s aerobics clothes, and he looks like trash.
But you know what? They're making it work.
What did the marquee of the theater say back there?
Because you see that marquee in the Creed video as well, and it says sacrifice.
Sacrifice, yes.
What does it say?
Wait, did I go by it?
You missed, you missed. Go way ahead.
It's past the close up of he and his wife
realizing that they do have common ground.
Also, you still got to take care of a tent.
Tents are done.
Where is where is Joe Merchant?
I think that's his book, right?
That's one of his novels.
You know, I didn't even notice that we got to.
Yeah. What is that the name of the book?
Well, I think totally Mars is trying to find Joe Merchant.
Wow, that's a great little Easter egg.
Where he's written a lot of stuff,
these written books about that involve the word Mars.
He might like all the Dick Tracy and Moon Maid.
He likes he references Star Trek here and there in songs as well.
So I think he has some affection for it.
Yeah. Where is Joe Merchant? Yeah, that is the name of the book.
I have not read this one.
I have read his book Swine Not about a pig named Rumpy, I believe. Yes.
And I've read some of A Pirate Looks at 50, but not all of it.
I'm sorry, it. Rumpy.
All right. Is Rumpy cute?
I'll ask. I haven't seen Rumpy.
I don't know if you see Rumpy.
Well, you see in any of the materials.
OK, so here's the here's the cover of Swine Not.
Hold on. Let me stop.
The title is not cute.
I'm voting on that one.
That pun is not cute.
Swine Not.
A novel pig tale.
There's illustrations in it.
I don't think this pig is necessarily Rumpy.
Yeah, that's true. I got to go get the book then.
Yeah. We'll have to choose.
Well, put in wait, put in Rumpy.
Yeah. I mean, I bet you have no Google image results for that, but.
No, nothing.
All right. Well, somebody find Rumpy and we'll find out if
if there's a listener who already owns the book Swine Not.
I think good for you.
You're living your best life, just like Micah.
I have to apologize.
Where is Joe Merchant and follows the character Frank Bama
looking for Joe Frank Bama, the character that Jimmy Buffett plays on Hawaii.
Five. Oh, that's right.
Yes. A little in the Buffett verse.
He has books about Frank Bama and he plays him in the new Hawaii.
Five. Oh, and the old one as well, I believe.
I don't know about the original.
Definitely the new one.
He's been on the new one a couple of times.
Yes. Frank Bama show up as if you're going to know who Frank Bama is.
He's certainly they presented like that, I think.
Frank Bama and his girl ex-girlfriend, hemorrhoid, ointment,
Harris, Trevor Kane.
This is so much like that dog patch shit.
There's a whole Joan.
There's a full opus maybe next year where we go through the full Buffett verse.
Oh, man. Man.
That's it. I'll like I'll go leave and have like a leisurely lunch
and come back in the episode will be not even halfway through.
We have to like I have to do.
There are much bigger parrot heads and Buffett files than me.
And I'd have to do a lot of work.
But there are so many books and ancillary material in the Buffett verse.
And we would try to piece it all together.
He is. Look, the man has been just churning out crap for 50 years.
This is what I don't understand.
I mean, I have look, I think my I've made my Beach Boys level
confusing, probably to some extent.
But I like is it like it's crap, but I love it.
Is this a Six Flags situation?
Well, I would think that 95 percent of all the people at that Buffett concert
or any Buffett concert have no clue about most of like
they don't know about Rumpy and Swine Not.
It's only the hard course. Yes.
Yeah, you're there to hear the hits and to get very drunk.
And then, yeah, they get hammered drunk and to yell salt, salt.
And they love it.
I mean, they love the people.
100 percent of the people are 95 percent of people there love
Margaritaville more than anyone loves anything.
Some of the happiest people I've ever seen in my life.
Oh, my God.
And maybe it's better. Maybe their way is better.
We were like we when we went to that Anaheim show
and Hollywood Bowl crowd was pretty well behaved, not the Anaheim crowd.
Because you can tailgate at the Honda Center.
Yeah. Yes, that is the difference.
And the baby boomers were like yelling and cutting in front of each other
and like kind of getting in arguments before the show.
And just like everyone we were like we had just gotten there
right before showtime.
And and we were like the we were like the parents.
And all these baby boomers were like just so drunk.
They were threatening each other with sharp pineapples.
I'll cut you.
Throwing coconuts at each other.
Yeah. So there's another world of Micah.
He points out that and I miss now I'm forgetting where it is.
Jimmy Buffett goes by the Lew Wasserman statue.
In the universe.
No, there was such a thing.
There's a statue of Lew and Universal Executive of the past.
Yes. Lew Wasserman.
So this is a thing.
This is probably an episode about this statue, because I don't think we've ever
talked about this, nor did I really realize that this was there.
There is a Lew Wasserman statue in Universal Florida.
And let me show it to you and you will be maybe as shocked as I was to find this.
Jason, did you know about this?
Yeah, it's over by the 30 Rock building, right?
It's been the park. Exposing himself.
Oh, my God.
He's like a he's like a crying clown.
Well, he doesn't always have the bird on his head.
I see you.
So I thought the bird was part of the statue.
Wait, they gave this executive a constant bird on his head, like a silent film star.
No, no, no. All right.
He's just a very thin man.
He looks like John Kerry.
They've they've built this very sad.
They built a statue to make him look like he's like John Quincy Adams or Ben Franklin.
He looks like Fred Gwynn.
He also does look like he looks like an emaciated Fred Gwynn, Herman Monster.
Here there's the plaque here.
Lew Wasserman was one of the most highly regarded figures in the entertainment
industry for decades. He had guided the course of film, television, music
and recreation, as well as the world of politics and philanthropy.
During his career, he built MCA, later renamed Universal Studios
into a preeminent entertainment company and simultaneously transformed the industry
through his innovation, creativity and vision.
I never knew that I did not know this.
Everybody's favorite attraction at Universal, Florida.
There he is. There's the man himself.
I just read an article talking about like the the the chaos at HBO
and AT&T running Warner now, and they compared it to like in the 90s.
This sort of happened when like Japanese technology companies like Sony
started buying either movie studios or like taking big shares of them.
And Lew Wasserman's attitude was, I'm not going to teach you how to do this.
You're on your own.
And a lot of those companies, Japanese and European, got into the business
and then got out very quickly.
Sony was the only one that really stuck around.
But like, yeah, Lew Wasserman, very pissed off that people were coming in
and trying to teach Hollywood how to make movies and stuff.
Mm hmm. Well, we'll do a full Lew episode.
Well, this Wikipedia says that his statue is decorated for Halloween horror nights.
Oh, yeah. Well, what did you I think that's hold on.
I think I found that picture.
They make him a scary clown or something.
No, here look at Lew like defaced.
Yeah, here it is. I think.
Oh, he's covered in thorns.
Oh, so he, I guess, is Jesus ish as well.
I know that Jesus wasn't wrapped in thorns like this, but.
You should you should have a crown.
And suffered for.
Um, OK, so credit for that, they used a very obscure detail of the park.
I mean, you know, this is they really used a lot.
I mean, I think it's hard to it's hard to top this.
Yeah, you get like you get as you get all the different like signage.
Obviously, you get some of that in the
Creed video as well, but like you really get a good view of the park
as it existed in this year.
It looks like the most fun place you could ever go.
And in the video you get, it's just some of the one of the great philosophers
of the 20th century.
Some very coherent thoughts that really make you think.
And yeah, hey, you know, all this stuff in the world,
who knows what's going on? I ain't got a clue.
The thing that I have a clue about, I'll I'll cast my vote
that I believe that Fruitcakes is the best music video
film that Universal Studios Florida.
Yeah, I mean, needless to say, I also I'm going to cast that vote.
I realize now that World of Micah also told me that the place
where Buffett and his wife here in the little scene,
it's now a Puss in Boots meet and greet.
So like a how like a kind of a Spanish villa house
and synergy got to make sure that looks like a modern
Puss in Boots lives in like a 1940 house.
Yeah, just yeah. He just bought it.
My bungalow. It's a bungalow.
They make the cartoon characters live in the old starlit bungalows
where they would make them have curfews and sign moral pledges.
Jason, do you have a vote to cast?
Ah. I mean, you know, I.
I feel like somehow the message of Fruitcakes is clearer than my sacrifice.
I'd say so.
Well, while technically less impressive, this is probably more fun because
yeah, my sacrifice is is kind of a bummer.
Mm hmm. So yeah, if I had to watch one of the three again, it would be this.
Yeah. With a break, as we've been staring at the frames of this for some time.
And maybe I'd skip the mea culpa mea maxima culpa part.
But besides that, I well need to declare it.
I think that. It's kind of an important part.
Not cuttable. You can cut the junior men's part, but not the mea culpa.
Movie theater is different than religion.
I'm declaring it Fruitcakes, the winner of the Universal Studios
Florida music video melee.
Congratulations. Since 1994, nothing has topped.
Not even some strong entries in 2001.
Some great tints of the early 2000s couldn't dethrone the king,
the king of the fruitcakes, Jimmy himself.
Congratulations, Jimmy, you did it.
I bet he feels like he's in paradise.
Yes, he had a view or hear.
He would say, thanks a lot.
Ah. I have to say the,
you know, just that this music video for fruitcakes being filmed at Universal
Florida, I think this is the most interesting trivia and the most interesting story
involving Jimmy Buffett and the Universal Resort.
Hmm. I can I can think of no story
that is more fascinating that involves both of these parties.
Yeah, you know, I think that what you're saying is 100% true.
So like I think by everybody, thank you so much for listening.
I'm going to.
We hold hold on.
Oh, I found a story on Google.
Oh, oh, the monster's rising.
Did you find Mike?
Mike's building something.
Wait. Oh, no, I better.
OK, you survived.
I guess the ride. You survived it.
There's a you can't go back once you survived.
It's been said you survived.
I guess the ride is a good game.
Jimmy Hemisphere dancer.
What we do stay subscribed three bonus episodes every month.
Wondered where that plane came from.
Jamaica, Mistaka.
No. OK. All right.
OK, that's it. I'm I'm stopping my space bar.
If you guys want to keep going, it's up to you.
But I say you survive.
I guess the ride find the story elsewhere.