Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast contains the names of many old timey people.
Retcons galore, a new ceramic based persona for Jason Sheridan, and an amazingly dense,
hard to follow interconnected narrative that is sure to confuse dads across the world.
We're talking Sea, the society of explorers and adventurers on today's podcast, The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, a podcast whose hosts belong to a secret society called Sun,
the society of obedience and niceness.
My name is Mike Carlson.
Joining me as always, another member of Sun, Jason Sheridan.
Exploration continuum, Michael.
But we don't need to explore, we're already obedient and nice.
We take that wherever we explore to.
That's true.
Also, Sun member Scott Gairdner is here.
Yeah, I'm a forced member, a member from birth.
You don't like this?
Whether I like it or not.
As an obedient, nice person, I can't call into question whether I like it or not.
I have to.
Yeah, that's a good point.
When we were all born, we got into this last week.
I think when we were born, this was our, yeah, as you're saying, our birthright was to become
members of this group.
Our mothers made it so that we had to be members of Sun, the society of obedience and niceness.
It's a society with all male members, but you're only initiated by your mother.
But I'm sure there's some listeners out there who are members of Sun, or if not, they like
to make fun of members of Sun.
I think a lot of members of Sun are out there.
I think we're a big group.
It's a big secret.
Maybe, you know what, maybe it's not so secret.
Yeah, it's like the Freemasons at this point.
Everyone knows about it.
Right.
Freemason.
Wow, they're actually maybe connected?
Because we're going to find so many connections today.
We're already doing it, which is very exciting.
It really is all about connections, isn't it?
This entire thing is about how do we connect as many disparate things as possible, and
maybe it'll add up into something like a television series.
Finally, maybe have the lightning rod that pulls it all together.
I have a table.
I have a chart.
I made a chart to try and keep track of all this.
By no means definitive, but the notes were just getting out of hand.
I was like, maybe if I use columns and rows, this will be a little cleaner.
I have two notes on my computer, pages full of stuff.
I was going to organize it, and then I went, I can't even.
I just started throwing stuff up.
I'm like, if I get to this, I get to this.
If I get to the connection to the Bengal barbecue, we get to it.
If we don't, don't worry about it.
I have much less than usual because I was sure that you two would have charts and overflowing
documents.
This worked out great.
Before I say any more, just in case everybody didn't read the description or doesn't know
what this is, we're talking about something called C today, the Society of Explorers.
And adventurers, which is something that started in 2001, which is a narrative and characters
that tie the Disney parks together, whether it be through restaurants, whether it be through
water parks, rides.
It's mainly restaurants.
That's what I've found.
The restaurants are the keystone.
When you have to explain what is this thing and who are these characters, or they kind
of tie together a lot of rides.
Actually, wait, if you do the stockpile, though, it's mainly like, here's a picture frame at
a restaurant.
There's a lot.
Yeah, it's like, yes, it's basically like if you were watching like a Marvel movie and
you just a lot of the secrets in it where, well, there was a picture on the wall.
If you look at when Tony Stark was eating at like Burger King, that's the secret connection.
So it's yes, as you're saying, it's primarily maybe not primarily, but there's a lot of
connections to see at places you eat a quick service or medium service meal.
We're tying together the Disney quick service restaurants with old stodgy people from the
late 1800s.
That I guess is what.
And when you put it like that, it's funnier.
And I maybe even like it more.
Because what's so much what's what's more fun than just tying a bunch of just cafeterias
together with a narrative like that's fantastic.
Yeah, restaurants that you say like, yeah, it's pretty good.
I don't know that any of these places have I heard like, oh, you have to eat there because
of the quality of the food.
It's like, oh, it's pretty good.
It's good in a pinch.
Sure. Well, now that you're saying that, I'm thinking like, wouldn't that be great if any
of these restaurant groups that own multiple restaurants, wouldn't it be fantastic if they
would tie like anyone who Landry's owns?
Wouldn't that be fantastic if there was a Landry's universe that could tie with characters
from the 1800s or anything like KFC, Taco Bell and Pizza Hut?
Who do you have with Landry's Bubba Gump's in there, right, which is similar to in C,
it's a bunch of characters and mainly their original.
But there's also one from the Indiana Jones universe.
Similarly, that means that in the Landry verse you have Bubba.
I don't remember Bubba's last name and Forrest Gump.
So they're part of it.
And then you have to go into like what else is Landry?
Morton's, Mane House, Chris.
Morton's Morton Morton.
Mr. Morton is a character.
Mr. Morton, the frog from Rain Carp Forest Cafe.
P.H. Charts, the founder of Chart House.
P.H. Charts. And that and that bull, that frog from the Rainforest Cafe.
He's the owner, I assume.
Yeah, the golden nugget itself, the hunk of gold.
Maybe they're all hunting for the golden nugget.
It's like a rat race kind of thing.
Look how this makes it now.
Dining is way more fun at a Landry's restaurant.
Now that we flesh this out, just a tad.
Looking for clues.
And the more the more you spend, the more clues you find.
That's right. And you can do it.
Any of the restaurant groups, you could do it.
Do it on Twitter.
Let us know what restaurant groups you want to have their own cinematic
universe or universe that's connected via just pictures on the wall.
Do you think TGI Friday and
Fuddrucker are friends in part of a shared universe or are they bitter enemies?
While they both like to collect a bunch of crap
to put on their walls, crazy crap on the walls is Uncle Mo.
Similar to the members of C who have all collected trinkets
from their travels across the world, except in the case of TGI Friday
and Fuddrucker, it's all garbage.
Everything costs five dollars or less.
Yes. And I'm going to quickly side note, I'm remembering now
that a friend of mine had an idea for Jason that I don't even know
if we ever told him about, like a TV show where Jason owned a TGI Fridays.
And he was like a guy who would go on a mission to try to get a new piece
of crap to put on his wall.
And he was like a Harrison Hightower type character.
And that was before I even knew who Harrison Hightower was.
This is great. That's actually, by the way, a great idea that I should
we should pursue.
Yeah, we should.
It would be like you would be like on an Indiana Jones adventure
and you would like find an artifact to put in your restaurant.
Yeah. Or a new fabricator, a new a new printer to make a pennant
that says like hometown USA.
Yeah. Because some of the places, if you look at like an apple piece,
this is like, wait, that has the impression of the town it's in.
But it's not quite right. Right. Not specific.
But I like to think TGI Friday and Fuddrucker hate each other's fucking guts.
That's better. Yeah. Yeah.
Dramatic there.
So if maybe Jason is a third, Jason is.
Yeah. Yeah. Another in this lineup of Jason is a third,
meaning like he gets together with them after hours or.
Oh, could be that too. Yes.
Yeah, that's a whole other ballpark.
I mean, it could be it's like strong, strong personality.
Like, like I feel like Harrison Hightower, the third and Barnabas
T Bullion are kind of at each other's throats.
I would imagine maybe maybe also feuding with disgraced member
Professor Garrett Reed, who knows?
OK, you know, we all have our own head cannons.
So you're going to OK, if you if you're listening to this and you vaguely know
what we're talking about as far as C is concerned,
we're going to be throwing a lot of names at you.
A lot of names, a lot of restaurants.
I would say maybe here's the thing.
Either really try to keep up, get a piece of paper handy
or just let it go and enjoy the ride and enjoy the jokes
because there's going to be I have so much information written down.
I apologize for this because it's going to be hard to keep track of all of it.
Yeah, because once characters from classic films start showing up
and actual real life explorers out of honorariums, you know.
Yes. Yeah.
It's where I thought it would be helpful in a way.
I'm justifying my relative laziness, which is like,
I'm like, OK, if we if I genuinely don't know things,
maybe I can serve as the listeners stand in.
Right. And when you say Jason Chandler, I can say who the hell is Jason Chandler?
Now, I do not see clearly, you know, Jason Chandler is,
although there's there's multiple versions of him, you know.
Oh, my God.
But I but then there's like all these because I still almost am like,
how do you have we even explained what this is?
It's all of these.
It's all of these characters who who who love to travel and explore the world
and they bring their goods back to these Disney parks locations.
I don't think it's literally I think I think there's all a suspension of disbelief.
It's not like they all work at Disneyland.
Like you're supposed to assume you're going to another world
when you're in the Jungle Cruise or the Tower of Terror.
But they like in some cases, it's the owner of the ride or the owner of the restaurant
or or this character is just somebody who frequents the establishment.
Some of these characters appear in the rides and some of them
have never appeared in anything.
There's not even a picture to go along with it.
So it's all extremely confusing.
Yeah, it's the shared universe.
It's the shared canon of like the adventuring kind of flavor
of parks, attractions and parks
or adventure like comics and and the Dr.
Livingston style explorers, but with the rough edges of like
accidentally giving smallpox to remote tribes or colonizing it for the British Empire.
All of that, like, you know, sand it off, all those rough edges, you know.
Right. Yes. Just the fun of taking things from people.
Helmets and camaraderie.
And yes, and that's an interesting thing, too.
And that's what we will talk about is like some people are bad
when they take stuff from like native cultures and that some people are nice, I guess.
Some people, they like it when they take stuff away from.
So I'm not sure about that.
We'll get into that.
But it's got saying, I feel like I have to keep like adding more explanation
in case you still don't know we're talking about like it's like, yes, characters,
as he was saying, like that have been created,
that you can find now links between things.
So you can see like, yes, as you're saying, a picture of the owner
of Big Thunder Mountain Railroad, who we've mentioned before, Barnabas T. Bullion.
And then you can, you know, you can read about him in a comic
that's published about Big Thunder Mountain Railroad.
And Mario Chenier is a character who is represented in Typhoon Lagoon.
But you also can see references to her on the Disney Cruise lines.
So these are like these are things for people like us to notice.
This is not for dad.
You know, this is for you, the listener, to tell your more, say,
civilian family and friends and them to go like, oh, neat.
OK. Yeah.
But this is to me what I've and I'm not trying to be a wet blanket in this episode,
but here's what I have to admit.
And maybe to me, I'm viewing this as sort of a make me like it endeavor,
because I think all this is interesting.
I even like we I mean, we've talked about doing an episode about it for a long time,
but I suggest we do it now because there is this news of a television series
maybe coming about all this from the creator of Battlestar Galactica.
Or not not the original, but the guy who knew it.
Yeah. Among other things.
But so that sort of mobilized, oh, here we should do an episode about it now,
because we might all be delving deep into the world of sea soon enough.
But I so I think it's all neat.
And I thought it was worth talking about.
But I always hit a wall.
I'm always like, which I will probably hit for 20 minutes in the episode.
We've been talking about all of these mostly unseen characters for far too long.
But also, and maybe you guys can agree, and it's kind of what Jason was just
alluding to, I have definitely started talking about this or somebody's asked.
So what's up with that sea thing?
And I will start explaining and I will watch the glaze over.
I will watch the person lose interest as I am talking.
And then it kind of comes to a quiet sputter.
Is this foreign to do you guys?
Have you guys found yourselves?
Oh, so C is this group of characters invented that tie together.
And then people just kind of like, uh, what's that now?
That's a good question.
I don't know that anyone's ever asked me to explain C to them.
I think C is something you have to find yourself.
If you're asking me about C and you, and you didn't put the time into Google C,
chances are you are going to do what you say and glaze over.
If you catch a glimpse of C, even with a slight understanding
that has something to do with Disney parks, I think if you're the type of person
who wants to Google and go down the rabbit hole, then you're going to be into it.
But as you're saying, if you mentioned C in a sentence and somebody goes,
Oh, what's that?
Just say, Oh, I misspoke.
I didn't say, did I say C?
Oh, I meant, uh, I was talking about C, like the wall, the ocean, like,
and then they'll go and then they'll get confused and then just change the subject.
But if you want to double down, what you can say is, well, actually,
if you look up a video interview with the Imagineer, Joe Lance, Lance Acero,
uh, you'll hear him say it S E A.
And that's interesting.
That might, I'm not sure if that's how he refers to it or if it's so as to not
confuse the listeners, the reviewers of that video with Disney.
Um, you know what I will hear?
You know what I will say though, is that having them do a show about C and maybe
incorporate, who knows, they could just change it into a bunch of sexy teenagers.
I'm not sure exactly what Ron DeMora's plan is.
Jungle Cruise movie with the rock.
Yes.
And where does that fit in?
That's confusing.
I think there's elements.
I've heard a rumor there's elements in there, but I would say being on TV.
Would really help see out in a lot of ways, because as we're seeing now with
Marvel, how popular it is, there's according to like, no one ever, like
people trash Marvel, but it's the most popular thing still 10 years running.
Jason and I as little kids are vindicated because the Marvel canon 80 years of it
is what you're saying is eyes glaze over.
What is the, how many times has vision done?
He's gone bad and good and like what version, how many X-Men teams are there?
10?
What?
At once?
Yes.
Well, there's X factor and X caliber.
All of this stuff that Jason and I told other kids on a playground and they glazed
right over and wanted to push us and maybe did push us down.
Like, I think thou making it into movies and TV has made it easier to digest.
It's more digestible to see it versus just to hear it from a giant loser.
It's a billion dollar industry, baby.
That's the traditional trappings of the society of the road.
It's so much where everyone's taking comfort in the obscure shared universes of pop
culture, detritus of the 20th century.
Exactly.
So cut to cut to five to 10 years, you're going to be talking about Harrison
Hightower with everyone, you know, like, did you, can you believe what happened
at what Harrison Hightower did at the end of season three and like everybody's
going to be a flutter and then they're going to realize it was in the parks
already and their minds going to be blown.
And I'm cool because I was in on the ground floor right far before the debut of
the of three seasons of Merryweather on on Disney Plus.
Exactly.
So when they need to address Albert the monkey shoplifting troubles, like
on Breaking Bad, you know.
So I so well, yeah, I yes, TV will will help because as we I mean, yes, there
being a television show about all this is better than it's a bunch of like
etchings in parks that in cruise ships and parks that are mostly not in America.
Like, I think that's some of why this has remained sort of quiet, this quiet
gurgle. There was very little sign of see it felt like in the American parks
until the last five years.
I was pretty I think I think the first I heard about it might have been on this
podcast from you at some point in time.
I mean, it's not something I've known about for too long.
I certainly was not aware of it when Disney see open or anything.
It took me maybe about in the last five, seven years is when I first noticed it.
Obviously, they put a lot more stuff in Disneyland and little references at this
point. So, yeah, I think that, yeah, at this point, the awareness.
It's skyrocketing.
Yes, yes.
Genuinely, I mean, when you look around when this was announced that there's
going to be a show set in this world, I was impressed like, oh, there is a lot of
coverage of this and there's kind of a lot of confident articles saying, you
know, it's the society from the Disney parks as if people know what it is, which
maybe more people do than I think or they will soon.
Yeah, I think I think at this point, maybe people have heard the name and know a
little bit about it at the very least.
If you're a nerd at this point about this stuff.
Can I start by dispelling a misconception about C?
Please.
OK, the Adventurers Club is not the original iteration.
The Adventurers Club was retconned into C.
The first attraction to mention C is a Tokyo Disney Sea exploration, like
a play area, essentially, for sex exploration.
Explorations. Yes.
Yeah. The Adventurers Club gets grandfathered in because what happens in
the real world is the Adventurers Club closes down in 2009, 2009,
yeah, 2009, 2008, thereabouts.
And the the props and such gets scattered to the winds.
And then the Adventurers Club kind of gets retconned in.
Scott, do you know about retconning?
I know that is the something is not part of a canon and then is sort of pulled into
a canon after the fact.
Right. Yes.
Yeah. A lot of the Fast and the Furious movies, a lot of retconning going on as
they have just gotten bigger and bigger and bigger.
They've gone like, by the way, these take place in the first place.
And then the Adventurers Club is kind of like a little bit more of a
by the way, these take place after number three.
You have to watch that, watch them in this order.
OK, I know suddenly these characters have iPhones and they have flip phones.
Don't worry about that.
Don't think too hard on that.
That's the defining of the rules.
And in that franchise, like, why are some of the why do some of the movies
have none of the characters from the rest of them?
Yes, correct. Yes.
You know, that's character finding themselves off on their own adventures.
Right. So what you're saying is like,
that when the Adventurers Club opened, it was not this whole concept
was not conceived of yet.
But the DNA of Adventurers Club, I think, is you can definitely see where it leads
to the Imagineers then in 2001, starting this idea
that they could link everything together and then, of course, retconning
Adventurers Club and then ultimately and Jungle Cruise and Jungle Cruise.
Rides that existed long before there was any of this.
And now we're going backwards and saying these characters are part of it.
And now we've even though we just thought of Barnabas T.
Bullion, the owner of the mining company this decade,
we're going to act like this was always part of the plan in the 70s when it
when it opened. Yes, exactly.
Should we just start with listing?
And I say, I think we've said this five times.
Well, we should start with and then we've said something.
And then I keep going, yeah, we should start with.
But should we list the characters maybe?
Maybe that's the best way to start.
Just say here are the characters.
The list take do you does the list?
Do we have to say that because some of the.
Well, yeah, I guess you're right.
I've only got to read. What does that mean?
I've only got about 30 members. It's OK.
All right. You know, you drive the.
OK, let's let's try it.
Look, feel free to cut me off.
Feel free to push me down as a child on a playground would be when I explain
to him who the third summer's brother might be in the X-Men comics.
In the same way, feel free to push Jason or I down.
OK, but verbally.
So, OK, Harrison Hightower is a member of C.
He is a character that you can find in Tokyo Disney.
See, he is the eccentric bad man.
I call he's the he's the baddest member of C.
I think he's the most evil, the worst.
He owns the Tower of Terror there.
And he was killed because he put a cigar out on like a tiki idol
and the idol killed him.
And you're caught.
It's not the Twilight Zone in Japan.
It is this other story about this character and this tiki idol
putting a curse on him and therefore you. Yes.
And there's a you know, we've obviously went on ad nauseam
about how great Tokyo Disney see.
And this is like one of the best rides on top of all of that greatness.
And it features a lot of very funny art
of him stealing things from around the world with his manservant Smelding.
Now is Smelding a part of C?
Is he a member of C?
I don't believe Harrison Hightower's
assistant Smelding is part of C.
A lot of there's a lot of great assistants on this list,
but I don't believe he's an official member.
I think he might be a adjacent or old superhero trading cards
would refer to someone as an ally of this team. Right. Exactly.
There's a lot of adjacent members, people around C. Right.
OK, a lot of people performatively on Twitter saying that they're allies of C.
It's a bit much, don't you think?
Well, yeah, you know, you want to show, not tell.
I feel like when you're an ally, you know, you want to be an ally of C.
But yeah. So all right.
Lord Henry Mystic is a member of C.
He is the man who owns Mystic Manor, which is in Hong Kong, Disneyland.
In the tree, it's barely discussed on this podcast.
Sort of a stand in for the haunted mansion.
It isn't exactly the haunted mansion, but they don't have the haunted mansion
in Hong Kong, and they do have Mystic Manor. Right.
They have Mystic Manor there.
He has a sidekick who I don't believe is a member.
It's a he's a monkey named Albert.
And he's the one Albert is the one who kind of takes you on the journey.
I cave during quarantine.
I had never watched it before thinking like, I'll get to Hong Kong one day.
I caved. I watched it.
I watched a little. Yeah, it's great.
I get it. I'll forget before I go.
It looks so fantastic.
I mean, this feels like one of those could be top 10 attractions anywhere.
But you have to go to know.
Yeah, I'm counting Albert the monkey as a member.
OK, but that's new.
Or you found information that I thought I think he's in.
Just from his number of appearances.
This feels like you can and though.
Well, it depends if you if you use Bengal barbecue as a keystone
and Bengal barbecue and tropical hideaway.
It depends. Harrison Eye Tower.
Do you should we mention every appearance of these characters when you name them?
That seems like too much, doesn't it?
Let's let's clip notes and we'll go back and we'll go back to talking about it.
I just want everyone to have like a baseline for like who we're talking about as we go.
And friend, just if you're wondering, just try to visualize
if you're like lost with all these names, just visualize an old white guy
with a beard or mustache, probably probably.
For the most part, unless we say it's a lady.
Yes, yes, which there are a few.
And then picture like Mary Steenburgen and Back to the Future three.
That's like they all do look kind of close. Yeah.
OK, so yeah, Henry Mist.
Now, Henry Mystic, I believe, is supposedly like a good guy,
even though he does the exact same stuff that Harrison High Tower does.
This is what I was saying before.
He collects artifacts and brings them back to Mystic Manor.
But for whatever reason, he smiles more and he looks friendlier.
So I guess he's OK. I guess he's a nicer man.
Maybe he gives money to people around the world for their artifacts or for their goods.
I'm not sure exactly.
Ask permission in the way it's more like Joe Roady would do.
Joe Roady, who travels to places like Nepal, the Imagineer,
and collects items and puts them in the cues of Disney attractions.
Presumably with permission.
Presumably this is a good thing to do, even though Harrison
High Tower, the bad character, looks like Joe Roady.
Several of these characters look very much like the the actual Imagineers.
Yeah, which is alternatively.
Part of me thinks it's cool.
And part of me thinks it's a little lame.
I can't quite decide.
I think with Barnabas, T Bullion and Harrison High Tower, it's teasing a little
because it's like, you know, they're there.
You know, High Tower is the opposite of how Joe Roady behaves, you know,
who Joe Roady tries to be respectful when he goes to other cultures.
Well, on the yeah.
Well, I will say this next character first and Barnabas T Bullion,
as we just mentioned, who looks like Imagineer Tony Baxter,
who owns Big Thunder Mountain Railroad.
He was another character who, when I look around at information, I go,
oh, he's he was a tyrant, too.
He was bad as well.
And then I and then I'm sure you guys read this or maybe not on the Wikipedia
that in Disney Kingdoms, which that's other the stories,
the comics, I believe, right?
Yeah, I don't know what Disney Kingdoms is.
Disney Kingdoms is the Disney Comics land that Marvel has quickly abandoned.
Right. That's gone. That's done.
That was to their two figment comic series,
a Big Thunder series and a Museum of the Weird series.
So this ties together quick service restaurants and abandoned comic lines.
Yes. Oh, my God.
No one's listening anymore.
Everyone turned it off. This is one of those.
Oh, Monday, stay away from this one.
Oh, my gosh. Just bail right now. This is. Oh.
So Barnabas T Bullion, I read here, apparently
the sympathetic interpretation of Barnabas in Disney Kingdoms
was the result of talks the author had with Tony Baxter,
who wanted the character inspired by him to be more of a redeemable figure.
Makes sense. A character looks like you.
You don't want him to be a mean, awful, like a Daniel Plainview type
of like murderous, negligent.
Yeah, sure. Munger.
I but Goldmine owner was not synonymous with good person,
much like we recently discussed the phrase Casino Magnet is not
usually short and for you.
Yeah, that's true.
So Barnabas is there.
And if you've read the Disney Kingdoms, he's nicer than you might think.
You know, that's what they're saying.
If you've read the Disney, if you read, have you guys read the Disney Kingdoms?
I have not read the kingdoms.
Big Thunder, I think one day we will revisit and I promise to read them before that.
Also, I do not make this promise.
I want to give an update. The Mr. Tato autobiography is on its way.
All right. Wow. It's on its way here.
OK. Captain Tato, not a member of C.
Not yet. He is a he is a potato character from a park in Ireland.
That has nothing to do with Disney.
Just to clarify, he hates the Pringles guy.
Their enemies are not.
It's sense to me. Well, the Pringles guy wants him dead.
That's right. He wants him and his kind fried up.
That's right. Although, wait, Mr.
Tato also sells fried potatoes, but he has permission.
He kills his friends and says, can I make you delicious
for people all over Ireland to enjoy? Right.
And they said they appreciate they they like a self sacrifice.
Feels good to them.
Do it for the cause. Yes.
OK. Captain Mary Oceaneer.
She is represented, as I said, in Typhoon Lagoon now.
She has a slide.
The slide is Misadventure Falls. Yes.
And she has a sidekick as well.
It's a parrot named Salty.
I like Salty a lot and Salty.
This is, I believe, from the YouTube video I was watching.
Salty is the first or or only animatronic
that you could see on a water slide.
Really? Disney parks, at least, if not around the world.
Salty, a member of C.
I don't know. Let's ask Jason. Jason has opinions on this.
Well, you know, it's when you start getting into the animal.
I mean, we'll have to I bet we'll have a ruling by the end
whether the animal sidekicks or or not.
Mary Oceaneer, also the namesake of Oceaneer Labs
on the Disney Cruise Line, Disney Magic Ship, a children's play area,
which names check name checks multiple members of C.
Misadventure Falls, the diving bell outside
has Atlantean text on it, which connects it to Atlantis, the Lost Empire,
the film. So presumably Atlantis, the Lost Empire is is
that is part of the canon.
Yes. So the character voiced by Michael J.
Fox, and I don't know his name, is he a member of of C?
Is Mr. Atlantis a member of C?
I'm going with Jason on to be the C judge here.
As far as I think, yeah, I think he would be a Jason.
Because there will eventually hit.
There's a character down the line that I would describe as an aspiring member of C.
You know, well, we all, you know, I should be so lucky.
All right. Dr. Albert Falls.
OK. Jungle Cruise Skipper Canteen.
Does he own he owns the Skipper Canteen?
Sorry, I Jason probably has even more complete information.
I think there's something like that.
Skipper Canteen, Bengal Barbecue, Tropical Hideaway.
It ties together a lot of these people.
Dr. Albert Falls that comes from the joke on the Jungle Cruise about like, you know,
Dr. Albert, this these waterfalls are named after Dr. Albert Schweitzer.
And it's why he named them.
Wait, what is that? How does the joke?
It's something like that.
It's something like that. That had no ending or beginning.
Some of the words you said were part of that joke.
Yeah. Yeah.
What's the joke? The joke is that it's named.
Wait, Schweitzer Falls and it's named after Dr. Schweitzer named it.
Oh, it's named after the one who discovered Dr. Albert Falls.
OK. I think. Oh, it's it's Schweitzer.
No, Schweitzer Falls.
Yeah, the joke is that you think it's named after somebody named Schweitzer,
but in fact, it's named after somebody named Falls. Right. Yes.
Got it. Joke really clungily.
And it's named after a person named Cannon.
Mm hmm.
Yeah. And kind of this is like a very old school Jungle Cruise joke.
And it's a very throw away this name.
Like, I don't think anybody thought there's an expanded universe.
Dr. Albert Falls.
That's like a like a like a sex pun name from a joke
your grandpa would tell you suddenly being there's all universe around
an IP freely or some such.
Really in C.
I do not think IP freely is it say or at least toilet magnet IP freely
expelled by Vitaly Rubusdeli.
All right. I mean, I wanted to wait for a while, but Ronald DeMore, please
create a character named IP freely for Jason to play.
If you're not going to cast him as Harrison High Towers
assistant smelding, please
connect all the characters from sex jokes, dirty limericks,
get them all in one place.
Please is the man from Nantucket in C.
Put the man from Nantucket in C.
That's where the group meets.
The way current television is written, an episode will end on a hard line
of someone going like we have to return to Nantucket like don't.
That's great. As long as once was a man from there.
The password to get into the C building,
the pass, the code phrase will be the backside of water.
So shortly a character will say his dying breath.
You'll think he's dead.
Characters don't die that much in Disney stuff.
You know, there's a handful do or they come back.
You know, these characters, well, they're all I mean, they're all dead
because this all happened.
These are entirely characters from the 1800.
Nobody is modern and in C. Correct.
18, 1900, Harrison Hightower
disappears on New Year's Eve, 1899.
That event occurs. Right.
But there are no current members of C.
Yeah, that's a good point.
That's a good question.
Even upon that, that's an interesting question.
I mean, that's definitely room for another 50 to 100 names.
To talk about, obviously, when a future podcast, but yeah, that would be
that would be worth exploring, I think,
maybe in season 12 or whatever of C.
You kind of cut to the present day of these.
Maybe it's maybe that's what links tomorrowland together with C.
To more Brad Bird's Tomorrowland, I didn't say Brad Bird's Tomorrowland.
I just said Tomorrowland.
Well, there is kind of the one this episode will take
so much work on my part, because I am the one who has the like
50 page document that explains it.
There was a
I forget what the term is, but it's like a game that takes place in real life.
There was a lead up to the release of Tomorrowland called The Optimist
that connected actual like Walt and Imagineer history
with like L.A. landmarks, Griffith Park, Chilly John's and Burbank.
And part of the mythology, Chilly John.
This is what we're dreaming of.
Yeah. Landry verse.
So there is kind of like it.
There was something that was kind of an imagineer movie
version of like the World's Fair kind of futurism.
So I guess that's experienced by 45 people in 2010.
Yeah. And those people's lives were changed forever.
You know, that's the thing.
It's but each one of them, you know,
there wasn't the most popular themed experience,
but each one of them started their own themed experience after they did it.
That's what's great.
None of which are the most popular themed.
No, but it can continue to sort of continue to one of those people's eventual
and it's not an ideal time to be the owner of an escape room.
You know, that's true. So.
OK, how many more to go?
OK, we don't know.
There might not be a bottom.
If we just say the major one.
Camel, Camelia Falco, Camelia Falco,
the star of Soaring Fantastic Flight at Tokyo,
Disney is the daughter of Salino Falco
and the first woman inducted into sea.
So she beats in canon.
She beats a Marriott chanier,
even though Marriott chanier was created before her.
Yes. And you can see a photo or a painting of the tail of the taily
vital. I don't know how to say it.
This episode is unreleased.
The the then president of sea inducting her.
And you can see sea members in the background of this painting.
You can see Lord Henry.
Got it. All right.
Let's get let's cruise a little bit faster here.
Jack Lindsay from Indiana Jones is a member of sea.
This is canon. This is canon.
It is noted in his bar in.
I always get confused who Jack Lindsay is in the movies.
What is Jack Lindsay in the movies?
He is not one of the most famous characters.
He is the pilot that flies in the away from the people
chasing him at the start of Raiders of the Lost Ark.
And Indy freaks out because there's a snake in the passenger seat
and jocks like, ah, it's fine.
And that's it. That's what he is.
Who owns the bar, Scott?
And he's got a bar.
His sea membership is confirmed in the bar.
Yes. So he's a member of sea.
And that bar is at Disney Springs in Florida.
In Florida. Yes.
Jason Chandler is a member of sea.
He built Big Thunder Mountain Railroad.
Well, he he invented the drilling tool.
That is used in Big Thunder Mountain Railroad.
Now, he also shows up, as we say, to Tropical Hideaway Skipper
Canteen. He's in the Disney Kingdom's comic.
He's he's I think in the background, in the painting, in Soaring Fantastic
Flight. But the thing I thought was interesting about Jason Chandler
originally made for Discovery Bay, the unbuilt section, right?
Unbuilt, you know, kind of Jules Verne inspired expansion
that was going to go into Disneyland that was dependent on the success
kind of of the Island at the Top of the World film, which was not successful.
That brings us to Captain Brio,
the star of the Island at the Top of the World.
He is in sea and was going to play a part in Discovery Bay.
Right. But that movie was not a hit.
So, oh, well, but they did not take his membership away
despite the movie underperforming at the box office.
They did not. And in fact, you can see his airship
in the Hyperion restaurant at Disneyland Paris Tomorrowland.
The airship that's bursting out of the worst restaurant
maybe I've ever been to.
The worst burger, the true if no question, the worst burger I've had in my life.
Wow. Was it the worst one?
Yeah, so, so bad.
I know we got the gripe that I am too hard on Disneyland Paris several times.
And I do blame food for that.
Food is so bad, or at least was on that day.
Maybe it's gotten better.
Maybe I was just hit a bad time.
I don't know. But we did.
And it kind of broke my heart because I have always loved that that building,
this cafe with this cool airship, you know, like a zeppelin flying out of it,
which is sort of what Tony Baxter wanted this Discoveryland area to look like.
Yeah, it sucks. There's just a bad restaurant in there.
But it's very cool from the outside. Yeah.
So those are the major ones.
We can we can say other ones as if they come up here.
But those are the major. I want to just there's going to be plenty of lists
that throwing you with this and the rest of this podcast.
But well, I have a couple couple.
I would say big ones.
OK, I apologize. That's OK.
They only mostly show up in paintings because of who they are.
Professor R. Blow and him or Blower Himmel.
And let's see our Blower.
Himmer is not a major member of C, but I think he's only in a painting.
He's in a painting.
But it's based on imagineer.
I believe it's pronounced Rops Coltrane.
And then these pronunciations.
I don't know how to say this guy's name. I looked for videos.
I found how to say Joe Lance Cicero,
and he is the inspiration for Dr.
J.L. Baturista, who shows up in the Mystic Manor Portrait
and Tropical Hideaway as well as Charlton J.
Tabaret. He is in the Mystic Manor Portrait of C.
He is based on the artist Chris Turner, who designed a lot of this stuff.
Can you explain?
Because I know I am so lost.
The Mystic Manor portrait.
What is the significance of this?
This is one of the early,
you know, documentations of C.
I'll share the screen here.
You'll see this come up a lot.
OK, yes. In my my find, yes, I've seen this painting.
And this kind of is like maybe the the the most major
work that shows all the members, maybe not all,
but a bunch of the members all in one place.
Yeah. A lot of the main members, a few of the imagineer based
members, a couple that are listed as unidentified, but they're speculation.
It's like, oh, that's supposed to be Jason Chandler. But it's unclear.
So all right.
Let's say if this image will tweet it or it'll be like the main image
of the show, of the episode, let's this.
So I think will be helpful if you the listeners looking at a photo
of a bunch of people in brown clothes and it is a banner up top.
It says Society of Explorers and Adventures 1899.
Let's go left to right. Who is who?
That's not that's Harrison Hightower, the third with his with a fez and the idol.
Yeah. The fezzes are a big thing.
It's the fezzes are the membership
like thingies there.
There's a lot of fezzes throughout the world.
Even though most of the people in this photo are not wearing the fezzes.
Yes, that's correct. You don't have to.
This next one, I believe, is Professor R.
Blower Himmel. Seated is Lord Henry Mystic.
I forget which one this is.
See, might be unidentified.
Here's Bartabas T. Bullion.
This one, I believe, is listed as unknown than Mary O'Shaver.
I know there's unknowns in that.
That's Dr. Dr. P.L.
Trevors. Yeah.
Name the great grandfather of the film critic for Rolling Stone magazine.
No, no. Of the Mary Poppins author.
OK, yes.
That's Peter Trev.
Is P.L. Trevor's related to Peter Travers from Rolling Stone?
I don't know. Well, not in reality, but in the retcon Trevor verse.
Yes, the Travors.
Mary O'Shaver and then Charlton J.
Tabaret on the end.
When you just said who Tabaret is, but where else can we see Tabaret again?
He can be found on a napkin in the restaurant
in Disneyland that's located next to the Bank of Barbecue.
I think mostly here.
Let's see. What other members are there?
Oh, I've got something.
There's is there's a big one. Go ahead, Jason.
Oh, do you have Maestro de Elfman?
That's exactly where I was going.
This is so stupid to me.
So one thing you might not know about the ride Mystic Manor
is that it has an original score by Danny Elfman,
one of the great film composers of all time.
You all know Danny Elfman.
And so thus they're in this in the queue is where a lot of the paintings
exist of these characters.
And I guess they consider a member of C to be.
What is his name in this again?
Maestro de Elfman. Yeah, it's just Danny Elfman.
It's just a caricature of Danny Elfman.
Maestro de Elfman.
And then it's an 1800s style photo of clearly the current musician,
Danny Elfman.
This one just feels lazy to me. Maestro de Elfman.
Would you say you were looking for more of a character for him?
Or you just think it's lazy putting Danny Elfman's face in there?
Hmm. Yeah. What would what would satisfy me here?
I mean, look, it's not, you know,
it's not mastered to Baxter.
They didn't just make it to one off of Tony Baxter.
It looks like but they made up a character.
I think I do want more.
How about like, yeah, like JP Notesman?
Works for me. That's what I do.
And I fixed it. Yeah.
Yeah. Just change the beginning.
I'm doing great. Yeah.
OK, that's good.
I think Danny Maestro de Elfman is definitely the most famous
of the sea members visually because he's the most famous man.
No offense to Tony or Joe Rody, but Joe Rody.
They were not annoying. Oh boy. Oh, let's be honest.
Yeah, there's no music videos, I don't believe, with Joe Rody
and a band that he was in. Right.
There are in terms of retcon, Mary Weather, Adam Pleasure.
Yes, that's right. Yes, he is a big guy.
I apologize for leaving him out.
Retconned. He is the creator of Pleasure Island.
Adventurers Club is was retconned to be like his outpost of sea.
And by extension, there is a letter at Alani, the Hawaii Resort,
from Pamela Perkins, who was a character.
She was the president of the Adventurers Club.
So she, I guess by default in that letter, she mentions Harrison Hightower.
And it's funny because Joe Rody, there's multiple tweets from Joe Rody
going like, huh? Yeah, no, I did not create sea.
The Adventurers Club was just the thing we did.
He's like, wasn't that fan made like wasn't a fan connections?
But eventually it seems like he started to play along a little more.
I mean, I don't know if he put that thing in Alani or another imagineer
did that. But a lot of Rody stuff,
including Rody himself, kind of have been grandfathered in to see.
I I'm interested to know, and this is probably not something
it'll ever be public. I am interested to know how
a Tony Baxter or other imagineers might feel about all of a sudden
a backstory coming onto a ride they may have created.
I bet they might be a bit conflicted because now if the actual like
retconning they've done of Big Thunder is there's like a ghost in Big Thunder
that's disrupting gold mining and runaway trains are happening
versus I think the original concept of Big Thunder is like
this train has been maintained very poorly.
So be careful getting on it.
And that was basically the premise.
There was no other character like a tyrant who ran the
ran the mining company or anything.
There's there you wouldn't it'd be weird if suddenly.
Oh, well, actually, there was a maniacal madman
who started shrinking people and putting them into his teacups.
And he invented a turntable machine to make them spin wildly
to the to the point of dizziness, to to to
throw people off and mess with their minds.
You're not just getting in a spinning.
The cups are big and you spin around.
But I don't know. I like Scott's because it connects the teacups
and adventures through inner space.
And this is how you do it.
This is how you world build, you know.
It is elsewhere in the magic kingdom, because that's what they're saying about
the sea show is that it's part of building the magic kingdom universe.
What did they what was this show release?
Because there's going to be more of this nonsense.
This doesn't stop at sea.
No, I was working on a movie like a magic kingdom movie a while ago.
And it seems like that got show just like that.
That's a movie. Who cares about movies anymore?
What we need now is universes.
We need this battalions of 200 films
and shows and tick tock accounts.
I don't think they'll build an empire.
I don't. I'm here's a guess.
My guess if we're talking like what they're going to do with TV,
I'm guessing that the show is not going to be about like 15 white colonizers.
Don't think so.
I don't think that seems like a good idea for a show right now.
Or maybe ever, probably ever.
So I assume what they're going to do is maybe take elements of like a secret club
and then try to tie it into famous ride things.
You know, that that would be a guess.
I don't know that to be sure.
They obviously have not spoken to Mr. Moore, but it seems like I'm.
Yeah, it seems like you would want to take elements from all of the different
parts of the parks and then tie them into an idea of a secret club.
Well, this is the speculation in this Hollywood Reporter article
that I just pulled up announcing this Magic Kingdom TV universe
in the works at Disney Plus and Ron Moore is creating all this.
So, yeah, the Magic Kingdom TV universe, there's so much more to go.
Connecting all these parks things and their this is pure speculation
from unnamed sources that then they back.
Let me let me just read this because this is going to confuse the entire thing,
but also lend greetings to what Mike is saying.
It's not just going to be this secret club of people who steal.
Yes. The idea per sources is to explore characters
like sea boat captain from the Jungle Cruise.
No punctuation or prospector from Big Thunder Mountain
or the climbers of the Matterhorn, for example,
as part of the Society of Explorers and Adventures to parenthetical.
To be clear, none of these characters or storylines are currently on the table
at this stage.
So one of the sources and they just Hollywood Reporter
just pulling this out of their ass is because the the climbers of the Matterhorn,
anybody can that's a real place and anybody can climb it.
That's why this free solo retconned into the sea.
Yeah, I mean, I think maybe at the end of the first episode
or the end of the first season, you maybe want to have
like a kid sweeping up and you learn that anybody can be a member of sea.
Yeah, we did get the gripe leave Broome Boy alone.
I know we did, but I like talking about Broome Boy, so I'm sorry.
But we can't invent new Broome Boys that are our invention.
We could do whatever we want with them, because anyone can invent a Broome Boy.
That's correct. That's correct.
Yeah, it always goes well when you flood in right now.
It always goes well when you put a kid in a Star Wars movie.
Actually, I I joke
or two, but as a kid, I really did like the the end or
the kind of made for TV and or movies.
Oh, yeah, I never saw them. Yeah.
Are they are they? Oh, they're traumatic.
Yeah. Oh, no. Yeah.
It's yeah, characters definitely die in those.
And that was upsetting.
But they certainly were on a lot on cable.
Yeah.
So I think, yeah, I think we're going to get a lot of like you'll
whatever property they're not thinking they're going to do for a big movie.
Like they've been they've been, you know, they floored it with the idea
of doing Big Thunder or there was a pilot or something, or at least a script, for sure.
I think stuff like that, they'll say, OK, now we're doing a big thunder show.
And it has an element of one character is in a group in the sea group or whatever.
I don't know if it probably won't be just about Barnabas T.
Bullion. Yeah.
One thing is for sure, all these characters, if it's like Prestige TV
now, they all these characters got depression and they're going to say
something epic and very modern, like in Enola Holmes.
That's where we all get our life lessons from.
There'll be a clap back of some kind.
Oh, there's going to be a lot of clapback.
Oh, Barnabas T.
Barnabas T. Bullion clapback.
Oh, yeah, he will.
He will clap back.
He will be like that CEO who made his
his salary seventy thousand dollars a year and made his employees like he took a massive pay cut.
My pitch would be for Big Thunder would be, OK, you know, Daniel Plainview
from There Will Be Blood, what if he clapped back?
And I think that's going to sell it.
Well, doesn't I mean, killing somebody with a bowling ball is kind of a clapback.
You know, I guess, you know, you're right.
It was before we were calling it that.
Some might call it the ultimate clapback is bashing someone's skull in.
You might call it that.
Speaking of TV shows, I found out while researching this
that apparently there was a Discovery Bay pilot made that did not go
and go anywhere starring Pete Rennaday, who has come up on the show a lot before.
Probably, I think most famously in the parks as the imitator
of the James Mason Captain Nemo in the twenty thousand leagues ride in Florida.
Right. So, yeah, that did.
So they've tried. Yeah.
So so that's probably that could be back on the table as far as the sea verse.
So I'm I'm interested to see where Ronald Moore goes with this.
And look, Ronald, look, if you're listening, which you are, come on, hook us up here.
It doesn't I'll be a P.A. on it. I don't care.
Actually, don't make a P.A. on it.
That's right. Not good. Yeah.
Yeah. No, no, no, no.
I mean, there's a lot of old artifacts.
I was a P.A. and it's hard work.
Yeah. I'm not knocking P.A.s.
It's just it's a pain in the ass.
But now P.A.s are all in charge of covid safety now.
So you really don't want to do it.
It's a good point. God.
It's poor guys.
OK, here's here's a little thing that happened.
OK, so we're talking about there was a reference made to Meriwether Pleasure,
and he is apparently a part of sea.
Well, Pleasure Island and the establishment, the adventures club in it
are not that predates all of this.
It clearly was the source of long rambling backstories
for what is ultimately a restaurant or a nightclub.
Because that's where if you like, if you don't know all this,
if you a while back we did, we covered Pleasure Island with Paul Scheer.
Yeah, Disney wanted to start a nightclub place to put
a downtown Orlando place called Church Street Station out of business.
They wanted there. All right, let's just do nightclubs.
And they did it.
And instead of just it's nightclubs, they it's this whole tale of this
all of Meriwether Pleasure.
And he crashed his ship and he thought this will be the place where I
I don't even I don't remember what the backstory is exactly.
But like it's it's it's it predates seeing that it's a backstory
that almost manifests itself in the experience nowhere.
Like then you're just in a 70s club called eight tracks
and there's no reference made to this old this old man who would hold court.
And so that's the sea philosophy starting, I feel like.
Well, we kind of led me into.
I would say we talked about on the episode, like there's plaques outside.
Yeah, you got to follow the plaques.
And there were these plaques with just pair thick paragraphs
of the explanation.
And this is all roadie.
Well, he didn't invent see he did do all this.
Right. Like insane backstory to a nightclub where you put on
like a funny afro wig and bell bottoms and listen to Casey and Sunshine Band.
But so now here's all that brings me to this.
I I was like, well, maybe I should do some research for this.
Maybe I should learn more about sea.
And that brought me to the Wikipedia that is all about sea.
There is a 100 percent sea wiki.
And I clicked around like, well, what are the most popular pages on this?
Maybe that can find me some odd info.
And when I clicked on that, I found one of the most popular pages
is about the funmeister.
Now, the funmeister, you guys probably know, but as a refresher,
the funmeister and I have a little Parkstar toy of it.
The funmeister is the Pleasure Island moon guy.
He is a bright yellow
party dude who has a moon for a head.
He is not Mack tonight from McDonald's.
He is a different moon guy, but he loves fun and music just as much.
So my childhood awareness of the funmeister is like, oh, yes.
So parents go to these nightclubs and there's this moon guy up on the sign.
And that's sort of where it begins and ends for most people.
Not according to the sea wiki, which let me know
that the funmeister is an ancient
icon with all of this like backstory and meaning.
I'll read as much of this as I can manage without getting bored.
The funmeister, as roughly translated ancient Germanic names called him,
was an ancient being that drove Meriwether Adam Pleasure to establish Pleasure Island.
This half faced moon icon whose roots go back to the barbarians
after the fall of Rome symbolized individuality, the celebration of life
and the sharing of laughter while traveling in Mexico.
Pleasure experienced a mystical vision of the funmeister
that told him to travel to central Florida in 1911.
After bringing his family down the barge canal system aboard a steamboat,
Pleasure saw an ancient totem of the funmeister on the shore.
There he met a ghostly Seminole tribe, informally known as the I-4 Indians,
that allowed Pleasure to set up.
What what is this nonsense? What do you mean?
He is like he's a fun moon man.
He is not an ancient totem.
And then on this wiki, they show a photo of like a wood carved version
of the funmeister as if this was like this was carved by a Seminole tribe.
And then but how does all this square with like
then I saw artwork of the funmeister and he's just like in a zoot suit
leaning up against a wall and like dipping his sunglasses like
picture mythology.
Is he an ancient Indian thing or is he a is he like a like a Chester
cheetah or Chester cheetah?
Yes, that's exactly how he's pictured otherwise.
Mythology gets reinterpreted.
It's like when you do a version of the Odyssey and it's about an American
soldier in the Iraq war trying to get home, you know, to the city of Ithaca
as opposed to the island of Ithaca.
Right. You know, what was that? What did that?
I I believe I don't know if that was ever made.
I I think was that a TV miniseries?
There has been versions where it's just like it's the story of the Odyssey
and the trials and tribulations of Odysseus are like it's World War
Two or it's the Gulf War, you know. Right.
Hmm.
Scott, are you saying, though,
somebody came to you and said, I want you to write a detailed 50 year
history for Macktonite and make a trilogy of films about Macktonite
and his rise to becoming Macktonite.
You were I think you're up for it.
You're up. I don't know if he's a god of some kind.
I mean, you feel free to pitch on it now or not.
I don't care.
Uh, yeah.
I mean, absolutely.
I would love to learn the entire mythology of Macktonite.
The the cool piano playing moon from McDonald's.
Certainly he's got there's like a lineage of musicians.
Like, I think I think the piano playing is in his blood.
Maybe there's sort of a purple rain thing going on.
There's a complicated relationship with his father, who was also a musician,
but didn't, you know, like excel as much as the system.
There's like a jealousy of Mack, who is now a popular restaurant icon.
So imagine like an old like an old, bitter,
wrinkled moon man, sadly drunkenly playing the piano
and then throwing a bottle at Mack.
Right. And then saying, you can't treat me like this, daddy.
And then there's like Ronald show up at the end of the first movie, maybe.
Oh, that's good. I'm putting together a night menu.
Yeah, that's great.
I mean, by Grimace, Grimace is wearing like a like a leisure suit.
Yeah, he's the agent Colson.
Ronald is Nick Fury.
OK. And Grimace is is agent Colson.
OK. Yeah, great.
Who's who? Yeah, who's who?
I guess. Well, Bertie has to be Black Widow, I suppose.
I guess we're going original Avengers.
So I'm just saying you're right that
the fun Meisters origin may be a little bit convoluted, a little bit.
I think, yeah, the problem is it's not rooted in what we know about the fun Meister,
which is that what do we know about him?
He's he wears a bow tie and he likes to dance.
I don't believe that he is an ancient totem.
But hey, this is what they got to do.
This is what you got to do.
It's there if you want it.
You don't need to know it to enjoy it.
But that's what they got to do to make theme parks.
It's like I had to make this chart with like another 15 people we haven't addressed yet.
Can we see the chart?
Yeah, I was on a screen share.
Yeah. Yeah.
So here's the chart.
They made it an apple.
You can put a table in Apple Notes.
You made a table.
Wow. Table.
Because here is adjacent.
I think we should.
Magell. Oh, they're all.
Yeah. So the honorary members that show up in Fortress
explorations are real explorers.
Sir Francis Drake, Leonardo da Vinci, Tycho Brahe,
Vasco da Gama, Cristobal, Cologne, Ferdinand Magellan.
And then there's also places where a sea handbook shows up,
like the UK Pavilion or a sea fez and Abra Kedabar.
OK, let me talk about this real quick.
Abra Kedabar is is related to sea.
And I had no idea until today when I was looking at all this up.
And there's a did you read the backstory about it, Jason?
I read the backstory of Abra Kedabar.
The sea fez doesn't have a lot of backstory, does it?
No, but there's a there's a thing and I have to get out of this view.
Oh, yeah. You unshare.
Now we've seen the table.
Abra Kedabar, the magic themed bar at the Boardwalk Hotel.
Yeah. Is part of the sea verse.
Yes. Did you know that, Scott?
I did not. Along with Captain Cafe Hyperion, we already mentioned
both Trader Sam's, of course, have a lot of sea connections.
OK, so this is the canon explanation of what happened at Abra Kedabar.
This bar once acted as a lounge for some of the world's most famous
magicians and illusionists.
However, this all changed on Friday, the 13th, September 1940,
when every magician inside disappeared without a trace
and have never been seen again.
Among the magicians props around this lounge is a sea fez, as we were saying,
indicating that one that one of the magicians may have been a member of the society.
It's one of them.
So don't worry about the fact that all the magicians disappeared forever.
One of them may have been a member.
We don't know that part of a weird club may have been a member of sea.
Or they I mean, they could have stolen the fez.
As far as like canon, it's not clear, like if you steal a fez and wear it,
does that make you a member?
If you kill a member of sea, do you become a member of sea?
I'm not exactly sure about any of this stuff, but Abrikadair
bar just has a little hint there.
I am I would be interested more in the actual like disappearance
of all those magicians. That seems interesting to me.
And maybe a little more interesting than just somebody finding a dirty fez.
An old, dirty fez.
Jason, what do you think about fez as a look? Is that
I don't know. It feels very, very much like an affectation.
Right. But it'd be perfectly natural.
I don't know.
I bet. Do they sell fezzes at Hong Kong, Disney and Mystic Point?
Probably right.
I mean, I think the Shriners are still around, right?
And the Shriners still wear fezzes.
I mean, I'm sure that's not the best organization to get in.
Is is Abu a member?
Jason of sea or the Shriners of the either one is Abu the monkey.
I would say definitely not the Shriners.
I don't know that there's much a Latin connection.
The other big movie that's kind of adjacent,
the the sole fact of a picture, the Humphrey Bogart, Catherine Hepburn
classic, the African Queen is kind of adjacent to see due to this picture
that hangs next to Bengal Barbecue, featuring Humphrey Bogart,
Catherine Hepburn and a Photoshopped in Albert the Monkey.
Pulling in. This is like Space Jam.
Have you heard of Space Jam? Yes.
Has Casablanca and Casablanca franchise? Yeah.
Yeah. I should have said Casablanca.
That's a better way to say it. Casablanca is in it.
What are what other properties are it?
Space Jam is now part of a greater Time Warnerverse HBO.
What's the company even called?
Eight to eight. It's a part of a greater AT&T Time Warnerverse.
Mad Max, Fury Road, I believe
is mentioned, and this is all and this and none of this included.
It's all separate from Ready Player One,
which also like throws everything into a blender.
Like it's how do you talk about charts and spreadsheets?
How do you figure out what pop culture item is in which
I've said this corporate umbrella and universe?
I've said this before, and I know I didn't actually cause this,
but it is like when I was 10, I wished on a monkey's paw
that all entertainment would turn into Marvel Comics.
And it's coming true.
It's like that is happening.
Now, here's I'll use that to segue into a feeling.
I am a little I like see a lot.
I'm I'm invested in it. I like it.
I do worry it's swallowing up the park whole.
And we'll maybe continue to swallow the whole park
if there's a show that starts linking it to every like, oh, did you know that
the man who owns the confectionary on Main Street is a member?
The candy striper.
Mr. You think there's too many things being pulled in?
I think so.
That might be controversial, but I feel like maybe there's too many things
now being pulled into it.
I like I there's it's obviously a personal taste thing,
but I like it when it's a little bit less.
I don't know. It feels like it's taking over versus a little bit more obscure.
Do you know what I'm saying?
Well, yeah, I think it is on the rise and we're only going to see more and more of it.
But I think the thing that's going to stop it at the end of the day
is our dads not giving a shit about any of this.
That is where point me to the rides, please.
Well, OK, listen, Pop,
Madam Zarkov is what is an adjacent.
I'd say an advisor to see because Jason Chandler
consults with her in a letter in the letter in the big thunder line.
And she was in the Adventurers Club.
She was a character there.
Jason Chandler mentioned she's at the Museum of the Weird.
So that connects three things.
Jason, does your dad know about C?
Because I think your dad of the thing.
I think, yeah, I think my dad might know a little because I've explained
or I've pointed stuff out.
My dad listens to the podcast.
I think I probably listen to almost all of them.
He's probably listened a lot.
He was not very into this, I don't think.
He listened to one last week where he complained about her parents.
He's a little behind.
He's been working from home, so I think he's a little behind.
He you know what? He would have mentioned that I spoke with him earlier.
So I bet I don't think he would have.
He does not. He's not like a guy who would have probably known C
before listening to this podcast.
Yeah, yeah. So my mom would think it was neat.
I think if I started explaining all this to her and it ties all these things
together, I think she would as a teacher, as an educator,
I think she would she would find it all clever.
It is all clever.
And we agree, I think that it's all clever and fun.
But yes, I am a little concerned with the seification
of the Disney. I like I would like the idea that
there's different little groups unrelated to each other.
I mean, we've talked about there's like the Tomorrowland in Tokyo
sort of mini universe kind of that links stuff together.
It ties into Star Tours a little bit, which I think I might have been.
I forget if I was saying that episode, I would like to tie that into like
Red Rocket, the owner of presumably the owner of Red Rocket's Pizza
Port, and I like that there's ogas and Rex there and Rex ties a lot together.
So like the space restaurant universe, I'm really I'm into.
Right. Yeah. But like you would I would think you would want to keep
you would want to keep like something like Everest.
I know Expedition Everest has a lot of backstory in the queue and stuff,
but you would want to keep that a little more pure.
You want to keep some of those rides.
You don't need to tie in, Jason. Yes.
I think it's already in canon a little in.
But it's a little bit.
It's just little hints like so Skipper Canteen.
There's a lot of details in Skipper Canteen in Orlando.
And the three books written by Harrison Hightower are references to Joe Brody.
They they they're called Treasurer of the Animal Kingdom.
Expedition Everest, Colin in Search of the Yeti.
And the last one, I think, is a pretty solid joke.
It's just called mine.
Am I an E exclamation point?
And that is kind of playing up on him being a pillager character.
So there's a little Everest.
I just don't think we don't need E.L.
Everest, the owner of the mountain character.
I don't think we need that is what I'm saying.
You know, not E.L. Fudge, E.L. Everest.
There's kind of blank slates for the TV writing staff.
Other there's characters like in Tropical Hideaway and Skipper
Canteen mentions characters S.
She Ho and Chef 10 10 dodgy.
And then in Skipper Canteen, there's Luana Texera.
You are going to keep trying to say names throughout the rest of this episode.
I don't know how these names are said.
They're just written down.
Anytime there's a lull, you just start saying a photographer.
Now, going back to Hong Kong, Disneyland, the Halloween overlays.
Professor Garrett Reed was the disgrace star,
disgraced excommunicated member, excommunicated by Dr.
Henry Mystic. He is the star of Jungle Cruise, curse of the Emerald Trinity.
Emerald Trinity, excuse me.
And then there was a show called Horrors of the Amazon,
which featured a character named Jonas Brisbane.
Talking about how he was an aspiring member of C.
He's a one. Jonas Brisbane is a wannabe.
He's a hanger on. He's never getting in the groove.
He's a leader. Holiday overlay shows.
You don't care. You think you can hold water next to Barnabas Bullion?
Yeah, F off Brisbane.
Let's real real quick.
And we've alluded to this.
C is and I don't think they're seen like this,
but C is a bad organization, right? They're bad.
Like they're bad.
Well, secret clubs are bad organizations or yeah.
Isn't something in Scientology called C? C-org?
Oh, yeah. C-org, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Well, that's weird.
It is. I'll tell you that. It is weird.
That exists and it is all Elrond is kind of this sort of guy.
He's not like a pillager, but he's like he liked his boats and his
weaving his tails is the master in.
See, I like that.
Well, I would love if the yeah, if the Phillips,
you know, happens character, the name's not coming to me, but if he's in it
and that fake Elrond Hubbard in that movie we talked about,
but that universal guy made like there was like
it was called like the Church of Scientific Skepticism or something.
Yeah. Like like M.
M. Ron Blowhard or whatever parody name they used. Yeah.
Well, I mean, if you if you start to make a Paul Thomas Anderson
universe with the master, then you start that gets so complicated
because like, well, if you include inherent vice, that includes the Thomas
Pynchon universe, right?
And the crying of lot 49 is all just different warring secret societies
that it's not clear what most of them do.
How do the Heim videos factor in?
Well, and then, yeah, where do the Heim sisters start to play?
They are. They show up at the end of one with drumsticks.
And then they just say like, we're starting a band, I guess.
Yeah.
Yeah. So so back to my back to my thought, though, about see, it's like.
If the group, I think, is not portrayed as bad guys,
but if you have Harrison Hightower in the group, you're a bad group.
He's he's like pure evil.
And even if Mystic is taking things from around the world,
he's still taking the things.
He's still a rich guy.
Like, I I guess where I'm going with this is like
what Disney won't do is make a series about like ten different Mr.
Burns type characters.
Yeah. Who are comically evil.
And then eventually, we hopefully would get their comeuppance.
I don't think that's going to happen.
I think Disney doesn't see the characters like this.
But let's be honest, see is not a good group.
They can't be all bad.
They all deserve ironic punishments.
The most of them, I think some are fine.
I think the Soren lady, she just likes she's a falconer.
And here seems nice.
Hey, this this bothers me, too.
There should be a lady tyrant in this group.
You know, yeah, I think it is.
Yeah, they've they've made it so that the female characters are kind of like,
you know, like kind and right redeemable.
But yeah, maybe you do want like we got Cruella coming out.
You know, you want your you want your villain.
I'm worried Cruella is going to like save the day at the end of that movie.
Like, you know, well, it is a weird.
Yeah, does Cruella end up bad with all things about that?
She was good. Yeah.
At some point, I'm just saying for true, you know, true equality.
You want ladies tyrants as well as male.
Yeah. You know, you're really fiction.
Not in real life.
You don't want that Cinderella's mom.
Can we know like, can we find out that Cinderella's mom was like a pillager?
She like stole that house that they live in.
Yeah, like kick somebody pulled some deed shit, some legalities and stole that house.
If you there's a BBC documentary series called Can't Get You Out of My Head.
It's from this guy, Adam Curtis, this documentary filmmaker
made this big movie hyper normalization.
One of the characters he follows in this documentary series was Mao Zedong's wife.
And she might be one of the most evil people.
She's like out of her mind.
And the whole the origin story is she is a failed actress
with a lot of grudges to settle.
And this is what happened.
Like she rewrote epic Chinese stories and operas to serve the revolution.
And then when people started to turn on her,
she turned like the young people against them.
Like it's so crazy.
Like she's the perfect kind of she's.
Yeah, she should be one of the evil people in sea.
Mr. Bird. Honestly, Mr.
Burns could be in sea now.
I'm thinking about it because Disney owns Disney.
Yeah. And Mr.
Burns was alive for some of Mr.
Burns was on the earth at the same time as some of the members of sea.
Yeah. So I just I think
as fun as it is to see little plaques and to see the characters,
I think that Disney should think of sea as villains.
I think that's a more fun way to go.
Like narratively, but I think sea is going to be all they're all going to be good.
I have a feeling.
I think it's going to be like Kingsman, where it's like the good guy secret spy agency.
But then there'll be one or two traders.
There'll be one or two, you know, heels kind of like when like
like Sabretooth joins the X-Men for a few issues.
And then he starts killing people again.
You know, they're all and look, we own.
I think I said it earlier. They're all going to be hot.
Every now and then.
That's where there's no way this is a bunch of old men.
Right. Not happening.
Right. I guess I maybe I'll speak for myself.
My dream show, the bunch of old people who are really bad,
like being bad and you enjoy it for a while and then they just get their comeuppance.
I don't think that's the show.
The show is going to be like sexy, spicy,
and they're doing cool stuff.
And they can't like kiss or anything because it's Disney and they stay away
from sexuality completely can't be Riverdale, but it'll just be other like here.
They're doing good things around the world.
The hottest guy named Barnabas you've ever seen.
They call him like Barn, Barney, Barney, Barney, Barney, still like barn, maybe.
Come on, Barney.
Oh, I'll be I'm very excited for the episode where Jason Chandler
discovers human growth hormone.
So everyone see can get like exactly jacked, like exactly the same way.
Jack. It's like, yeah, River River Pills or something.
Magic River Juice, the Enchanted Spring.
Yes, that's OK. That's much better.
Yes. Come and drink from the Enchanted Spring.
It will make you more vascular.
Well, that's what all those old pulp care, all those like doc, doc Samson and stuff
like they all figured and even like I think the early Batman comics were like
he became a peak physical specimen or like found some sort of serum
that gave him super strength and endurance.
There's always a lot about endurance.
Super soldier serum. Super soldier. America took it.
Yeah. Yeah.
Always a serum.
But really, all they mean is just HGH, human growth hormone.
That's right. The same thing that many of your favorite stars are on right now.
As we speak, they're doing a cycle of HGH to get prepared for a new movie role.
The real superhero origin story out it.
Yeah, it's HGH and it's lean meats, very little carbs, some greens.
How do you think they go from giant to like much less giant in a different movie?
Come on, wake up, folks.
I don't know why I'm arguing with somebody who's objecting to this.
Who's denying the use of.
I can just hear thousands of people saying, no, I don't believe it.
They just put another five pound weight on each weight and they did it.
They got big.
Well, what then?
Maybe do we need to like flesh out what is an example of something we want?
Like, what is it? What does one of these characters do?
It is bad.
And it wouldn't be that bad because we don't want to see like inflicting
pain on native populations and that kind of thing,
unless the punishment is just an immediate.
But like, you know, it is it does have to be in that Mr.
Mr. Burns blocking the sun vein. Right.
Well, it's yeah, it's like stealing.
He's stealing like hairs and eye towers, stealing stone head and sure something.
Or something else. Right.
Yeah, he's making who's the assistant?
Who's his smelly smelding smelding?
He makes smelding carry each stone.
He gets smelding too much of the magic serum.
It makes him very strong forces smelding to take Stonehenge out block by block.
So he can put it in his front yard and nobody else can have access.
Or he just it's maybe he has his tower. Right.
So he goes up on the seventh floor of the tower or the 13th floor,
the unlucky floor, and he puts Stonehenge inside.
This is in my building now, but it's too heavy.
And all the stone and blocks crash through all of the subsequent
floors and destroy the building. Yeah, that's good.
Yeah, that's good.
And then I bet the Lord Henry Mystic, probably the Professor X kind of character,
Nick Fury kind of sending probably sends Jason Chandler
and either Barry O'Shea or Camelia Falco is like you two are going in this office.
Albert, keep an eye on them.
OK, so they have to like look out for each other or try to land
maybe to keep the organization under wraps.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, I think if you want to make your Lord Henry Mystic or other characters
like not evil, you probably cut down on them taking stuff from different cultures.
That would be my that would be my punch up.
Henry Mystic is going to learn about people and maybe he gets gifted things at the end
for, you know, sharing his wisdom and their exchange of ideas.
And then he brings that back to his house.
As a poor how about this?
What if it's people who did who like went?
All right. They know people who went and bought things fair and square
at marketplaces.
They put money into the local economies and then the sea people like Hightower.
They all like wait for things to be brought back to like a block away
from where they live and then they go like sneak into people's houses and steal them
for them and act like they got it.
And like I'm trying to pull Falco in this Falco woman.
And if we want unredeemable FEMA, she could send that bird to go steal.
You mean salty?
No, no, no. Oh, the other the Falcon.
Well, sorry, no, any anybody can send any of their animals to go steal gems
and rubies from place, bring them back for their own.
I want all the animals to be evil. Everybody's evil.
OK, everyone's evil. Salty is the evilest of all.
I realize. Did you guys come across Barnabas T. Bullion's assistant?
Nope. Oh, no. Oh, baby.
Here we go. Barnabas T. Bullion's assistant has a name and the name is Willikers.
Well, now, come on.
Now, Jason Sheridan could easily play Willikers, please.
Oh, I would love to play both.
And then there's a little jokes of like, I feel like I've met you before.
Couldn't be me, sir.
Listen to that voice. He just did. Couldn't be me.
So it is very time accurate.
Yeah, I've already spent much of quarantine
growing a mustache, you know, halfway there.
George getting getting curlier.
Once you can get that thing to flip up, you can get any of these parts.
And certainly Willikers. Willikers had a mustache.
It was more of like a wild west.
I can share a screen and show you what Willikers look like.
He's, of course, one of my favorite characters in fiction immediately.
Here he is. George.
So his name is G Willikers. That is correct.
That's pretty cute.
Scott, is that too cute for you?
I guess I can give it up for G Willikers.
All right, Scott, that's official.
Scott gives it up for G Willikers. That's fine. I give it up.
We have talked a lot on this podcast about our characters cute,
but we have not dissected a lot of is this phrase cute?
And I think we all agree that that's a cute phrase.
Sure. Yeah.
And something we should say instead of profanities.
G Willikers that tease me off.
Yes, because we're members of Sun
who are very nice and obedient and follow the rules against cursing.
Sometimes there's the discussion.
What episode of Pakistan do you start with?
This one I can definitively say no, not this one.
Do you start with the one with a bunch of lists of name?
Even they themselves are in a group and then they make up a bunch of groups
that they'd like to see.
This is the episode of the most capital letters.
This is three of the show is going to have.
I think they count podcast listens by if you completed it.
And this is going to have a maybe like a couple, ten,
maybe ten at most who actually finished it.
I think a normal people will start it in earnest and go, oh, I see.
I'd love to learn more about it.
They may be by the end of throwing their phone out the window.
You two are fun. And this was demanded.
We were demanded. We're few weeks.
People thought we were going to drop what we're doing every week.
Some news happens. Do you see?
And we're sons of bitches.
We will. Yeah.
I mean, they wanted to hear us discuss the fact that Auntie's Beach House Kids
Club in Alani has a reference to see because it has a letter from
the letter Perkins that references sea member Harrison Hightower.
So it's on Adventurers Club Stationary and it's on Adventurers Club Stationary.
And that they had to hear that Professor Garrett Reed was seeking out
a legendary set of jewels known as the Emerald Trinity,
a set of jewels that was hidden at the altar of souls at the Temple of Immortality.
I don't know what is any of that.
And also, they would.
The one thing to pull from all that, though, is this guy, Garrett Reed,
this disgraced guy, he was he was looking for jewels.
Right. Wonder what do you think you wanted to do with them jewels?
Maybe you wanted to suck them jewels.
Maybe maybe Garrett Reed wanted to be sucking those jewels.
Now, hold on a minute.
You have a problem with the sea continuity, but you're going back in podcast
content. You don't think that's so fun?
All kinds of people who like to suck them jewels.
Bugsy is not a member of Sun.
I can definitively say that.
That's why we spar with him so much.
He is a different. Yeah, he is in whatever our podcast
canon evil group is bad.
It's it's Nick Mundy and Bugsy in a different group.
And according to listener feedback, Jesse
Jesse Farrar.
Because he said once he doesn't like theme parks,
he's now the biggest villain in the history of the show.
It is a fearsome group, the injustice.
I like for now. Right now, I'm calling them the injustice gang,
which is the name of the DC villains.
But we'll punch that up at a certain point.
Wait, if it's big, Jason, it was bad, right?
So is that how do we let's figure that out?
Boys against decency.
Oh, yes. Very good. Wow. Fantastic.
We can say Disney, but that limits it too much.
Yeah, boys against decency. Yeah, yeah.
OK, great. So we have Sun and bad.
Sun wars with bad bumper car boys are definitely
part of Adams. I'm still scared we're going to meet them one day.
Yes, we really know this episode should just be us
unleashing every dumb piece of canon we have on the audience
to really see.
Let's see if we can get them to turn it off.
Let's see.
Let's see if we can.
Let's see. OK, what else?
What other facts for first of all, do I have here?
Oh, the United Kingdom Pavilion has a reference to see.
It's got the hand of the fake handbook. Yes.
Has the fake handbook. Yes, of course.
We mean fake. What does that mean?
What it's a bookshelf.
It's like a peanut ceramic bookshelf and they paint.
There's a lot of fake books in Skipper canteen written by
C members or their fezzes, their ceremony.
And the book is fake in that like everything's fake in a theme park
or that are people writing fake books in canon?
No, it's that. Well, it's it's books within the universe,
but we perceive them just as like ceramic or plaster.
OK, we perceive them.
This is like that. What are what is tune stuff made of again?
Yeah, our tune is our tune items and chairs soft or not?
Well, or or their actual books like I can't picture it.
It's actual books they bought at like an estate sale and then painted over
for it to be like more of a prop. Right.
An actual book.
I think everyone should say the last things
that are fun to them on their list of things.
And then we should.
Then we should.
Mike has a wrestling.
Yeah, Scott, blame it on my wrestling for the reason you want to get out of here.
We do have a time cap.
I will say, you know, this is such a condensed.
This is such a condensed amount of information.
The listener really should not have to listen to it for two hours.
So I'm going through and seeing.
We really didn't talk about Magellan's,
which is the restaurant in Disney Sea, which I did.
OK, here's how stupid I am.
I did not eat at Magellan's.
I did not really explore it.
I didn't even realize there was a whole crazy underground thing by Mount Prometheus,
which is like another thing that's kind of like,
what would you call it, an explorer, an area to explore.
There's a thing called the Chamber of Planets, which just watching the video
is this cool, like observatory type thing that looks very expansive.
And I go, what the fuck was it? Where did I miss this?
I was there when in this.
There's like a thing that there's a place with a lot of optical illusions
and little like models and boats to play with.
I think I did this.
I miss this and I'm looking through it and it's like, this is so cool,
whether it's even tied to sea or not.
So, yeah, so looking on the other's various YouTube videos to see just sort of how much
cool stuff, again, without the actual sea back story is associated
is impressive, and it's not all fake books is my point.
This is all Tokyo Disney is the is responsible.
We maybe haven't said that the Tokyo the when Tokyo Disney Sea came into being,
that's where they they planted the seeds of this, maybe when that without a plan
to tie it all together.
But this and this notion of this organization started there
and it's only grown and grown. Yeah.
Yeah. And those those imagineers that are drawn in some of the Mystic
Banner portraits, Rob Coltrane and Joe Lance Acero,
I think were some of the big like drivers of like, you know, they were
they were working on this stuff and they're like, oh, let's connect it to this stuff.
And so some of the early proponents.
There is an immense amount of cool stuff that's been done in the parks
in this genre, sort of like it did adventure explorative.
I think some of the best stuff Disney's done recently is in this war.
So it is a nice tribute to, you know, to all these great attractions
that have come into being since 2001.
And I did find it cool when when, yeah, when you're in that area
that the in Tokyo, Disney Sea or in the birthplace of sea,
that's where this whole weird mythology started.
And I did think, oh, that's cool.
I came all the way to Tokyo and there's a little outpost of this thing.
And then there's you could go to Florida and see some of it.
It is like a weird little like collect them all.
You know, I have to experience every facet.
It rewards your world traveling.
If you go to all these parks across the globe.
And it is it is nice.
And as much as I said, like, I don't want it to like swallow up everything.
It is nice because it's not in your face.
It's not like you have to take a little quiz on what Barnabas
T. Bullion's intentions were before you get on Big Thunder Mountain.
So it is choose your own level of getting involved with it.
It's like, you notice it, you want to read all the plaques
and you enjoy that you can.
But it's not it's not a necessity as far as getting on these rides
or or eating a quick service meal.
Yeah. And there's like there's an interview with Lance
Ossera where he talks about like creating this universe,
creating this believable backstory and a world history.
And it's fun, but it's got a purpose.
And it's just kind of like to help them while they're making the attraction,
like flesh out the world a little and like inspire other ideas to like,
you know, make the attraction feel more fleshed out and lived in.
Yeah. So we like see, I think we do like.
Don't get us wrong.
Yes, it will be very interesting to see it adapted for.
Yeah. Streaming TV because theme park adaptations are like
so hit and miss for the most part, you know.
And yeah, and like I just all really the only question is,
how hot will the members of CB?
That's the only question I have.
And I'd like them to turn the dial up on it.
It can't be Riverdale level I get, but but I want.
Yes, as hot as possible, please.
Get casting.
Let's keep like maximum age on any of these people.
Twenty four. Right.
Yes. Before you have before skin starts to degrade like it does on my face.
Well, it depends on who's consulting.
Is it the Lucas film doctors or is it the Marvel doctors?
Because Star Wars universe, a little grittier, a little dirtier.
And that feels more appropriate for like a world adventuring,
like dusty kind of world.
But the Marvel is very glossy.
Yeah. Well, let's see.
Feige is Kevin Feige is only making 12 shows and five movies a year.
I think he can oversee it yet.
It's another cinematic universe here.
So maybe and he's a big look.
Ken Feige is a big parks fan.
I know this is a fact.
So I think he probably would be interested in getting in here
and having to produce another 10 series a year and five films.
So, yeah, why not?
Why not put more on the man's plate?
Let's do it. And Kevin, come on the show as well.
Come on the show.
And if you do, you will meet the obvious choice to play.
G will occurs and what smell smell this smelding.
All right. He's going to be both and new character created by Scott
earlier in the episode I.P.
Freely, the toilet magnet.
Jason Sheridan is I.P.
Freely. Sure.
I dream of a place where there are no limits placed on where I urinate.
And if if you want to know, is I.P.
Freely on a cycle of HGH and a cycle of steroids, the answer is fuck. Yeah.
He is huge. Jason Sheridan is huge.
Oh, yeah, sure.
Well, not again, just as long as the doctor is overseeing everything.
You know, it is OK.
Yeah. Yeah. Doctor feel good.
Is it? Yeah.
All right. You survived podcast, the ride, dense mythology edition.
I have a headache. I have a headache.
We'll try to present supplementary materials and visuals.
You can understand everything that was just said somewhere
on our social media between Twitter, Instagram and Facebook.
And for three, if you're adventurous enough for three bonus episodes a month,
go to let set your compass to the second gate at podcast at patreon dot com
slash podcast, the ride.
Well, gentlemen, another successful meeting of sun has commenced.
Let's do the sun official goodbye phrase.
Is it just congolous?
It is. It is congolous, please.
Or like what's more polite?
Congolous, if that's OK with you.
I'm sorry. I have to.
I'm sorry.
I have to check with my mom.
I need to get permission first.
We have permissions.
We have to get permission slips to do each podcast.
Did you guys know that?
Oh, shoot.
We're doing. It would be best to keep everything orderly.
Yeah. All right.
And everyone, I want you all out there to turn your permission slips into us
before you listen to any of these episodes to make sure you have your parents' permission.
All right. Thanks for listening.
Sorry. Sorry. Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Forever.
This has been a forever dog production executive
produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner,
Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.