Five, four, three, two, one.
I'm rapping Jason and I'm here to say,
I love to rap in a second gateway.
You think this is cringe?
Wait and see.
We're talking Mickey on rap to thee.
Hi, I'm Jason Chardon.
This is the Mickey on rap episode of Fuck SRI, the second gate.
And that's what it is.
That's what this is today.
Mike Carlson, Scott Garand, both also here.
Yeah, we are here too also.
No, nevermind.
Here we go.
I'm feeling the flow.
Those are low impact rhymes I know.
That's good.
That is good.
Glad you liked it because that's the end.
That was kind of where I was too.
I was so excited earlier when I came up with a second line
and I was like, I feel like one of us is going to probably do,
this will inevitably get said, this kind of like,
I'm here to say.
I'm here to say rap, which is where our parents,
at least my parents got stuck.
Rap is just this.
So and so my name is, I feel like I remember my dad going,
my name is Joe and don't you know?
What did you hear that makes you think rap is this?
The best, my friend's dad, my friend's dad once,
I think he was having a huge argument about Jay-Z with him.
Like I could do this.
And like we were hoping, because we left to go like lunch
and we were hoping this didn't happen,
but we were hoping we would come back and there would be like a notebook
on the table that his dad, and we were like,
so like, please let your dad try to write a rap song.
Please make good on this promise.
It's been very fun for me.
Like everybody who I liked, like Jay-Z or people I argued with my dad
about in high school or middle school, like watching them all become like
humanitarians, like people who do like a bunch of good.
And like there's really, you just like have no leg to stand on.
I feel like it's also, yeah.
Yeah.
It's also like, at this point, hip hop has been around for a long time.
And it's like, you know, you, you remember when you were young
and people were like, this isn't music.
Do you remember like there, there's parodies of it back then.
There's people like parodying the, I think like Alan Sherman has like Beach Boy
parody songs, which are valid and it's fine to parody things.
Oh, it's the, well, yeah.
I mean, Eva's big on all this is the, the like,
what's the, it's pop goes the weasel with I hate the Beatles.
Or pop hates the Beatles, something in there.
Maybe it's a bad thing when you're my parents, because they love Alan Sherman.
Sure.
They're fine with being Alan Sherman.
He's got some fun stuff.
I'm just saying if you look at the cyclical nature of, of entertainment
and pop culture, I mean, come on, look what's happening now.
Yeah, I love, there is a recording from like a TV variety show of Tennessee
Ernie Ford, famous for singing the song 16 tons.
And he's like, well, music's a little different recently.
And I thought we'd get a little bit of swing on one of my hits.
And it's like a swinging like go-go cover of six.
He sings 16 tons while go-go dancers dance around him.
Wow.
Tennessee Ernie Ford, of course, also on a very famous episode of I Love Lucy
that I love.
Well, tread lightly.
Don't start saying stuff you need to take back.
I'm going to have to take this back.
There's going to be a gripe.
I believe he's on one episode.
Maybe he's on more than one.
I apologize.
I say I didn't know, so I'm not saying definitively, but Ricky's, Ricky's got to
get his band out of some trouble.
And they put, Lucy, I believe puts cheese in the instruments and clogs them up.
And that's the end of the episode.
It's a big reveal at the end of the episode.
I'm sure I butchered that.
I apologize.
I will say this type of cheese.
I don't remember.
It's important to know that it's monster.
I'm so sorry.
Don't don't yell at me.
I will say my mom, all of a sudden, and I, whatever that came out in 1999, I think
is when the song came out.
Also, my mom was like, you know, this Nelly song hot in here.
Whoa.
This is a good song.
Wow.
That's a funny one for you.
Like mom.
She's like, but I guess she was like singing it.
They sort of self sensor in a way, a little bit of and a little bit of like, so maybe
that helps it along that it's not those aren't suggestive words.
Yeah, it wasn't tip drill.
It was not.
I don't even want to get into that.
It's tip drill.
I don't think I know.
Oh, I don't want to.
We don't need to.
I think we could draw conclusions from those two words put together to a little Google
search.
The second gate.
But still, I don't know.
Well, there's going to be nothing.
There's going to be nothing too filthy today because we're talking about Mickey Mouse's
rap career in the mid nineties.
Disney put out an album called Mickey Unwrapped.
And this was a listener suggestion.
I feel like this came up on Twitter.
So, so thank you for it.
Maybe we'll see how we feel at the end.
But definitely worth talking about.
I was a little bit aware of it.
Aware of the cover, certainly.
That's what jumps out at me.
Which is maybe the most regrettable thing about it, I would say.
Maybe we should describe that or hopefully you're looking at it in the in our episode
art.
But Mickey in a backwards red cap, some jeans slung down.
The curse of the nineties.
Before America's greatest enemy was international terrorism, we were plagued by the scourge
of saggy jeans.
He's in sunglasses.
The cover is kind of in front of a sort of brick-esque pattern.
The shoes, it's like a bit like a boots or something.
The cover is just one of the most regrettable things I think they've ever had to do.
This is shameful.
Yeah, well, because he's wearing the saggy jeans with his little red shorts.
And I know that was a look where people would wear it like, you know, basketball shorts
or jeans would just sag down if they were wearing boxers.
But it's confusing.
Here's a plus up real quick for this image.
I don't think he should be wearing big pants.
I think he should be sagging his little Mickey shorts.
And he should have some sort of undergarment under it that he's showing off in that manner.
Because this makes it look like Mickey's wearing underwear always.
That's what the shorts are, is underwear and always has been.
Exactly.
So I think, and maybe there was a discussion with the graphic artist who did this,
that Mickey should be sagging his red shorts, his little red shorts.
That's a plus up.
If we were doing this again tomorrow, that's what I would say.
But would it not just seem like he's taking them off?
You know, because he's wearing jeans with a belt,
and the belt kind of cinches it so that it doesn't fall all the way down to the knees or below.
But you know, it would be weird if there was a belt on the red shorts.
We know there's no loops on his shorts.
So if it was just his famous little red shorts falling down,
wouldn't it seem like he was removing his pants?
Okay, I have another plus up to that.
Make his little red shorts a little bit more loose.
Make it the same design.
Make them a little bit bigger and have them sagging, as opposed to this,
which makes it look like he's just wearing two complete pairs of pants.
That's what's happening, which is maybe what they thought.
You know, you've got things like crisscross wearing backwards pants.
That's the kind of thing rappers do, right?
Wear two pants?
Sounds good to me.
Yeah, two pants.
Two pants.
Put Mickey in Tim's.
Done and done.
Michael, I mean, did this go across Michael Eisner's desk?
Did he have to approve all this art?
Did he have to approve the project?
I'd like to think he did.
And he's like, yeah, put him in two pants.
Two pants.
He has to be wearing two pants.
That's all I know about hip-hop and rap.
Maybe he must have been on his radar to some extent.
Take his shirt off.
Mickey's got to have no shirt.
I'm sick of those overalls.
Yeah, I mean, I think, yeah, he had to approve the outfit.
I'd like to think every dumb thing Disney did while he was a CEO
was something he had to actually read and approve, which I think is possible.
Maybe.
It seems kind of likely.
We'll ask him when we have him on.
We can't end the podcast until we have him.
So if it takes us 34 years.
He's born on my birthday, too.
That should be enough.
We just learned this the other day.
Just figured that out.
I know.
Thank you to the listener who pointed out.
Boy, Michael's, Carlson and Eisner share a birthday.
Crazy.
Man.
And I also presented it the way that he was born on my birthday.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's yours now.
You're the new kid on the scene.
Do you feel more cosmically connected to him or do you feel like there is any sort of like astrological?
Oh, I've always now I know what I connect to about Michael Eisner.
Yeah, well, now that we share a sign, I feel like I know him better.
I feel like I know I know where he's maybe coming from, you know, because as Jane pointed out,
there's spicy.
Pisces are very sensitive.
Yes.
OK, so I kind of understand.
And I can imagine now, you know, sort of when he was getting a backlash at the later part of the 90s and he was in his mind,
he was trying to keep Disney afloat by cutting budgets on things.
He wasn't trying to deliver a bad California adventure to us.
But I feel bad now.
I feel like he was getting heat and he was like, I'm trying.
I'm just trying to help.
I'm just doing my best.
And, you know, I have sympathy for him now.
Trying his best, like so many of the characters that thrived under his watch.
Exactly.
And he had a watch that looked like him or Mickey.
Now, that's Mickey fashion that I can get behind.
Is Michael Eisner watch in that one thing?
I thought I was going to talk about, but I feel like we could just dive in.
I mean, we're so we're deep into the into Mickey's rap game now.
Do we do we establish this?
Ninety three.
Ninety three is the year on this.
So you're in a very particular strain of rap, obviously, you know, sort of West Coast G funk is happening, but we're not really going there.
It's kind of more in the zone of the pop rap of the time.
These I just started to correct you.
I'm seeing 94.
September 94 is when this came out.
Who knows?
But it seems like any time a corporation does something that's trying to capitalize on something that's cool or popular, they're, you know, five to ten years behind.
That's just about often.
I mean, I guess they're actually a little bit.
It's not even five years maybe here, but they're a little behind on the actual trends.
You know, what's you know, to that end, I think that the out of date nature is maybe not what's annoying about this.
It almost isn't in that they are parodying or tributing songs that are like from the last two years.
I guess I will give that to Mickey unwrapped.
I feel like what is bad about it is how do I finish the sentence that it is bad?
It's bad because it's bad.
It's the the.
Or is it maybe it's not bad.
I don't know.
Do you guys have an overall from what you listen to?
Because we kind of divided and conquered here.
We each took four songs and then we're going to put all our thoughts together.
If it's if I'm putting on my irony, fun, find hat, it's not great.
Yeah, there's some corny bullshit in here for sure.
Yeah, there's fun stuff.
There's.
But it's it's not like is anything better than another Chuckie Day?
The Chuck E.
Cheese parody.
I don't think so.
Not from what I know.
No, that's what's a legitimate song.
And they went in the direction, which maybe is key.
They were maybe afraid of doing that.
That was a dicier area at the time.
But yeah, now Mickey could do some G funk.
No problem.
Right.
So I one of my songs is just like a straight kind of like nice sounding
gospel song with no Disney characters.
And I'm like, what?
OK.
And then that if I'm just listening to it as a as a music fan, I go,
this sounds nice.
I like this.
There's a little bit of that.
So I don't know.
I think this maybe doesn't succeed in most directions.
If it's like, is it a hilarious thing to make fun of?
It is.
It is fun to make fun of it, but it is not.
It is not near like a McGruff level of, oh, my God, this was this was
obviously supposed to be like a weird type of tool to keep kids away from
drugs, but ended up being this like little masterpiece accidentally or on purpose.
This is like intended to be novelty.
You've got to view it as either a kid's album or a or a comedy album.
I'm not sure quite works as that.
Yeah, it's not.
It's not so funny.
I wasn't doubling over laughing while I was listening to it either.
So, yeah, I feel like what's notable about it almost is just hearing these
these voice actors because it is definitely, you know, there's no off brand in here.
It's definitely Wayne Allwine and Russie, Russie Taylor.
It is like Bill Farmer.
It's the guys, right?
Yeah, it sounds like it.
But wait, wait, Jason, what are you?
Did you have something that contradicts this?
I got a track that sounds a little off.
Well, it's later in the album.
So are you saying Bill Farmer doesn't know how to drop bars, Jason?
No, no, I'm not talking quality.
I'm talking like that hits my ear weird scenes or it's just the performance.
That's just rubbing me the wrong way.
Could it be the Mickey from that one?
The den use the den Mickey.
It's not Mickey.
It's not a Mickey.
We'll see.
We'll get there.
We'll get it out when we get there.
Sure.
Yeah, I think for at least my my tracks, my hot tracks are seemingly the real people.
And I'm mainly just like amused by that they they had to do this and gave it their all.
But to with results, sometimes they're like, what?
Oh, these poor, these poor people,
these people like in their 50s and above, in most cases, probably already.
And now having to get funky.
Yes, it's I would love to see.
Yeah, I don't think this was a big hit also.
So I don't think there was like making of specials or anything or documentation of this.
This felt like I mean, I guess one of my point is I'd love to see this happening.
I'd love to see Bill Farmer in the boot.
Yeah, yeah.
Being taught how to rap because they do they don't get it wrong.
It's not as if I feel like they capably figured out the tempo of current rap.
And it is not yo, yo, I got the flow.
Right.
Sometimes.
Yeah.
So we'll see.
I don't know.
Do these people still have the skill like this?
So could Bill Farmer do an episode of off book and with a sort of rap song?
I don't know, but I'd like to see it.
I want to see if he still has it in him.
He might get a practice.
Keep the tools sharp.
Yeah.
Telling if he did or not.
Should I dive in to my first four?
We all kind of we split up the assignment so that nobody was too burdened with the entire runtime of Mickey unwrapped.
But I'm excited about my four.
I think some of the I think some of the singles literally the single is in the first four.
But where do we start?
Well, you kick it off with one that sounds familiar from title, but it doesn't really go where you think it might go.
And maybe I'll just have you play as much of it until we feel like talking.
And that is a song called Ice Ice Mickey.
Now sing it.
Ooh baby.
Ice Ice Mickey.
Get down.
Everybody.
Ice Ice Mickey.
Now get back up.
Sing it with us.
Ice Ice Mickey.
Oh oh oh.
With a mission, a fine musician, fun and dancing are the first requisition music in the key of peace and harmony.
The world altogether.
That's the way it has to be.
Yellow shoes on his.
There we go.
Get you off your seat.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Seat.
Whoa.
Minnie just said, get you off your seat.
That was the context that we use seed in.
Yes.
Yeah.
Kind of pioneered here.
Wow.
Did you notice that the first time or did you just catch it here?
I maybe wasn't paying attention that hard.
How could that be possible?
To think about it.
I.
Go ahead.
I was just gonna keep playing it if there's more.
I'll tell you a point to jump ahead to, but yeah, that's some of the hijinks that go on.
Like they do seed some of the rapping to anonymous rappers.
They have some some ringers, I suppose.
But where the money really is is hearing the characters.
I was almost going to tell you to shut it off until many came in.
That's what you want.
You really want a full.
I would almost take just many rap.
I think that's always pretty good.
That's you want more of that.
Yeah.
The word there is.
There's a lot.
There's maybe there's a ton of many.
They really gave her the ball here.
Mickey in this song kind of factors in with these little sides that sort of deconstruct the kinds of things you would say in a rap song, especially in a hype manner.
And maybe could you take it to around one twenty three?
And there's some good examples of that.
Mickey.
Now I'm looking to do the left thing.
Everybody ice ice.
I'm so cool.
I make polar bear shit.
What?
Disney is coming at you.
That voice getting a little weird there.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I don't think he knows how to say.
Like, that's a tough ask of Mickey to like sell, hit him off at the past.
Homies and the purposefully mispronounced homies.
Yeah, it's it's yeah, maybe it's just yeah, there's only so many things you usually say is Mickey the voice of Mickey.
And now here he goes.
Obviously, ice ice Mickey is a parody of ice ice baby in name only.
It is not ice ice baby.
Which it would be a better beat to go with the ripped off under pressure.
I would love a video of Mickey explaining, you know, no, no, mine goes like this.
Like that would be really great.
It's a tick.
See, we put that in.
So totally different.
Totally.
It's not a queen or vanilla ice.
But I guess they wanted to avoid that.
So they went with this sort of generic ice ice Mickey.
You also wonder if they like approached so because there are some like some ringers and like name ringers.
There's celebrities threats.
Well, sort of questionably throughout this thing, but not vanilla ice.
You you think maybe you have to wonder if they threw it to more of these people because there's one a few tracks away from me that is a literal parody.
But the actual artist didn't get involved.
But then there are some real artists.
So did they try?
Did they try to build ice?
And did he have to say, guys, I'm not cool anymore.
Nobody likes me anymore.
It's 1994.
This seems like something though.
How could vanilla ice have turned down if he was offered it?
You know, like I don't know.
Already.
So he's down to clown with cartoon characters.
Right.
So it seems odd that he wouldn't.
I mean, is it a weird Al thing where, you know, famously weird Al had asked certain people to parody songs and they said, no, Prince never allowed him to parody a song of his.
All right.
I kind of think is it the guy there's the controversy gangsters, gangsters paradise where he he did it, but he didn't officially get word and he thought he had word.
So maybe it's a situation where Mickey reached out to vanilla ice and there was some confusion about it.
Maybe so.
Is it possible vanilla ice was just it?
When did shook night threaten him on a balcony?
Before this, I think.
Yeah.
Was he still just like, no, I'm not.
I don't want doing that one right now.
I don't like laying low, lay low.
Rob's laying low right now.
Or did shook night dangle Mickey Mouse over the bat?
Like you parody this.
You are a dead man.
I won't do any death row.
I won't parody.
Murder was the case.
I swear.
Oh, don't pull my hand.
My shorts off, please.
I'm going to need those for the cover.
That's that's kind of what I wanted to play of ice ice Mickey.
I'm being a little sparing in mind.
Could we listen to full tracks potentially?
But when I hear Disney Posse, I'm like, I think I'm good on that one.
I think I get the gist of ice ice Mickey.
Here's I mean, this is going to be a common refrain.
I feel like the people involved were lazy doing this.
I feel like this is one of the laziest sounding cash grabs that I've heard.
Yeah.
Give me some more effort, at least like like give me some like take some time to write these things.
I'm like, OK.
Well, I was going to say if just on the behind the scenes front, I did learn a little bit about some of the people involved in the in the record.
If this is a good time to talk about it.
Yeah.
The because they're people who are clearly capable of being not lazy, I think.
They all have like this legitimate roots, I feel like.
Some of these folks.
The album was mastered by Bruce Botnick, which is a name that sounded familiar to me.
And when I looked it up, he is the producer of Loves Forever Changes.
He produced the Doors, L.
A.
Woman.
He produced the MC5's Kick Out the Jams.
This is like a guy who did fundamental, cool, great, revolutionary music.
He engineered good vibrations.
He was part of Pet Sounds.
This is a luminary who then is just like, yeah, I'll get the bass higher on Ice Ice Mickey.
Why not?
How long will it take?
Can this be an afternoon?
If so, sure.
Well, he's an accomplice of Jim Morrison.
So already that suspect is one of the most annoying men of the 20th century.
Jim Morrison.
He would have been part of this album.
Oh, Jim Morrison lived.
Oh, man, he would have been.
I was such an insufferable.
He would have been like the worst Johnny Rotten.
Johnny Rotten's really cheese.
Oh, yeah, that's Morrison.
He would have been.
He would have been on that single with Clapton and what's his name?
Van Morrison.
More lockdowns.
Yeah.
Did you come across Bruce Botnick's theme car connection?
No.
So he has a very long list of credits on IMDB because he has worked on a lot of scores for movies.
It was like on the sound mix for like Larry Crown and Jack Reacher, which I just think it's funny to back to back to full name movies.
But for theme parks, he is credited on the sound mix for Soren.
Wow.
That's cool.
That's a good one.
That's a powerful boy.
I'd love to hear that in the room as soon as possible.
Sure.
I would love to hear that chopped up as a sample and then have Bill Farmer rap over it.
That's the thing I would like to hear.
But like an aggressive, goofy, like run the jewels style rap would just be terrific.
Yeah.
Oh, sure.
Can I say one more person who is involved in this?
And I may be opening up a can of worms by bringing this up.
The album was produced by somebody named Robin Frederick.
That's a female Robin.
And she was involved in her Wikipedia says that she was like in co wrote did work with Nick Drake and also John Martin, who's a similar just like, you know, I don't know a lot of his work, but like it seems like pretty lush, stirring English folk.
And she wrote songs with them and then became started doing children's albums where she did many years later where she did not only this, not only this Mickey Mouse rap album, but an album that have you guys ever come across this or did you weirdly have this as kids?
Something called Bugs and Friends Sing the Beatles.
I don't think so.
Then, sorry to take us into a different kids novelty.
We're crossing the moat from Mickey to Bugs.
And I didn't time this out, but let me see if I can grab just a good random sample of Bugs and Friends Sing the Beatles.
Stop and say hello.
The nasal Beatles.
It's the it's the Beatles see doesn't even feel like books to me.
No, it doesn't.
Yeah, it's a really grating very grating.
So they have Hello Goodbye I see up there.
Yeah, it's a there's one.
I think they am I making this up.
It's like one of the artier ones they do like day and day in a life entirely with Road Runner and Wiley Coyote sounds.
Wow.
I didn't listen to the whole thing.
That's what I believe I heard.
Can we cancel this one and do that?
No, it might be.
Maybe we have to visit this one down the road.
I don't know.
Bugs and Friends Beatles.
It's deeply more apparently in the liner notes.
They're referred to as the fabloonies.
Come on.
That's lazier than any of the other.
This is a warm guy.
Bang, bang, bang, bang, shoot, shoot.
Happiness.
I won Langhorn.
Why don't we do it in the road?
I say I say why don't we do it in the road?
Let's go forth.
I feel like I really wouldn't go on with that for a while.
Well, she was just a little girl.
You know what I mean?
Oh, no.
Oh, Pepe.
No, no.
Michelle, my Bella.
No, cancel.
You are not in Space Jam 2, Pepe.
I was surprised twice on that reveal because when you said bugs,
it's called Bugs do the Beatles.
What is it?
Bugs and Friends Sing the Beatles.
I thought it was like Beatles and caterpillars like singing Beatles.
Like I thought it was like the sounds of insects.
I also thought that's what it was.
Oh, oh, I mean.
I didn't realize it was Bugs Bunny.
Bugs Bunny.
Okay, so you had a kind of a delayed reaction.
Once you saw the mop-topped Bugs.
The mop-topped.
I've seen that.
I don't know what, wait, Taz ends up in Penny Lane and Birthday, apparently.
Taz all over it.
Taz does not.
Taz can't have a very good voice, can he?
It looks like Jim Cummings does it in it.
I mean, they probably play it for laughs.
And I was wrong.
I mean, it's even a crazier one that is done entirely by Roadrunner,
the long and winding road.
What?
Maybe this is good.
Maybe I like it.
I get it from a thematic sense because he runs on a long and winding road.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
That's always where you meet him at the beginning for the genus classifications.
Wow.
Well, I guess that's.
Just shift over.
We just ignore the rest of Mickey.
How mad, like listeners, how mad would you be if we did that?
Right now?
How mad if we had been in that this episode?
I feel like a couple of people, maybe, but I don't think everybody I don't know.
Boy, we'll finish it out.
We'll keep our way.
We'll keep going.
We'll hang with Bugs and Friends later.
Yeah, I am, however, plowing through it.
Let me see.
Can you just go 10 seconds into the next track?
And just to get a taste, I don't got a lot to say here.
This is in that genre of the characters aren't really involved.
And it's in a song called Minnie Mouse in the House.
Okay.
Get into the chorus here, mainly.
We're talking, talking, talking about it.
I wish you'd hurry up.
It's no fun without her.
Have you heard, have you heard?
It's a song about waiting for Minnie to get here.
The waiting for Godot, the song.
Yeah, who is the one we're waiting for?
To soar through the door and score.
So we're waiting for her.
To recap, we're waiting for her.
They've been waiting for her for a minute.
Minnie Mouse, Minnie Mouse, Minnie Mouse is in the house.
Minnie Mouse.
Okay, that'll do it.
For efficient storytelling, write 15 pages.
Don't throw out the first 10.
Keep the first 10 and write an additional 10 before those first 10.
A lot of time before the character shows up.
That's a good storytelling.
Yeah.
I mean, there's a very like a very Shoop, Salt and Pepper vibe to that going on,
which I like that part of it.
I like that like tea kettle, that the sample of the tea boiling.
I feel like multiple songs did that.
There's an MMC kind of R&B song that does that that I genuinely like called Real Talk.
I wish we were listening to that.
The Real Talk is I think a sleeper hit, like it should have been a bigger hit at the time.
Well, that's still that has to come on the music and a future episode as well.
We've been kind of talking about that forever.
Yeah, MMC's music.
Mickey Mouse Club, for those of you who don't know.
When they got cool and shortened it to pure MMC.
Yeah, this is not the end of Fudinchella, which is also a music episode in the future.
And who Bruce Botnick, this guy also cut his teeth on a bunch of Annette albums.
Wow.
Yeah, produced him, ran the sessions.
And he described, he said like a typical day for him might be,
I'm in the studio all day.
It's Annette most of the day.
And then at night, I'm going to sneak Jim Morrison in here and we're going to cut door stuff.
So, wow.
Yeah, he'd like do little handoffs between Annette and the doors.
So in the morning or at night, he's recording like, yeah, LA Woman or whatever.
And then in the morning, he's recording Annette's Italianette, Italian themed album where she sings about pizza pie and stuff.
Full album with the premise, Italianette.
Italianette.
There's Dancinette, Italianette.
There's Beach Party Records.
Yeah, it's Hawaii.
There's Hawaiianette, which is a Hawaiian themed album that's in the lobby of the Polynesian and Disney World.
These are all, you must like it kind of on an action figure level and that you have like the different modes of the turtles and then the different modes of Annette.
Yeah, it's like, yeah, she has something like a fireproof Annette suit.
Like it's Annette, but she has like a fire suit.
Like a Batman figure who would have like an orange suit and then you'd go into Toys R Us and you'd be like, I've never seen Batman wear this suit, but I should buy it.
I should buy this toy because he's going to need to be protected if I'm playing and he has a fire happen.
Obviously, I was always worried about fire because my mom put that into my head.
Everything's flammable.
Yeah, spontaneous fire.
Really hard collectible to track down, mech suit Annette.
Okay, so I'm going to take it here to the let's get to the single and I remember this very strongly.
I remember that there was a music video.
They probably showed it on the Disney Channel.
There was like a separate kind of more live performance music video that was shown on the show Walt Disney World Inside Out.
And that is a song called Womp There It Went.
Now, this is one where the actual artists got involved.
Tag team actually got there.
Tag team continues to make ironic appearances and things purely for money as they currently are in a Geico ad that you see a lot.
What are they telling you to soup?
There it is, right?
Yeah, right, right.
I think.
But this they maintained the Womp.
It's still Womp.
But they make it this new story that involves a party happening in which people are dancing and trying to bring cakes out.
But through various mishaps, they keep falling.
And that causes everyone to say Womp There It Went.
And that is the setup here for.
And this, I think this is the one I probably want to hear the most of.
I think you can tell why it's the single.
All right, here we go.
Party people!
Here's squeaky clean music with full effect.
Squeaky clean.
I don't care for that.
The first thing I did on my main duck, Donald.
We're kicking the flow and we're going to do it something like this.
Donald Duck, back again.
Turn up the music, let's begin.
Party on party people, let me hear some noise.
Party with Donald, Daisy and the boys.
There's a party over here, a party over there.
Tossing Donald up in the air.
And now trying to catch him, he falls down.
Womp There It Went hit ground.
Womp There It Went.
Let me hear ya.
Get dizzy.
Whoa, whoa.
Yeah, I like that better.
That's more, the artists are involved.
They get a payday out of it.
They at least get some money.
It's not just the Disney corporation profiting off of a cool new form of music.
Yeah.
In reading a little bit about Tag Team, I was especially happy that they got this Disney money.
Because Womp There It Is came from one of the guys in the group was the main DJ at Magic City, the Gentleman's Club in Atlanta.
Where I don't pretend to know everything about this, but I think a lot of music was broken there.
A lot of singles were debuted, and if you could make it at Magic City when the dancers are out, then it might go wide.
I think this was the first big Southern bass song in a way, the first mainstream-y Southern bass song.
Knowing that these guys were like Gentleman's Club DJs, and then before too long, they're hanging out with Mickey Mouse and that's great, making a Disney book.
Not only with that, but Womp There It Is featured very heavily in D2, The Mighty Ducks.
It's such an unlikely pairing.
In 92, they're DJs at a classy strip club, but a strip club, I think.
And then not too long after, important pieces of the Disney empire.
What a journey.
I loved, I remember we would jog around in gym class.
We would have to jog for 10 minutes or 5 minutes or whatever.
We would jog to Womp There It Is, and I was so excited when they would play it.
I was like, this is great.
I love this.
This version, not ideal for Donald, doesn't sound like a great birthday for him.
They're tossing him around.
Tossing and throwing him.
Yeah.
It's like when you're like, I don't want a whole thing for my birthday, and then someone does a whole thing.
And it's like, well, this is for you.
This is not for, I told you not to do this.
You come into my house, you come in my house, you bake a cake in my kitchen and then spill it on the floor, and then spill me on the floor in front of Tag Team.
Tag Team though got the game.
They knew that you always have to harass Donald, and that's what's funny about it.
They knew, they understood the game of Donald.
Tag Team infiltrate me again.
I think if you synthesize a monster from R3 Donald's, maybe you get one passable.
You just, you have to take like slim pickings from all of them.
Yeah.
If you want to skip ahead to, now as much as I like this, I think it's the most successful thing on the album.
If you go to around, let's say 110, this part's rough to me, I have to admit.
Okay.
Well, here we go.
Daisy is falling by now.
This is
Down the duck.
She's got the
So just to pause it for a second, that, I think I've said on the show before, if there's something that's extremely corny musically, I get embarrassment goosebumps really bad.
All the hairs on my arms stand up and the, when the characters all say boom, do boom, shock, a locker together in mass, you could see these goosebumps from space.
There, it just real, a shiver goes through me.
It is the corniest thing I have ever heard.
It has a very like vibe of a wedding DJ, like holding a mic out to the audience and like the seniors in the front, like during like say, whoop, there it is, whatever.
Like now you guys, shock, a locker, shock, a locker, like, yeah, like clapping on the one and the three, trying to do what the DJ has said.
They sort of heard this song 25 years ago.
It's that vibe of like, oh God, they're, they're, they're participating.
That's the main thing.
Sure.
Whoop, there it went.
Hey!
Cool, the Tellio disco sample.
He's in there.
W-H-O-O-M-P, it was time to eat the birthday treat.
Everybody lined up for the 10 layer cake.
It took Daisy all day to bake.
Who will bring it in?
Goofy will, but he tripped on his feet and he took a spill.
Out of his hands the whole cake flew.
Whoop, there it went.
Goofy too.
Can you dig it?
We can dig it.
Can y'all dig it?
Ooh, that again.
We can dig it.
Can y'all dig it?
Can you dig it?
We can dig it.
Can y'all dig it?
Can you dig it?
Maybe we're almost to the announcement.
I might have made a mistake playing all this.
Squeaky clean music coming straight at ya.
That's me.
I can be a mouse for fame.
Turn it all over to my pals, tag team.
Turn it all over to my pals.
Bring it back y'all, bring it back.
Here we go.
What's, Mike, what's your problem with squeaky clean music?
Because it's trying to be like, don't worry, it's not the bad kind of rap.
It's definitely trying to be like, don't worry white people.
Everything's fine here.
Not gonna hear anything bad on this.
He keeps saying it.
There was like a note where like somebody was like very worried.
So like, well, we have Mickey announced that it's squeaky clean music.
Yeah, no, that's a description of actual murders on this.
Right.
So yeah, that's my objection.
Not that I'm, of course, I'm always against clean, clean entertainment.
No, that I'm just saying the context for this.
I don't care for music being squeaky clean.
You're fine with I imagine the Annette albums you would describe as squeaky clean.
Yes, except for the album Murder Annette.
Just all murder ballads.
So that's that's whoop there.
It went.
I also I in terms of these guys getting getting money, I like that they not only did this, then they hopped across town and they went to Paramount and they did a version of whoop.
There it is very cleverly reframed to be whoop.
Adam's family.
There it is.
Yes, yes, yes.
Change the song, just kind of inserted it.
Whoop.
Adam's family.
There it is.
They kind of sample the theme.
That's how they customize it.
But I was revisiting this song.
It is a delight because I mean, I feel like there's such a generational bug at this point.
Adam's family values is just like a tent pole classic and rightfully so.
What a great movie.
And it's fun to listen to their version of it because they describe the story for a while and you know, which involves Joan Cusack as this nanny trying to take the Adam's fortune.
And they I just really love the nitty gritty they get into with the plot where they say makes Fester fall for her thing gets wise and spreads the word.
The family comes to Fester's aid.
Dry line.
A conclusion is soon reached.
I haven't heard that one in a while.
Is it better than this?
I like it more because there's not cartoon characters bothering you.
Yeah.
Yuck.
I like Goofy and I like Tag Team evidently.
But the mix.
I guess the one poisons the other.
I'm not sure.
Adam's family.
It's pretty good.
And then, you know, you watch the video, you get to see Pugsley and Wednesday hanging out with Tag Team.
They made so many music videos in this era.
And then there's the Hammer song too.
Of course.
Yeah.
Another custom.
What franchise got two custom like Men in Black, obviously, what with your black suits coming and the original.
But that's the star of the movie.
How do you get two custom rap songs from artists who are relevant only in that month and then faded immediately, perhaps because of the Adam's family song?
It's possible.
Yes.
No, I can't think of another example of that.
But because you bring up like a very like kind of Keystone 90s comedy we watched.
So I married an axe murder the other night.
And you want to talk about a big musical choice.
That movie plays.
There she goes.
So many times like we just started laughing.
By the last time it came out, it's like, are they fucking with us?
Like, what is this cute like three or four times in one movie?
And it's always just Mike Myers driving around San Francisco.
There's some perplexing stuff in that movie.
You forget like it's got a little bit of sketch comedy logic, but otherwise is very grounded.
So then it just makes the weird choices seem that much weirder.
Because there's like really normie romcom stuff.
That is very like normal editing.
They don't make a joke of how many times they play it.
But then they'll do.
There is some like crazy absurd Austin Powers style comedy in it, but not fully.
Phil Hartman as the prison.
Like that Al Khajraj poor guy is very weird and funny.
Of course, Mike Myers playing his character's father too.
He essentially does like the fat bastard, the Shrek and the Dr.
Evil voice at different points throughout this movie.
I love when like a more absurd sensibility has to be as to like slide into the like comedy plot box.
Like you got to save grandma's house or like like a love interest that the movie itself doesn't care about.
Like dirty work is one of those.
Norm is not thinking remotely about like chemistry with this actress.
He doesn't care about the stove saving the grandpa's house or paying for his surgery.
Like he was just told they put a plot in there.
All right, whatever.
And then I'll do a bunch of jokes about whores.
Yes, that is absolutely what his main concern was.
That was her number one with that movie.
Anyway, the I'll end my run.
I mean, now I'm like, this is one maybe we have to hear a lot of.
And I don't there's not a lot of intro I can do.
I think we just have to play.
What a mouse.
All right, so we know what this is.
But yes, no salt and pepper.
Right.
So it's a parody without the actual artists.
Yes.
It's strange because Coming to America just came out and that is what a king in it with real salt and pepper.
We get all right.
A lot of chorus to get through.
Well, it's so compelling, though.
But here we go.
Because you never hear about him with another girl.
I don't sweat it.
He's always sympathetic.
I get it.
Get around it.
He's a number one mouse for me.
I know that no mouse is perfect.
I give props to those who deserve it.
And believe me now, he's worth it.
So here's to the because we've had a great path.
No mouse is worth it.
Could make me laugh.
I get a kick.
He's my Mickey.
So feelings, thoughts so far?
Okay.
No offense to what's her name.
Who did Mickey Minnie's voice?
Lucy Taylor, Russie Taylor.
I don't think I know the yeah, I don't know that she's really like spitting here.
I wouldn't say it's very quiet.
It's very timid.
Maybe not though, you know, it is.
But totally many was a little bit more like, you know, big bombastic.
You know, she was a little more out there versus this where it feels like this woman is like trying to like just hold on tight while she has to do this.
She's just like holding the holding the clipboard, holding the music stand in front of her while she's like white knuckling it, trying to go like I got a rap.
What is this?
I don't know how to.
And this woman like looks like she seems like the sweetest woman.
She looks like a, you know, a teacher librarian of yours.
Like, yeah, this woman having to do with salt and pepper.
It feels like they turn their head, their turn or volume way up because they're like, excuse me.
You're not.
You're just whispering this.
I'm not confident in what I'm doing.
But then if she goes too loud, is she like now is she like trying to sound like salt and pepper, which has its own problems.
It's essentially got it's a Kobayashi Maru, which is a Star Trek reference to the no win scenario here.
There's no winning for this poor woman having to do this.
It's a very sexy song.
So you got to be careful.
It's a very sexually charged song.
And there's one this is where OK, you're right that she's very quiet and muted.
But there's this one part and maybe just try to get past the chorus if you can, because I don't hear that chorus anymore.
But the next verse is this part where she's full on trying to do what they did.
And I commend her for it.
He isn't fast like Speedy doesn't have a deep voice.
But if I was that a reference to Speedy Gonzalez, she isn't fast like Speedy.
There's no space or a Disney.
It's weird.
I know of it's weird.
They would acknowledge the other set of characters and almost like a diss a little.
Someone have written this not knowing that Speedy wasn't a Disney character.
Oh, that's very possible.
I feel like whoever was shitting this out was just like fast like Speedy, right?
Speedy's in the Disney.
He's a Disney character.
The way we watched Adam West in a thing improvising about like my buddies, Superman and Spider-Man.
Spidey, baby.
I love that he doesn't know that's a different like that's so much better.
I feel like than an actor knowing every little bit about the mythology.
I'm like, oh, yeah, I yes, I I some people get, I think, upset when actors are like,
I don't know, Scarlett Johansson's on like a talk show and she's like, I don't know.
I just show up.
I don't know what movie it is.
I just I did two weeks.
I don't know.
Like some people, I think, get mad about that.
I don't give a shit.
It's really funny to me.
Better.
When it's cool.
Didn't know she was in a movie.
A couple of weeks ago, they were like trying to remind her like you were in that movie.
You're in Spider-Man.
I was.
Remember we were at the end.
Billy D.
Not knowing what the hell Donald Glover is talking about about playing Lando.
That's the funniest story.
I love that.
They had a meeting about like, how do I play Lando?
And right.
I was asking a lot of questions and he's like, I don't know.
Just be charming.
Yeah, right.
It's as much as Billy D.
No, it's about it's great.
It's great.
All right.
Back to back to Minnie Mouse.
Okay.
He knows just what to do.
I don't have to say please.
In my life.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
He knows which is what to do.
I don't have to say please.
What is she talking about?
Nice.
I said on the Mickey's house episode that Mickey and Minnie's love is, I believe, sexual in some way.
Hey, you didn't just say that kind of dry stating a fact.
Yes.
I did say that.
I remember I saw some people point that out that I said that.
Minnie and Mickey's love is sexual in a way.
It's in a court document.
It'll be in a future court document.
But this is what is she talking?
She didn't.
This line about baking cookies didn't precede this, right?
I didn't miss something.
Not sure.
Let me go back.
I just want to make sure.
I mean, some of these lines are probably just from the real one.
He doesn't have a deep voice, but if I had to pick, he'd be my choice.
He knows just what to do.
I don't have to say please.
In my life.
He's number one.
The really big cheese.
I go.
Yeah, no way.
As far as I'm concerned, she's talking.
First of all, she's talking about how fast he is with his, I guess, his sexual prowess
earlier.
He's not fast like speedy.
You think that's what it is?
I view that is that he is not as fast at running.
You think it's literally just running?
That's what I think.
She's saying.
You're seeing the sex in it.
You're saying the stamina.
I'm seeing sexual stamina.
You can't.
You all you gravitate towards the sexual nature of Minnie.
Isn't this the isn't that what happens when the most repressed person hears anything?
That's all they can see.
You know, that's all they're obsessed with.
But I think that one the mid that one line, I'm not that's not much of a reach.
I don't think so.
What did he knows just what to do about what?
What would he know just what to do about in regards to many?
I don't like what to get at the grocery store.
What did you get for birthday?
I this to me is like you're getting offended in that way, like to bring the doors up or like the with the kind of like relatively tame lines they would have to censor on the Ed Sullivan show.
Yeah, I didn't get much higher.
I couldn't get much higher.
They're talking about drugs.
Let's spend the night together rolling stones on the end.
Sullivan, they had to say, let's spend some time together.
This is a lude song I've ever heard.
I think that line is more dirty, though, than let's spend the night together.
But you don't wait, wait, say it again, though.
Say it again.
Now the she knows just what to do.
I don't have to say, please.
Yeah, on its own is like filthy, filthy, filthy line, filthy lyric.
Many think about like cleaning the dishes.
Well, let's see.
Is there any other here?
I'm happy to be wrong.
But is there any more after this that would give a little more contact?
Let's hear it.
Every time I see a lot of other mice try, but they couldn't be him.
He never let me down in a cartoon yet.
Once you get to know him, he's the kind of mouse that you never forget.
Well, OK, listen to the way she says that last line.
He's the kind of mouse you'll never forget.
You'll never forget.
That's lust.
Yeah.
I mean, it is a look.
It is based on a horny song.
The song is very old.
The original song, very horny.
But they didn't take the they really needed to get to take all of that out.
And they did not do a good job.
That was left over in here.
And I'm not look, I'm many as feel as free to express herself in any way she'd like.
I'm just saying I'm a little surprised by it on this album.
That's all.
Well, it's very, I guess, very forward, but very pioneering in a way.
And that's right to the upfront with sexuality.
And there's nothing wrong with it.
Exactly.
Yeah.
So I'm just surprised.
That's all.
Can we hear chorus?
Can we skip the chorus if we can try?
I can try to do that.
Let's see here.
Because there's one more, I think that's a good.
Okay.
If you're if you're.
He's got a sense of humor and it's taken him far.
He's not a fake wannabe trying to be a star.
He's got his own style no matter what the scene.
Makes a cool fashion statement.
He's the mouse of my dreams.
Yeah, my mouse says he loves me.
Never says he loves me.
Now he takes me out for cheesecake.
And all the right spots, other guys that I met, they don't impress me a bit.
And every time they try, I say that's not it.
Nikki loves that cheese.
She's buddy loves that nut.
T whiz.
I say that's not it.
Is many talking about me there?
I mean, she's not about my but is she is she throwing shade at me?
Now the guys show up at Park photo ops.
Older men with no one around.
If they do have a girlfriend, she's nowhere to be found.
I make a smooch and say, go away.
I hope that man's locked up one day.
I'm pretty good.
I'm pretty good at this rap game.
Come on.
When it's the character you understand.
Yeah.
Okay.
So let's let's see what else we got here.
He better know.
Yeah, she knows.
Good mice are hard to find.
Wow.
Well, that's the winner so far.
Yeah.
I think that's I mean, that's a that's a really solid.
If you had questions about the quality of the album and tracks one and two, three and four, that's a real good stretch.
But does it maintain in track five?
I don't know the answer.
I don't even remember which of you covered this one.
I know that's me.
And all right, everyone buckle up for Bow Wow to the Beat featuring Whoopi Goldberg.
Oh, Mike.
Yeah.
Hit it.
Hit that beat.
Here I said there was no G funk on it.
Yeah.
All right.
Cut it.
Okay.
So this song should just be called Whoopi Goldberg's explains dogs to you.
She first of all, it's not featuring what we go.
It is starring what we go.
What we go.
Berg is the main star of the song.
Yeah.
And if I heard Whoopi Goldberg rap, I don't think I had I kind of wasn't prepared for that.
Interesting.
So but is she talking about Pluto or goofy or great question.
So about a minute in, there's still no mention of Pluto about two minutes and three seconds and you finally get the Pluto.
But can you jump to like one forty five real quick?
Yes.
Because then something else happens before.
Stop that.
Come over here and behave.
Now, come on and let me think.
Stop biting me.
Let me see this song.
Okay.
Cut it.
So in the middle of the song, she just yells at a dog for some reason.
And you're saying up until this point, there's still no mention of any Disney dog or.
No, still still no mention.
If you hit play from this point on, we start to get to him.
Okay.
All right.
So just to repeat that line is on a scale of eight, he's a big K9.
And then she goes, I like that.
Scale of eight.
I guess that ever used.
Let's think about this.
If you went on a scale of scale of ten, he's a big K9.
It makes it seem like he's not the best.
You have to make him sound the best, but you can't rhyme nine with K9.
So they have that.
They decided on eight.
I get the conundrum they were in.
Yeah.
The scale of eight is strange.
Hmm.
Interesting one.
I mean, good for her for being being game.
Yeah.
So the song ends.
And at some point she says the dog's got a brand new bag and a scooper, too.
If you recall the 1990s, Pooper Scooper was the big comedy reference de jour of the time.
We had one sold on TV product.
Sure.
And then a thing that happens like on most tracks on this album is they all kind of fade out in the same way.
And when this one fades out, you can hear what the Goldberg very quietly saying, what did you put on the side of my pant leg?
So like Pluto Pete on her.
Like one of the dogs defecated on her in some way.
So Pluto made we think it was Pluto or do you think it was just because there's a lot of dogs in this?
It's hard to say.
Yeah, there's like a wrecking crew of singers and a wrecking crew of dogs in this track.
So could be any number of dogs.
Any number is possible.
Could have been Beethoven, Lassie, Renton, also referenced.
That's true.
Yeah.
He doesn't own as well.
Speedy was referenced earlier.
Get some shade thrown at them, too.
Yeah, Beethoven was not Disney.
So they're referencing more like it's open season apparently with different characters not owned by the Disney company.
Well, they got this right about rap of the time.
This feuds.
They're like they're calling out other companies IP.
Yeah, I think it's great.
Yeah, but they should take it a step further and say we're going to shoot Beethoven.
Pluto is going to shoot Beethoven.
Put him down in the middle of a field.
Pop pop.
His misery.
Uh huh.
All right, Jason, you want to go to the next one here?
Yeah.
So track number six, DJ goof.
Oh, no.
Uh huh.
All right.
Here we go.
Graduation theme.
Break.
Very loud.
Mr.
DJ goof.
Hit it.
Now he's a DJ and he's gone to school to learn the golden rule about scratching in fashion spinning records on the school.
He's going to do his best and put it to the test and the rest is up to the beat.
OK.
All right.
The premise of this.
Yeah.
Is that goofy is going to a higher an Institute of Higher Learning for rapping and DJ for scratching for scratching for scratching.
Yeah, sorry.
And and they say he graduated summa cum laude.
Very loud.
Which I think is meant to be goofy makes a lot of noise.
But I like to think it works in that goofy is smoking that loud.
He is smoking the loud loud as a sign term for very potent marijuana.
Well, Jason, you've enlightened me yet again on this podcast.
I did not know that.
Yeah.
Puts it over our heads.
So are you Jason?
Are you getting loud?
Are you?
Would you say never before I record Michael?
Never.
No, I like to be sharp.
You're too sluggish.
But they do really dig in their heels on the higher education thing.
Later on, he says rap alumni.
That's me.
But you can call me goof.
J.
D.
is a law degree.
What?
But also in this song, he seems very confused by the trappings of DJ.
Like he doesn't know.
He says, where is the base?
Guess I left it in the backbeat.
So he kind of knows everything.
But if he had graduated summa cum laude, pretty good in terms of graduating honors.
But goofy, he's going to school to learn the golden rule about scratching.
There's a thing on this record where they do very rudimentary rhymes and then seem very pleased with themselves at what they've accomplished.
Mickey congratulates himself.
Whoopies.
That's good.
Yeah.
There's a lot of two acknowledging wordplay.
Like the other guy says, give me a beat and goofy goes, wouldn't you rather have an apple?
Like, come on, man.
Fuck off with that shit.
Get out of here.
So is there any other part of this song we need to hear?
No, not really.
I think you got the gist of it.
All right.
I'm so relieved every time.
That's the answer.
Yeah.
OK.
Ducks in the Hood.
Yeah.
We have seen very little of Ducks in the Hood.
Uh oh.
All right.
Here we go.
Get it.
Yeah.
We're all just eerily silent here.
No, it's creepy.
Oh, them.
OK, you can cut it there.
Oh, are you sure?
Yeah.
So there's a few things going on.
One, this song appears to be about the school to prison pipeline.
Maximum security kindergarten in Anaheim.
Right.
Huey, Dewy and Louie are going to kindergarten in Anaheim.
Yeah.
I guess in Toontown.
Is it Toontown?
Well, at some point they say, like, crowds of children have gathered in front of the
Magic Kingdom castle as if there's about to be a riot.
But this is what I was talking about.
This sounds like the B team of Huey, Dewy and Louie.
I don't know, though, because I was thinking who was their voice?
And I just checked and it is Rue C.
Taylor.
So they had her.
I will say that.
I think maybe it's just maybe what you're hearing is that she is, again, not at ease
with rapping.
Humiliated, you could say.
She's feeling humiliated.
She was, according to Wiki, 50 years old when doing this.
So tough age to be rapping.
Well, then maybe.
Now there's plenty of north of 50 rappers.
And plus, if you look through the glass in the studio and you're looking right in the
eyes of Phil Spector, I'd like you to not sound nervous either.
Oh, Phil produced this track?
Phil Spector produced this track.
Phil Spector and Rick Rubin.
They did not decide.
OK, so this is another one where they went with a parody title yet did not parody the
actual song.
This is not a parody of Boys in the Hood by EZ.
No, but it's like imply it's confusing because it's like it's like that Aerosmith video
game where it's like music has been outlawed.
This is dangerous.
Right.
Yes.
Revolution X.
I think you're talking about.
I'm talking about Revolution X.
Yes.
Because I don't know why Huey and Dewey and Louie are a problem.
They there is an exchange where one of them says we throw down the rhyme and then another
one says, yeah, then we pick it up again.
And one of them says, hey, Louie, get a clue.
That's right.
Bold stuff.
Yeah, this is yeah, they're paired.
They're saying, oh, wow, they're so scary, these ducks.
But of course, they're just loose on the streets of Anaheim.
After being locked up in an elementary prison.
At kindergarten, were they that young?
Are the nephews that young?
They're in kindergarten.
I always thought of them as a little older.
I thought elementary school maybe.
Yeah, I felt like fifth grade, fourth, fifth grade.
That's how they seemed to me.
I don't want to go on a tangent, but like what was going on with that thing where Danny
Pooty said, I don't have a lot of money.
I make DuckTales money to Larry King.
And people are like, hell yeah.
You show.
Yeah.
Put Larry in his place and then Larry died.
Like, what was all that?
Why would why are we?
Oh, is it funny?
Did you watch the little clip?
I yeah.
Larry, they haven't.
I feel like people were celebrating it like, oh, I don't know.
In an annoying Twitter way.
Like, I mean, that's just Twitter.
You put Larry in your place, Danny.
The context was funny because Larry said, what are your guilty pleasures?
Your indulgences.
And he said, like, oh, I like coffee and socks.
And Larry goes, socks.
No, I'm talking about what he's like.
Well, what do you mean there?
And he goes, I don't know, private plane or and Daniel goes, Larry, I'm a DuckTales.
Not a really care.
That is funny.
I think it was like in an annoying way.
Am I crazy?
Every I mean, I see that, but that's everything on Twitter.
There's trending and you're like, what?
Why is this an issue now?
Is this like a do I have to be?
Do I have to sign a petition?
DuckTales and Larry King?
I mean, yeah, probably.
It's probably a petition out there.
But yeah, look, I don't know.
The Twitter can ruin anything.
Really can't.
Yes.
Yeah.
Things I love.
Then I see tweets about it.
I'm like, I don't like this anymore.
Yeah.
You like it.
It's an annoying way.
It's too much information.
As I've said before, it's like Professor X and Cerebro.
He's getting all the information from everyone's head at once in like on Earth and it's too
much for him sometimes and he flips out and passes out.
That's exactly what Twitter is.
We shouldn't be getting too much that much information at once.
Yeah.
That's like the most beautiful way to put it.
That being said, stay tuned to podcast the rights Twitter for updates about the only
follow us.
That's what my wife does.
And she's right.
Yeah.
And like the 2000s design accounts that post like, oh man, look at this cool plastic watch
that's real blobby.
Yeah.
And non-standard McDonald's.
All those guys.
The account that's just like weird Japanese mascots too.
Oh yeah.
Mondo Mascots.
Yeah.
Mondo Mascots is a mascot.
Definitely.
All right.
But we're going to stay.
Now it's just going to keep growing.
And then like this other guy, Tim Poole and this other guy.
No.
Oh no.
You know about him.
Okay.
Anyways.
Go to.
Okay.
And in the duck song, go to like 227.
Here's an example of one of the fade out gags that are in this album.
What did he say?
He says, I'm so thirsty.
My grape juice went everywhere.
And then another one says, Hey, how come we're fading?
We're not done yet.
And then the third one says, I am.
So that's kind of funny that they acknowledge that like someone should acknowledge that
like, yeah, every track on this album fades out the same way.
Strange.
Well, I mean, I would, I would like to think that the album was actually like double the,
like double the length.
And then somebody listened to it and went, Oh, God damn it.
All right.
Just fade out halfway through each song, just to make it shorter.
We got to do something here.
They didn't want to release like an all things must pass double album.
Oh yeah.
It was a double album.
All the songs double the length.
Yeah.
Ice ice Mickey was 30 minutes long.
You got to let it play out.
It's an Odyssey.
I'm doing work.
I'm making art here.
Okay.
Yeah.
We can go on to track eight MC Mickey.
So finally the mouse is back.
Right, right, right.
As a long break on the talk about him.
Yeah.
So, okay.
Okay.
MC Mickey, he's the mouse that rocks.
He turns up the boom in the bus.
Going to send it out.
Going to take it to the house.
He's a rapper who's dapper.
Yeah, he's the mouse who could do it.
Got a positive message and you know he's into it.
Talk about is.
Oh, the better to hear the mouse continue saying.
All right.
Got it.
Oh, oh, I see what that is.
Yeah.
That's a sample from the original from the 50s opening.
Right.
Yeah.
They also yay Mickey.
They kind of remix the Mickey Mouse Club theme a little at parts.
Yeah.
And there's a little later.
There's a little more of that coming of course in the album as well.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
What else?
Mine all got worse as they went on.
Like it's hard to top the Whoopi Goldberg song and then MC Goof is pretty.
DJ Goof.
DJ Goof, sorry.
Mickey is an MC.
Yeah.
And this is just, this sounds like a guy that got like an assignment to like put over Mickey
as an MC.
It's like, Hey, you know, make Mickey look good.
He's not actually that good of an MC.
If you could get on this track though, people might believe you.
And he's like, all right, I'll do my best.
And this is his effort to like make us confuse us maybe into thinking, Oh yeah, Mickey is
a good MC.
He really knows how to rhyme, but it's that's bullshit.
Mickey's not a good, he's not a good MC.
No offense, Mickey.
Sorry.
He's good at plenty of other things.
You almost everything else he's tried.
He's pretty good at.
Not this.
Let's be honest.
He says at some point, guess I'm a wannabe.
I just want to be me.
These are not the rhymes are not clever.
They're not, you know, he's not spitting them with fire.
There's no fire.
It's a lot.
A lot of these songs sound like if you take an improv class and they're like, okay, this
warmup is called build a rap.
And everyone tries to like rap together and it, it kills a couple.
It makes you be spontaneous in the moment and it gets you used to looking foolish and
trusting your classmates.
But it is often excruciating to do and see.
We humiliate ourselves in empty theaters down on Santa Monica.
The chains I forged in life to podcast.
What else?
Oh, jump to two minutes, 40 seconds.
All right.
Two minutes.
No.
All right.
WALT.
Yeah.
The DJ goof at some point says like brought to you by WD and it's like, I don't know that
Walt would sanction this buffoonery.
I don't know that it is brought to you by WD.
WALT now it carries Glenn Beck's show and Sean Hannity's show.
It's really the format has changed a lot since the nineties.
It's changed a lot.
Not any longer.
R&P Rush.
Yeah.
So WALT.
I like that bit of.
I like that bit of canon.
I don't know if that's anywhere else.
They use that in ToonTown.
I go like, that's clever.
But it being a hip hop radio station.
I don't know.
Yeah.
Walt.
OK.
Yeah, that's bad.
Yikes.
Oh boy.
Well, Mike, do you have anything that will change our mind about.
Take it away, Michael.
I don't have anything to change your mind.
Here's a song called You Can't Botch This.
Oh.
Can't botch this.
My, my, my.
I turned on the hose to water my lawn.
I went inside and left it on.
Now my yard is a great big lake.
It did my garden wavering.
It all got all covered in mud.
So I gave him a bath in the tub.
He farted out and shook his coat.
Now I'm the one who got all soaked.
The senseless things turn into a mess just when you're sure you can't botch this.
Can't botch this.
All right.
I've heard.
OK, now having heard all of your songs, the ones you guys have previewed, this is a lot
better than some of them.
Yeah.
Sure.
Interesting that all these songs are like a picture of domestic life, a birthday party
chores around the house.
You know?
Yeah.
You can't botch this, but it's goofy's botching everything.
At least.
Botching is a funny word for it, too.
I don't know why that makes me laugh.
It's weird.
You can't touch this and to botch this.
Yeah.
You botch is a word that I always associate with professional wrestling.
If some move goes awry, people say it was a botch.
But I don't think about it when goofy's doing housework until now.
So.
But yeah, it's obviously you can't touch this parody, which believe me goes farther on this
album if it's a parody of a real song that's actually using the music, because we do have
affection for the song itself.
But yeah, that's basically I mean, there's.
Can't botch this.
There's like a little bit of business with like Pluto being feral.
Cooking is simple.
Easy as pie.
Who needs to be?
I'll just try.
Cooking is simple.
I went to a store and bought a bike.
Put it together.
But it didn't look like there's handlebars in the back.
You see, in an extra wheel where the seat should be.
One or two shirts.
I took a guess it's set on the box.
You can't watch this.
It's set on the box.
It's like they're close to like having a premise that makes sense.
But it's like it says on the box, you can't botch this.
That type.
It's like things for dummies.
Yeah.
So I get where they're going, but this feels like a bit of a first draft, though I do like it.
The Disney characters, they're all they're all bad, I guess, at everything as well.
So this is this implied this is this like folksiness that runs through this.
And maybe I say that because of Goofy's accent.
But like in general, yeah, the bacon, the cake, it's like they're all is the comedy of the Disney characters that they're like
They're like so they're this folksy down home.
And yeah, we get ourselves in a fix and the dog ends up running through the laundry line and gets messed everywhere.
But then we break bread and we are thankful for our day together as a family.
I think that this is I think this is very mama's family.
I think that's correct.
I assume you watched a lot of mama's family growing up as well.
I don't mama's family is one of those things that like as soon as it came on out, out, hate, hate this.
Yeah, I like it.
I like I said that's why I don't what I just said is not an accurate reflection of what mama's family is because I've run for the hills every time it's appeared.
I don't know either.
It sounds like you're describing the Waltons.
Yeah, it's that this is like 70s television, like wholesome.
Yeah.
I believe we have a little fun, but not too much.
Right.
It just feels like this is probably a TV that you were raised on.
That's all I'm that's all I was saying.
Oh, yeah.
Well, I watched the 90s version of it.
Seventh heaven.
Right.
There's so much seventh heaven in my house, which boy was it hilarious.
Then when the star of the show turned out to be the biggest creep in the universe.
Yes, I call this like my family truly did not know what to do.
It's just like, well, slide the DVDs to the back of the shelf.
I suppose.
What a day that must have been.
I wasn't actually there.
I've never talked about it.
And if I did this, it would change the subject.
Right.
Let's talk about politics instead.
So, yeah.
OK, so you can't watch this.
I don't know.
There's nothing too much more exciting.
Like, that's my thing.
I bought a guitar and I started to sing.
But every time that I begin, the neighborhood dogs, they all join in.
I went outside in my underwear.
The door blew shut.
I stuck out there.
Pulling a bus full of kids.
You know what they said?
I can't watch this.
Why?
OK.
What?
Yeah.
First of all, Mickey's playing guitar.
He's bad at it.
Dogs holler.
All right.
Fine.
He botched playing the guitar for the first time.
Whatever.
Goofy went outside, got locked out because he was in his underwear and a bus of kids
drove by and yelled, You can't botch this, Adam.
What?
Why would that happen?
What is this first draft?
This isn't
It should be like, You screwed up.
It should be something that said like, Oh, you screwed up.
But like, You can't botch this.
You can't botch going out of your house?
I don't know.
Yeah.
Hey, mama's family update.
There's a divorce involved behind the scenes.
Carol Burnett is pissed because someone else took over a role.
This is a spinoff of the Carol Burnett show.
Yeah, it was a character from Carol.
It's why it looks like a broad sketch character.
Yeah.
And, you know, for the most part, some of these characters look like they were storming
the Capitol.
Does this picture, just these vibes, these folks are giving off.
Mama wanted to be there, but mama's in such poor health.
Yeah.
She sent the boys instead.
Not during a pandemic.
Which is fake, by the way.
Even though mama
They won't admit that mama got COVID.
Yeah, half of mama's family.
Mama's family got cut in half by COVID, but they still won't acknowledge it.
Still don't believe it.
Flu was really bad this year.
Moving on.
This next one's called Little Red Rapping Hood.
Oh, come on.
This is another one where it's like, what are we doing here?
What is
I know there's like a red riding hood in the Big Bad Wolf.
I will say, because the Disney characters aren't on it, there is some more legit stuff in here.
Like that eye level bass that walks down, if you hear that again, I think that's a pretty good bass line.
And it's got some energy to it.
This woman is one of the more talented performers.
I mean, I said what are we doing here?
Because I don't know what this is doing on here, but it is better than most of the other stuff.
Yeah.
And yet, don't you like
You almost want it to be worse in order to be something.
I mean, you do get
You finally get some characters.
So like Minnie is like Little Red Riding Hood now.
And then she's talking to a wolf who's not one of the Disney characters, who's just the Big Bad Wolf.
No, the Big Bad Wolf from the three
Oh, you're saying that's probably
They're trying to do his voice from the thing.
I don't know.
It doesn't sound
Yeah.
The guy goes, oh yeah, or something.
Does the Big Bad Wolf go, oh yeah, or anything in those old cartoons?
I don't remember.
I don't recall.
Yeah, I don't know what's going on here.
This maybe could have been a trim.
Just got like off the game, I think.
Right.
But again, yeah, save the bass line for something.
It's like
I mean, you are like, oh, thank God that woman came in to stop Minnie from having to rap.
Oh God.
More, please.
Put this
Let this poor woman go home.
Anyway, that's Little Red Riding Hood.
Let's get to Mickey Mouse Club Mix.
Oh, oh, this is the theme?
It's going to be like the Bat Dance.
So you got a sample there.
Is this going to do a record scratch?
Oh no, it's just at up tempo.
Maybe this is my favorite one, weirdly.
Well, as far as the genre, I have a lot of affection for this.
Kind of jock jammy.
Yes.
This has energy.
Come on, come on.
Get it, get it.
No, no, no.
Yeah, that Mickey comes in and he kind of ruins it.
Yeah, exactly.
Stay out of the music, Mickey.
Yeah, yeah.
They kept playing that original sample where he says a lot going on today, you would have heard.
America has invaded the Korean Peninsula.
If you play, yeah, if you continue that, it was on the original track.
Yeah, these are all these.
There's a lot of great like old early 90s, like club mixes like this.
And I'm trying to think of the names of some of the best ones.
That's worthy of, you know, it's adjacent to Quad City DJs.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, on the pre-proto Quad City DJ.
So yeah, then Mickey comes in and he ruins it.
But that's the I mean, that's the gist of it.
You know, there's still a little more of the samples to be had, which is not so great.
Get right to the get to the beat.
Get to something we can dance to here.
I kind of like this.
Yeah, there's a nice little guitar in there.
Crystal Waters.
100 percent.
And then like the sample.
No, get the fuck out of here with that sample.
Yeah, I don't.
OK, boo boo.
Oh, yeah.
All right.
Back to OK.
OK, yeah, here we go.
Yeah, I'm a dancer, man.
Mickey, like a lot of that pronunciation or enunciation.
Yeah.
So so that's good.
I mean, I would put a chop out those bad samples and you could put that on a CD.
You could put that on.
You could DJ a party with that.
I don't think there would be a problem there.
But you've already got a cool Mickey Mouse Club, you know, in Orlando.
They're covering that with who some of who become the dominant pop stars in the world.
So let these future pros handle it.
Yeah, exactly.
Why are why are these?
Why is this anonymous club mix here?
I mean, it says it's the tired old refrain of this episode.
What are we doing here?
I did want to say in that in the one track earlier, MC Mickey, that saxophone solo
sounds like something from, I think, a current song.
And it was driving me crazy.
Like, and I could not figure out what it was.
I think it's a newish song or it's a song that is new to me.
And I still have not found the answer of what that sax sounds like.
But I swear there is a hit song that just ends with a saxophone recently.
I don't know.
Well, we'll have to ask the listeners.
I know.
I think there is one.
I don't know what it is.
Yeah.
Hmm.
Not that with it.
Where does where where does this go?
Where do we go?
Well, we go to the color of music, which is a song featuring color me bad.
Uh huh.
Star power at the end is yes, star power at the end, which of course color me bad does
the song I want to sex you up.
Mm hmm.
And they sure do.
Yeah.
They are fairly embarrassing to look at if you look at photos of them.
They probably wish that they didn't exist to be to be got that there's some funny
recent.
You talk about recent photos.
No, I just know.
Look at them at the time.
They look so insane.
Oh, oh, I see.
Weird laptops and Bell mustaches and George.
Oh, as far as the look dies.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The head, the pants, they all have like these like poofy leather pants.
Mm hmm.
I've there's some recent photos too that are a little so I'll say they're kind of like
fedora guys now seem right.
Yeah.
There's a profile of them on a color me bad want to prove it.
They're in it for the long haul.
A feature on entertainer mag dot com.
If they can get there.
Make it anywhere.
They're playing at the Casinos Ovation's live showroom on with the Brian Adams.
All right.
Parentheses maskless.
Yeah, that's this week.
These maskless audience.
Call me bad singer arrested after pushing band member on stage.
You hate to see it.
You never want to see that Joe.
Joe Perry showed Steven Tyler off the stage and he didn't get arrested.
There's a video.
Look at look up Google on YouTube search.
Joe Perry kicks Steven Tyler off the stage.
Joe Perry very clearly runs into Steven Tyler and knocks him off the stage into the audience.
Probably out of anger.
There's clips of Steven Tyler like messing with Joe Perry during concerts.
He's clearly mad at the illusion of my two best friends jamming together.
I'm sorry.
There's a bit of animosity over the years.
So color me bad.
That's going to happen to Jason and I at a live show one of these days.
We're going to be happy to see each other again in person once and then it's all going to rain.
I'm going to ramp the fuck up.
This is going to kick me off stage.
Yeah.
And I'll deserve it.
All right.
The color of music.
This is featuring color be bad.
And this one I'm just like, what is this doing here?
Well, we are all the same in the same.
It was like a harmony song.
They're just the Disney characters are all just sitting and nodding like they're in the front row of a president's funeral of a color me bad concert.
That's also a president's funeral.
Nixon has died and color me bad will be here to tribute.
But it's just I'm zooming through here.
There's no Disney characters.
Just color me bad harmonizing.
And that's the end of the album.
That's how it goes out.
It's pleasant.
I like the sound of it.
It's very pleasant.
Very nice.
I don't know why that's at the end of the album.
So there you go.
That ends on a strange note.
That's strange as yeah, as it causes us to do to.
It's funny.
I just watched an old Grammy Awards as I want to do where they do an acapella harmony thing, but kind of back to back to them.
And then boys to men do the same thing and boys to men blow them out of the water like the audience does not respond at all.
The color me bad and boys to men.
Everyone like gets up and cheers and loses their mind.
So it's not like this.
The color me bad is that compelling doing what they're doing here.
Right.
But yeah, it's pleasant.
I just you're listening to a bunch of like cartoon characters try to do popular music.
And then all of a sudden the album ends with like a nice little minute and a half from color me bad doing it like a sincere, like gospely kind of song.
And that's it.
It's the kiss.
Good night.
Yeah, that's true.
That's true.
It's a nice soft little kiss.
Good night from color me bad.
Everyone's every lady's dream.
I want to kiss you.
Good.
I want to kiss you up.
I want to kiss you.
Good night.
Out your hat fell in my eye poking me with your fedora.
Strange.
Well, they brought him in to do something not Disney ish.
Maybe they just bought a color me bad track.
Very possible sale.
Yeah.
Weird.
Well, I don't know.
Boy, that makes me feel uneasy.
We didn't even get to go out on like a crazy.
Well, I have something to say at the end of the episode.
No, perfect.
We could.
It took into rescue us at this point.
Yeah, yeah.
Save it.
But now I have to rescue.
I mean, to sum up, to sum up, I mean, you know, the album is like not particularly good in any of the directions.
Like, it's not so horrible.
That funky.
It's not.
Yeah, there's there's good parts, stuff we like.
The comedy is not on a high level.
I'll say that.
I wouldn't say so.
I didn't laugh at the things that are said, but the it's better than the cover.
The cover is the most damning part of it.
It almost like makes you wonder if this is like offensive, what we're going to experience.
And then it wasn't.
I wasn't offended other than that.
I was not.
I was not a fan of some of a little bit of it.
But yes, this is this raunch coming out.
This is coming from Minnie Mouse who needs to clean up her act.
That's true.
Yeah.
Well, no, maybe I secretly like Minnie Raunch.
I'm just talking about Mickey trying to make the white people feel OK.
That's my problem.
Squeaky clean.
Yeah, sure.
But yeah, I don't know.
I mean, worth a trip.
Thank you, listeners, for directing it.
But I will I might have to say burn it to the ground for insurance money and not burn it like a like a CD would be burned.
Yeah, I mean, I would say that's probably the closest I would rescue some of the baselines and maybe the club mix.
I'll rescue that from the fire, but burn most of the rest of it down.
Goofy smoking weed.
This is a real good one.
I've seen this this single still from an animated and he looks a little out of it.
Oh, baby.
Yeah.
Wow.
I saw somebody I saw a picture of somebody who got vaccinated and they were wearing a Donald Duck smoking weed shirt.
Well, so only the only the best.
Well, sure.
You got to relax.
Well, I know no one's worn a pot tannic shirt yet while getting vaccinated.
But I would really maybe I will.
That's a great idea.
If everybody who's getting vaccinated where they're puttanna kush pot tanna kush shirt, excuse me.
Like, what a what a beautiful time capsule that would be.
That's true.
Yeah.
We'll throw that out there.
Pot tanna kush loves loves that loud and he loves those heroes and pot tanna kush.
That's how to push.
Let's get loud.
Can we get a let's get loud shirt with pot tanna kush?
It's here.
Teakley scream.
Let's get loud.
Magdahl.
The flop gloppel.
Yeah.
I'm sure there's a pot we could get pot.
We'll come up with pot characters for all the other Green Planet friends.
Oh, that's yeah.
You should have buddies.
That's true.
Oh, yeah.
Aaron might enjoy that assignment.
The Brodo is Zoggy friends.
That's ET's home planet.
It's REC.
ET's real name.
Teakleaf is pretty good.
Yeah.
That is pretty good.
And it's all yeah all weed leaves exploding out of their head.
Okay.
So here's what I want to you guys will help me workshop how we're going to do this.
I have found something in my archives that I believe the listeners might be interested in hearing, but it is so humiliating to me.
I would prefer that we give a goal of some kind on the Patreon.
Whoa.
I have found a full album of mine that I made.
Excuse me.
Oh, boy.
Oh, my gosh.
I have found a full album of music from when I was 20 years old.
I actually didn't realize I had even full like made this much.
And I remember all of it now.
But I went, oh, my God, you put it all.
Yeah.
And an album.
And these are all songs.
None of them meant to be ironic, all sincere.
Oh, boy.
Really just the dumbest, most sincere, humiliating lyrics.
Wow.
Right after you've been saved.
You know, some of them do.
I was never religious, but some of them do sound vaguely religious if you listen to them.
There was a lot of that in like rock music.
Yeah.
So here's the thing.
This ain't coming cheap is what I'm going to say here.
Yeah.
This has to come at a price for patrons.
We need to get to some astronomically high patron.
That's the way I'm thinking of it is if we can hit a certain amount of patrons or something,
we will unlock my music album from and we will dissect it on this spot on the Patreon.
It has to be.
Well, we get to hear it.
It's not just you bring it out.
No, no, no.
It'll be you guys.
You can humiliate me with it.
Like you can make fun of it.
We can do a full analysis of it on the Patreon.
But I'm this has we have to get so many more patrons.
I don't know what the number is.
Is it five thousand for that?
Maybe it's four thousand.
This has to be like a goal we're working towards for a while because I implore I'm telling you this is so embarrassing.
I don't want to do this.
So you're singing.
You're like and playing everything.
I'm playing.
My friend John at the time is playing guitar and might do a little singing on it.
But most of the songs are mine, my creation, my writing.
And yeah, and it's just like the lyrics.
I can't every cliche you'd ever have ever heard.
It's all Matchbox 20 inspired.
It's all boy.
Oh, boy.
There's one like there's one rock in the song on it that's like I guess we just heard the hives or something.
And we're like, yeah, let's do that.
And there's a bad drum machine on it.
And oh, goodness.
Oh, shit.
Well, you know, I do commend you because I'm not sure I've ever made anything that's intended to be sincere,
which is kind of like a like even in high school, I'm trying to do like it's like my I'm trying to be like a little Austin Powers or something.
I was never willing.
I'm too scared in a way.
I like I I commend you for being fearless at that time to put your heart on the line.
I think it was more stupidity because I was my trajectory as a human being was like, oh, I'm going to like do fun like movie acting stuff.
And we made videos at 14, 15, 16, 17.
And then I started listening to music and I was like, music is serious.
That's what you do when you're writing songs.
Ah, maybe I will write songs as well.
So I started writing songs and I'm like this.
I'm trying to feel something.
I am writing about important things like I don't know anything.
I'm an idiot.
I'm just mimicking Stephen Jenkins or I'm mimicking Adam Derwitt.
I don't know what exactly you felt a feeling since you were 20, not as long as I've known.
It's a very good.
It was a very good chance.
I really in hindsight, I was like, you know, you could have like, you know, you like to be funny and like movies or whatever.
You could have tried to be funny in one of these songs.
Crazy if you if you went back to your album and it was bizarrely like like and you had no idea.
You didn't even remember you blocked it out in the album is just like, yeah, I want to lick that pussy and fuck.
You're like, whoa, Mike loves cheese, likes cheese, but he loves that nut.
I will still I have more seed.
I'm going through CDs.
This is how I found this.
And I will let you know if I say anything about liking that nut in any of those.
I don't think that exists, though.
I'm hoping you find like a bare naked ladies.
They might be giants more like goofball.
Well, I have I do you know what?
In the band I was in, I do have some songs that are slightly comedic, but this is more of my solo work.
This is not necessarily the work of second level, which I guess we could put some of second level stuff on there.
This is more of my work.
That was the band I joined.
It was already in progress.
Yeah.
And our friend Milos quit and then I joined the band as the singer.
So that was your alter bridge.
But your solo stuff is more like Scott Stapp solo.
Yeah, that's true.
But imagine you have Van Halen and David Lee Roth left and then Sammy Hagar joined, which is me.
But then David Lee Roth came back as well.
And we were both David Lee Roth and Sammy were in the band at the same time.
That's what really, really was happening with second level.
Well, what do we you know, one thing is that the second gate could get you might call a second level.
And that's possible.
A reason to go there.
The next tier of the picture is only you get this album.
You get Mike's high school album and that's it.
Well, and maybe my middle school performance.
That was a 2020 project I was going to do.
It's like, OK, I'll get together.
We'll watch the entirety of my middle school play.
We'll cut up what I should what we should put out.
And then a pandemic happened and it took a back seat.
Well, you don't have tapes.
They're probably back at home.
You know, I have it.
You do.
You were sitting on your this is revelatory.
You're sitting on your high school, your middle school plays.
I we talked about this.
I have it.
Yeah, I have a DVD, but we got to cut it up a little because I don't want to put on blast a whole two hour.
Oh, yeah.
All all the cast of thousands like 50 people or whatever those middle school where they just try to shove every kid who wants to do it in.
Right.
Well, you know what?
Let's say that.
Let's just let's let's stop it here because obviously we're going to have to announce this on the main show as far as because everybody is on the Patreon already.
You know, they're in.
So we're teasing this.
This is going to be coming soon.
There's going to be some sort of either a T another tier or a stretch goal to get to these treasures, these childhood treasures.
You want to dig in the archive?
You can find anything.
I'm sure you've got something.
The one that comes to mind and I cannot I don't want to tease this and say that it does not and then find out that it doesn't exist.
But I think that there might be video of me dancing at a nine years old dancing at a Beach Boys concert after a baseball game at Jack Murphy Stadium.
They would like package it like see the full Padres game and then then a Beach Boys concert and the Stamos was there.
I don't remember, but I think my dad may have taken video.
And if not that, then there also may be a video of my Boy Scout troop doing a lip sync to Little Deuce Coop.
You mentioned this before.
Now we're getting now we're getting maybe video of that one, maybe even more likely video of that one.
Okay, so so we'll be announcing soon some kind of tier or stretch goal on the Patreon for all of you to enjoy some humiliation on our behalf.
I don't know exactly what form it'll be in, but it's coming in some form because I was just listening to this and going, oh my God, I believe this exists.
You're going to pay money for our humiliation.
And that's totally that's fine and normal and good.
That's like OnlyFans.
That's how people are making money these days.
That's a good point.
Yes, that's a good point.
Instead of like, yeah, I'm shirtless.
You're paying to hear the sincere like crooning of a 20 year old who's trying to get in touch with any kind of emotion possible.
Let's make this clear.
This is much less dignified than only fans.
That's a good point.
It's good.
You know, people can make money.
God speed.
God bless.
Yes, you're right.
It's much crappier.
No one would take the Boy Scout troop performing Little Deuce Coop is not a cool path to go to.
But but paying for I mean, like staying tuned to the picture and telling your friends to do so to see this and to hear all these things.
That's great.
The the embarrassment here.
That's right.
The embarrassment here.
Yeah.
It sounds good to me.
I got no problem with it.
And then appropriate to bring up in an album that I think is mildly embarrassing for the voice actors, for the characters.
So every one of you for Whoopi Goldberg potentially, it's a lot of embarrassment.
She gets out OK.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I think so.
And and we're getting out OK.
You survived podcast through the second gate.
Stay tuned here, obviously, obviously, because you're going to get there's some very good content deep, deep in the archives that will be coming your way soon.
And we'll figure.
Yeah, we'll figure out how to how to get people to what what what will make it worth.
I don't know.
We're at like we're getting close to twenty five hundred, which is very exciting.
That's great.
Do you is it is twenty five thousand.
OK.
All right.
So so all your friends and enemies get as many people as you can do subscribe and hear Mike's record.
But for now, yeah.
Peace to your posse.