Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast contains Telethon Joker, Zips, Bangs and Pows, and gushing Batman
Forever praise.
Podcasters by nature are a cowardly and superstitious lot.
It's Batman the Rides on today's podcast, The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride where we say, hold me, thrill me, kiss me, thrill me again
on a themed experience, please.
My name is Mike Carlson.
Joining me as always, Jason Sheridan.
I can't get it out of my head.
I can't get the song out of my head.
I watched the music video shortly before we were recording and my jaw dropped.
Yes, Jason put this in my head.
No one had a really catchy thing to say.
So I just had this wonderful Batman song from Batman Forever in my head.
Scott Gardner is here as well.
Yeah, I think we're going to have more fun than a kiss from a rose on the gray.
When you get more fun than when you get kissed on the gray.
And don't forget that that's what's being said.
People don't believe it when you tell them the gray.
It is the gray.
Do we know what he means?
What seal meant by the gray?
Don't think we do.
Do we not?
Like just the gray of the of your life of the night of smoke and an ash and a rose is
colorful so it like kisses its way through and creates joy.
That's very beautiful by the way what you just said.
It might be more thought than was put into the song.
I don't want to give seal little credit or no credit.
Maybe he has the same sort of thought.
But we're talking Batman in the theme parks today.
All theme parks.
A very wide topic.
Yeah.
There's a lot.
Am I correct that the episode is going to be called Batman the rides plural?
Pluralized.
Oh, that's good.
I had not considered that.
That's what's been in my head.
Batman the ride, which you might look at first glance and think that we are talking about
the roller coaster that's been at Six Flags since the 90s.
That's a stalwart of Six Flags.
And certainly we will talk about that.
However, it's more it's rides.
There are a lot of Batman rides out there.
But do any of them really scratch the itch?
That is the question.
And I think that's what we're going to try to get into today.
And let's be clear, just everyone's screaming at their pod catching device.
Batman the ride is different from Batman Adventure dash the ride and Batman Adventure dash the
ride to the right.
And not all of the Batman the rides are the same ride.
There are things called Batman the ride that are a completely different type of roller
coaster.
But we'll get to that too.
We know that Batman the ride encompasses different things.
Of course.
Yes.
There are like there are villains represented with their own rides in the Batman universe.
This is very rare to have like an IP like this to have so many different things in different
parts of the world and different types of parks.
Different characters have their own rides.
I mean, obviously it happens in Disney, but that's Disneyland.
It's not Batman land.
You know, it's not a specific Batman land.
That would make sense there.
But there are so much.
Completely different eras of Batman are represented.
There's like this is clearly Nolan.
This is clearly Burton.
This is clearly nothing.
This is just like Batman generic.
This is like could be any Batman.
And then there's ones that aren't covered whatsoever.
It's a big messy array.
Yeah.
The dream of Batman forever is alive at Magic Mountain in California.
There's so much Batman forever.
I think we said this on that episode with Anthony Geo.
The font of Batman forever is everywhere.
And I hope it lasts forever because that font, I have such nostalgia for it.
But the Riddler's Revenge coaster that's there is obviously Batman forever with the those
like blender type things that Nigma puts on people's heads to steal their thoughts.
You know, so it's so interesting.
So it's such a mishmash.
It's just sort of by like grace of like whenever something was built, it's now stuck in that
era of Batman forever and Batman forever.
Not the movie Batman forever.
Batman in all of eternity is what I'm saying.
There's another one too, which is that there's Batman night flight, which is too different.
Too completely different.
There's one that's in a Six Flags and one that's in Dubai that's like an immersive Harry
Potter type ride.
And the other Batman night flight is just a coaster.
There's so much confusion.
You're going to need a chart for this one.
And you know what?
I think that's all beautiful.
I think the chaos of that adds to the character of Batman in the parks.
And even I think it's more necessity is the mother of invention.
I believe the current DC Comics thinking is because Warner Brothers seems to really want
to desperately stop publishing comic books.
It seems like the current line of thinking, you know, there's a lot of crises to try and
justify like decades and decades of comic book.
Like, well, how did he do this?
If he did that, the current line of thinking seems to be it all happened.
It all counts.
Don't worry about it.
And that's kind of what Batman in the parks is like too.
Yes.
Yeah.
All the areas existed.
There are artifacts now in the real world of all these eras of Batman or Batman, Batman,
whatever.
And yeah, they're all part of canon.
They're all part of theme park canon, which of course is our most important canon on this
show.
Yeah, absolutely.
Which makes it if you are like viewing this in a galaxy's edge fashion, where if we're
holding things to the standard of there's a consistent story, like how do I write?
What how does the Batman theme park canon work?
It makes no sense.
It just does it.
It doesn't work because you're not so many of them are just like, wow, I'm in the Riddler's
lair.
And then I go on a roller coaster after that.
There's not a lot of consistent storytelling.
The Riddler's revenge is to send me and have a good time.
The Riddler's revenge is me enjoying myself.
That's what his revenge is.
I get to have a fun time where wind blows in my face and I go at a high speed.
Yeah, it doesn't it doesn't really make sense.
You know, the history of any of these characters that have been around for a long time don't
make sense in general.
Batman I think is very flexible, probably the most flexible character in the sense that
he can be dumb, stupid, he can be fascist Frank Miller Batman, he can be Adam West Batman,
and it all works.
So it really it does.
It makes sense that the properties are like the Batman properties are like this, where
there's just no logic really when you look at the whole thing as a whole, you know, 80
or whatever, how long 40 years of Batman rides, whatever it is.
I guess you're going back.
Are you starting from 92 in your mind?
Yeah, I guess that's all right.
I guess I can't do math.
I guess that's more like 30 years.
Yeah, still quite a while.
Let me throw down this this blanket statement.
Why I think, you know, we've certainly talked about all this over the years leading up to
this episode.
But this is I was trying to encapsulate what is my thinking and what I think how do I think
I explain the like the disappointment maybe of where Batman lies in theme park world and
tell me if you agree or disagree with this statement.
I think that Batman is the biggest American pop culture property that doesn't have a huge,
immersive, technically innovative ride in America and ticket type ride.
Now I'm overlooking some of the international stuff by saying this and international properties
and IP.
But can you think of anything that, you know, tops Batman in terms of like pop culture,
the reverence we have for it and that it isn't represented in like an Indiana Jones
adventure rise the resistance kind of way?
No, I mean, he's like the most popular superhero, I think still.
I don't know.
Maybe maybe it's slightly different these days.
But I think we're already talking about like having three Batman movies a year, different
Batman.
Like we're going to have so many versions of Batman now going at the same time.
We'll have Michael Keaton, Batman, maybe Zack Snyder, Affleck, Batman, the Robert Pattinson
Batman Lego Lego Lego Batman's going on.
And then there's the animated movies they've been making like TV shows which go in and
out.
There's one right now.
I don't even know.
There's probably like four animated ones.
We don't even know if you go to HBO Max and type in Batman, you are good for a month.
You are just set of every level of quality, every level of of era of.
Yeah, whatever you want is there, including like meet Scooby Doo or meet the Ninja Turtles.
This is one of those, I believe he met the Ninja Turtles.
Yeah, there's a rumor that the animated series is going to come back soon.
They're going to just do that again.
Wow. I don't know if that's true or not.
Yes, he's so popular.
The character has lasted forever.
And it was what I was saying.
He's like very flexible.
You know, you can put him in a lot of different tones and it works.
And yet to not have like a Spider-Man Islands of Adventure style attraction for him is crazy.
Yeah, it's really crazy if you think about it.
I mean, it makes Superman two should have something like that.
But Batman is, you know, more popular than Superman because we like a sexy billionaire
versus like a humble farm boy who just wants to help.
You know, we are all we all have like we like our Tony Stark's and our Bruce Wayne's.
We like our Elon Musk's in this country.
We don't like humble newspaper man who's just trying to do his best and live a nice life.
We like Jim Acosta.
Is that what you mean?
We need more Jim Acosta worship and less Elon Musk worship in this country.
That's what I'm saying.
Can I also I don't want to sidetrack too much, but I was just trying to go is this is what I'm saying
literally true that there is not a property bigger than Batman without a theme park presence.
And I did I looked at like a Wikipedia of the most successful franchise.
There is one. Can we think of and it's and this is apparently the biggest.
This is bigger than anything. Disney is bigger than Mario.
There is something that is that it does not have a permanent theme park presence.
Do you have any James James Bond?
James Bond? No, that's a good one, though.
There is not really is that there's very little James Bond in the little stuff.
What I'm thinking at like teen Asian, I'll tell you.
Huh? Is it like Tintin?
No, no. From another country or
a land before land before time to the Beethoven.
Beethoven's third Sandlot.
Anything? Oh, the air buddies, the air bud movies.
Well, there should be. Those are like 10 of those.
Really be air buddies attractions.
Is it SpongeBob?
No, and even that would care.
There is that right. There is some presence. Yeah.
Pokemon is what we are. Oh, of course.
Pokemon is bigger in terms of profits than like anything else.
And there is not a committed.
There was apparently some traveling theme park called Poke Park for a while.
But there has never been like a like this is the committed,
which that seems kind of crazy.
And you wonder if that'll work its way into Universal and Nintendo.
Yeah, that's got to be on the plan.
That's got to be in the next because they're doing Donkey Kong in Phase
two and in Japan.
So I had imagined that Pokemon is coming next or fourth.
Who knows? Gotta be. Yeah, it has to be soon. Yeah.
Maybe Lord of the Rings close also.
That's the only other possible competitor.
But I don't I still don't feel like.
And again, there are Batman rides, of course.
But you know what I'm saying? There isn't. Yes. Yes.
Here it is. The Batman ride.
Lord of the Rings is still mega popular, and this is only anecdotal.
But it's like my mom likes Batman stuff.
And it's like Lord of the Rings is like, oh, she knows what it is.
But it's like I feel like Batman's a little bit more universal in the sense
there's at least one version of Batman you were having.
You had a lot of affection for it a certain part in your life
versus Lord of the Rings, which has had the movies.
But that's only in the last.
I can't do math. 25 years, 50 years.
The first one to come out in 1998, 50 years ago.
It's like entirely about those movies and Peter Jackson, as opposed to like
that there's like you are there.
What are there five eras of Batman just in movies that people are
very passionate about all of them?
Yeah. And then say on the 60s show for people that were young
and old at that time was a big deal and people loved it.
And that still looms large and is still, you know, the best show ever made.
Still. Well, yeah, it's fantastic.
So, yeah, I think that it has to be that just from just from the fact that like
everyone in America has to have like, well, yeah, I liked Batman Returns.
I saw that. That was good.
Yeah. Versus I don't think Lord of the Rings is quite there,
but it's something that is just completely out on it as opposed to.
But as I said, there are of course there are Batman attraction.
Does anybody have a more accurate count than I have?
I counted 22 separate
Batman related ride premises and then an additional two
based on the Justice League.
But I could be wrong. I might be missing a bunch, but there's at least.
So if we're counting Justice League 24.
Yeah, that's like the count, I think, on the Wikipedia
of it, because the Wikipedia lists all the rides.
I'm sure there's little shows and things that they're not counting. Yeah.
Because they do have stunt shows,
but then they don't have like the street misfit or show.
They do it. The Dubai world.
On this list, that's not tracked by Wikipedia.
The Dubai street.
For some reason, the show where the Joker picks someone out of the audience
in Dubai and goofs on him is not on this list.
Oh, I'm excited to learn.
So there's stuff. Yeah, there's stuff not here.
Yeah. So that's about right.
But I'm sure there's an actually very specific number.
Yeah. That somebody is mad at us now because they knew it already.
Well, it fluctuates so much because some of these are closed.
I've got some that are like, and these all closed or these all closed in this year.
There's one.
There's a coaster that I myself experienced that did not last super long,
unlike the original Batman, the ride,
which that I will say at its time.
I let's maybe we should just get into this.
Is this the first one?
Batman, the ride notable for a number of reasons.
First, open that Magic Mountain in 1992, then Great Adventure in 1993,
and then just down the list of Six Flags parks.
They put it everywhere seemingly.
The first notable for being the first inverted roller coaster.
The first your little little footsies are dangling off the coaster.
The track is above you.
This is different from a suspended coaster, like, say, the big bad wolf
in Busch Gardens, where the there's a car.
You're in a car that's dangling below the track.
But this right BNM coaster developed with Six Flags
was that technically was a technological innovation
at its time and had a big property.
You know, it's 1992.
It's a few years after the first in Burton Batman.
It's the same summer
that Batman returns opens.
That was also 92, I believe.
Can I can I correct you and say that I think I believe Great America
was the first one.
What did I say?
Adventure is second. Great Amer.
Wait, it did.
We went Great America, Great Adventure, Magic Mountain, evidently.
And Great America is was Mike's.
Oh, you're right.
I can never. Sorry.
Great America and Great Adventure.
This is another one of these thin parses of a theme park name
that I can never remember.
But that's but that's yours, though.
Yeah, Great America was mine.
I remember this commercial coming on TV and like Batman, the ride.
Yeah, I was very excited at first.
And then I saw a dangling legs coaster.
And I was like, I'll never ride that.
I never never go on this.
And I'll be very honest with the audience.
I still have not been on a Batman ride.
I've been on a Batman ride coaster,
but I've not been on the Batman, the ride ever in my life.
Wow. I am.
I will. I would do it now.
But as we've said before, I don't like dangling legs.
It scares me. Sure.
It just feels it feels unsecure.
I feel like my leg is going to get caught on something.
You know, well, this is one of the rides that has killed somebody.
Somebody did die not on the ride, but like it was.
This was the one where somebody snuck into an area they weren't supposed to be in.
And then a train went by, which led to the thing where the Six Flags
CEO or whatever is saying this very gravely in front of a dancing octopus.
So there is a danger to it.
So you're you're trying to scare me further.
I guess so. Going on it.
You're going to hurt some kid at this point.
I remember this is a time.
How old am I? I can math here.
I was 31 when this came out.
No, I was eight, I guess.
Yeah, I was eight when this started.
I had not seen the first two Batman Michael Keaton movies
because my mom thought they were too scary for me.
And she I guess she just she went to see Batman Returns.
I remember with her friend and came back and was like, you can't see that.
She didn't say it's because the penguin is too horny.
And I will not allow you to watch that.
But I bet that was part of she might not remember.
That's why. But if you watch the movie now, you go,
the penguin is too horny for a young child to watch.
Like they do not need to see this man do this.
I'd be more I just wouldn't let a kid watch it almost more out of the
the various Biles and.
Yeah, the black blood is scared me.
I never saw any of these in theaters until Batman Begins.
I don't think I saw really you didn't see the other.
Whoa. But I had all the toys.
Yeah. At least Batman Returns.
I don't think I maybe I had a little from Batman forever.
I that's interesting.
I saw I saw a clip.
I remember we were walking in a mall in like 1990 or 91
and some some store was playing a clip of Batman, the 89 Michael Keaton,
Jack Nicholson version.
And it's the scene where jokers put the makeup over his white face.
Oh, I like he has skin tone.
And then she throws the water at him and he pretends that like acid is burning him.
And then he like takes his hands away and he like scares her
because it's like half white, half skin tone.
I got so scared from just like standing with my like
hands on the glass of like a video store.
And I remember like running away from the store.
I was so afraid of Jack Nicholson and that thing.
And I remember going, yes, my mother is correct.
This is not a movie I should be watching.
I am not ready to handle this.
So I was not ready for the bride.
I was not ready for those movies.
I think it was the fact that I was young and scared
and that my brother was three years younger than me.
So even more young and scared.
So the first two Tim Burton movie, Tim Burton, Batman movies off the table.
Yes.
Batman, I don't know why we didn't see Batman forever in Batman and Robin.
I swear I did not see those in theaters.
For whatever reason, my middle school got a hold of a copy of Batman
and Robin on VHS and teachers would put it on on fun days.
And I was very into Batman at the time, but I was very serious Batman.
And I thought Batman and Robin was very ridiculous.
You were mad at it.
I was mad at it.
Yeah, I didn't really remember much of clips from Batman forever,
but I rewatched it a couple of days ago and I was just the mind boggles.
That movie is really something I see.
I had a great time.
This is what we were trying to avoid when we started doing this episode.
We put a stopwatch on it.
You're going to really have to because right now, Jason's I'm itching.
I'm itching to talk about the movies.
I just want to talk.
I think the biggest thing was the Chase Meridian, the hoardiest
character in fiction.
Well, for the first half of the movie.
And then they remember they made her a psychiatrist and they're like,
oh, we should have her do some psychiatry, make her go like,
your dreams, your dreams are telling me something, Bruce.
Like I saw Batman forever and loved it.
We saw it. I loved it.
I was obsessed with it.
And this is going to this is too personal and I will keep this as clean as I can.
I the one of the first memories I have of like
any sort of feeling amorous was watching this movie.
I'm you've said this, but I'm very confident.
If you haven't said it before on the show, you've said it to us in person
upwards every time we've ever been together. Yeah. Yeah.
Did you guys know that when I saw Batman forever, I sort of felt like an
like, you know, those urges you do when you're in your like formative years.
But why did you call me at two in the morning to say that?
Oh, I just thought I hadn't told you about it yet.
I just thought I just thought you should know.
You've never called me before for any reason.
Yeah, no, but I just I just kind of came across my mind
in the middle of the night and I felt like,
yeah, no, but the whole movie, everything about it,
Jim Carrey was the hottest actor at the time.
I thought he was the funniest guy.
I had just seen The Fugitive, I think, on video cassette.
I like Tommy Lee Jones.
Oh, Jim Carrey, every element of his game, like at the top.
Yes. Height of his like success.
And and let's not forget the McDonald's glasses, the cups,
the glasses that were like I still have.
We still have them at my parents' house.
It's like two face carved into glass is coins or the handle.
Some of the finest glassware I've ever seen.
They've lasted the test of time alone.
Oh, I can't even I can't say enough about those glasses.
OK, but back to Batman, the ride back to the bird.
If we have to, because Batman, the ride is so Tim Burton, Batman.
And, you know, the coaster was, as I said, the first inverted roller coaster.
And it also I have to give it a lot of credit because I think Batman, the ride
and its surrounding like Q and stuff is a great demonstration of like a lit.
If you if you don't have a lot of money or I mean,
I guess they had a good amount of money.
But if you don't have Disney or Universal level budgets for theme parks,
Batman forever, you if you Batman, the ride.
Sorry, you got better.
Forever is on the. Oh, God.
It's like Nigma put his machine right on.
Oh, my God.
Too hard. The pull of the movie is too great.
The theming for six weeks, the theming of Batman, the ride is pretty good.
There's a beat up cop car.
There's like pipes.
There's it's very industrial.
That probably helps that you can buy pipes and concrete very surely.
Beat up cop cars.
The news that was those big statues in the front statues.
And like you enter through like a base chemical plant kind of.
There's a there's a Batman suit in some of them.
And I the Gotham City music.
I mean, it probably helps to have Danny Elfman music and
Prince music at your disposal.
That probably helps your scene.
Do they still or is that still what you're hearing today?
If you go there or do they now just plan like rock from eight years ago?
Like what have they kept up?
The theming is mostly playing the greatest hits of the fray
in there or a vertical horizon.
Yeah, some 41.
Yeah. Fat lip by some 41 on a loop.
Dan and Dan down, Dan and I'm down.
I actually don't know that. That's a good question.
I would hope that they are still doing that because that at least
music is so important and soundtrack is so important.
I think we were talking about in our Jurassic Quest Patreon,
just having a soundtrack can do 50 percent,
25 percent of the work of a themed experience.
Yeah. I would hope at least that great Danny Elfman Batman theme
is in there, if not Party Man or Bat Dance, which is
we should talk about at length at a certain point, too.
I remember when I went a few times in the span of a few years in high school,
I just remember that song like in Gotham City, like kind of like a ballad
song about. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Are you talking about the R. Kelly song?
No. Yeah. Oh, yes, you are.
I think you are, my friend.
My friend, you're talking about artists.
I didn't know there was an art.
You are talking about the Batman and Robin song.
It's from that movie.
And it's R. Kelly and they were you're if you want me to do a chorus,
it's City of Justice, City of Love,
City of People, Home to Everyone.
Oh, my God. I forgot.
We all need it.
Can't live without it.
Gotham City.
Oh, yeah.
Well, that's what they're playing in 2001.
Well, that's not as good.
Turned yet. Yeah. Yeah.
That's not quite as good.
That song makes no sense.
That's not what Gotham City is like.
It does not reflect.
It's almost as if he didn't learn anything about what Gotham City is like
to make the song Gotham City.
I think that that's a strong possibility.
Yes. That song makes no, absolutely no sense.
But they were they were going to try to get a big hit, I think.
I don't know if it was a mild hit. I'm not sure.
I don't I get cannabis.
They like pushed it to where we thought it was a hit.
There was a similar bad one for Ali called The World's Greatest.
It was like a ballad about being a boxer.
These were not this is why like, all right, guess what?
You can't listen to R. Kelly anymore.
Sounds good to me.
Yeah, I'm not going to miss the world's greatest.
That no problem.
Yeah, yeah.
But I mean, nothing can touch Kiss from a Rose
as far as like a big Batman ballad.
Even I even I like Hold Me Thrilled Me, Kiss Me, Kill Me a Lot,
which I referenced earlier.
But now that was not a hit like Kiss from a Rose.
That is not culturally lasted.
I think the DNA of the Spider-Man musical you could hear in
Hold Me Thrilled Me, Kiss Me, Kill Me. Oh, I've I've yes.
I think I've brought up that on this podcast before that.
Yeah, yeah. They've yeah.
I think that's probably other than a freak like me, the best,
a better song than most of the Spider-Man soundtrack, honestly.
But that's it. We can't talk about the star.
The highest part is the compliment I can give.
It's a song.
It's better than the Spider-Man turn off the dark soundtrack.
It is better than you're welcome for that compliment.
Yeah. So the other thing that sticks out,
some other stuff that sticks out in my mind about Batman, the ride.
I'm going to show you guys an image.
This image, they got so much marketing material out of this loop.
I remember as a still image and as footage.
Six Flags used this for years and years in at least
in great adventure advertising, I think in everywhere advertising.
Right. It is very familiar.
I think it's a more confident choice than this marketing
they were going with at the time.
Six Flags Great Adventure, bigger than Disneyland and closer to home.
There's an yeah, there's an ad I saw where they go,
hey, Disneyland is great, but hey, you can't always go there.
So it's a whole thing.
It's a whole thing.
And that that ad, they have to put fine print on that Astroworld is not bigger
except Astroworld at the bottom of the screen.
Literally undercuts it.
It does undercut it.
And then like it's always closer.
They say it's like closer to home to and they like show the map
where all the six flags are.
And I'm like looking and I'm like there's several states where
there's not a very close one, not a very just because there's
like 10 of them and not two.
And the other thing they bury the lead on,
if you look at this operating character, you'll notice
operating calendar is closed
for six months of the year.
Six Flags Great Adventure and I see that.
Yeah. All of March, all of March.
You could not go there during that time and buy this shirt of Batman perched.
Oh, man.
Oh, I love that.
That's probably worth a hundred.
I don't know. This is a side note.
But do you know these old Batman, like comic shirts are worth hundreds of dollars now?
This, I think, is 50 or 70.
That's not bad.
Vintage comic book shirts now from like our childhood that are worth like 800.
Like a full Magneto face T-shirt is worth like two grand.
If it's in decent shape, it's crazy.
Great Velcro wallet here for Batman.
Hey, did we all have Velcro wallets as kids?
Multiple. Yeah.
Yeah, I think so.
Maybe even with it might have even had a Mickey Mouse one.
If you can believe it.
I had a baseball one, believe it or not.
I know that's a character baseball.
It was like blue and I like just a baseball on it.
Wow. It's the idea of baseball.
It's so funny because it's kids carrying wallets is just like you're pretending.
It's like you have a five dollar bill in there and that's it.
Yeah. What do we put in them?
A photo of Dr. Chase Meridian.
Well, I had a full fold out wallet like, yeah, your kids in there and it was just
Chase meeting Batman on the rooftop.
Chase meeting Batman on the street.
They're centerfold, but fully clothed.
Right. Chase from the promo shots that were in the soundtrack I owned.
I bought a Nickelodeon Velcro wallet at King's Dominion
and then proceeded to place the dollar I had left
into the wallet because I had spent the rest of my money on the wallet.
And so that's something.
And then when I started to get into like eight, I think when I turned eighth grade,
I was like, I need a different wallet and got like a surf company,
like just a blue canvas like Velcro wallet.
That sounds like that's the choice you made at that time for us in the late 90s.
Yeah. Well, how do I dress cool?
These people are wearing a shirt with like a wave on it.
Great. Am I cool now? No. Yeah, great.
But yeah, I, you know, I don't mean to undercut
Batman the ride with what I was saying.
I'm just thinking, you know, for the stuff that we salivate over,
which is like robots and technological innovation, it does not have that.
It does have technological innovation in that it's the first inverted coaster.
I don't know. It's like a good it's a it's a real good start.
You got good ads out of it. There's mood.
It is like let's take the Burton vibe and put it in a physical
place. You got the just the the logo, just just putting that logo
and putting it into stone goes a long way.
It's still one of the great logos.
Wordless, you like get kind of a chilling feeling from it
without any further explanation.
So they I don't know, they they they like squeezed a lot
out of that fruit, I feel like with this ride. Yeah.
It just yeah, it just you never quite got
the feeling.
And I'm especially like Spider-Man or of, yeah, as you're saying,
Indiana Jones, where you were like transformed post ride,
you know, where you're like, oh, now I've now I've been on an adventure
with the character in a way that felt way different.
Yeah. From anything I had been on before.
And there's attempts just clear getting closer lately, but still not there yet.
Quite. Yes. Yeah.
Now, there was a thing at the time that I think got like that
I didn't know about that is like a little like, OK, that's getting there.
That's almost like Star Tours, but for Batman,
as Jason mentioned earlier, Batman Adventure the Ride.
But the audience probably doesn't know about this because this was in Germany
and Australia.
So it was difficult to go on this thing.
But this was essentially if there was Star Tours, but for Batman Returns.
Yes. And this is closer, I feel like, than the new Dubai version of this.
I think so.
If you watch that video, which still looks fun, but it's a similar ride.
But I think that other one seemed like it got closer
because I think you got, and I'll say it, a little bit more intimacy
with the characters.
Yeah. Not with Chase Meridian, but with other.
No, not with the other characters.
Yes, exactly.
I mean, Batman, Batman Adventure, the ride has a lot going for it.
You enter through a secret passage in the library. Good.
The team members, the employees dress like little Alfred
helpers with waistcoats and bow ties.
That's good. Yes, very good.
One iteration of it had an animatronic Batman.
Not a lot of movement, but sitting at the back computer
right in front of you. Good.
Yeah, that's good. Yes, like that.
That's what's still very rare, I feel. Yeah.
Yeah, it's it's and I think I was saying this.
I know people are I saw people were mad at us
and he told me to rise to the resistance.
But the stuff on Rise to the Resistance,
the Rise to the Resistance, I like the best is when your character,
you see them, they're interacting with you.
And I think that's the I think that's sometimes what
maybe the people designing they want to go with thrills
and even like feeling of scope over moments like that.
Because I think what Spider-Man did in such a perfect way
is combine all of it.
The characters are so big, they're on the hood of your vehicle.
So you leave that ride going like Doc Ock was in my face.
He was in my face for a moment of time.
I know that character already.
That was either cool or scary, interesting, whatever.
And then Spider-Man as well.
So like it feels like you were next to them
while it was happening versus some of this Batman stuff where it's like
Batman's in the bad plane and he's like maybe five thousand feet away from me.
And I'm squinting a little bit.
I'm sure it was better when you were actually on the ride.
But it's like that's that's the thing that's missing.
And it doesn't even have to be robots.
It would be preferable to be robots.
But it's like I think that's sort of the human element of it
to me is actually what you want.
And I almost feel like some of these
there's like a Joker maze in one of these in the Dubai Park.
It's like stuff like that almost ends up maybe being more memorable
than some of these like simulator rides that they've done.
Yeah, here's here's what I think is maybe getting in the way of
the great Batman ride is the casting.
The eras have changed so much.
Almost nobody has been in more than two or three Batman movies.
So like who is Batman?
Who is the Joker?
It changes all the time.
And often they're the biggest stars in the world.
And in the 90s, it was tougher to get the biggest stars in the world
to be in your rides.
However, the Indiana Jones adventure
is an extremely successful Indiana Jones ride
that does not have Harrison Ford.
So it's it's possible you can do.
And I think like a Batman figure that reminds you of Michael Keaton
or Val Kilmer to a much lesser extent, George Clooney would still like
it's why the one that even doesn't even do anything in the simulator.
I'm like, OK, closer.
That's it's almost there.
But I think it makes the casting thing gets in the way of the intimacy
that you're looking for, like who is going to do it, who will agree to do it?
Well, I mean, they have the longest running Batman is a guy named
Kevin Conroy, who's been doing the voice in a lot of different media
since animated series.
His voice is on the Justice League ride.
He did the Arkham City and Arkham Asylum games.
So they have him.
But as far as look wise, he has now done the character
in different media with different looks.
So he looks like the fun Bruce Tim, like noir, old time, cool animated style.
But he's also looks like that, like everyone's just dripping
with steroid Arkham Asylum video game aesthetic
where everyone's just fucking jacked and mad.
And it's cool. It's a cool look, too.
So it's like there's like I guess they're
yeah, they're like probably in a tough spot because it's like, well,
what do we even do right now?
People probably know, even though Ben Affleck's been Batman more recently,
people probably know the Christian Bale stuff the best right now.
That's probably the freshest in people's mind, because
some people don't love Batman versus Superman.
Some people, it's their religion, in case you didn't know.
Yes, yeah. I'm scared of it all.
I saw the one movie three hours and four.
No, no, Batman versus Superman.
Oh, I see. Extended cut that's on HBO Max.
Yes, yes. Is like three hours or two and a half hours.
It was like, oh, that's long.
And then Justice League is four hours.
And I'm like, I don't know. I liked Aquaman.
I thought Aquaman was fun.
I don't really. I haven't seen most of these other movies.
I'm tapping out.
I've been I've been trying to spend less time on the Internet
and meditate more, and it's been much.
I'm happier. I'm less depressed.
It's nice.
But because you mentioned Kevin Conroy,
Kevin. OK, that's the name, right?
Kevin Conroy, Kevin Conroy. Yeah.
It sounds like it's him in the second version of the Batman adventure.
Because I think, yeah, I think it is.
I think that's right.
So the Batman adventure motion simulator ride.
The first version is like a live action in the Tim Burton verse.
And on the sets and you can tell like they're at Warner Brothers.
Like when the movie cleared out of shooting,
like it's like the Penguin rubber duck and all that stuff.
Like you so feel it.
I was like surprised how much this stuff seemed cool
and that I had didn't know about it before.
So, yeah, like this is neat. Pretty good.
And I at first I thought we were going to clown on it
because the opening of it is slowly driving through a lot of crowd scenes,
then quickly driving through an alleyway.
And then it opens up to like crazy action sequences.
Right. Where does it go?
I don't I so remember that you're on the streets of Gotham,
and it's so cool to see Burton Gotham and that they just moved a camera around.
But what's the second half? I actually don't remember.
They the Penguin rubber duckie vehicle flies.
You start flying and chasing it.
And then I believe you chase him into his lair and like stuff blows up.
I think the Penguins are shooting the rockets at you.
There is footage where a sound alike is speaking in German,
like doing the Danny DeVito Penguin voice in German is just it's great.
It's it's delightful. Cool.
Yeah, that's very cool.
I watched Batman, Batman Returns not long ago.
And just the whole aesthetic, it's so Burton.
It's so much like Burton.
I was ever watched this recently.
Yes, I did. Not to sort of issue that opening.
I mean, yeah, everything aesthetically, those ducks,
everything like lends themselves to like such a cool like theme park world in that movie.
I mean, a lot of the Batman movies, but the first four, I would say,
not not as much the Nolan, even though they've done stuff in Dubai that's Nolan inspired.
Well, so much of Nolan is in like Chicago or in Pittsburgh,
as opposed to the stylized shot on the lot shot in a giant sound stage,
which is like lends itself to theme park more easily than a real city.
Yes, I remember this is how stupid I was.
I remember being like Batman Begins and I like Batman Begins and I still do.
But I remember being like, yeah, this is the way it's done.
It's not the old way. That's stupid.
And then a couple of years later, I was like, what was wrong with you?
Yeah, like a fun nonsense is better than as good as as Jason said.
Like Batman Forever is the sweet spot.
Batman and Robin, it is kind of the definition of jumping the shark.
I would love I will gladly watch it tonight.
I love watching Batman and Robin.
But I remember how even at the time, like you like Jason was saying,
you know, it's got to be grittier.
Even I felt that way even as a kid didn't like
the I think kids were not tricked by it.
There's something no, I didn't quite work.
I agree. I mean, I was we made fun of it, I think, immediately after seeing it.
Like we knew it didn't work.
We couldn't articulate why.
But I do maintain that you take all the sets and the actors
and you just make a better script and direct it differently.
And it's closer to a 60s.
They thought they were making 60s Batman and 60s Batman.
I think somewhat there's a misconception that that was like
an earnest attempt at or like a sincere attempt at a superhero
versus a subversive, funny, tongue in cheek.
It's like, you know, like satirical almost.
Right. Yeah.
It's funny on purpose before naked gun.
Yeah, it's funny on purpose.
But I still think people think, oh, that was the cheesy one.
And that was like, but it was like they knew what they were doing.
And it's funny.
I think they thought Batman and Robin was that.
Yeah. Well, I think.
I think Batman forever does a better job like Batman.
Oh, sure.
Mary Lee, the Tim Burton
aesthetic and the 60s
Batman vibe and adds a lot of camp.
Oh, yeah.
And there's a well, I think we tried this before.
There's supposedly a three hour cut somewhere, a shoe market
out of Batman forever, which I want to see.
That's the cut I want to see even more than the Snyder cut.
But what Jason's saying, if the R.A.
said in a sprinkle of camp, and that's what helped forever be good.
Batman and Robin is like your little like container of camp.
The lid came off and like the entire container of camp.
Yeah. As if like a whole thing of cinnamon just like
plopped into your whatever dish you're making.
Like it's kind of like if Batman forever is you were out all night
partying and having a great time.
Batman and Robin is like when the sun is coming up
and you catch a look at yourself in the mirror and you're like, oh no.
Oh, dear. Sleep.
I completely agree with what you're saying.
I'm just saying that I think in hindsight with Batman and Robin,
they watch the 60s show and they go, OK, got it.
It's full of puns.
Yeah. And they're all winking at the camera and they're not like
Adam West is playing it as dry and straight as possible,
including doing that whole performance, like kind of winking at the camera
the whole time.
The script isn't funny.
It's full of bad Arnold Schwarzenegger puns.
Like I'm just saying, I think aesthetically,
there's it's not such a disaster if they had made some tweaks to it.
Oh, yeah, I would agree with this.
Costumes are cool. Like the costumes are cool.
The sets are cool.
Like all that stuff is fine.
I can't just end, though, the you know, this is well tried and territory,
but the nipples and the and the penises is so in the nipples and the penis.
It is insane with your action figures and your intimacy.
Yeah, you know, I the nipples are crazy.
The nipples are crazy.
They didn't just do it.
And like, if you notice it, you notice it.
It's like punch in on nipple close up of rubber nipple.
It is pretty crazy.
One of the craziest things ever to be done in like a 200 million dollar movie.
It's like, like at Batman suiting up and making sure to take
an extended shot of ass.
Just punch in on his butt.
Yeah, there is. But
there is a figure, there's these figures called hot toys
that I've brought up before that are what that's unfortunate timing.
Unfortunate.
The Adam West that I have that Batman is a hot toy.
And it's like a very articulated doll.
And they're making Jason has seen this.
They're making Batman forever once.
And Scott, I don't know, did I send this to you?
I don't think I did.
They're making Batman three in the morning several times over the last six months.
Oh, man, I must have blacked out and done that.
They're making Batman forever once.
And I will say, I'll show you the picture of Chris O'Donnell's Robin.
Oh, boy. Here we go.
Here, let me show you the hottest hot toy that ever was.
Yeah, it is.
He's pretty cute.
My killing time pretending he doesn't have it bookmarked.
This looks got here. You see this?
Wow. Oh, my God.
That is the bulgiest.
Why are you?
You should be offended by this, Mike, by your your typical demeanor.
I am offended by it.
It's so I don't know why it's like this.
I don't know why he has such a big bulge because it wasn't.
Yeah, you see, like it's like shadowed.
There's a far away picture of the toy here and it's got the shadow.
So that's good to be bad.
You would be able to see this toy's giant dick like from 100 feet away.
It's like he has two extra penises in there.
He jammed a couple more in that is and nipples.
There's nipples on these.
There weren't nipples. Oh, yeah.
And forever. This was this is crossing.
I don't know. Wait a minute.
Wait a minute. But it was such an uproar in Batman and Robin.
Well, in the first half of the movie, he wears the Burton suit
pretty much with the yellow and then that gets destroyed.
And they're like, try, try.
Oh, they got nipples. Yeah, he's got nipples here.
Look at that nipples.
And Robin gets a suit at the end of the movie when Batman gets his new suit.
So Alfred's like, I took care of it.
I added the nipples and Alfred.
Now, don't forget that Alfred himself molded the nipples.
Heavily applied.
Suit me up, Uncle Alfred.
We're going to buzz saw zzzzzz.
Almost done, master.
There is. I mean, I don't know that it needed to be explored
in like a big budget movie, but there is obviously some weird
like S&M shit going on with a guy who dresses up in black rubber
at night to beat up people like.
There's some weird.
There's some weird stuff going on there.
So I wouldn't.
It wouldn't be crazy if you go like if we knew in real life
there was a person that was dressing up in black rubber
and went up like outside to get like to get himself beat up
and to go beat people up.
And you go, that guy also has rubber nipples on his costume.
You go, oh, yeah, of course.
Of course, that makes total sense.
Surprised and scandalized. Yeah. Right.
Oh, all superheroes have psychosexual madness behind.
I mean, Wonder Woman, the guy created Wonder Woman
was very into bonded stuff.
And that's why all the early, early Wonder Woman comics are like
women who are dominating men, tying men up.
William Marson, William Marson.
Yeah, they had he and his wife had an 18 year old lover
who was the basis for Wonder Woman.
He he was of the idea that men should just
like submit to women in every like every way, essentially,
and that society would be better for that.
That was his philosophy on it.
There's a lot of interesting stuff.
So, you know, you give Schumacher a lot of credit for going there.
That's what I'd like to say.
Sure. And I like the way he was trapping into a comic.
He almost was thinking more like a comic mind in a way.
Yes. He and I like to and I'd like to thank the good folks at Hot Toys
for making a giant package on the Chris O'Donnell toy.
Thank you. Pretty jaw drop.
That feels bigger than in the film.
I will say I will have to put it if I want to.
I was going to say when if I get it.
But let's be honest, when I get when you get it, I'm going to put it away.
I'm going to put it like, oh, my boss is coming over.
I'm going to have to hide the Chris O'Donnell toy.
And that's like it's like Frank Nelson, Gil Gordon type character.
Well, Michael, thank you for inviting me to your house.
Go great. This is what a wonderful evening.
Let me just go get my coat out of the closet over here.
It's me, your boss, Peter Forever Dog.
The pret is scandalized.
Oh, wait to my coat is caught on something.
I don't. Oh, he falls.
The toy hits him in the head.
He's stuck under it. The weight of it.
Chris O'Donnell's toy penis is holding me down on the floor.
I call if you know, don't move it, because if I pull it out,
you might bleed more. It's actually stopping the bleeding.
So we have to keep it right in your eye.
We have to we have to get to the hospital.
We have to we're going to have to drive all the way to the hospital,
which is a half hour away and past everyone you know.
And they may see you with Robin thrust into your face.
I'm sorry, Mr. Forever.
Mr. Forever, we have bad news.
We're going to have to chop off the figure, but you will have to
have the penis remain stuck in your head for the next six weeks.
Why? I've got a meeting tomorrow with John and Jane Brooklyn.
And what are we going to do about that?
We all have to just dress it up.
I don't know what to tell you, but this is just a medical opinion.
You can get a second one if you want, but then you'll have to drive by
another set of people.
Apologize for that, but that's the best we can do.
We've seen this a lot lately.
Please don't take away our Christmas bonus of a second.
Hello, fresh ad read.
It's going to happen pretty much just like this.
We were right in the middle of a really specific Jason fact,
which was that it's about Batman Adventure, the ride.
There was this Bertany one, and then they redid it in like 2002.
Correct. I think around that.
Yeah. So the Bertany one is is live action footage.
Some some, you know, plenty of effects and stuff.
And then Batman Adventure, the ride to they redid it with like
computer generated animation.
And this is kind of more as Mike was saying, like, I guess the term
for simplicity sake, generic Batman.
It does have the Kevin Conroy voice, but you kind of get
a more generic version of Batman and Batgirl Catwoman.
Mr. Freeze. It does still come out in.
There's a crashed thing in the penguins layer.
I think you still exit into that.
But who cares? It's fun.
But you like this is where and like this.
Well, we have a number of things to hit a lot of them.
I'm not like super like, well, we got to talk this and this and this,
because there are there is this format that I feel like a couple of things
have hit that is and then there's all the villains.
But there none of them are in like a sort of iconic mode.
It's like the way they would all look on a on a folder
or a lunchbox you would have.
Like, I think I think some of these brides fall victim to the same
trap of, all right, so you got to fit them all in.
And then there's the Joker and it's him with a big smile.
But like, which Joker is this?
This is just like every Joker and no Joker.
I think I think that generic CGI jokers don't do it for me.
I don't think they solve the getting the great Batman ride.
Yeah, I mean, that's part of it.
I mean, the animated I keep going back to Spider-Man,
because I think it's probably the gold standard superhero
ride at this still and that is generic.
We aren't like like it's great because Tobey Maguire is in it.
That's not what it is.
And yet it's it's really wonderful.
Yeah. But I think that
yeah, you feel like you know the characters better coming off the ride.
I think if you were to really if you were on some other planet
and the Joker wasn't the hamlet of our time
and you didn't know that character and you didn't know that he's
multiple Oscars have been won by playing the great take on.
Right. I think you wouldn't
have a feeling about him from seeing the just the ride versus like the
you would kind of remember like, oh, yeah, there was like that scream lady.
I remember what she looks like. Right.
She really scared me. I remember what she did.
Like, I think all those characters make such a better impression on you,
partly because they're so much closer to you.
And then I don't know, I don't want to say something crazy like, oh,
the characterization of them are so much better.
I don't think that's it.
But I just think things they do are more memorable
and they just they're they're with they're closer to you for a longer time.
I think that's the I think that's more of the difference.
And maybe the maybe what you're saying, though, with Joker is like
we've seen so many in so many great versions of the Joker, like
which is making fun of it.
But like all the Jokers are pretty good.
Caesar Romero, Joker's great.
Mark Hamill, Joker's fantastic. Yeah.
He fled your Joker fantastic.
I don't love the new Joker movie, but walking thinks is good in it.
Like he's he's doing.
Yeah, well, it's and it's like iconic immediately whether or not you
you like it. And there's moments that I make fun of.
And then there's one something.
He's pretty good. He's pretty good there. Right.
And obviously Jack's great.
And then there's been other like other ones like John DiMaggio played him,
I think, in one of the direct to DVD movies.
Pretty. So I yes, it feels
after all of those Jokers to sort of just see
you know, OK, guy laughing.
I've got you, Batman. Yeah, it's just not. Yeah.
Like, yeah, you got you.
There's got to be a choice or you have to use one of them or or something.
Yeah, it's maybe you just got to stay away from the Joker,
which seems like why take that off the table with a Batman ride.
But it seems like a like a trap.
It's a ticket to generic town.
Well, let me pitch you.
What happens sometimes if you try to get away from the classics,
let me pitch you a Batman ride that is like the antithesis
of Batman, the ride. OK.
And it's a coaster and it's called Batman and Robin the Chiller.
Either of you guys know about this.
I know there's a big video about it, and I don't I don't know the gist, actually.
OK, I want to talk to you now.
I know I just looked into a little bit.
I think Jason obviously knows more than I do, though.
So go ahead. Oh, because I wrote it.
I did this ride. Oh, wow. OK.
Let me show you this image to give you an idea of what you're working with here.
So this is what you enter into.
There's a lot going on in this picture, which I'll make sure to post.
You know, you've got more industrial stuff.
You've got the Batman and Robin logo.
You've got the funky 90s, fast lane, skip the line.
That's quite a lot.
And you got like sort of a big Limp Biscuit head hanging out.
I wouldn't go in this line, not because it's a scary coaster,
because I'd be worried about that guy.
Well, he might start moshing.
He might tell you to get in the pit.
He's going to moshing me.
And the guy, the other guy over there, I think the Six Flags employee
is sort of dressed like Dennis Nedry from Jurassic Park.
Big yellow slicker.
Yeah. And a hat.
Rightfully sure. Yes.
The other employee has some real baggy khakis on.
This is a this is an era.
And you've been on this. I've been on this.
So this ride, it comes to a dead end.
That's the other thing notable for this.
It dead ends.
This ride opened in June of 1997, same month as the Batman and Robin movie.
And I remembered this ride because my dad and I went to Six Flags once
and we rode it and immediately both had to sit down because it was
one of those ones where it's like, oh, my God, I feel awful.
Like, what the hell?
The shoulder restraints.
You just got rocked by those shoulder restraints.
And it was it was it was just so unpleasant.
My dad had been having like hip issues, like on and off and like getting off this ride.
He's like, I have to take an Advil like that was so bad.
And then we went on Superman, the escape, the drop ride that slides down.
And he's like, oh, that fixed it.
The one ride that fixed it.
I feel I feel 100 percent.
I texted him to confirm, did this ride fix your hip or fuck it up?
And he's like, no, this ride was awful.
This ride was rough.
Superman, the escape was the thing that fixed it.
The cartoon characters solve problems.
That's right in the head and it fixed the
back into place.
So you remember Jason as a kid, though, that like jacked you up real bad.
I would have been like 15, maybe.
And so like prime roller coaster riding age.
But yeah, I didn't realize I was like, is this still there?
And it closed in 2007, but I didn't realize it was plagued with
technical difficulties.
So it opens June of 1997 and then it closes two weeks later
because it was it's a launch coaster
that used the linear induction motors to launch like, you know,
this is shortly after Outer Limits Flight of Fear.
And this is right before the Incredible Hulk Coaster.
If you remember the Incredible Hulk Coaster, they built extra generators
so that it didn't fuck up the power grid using so much energy.
Batman and Robin the Chiller used just under the amount of energy
as the Incredible Hulk Coaster because it launched two coasters at once.
The Batman track and the Robin track were different.
And it was pulling so much power.
It became a real problem that Six Flags had to fix before they could reopen it
a year later in 1998.
Wow. That's crazy.
Yeah. All right. We got it.
The other thing that was notable for me and Theme Park
history has a long video about this on YouTube.
The shoulder restraints, everyone hated them.
And they became a real problem that you could not ride this ride
if you had earrings in because you would get bounced around so much.
People were coming off with bloody ears.
Oh, my God. Jesus.
Yeah. So that's insane.
And then they sold it to a park in Brazil.
It languished in a lot in New Jersey.
And then they decided it was too much work to install.
It was just a debacle. This whole endeavor.
This is crazy, because it's like this is still this still happens.
Like that Green Lantern Coaster they opened a couple of years ago
and had to take apart because it just it was too painful.
It was like they're like really still experimenting
with what the human body will accept as a thrill experience.
Six Flags. Yeah, they'll just like hammer something together and like,
goes it safe? Yeah, sure.
Probably. I think only one way to find out.
If if if we get 10,000 guests saying they hate it, we'll take it down.
And like we got to get to that number, though.
I mean, everyone, the governor,
you just need a certain amount of signatures and then we'll consider it.
Yeah. If somebody comes by the the the like guest services booth
and says, that sucked.
If we get to 10, we'll mark it down on a whiteboard. One.
Wait, in my school growing, I always my I think my mom told me like,
well, if you if we get three inches of snow, you get a snow day.
And I was always just watching the news broadcast.
Did we get three inches? Did we get three inches?
Does Six Flags have that for amount of blood?
Like it's like, all right, once we fill up this beaker with blood,
we got a redo. We got to double check everything.
Put in a wider beaker.
Then it'll take longer.
No, same height, three inches, but make it more of a trough.
Yeah. Yeah, that's that's.
So when did you say that they took it down?
How long? How long?
Two thousand seven. It was it was finally closed.
Still lasted a while.
Yeah, it lasted a while.
Ear bloodener, ear blood and ear blood in her lasted like a decade,
over a decade. Ear blood.
And then imagine the high that they must have been on the Six Flags
Great Adventure executives of like we got a Batman and Robin coaster
the same month as this big movie. Yeah, we did it.
Well, I think that I think Batman and Robin was cursed.
The curse of the movie itself, I guess, cursed this attraction.
And then another one, which is Mr.
Freeze, the coaster, which is in, I think, a Texas one
and a St. Louis one.
And I will never remember the Six Flags park names.
This will not happen.
But I think those are the places.
And Mr. Freeze was supposed to open in May 97 to go right alongside the release.
And as part of that, Schwarzenegger and Clooney were going to be there.
They were actually going to come and be the first to ride it.
But the launch is another launch one and it didn't work right.
So they had to push it till the next year.
And by that point, of course,
Schwarzenegger and Clooney are washing their hands of the entire thing.
They don't want any part of it.
So that all fell apart.
But they still got their
promotional opportunity and their big celebrity.
Not not to like they have got it eventually because they changed the
eventually they put it in reverse.
They reopened it and just put the ride backwards.
And to do to commemorate that, they did an event where
OK, look at the lavishness of this event.
There are silver balloons that say, Mr.
Freeze, the letters are starting to come apart.
So you might not be able to it might not be too legible.
There's a bunch of silver women, you know, like Mr.
Freeze would have around their dress.
They're dressed like his his wife that's in the tube.
They're dressed like they're dressed like Nora.
Nora Nora, which is how the guy said it on the animated series,
which I always say Nora.
Oh, I just got I mean, it's in my head from the movie because that's that's
that's the Arnold version's quest is that's why he's doing all these bad
to get the one more giant diamond, my love.
One more so I can find a cure.
They make him like a moat and he cries and then the tear.
Yes. Turns into ice.
Yes, that's fantastic.
I do like that movie.
But this this photo, you might not be able to see the celebrity
because there is an ice sculpture with the name of a Mr.
Freeze reverse the attack.
I don't know what it's called.
But there's two guys with chainsaws.
One is some guy in the other one.
That's vanilla ice, baby.
Oh, wow. Ice to come.
Who I think raises it and like Mr.
Freeze, you ready to write it?
Here we go. Here we go.
Yup. Yup.
So don't say that you can't get star power at Six Flags over Texas.
Wow. That is interesting.
When backwards, they have since you said back
the train going backwards, the ride going backwards.
Batman, the ride has been run backwards to they figured out how to do that.
And they also for some of the Batman, the ride tracks,
they painted them over the some of them are bright yellow now,
which I don't quite get.
They were a lot of them were black.
Some of them blue and like yellow is that like little accents on his chest
in some of the Batman outfits.
But a big yellow track does not scream Batman to me.
Meanwhile, Batman and Robin the coaster.
So that came to a dead end hill.
And then you went back all the way backwards on the track into the station.
So very complicated ride.
But, you know, hey, if you want to look on the bright side,
probably an example that the universal people were like, well,
let's make sure this coaster works.
Let's make sure we don't replicate those awful problems with the launching.
You know, right here.
Let me to jump.
We're jumping all around here.
Did you guys come across the Penguins Blizzard River?
No, no. What? Please.
OK, so I believe there was and somebody's going to correct me.
I'm sure I'm wrong a little bit.
But here's the logo for Penguins Blizzard River right on the right there.
And looks cool. That logo is cool. Yeah.
And there looks like there's there was one in Kentucky Kingdom.
And look at the outside of it's got like his big top hat there.
Oh, I mean, it's completely this looks good.
And look at these pictures like this.
That's cool. So it's a rapid ride.
So it's a rapid right. Exactly.
And there's like penguins, like big penguins.
And there's kind of some Gotham City type theming as you're going in the
the raft like Blizzard Beach.
It's cold everywhere.
But you could ride on a hot day. This is good. I like this.
OK, but they made another one.
And it was at the great Six Flags America
in Maryland, is that right?
This is what that looks like.
That's just that's just a building.
That's just that. Wait. Yeah.
It's a water tower.
Family water. It looks like shit.
It looks awful. Yeah.
Multi-color like it's just a slide.
It's just the device to make the raft go up.
And it's like a couple spins around and then you're done.
That's not the aesthetic of the penguin whatsoever.
Yes. So so they sometimes they like got it
writer in a different way, but then use the same name and logo
and then just did a much cheaper version.
Like, you know, there's a big penguin outside that looks kind of like shit.
And it's just like a warehouse with that logo on it.
And that's about it.
Again, what's if you're thinking like Riddler's Revenge, there's a there's
like a plan like what is the what's the point of the penguin
having made this blizzard river
that's just going to take you up from and take you down?
He's just like that seems to me like the villains are very generous.
They want us to be happy and smiling.
Yeah, they're like they're like kind of secret.
They're angel investor types who are, you know, trying to trick us to go on.
Maybe we think that are bad, but they actually just want us
to have a nice time at a theme park today.
That's really seems to be like a common thing.
They're not trying to destroy us.
The joke will be on them because they'll be having a fun splash of a time.
Maybe the trick is like then they'll want to pay five dollars
and get an annual pass for six flags.
They'll end up buying a T-shirt.
We had we cannot do this without going McGruff.
I've never got both doing McGruff as I have.
Why? Why? Why?
Penguin, penguin.
How would you do penguin?
I'm penguin.
Oh, yeah, Jason.
I would be Jason go for penguin.
I was trying to push Jason to be penguin on Gotham.
I was emailing an agent I had at the time going,
get Jason an audition for Penguin.
We real quickly threw together a real like there was something
enough level, a few levels removed.
This is years and years and years and put on a top hat and put it in.
Oh, no, no, no, no, if only they was young penguin.
And I was like, hey, you could do young, you could do young penguin.
They went with a very like tall, lean Broadway guy coming off Broadway, I think.
And he was pretty good.
Now's your chance.
Now's your audition.
Yeah, now it's a big audition.
But OK, I got to say a line, a different character said, why won't you just die?
Oh, I know means family.
Wow. I know he's family.
Why won't you just die?
Wow. Well, it's pretty clear you should have gotten the role.
It's the show.
These guys know a lot about theme parks, but then also they're such great
impressionists, all three of them.
Uncanny.
Who do you think, though, who who who do you think was the who?
Would you say your entrance was good?
His was better to famous Jim Carrey Lide,
which is also recycled in such shows.
All right. His was better.
Who who if we had to all play Batman villains, who would they be?
Who would you who would you truly want to play?
It doesn't matter.
It can be any version of any character.
Who's the most fun?
Hmm. Probably Penguin or Mad Hatter.
They had her in none of the live actions, right?
Not been used. Not in any of the live.
I would love a good like trippy Lewis Carroll Batman with the Mad Hatter.
And it sure had her with the ventriloquist.
That's a tough one, Michael. Quite a riddle.
Well, I think we know the answer.
God has. Yeah, I nailed it.
Are you sure the listeners should have seen the face I made?
I went real rubber faced with it.
Mm hmm. I like that. That's good.
I like the ventriloquist.
I think. Hmm.
What else? Who's that?
I like clay. Can I be Clayface?
Clayface could I be CGI?
The Condiment Clock King.
How about Clock King for me?
You don't want to be Condiment King.
I could be Condiment King, too, or Egghead.
Yeah. Vincent Price's villain, Egghead.
Oh, yeah. He's got to go ahead, I think.
Yeah, maybe Egghead.
Or B, I think I also like Bane, not Tom Hardy Bane,
but Batman and Robin Bane, who just seems like sleepy.
Bane's whole thing was like in the comics, he's like hyper intelligent guy
who's also like very strong and they did.
They went the other way with it in that movie.
Please, why do you not make me smarter?
Yeah.
Or you know what?
I could be Louis the Lilac, the Milton Berle villain from the 60s show.
I'm not sure I ever saw it.
I remember looking at books that would say things like that.
Like, what are you talking about?
Milton Berle was on it.
Louis. Well, there's also Jacques Gabor's Miss Minerva,
who owned the Evil Day Spa,
which is fantastic.
They put on like avocado rubs that burn your skin.
And then Batman and Robin both have like the towels on with their outfits.
In the episode, this is what you got to do with that Robin when it shows up.
You got to get a towel on that little guy.
A little towel.
To cover the nipples, a little.
Yeah, but not just the nipples.
All of it.
I think I have to go back to when the OK, in the episode where you said
that you made little beds for the Ghostbusters or your babysitter did
and that they were made of paper towels.
When Erin was listening to that, she was like, well, you guys shot past the facts
that the OK, yeah, the beds are weird, but then that
Mike's mom thought that they'd be a fire hazard.
I think we didn't address that part.
And I want to give a little time to that if we could.
Oh, yeah. I mean, this is this is give you a little bit of a window into my childhood.
Oh, great. Great. Yeah.
That so loose like napkins inside the plastic Ghostbusters house
would just spontaneously catch fire in the middle of the night.
That was that was some of the thinking.
Because like with something spark, like what if like
a cat knocked a water glass onto the electrical outlet
and then a spark came off of that and flew into the Ghostbusters house
and into their paper beds?
I I don't have a good answer for this.
And I have I bring I relitigate this every few years.
And I have yet to really get a good explanation of what the concern was, really.
But my recollection was they were thrown out maybe the night of this happening.
OK, like the night of I remember I it's a very vivid memory.
It's traumatizing to me, too,
because I was like, well, their little beds are gone.
They threw my mom threw them away.
Worried about a fire.
Don't have any. I don't have there's like why wouldn't.
So then wouldn't a paper towel roll be the ultimate fire hazard?
There's so that's like big and thick.
That's like that's like, you know, having an atom bomb in the house.
I guess the risk of having a paper towel roll in the kitchen
was less great than having from the risk of having a few pieces of it
in the child's bedroom.
And it's got I was warning you maybe.
What's that?
I would warn you just maybe don't leave napkins lying around
because they could just set on they just catch on fire.
I think that's what my mom was saying.
Well, the baby's already trying to eat napkins and choke on them.
I'm worried about that.
But I was not.
I've maybe not paid enough attention to the fire issue at hand.
We've all seen all these news stories about napkins just going up in flames.
Spontaneous napkin fires.
They're everywhere in your neighborhood, in every neighborhood.
Yes. There are there other things like this from my childhood?
Or you would say, why was that a concern?
Yes. But they have to be sort of unearthed organically, I think, or else
I would shut down or go into sort of a fugue state
if I were to try to bring any other ones up right now.
If they're related to an IP, that's how well, yes.
And all which I imagine a lot of them are.
I know 100 percent.
Oh, I had a similar thing where like
we were at a toy store and I wanted to get an action figure
that had like a rocket launcher, like so something that went into a spring
loaded launcher. Yes.
And my mom was like, no, no, I don't think you should have those launching things.
That's probably not good.
You don't want to get something in the eye or hit your brother or something.
And I'm like, what are you talking about?
I have two dozen things that shoot missiles like I have Power Rangers,
Ghostbusters, Ninjas, they all shoot like why are you suddenly?
Oh, and you know what? I'm remembering now.
I believe it was a last action hero action figure,
which another movie I did not see.
I would have all these toys from trading cards for PG 13 movies
that I was not allowed to see.
And I have no idea why that day she's just like, no, you're not getting something
that shoots. And that was the rule from then on.
And I think it's probably just like, I don't want to buy another piece of garbage
where you just got one.
But I don't know if she had seen a news broadcast of like someone firing
a GI Joe missile into someone's eye or something.
But I would be the nearest excuse to not pay for this.
Yeah, I would be more concerned about the thing kids do
where they're like overcome with emotion.
They just like throw something.
It's like I was like, well, we're not going to stop just throwing stuff
at each other when we're mad.
You have two boys.
What do you think is going to happen?
What we're put on this earth to do?
Yeah, that's where we're good.
That's the other thing. We were good boys, like rarely got in trouble at school.
And it's like, what are these parameters you're establishing?
What is your concern?
Are we are we maybe unearthing?
Because I think I'm with you guys on this.
That obviously we, you know, we now go by the moniker of good boys.
We're always very well behaved.
But you guys find that despite being good boys, it was often still not good enough.
You're like, compared to other kids, mom and dad.
I think you may be hitting on something that's a very common feeling on this podcast.
Yeah, I think that's right.
I think that sort of feels like you were like, put these other.
That's I said this all the time, all the time.
These other kids are dirty, like they're dirty and not it's like because it's like
like their parents are rich, but these kids are still filthy.
Like, yeah, and they're like, would you prefer I was that
a little dirty kid?
Let's see how you like it.
Am I look, am I still using this argument to this day?
I might be, I might be.
Well, do you want me like them?
What would you prefer?
Have I said that in the last six months?
Yes. If I said in the last six weeks.
Yes, also.
I don't know that that ever ends.
I think dynamics end up being the same your whole life.
I'm not sort of fighting the same battle.
I'm not going to be better because I get a real estate license, OK?
I'm not going to law school.
I'm not going back to business school.
I can't go back to what do you want me to do?
Own a business like that's riskier.
Look, I'm a comedy writer.
I'm sorry that it's not on a show that your parents have heard
or that your friends have heard of.
It's hard to get a job on The Mentalist,
and it's not not really what I'm trying to do.
I'm thrilled.
I'm thrilled to be on a thing that is canceled immediately.
Like, I'm thrilled to be on one episode.
We're all fighting to be on the people to be on canceled platforms.
Mom and dad, people listen to this podcast.
We do a podcast that there are some people that listen to it.
That is actually a thing.
Or my argument, people listen to podcasts at all
because it doesn't come in on your flip phone.
Doesn't mean it's not a viable medium.
You saw it. People showed up at a live show.
That doesn't just happen.
Not just like off the street.
We didn't pay anybody to come in.
I guess, as with Batman and the Joker and the Penguin,
our battles with our nemeses,
our arch nemeses will go on and on till the end of time.
We're dying.
It's like Joker says we're destined to do this forever.
You and I are destined to do this forever.
Big breakthroughs here in hour and 15 into the Batman rides.
Do you do you want to know how we got these scars?
We were not.
We were denied napkin blankets and and missile launchers.
It's way missile launchers.
I this is the first I've been tempted to
walk out of the room and take a break during.
Yeah, sure.
Where to go from there.
Now we just got to start saying names of rides again.
Yeah, well, I'm panicked.
Find one of my links here.
I mean, did any I think Batman the ride was my my kind of favorite
that I call that I called before we started recording.
Like we got to make sure to talk about this.
Well, you know, start with it.
I don't know if you guys have other notable like good or bad
like ones where you're like, I feel like I got to talk about this one.
Well, how about this?
I don't have a time to say about it, but there, you know, we said
it's pretty rare that any of these attractions have actors from the films.
As I say, usually the Batman films are populated
with the greatest, biggest actors of all time.
But there is one there's one that I could think of
that actually has a pre show with somebody from the movie.
And that is the Dark Knight Coaster, which is at three of the Six Flags.
Great America, Great Adventure, Six Flags, Mexico.
And that has an appearance from Harvey Dent as played by Aaron Eckhart.
Yeah. Did you know that there was there is a pre show with Aaron
Eckhart doing a part from that?
That's like the most legitimate thing from the movie world, I feel like in
in any of these.
And it's cool. It's good.
It's kind of like
the writing in it is like Nolan Light.
It's all that like philosophy kind of.
He sort of like reiterates the the kinds of things that the
the Nolan Batman characters would say.
And he does a he's doing a press conference.
But then the Joker hijacks the feed.
So it starts like cutting it up and sort of like almost in like a right wing
media Twitter way, like using his words against him, using the power of editing.
And then the feed gets hijacked entirely and Harvey Dent gets ushered away.
And then the room goes dark and it comes back on.
Well, depending on which one you're at in at least one of them, then
like the room goes dark.
And then what comes back up, the lighting is different.
It says ha ha ha everywhere in like day glow lighting.
And, you know, that's cool.
Like then then what follows is essentially like a wild mouse coaster indoors.
But that pre show, I'm like this here we go.
This feels a little bit like Disney and Universal.
It's one actor from the movie.
They like created a panic.
It's like, oh, what if we were in a place that the Heath Ledger
Joker was creating havoc in and we're trapped?
There's nowhere to go now.
Now we got to go on the scary machine.
So I actually think they did a good job with this.
I this is kind of cool.
Yeah, that's cool.
I I would say like for your question, and I kind of felt like I was putting it down
a little too much, the WB world, the night flight, the practical stuff
in some of the screens, it's close.
I don't want to sound like I'm so talking so much shit on it,
but it is close, like even like poison ivy coming toward the screen.
It's not bad. It's pretty I got that.
I like that. That feels closer to being right and closer to an experience.
Well, we should explain this one from the ground up, maybe this.
Yeah, this is in Warner Brothers, Warner Brothers World Abu Dhabi.
It's a pretty recently opened park that is indoors
and they have a whole indoor Gotham City area.
And this ride is sort of a culmination of it, which is very,
I believe Harry Potter.
I think this is a kooka arm
whipping you around between screens and some like transitional practical sets.
And there's a little bit of real animatronics in it.
It's yeah, it's hard to find.
As with a lot of these, it's hard to find like a really good ride through of it
because it is 3D.
So the videos are a little confusing to watch.
But it's yeah, this is this one's maybe the closest to me
for being like a modern current e-ticket.
You know, I like I bet it's fun to be on in ways that we can't even tell.
There's probably like 4D kind of elements that we aren't aware of.
Right. So I do think it gets from just watching it.
I think it gets close and like they it has a cool cue
and there's some interesting details and fun stuff.
And then, of course, everything, as you were saying, like everything video wise,
it's hard to tell.
There's like I found videos of just the cue.
I don't know. I didn't find a great comprehensive video that might be there.
I just didn't see it of you going through like a very Nolan Wayne tech building.
And like the premises, you're you're all tech experts.
Well, you're you're yeah, that's really strange.
You're I think going to take a minute
to take a meeting at Wayne Tech.
You're and you get in an elevator that's going to take you up to the 53rd floor
to have a meeting up there.
You're having a general with Bruce Wayne, I guess.
And but then there's a little glitch in the feed.
And then Batman appears on a screen that you couldn't see before
and tells you that he's been watching you and he knows that you're all tech experts.
So actually, he needs you somewhere different.
And then change, of course, you end up in the Batcave.
Yes. And there's a the video I was watching.
It's like tired dad, a couple of kids.
And Batman goes, I can tell you're all tech experts.
And then there are no no no emotion on anyone's face.
Like, like, oh, wow, it's so cool or whatever.
It's like, uh, like no one's even paying attention to what Batman is telling them.
Very funny. Yeah, it doesn't.
I feel like a lot of those videos you're seeing these things played empty rooms.
I can't tell if these that what we keep hearing is that Warner Brothers World
Abu Dhabi is pretty cool.
Like it's like it is like it is kind of next level
and like a a pretty good use of all these IP like Warner Brothers
or like Looney Tunes rather, where you complain that there's not great rides
about them or of these properties in the Six Flags parks.
I don't know. All the videos are cool.
But then we're never going to go like is anyone going?
That I there's a lot holding you back.
I feel like, yeah, it's these things.
I can't tell. I mean, yeah, there's you were saying the indoor,
like it's an indoor park and there's a Gotham City area.
There's like a metropolis area.
And that's pretty impressive as far as like from the scale
you can see in a YouTube video.
It's like, yeah, that feels right. It's dark all the time.
It's like you see the Wayne Tech building and it looks impressive
for an indoor thing.
But then you get inside the queue and you're like, this should be the
this should be packed. This should be your 90 minute wait.
And there's like no one in line ever on any of the videos.
And you're like, how's this doing?
This was pre all the stuff.
This was a great pandemic.
So who knows? I don't know.
But they're like they're getting closer.
And that's part of what I said at the beginning about.
All right. There are good Batman, rather.
Where we used to be, I think a cool one, as I said, in Germany, Australia.
There seems to be some good stuff happening in Abu Dhabi.
But America, we're just really suffering from these
these and I mean suffer.
We're really suffering by not having Batman rights.
But we're like we are the victims, essentially, of these
this six flags licensing deal
that doesn't get us the universal level caliber of of Batman attractions.
Right. And I mean, there's been, you know, Warner Brothers had
that fully owned six flags at a certain point.
I forget if it was fully majority owned or a lot of it.
Yeah, I think I forgot that the Time Warner bought
at least the controlling share in around 92.
But then they don't own it now.
We've talked about this at length, I'm sure.
But like it's just always been stuck.
It was almost of course, we didn't we're not even we haven't even talked about
how it was almost an island of adventure.
And there was going to be a Batman penguin coaster competing there.
Yeah. Well, we know we got we got time to.
Sure. No, we can't.
I'm saying like it's like it's been it's been it's with all this stuff.
And we've said it before, like it's right place, right time
for certain properties to make a certain level of right.
So it's like it's been in the wrong spot.
They couldn't get out of negotiations for Islands of Adventure.
So that fell apart.
It's never been right now.
I think we're the closest to it maybe being possible.
But six because six is trying.
Justice League was trying to do more of this.
They still didn't quite get there.
Yeah. And well, we may.
Yeah. Justice League, I guess, is its own.
I mean, I got to go on that ride.
Oh, yeah. I'll go.
I'll go to measure round and only go on that and then leave.
Probably. Sure.
Well, you want to go to you'll go to the lounge and stuff like you'll go
to all those places that we're going to go to Johnny Rockets. Yeah.
It's a job.
And then and then we'll trick you to go on Twisted Colossus.
Oh, yeah.
Maybe I do Batman the Ride.
Maybe it's I don't know.
I think you could handle Riddler's Revenge easy to Riddler's Revenge.
Not a big problem.
OK, it's fun.
And is that the stand up one?
Yeah. Yeah.
But it's not. I'm not good on that one.
Too little.
No, I mean, the bicycle seat destroys my that one is the one that destroys
my genitals. Twisted Colossus destroyed your genitals.
Well, they both they both weren't like the easiest on my genitals.
The twisted Colossus was more aggressive to my genitals at that point.
But neither of you are going to be Chris O'Donnell level
the more you go on these things.
Yeah, no, it's it's not going to happen.
But, Jason, you're comfortable on Tatsu.
Yes. Where you're flying like Superman.
Oh, I love Tatsu. Yeah.
That's wild. That feels so scary to go on where I'm at.
And arms are just like floating.
That's wild.
I think it was just the novelty of it kind of carried it.
The uniqueness. Sure.
I was just delighted by.
Well, we'll see. Look, we went on Hangtime together.
That's not me. I watched it.
I'm checked out of the whole thing.
That's coaster hang time, which, by the way, is only the only scary part
is just the start of it.
The rest is a perfectly fun coaster.
Yeah, I have no problem on past a certain point. Yeah.
But the first part is pants shittingly scary.
Sounds like it. Yep.
Well, so yeah, so the whole
I feel like it really unlocks
the mystery, it solves the riddle, if you will.
When you as you're going, like, why are there not better
Batman attractions, especially in America?
Oh, my God, because they were trying to do it
at what became Islands of Adventure Universal was trying to do this
in the late 80s, early 90s.
They negotiated it.
They could not make a breakthrough on it.
The Universal and Warner were fighting bitterly and
didn't come up with a breakthrough.
And thus, we don't have these.
And they they went off to Six Flags.
Yeah. But so like finding out that there was
it really in a way, I think the premise of the park changed.
Maybe it was never going to be Islands of Adventure with a Gotham city.
But in a way, I don't like
I guess the whole thing is that there was the initial premise
of the park was cartoon world.
It was all going to be animated properties.
Seuss was part of it always.
Seuss and Popeyes and, oh, man, we got to do a whole cartoon world thing.
The the unbuilt Popeye stuff is insane.
Like a whole Sweet Haven village.
What? In addition to the Malta one?
Oh, an indoor boat ride.
Build rap barges was always happening.
Of course, the original Dudley do right plans.
That was always still is a dual shoot, a dual log flume.
But I think we talked about the buzzsaw.
It was going to cut your log in half.
The logs in half. So cool. Yeah.
The Looney Tunes stuff looked awesome, too.
That was the big the thing that had to change is they couldn't do Looney
Tunes and they couldn't do DC Super Heroes, which it was going to be like half
Superman, half Batman, which is fitting because I forget who says this.
But there's a thinking that Metropolis Superman City,
it represents New York City during the day.
And Gotham is supposed to be New York City at night.
And so splitting that park with these two iconic characters,
it's like a given.
And so much of the ideas seem to be good.
Like the Superman ride, so much of the Superman ride ended up in the Spider-Man ride.
Right. And it seems like Batman still wouldn't have had the ride
we're looking for completely.
No, I don't know.
I think some of these could have if they really did.
Well, I think could have been cool as hell.
Would have been certainly better than the majority of stuff.
It's just like I think the Superman ride would have been more
the Spider-Man ride with like that would have been the full experience.
Like Batman, they were saying they were going to do a penguin.
I have it written down. They were going to do a Batman penguin coaster.
Where is it?
Different cues like you would.
Yeah, you would load in either the Batcave or in the penguins layer,
depending on what you pick.
So that stuff all seems like it would be awesome.
And then it was just sort of a roller coaster.
I'm sure it would have other elements as well.
Well, no, I think this was a like from the various videos and descriptions,
it was like three show buildings.
You keep going in and out of sets.
You see different stuff on the two tracks.
And I believe Spielberg's suggestion guns.
Why not throw guns on there, too?
So it was like in hypothetically, this was a or is this suggestion
that you keep score some that you get a score at the end of it?
So it's supposed to be a shooting coaster, which sound I mean,
I don't like to me, everything I saw from this and just from the look of what
these these little cool boxy bat wings and with that, they were going to go more
penguin forward on it.
Penguins, I believe, was the terminology.
Which I think this is the one I'm this thing seems pretty fucking cool to me.
Well, the video I watched that made it didn't make it seem as cool,
but it still looked better than most of the stuff as far as theming and cues
and stuff. But yeah, you're just I mean, yeah, it would have just depended, I guess,
how how how fast it went, like how much show, how many show elements
you could put in it that you could actually see while you were actually competing
against another car. So in a fast situation. Right. Right.
There was also a great of a Batman and Robin stunt show in the lagoon.
Yeah. There there was going to be some sort of body of water.
That that was always the case.
So there'd be a stunt show in the water.
And then Joker's Madhouse, which was an indoor coaster on a wildcat
wild mouse, wild mouse, excuse me. Yeah.
On a wild mouse track with a false ending,
with a like ride broken kind of ending, which eventually worked its way
into the mummy ride. Right. Yeah. Right. Right.
Yeah. There was so there was supposed to be a track out at some point,
but which deceives the path to what where it becomes.
I think a drop is what they were trying to do.
They were like maybe similar to Hagrid's.
It was just going to go straight down at a point instead of, you know,
veering off track. Right.
This this sounds really cool.
There's also like then there's I think Theme Park University
is one of the sites that has found all this stuff and a number of good videos
on YouTube if you're curious.
But like there's a lot of concept art floating around for this stuff
and what things would have been.
They even fleshed out what the the shops and restaurants would have been.
We're going to have Joker's Diner, where you got your food served to you
in a Jack in the Box box.
Penguin Pizza.
I have no further information about it, but the name is great.
I'd love to try some Penguin Pizza.
Not a fish sandwich or a fish place.
But maybe you're getting anchovies there.
I don't know. Yeah, maybe until again, until per usual.
They realize the theme park audiences, at least in the 90s,
don't want anything. Just cheese and pepperoni. That's it. Yep.
That's what we sell at Penguin's Pizza.
Those are Penguin's favorite flavors.
But there is also
we just pull this up.
So we're all looking at the same screen.
I don't know where all this text comes from, these these plans.
But one thing to point out, the Bat Cave,
which is described as a video.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Club. Wow. My God. Yeah.
Yeah. Which would have had, I think, a fake out.
And like you're going into Wayne Manor, similar to the ride that ended up there.
You're going to Wayne Manor, but then you end up in the Bat Cave instead.
I think we're going to be like for sure there was going to be a big visible
bat signal as part of all this perennially in the sky.
But yeah, fog and themed rock tables.
This is a fake rock environment nightclub.
I mean, this this seems amazing.
This is yeah, this is this is where I wish a whole scene had sort of developed.
They had made this and like as if it was Pleasure Island, a whole like,
you know, generation defining scene had happened at the bat cave
at Universal Islands of Adventure.
We talked about it in our Pleasure Island episode a while ago.
The Facebook is a Facebook group of people that partied at Pleasure Island
a lot for years, and they still are very active on this Facebook page.
This looms large.
I wish the Bat Cave was the same deal
where people would be like, man, remember the Bat Cave?
Those were the days you'd put on your black leather with the nipples
and you'd go party at the Bat Cave.
You take your special lady to Catwoman's Lair.
Get her a cigarette case and a faux fur.
This was that was the other thing I was pulling up for.
Yeah, that there was like a high end
Catwoman store where you bought like
late 80s chic women's style.
Yeah, high fashion hats, exotic lighters, fans, day planners.
I love this sort of like
woman on the go, like Wall Street era.
This this sounds and say I would love if this was there in a velvet walls.
And you could buy fake furs and stoles and capes.
You buy like a big 80s lady cape in a theme park.
Really wish this was there.
Yeah, your mom wants to go to Island's Adventure
because she needs to get a new mink fake mink stole.
Like what?
I guess maybe.
I mean, if the market we didn't know if no one's doing it right now.
So we don't know if it would have been failure.
No one's tried this in a theme park.
Mom needs a new very wide hat
in a fine and a faux fur cigarette case.
And it did.
I feel like I heard a story once where it's like, well, you know,
whatever the big thing everyone has to have is often stolen.
Now it's smartphones before that cell phones and beepers.
But I feel like I heard someone talk about like, oh, yes, stores used to get
day planner stolen all the time or like a little black books.
Because everyone needed to have something like that.
Sure. You know?
Yeah, I wonder when that whenever the phones,
smartphones started and day planners thefts went dramatically down.
But you know, villain themed day planner store and you're asking for that.
Yeah, because everyone feels so much more villainous
when they're shopping in these stores.
My inner cat woman is coming out.
I'm surprised that they didn't,
because this seems like a little bit more adult as far as what they ended up
putting there with Marvel Superhero Island.
I'm wondering why they didn't then just take these ideas
and put them just use a marvel.
Like, why didn't they use like mojo or arcade?
These X-Men villains, why didn't they have a club with their like
their characters on the front door or the Hellfire Club?
Well, which is Scott, just to quickly educate you on what the Hellfire Club was.
It was a club where like mutants would dress up as,
what would you say, colonial era?
Well, when it was like a rich and famous private like high end club,
there's still some fancy clubs.
But then the inner circle of the club, the bad guys would dress.
Yeah. In like regal Victorian wear.
Powder wigs. Yeah.
It's where Emma Frost comes from and the character
Kevin Bacon plays in X-Men First Class.
It's also lost. Sorry.
He mad. I know he was in it.
It's based on some downtown sex clubs that
certainly based on a real would go to in the 70s.
Based on a real fetish sex club.
And then Jason and I was like 10 year olds who were like,
oh, the Hellfire Club.
OK, cool. Like the fancy villains.
I got it. Yeah.
They like history. Right.
So why wasn't there a real Hellfire Club is what I'm saying
in Marvel Superhero Islands.
I think that one's fine.
I think maybe you got to skip the Hellfire Club from the sound of it.
I don't know.
I mean, it didn't have to be as intense as it might have been in real life.
I'm just saying there were ways to do it.
I mean, who would in the Marvel universe have a fancy hat?
I mean, there's the there's the ripoff catwoman Black Cat,
character in Spider-Man called Black Cat, who was a thief as well.
We'll be getting movies of all these soon.
Oh, I think Black Cat is on the way, right?
I think that's coming. Yeah.
Mary Jane is a model sometimes.
Sometimes she is a big cat.
Oh, yeah. Mary Jane's boutique. That would be great.
I just don't know why they went with like,
yeah, throw a comic store in Fantastic Four cafeteria.
Like, they got lazy is what I'm saying.
Yeah. But in a big science is pow where it's a comic world.
They're done.
They were going to they were going for a high end thing with this Batman land.
And then they obviously switched, switched
what they wanted to do with it.
Well, 90s Gotham was so fancy like they they remade the
they redesigned the Sony lot around this time to build.
This needs to feel like Gotham City and Batman.
Like this was like it's like
hearkening back to the 40s in the fanciest way.
Everything should feel like, you know, where the waynes walk out of.
And you should be able to buy pearls that break away.
Collapse easily.
Your parents. Yeah.
A simulation of your parents getting blown away in crime alley.
And you get everyone had that opportunity to like, all right.
You like we're pulling your mom and dad from the crowd.
And there's what it would be like if the Joker killed them.
Coming soon to Disney's Avengers campus.
Pay an upcharge and get trapped in an iceberg like Captain America for decades.
So everyone you know and love is very old when you come out.
I really yeah, they should really do this with tragic superhero origins.
We should be able to experience those in the theme parks.
We want a next level experience.
So it has to be Uncle Ben dying in Spider-Man.
You want that?
And you didn't you watched as the guy ran by.
He didn't do anything and you could have.
We want that experience.
Experience Wanda's trauma on a new e-ticket attraction.
That's right.
We need these experience.
We need next level theme park.
And we're not just saying that because we're complaining about our parents earlier.
We don't actually want the Joker to kill them.
We just want a fun thing.
We watch some pearls fall.
We want pearls to fall. Right.
Simulated. You know, it's these are the simulated experiences.
Can I quickly play this thing from Dubai world?
Speaking of get your parents involved.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, please. Oh, yes.
So there's not just rides in the Dubai Warner Brothers thing.
There's a little show.
So a lot of people have played the Joker and.
I love this.
I don't know this gentleman's name.
He seems to be their Joker.
He plays this Joker as if he's Jerry Lewis in our six of a telethon.
And I love it.
I think it's great.
I think it's a great take on the character, because why would you want to rip off?
Anyway, here I'll play this thing.
It's in the right spot.
Like this one.
And it's Harley Quinn.
With you. Yeah.
I was going to use this, but I'm already scared his hair away.
I like them, so you're going to stay up here.
Well done, my dear. Let's take the guest.
Let's prepare him for the grand finale.
But kids, this is an ugly shirt.
It's hurting my face.
After the show, you buy him a Joker shirt so I can pay rent on that funhouse.
Go, go, go. Ugly shirt. Go, go, go.
Let me take this opportunity to thank you all for coming.
The real question now is
how many of you will leave?
I mean, I just like I want to say thank you so much, everybody, for coming.
Thank you. Thank you to Dean and Sammy for showing up tonight.
The work the work we do here, the work we do in the madhouse.
So it drives people crazy all over the world, and it's important work.
And that's why we do it.
I mean, isn't that that's a fan.
I love that take.
He's so tired. He doesn't want to be there.
You're you seem like a nice fella, but the shirt is ugly.
That's all I'm going to say.
Get yourself a new one.
Don't make me squirt my flower onto it.
St. Charisse, we know you broke your famous leg and we wish you the best.
We know you're in the hospital.
We saw you couldn't be here tonight.
I'll braise it with you, Sid.
I want to thank Harley Quinn and Poison Ivy.
The jokes didn't land.
We know female super villains are not funny
and not good at what they do, but thank you regardless.
Thank you for trying regardless.
Yeah, it's I think this guy deserves an Oscar for Joker as well.
I'd like to get an Oscar for everybody.
I like this guy. Yeah.
Thanks, Mr. Dubai. The yeah.
So really quick, what ended up at why isn't any of this in Universal?
Why isn't there a big committed Batman land?
Because they were negotiating, as Jason said, not just for the DC characters,
but for the Looney Tunes.
That's a lot.
Those are the the crown jewels in the Warner Empire.
And it came down to royalties.
MCA wanted to pay them six percent for royalties for their characters.
Warner Brothers wanted 10.
They eventually came down to eight.
They got stuck at eight.
That all and this all led up to Sid Sheinberg from Universal saying to Terry
Semel from Warner Brothers, we don't need your fucking characters.
And that was the end of that.
Yeah, a genuine quote, apparently.
And yeah, and then thus those walls are up forever because you
mean, maybe not forever, but you would have to think like it seems.
Weird, especially with Marvel now, like you're never going to see
Disney pair with DC. That's not going to happen.
Universal is the other catch all that grabs entities from other mega corporations.
Like, so shouldn't they end up with and especially now that they can't do any
new Marvel, I don't know.
Will they ever make amends?
Are we ever going to see anything really next level with Batman in the states?
Well, the timing made sense at the time.
Disney, MGM Studios, Universal, Warner Brothers teaming up to take them on.
But it would have been competing with Six Flags.
Yeah, it's it's crazy because like we've talked about, Warner Brothers
has flirted with doing stuff.
They know now as far as Harry Potter, like they should have had their own
theme park that they could have plugged a crazy Harry Potter land into.
And then they would have gotten all the money for it.
Yeah.
But it's still like, everything's a mess, you know, as far as like all the
merger stuff happening and their TV and movies, everyone's mad HBO Max movie.
Like it seems like it's just a disaster.
Like it seems like it's going to be years before they really get to
figure out what's going on and either either like buy more interest in Six
Flags and pump that stuff up or decide to just do their own thing, which would
maybe be a better thing, maybe be a better idea.
But I don't know.
It seems hopeless.
It truly seems like we, we need a hero right now and we don't have one.
And our, and the, as we said at the beginning, our heroes are billionaires
and billionaires run these companies.
So we need a hero billionaire looking out for the kids on the ground here.
Right.
Really want a really good Batman ride.
And the right merger needs to happen to make it possible.
Yeah.
We want more companies to merge.
Yes, we love mergers.
It's okay.
It's, it might not be the hero we deserve, but you know, maybe it's the one we need.
You know, right.
All the, okay.
Yes.
Let's come by Disney should buy Warner Brothers and sick all the Six Flags.
Yeah.
Disney Six Flags.
Oh my gosh.
Buy all of it.
There should be two companies, Universal and Disney, the two theme park companies.
And then that'll be it.
And then Superman can be in WandaVision.
And then, yeah, yeah.
And then the other one, uh, I mean, I guess the HBO side is what, what?
No, Universal is one.
Um, that's all going to be, I think like Rogan.
Um, that's all going to be, I think like Rogan, Joe Rogan's could just going to be the
other company and hopefully he starts theme parks.
That's where it's all.
Rogan's Spotify.
Yes.
When he, when he ends up in the name, when it becomes Joe Rogan's Spotify.
Right.
Um, so yeah, it's no, it's, it's feels like the future is bleak.
Maybe we'll get another like slightly better justice league thing, but maybe not.
Not probably in the future, especially because, you know, I'm sure six
flags needs some money right now.
Yeah.
So, well, this is a can of worms and we're winding down, but I feel like we have to
give a little, we have to attempt to talk about like, okay, so what if this all does
get solved, Joe Rogan purchases the Batman and makes a good ride out of it.
Um, what, uh, what do we want?
What's the Batman ride?
What is the great Batman ride?
Well, the toughest question, cause there's so many eras, so many, I, I, you know,
there's like five or six things about things like a Batman stories that I love
equally, uh, Jason, what are you going to say?
Well, I was going to say, the only thing I'd be concerned about is, uh, I feel
like his type isn't really fond of regulations, so may he may end up making a
Batman ride that leads to the creation of Batman asks super villains because
something actually goes horribly wrong at a chemical plant or something.
So like he's got, so Joe Rogan has Ben Shapiro on an episode of his podcast and
then Ben Shapiro gets like into a chemical plant and there's an accident.
He turns into like a super villain.
Well, even if he takes him on this new Batman ride, but he gives him DMT and
then he gets, you know, falls into the bat of, of hydraulic fluid and you know,
all these people do seem like super villains waiting to happen.
Like, like there are one mutation away.
Wait, sorry. What were you saying?
Mike? Oh, I was just saying Alex Jones is on the podcast podcast a lot.
Like there are all these different guys that are, yeah, what you're saying is one
like chemical accident away from being a Batman villain.
Yeah. And we're aware of all of them.
Like we're seeing where we know who all of them are.
There are all these weird celebrities and they are, they're all merging like
the villains in like, wait, wait a minute.
Now there's a pair up between Gina Carano and Ben Shapiro.
Like she's joined up in a cat woman.
Wait, them now?
Yeah. And then just it all it takes is one spill and then, yeah.
And then they all can like jump really high.
Well, that's damn it.
No, they all just got, yeah, they all just like are like have the power of a
grasshopper for some reason.
Oh, they all got frog man powers.
Now I'm going to fight over who gets the frog man outfit.
Shapiro is already like, what's his fuck the who's the scarecrow?
It's the Sillian Murphy.
Killian, John and Jonathan, Dr.
Jonathan Crane. Yeah, yeah, he's he's kind of like him already.
He's like kind of the you know, he's a little more like the on the show,
Gotham, their Edward Nigma, I feel like.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Who's sniveling more like that?
Well, the OK to not give these guys too much of our time,
the because I was trying to think like, OK, there are there's obviously
so you would of course you would want like a full land that all right,
here's Batman forever world, here's 66 world.
But in lieu of that and maybe YB in lieu of that, let's do that.
But I was trying to think like what genuinely is OK,
because I think the closest ride,
I think my favorite of the ones we've talked about is that Star
Tour Z analog Batman Returns era attraction.
But you're still missing some stuff.
You're like, where are we?
We're in like a we're in a moving box theater where we are not.
Is the Batmobile and you talk about intimacy,
you talk about places you want to be, you want to be in the cockpit
of the of the Batmobile.
And maybe it doesn't make sense to be with Batman,
although being with an animatronic in sort of a rise of the resistance way
seems pretty cool.
But I was like, earnestly, I was thinking about how we've certainly complained
about Millennium Falcon Smuggler's run.
And I think the complaints are more about like what happens and like
this the video game aspect of it really.
Is there enough payoff for it?
I think that that type of ride system where there's a bunch of little pods
that you get in.
I mean, now with COVID, that's tougher.
But forget that the idea that like there's a turntable
and you can actually be in a little space instead of like
Doc built a big DeLorean for you.
Like you want to be in the actual thing.
So if there was a Millennium Falcon,
like a similar setup to that, that let a lot of people be in kind of
a private Batmobile and then you take a real like a gritty trip
in the Batmobile and maybe Batman's piloting remotely, sort of like Doc.
Sure.
But in the future, I think that happens in one of the movies.
You could see villains, you could not see villains.
Maybe it's more about going to places than encountering characters.
I think a really a very good Batmobile ride is really the key thing,
and that might be able to transcend what era it's in,
because the Batmobile never changes that much, I feel like.
Yeah. Yeah.
I think you could play with
like, yeah, the Batmobile, if you were getting in the Batmobile
and you're going to Batman, a lot of these rides don't really utilize the like.
Not seeing Batman, like Batman being like stalking in the night.
So what if like he didn't show up until like halfway through the ride,
like at a big moment, someone's about to get you and then he shows up and helps.
Yeah. The other thing that these rides never do.
Sorry, Mike, but is no doing the other perspective
where you are a bad guy being pursued by Batman
and it becomes like a haunted house, like it becomes a horror ride.
Sure. Yeah.
I mean, that's I assume that's always like a problem.
They're like, we can't make the guests be bad, be bad people.
Yeah. The villains are so exciting in Batman where like you want to team up
with them, certainly.
Yeah. It's all about the villains for me.
So I think I think if if I'm if I'm thinking of what the ultimate
just single Batman ride is, I obviously want.
Separate rides for all the villains, for all the side characters,
for Nightwing, for Damien, Robin, Batman's 10 year old killer assassin son.
I want separate stuff for all of it.
But if I'm thinking of the thing that's going to scratch most of the itches,
I think it's an Arkham Asylum ride of some kind.
Yeah. Where the bad guy, it's like sort of the premise of the first PlayStation game.
It's like the bad guys have taken control of Arkham.
Maybe you're on sort of an Omnimover, like Rise of the Resistance type vehicle
that like, oh, you're going through, you know, this is a you'll say you're
you're all scientists or you're all psychologists.
You're taking a tour and then the villains have taken over.
And I don't I would say, you know, you do a ride vehicle like Rise of the Resistance,
but it's somehow figure out a way to get that force feedback,
that Indiana Jones movement this just to make it feel a little more chaotic.
And then I don't even think it needs anything super
thrilling other than just you go into a room.
There's a really great poison ivy animatronic.
There's leaves, there's, you know, plants coming through the room
somehow with robot stuff could be accentuated with screens.
And you get like a 30 second, 45 second show scene with all your favorite villains.
Batman is with Jason's idea.
Batman comes in maybe halfway through.
Nightwing comes in, whoever.
And it's like and then there's a big finale.
And I don't know, it could be a drop like at the end of Rise of the Resistance.
It could be anything.
I don't think that stuff is as important, though, as just
really feeling like you've you've been in the most immersive
Batman experience as possible.
And I feel like you need.
You need those rooms with like practical things in them.
It could be accentuated by screens and part of it could be screens,
but I think that would be awesome.
And especially if it was tight, tight rooms,
because I think that's even cooler.
Like aspects of Rise of the Resistance where you feel like you're in a really small space.
Feels really cool. That's really great. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Arkham is a great idea.
And Arkham isn't like so there's not like the cinematic depiction of it
they were tied to that you couldn't reinvent to some extent.
Right. And you can have a scene where like somebody blows up the floor
and you fall into the next show scene below you and then you zoom somewhere else.
Like there's a lot of different ways you could have exciting stuff that doesn't
necessarily need you to actually have a thrill element or go on a roller coaster.
But yeah, you can make you can make the layout whatever you want.
It doesn't there's the video game, but that's probably the most definitive
version of Arkham, honestly, that there is.
Yeah, man's I think like an animatronic that's mainly in the suit.
So you you could sort of get away with the Indiana Jones effect if it's not Harrison.
Like if you're if he's mostly in shadow and he just kind of is reminiscent
of all of them in a way, I think that works.
And yeah, and you could go like there's there's more iconic art styles.
I mean, you could go full those Arkham games, the style of Batman and the villains,
I think, loom pretty large now.
You could go with that type of style.
You could also just pick an artist, you know, Jim Lee or any other current.
I'm trying to think who else has been drawing Batman.
Greg Capolo has been drawing Batman.
You go with any of these like styles and see what works for robots.
And as long as I think as long as it feels like it as a take,
I think it's OK versus having like a particularly iconic take.
Now, would I also like getting the likeness rights to all the villains
from the movies and putting them in this right?
Of course I would get Arnold, get Uma, get them all and make the animatronics
look like them. That'd be awesome.
Oh, get you get all get Hathaway, get Eckhart.
Sure. Get Billy D.
Get Billy D. We get two two faces, you know, just right.
Billy D. was supposed to be Harvey.
He was Harvey Dent in the original movie.
Yeah, supposed to be two faced, but they and Damon Waynes, right?
Was supposed to Robin.
I have the they famously made the action figure and then painted it white
and just put out a generic Robin action figure for Batman Returns.
But they were getting ready to like make the Damon Waynes like action figure.
Weird. Yeah, so bizarre.
I think the other stuff you I would like to Wayne Manor,
something in Wayne Manor, the Batcave, the roof with the Bat Signal
and Commissioner Gordon like, oh, yeah, you're going to go there. Yeah.
Yeah, those I think you can.
I think people have a general idea, but I don't think there's, you know,
the big computer.
I think there's a lot of different versions of those things,
but I think people would recognize most versions of those things.
And I think maybe, you know, for people like us, I think having
a walkthrough or an experience where we got to get a psychological evaluation
from Dr. Chase Meridian would really be a nice capper for the trip,
for your day at the park where you get to explain, Chase,
what's going on with your life and your childhood.
And this isn't like a high capacity attraction.
Like you'd be this would be you wouldn't like want to be sending so many people
through. You would want this to be intimate.
You want to make sure that you're locked in and you have a good long moment
with Dr. Chase Meridian.
Well, it would be like it would be like meeting Mickey in Disney World,
where there's multiple chase rooms and you don't get to see that those exist.
Like you're saying with the Millennium Falcon, you know, you would just like
go down and you would never know that there were multiple chases.
So you could get a couple.
She's all yours.
Well, yes, I think you would need to rotate every other hour.
Would have to be meet and greet with Sugar and Spice played by Drew Barrymore
and Debbie Pazard.
Well, that's Jason. That's a different I think that's a different area
of this of this hypothetical part. OK.
Well, they're all in there.
Yeah, you have you have your opportunity to meet all the Batman forever base.
Yeah. And then a different area where you just go up to the tube
where Nora is being frozen and you get to say Nora
as you're holding your hand against the tube.
That's a different thing. That's a different part.
Insert a diamond that saves her,
that like turns into a cure, like, all right, you put it in
and then like a bunch of tubes go by and then trip, trip, trip.
She's cured.
Yeah, so that's all these are all great ideas.
Yeah. The cure Nora experience.
People are dying for it.
Let's merge as many companies as we need to in order to make this happen.
Sounds good to me.
I guess we all survive podcast the ride Batman.
The rides edition.
Boy, hey, that was pretty tidy.
That could have been a lot crazier.
We still got to explore everything and we got to, you know, hey,
we got some stuff off our chest about our parents that I think Dr.
Chase Meridian would be quite interested.
They did not get into the water stunt shows and we'll have to get to those
at another time.
Obviously, everyone's going to tell us we missed a big part of Batman theme park
and you will tell us online.
Do not tell us in the gripes.
We don't care about those anymore. Tell us on Twitter.
Turn that show yourself.
Gripes is condemned like the like Arkham.
I heard locking it up.
Yeah. So you know what?
Let us know if we if we missed something
that you really like in Batman theme park lore,
please tell us on social media using your names
on Twitter, Facebook or Instagram.
Could email us at podcast, the right at Gmail dot com.
And hey, for three bonus episodes every month, you can subscribe to podcast
through the second gate at Patreon dot com slash podcast, the ride.
And yeah, which one are you?
We're all going to watch one tonight.
Now, what's it going to be?
Is it an episode of the show?
Is it just are we going to hang out with sugar and spice again?
I have been really wanting to do.
I have I feel like I've been really wanting to watch the 66
Batman movie again and watched in a year or two.
So that might be the next Batman thing I watch.
I could watch a Batman movie every day, I think, and that gets sick of it.
I think I said this earlier in the pandemic
that I was watching Batman forever a lot.
It's in the longer it goes.
All right, we're back around to that one.
It's Batman forever time again. Yeah.
I think I'll watch the weird, you know, the weird like wrestling promo or something.
I forget what it is where Adam West like post the series.
I mean, am I crazy that it culminates in him?
Some wrestler or somebody says something weird him.
And then he's all over. Oh, it's Jerry Lawler. Wow.
There's some reason why
Adam West in costume is to say, I've heard of your box.
I don't know why or what it is.
I don't know what leads to that, but I think that's what I'm going to watch.
Yeah, Jason, have you seen that clip?
No, I haven't. You said that to me.
All right. Well, do you want to just play it right now? Yeah.
Let's go out on that box part.
I think it's this.
I'll have to edit it if it goes this.
Well, just find the BIA, find the best part, but we'll just watch all together.
Thanks for listening.
Take it away, Adam and Jerry.
Well, you know, I've heard he's had his troubles with the Joker
and the Penguin and Mr.
Freeze, but he hadn't handled the king yet.
And I got somebody in a box that I'm going to bring out here.
Usually allies, not adversaries.
Joker look like Mickey Mouse.
I can tell you that I've heard about your box.
But I want to say that that costume that you're wearing,
if you are indeed the evil king of Memphis,
has been stolen from a friend of mine, soup.
Superman, I call him soup.
And I think that Spider-Man, Spidey Baby would probably object to.
Excuse me. By the way, looking at you, I don't think it's too late for you.
I think it's possibly.
If you change some of your habits, some of your methods of wrestling,
if you used your left and right turn indicator in your car.
Did other things that.
People normally do when they're polite and courteous,
and you weren't such a naughty, mean person, it wouldn't be too late for you.
I think maybe we we better settle this elsewhere.
And again, both of you are going to be at the Frank in here anyway.
Both of you are going to be down at the Cook Convention Center
at the car show all this weekend, and maybe you can settle it there.
Batman Prisic coming by and thank you very much.
He's not a nice man. No, he is not.
This has been a Forever Dog Production,
executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Bohm, Joe Silio and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify
or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news by following us on Twitter
and Instagram at Forever Dog Team and liking our page on Facebook.