Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, The Second Gate, where today we will unveil PTR Forward, a new
proposal that puts forth an initiative that might shape the future of Podcast The Ride.
My name is Mike Carlson, joining me as always, Jason Sheridan.
Michael, I'm feeling very interactive, very immersive, and very mixed use today.
Great, that's exactly what we need to be feeling.
Scott Gairdner here also.
That's right, and I couldn't be more excited about zoning changes.
We're going to rezone the hell out of this podcast, out of this second gate.
It's going to be, as Jason said, we're going to really mix up the uses over here.
What I want to propose for the podcast is I want the audience to sign off on approval that
Scott and I can talk about classic rock and roll more.
I want them to approve us doing that.
I want to be able to comfortably talk 50% of an episode at a certain point about
just maybe the guitar riff in Let Me Roll It from Wings, from the Wings album,
Band on the Run.
I want to talk about that.
It's a great riff.
I want to talk about it at length.
Yeah, I've never gotten to really air my full thoughts on how Kevin Cronin from
REO Speedwagon is a little weirdo.
I think it's going to take at least an hour and a half for me to get that all out.
Yeah, so that's just one of the things I'd like the audience to sign off on.
Jason, do you have anything you'd like the audience to approve as far as what you
want to talk about on the show going forward?
Oh, that's a great question, Michael.
You know, if you guys go all in on the classic rock stuff, I can snooze a little
and then chime in with the one thing where it's like, I have that album, I have that album.
Let me.
I like the single.
And then we move on.
I want to make it so that you can nap while doing content that people pay for.
Like a fugue state where I'm not like totally out of it, where like I can jump
into action if needed.
But will the listener approve Jason doing a lot less work and putting a lot less
effort into the podcast?
That's what he wants.
Will you approve it?
Will you sign off?
The Board of Listeners, the official Board of Listeners will sign off on all of this
eventually.
My good boy, good student anxiety would never let me get away with it.
All right.
Fine.
Well, then you have to think of your proposals that we put forth to the listener board.
OK.
And it doesn't have to be now.
Because we owe it.
No, we owe it in three years.
So we have three years to come up with the proposal.
Yeah, we owe the proposal in three years and we won't enact whatever changes we're
talking about for probably another five to ten years.
That's when the changes will take place.
They may never happen.
They might never end up happening.
Right.
We're talking today about things that might never happen.
Yes.
But there were photos released of what if they did.
So what we're going to do is talk about concept art and a map about a bunch of things that
Disneyland might do, but they might not.
So it's very relevant in terms of it all happened this week, but potentially the most
irrelevant episode if none of it happens.
Yes.
And we've talked about things that didn't happen before.
We certainly talked about the proposal for this giant, ugly hotel that they were going
to build where the Rainforest Cafe and the ESPN Zone sit right now in downtown Disney.
That is not happening.
No, but it is relevant to today's episode.
It absolutely is.
I'm just saying there are definitely pockets of irrelevancy.
We thought for a while talking about Epic Universe would be irrelevant, but now it
looks like that's going to proceed and they're going to restart construction.
Yeah, but Disneyland Forward, you know, no details, no specifics, just vibes.
They're vibing down in Anaheim.
They've got a handout.
We got a bunch of, they released a bunch of graphics and like one sheets.
And then there's a website that turns those handouts into like six web pages that just
kind of flow into each other.
Yeah.
So if you don't know what we're talking about, we're basically, Disney a couple days
ago, put forth a proposal called Disneyland Forward, which is just as Jason is saying,
all of these pictures and info and pamphlet information, basically asking the Anaheim
government to allow them to rezone like existing land that Disney owns.
So basically saying, hey, we want to be able to in the future have the ability to make
new rides in places that are now a parking lot, make new shopping malls in places that are a
parking lot and basically do whatever we want with the land we have in Anaheim.
We want you to sort of blanket sign off on that.
And to entice you, we're going to show you all
sorts of fancy little pictures that aren't so specific to what we might build.
But you can see how cool it would be if, oh, if there were four new giant lands kind of
hanging around the Paradise Pier at Disneyland Hotel.
Yeah, correct.
The how this came to me when I heard about all this.
OK, so a couple of days, the day that this all dropped, just various things work and baby
a lot was going on and they really knocked me on my ass.
And I was trying to nap and I settled down for a nap and then got a text from you guys that when the
info was different, this was not about zoning at the time.
When this all came out, there was a headline that essentially said Disneyland announces
Third Gate.
And I'm like, what?
I was I was mad a little bit.
I wanted I needed this nap so much that I'm like, I can't get this news, this earth shattering news
for me and the pie.
I'm like furious that there is a possibility of a third gate, not now a third gate.
Yeah.
And then as days of even as that specific day went on, it became clear.
No, no, no, this is not certainly not that there is not a third gate and there may not be.
What we might actually be talking about is expansions of Disneyland and California Adventure.
And mainly, yes, it is all about zoning.
We want to be able to not say this big chunk of land is all hotel.
We want to be able to like mix in a bunch of theme park, every possible square foot next to the hotels.
Everything that's a parking lot at Disneyland currently would become a theme park.
Yeah.
Well, I from my angle, what I saw, I saw Carly post the O.
C.
Register article.
I read the article.
I made a joke about it.
And then after that, I walked away from my computer.
I came back to a text from Mike who sent a different websites write up about it.
And he went, is this a joke?
And I went, I don't think so.
The newspapers have it.
So I was sent that article by friend of the show, Matt Cardona.
Yes.
And he and I said, oh, my God.
And I was like, I was just as frantic as you would imagine anyone who does a podcast about this would feel.
And I think I sent it to you.
I sent it to maybe one other person.
I probably yelled at Lindsay from the other room, like, get in here now.
And then I clicked on the article again and they had changed the headline almost immediately to something much more vague, something much less like exciting sounding.
Because I think they realized, OK, maybe not a third gate.
It looks like it's expansion.
Now, there's still people saying they're not official.
Since there's nothing concrete here, nothing says you couldn't just build a third gate that way.
It's kind of odd, but it's not impossible that that could be its own thing as well.
Well, I think the whole thing's kind of I mean, one thing that rubbed me in an odd way is that, yeah, these these expansions,
which seem to involve like bridge or pathway, like essentially they're building bottlenecks to transport you to these new expanded lands,
which appear to connect to Disneyland and connect to California Adventure and surround the Paradise Beer Hotel and the Disneyland Hotel.
So part of what would have to make that to get this to happen, they would have to surround three hundred and four hundred dollar a night hotel rooms
with construct multi-year long, incredibly loud construction projects.
Yes, that is 100 percent correct.
What you're saying, which doesn't sound ideal.
It's not.
But they've done it before.
I mean, if they tore the whole pool area apart, even like, yeah, do some of the new parking situations, it's definitely happened.
And the other thing is people will keep paying for the hotels and not change their habits at all and they will not lose any business whatsoever.
That's true.
If you've stayed at the Disneyland Hotel and the Grand California,
you really get a glimpse of what how far soundproofing has come between a hotel built a long time ago and a hotel built in 1999, 2000.
Oh, yeah.
Would that a like monorail runs through all the time?
Yeah.
You don't hear it at all.
Yeah, you don't really notice it.
But like, oh, the Disneyland Hotel, every room kind of connects to each other.
If you use those dividers with the two doors, you can kind of hear everyone getting ready in the morning.
Very good.
Interesting.
That's a real part of the theme park experience, though, in general.
And anytime I've been to Disney World, I felt it in Tokyo that you're like, a good night's rest is probably not in the game because you will hear families scurrying down the hallway at six in the morning.
Yes.
That's just that's that's part of doing it, I suppose.
That's true.
I mean, if you really take advantage of everything, you're kind of exhausted at the end of the day.
So you sleep like the dead.
But yeah, you'll hear everyone making it to the elevator.
Yeah.
When I saw this, I saw the proposal, we'll talk we'll get into this as far as at least what they're showing on these pamphlets.
I do think this is probably their ultimate idea.
I don't think it's obviously finalized, but I do think this is kind of the gist of what they're thinking maybe in the next decade.
But I wanted to say, remember back to when we interviewed Mr.
Tony Baxter and he said, you know, I was just in a meeting and at Disney and I don't think people know how much land there actually is to be developed still for Disneyland.
And I have to wonder if this is the land they were showing, they showing in this presentation, or if there's other secret land, we're not even thinking when we look at the map.
I thought this exactly like, is this what Tony was alluding to?
You never think about this.
Oh, yeah.
All those parking lots could be you just never think because it's across the street.
You have to walk across the street and you don't think about that.
They're out there become weird bridges that take you over Disneyland Drive to more Disneyland.
You think Disneyland is all contained in the train tracks, but Star Wars already proved that doesn't have to be true.
California Adventure has a shape that makes no sense anyway.
And you know what all this would be if now Disneyland has weird like little island parts of the parks.
Disneyland now would be Universal Hollywood with the Starway, like the bizarre layout where you have to go down a bunch of escalators to get to less than half of the park.
That's kind of what this would be, but better.
Probably those bridges are going to be fine and well landscaped.
And if you look at the art, so yeah, basically the way it is on the art is that there are two like islands essentially, and one is in the now downtown Disney parking.
Like one of the Disneyland expansion would be in the downtown Disney parking right now, which is not a parking garage.
It's just a flat lot.
And then the Paradise Pier parking would be the California Adventure expansion.
And they're both.
Yeah, they would have to be accessed if you're in the main park from some sort of bridge because there's a road there.
But in the art, they're also showing a second Esplanade.
Yes.
Notice this on the Toy Story lot.
Is that what you're saying?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Yeah.
Okay.
Between I see what you're saying, but the Toy Story lot does come into play.
It does.
But that's a whole another thing.
Yeah.
So yeah, there would be a second Esplanade, which is the entrance, entrance area by Disneyland, California Adventure.
There would be a second one in front of the Disneyland Hotel.
So right now where ESPN Zone, that would be another separate entrance.
So you could enter the new areas and then go over the bridge into the sort of main part of both parks after you've seen the new stuff.
Yeah.
It would be just like the one that exists currently where you go one way and it's Disneyland, you go one way and it's California Adventure.
The exact set like a mini Esplanade.
And that I think is why it can't be a third gate because if all of that land in front of the hotel was pure theme park, then Disneyland Hotel is boxed in.
Right?
How do you get to it?
But with this, with this entrance plaza, now you step out from your room and are just immediately in one of two theme parks and Downtown Disney remains as is.
Thank God.
That's the big headline that nothing will change about Downtown Disney.
Hopefully, especially not the fonts.
Everything will remain intact.
And well, I mean, the stuff that's already been closed will probably go, will keep, obviously that's going to stay closed because that's where the Esplanade will probably be.
I mean, like that second Starbucks might be going away.
I'm sure they're demolishing the movie theater and Sugar Boo is probably not going to this world.
No, cancel it.
I'm not a supporter of Disneyland Forward.
I want my inspirational tarps.
I apologize for bringing that in.
And the soap, that secret soap store, I think has to go probably.
Yeah, might have to stock up.
I like that soap store.
Listeners, if you want to follow like what we probably will talk about the most, what we can devise from these diagrams and the concept art, go to DisneylandForward.
com.
Click the tab, the drop down tab called possibilities.
And that is the big ticket on this website because there's timelines of how Disneyland got here.
There's limitations of what they have now.
There's a pen, essentially like, look at all this cool stuff we're building in the rest of the world.
But the possibilities tab is where like the meat of it is.
And then there's a leading together tab and that has all the buzzwords that a forward thinking city council wants to hear.
Union contractors, diversity hiring, environmentally conscious construction, like good paying jobs.
That's all on its own tab.
Like that's for the residents and for the city council.
But possibilities is where the stuff is.
Why did they list all that stuff and then leave in where they said blah, blah, blah, you get the picture?
Yeah.
It's almost like they didn't care about putting that stuff in.
Yeah, they did not.
They did not say good paying jobs.
If Bernie Sanders is 90 and comes and yells at us again.
I would like him to come down and supervise some of the construction.
Yeah.
When he's 90.
It'd be nice to see him on a ride.
Be nice to get a photo of him on Splash Mountain or something.
Or recreate the Billy Corgan Big Thunder.
Oh, yeah.
I smell Bernie's next meme.
That's right.
That's where I was going with that.
He's wearing the same jacket and the gloves on Big Thunder Mountain.
He did it again.
In the middle of summer.
So I guess let's keep talking about this area.
Well, let's pull up the art maybe.
Mike, you decide.
You take us where you want us to go.
Well, yeah.
Let's bring up the art since we're talking about this here anyway.
Yeah.
Hold on.
But I think that the map is also fascinating.
While the more fleshed out concept art is cool, the map unlocks many keys as well.
Well, the map is different.
This is the piece of nice looking pro-mart that's showing you the majority of changes will be, obviously, at this side, we were saying, by the hotels, by these two hotels.
And Jason, this is what I was saying.
The esplanade would be right here.
Right.
Okay.
Yeah.
I see.
Where the monorail currently lands.
That's not changing.
We're not changing the station.
So now the monorail delivers you right to the door of the other place where you enter parks.
And Mike, I actually have that.
I have that same image and I doodled on top of it, which I what I think is happening.
Well, then that's going to have to be the version.
Well, sure.
You tell us straight.
Like a sports cast.
Yeah.
I.
Okay.
Let me see if this works.
So here is the circle.
Stars, circles.
I figured out how to draw in screen grab so that it was a straight line and not a horrifying murder line.
So this one at the left, this circle, this is the entry from California Adventure into this new area.
This oval is the entry from Disneyland Park into this area.
And the two stars are the Paradise Pier Hotel and the Disneyland Hotel.
This building right here is actually, I believe, the parking garage for the Paradise Pier Hotel.
What they're going to claim for this, what land they're going to take back is the symbol lot, the downtown Disney lot and the cast member parking lot over here.
Right.
Because the Disneyland Hotel still has its parking garage right here.
Yeah.
Kind of behind it.
Right.
And then also the pedestrian.
I was trying to figure out where's the pedestrian bridge from the Pixar Pals parking garage as well.
Is that in the art?
Well, I so I also grabbed the Google Maps satellite view and drew what I think is the pathways.
So here's the website diagram with the pathway and the land does follow the shape.
So it's a fun game of what's expendable in California Adventure.
And the answer is probably Paradise Gardens Park.
I think so.
But isn't there an opening by the OK, like probably where this new entrance would be is just between the end of and credit coaster.
And maybe there's a way to only kill half of Paradise Gardens Park or none.
Yeah.
But it is between there either way.
It's definitely that it's just like if anything goes because they have to create so much space for people to walk through.
Yeah, it's going to have to be an elevated thing to connect.
They just put a big staircase up and not get rid of a lot of the park.
I mean, it's going to go over.
Do much.
I don't think and I, you know, I'll say this.
I'm not going to be sad.
I mean, I go get water there sometimes.
But besides that, that can go.
That's OK.
Mm hmm.
It's better than losing a ride.
Well, yeah, no, I agree.
So, yeah, that's the entrance there.
I assume unless they're going to go like underground or something, which would be cool.
But I assume it'll just be like, you know, what you're walking over the street, much like the the walkway they built over on Lankersham
for to get you from the one side of the street by the train or the subway to Universal Studios.
There's like an elevated platform you walk across or like Vegas.
It's it'll be like hopefully like where there's escalators and elevators unless they find a way to do they can't like,
no, I guess the street is street level.
They can't do it like downtown Disney where it goes under the bridge.
Right.
Yeah, I think they would need to keep Disneyland Drive and build above it.
Because the the Magic Kingdom expansion, which we're looking at here,
it also appears to go above Disneyland Drive just south of Magic Way.
So here you can look at the Disneyland expansion.
Clearly, the Stitch parking lot does not appear to be long for this world.
And the closest part of the Magic, not the Magic Kingdom.
I mean, I guess the Magic Kingdom of Disneyland Park.
It's called Disneyland Disneyland.
That's the name.
But if you go straight ahead from if you were to run across that parking lot
and run straight forward into Disneyland, you hit critter country.
And I think you can lose a lot of that for a walkway.
You think maybe what you're saying is you think that where you get across the street will get rid of not the Winnie the Pooh ride,
but all of the stores and everything near it.
Like you would leave where currently there is a Winnie the Pooh store would now be a pathway that gets you over across the street to more Disneyland.
I think that's definitely likely.
And I think you could also lose that Pooh ride.
Like I think anything that's not like Splash Mountain is not going to go.
They talked about how they're going to get rid of Pooh.
They don't have to get rid of Pooh.
I will say this.
I go in the Pooh gift shop way more than I go on the Pooh ride.
I like that gift shop.
You're sad to lose the gift shop.
I am sad to lose that gift shop, but I think you're right.
I think that's going to have to be the spot where it starts there.
Wait a minute, though.
I'm going to bring this map back up because I had a different idea.
Like what I saw and maybe this doesn't line up with what you're saying, Jason.
But like to me, I look at to me, this seems like lower.
It seems like in kind of the lower third of Disneyland,
I think it's possible that actually where you exit, where you'll go to the new area is maybe between the Haunted Mansion and Pirates.
That like maybe some maybe the train station comes out.
I might again, I might be reading this wrong, but it seems like potentially a viable place to do it.
I don't know how you get over under the train tracks, but right.
Interesting.
I think when I was the Google Maps, I can bring up the Google Maps.
Bring Google Maps.
Let's solve this once and for all.
Scott, I know what you're saying on the Google Maps.
The Haunted Mansion ride show building is just so big.
Like I think to me, it seemed like I don't know.
I was just kind of eyeballing those charts.
So no, you might you might be right.
It's hard to say.
Yeah.
And listener, I don't know.
Look, pull up your own.
Right.
We're consulting them.
We'll put the we'll tweet it.
There'll be a map and there'll be concept art and you'll you'll get through it.
Yeah.
Or you'll put on another episode.
You might just put on another episode while we struggle through this.
So you're Scott, you're thinking like here.
Maybe.
Like like here's zoom in further if you can.
Like, OK, so and go a little bit lower right at the the the very corner of the park.
There's two big show buildings.
The one you're currently pointing to is Pirates and up there is Haunted Mansion.
I think between those two, maybe there's enough space to build this little bridge.
But although that goes right next to the monorail track, which they're not going to move.
So maybe it would have to be a little country exit.
It would have to be kind of like maybe move like this unless they get rid of this build.
Like it would have to go like this way.
A little curve.
But that might be.
Don't you feel like all of this like this is not good for employees, I feel like.
No.
Park really far away.
So much every bit of backstage space is gone.
This is going to make it really complicated to work there.
Yeah.
That keeps happening.
They they demolished a building.
They're building Mickey and Minnie's Runaway Railway and they had to demolish a building that was being used for cast member stuff.
And like they have to like, I think they have to move the horses in.
Correct me if I'm wrong, but like horses used to be able to be like stored right behind like where Galaxy's Edge is.
But I believe that's not the case anymore.
I think they have to like bring the horses from a farther away distance.
So that's that's going to keep happening.
They are talking about doing the parking garage.
OK, so a couple of projects ago that didn't happen, they were going to do a parking garage on the other side of Harbor.
And Anaheim was very upset with them because the bridge that would have connected that parking garage to Disneyland would block off access to local businesses.
And they didn't like that.
And Disney, instead of just saying, yeah, all right, here you can go to local businesses.
They said, no, fuck off.
And they've learned they've learned from that because that's on the website, too.
Yes, that is mentioned.
The concept art is reused.
It's mentioned and it goes out of its way to mention working with local businesses and politicians to like the area, the Harvard area hotels and businesses.
They go out of their way to mention if we'll try again.
Well, it feels like the whole thing is kind of like like sort of kissing Anaheim's ass and kissing the local businesses as because this is all couched kind of in.
Look, it's been a tough year for everybody.
We had to shut down COVID-19.
We have to think about how to go forward, move forward Disneyland forward.
And the way is for you to let us put up whatever we want.
And that's going to save your city and all the restaurants or whatever.
Yeah.
Which I don't know, they might have something.
Although I do think just reopening regular Disneyland will go a long way.
That said, look, I don't know how you guys, but I want every bit of this to happen.
I am thrilled.
I want every single square foot that they're proposing to happen.
Well, I was trying to look I I was trying to figure out like sneakiness.
What's the sneakiness here for Disney?
Because there's always got to be something right.
So I can't really see anything because I think they still have to get a proposal.
Like I think I saw some chatter of like, oh, you know, Anaheim could approve Disney to zone anything because they basically they want to be able to build, as I said, a hotel, a restaurant or ride anywhere on the land they have.
They want to blanket freedom to do it.
But I think they also need further approvals then once that happens, because I saw some people saying, well, they get the approval and then Disney just builds a bunch of hotels and restaurants and never builds another like cool new ride on this land, which I guess is possible.
But don't they then have to get more approvals once they've sort of just gotten this blanket approval?
I could be wrong unless that unless in twenty twenty three, their proposal is going to have all the rides, all the restaurants, and it's going to be a fully comprehensive.
And maybe that's what they're talking about doing.
Yeah, I mean, it's very funny.
There is a big, bold section of the website that says and Disneyland is not looking for any more tax breaks.
We're not looking for any more public funding like they go out of the way to go like this is not this is a play, but this isn't the play you're assuming it is.
Yeah, I I'm cautiously optimistic that this is just neutral.
I mean, it's good for us if there's no more rides, obviously, but I don't want it to like, you know, hamper the city or whatever anymore than Disney.
I mean, Disney helps, but also, you know, sucks resources and they'll have tax deals in places.
But I I want to think this is maybe just sort of a neutral neutral to slightly good thing for it.
But somebody feel free to correct me if they've noticed some weirdness.
Nobody immediately had the argument of why this is bad.
I feel like somebody would have thought of it real fast.
I think what if it's just good?
Maybe it's just good.
Here, Mike, pull that concept back up because let's talk about it like creatively and almost.
We're actually really the map maybe shows you more.
But like what can we glean from this?
What do we know?
I think they like they left a lot of Easter eggs in this map and people noticed the Easter eggs on Twitter.
Again, this they're just showing hypothetical.
Here's rides we could do.
But some of them are so specific.
Some of them are things that exist already in other parks.
And it really gets you thinking and wondering and excited about really cool stuff that might be thrown next to that hotel over there.
First, let me say if just looking at this overhead art, California Adventure gets three lands of some kind, maybe more.
And Disneyland gets one.
Yeah, yeah.
So just the way it breaks down is that the Esplanade is right here.
So this is a land for California Adventure.
These are all California Adventure.
And then there's one big one for Disneyland.
So I just want to say that it seems like California Adventure might benefit more if all of this goes forward.
Very lucky.
That's true.
Yeah.
Well, look, it's smaller to begin with, but this would at least catch it up in terms of acreage or make it go over.
This thing we keep harping on that California Adventure is like the second best park in the world.
I think this does this bump it up to one.
I don't know if we beat Disney Sea with it, but I don't know.
But speaking of Disney Sea, they're talking about, as you were saying, types of lands they're building over there, over in Tokyo Disneyland.
Yeah.
And I think seemingly what that might be is less likely to be the Tokyo specific IP.
I don't think we're suddenly getting 20 years later or more a journey to the center of the Earth or the volcano or the aqua topia.
I don't think that's going to be it.
I feel like that Disneyland stuff up there on the right of this photo, I think it might be the new stuff going into Disney Sea, which is very IP.
It's frozen, it's tangled, and it's Peter Pan.
Peter Pan.
So again, I have my questions about Disneyland forward.
I don't know if I want to go Disneyland forward.
Yeah.
And they mentioned, somebody mentioned this, when they were doing the presentation.
Is it in the pamphlet or was somebody just like a PR person talking about those?
Because they mentioned those are things that likely could go.
Things like this could appear in this expansion, they were saying.
Well, that's and it I think it's like, here's what we're doing already in the park.
And here's what we're doing at our parks around the world.
And it kind of that kind of goes back to someone posted.
I sent you guys someone preserved like a similar, a very similar website to this from like 99 2000 2001 of like, and here's what could come after California Adventure.
And they're showing what they have built recently and they're showing what is now the Toy Story lot.
They literally lay lit a third Disney park and then they label a chunk neck on the east side of Disneyland future parking.
So they were doing same shit, same shit.
Yeah.
So I think a lot of that might have been like because I remember always hearing the rumor of a coaster based villains park.
But I don't know if any they didn't say anything.
They didn't know this website is one page like you can you can read it in three minutes and all you could do back then.
That's all you could do back then.
But it is very much the 2000 equivalent to a 2021 website where like at the bottom of each page, it just takes you to the next page.
And if you laid it all out, it would be six printed out pieces of paper.
It would be a square space.
They put up a square space.
They put out a square.
Yeah, they put out they put out a PowerPoint deck that also works as handouts to the executives who are simultaneously looking at their print out and then looking up at a screen in a conference room.
But it works for me because it has some vague what rides might be.
And then look in all of this, the OK, you know, the main thing is if they get their way and any of this happens, no matter what the individual rides are, we're getting a major influx of fake rocks onto the Disney property.
That's like all there is.
And they need it.
They need like backdrops and facades to block the fact that there's like a house, you know, 10 feet away from some of these new attractions.
Yes, that struck me immediately is how much how many fake rocks there were in this art.
It's like every that's like, yeah, as you're saying, all there is, like, I guess maybe on the on the Disneyland side of things is the least in the in the art on this picture.
There's some there's like and where maybe I'm seeing like potential volcanoes.
I'm no fan of the character Peter Pan, but I but a Never Neverland mountain range with a nice lagoon around it.
That looks pretty good if that's one of the things that's happening.
And people have certainly mentioned the possibility that some of the fake some of the best fake rocks around that being the world of Pandora might be.
This might be our way that we get Pandora.
Yeah, Disneyland.
That is possible.
Yeah, a couple of the other they also mentioned the Zootopia land they're building in Shanghai as well as a possibility, which I think has less mountains and more city type things.
But yeah, all the stuff is on the table.
I have, of course, also seen people speculate about Wakanda.
Yes.
Yeah, because one of the overhead drawings.
Yeah, and I don't have a high up, but the one that you when you first go into the new Esplanade and you take a left.
Yeah, people here.
If you look on the adjacent.
Yeah, let me take over.
I have it.
So I think I saw Freddie Chambers caught it first on Twitter.
I'm about to Freddie from Batu and so this area.
Let me I drew on it here.
OK, so here's Paradise Pier Hotel and this oval is appears to be an overhead drawing of like the big Black Panther statue that is in Wakanda.
And then this circle just southwest of it, it looks appears to be the Hallelujah Mountains, the floating mountains in Pandora.
Yeah, yeah, and a big old show building that probably that looks very like the space that would be required for flight of passage.
Yeah.
Does anything else look familiar?
Like, what's this bit?
What's this like Matterhorn looking thing that a bunch of tracks are going through that looks great.
Yeah, whatever it is.
It's interesting because on the other art.
So if you're looking at the main art, it's the thing on the left for California Adventure on that other art that looks like Peter Pan to me.
The Peter the promo art for the Tokyo Peter Pan expansion.
Yes, you agree.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
But there's no reason that couldn't be.
I mean, it makes more sense in Disneyland, but I guess you could do it in California Adventure because California Adventure is whatever at this point.
But this looks like because there's white and it's snowy.
This looks like it could be an Arendelle.
This looks like it could be a frozen.
Oh, but there's not a frozen stone here.
There's not a ton of like there's not a ton of snow.
I think in a lot of this stuff.
There's a little white on top of the mountain.
But right now saying what else is it has a mountain that's snowy right now.
That's true.
It's got like is this a coaster?
Maybe Carly was talking about the possibility of a frozen coaster.
And that sounds better than the boat ride that's there.
And is that what we're looking at?
Maybe I think that's what we're looking at here.
And I think obviously Disney knows what they're doing.
They're not going to.
These images are not the same.
This overhead thing in the promo art are not the same things because they don't have the same details in them.
So I'm sure there's a scenario where they put frozen right there.
There's a scenario where they put that Peter Pan land there.
I'm sure it's flexible, but it makes sense.
I mean, it makes sense because they've been trying to get a big presence of a very popular movie in the parks for a while now.
Yeah.
And then, of course, you got to see on the other side of Disneyland and the other side of the Esplanade, possible new parking.
The dream will not die.
The dream of decades now.
Yes.
And that's the real thrill.
I mean, that's what we're, you know, we just we need this garage.
Otherwise, we can't have Nick Weiger back.
He's a great guy and a good guest, and we'd love to have him on more, but we're stuck now.
So we might not have we might not be able to have Weiger on for another like 15 years.
Yeah, this gets built.
I will say the other the orange part here, the Disneyland.
This feels like maybe Zootopia partly.
I can't tell exactly that.
It's it's yeah, it's very orange colored in the map that we're looking at if you're looking at a visual key here.
And yeah, I don't know.
It's the most question mark for me.
Okay.
Yeah.
So yeah, they mention all those things.
I think they probably wouldn't.
I've heard for a while they've like thought about putting Wakanda somewhere, whether it's like Animal Kingdom or an Epcot inside Wonders of Life is rumored for a while.
Yeah, that was not happening now, but.
So that would make sense to do something like that.
And I assume they probably wouldn't tease a new land yet.
Obviously, they just said things that existed.
I will say this.
My first thought when I saw Third Gate announced at Disneyland before people had amended that headline was my first thought was, oh, my goodness.
Third Gate means we'll at least get one original ride.
That was the first thing I thought of because that's what we always that's what I always say is I feel like we're not going to get an original Imagineer ride until there's a full Third Gate.
And they have like the space to go.
All right, we'll let the Imagineers do one creative thing.
Because you have to, just to fill the space.
Right.
Yeah.
But I am less optimistic now that this is all just expansion that we would get like a Mystic Manor type ride or any sort of classic kind of dark ride from Disney history.
Well, I think I think some of these diagrams, you got to think how much of that was the directive of like, put some Easter eggs in there, get the Internet talking and how much was like, just draw a bunch of, you know, let's just draw a bunch of stuff that could kind of be.
Yeah, some of it's just kind of generically landscaping.
Some of it's kind of generic water bodies, you know, and then just shapes of buildings.
It's still possible what I'm saying, but I was thinking, oh, that probably takes the chances down.
That probably the percentage of a chance that we'll get like an original new thing is probably lower now.
But I could be wrong.
I hope I'm wrong.
What you're saying?
Yeah, yeah, I'm not sure.
Like in order to even have a theme for a whole third theme park, like there would have to be original IP to to flesh it out.
Yeah, it just be.
And here's some ABC shows and stuff.
Maker Studios.
What else do they own?
Maker, yeah.
Yeah, so so it'll be interesting.
I'm sure obviously we talked about a lot of timing is everything when it comes to rides just because of the company's wanting to build of the company has enough money.
What movie was popular in merchandise sales in the last so many years?
We know Mr.
Chaypeck is big on that type of thing.
So I would love to think that the sky is really the limit to here with as far as like maybe like an alien ride or something.
Now that they have Fox, like could we do a Simpsons land back here?
Because Simpsons is going to run out as far as our contract universal by I think 2028 and they either need to strike up a new deal or go away.
Like I would like to think there's some curveballs coming and Wakanda is obviously a curveball.
So it's interesting.
It's exciting.
There seems to be like four ish four and a half five big plots of land that could be their own kind of spaces, be their own thing.
Yeah, I think I'd be deflated if it was different Simpsons.
I think that'd be unless it's like such a mind blow of a different thing.
Yeah, Simpsons world to pull from.
Yeah.
But what if it's like a more of a dark classic dark ride with Simpsons animatronics?
Yeah, that's pretty good.
Yeah, if they're real.
But yeah, it would feel like a little bit of a copy unless yeah, unless they really like set out to kick the ass of universal and like developed a galaxy's edge level Springfield.
He's sort of like the like a new dad really wanting to kick the old dad in the teeth and like just like give the kid the most kick ass life ever.
Yeah, well, he's going to be courtside at the Lakers and I'm going to take him in a real jet.
What'd you ever do?
Or or they build itchy and scratchy land or something.
They build a little scratchy land.
That sounds good.
That sounds really good.
But I doubt they're going to do that.
I'm just saying I wonder I wonder if there's any chance we get something crazy like an alien's ride or something.
That's a good I had not brought Fox into consideration here.
Is that the big what is up Fox wise that I feel like Ice Age always comes up.
But I don't know about Ice Age.
Why are we doing?
Why would we do a bunch of Ice Age?
Like what is the Fox stuff that you go and aliens of great example.
But you know, do we need a night at the museum ride?
I don't know if we do.
Well, what's in Fox that we will name Galoo.
You can watch.
You can see Nimgaloo on Disney Plus.
They do have epic.
The two weirdest things when I've been coming through Disney Plus, I was like, oh, Disney Plus is Isle of Dogs.
I forgot about that.
And then they have epic.
And I was like, wait, epic is what Nimgaloo is from.
Yes.
And it is on Disney Plus.
I thought about this more than most people and I have to like remind myself every time.
Like, yeah, what's Nim?
Who's Nim?
What's Nim?
But if I could go to Nim's house, I say I'm going to look at like whatever the biggest show building is on this map.
It's probably Nimgaloo's house.
It's just a walkthrough to meet Nimgaloo.
Yeah, three hour lines.
They have to build so much queue space.
Yeah, because that's going to be longer than flight of passage as far as a wait time.
Yeah, there's nothing Fox.
I mean, there's Predator, there's Alien, there's Die Hard.
I mean, there's stuff that's maybe doesn't.
I mean, Alien lends itself to a theme park ride for sure.
And Predator probably could.
There's something there, too.
But those aren't so popular right now.
I know they're still like talking about doing like a new Alien show with Ridley Scott, who's like, you know, 90 years old, but he keeps going.
He keeps making a movie a year.
So maybe maybe if like Disney plus does an Alien show and it's very popular.
Yeah.
It really is super scary.
I'd be pretty terrified of even just the one scene in the great movie, right?
It was always so scary as a kid.
Yeah, the scariest.
Yeah, so we'll see.
I don't know.
Hey, Marvel's publishing a new series of Aliens comics and it's getting bad reviews.
So maybe they'll turn that into something possible.
Terrible new.
You know, we haven't talked about.
We got to go.
We got to go a little bit east and a little bit south and talk about the weird little little runt land in the Toy Story parking, what is currently a mass vaccination site.
And I hope doesn't have to be for too much longer, but isn't permanently that it seems like they're going to have it all taken care of.
And yeah, so the parking lot that you don't want to be in because then I get stuck on buses and be in the parks later.
Maybe it's going to turn into something.
And this concept art is the most confusing because that land is not a lot.
If they put a full theme park there, that's the smallest on property.
Maybe it's maybe the smallest of any Disney park, so maybe you don't get a full theme park out of it.
Yeah, what they've done here, it kind of looks like some sort of lush vacation club or Disney Springs type environment.
It kind of seems nice.
Oh, they say that out now, like inspired by Disney Springs and like have pictures of Jock Lindsay's hangar bar and stuff.
Oh, OK.
Yeah, that's what I've that's what everyone has been saying.
It's it's like sort of their version of a fancier outdoor mall with restaurants and stores.
And I think somebody even said like if they will like will zone it.
I mean, this actually has been zoned for the third theme park for a long time, but it looks like they're not thinking of that at this point.
But they're saying like, oh, they could throw a ride of some kind in here.
They could put some sort of experience.
To go along with the Disney Springs, I don't know if they will, but that is a possibility.
I mean, I've always liked that idea.
And there's their epic universe.
There's there's talk of that at Epic Universe because Epic Universe is four lands and they all have to be accessed by whatever their version of an Esplanade.
But their Esplanade is basically like City Walk, a fancier City Walk.
But people are speculating that they could they're like could be just rides there, like freestanding rides in the middle of that shopping mall that you could go on.
And who knows if that'll be cut now that a pandemic happened or who knows?
I mean, the literally the language on the website is a new kind of Disney entertainment destination.
This property could be the perfect location to cater to locals, conventioneers, hotel and Disneyland resort guests.
Yeah, I think that because because it's so close to the Anaheim Convention Center, I think they're probably seeing dollar signs as far as you know, you get a bunch of convention goers leaving whatever convention they're at at 6 p.
m.
They walk over there and spend a bunch of money like that makes probably sense to them.
It's just a quick walk over there as opposed to because Disneyland's a little awkward to get to from the Convention Center at this point.
But maybe this is easier in a way.
It looks nice.
I like those little houses.
Can we live there?
Yeah, that's a good question.
I think people have speculated that could be a hotel.
But I'd like to think much like the Americana.
Maybe those are just apartments.
Yeah, I mean, I'm there.
I'm there right away.
Oh, yeah.
Opening.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
We'll we'll get the first set of apartments down there for sure.
Yeah.
Finally, the dream.
Ten thousand dollars a month.
But yeah, we're looking at our new house, gentlemen.
All three of us.
That's right.
Our significant others having left unwilling to have a baby live at Disneyland all the time.
Well, yeah, there you go.
Future PTR pad.
Excited to live with you guys.
And then we can because we're going to have to we're going to need proximity when all of these new lands are open.
There's no choice but to live there.
Yeah, no, it would be.
I wish you know what is the bit aside.
I wish that there were apartments and I wish I was I mean, I wish I was younger in general.
But if I was a younger man with a job, man, would that be a funny bit?
Man, would that be great for like a year to live in the apartments above the new Disney Springs on the former Toy Story lot?
That would be fantastic.
A funny, expensive bit.
Very expensive.
Priciest bit that was ever achieved.
Maybe if maybe if it would happen 10 years ago, though, and Disney wasn't doing as well, the parks, maybe then that would be the time when I could afford it.
Although I had a lot less money probably at that time.
So, yeah, probably not a practical bit.
I agree.
But your only choice is to sneak in to like hide in a bathroom every night and sleep on top of the toilet.
So when they do the checks, they don't see your feet.
And then Disneyland's yours all night.
I believe pro wrestler Terry Funk has talked about he's an older guy now.
He's retired.
Finally, he used to do stunt work in L.
A.
to get his health insurance through SAG.
And he never paid for a hotel room because he had a skeleton key.
You just go room to room in different hotels and see which room would open up with the key.
And then you would just sleep in there.
So it's just the similar thing I would have tried to pull with a skull.
I would have an old fashioned skeleton key or I guess a skeleton key card is what the new version of that is.
Yeah, that's cool.
You definitely want like an old grimy key that looks like a skeleton.
Yeah.
But if the like the kind of thing you would put in the door was in the shape of like a skull and crossbones.
Oh, and like eyes went red once the insertion.
Yeah, that's cool.
That would be cool.
I seeing this like Disney Springs art, I was thinking, come on, throw us a bone and build a new Pleasure Island.
Come on.
Oh, we're just going back to that.
That's interesting.
Pleasure Island 2.
0.
Come on.
Throw us a bone, Disney.
We want the fireworks factory.
Yeah.
Mannequins, mannequins, part two.
Obviously, people are dying for mannequins and eight tracks.
Neon armadillo.
Can you imagine how excited we would be if that's how we would be at all the residents just glaring like Moe walking across the stage at the bachelor auction and a whole pissed off audience like all the residents just like it's like, guys, we're going to build 20 to 30 new bars right in the neck.
Your neck of the woods.
We're like in our mid to late 40s and like we're at mannequins five times a week.
Yeah.
Wearing like just like netting like netting shirts and just like loving it, the loving the lifestyle there.
We're wearing netting shirts like we're like 90s clubbers.
Yeah, like 90s clubbing outfits.
Yeah, like hackers.
We look like Wright said Fred.
Yeah, we look like Wright said Fred and we're there.
Shaped our heads too.
We're like old and we all have kids at that point, but we don't see them a lot because we're at mannequins too much.
What a time to be a lot.
What a great time it would be.
Sorry, sport.
Would love to love to go to the baseball game, but it's it's 80s night and they're going to play.
You got the look and I gotta be there.
Five dollar you call it's at mannequins tonight.
Little little guy.
Sorry.
Scott, Scott, I was looking at our credit card bills.
It appears you've maxed out a card at the Spring Hill Suites, Anaheim.
Please just drive back.
Please just get just get a driver.
Get a designated driver.
Look, I know that I could just get bottles of liquor from a store and bring them in there, but many fridges are so convenient and fun.
And what if I want to spend $500 in tiny vodka bottles every night?
That's my prerogative.
Plus that one time you tried roller skating home from Anaheim and it didn't work.
You were too drunk.
I thought my skills were sharpened from roller constant roller disc going.
My last thought for this whole thing is a concern.
Another concern.
And I'm sure you share the I hate to go out on a down note.
What does all this mean for Tomorrowland?
It means nothing.
I've resigned to it.
I know what's happening.
Yeah, I know that nothing's happening.
I know they're letting it die on the vine.
I mean, I guess if this is some sort of 10 year timeline we're talking about, Tomorrowland could still be on the table.
But wouldn't it have been nice in Disneyland forward to also throw us a bone like we are still going to be doing things in the parks.
Obviously they have to do that, but we still have a timeline as well to build rides in the park.
I guess it doesn't have to be anything they approve.
But it would be nice to see the future a little bit and say Mickey and Minnie's coming in.
Was it next year already or is it 2023?
I think it got pushed.
So it's maybe 2023.
Yeah.
Well, we will build the Avengers e-ticket that still will be coming.
And then, yes, finally we'll do tomorrow.
Like Tomorrowland.
Wouldn't that have been nice and given us a little peace of mind?
I guess.
Yeah, of course.
But I see what's happening.
They're rezoning.
They want everything to be mixed use.
I think in six years Tomorrowland is just is going to be condos.
It's going to be nice, expensive apartments.
And you know what?
Fine.
Just do it.
Get it over with already.
Put it out of its misery.
But could we live in the condos at least?
And if that's the case, then great.
If I have a Space Mountain View room, I'll pay what's an accurate number?
Seven thousand dollars a month.
Yeah, I'll do it.
Probably.
Yeah.
Seems right.
Well, I see that that kind of gives me a good opportunity to jump in.
And I have a little game prepared if you guys like to play getting because I think we're really underselling how much corporate mumbo jumbo is on this website.
How much like marketing speak like a lot of stuff about immersiveness and interactiveness.
So this game is called Real or Fake website.
So I've come up.
I have a bunch of quotes here and you're going to tell me whether these are on the Disneyland Forward website or they are fake.
Oh, wow.
This is like the Walt game we played.
This is very much inspired by the Walt game.
Yes.
OK, great.
Great.
Oh, boy.
Let's we're going to go jargon crazy.
OK.
OK, first up, now is the time to be bold, to dream, to believe and to lead.
That seems like the sentiment of now and of like, let's get out of Covid times.
And I and plus maybe I saw that.
I think it's I think maybe that one's real.
I think I saw it as well and I believe it's real.
That is real.
Correct.
You're both correct.
OK, the second one.
It's a little wordy, but I think.
Can you read it one more time?
Flexibility in use classification will energize and diversify sector growth for the hard hit resort district.
Can you spell it?
The whole sentence?
Yeah, everything.
I think it's real.
Scott.
Yeah, I'll say real.
Sure.
That is fake.
That is nonsense.
That is a bunch of Bud's words that mean nothing.
OK, I guess sector.
I guess they don't use sector.
I'm on the hunt for sectors.
Yeah, we do.
They the term resort district is the official city and Disney term for that that area of Anaheim.
OK, next one.
It's time to look forward.
Time to turn Anaheim into Canaheim.
No, no, no, no.
That can't be real.
That's fake.
OK, yes, that is fake.
Canaheim.
Today, hotel, theme park, retail and dining are all part of one immersive experience.
I saw that.
That's real.
That is.
That's gotta be real.
That's real.
OK.
Yeah.
The next one.
Imagine the hotel of your dreams steps away from the Disney park you've always wished for.
Hmm.
I'm just I'll say fake, not because I smell a rat there, but just, you know, maybe that's the pattern.
I'm going to say fake because I don't remember seeing it.
That is fake.
Yes, I just tried to cram in as many Disney buzzwords as I could.
Imagine dreams, wishes.
OK.
Then this last one.
Walt Disney once said the only thing I like more than a proper execution of an idea is proper planning in order to achieve it.
Fake.
I thought it was going to be the proper execution of a communist.
So if it's not that, then that's a Walt one, too.
That's kind of I'll say fake.
It is fake.
Yes, that one is fake.
Wow.
Well, we had we had Walt practice.
So, you know, yes.
Well, but on the front of this website, they have weaponized a couple of things.
One, they use the Walt Disneyland will never finish.
And then there's a very funny portion of the website.
A lot of people jumped on where they said,
Unfortunately, the addition of more attractions and experiences in the future may be limited under current inflexible planning restrictions unless we remove and replace some treasured rides and attractions at our parks today,
which really has to do it.
Don't do it.
It has the vibe of the national lampoon by this magazine or the dog gets.
Yeah, I mean, it's a very mob.
It's a mob.
Yeah, you wouldn't want to see you when was he on a mission.
Go away, would you?
Be ashamed of something happened to it.
Be ashamed that these ghosts could finally rest, you know.
Yeah.
Come on, and I'm City Council.
You have at least how cold hearted are you?
Well, they're more than you've taken a little boat around.
You don't want to see it die.
We did an episode about the Anaheim politics a while forever ago at this point, and the City Council, I think, is a little bit more right leaning and probably more favorable to Disney than it was at that time.
So I have a feeling I have a feeling they're going to approve this.
Yeah, I think.
Thankfully, that happened already a few years ago, and a steal didn't have to be stopped because, you know, we would have been the Anaheim, the AFBI, the Anaheim FBI.
You would have seen all our faces in the on their Twitter account.
That's a good point.
But if Jason does lose some sort of mayoral bid, it will have been a stolen election for sure.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah, they can't steal it until you run.
I mean, I can regard them all as stolen, but also we haven't filed any paperwork or anything.
So yeah, once we do.
Okay.
Well, you're right.
And once Jason.
Wait, but Jason's the mayor of Disneyland, not Anaheim.
Or wait, was there that thought too?
Are we trying to do or are we just trying to do both?
I think maybe both.
Sure.
I mean, you have to live in Anaheim to be the mayor.
Probably, right?
Probably.
Yeah.
We're heading there, obviously.
If we just get one of those Disney Springs apartments, though.
Oh, yeah, that's true.
Yeah.
Done deal.
Go back and forth like Congress people.
You can sort of like annex.
If you're the mayor of Anaheim, you can say, well, Disneyland's my territory.
That's like as part of like I'll let you build the rides if I am the mayor and I get to walk around with a sash.
Mostly by the sash.
Yeah.
You got a good negotiation tactic.
So all right.
Well, when Jason runs, we will get everything we want.
It'll be Disneyland.
Fast forward as forward as things can possibly be.
And I guess you survived podcast the ride.
The second gate.
Yeah, I don't know.
Here's hoping to, you know, to have the beautiful, the kingdom of Pandora, just a drive away, to have mighty Akrons in our own state.
We can only pray for this.
Yes, that would be a dream.
Well, you know, real quick, what is the number one thing you would like other than like an original IP?
Which land is the number one land you'd want of all the things they're talking about?
Because they also threw Tron in there as well, which I still thought was maybe going in our tomorrow land, but they threw that in as well as a possibility.
I think it's either Pandora or Wakanda.
Like, I think they could do some really cool stuff with place making with Wakanda.
Yeah, maybe I'd say Wakanda because we don't have one yet.
It's tempting.
I mean, I'd like all of them.
I'd like like Seven Dwarfs Mind Trap.
I'd like some of that extra fantasy land stuff that they've been doing.
But yeah, what kind of exciting to think about just because we have what is it?
Yeah, that's probably right.
As far as that's probably my choice as well of the stuff they mentioned other than the Simpsons land, the itching scratchy land.
Yeah, a real itching scratchy land where the rides actually hurt you, where the blade on the way into the restaurant is very sharp.
And Nimgaloo's house.
I just hope this all results in me getting to hug my best friend Nim, whose movie I've never seen and likely never will.
Well, guys, keep it tuned here to the second gate for more bonus content, three episodes every month.
And follow us on all the social media and check the social media if you need visual references and guides and circles and stars, because this one was this was diagram heavy.
But that's a sign of a good episode, right?
Oh, we complicated episode.
Very complicated.
Yeah, that's a good one.
Less jokes, more discussion and like looking at charts.
That's what people want.
We knew it.
We knew this was this is what this was going to be.
But, you know, there's jokey ones and there's zony ones.
I think that's what we promised and delivered.
Yeah, absolutely.
And I do have to say some people did immediately send it to us and go like, can't wait for you guys to talk about it.
So you're getting your wish.
The funniest one was someone sent it and was like, can't wait to hear about this on podcast the ride tomorrow.
It is like Thursday at six o'clock.
If we're recording Thursday at six o'clock, something has gone wrong.
We're scrambling.
So I like the idea that we like do it live at like midnight on Friday morning.
Yeah, we're live.
Yes.
Live broadcasting as you're listening.
Right.
Yeah.
Don't try to skip ahead because it's impossible.
So yeah, yeah.
Sorry we didn't do it on Friday, but here it is.
Yeah, I guess the ride forward.
That's all we can do.
Try to get it out in the week.
And we did.
Hey, thanks for listening, everybody.
New episode in a couple days on the main feed.
We'll see.
We'll listen.
We won't see you then.
Well, you'll be listening to us then.
Bye.