Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the second gate.
McGrew, the mobile gripes response unit.
My name is Mike Carlson, joining me as always,
McGrew member Scott Gerdner.
Yeah, wait, is that an acronym?
What is McGrew?
Yes, it's M-G-R-U, mobile gripes response unit.
Okay, okay, that is the, all right, mobile, all right.
Yeah, I mean, we're not so mobile, we're wired up,
but we could be, just couldn't record.
Yes, I thought about making a but
to make it sound more like McGruff.
I wanted to put M and I needed an M there.
So that's why the M-
We're technically mobile, I'm in a rolling chair.
So yes, I'm playing mobile.
I'm recording in a different room than normal.
So I feel like there's some mobility as well.
And we can still, we can record anywhere we've recorded,
in an empty sports chalet or whatever in the valley before.
So we are somewhat mobile.
Jason Sheridan also part of the team here, are you ready?
I'm ready, yeah, I'm ready now.
You disappointed me with the first answer.
Now I'm with you.
Well, when we first, these gripes first started coming in,
I was, I feel like we've all had our ups and downs
in quarantine, but I feel, right around,
when we first asked for these,
my mental state was very emotional,
like overcome by any slight friction.
It takes everything very personally.
So I read about five and I was like,
I don't know if I can do this episode.
And now I kind of get it a little more,
cause I found some good conversation starter.
Well, yes, when we called or when we were talking
about this, I think I told the audience, I said,
maybe don't make them so mean.
Not everyone listened to that.
A few people decided-
For the most part.
Mostly people, yeah, yeah, yeah.
But I'm saying there were a few in there where you're like,
I don't know, this seems kind of mean.
I don't know.
Maybe you didn't hear me say, no, don't be mean.
But you open yourself up to that.
And I guess you can't be picky with, I mean,
I think we'll show, Mike put this great,
use the phrase, there were people
who understood the assignment.
There are certain ones that really understood
the assignment and there's other ones that are just like,
well, here's my chance to kind of cut them
in the chest a little bit.
Which you know what?
I love your podcast, you dickheads.
Fair enough, you know, anonymity,
you grab people anonymity on the internet
and that's gonna happen.
It was-
I know, we asked, we called for this.
It's amazing it wasn't worse in a way.
Yeah.
It is true, it is true.
It could have been much worse.
We have lovely fans, but it was very funny,
like half a day later when Mike was like,
I'm sorry I suggested this in the group text.
There was a minute, yes.
Yeah, there was a minute where it was looking bad.
There were a couple in there where I went,
I don't need to hear this today.
Yeah.
We got almost 300 responses.
Wow.
Some of them were duplicates.
Amazing.
Because Google apps like any cloud-based apps
are kind of a pain in the ass.
So thank you for navigating those.
You know what it is nice, it is nice.
I do, I do, I may be not nice to work,
but it is interesting to see exactly, you know,
what people's thoughts are.
And I will just, this is a quick one.
And maybe you guys have this
and I'm ruining what you're gonna say,
but this is sort of indicative of some of,
of what we were looking through here
is that somebody said to us, they had a gripe
that the term seat has gotten out of hand
and kind of isn't funny anymore.
Okay, somebody said that.
All right, that's fair.
You know, I'm sure there's-
I mean, I agreed, you know, a year and a half ago.
I was on board with this gripe.
Right, now, if you go down, I believe four gripes,
somebody commented,
there hasn't been a thick seat final four yet.
So what are we gonna do with this, folks?
Everyone's all over the place.
I thought the same thing.
I have another example of the duality of the gripes,
which is that the very first one
that wasn't just us testing the system,
the very first one was remove Bugsy.
And then about 10 later, just several hours later,
Bugsy is criminally underused.
So there's really no degree of it.
It takes all kinds.
Yeah, there's no consensus.
It's all about balance, you know?
Podcasting, like many things, all about balance.
Cause we, you know, there was one or two that was like,
hey, you have to explain what the George Clooney briefcase
is a money mean to new listeners.
You have to explain what Terra Monic tequila is,
like what the rocks tequila's significance is.
But on the other hand, you know,
you are rewarded if you stick with a show for a long time
by running jokes and some people don't wanna hear
the explanations over and over.
So I think we try to tread that line.
We try to be cognizant.
Sure, of course.
I will say gripes inspired by a Funny or Die video,
the term.
Oh, you mean King of Gripes with Nick Carpacioso?
That's correct, yes.
I was looking for it and I couldn't remember,
Scott, do you have something to do with this video?
I do not, but it's my friend and collaborator,
Nick Carassi, who bears a resemblance to people
who've appeared on the show
and have been mentioned in this episode.
No, I'm not part of that.
It seems like kind of a cousin of our ClipCup franchise,
but it is actually, we noticed that it was not available
online and we did track it down recently.
And you know what, there has been a private link
for a while on viewboo.
com.
So maybe I'll just make that public on viewboo,
which is a great streaming site
that we might also have something to do with.
Yeah, that's kind of his sort of Dennis Leary-esque.
Yeah, I got a gripe.
Hey, don't tell me not to eat red meat, okay?
Look, I want a cigarette.
I want it absolutely bloody.
I want it beet red, okay?
And I don't want PC police coming down on me, gripe.
So yeah, check out gripes, the video.
Yeah, we'll find a way to get that out there.
Maybe you share some of those gripes.
That's funny that inspired that term.
We should probably remind people also
of what happened here exactly,
which is at the beginning of the year
that we put out a very first episode of the year,
we put out a call for your gripes.
We put up a Google forms link,
which is still available and we'll repost it,
assuming that by the end of this,
we don't wanna erase it forever
and make sure there's no gripes anymore.
But we made it an anonymous feedback box.
Now we've had, look, we've done mailbag episodes.
We've said, we'll reply to this tweet
and ask us some questions and stuff,
but this is kind of a different way to go with the anonymity.
And I think an interesting experiment,
which some people just said their names anyway,
and I appreciate that.
They're like, I'll put my name next to anything
that any thought that I have.
There's also, you guys probably noticed
that there were some gripes that were about the notion
of doing the anonymous gripes,
including this one that I enjoyed, which is,
oh, I forgot also, I tried to mentally prioritize
any gripes that followed the requested pattern
of saying at the beginning, yeah, I got a gripe all right.
And this one followed that.
So here we go.
Yeah, I got a gripe all right.
You wanna solicit comments from your listeners
and use them in future shows?
Isn't that how snakes on a plane happened?
Ha ha ha ha.
Very good, very good point.
Yeah, yeah.
That's a reference, I guess, to the fact that
people were upset that there weren't,
wasn't more swearing in snakes on a plane.
I forget that.
Oh, it was just that it was like
people's idea of the movie didn't match.
They made like a pretty boring movie, I think,
and what everyone was imagining was a crazy movie
where snakes bite people in the dick,
and Samuel L.
Jackson says,
I want these motherfucking snakes off this motherfucking plane,
and they didn't have any of that,
and they were like, shit, we gotta make this movie
something.
He does say that line.
Well, he does now, it was a reshit.
But they added it.
That was for the fan, yeah.
So this is an example of fans dictate
what they want the movie to be,
which is now buy everything always.
So this listener,
so this listener who wrote this anonymous gripe
is worried that we see something about seats,
and maybe we never say seats again,
and maybe that's not what the audience wants.
We don't know, maybe that's not what the majority wants.
We take one message from that.
That's what his concern is.
You read a lot of like, you know.
Or he or she, excuse me.
Interviews with artists or musicians and stuff,
and big actors, and they're like,
oh, I don't really read the reviews,
I try not to let it get to me or get in my head,
I just kind of like, you know,
I have to just do what my gut tells, you know.
So I understand that to a certain point,
but we're not fielding, you know,
a million sort of like, then this is what the show is now.
It's all question and answer, it's all feedback.
We have our own gut.
I don't know, Jason, I think maybe by the end of this,
I'm gonna change my philosophy.
I have a similar one to what Scott read.
It said, Michael, why did you do this?
You are a Pisces, and Pisces are too emotional
for this kind of thing, Jane.
So, you know, some to consider.
Now that Jane presumably being your girlfriend.
Coming from the other race, yeah, okay.
Yes, yes, my Jane.
I appreciate Jane's concern.
I appreciate her understanding
of what it's like to be a Pisces.
I appreciate that.
But I think that I, sometimes you have to put yourself
through some trials, you know,
to come out stronger on the other end.
Sure, that's fair.
And I think that's what's going to happen today
is we comb through the gripes.
Yeah, yeah.
I feel that way already,
because there were a few that were like,
ooh, that is the meanest thing I've ever seen
related to me, and to me personally, and the show.
And it like did sting at first,
and then like, whatever, get over it, it's fine.
Because, boy, let's reiterate,
the fans of this show are so nice.
It's almost crazy that we did this
to counteract the niceness.
And there were also so many of the gripes
that were like, I don't have one.
You guys are great, and I'm all punchy in quarantine,
and I don't want to take it out on you.
It really speaks to the niceness of the fan base,
that many gripes were nice, or refusing to do the gripes.
Yeah.
Yes, they were nice gripes.
Can I kick us off with, I have one that's like,
a good conversation starter, I think.
because I am, I think, the hardest,
the biggest Universal stan.
I have been like the biggest proponent of Universal.
So I'll, I have some thoughts on this.
It says, you seem to cut Universal a lot more slack
than you do Disney, for the exact same stuff.
And I just find that odd.
Okay, so I think I get it.
I think I see where they're coming from.
Like screens, or cutting corners,
like that's what I am guessing.
And I personally, yeah, I am a big Universal fan.
My family has had lots of nice memories at Universal.
So I am probably more likely to defend it.
I think the one thing though, personally,
if I'm as a podcaster with opinions on this stuff,
I may be cutting Universal more slack,
because I find overall Disney is cut way more slack
and Universal gets way more flack.
You guys ever know,
like the way people discuss some of this stuff,
it's like, all right, well, just,
for one, and the other part is,
there's different expectations here.
Like Disney's been in this business since the 50s.
Universal slowly got into it for decades,
but not really like all in like full speed ahead
until like the mid 80s and the early 90s.
So I think like there's more expectation with Disney
as like the multi-decade detail oriented company,
whereas Universal still, you know, similar money going on,
but like still more of the young upstart.
I think it's, I mean, I would like a couple examples
of what this griper, should we, griper, the griper maybe?
Sure, in this case, yeah, they were all grandfathers.
Griper is talking about,
I mean, there's probably some truth to that,
but I think you gotta have, yeah,
so Jason, as you're saying, there's different levels.
Like we're not mad at Knott's
for not having Rise of the Resistance, you know?
So we're gonna cut Knott's a lot of slack
in a lot of ways that we won't.
And then similar to Universal, Universal in like,
especially like is it 10 more years or even now,
okay, then you can start like a new park they build today,
I feel like we will give them the full, you know, criticism.
That being said, I don't know,
I feel like we goof on the lot of screens they have,
you know, I don't know.
Yeah.
I'm not sure exactly what you're saying.
Yeah, I know, I need for any concrete evidence of this,
but maybe what would settle the score is if,
what if Jason says something he doesn't like
about Islands of Adventure?
Maybe that's what has to be done.
Yes, Jason, will you throw, yeah,
say something bad about it, something you hate.
You can't be, I hate that I don't live there.
I don't live in the tower with the searchlight.
Yeah, I can't be the searchlight operator
and live in a little bed up there.
I hate, okay, yeah, that episode will be out by now.
I hate that they, I think they,
a problem with Islands of Adventure,
one of the problems with it is a problem
with a lot of the Vegas attractions that are gone now,
where it's like they gave it a year, maybe two years,
and they let a lot of stuff go to hell pretty quickly,
or they started cutting, like, okay,
we're not doing fireworks here,
that boat, the boat that'll take you across the water,
that's gone, the Dr.
Seuss people moving around
and they're like, oh, we're gonna move over
sort of a thing that goes above the land
that took like years and years and years to finish.
There was some stuff that they let go to rot
way too quickly and some improvements,
like they, I think the improvements have gotten better,
but they let the improvements go for too long.
That people move or ride whatever you're referring to,
it's some like flab-trap-ulous machine.
Yeah, yeah.
That's one of those, I waited in that line,
I don't know if it broke that day,
if it's just like a maddening line
that loops around and around and around,
and I think it was over an hour to then kind of go above
what you walk around already, that's a rough one.
If we're gonna throw things under the bus,
that one I am no fan of.
I feel like if I'd gotten on that
with a five minute wait, no problem,
but oh my God, it broke our brains
and we went there like over a decade ago.
Yeah.
And yeah, it's not, I'll say, like it's not,
the park isn't laid out the original Universal Florida,
park not so laid out well, how about that?
Like it's, it could be much better.
That's what I'll say.
So I don't know, is that harsh enough?
I don't know.
This is what I think, I think that we built up,
we saw some of the harshest things ever
and then this question and our answers were all so tame.
Every bit of it was the tamest thing.
I tried to phrase this one,
it's like a good conversation.
I think the ones I gravitated to
were like good conversation starters.
Okay, let me get into a different gripe.
We're gonna start slow here, folks.
The bill, okay, somebody said, yeah, I got a gripe.
You don't spend enough time talking about
how bad the Simpsons area of Universal is.
It's just so dismal.
The buildings are all wrong,
the flaming mos are green instead of purple,
but the thing that sent me over the edge
is that they serve special duff beer,
but it's not in a bottle or even a Moe's glass.
It's just a crappy beer in a plastic cup.
So what do we think about this?
Because this is actually not something
I've even thought about.
I've never even considered how inaccurate
this Simpsons land might be or is.
Well, I like this stuff.
That's why I'm not complaining about it.
I like Duff Gardens and I-
Yeah, I do too.
Yeah, and the duff beer, they were for a while,
it came in a bottle and they would pour it in a cup
and they're like, you can take a picture with the bottle,
but then we need it back because it was glass.
And yes, I would prefer people walking around
with minimal amounts of glass at a theme park.
Well, that's a practical insert.
The flaming Moe is wrong.
That is 100% true.
Yeah, it is wrong.
They messed that up.
That's bad, that's bad, bad, bad.
It's very bad and it's also a gross drink.
The drink should be actually good
because the flaming Moe from the sound of it
on the episode is delicious.
That sounds like the best drink ever.
It's all predicated on it being the best drink ever.
Yeah, I can picture in my,
do you think it is it kind of with the fruity
and the sugariness of it,
do you think it's kind of like a boysenberry beer,
but not electric?
Well, they say that there's cough syrup
and cough syrup I feel like is like kind of a grape-ish,
can be a grape-ish flavor.
So yeah, maybe it's adjacent to a boysenberry.
Could be.
So yeah, I feel like it's a delicious grape berry type
drink that has a little taste of medicine.
they taste medicinal but they're not?
Neko wafers, yeah.
They taste medicinal.
Neko wafers are like that.
I feel like there's a hint of medicinal quality
to the flaming Moe that they just didn't
spend too much time on.
And I think maybe they were a few years too late.
Because like Harry Potter rolls in
and then that's a whole new paradigm for a themed land.
Yeah.
And I don't think Matt Groening has the grip
on Universal like J.
K.
Rowling does as far as approvals.
Nobody maybe has never had a flaming Moe,
maybe never like stopped thinking about this
as soon as it was up and running.
Right, might be, yeah, might be checked out.
I don't know when it comes to theme park stuff.
I'm not sure, but yes, he,
I will say I've actually just never thought about it
because I think what it is is with The Simpsons,
my expectations aren't for screen accuracy
like they are for other properties.
Right.
And maybe it's because of the nature
of The Simpsons itself, stuff moves around.
I know stuff is stacked on top of each other,
especially in the Universal Hollywood one.
And obviously that's not represented in any episode.
But I feel like The Simpsons is something
that I just feel like as long as it's kind
of partially represented, I'm okay with it
versus like if Hogwarts, I mean,
I'm not a big Harry Potter fan,
but if Hogwarts was all jacked up,
I might go, well, this doesn't seem right.
Yeah, I think also this person might not be remembering
that a lot of the buildings in that stretch beforehand
were very gray and most dire would have to be
the food served at the International Food
and Film Festival restaurant at Universal Studios,
which was really, I mean, rough.
I mean, that's another criticism of Universal.
I think it's gotten better in recent years
and there's some good table service restaurants
at the hotels and at CityWalk.
And then like Kunfisco Grill and Mythos
were always good at Islands of Adventure,
but some of the food stuff at Universal Florida
was kind of dire.
I will say though, this gripe got me thinking
and did kind of go, you know what?
We could demand better from a Simpsons property
and maybe at this point it has to be a Disney Simpsons land
because I don't think they can add to it.
But honestly, I hadn't really even considered this.
So this gripe made me think, and I appreciate that
about a good gripe, is that it put a thought into my head
that might have not been there before.
And now anytime I go by there,
I'm gonna be a little less happy.
Oh good, they ruined the cartoon beer place for you.
That's right.
I wanna congratulate this griper on ruining
a little bit of my happiness every time I walk by
Springfield in Hollywood.
I appreciate that they committed to Duff being like,
like an okay Budweiser.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, fine, yeah.
I appreciate that, especially like,
I do not wanna walk around in Florida humidity
and drink like a double IPA.
That sounds awful to me.
I like the taste of like a hoppy beer sometimes,
but like it's a good walking around a theme park drink.
Theme parks and really basic beer do kinda go together.
I agree.
But although I've mentioned before,
they have holiday Duff that's pretty great.
It's like amber and good.
I have one that's similar might that's sort of,
it's directed at me and that did kind of change my
perspective on something and challenge me and made me think.
And it's it, it starts very threateningly.
Got a big gripe.
I didn't appreciate Scott making fun of the 1984
Tina Turner hit, What's Love Got To Do With It
on the Opryland episode.
It's a corny love song and I love it for being like that.
For being a synth enjoyer,
you should enjoy even the silliest of synth solos.
And yeah, I am a synth enjoyer.
And I felt a little snobby reading this.
I was like, yeah, no, but I know that solo.
That solo is silly.
And but you, all right, I know she's saying,
or they're saying enjoy silliness,
but I still can be demanding with.
And then I stepped back and I thought,
like, well, let me listen to that solo.
And then I mentally paired it with another song.
Okay, I've said that I don't like the solo
in What's Love Got To Do With It.
And then I thought about a solo
that I do like and listen to.
And I listened to them back to back
and I realized that I am being ridiculous.
First, let me play the one that they are talking about.
This is from 1984,
is What's Love Got To Do With It
that I complained about a couple months ago.
["What's Love Got To Do With It"]
And I was being snobby about that.
And then I thought about one that I've said,
you know what I really like is this.
And this is from the song Valerie by Steve Winwood.
["Valerie"]
I mean, that's as flatulent as they come.
So who am I to-
Kazooie.
Yeah, ooh, very, very good word, yes.
They sampled a kazoo.
You know what, absolutely, that's right.
Dorky synth solos, I think beauty
is in the eye of the beholder.
And now I realize those are like almost identical
in their goofiness.
And now I'm like, you know what,
the goofier the better, whatever you want,
except for the recent Weezer covers and those synths.
Those are out for me no matter what.
Now that brings up a gripe I saw.
Oh, damn it.
Somebody said,
I like Weezer's cover of Take On Me
and don't understand what's bad about it.
That was a gripe.
Scott is getting a lot of gripes
for his music opinions.
I guess so.
Well, it's another synth one.
I just don't, if you're gonna do a cover,
don't you wanna do something to it?
Transform it.
Yes, any change, decision, make it like Weezer,
which I feel like they have done.
I think they have done covers and they Weezerified it.
All those covers, the Billie Jean
is the boringest shit I've ever heard.
It's a wedding band, they're a wedding band.
They did nothing, they brought nothing
about what you like about Weezer to those songs.
Oh God, it makes me so mad, that album.
I think that was a hit, right, the Take On Me?
Was it?
I think so.
I think one of those songs on that album was a decent hit.
It's sort of like the sometimes shot for shot
Disney live action remakes.
Why would you not just watch the animated one?
What would ever compel you to choose?
And even more so, because at least there are new things
and new actors in those live action movies.
Well, I think if you have a child,
if you have a child who gravitates toward,
you know, people, the kids especially latch on to stuff
they see very young, I think.
I can see that.
You're talking about Weezer's Take On Me?
Kids love it.
It would be my son's favorite song.
50 year old Rivers Cuomo more than the lead singer of Aha,
which I don't know.
Well, in some sense, like if you're eight or 10 years old,
and you're driving around,
if you're riding around in your parents' car
and that song comes on the radio, like you're not,
I guess now you can just on a phone,
you can pull up the original, but like, yeah,
they just might like the first version they heard, you know?
That's true.
Or adults could do that too.
I've heard covers before originals.
I mean, I am the biggest Weezer fan on the podcast.
I will say that album is not in heavy rotation
on my Weezer listening.
You've never been particularly a defender of it.
And even you were saying there's a newer Weezer
and I was dismissive and I listened to it.
I was like, yeah, fine.
I'd never put this on, but like this,
it's there in it.
I get it.
I get why you would listen to this.
Yeah, there's Beach Boys and Nelson in there.
Somewhere.
You can hear it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But not these cranked out cover, these lazy.
I don't even like take,
it's not like I'm such a stand for take on me either.
It's just like, just do something.
Change one thing about it.
You're not a big, I think take on me is fantastic.
Oh no, I like it.
I'm just not like, I don't know the name.
As with you, I don't know the names of the members.
I'm not like a hardcore aha person.
This is something, can I have a gripe with aha real quick?
I said, you know what?
I've been listening to take on me for my whole life
and I really like it.
Let me hear maybe other aha songs
that are as good as this.
And I did like the top 10 or whatever on Spotify
and I went, nothing is close.
No, not really.
As I recall, I like their James Bond song,
The Living Daylights.
Yes.
Yeah.
That's the one I would say.
I like it, but it's interesting.
It's like nothing is close to that level of like,
oh, everything is a fantastic hook.
Yeah.
There's other bands like that.
And I don't even mean to trash aha so much.
I was just thinking there has to be something
similar to this and it feels like
that was like a fluke almost.
Like a fluke, like as if fly happened with Sugar Ray
and then they didn't lean into being more of a pop band.
You know?
I guess.
Exactly like that.
I got really into a blur in high school
and starting with like their best of,
they have like a big long best of that's two CDs.
The second one is like a live concert
and it's all the hits and like the popular album cuts.
And then when I go back and try to do like albums,
I'm like, oh yeah, this just doesn't,
I think I just want the best.
I just want the like best of.
Sometimes some bands.
I'm going with that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
There's bands I would say are great.
That, you know, if you have eight to 10 great songs,
then I think you're great.
That's a miracle by the way.
Yeah, yeah.
That's not easy.
Absolutely.
Yeah, yeah.
It's just, it's like the greatest to the greatest
where all the album cuts are good too.
So that's that.
You want to keep going in a rotation, Jason?
You want to do one?
Yeah.
Oh, here's a good one.
Okay.
This is also kind of universal.
This is as multiple parts.
And the second part is more conversant.
The first part I can answer immediately.
How have you not talked about the Spider-Man ride
at Universal?
The answer is we did.
In an episode dated April 12th, 2019.
So check that out.
True.
I think somebody realized, Jason,
I think if you go down in the gripes though,
the same person came back and realized that we had done.
Oh, okay.
Oh no.
All right.
But the rest of the gripe I do think is very interesting.
It's one of the most successful theme park rides
of all time and yet it has the most baffling
character selection for an IP ride.
Why does the Sister 6 only have five members?
Why Hobgoblin instead of Green Goblin?
Why Shriek instead of Venom?
And what's up with Scott Trowbridge?
He's obsessed with selecting obscure characters
for marquee attractions.
He created Spider-Man ride featuring the Sinister 5
and a Millennium Falcon ride featuring Hondo Anaka.
What other insane choices can we expect now
that he is the most senior Imagineer Latin at Disney?
I think I can answer some of this too,
which is in the 90s, Venom was like a complicated good guy.
So I don't think he was like,
I'm surprised he's not in the ride
because he was so popular.
I'm not surprised like when they needed a villain,
they just went to like a secondary symbiote.
I would have thought they would have gone with Carnage,
but his origin story is he is a serial killer
who has killed a lot of people
and that might be too heavy for a theme park.
Yeah, but the Joker's been in a theme park
and Joker's done some really awful shit.
I guess that's true, but he makes us all think, you know.
Maybe Trowbridge doesn't like Carnage.
Maybe he doesn't like symbiotes.
Well, I think the other thing is that like
a lot of the bigger characters,
especially with Star Wars with like the story committee
and stuff, there might just be too many like,
oh, it's gotta be, this has to be this in this way
and it's gotta behave this way.
But if you use a more ancillary character,
you have a little more wiggle room with like the jokes
and the prompts and stuff.
Maybe, yeah, perhaps that's what it is.
I mean, I think with Galaxy's Edge,
it's like, it seems like it's,
they were going away from like the legacy characters,
so to speak, and it takes place in a certain time
frame, so we weren't gonna see a famous character,
as famous of a character maybe.
Yeah, I mean.
Unless it was from the new trilogy.
A Chewie animatronic would have been cool,
but he shows up in the video footage.
Also, it's a little hard for Chewie
to give you a clear mission with words.
Yes.
I think that Hondo and Naka thing is cool.
I'd certainly never heard of that character before
and it does, it makes, it feels like more akin to a Rex,
a new character in Star Tours than like,
yeah, this is the thing that's kind of special to the ride,
even if they have existed before.
Yeah, I feel like people,
I feel like there's some people that complain
about Galaxy's Edge,
because like I'm certainly, I'm like,
let's just put all the characters in.
Give me the prequel characters,
give me the original trilogy
and put the new characters in there.
But I think some people are complaining about Hondo,
like that should be Han Solo or a famous character,
and I don't mind that at all.
That doesn't bother me at all,
having like a slightly obscure character in there,
because as Scott's saying, it feels like,
well, that's, Hondo is this original,
I mean, even though he's from whatever, Clone Wars,
it's like, well, I don't get to see Hondo a lot.
I'm not even that familiar with him
and I make, I become better friends with him
each time I go on this ride.
Like that's sort of how I feel about it.
So I'm all for Hondo being on that.
And I don't know, I wonder if, I wonder,
I wonder if Troll Bridge is a big,
is he like actually pushing these characters or yes,
is Jason saying, is it a mandate?
I'm not sure, we need to have Scott on the show,
but I think until he works, doesn't work for Disney,
maybe that won't happen.
Yeah, I don't think we're getting current people probably.
Yeah, it's at least they can't be a candid as possible.
They can't gripe about Disney, you know?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's what we're all about now,
especially me as an edgelord.
That's why, it's funny when we thought of this,
I wasn't an edgelord yet.
And now that I am, I am swimming in it.
Yeah, it's like, yeah, it's, what actually came first?
Is it your new attitude or is it the call for gripes?
I don't know.
Who knows what caused what?
Yeah, I don't know, it was all in the water.
All I know is that I'm an edgelord
and I eat up these gripes like it's delicious spaghetti.
I slurp them up, spit them back out at you
because I'm an edgelord.
Wow, very casual.
The most upbeat edgelord in the world.
Yeah, yeah, try to keep a positive attitude.
Edgelord doesn't have to be dour.
Yeah, nice bringing your step, you know?
Oh sure.
You make people smile.
I got to.
All right, I feel bad about this gripe
and I'm gonna say it now here.
So, and then they did not do the gripe intro,
but that's okay.
Mike implied Tyler Mane, who plays Sabretooth
in the X-Men movies, had died
in the Villain Ted Halloween episode
and caused me a moment of sadness
because he was very nice to me at a convention.
Thankfully, he's still with us.
So, I know exactly what happened here.
I know exactly what I did
and I am very sorry to Mr.
Tyler Mane
and anyone who was confused.
I was thinking of the actor who played Bane
in Batman and Robin, Jeep Swenson,
who has sadly passed away.
And I was confusing, these movies came out
within a couple years of each other.
I was confusing two wrestler guys
who were not huge names in the companies.
I was confusing these two wrestler names
and confusingly said that Tyler Mane had passed away.
He is still alive, I apologize.
That's my bad.
That's good one.
You know, it's really one of the balancing acts
of doing this podcast is trying to remember stuff
off the dome versus how much do you look at
while you're, like look stuff up while you're recording
because you don't wanna slow down every conversation with,
let me look that up.
Yes, I know, yes.
Sometimes you reach for something and it's not there.
It's not there.
Or you say the wrong guy is dead and he's not.
It's not and it was always very mentally taxing
in COVID times.
It is, it's just not even, it's just impossible.
Like my memory.
I don't know if I'd say very.
You get very mentally taxed
because you can't remember a thing.
I trying to like keep a lot of balls in the air,
keep the conversation going, look at your notes,
like in terms of like a recording performance aspect,
it can be difficult.
So maybe not very mentally taxing,
but it's certainly a thing.
But like my memory is just shot during this day and age.
It's become to the point where like the conversations
about which day is it?
It's like, I don't even know it's Pat.
I don't wanna keep doing that.
Like what I, it doesn't matter if we know what day.
It's fine.
There's some.
Sure.
There's one that maybe similarly is about some fudged info.
First of all, let me say, I really like,
I think we announced this episode around when,
right when we did the Fast and Furious and Living Seas.
So a lot of the gripes are about those.
And that makes sense because they just happened
and people are on the hunt for gripes.
But I really like when there is a gripe
that is from forever ago.
And that's what this one is.
And it's also some fuzziness on my part.
Or so they think.
Okay.
On the Splash Mountain episode,
that's in the first 20 or so.
Scott mentioned a picture on Flash Mountain,
you know, where people would show their boobs or whatever,
and it would end up on some site.
If you did something weird, essentially,
on Splash Mountain when going down the drop.
And I mentioned a picture of somebody
with a video game console,
quote, playing Donkey Kong on an Xbox.
This was my first red flag
that Scott Gardner is one sick fuck.
Donkey Kong is, of course, a Nintendo property
and would never and will never be seen
on a Microsoft console.
Furthermore, the game from the picture
was Super Smash Brothers Melee on GameCube.
Me think Scott had a few too many sips of wine that day.
Fair enough.
But let me say that.
Okay, so you assume that I'm talking about
some specific one with Super Smash Brothers Melee
on a GameCube.
How do you know that I'm not talking about
a different one entirely?
the time that somebody went on Splash Mountain with?
Well, let me pull up a video to explain what I'm talking about.
You say that Donkey Kong has never been on Xbox.
Well, what do you say about this video
from several months before our Splash Mountain episode
where somebody has rigged up Donkey Kong bongos
to control the racing game Forza X,
or, I'm sorry, Forza 7 on Xbox One X?
This is a video they figured out how to use
Donkey Kong's bongos to control a race car.
You remember this, right?
You guys, we all remember how viral this video went.
Oh, of course.
It was the winter of 2017 and I'll never forget.
Yeah, yeah, it was the talk of the internet.
And obviously several months before we recorded that episode.
So how do you know, Anonymous Griper,
that I am not talking about that I saw people
go down Splash Mountain with this setup,
rigging up bongos to play Xbox?
That is what I saw.
I saw it.
It's now I checked it's been scrubbed from the internet
so I can't prove it, but that clearly is what happened.
Somebody took an Xbox with Donkey Kong bongos.
And you can blame it on me being one sick fuck
and having too much wine.
And that part I won't deny.
I am sick and it's the wine that makes me sick
and I don't ever wanna get well.
That's the end of this gripe.
Wow, that was an epic gripe clap back, I guess?
Yeah.
Which is a first on the show.
Oh, I clap back at this.
This person will never show their cursor
in the gripe box again.
I proved definitively that somebody took
a rigged up Xbox on Splash Mountain.
Wow.
And you were likely, you might've been coming off
another podcast, you made an appearance
where maybe you were discussing the N64 game,
Perfect Dark, which is developed by Rare for N64.
And eventually they did re-release it on Xbox 360.
Yeah.
And the ownership of the Rare company
gets very complicated and I believe,
I'm doing this off the dome a little,
but I believe Rare, they did GoldenEye
and yes, they helped with Donkey Kong and Banjo-Kazooie,
which were of course N64 games.
Yes, yes.
There's so many, there's been so many ways
to play Donkey Kong on an Xbox over the years.
And that's why I said that thing that I said
many, many years ago.
And if it took, if you didn't do the proper research
to realize that, then I can't help you.
Wow.
All right, well we got a lot to live up to.
I don't think anyone of us is gonna clap back.
Everybody's gotta clap back as hard as you can,
even if it's the softest thing,
even if they're really nice to you in it.
Clap back.
All right, Jason, Jason, get geared up here.
Okay.
Clap and level.
Baby Aladar is neither cute nor ugly.
He has transcended what can be classified
as mortal or earthly and can no longer be judged
by such fleshy qualifications.
He is my world, he is my Alice star.
You must subject yourself to him immediately
or face the wrath of a 10,000 lemurs.
I mean, that's fair.
That's really fair.
Hard to clap back at that one, I suppose.
Hard to clap back at that one.
Seems right to me.
I mean, seems, I get it.
To break from the bouncing around pattern,
I think there was a lot of dinosaur divisiveness.
Some of it's about Aladar.
I noticed some things about the good dinosaur.
People were defending the good dinosaur,
often in ways that still seem like they didn't like it,
but were, I don't know, still something.
Somebody said, I think you owe an apology
to dinosaurs everywhere and promise to be more inclusive
of dinosaurs in the future.
And somebody called us low energy on that episode.
What?
Was this Trump?
I think it was Trump.
That's one of the things he says.
The dinosaur, yeah, the dinosaur episode.
Somebody said we were low energy.
We have to redo it.
Well, I guess so.
Well, it was just so dark in there.
We made all our studio spaces pitch black
to simulate dinosaurs.
We got a little sleepy.
Yeah, exactly.
That's right.
So we'll redo it eventually in 2028.
But we're gonna redo all the quarantine ones
like better since we're sad.
Special editions.
Although, somebody brought up,
let me go real quick to this.
You should redo the Indiana Jones Adventure episode
since it was the first episode
and only covers the ride for a small portion of the episode.
And I say, I agree.
I agree 100%.
Let's announce now we're gonna do this.
Oh man.
Maybe not so soon.
Amount voted.
But I think you've been outvoted
if we just all had a vote of enthusiasm.
We have talked about revisiting earlier ones.
Yeah.
You were the most excited about that.
You've been on anything on the,
doing something again.
Yes.
Yeah.
That's the opposite of low energy.
Again, again.
But there's new things to do.
Don't we wanna do new things?
You know, but you rewrite, you know,
you wanna rewrite that ride, you know.
There's other angles.
There's other, yeah, there's other ways to do it.
There are a few I think you could do again,
but I'm worried about a slippery slope here
where now we're doing the City Walk Saga 2.
We're just doing it all again.
We're, I think you flow to the idea
of doing more of the same City Walk Saga to be honest.
Doing more of it again?
I think so.
Or at least we've talked about the fact
that it's gonna change so much, we'll have to do it again.
I mean, I'm a proponent of new sectors when they come up.
and Popcornopolis.
What if Zen Zone installs new water coffins
and we have to try them out?
If something new, if there's a new element to something,
don't you think we would have to then go in and try it again?
No, I'd be fine with that, yes.
Yeah, new is the operative word, yes.
But like with Weezer, you have to add something to it
to make it new and fresh.
Say the coffins are the same type of coffins,
you're just newer so they work better.
Oh yeah, or if they're like green vinyl,
hitting your back instead of blue vinyl.
No, I'm on board with every one of these.
You haven't lost me on any of them.
It's going, it's doing anything that hasn't changed.
That's my
Well, I'm not saying we go back in and revisit
the Ace Ventura Disney's Hollywood Studio show yet.
I'm not saying that, but I am saying maybe some of the heavy
hitters, some of the stuff that it feels like you could talk
ad nauseam about because they're so great or so fruitful.
Well, yeah, sequels.
I'm just worried that that heavy hitter definition
suddenly expands and now we're doing Day in the Park
with Barney Six.
Well, yeah, we all have a couple different heavy hitters
probably in the categories that maybe Jason or you don't have,
but yeah, is there more Rift talk coming on this show?
Of course there is.
Yeah, absolutely.
And they closed Day in the Park with Barney as well.
I know.
That's apparently closed forever.
Rest in peace.
Yeah, it's gonna make it a lot harder
to do six episodes about it.
Right, I mean, that's like, we're gonna have to have
a really thin excuse to do something,
which is rare for this show.
We have the thickest excuses in the business.
That is the new tagline for the show,
the thickest excuses in the business.
That replaces childless men in their 30s.
Are you up, Mike?
Well, I just did the Indiana Jones thing.
I guess that didn't count as a full,
maybe it's not a full gripe, so I can do a full gripe.
Well, I have one to throw your way.
I hate to direct one, put you in the line of fire.
No, no, hit me with it.
But you can always go back.
Yeah, I got a gripe for you.
In the Tato Park episode, Mike was waiting to receive
the Mr.
Tato autobiography, The Man Inside the Jacket,
and he's never talked about it,
despite promising an addendum.
What am I supposed to do?
Also risk getting my credit card stolen?
Hell no.
I need to do here a, and it's the acronym
that I think is too long, didn't read,
of this surely incredible tome, please, and thank you.
Okay, so what happened is real quick refresher
is that on the Tato Park episode.
Which is a park devoted to potatoes,
and there's a potato mascot who is a big potato, Mr.
Tato.
Crisp, yes.
Like an hour or two before,
and I was doing some last second research,
I saw that there was some sort of autobiography,
supposedly written by Mr.
Tato about himself,
and I was on some website that was pretty shady
that offered me a digital copy.
Now I think what this website was
is that if you just search for a book and digital,
it'll kind of give you a fake facsimile
of what that might be, and try to trick you
into putting your credit card information in,
in order to steal your identity,
or just to buy some expensive clothes online or whatever.
So I was in such a rush, I did it,
thinking that it might be legitimate,
and I will say that this doesn't end spectacularly.
Basically the credit card charge was declined,
I don't think my credit card was stolen,
I was monitoring the activity.
It was absolutely a fraudulent website though,
it was not legitimate.
I should not have put my information in there.
As far as I know, nothing has happened yet.
I guess this could be a long game of identity theft,
maybe even by Mr.
Tato himself.
I don't know all the players in this type of agency.
Oh, but he's such a rule follower, remember?
He was like a prude, he's telling people to cover up,
and be more modest in those weird commercials we saw.
Right, Jason has sent me a copy of a website now
where I can purchase the book for a very low price.
A very low price, but a high shipping fee.
This is Biblio, which I believe is the largest
used book website in America.
I've spent a lifeline for me.
I will say, yeah, sometimes if you're an eBay shopper,
you'll notice that oftentimes the price of an item
will be very low, but the shipping will be very high,
and you have to pay attention for that,
and that seems to be what's going on here
with a $4 price and a $12 shipping.
Although it is shipping to US if this is coming from Europe,
so that is a bit more expensive.
So I will make this guarantee, I will purchase this book.
I will not get defrauded.
There will be, again, we will find one of the thickest
excuses to talk about Mr.
Tato and his life story
in a future episode, I swear.
Such a thick excuse.
So I apologize for not updating on that,
the update in that, but I wanted to wait
until I actually had a book in hand,
and Jason has now given me a way to do it
in a very $20-ish way.
I will buy the book, you can buy the shipping.
How about that?
Very generous.
That's your penance, that's your penance
for not doing more Silk Road potato mascot bookshops.
Can you do that line as if Wimpy was saying it?
I'll gladly pay you for the book.
I'll gladly pay you for the book
if you cover the shipping.
Wait, I actually, I just didn't document it,
but on Biblio, I did buy, there was no cover image.
I have a copy.
This I will promise in no speedy manner,
but I will do a book report episode
about the Harlequin romance novel
that is set at Walt Disney World.
I forget the title of it, I don't have it in front of me,
but that was going around the internet for a few days,
and I did track it down.
I think our listeners bought a lot of the copies
that were out there, and I got one of the last ones.
And it took about a month to get here,
but it did get here.
It does have a couple swooning in front of Spaceship Earth.
It's really quite a beautiful cover.
Yeah, please, fill us in.
Well, that was kind of a rapid fire.
We sort of all did one.
Do you wanna go back to Jason?
Sure, yeah, go for it.
Sure.
Hi, PTR, I have a gripe.
In the Frozen Every After episode,
you guys say that no college-age kids listen to your show.
I am college-age and listen to your show every week,
and I was for sure judging you old people
for your back issues.
JK loved the show.
I laughed at that one.
I think I was not present in that conversation
that Frozen Every After episode,
because I spent a significant portion
of the later part of college listening,
walking around campus listening to podcasts
in the early days of podcasting.
So yeah, I absolutely do.
There were some podcasts.
College kids listening to the podcast.
I think people took that too seriously on my part.
I think I was being a little facetious
in an episode with as many of them are
with sort of old man references.
Yes.
I feel like I was like, oh, we don't have any,
but yeah, I do appreciate people raising their hands though.
And yeah, it's always great to hear they exist.
I think we were giving you guys credit
for being like cool and young and on the cutting edge.
And like, well, surely they won't listen to these old times.
We hopefully we aren't ruining promising lives
with the lame niche interests, but I guess we are.
I think we are.
But I apologize.
Oh man, college, I had plenty of niche interests.
That Mr.
Pibb, yeah.
It was an exciting time the first years of YouTube,
buying snakes on a plane, T-shirts, fan made
and the Chronicles of Narnia rap video
really hitting big, you know?
The comic book Excalibur.
Yeah.
My favorite thing about that time really quick is how,
all right, so yeah, there was Lazy Sunday on SNL
that kind of like changed the show
and launched Andy Samberg into the stratosphere.
And what I like is that there was also
a lot of people doing like Lazy Monday
who were doing like, all right, you guys on SNL,
we're gonna show you how we do it on the West Coast.
And they, like, there was so many things like that.
Notably none of whom rocketed into the stratosphere
like Andy Samberg.
Like the Lazy Sunday disses and baits into a rap battle.
You'll notice that they did not feel the need to respond
and do a diss track back and forth.
That was a fun time.
That was a good.
It was a fun time.
I remember a brief period where I kept taking my laptop
to the tech support on campus.
And I'm like, why does the website YouTube not work on Macs?
And they're like, something's going on.
Like, it's not supported right now.
And it's like, can you imagine not getting,
like there was a time where not only could you not get
YouTube like on your refrigerator,
you could, it wouldn't work on a Macintosh.
At all?
What a time.
Wow.
You know, at all.
Yeah.
It's wild.
I think it was a bug and I think it was resolved
reasonably quickly, but it's like, oh yeah.
Now I just like flip on YouTube, like drinking water.
It's crazy.
Mike, you got anything?
Yeah, this is a quick one.
Somebody says they got a gripe.
Yeah, I got a gripe.
All right.
I feel like the world of Sid and Marty Croft
got overshadowed by Hard Rock Park
since they were in the same episode.
And I also very much agree with this gripe.
Yeah.
I think at the time, you know,
we were still figuring out the show and we were like,
well, I don't know, will we have enough to talk about
about Hard Rock Park?
That was an educational episode for sure.
That was one, yeah, we had to,
we realized midway through it had to be split.
We felt so insane.
I think that still counts even though it's a two-part.
I think that's the longest we were ever recording
in one stint.
And it's truly demented now to think that we thought
we could do both parks in one.
Yeah, like if we, if we, right now we would be like,
oh, have you heard about Hard Rock Park?
And then like, you would Google it and you go,
Winston the punk rock dog.
And then we go, well, we got 90 minutes right here
at the very least.
So it is crazy to think about the old days.
I saw a couple of gripes also about segments.
Some people miss the segments we would throw in
a lot more often during the first few years.
And I can't disagree with that either.
These are legitimate gripes.
I think we could be adding a few more segments here and there.
Yeah, yeah.
But I also think, I also think early on,
we were just trying stuff out.
We were feeling it out, you know?
It's before the era of the like two hour,
two and a half hour.
Like I think we didn't, like being new at it,
I think we felt like, can we even do 90 minutes?
And now we know we can do it off of nothing.
We even, with a not thick excuse to do an episode.
Right, riff.
I mean, riff, yeah, we would, I wouldn't have,
I wouldn't have known like riff would be like a 30 minute
topic of conversation before.
So yeah, we apologize.
I do think Sid and Marty Croft,
there's gotta be other theme park stuff.
I am fascinated by all of those weird characters.
And we have to, we still have, we still owe a McDonald,
like a pure McDonald land episode.
Oh yes.
So then there's connection to that
because they ripped off Sid and Marty Croft.
So I think there will be more
Sid and Marty Croft material coming.
Practically too.
I think as we were doing that episode,
there was not a ton of scans of like
the Sid and Marty Croft park online, scans or footage.
And as the years have gone on,
more stuff has been uploaded.
Either video or.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, so that is, you know, there is a certain point
with some of the more obscure stuff where it's like,
I have hit a wall, like I've run out of things
I can search or search for.
It makes it hard with like some like kind of,
like some seventies rides a little bit.
Like there's just not a ton out there.
Yeah, you do.
I don't know if we're more recent,
it might be for reasons like that.
I have another, it was going off of McDonald land.
I have a food related gripe
that I do think is an important one.
Yeah, I got a gripe all right.
I don't need, well, this was the Fast and the Furious one.
How dare the Rock and by extension, you good boys,
think that the term cookie puss is an insult.
That's something the Rock says in that attraction.
And I judged it as an insult, but he says,
we should all be so lucky to be associated
with Carvel's celestial person from outer space.
If being made of delicious soft serve ice cream
and delicious crunchies is wrong,
then I don't wanna be right.
I am particularly upset with Jason, no, no,
as the East Coast and treats good boy representative
for not defending cookie puss.
He also has themes.
During St.
Patrick's day, he is cookie opuss.
I know all about cookie opuss.
I know what you're gonna say, yeah.
I demand extended time to discuss cookie puss.
He is at the very least deserving of a five minute tangent.
Nothing wrong was said there.
No clapping back to be done there.
I mean, cookie puss rocks.
All the Carvel universe stuff rocks.
I think in the context of the Fast and Furious ride,
that was literally, they were sitting around
writing dialogue and like, oh, that's a,
what's a funny thing for him to say?
What's a funny thing for him to call him?
Like, this has gotta be G rated.
This has gotta be PG at worst.
Like, oh, I don't, and someone's like,
that's, it's a funny name.
It's a very funny phrase.
So I think that's, that would be my guess.
I do would, I do still think it is an insult and not,
but not, I think because of the phrases,
it's not the harshest insult potentially,
but yeah, no one is casting aspersions on cookie puss,
who is great.
If you haven't seen cookie puss,
he is a cake face with a nose that is an ice cream cone.
And he's very cool.
I'll do a quick clap back here.
Just a quick one.
I'm not gonna do an epic one.
I'm just gonna say, here's the thing though.
Calling someone, let's say Bozo, hey Bozo,
first of all, kind of a neutral insult in this day and age,
but I'll say this about Bozo.
I'm a big fan of Bozo the Clown.
So you can sort of use it.
It is sort of whatever your intention is, you know,
means more than actually the word you're saying,
I think sometimes.
Cause like Bozo is a beloved clown,
many versions of him.
I like a lot of the different versions of Bozo,
but I would recognize it as an insult.
So that's my slight clap back.
Doesn't mean the person saying that hasn't watched
and enjoyed Bozo at some point in time.
Maybe it's that like, you know, with Fast and Furious,
they're heading into a big high octane, high artillery,
heist or mission or something.
I still don't really know.
And it's maybe a situation where, what was that?
Chase.
Chase, sure.
Yeah.
Expedition something.
And it's maybe a situation where I don't know that Cookie Puss
as great as he is.
I don't know that he, an ice cream cake would get a lot done
in that particular mission.
Although maybe I'd love him to always be around
no matter what.
I wish he was by my side right now.
Of course.
Also, we can't like do jump on every,
like I've got to defend this or like,
well, I actually know an interesting fact
about that ice cream purveyor.
And then like, you got away like,
oh, is the episode wrapping up?
Are we about to go into another thing?
You know, like, should I derail this
to explain the Carvel universe?
I guess in this case, yes, was the answer.
Maybe not every case, but.
Kind of, yeah.
In this one.
And I, and it's.
As far as Carvel.
Well, Carvel, yeah, Carvel probably deserves its own.
I don't know.
It was always kind of mysterious to me
because there was no Carvel outlets,
but we would certainly have the like,
default ice cream cakes for like,
school birthdays or parties and stuff.
But I did not have a lot of exposure
to the characters growing up to the more fun cakes.
That's true.
Yeah.
They're also, the Cookie Puss is an important part
of hip hop history in that Cookie Puss
was the Beastie Boys' first single.
So.
Oh yeah.
Don't forget that.
Also, like Kickstart's an incredible career.
So I have the utmost respect for Mr.
Puss.
Yes.
Thank you, Mr.
Puss.
Thanks for everything.
Jason, you got anything?
You don't have to.
I got something if you want me to go.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, go for it.
Yeah, Mike, you go.
Yeah, I got a gripe.
You are dead wrong about the Mickeyverse theory.
There is only one Mickey Mouse and he is a talented actor
who plays many roles and occasionally gets a new look
from hair and makeup.
This appears, and here's where I think this,
maybe there's some holes in this person's gripe.
This appears to be the case in prominent Mickey media
such as Roger Rabbit and House of Mouse,
which features Mickey personally introducing
some of his films for all his Disney friends.
It pains me to write this gripe as I am a huge Mike head
and I wish only the best for Mike and his friends.
Now, I think they're talking about me
and didn't forget to put a y at the end of each of those.
But.
You?
I think they're talking about me
because I guess I'm the one who kind of put that theory
out there in the first place.
Also, they say love the grunch.
They call themselves the grunch.
I gotta like that.
I like the grunch, yeah.
So they're calling me out for what they believe
is an incorrect theory that there is a multiverse of Mickeys.
I don't know.
I don't know that this evidence is so clear to me
because I think that there's a lot of contradictions
when it comes to sort of what Mickey has done
and what Mickey's been up to,
where he lives, what he's done and what his friends do.
I think it's very flexible,
which is what leads me to believe there's a Mickey-verse.
Look, I believe Mickey is a very talented actor
who plays many roles and occasionally gets a new look.
Yes, that's true.
But I think the physics and the reality
change from cartoon to cartoon,
which is why I believe these are different universes.
I don't think Mickey can do the same things
because you can't see a gross closeup of Mickey's face
on a classic Disney cartoon like you can now
on the new ones.
And there's the different voices.
There's the one that sounds normal
and there's the one that sounds like shit.
So what does that tell you?
Exactly, there's completely different voices.
Is he changing his voice?
That doesn't make sense.
It would be a different character.
Is Mickey in the park?
Mickey in the parks is a different character
for sure than Mickey in the cartoons.
I stand behind that.
Now, if there is some sort of guidebook official Disney
source that has this information,
I'm happy to say that I'm wrong.
But I'm gonna need to see this documented somewhere
or I'm gonna have to hear it from somebody who leaked it
when Walt was drunk at the Tamo Shantor one night
that Mickey is always the same,
even when he looks different.
Even when Mickey looks different, he's the same.
If he said something like that,
then maybe I will see what you're saying.
I appreciate your gripe grunch.
I'm just saying, I'm not convinced.
I appreciate you being a huge mic head though.
I don't know that I've ever heard a person that likes me
say that they were a mic head
and I can appreciate that branding.
Do they think the show should be called Mike and Friends
instead of podcast the ride?
I mean, I like the sound of it,
but I don't know if that's what the grunch is saying.
We could talk about our branding off the air,
but I mean, like, yeah, everyone thinks
that's how we should brand the show.
Just send us another email or send us a gripe.
I wouldn't agree to that
before I would agree to this show being called
The Edge Lord Hour.
Uh-oh.
With The Edge Lord and some other people.
Okay, well, look, I don't know if there's a gripe in here
saying The Edge Lord should be the branding of the show,
but I'm open to all of these ideas.
I'm flexible.
There's one.
There's one idea in here that I'm curious
if you're open to or flexible about.
Okay, yeah, go ahead.
I don't know, this one's a little more personal,
so just buckle up.
Okay, I'm ready.
I've got a gripe all right.
Michael has been living in sin for years.
Well, I'm-
I saw this.
There are certain ones that I avoided being too personal.
This one has to be read.
While I'm perfectly fine with this morally,
it conflicts with his podcast persona.
You're telling me a sexually repressed character
who's afraid of bodiness goes to sleep
with an unmarried woman?
For the sake of podcast character integrity,
Michael must move out until he makes
an honest woman of Lindsay.
Response.
Okay, look, I would like to say that my characters
from episode to episode actually exist in a multiverse.
The microverse.
So sometimes when you hear me, it's the microverse,
so sometimes when you hear me curse,
that's actually a different Earth's Michael.
And when I'm talking about how Lindsay and I
are living in sin, that's that other one.
That's the one who curses.
Sometimes it happens mid-episode.
Sometimes it depends.
Sometimes I'm completely uptight,
and then obviously like in Europe,
I just go wild like I'm at Mardi Gras.
So even that was a multiverse situation.
That wasn't a permanent character change,
and that's why you essentially changed back.
Right, I snapped back, but that's actually
a different character from a multiverse.
So I mean, I think it's an interesting,
if you're a long-time listener,
I think you can probably start to identify
the different characters in the microverse,
which have different qualities,
and I think there are at least three
that I can think of.
Yeah, like radically different mics.
can't hear anything sexual,
like stuck at eight years old Mike.
Thinks that King Kong burping qualifies his body.
Right, he's like more of like a 19,
he would fit along with a Jason verse,
like 1950s little boy character,
or 1920s little boy character.
A newsie.
Like we're just like two little rascals,
but we're so innocent.
We have never heard anything bad or a curse word before.
And then there's obviously,
there's a one where it's like maybe it's like 11 p.
m.
,
and I've had half of a fruit-based cocktail,
and I'm getting loose, you know?
I'm saying, I'm not saying seed, I'm saying asshole.
I'm saying like doing your stuff,
and that's a different character.
It's like that bad Spider-Man,
who's the, when Tobey Maguire is bad?
Oh, Spider-Man three.
Yeah, the symbiote suit.
Yeah, but that's just still Spider-Man,
or does he have a different name?
I think he is, I don't think they call him
something different.
He's sort of, is he influenced by the venom?
Yeah, the venom suit is starting to turn him.
Like the venom suits inside him,
it's starting to turn him,
and then it jumps to Toifer Grace Eddie Brock.
Right, and then as far as the,
just these are off the top of my head.
I'm sure there's more, and people can identify him.
The third one I can think of is Mike Ademus.
Oh, that's right.
Of course, Mike Ademus.
Mike Ademus.
Yeah, so that's what I'm gonna blame
what you're saying on, what your gripe is about.
You gotta think about which Mike you're dealing with.
I've seen wide-eyed Comic-Con, Mike.
Comic-Con is kind of like energizing to Mike
in the way that Orlando is energizing to me.
Like- That's a good point.
Sleeps only a few hours a night,
but wants to stay out all night is like,
can I climb over that fence?
Like, who do we know?
Who can we lie and say is already in the party?
Who has like-
That's when I'm willing to, yeah,
that's when I'm willing to be a little bad boy
to get into free Comic-Con parties.
That's right.
It's like, well, we know the writer of this.
Are they here?
And- Do we know too?
Yeah.
After a year of pandemic and baby,
energized Scott is dead.
There is no such thing.
Ha ha ha!
Maybe some, maybe he'll come back in 12 years.
There's only one Scott in the Scottverse.
Yeah.
One Scottverse.
There's multiples of us.
That's right, that's right.
And he's a nudge lord.
That's right.
Maybe we do like one more run
and then we, I think we know the closer.
Yeah.
I mean, I have a lot, there's a long one I can-
I know, I ended up with a long one.
We don't have time for-
Yeah, I have a long one too.
Hey, let's maybe just do a long one.
Yeah.
Okay, I got one.
Yeah, I got a gripe all right.
Gentlemen, big fan, listen to all your collective catalog
and we'll revisit old episodes during content lulls.
In an old episode, Jason insulted people
that got married before 25.
I was fortunate to meet my soulmate and was married at 22.
We have four wonderful children, all theme park fans,
and just celebrated our 23rd anniversary.
I would ask Jason to please consider that love
isn't constrained by time and can transcend
established norms.
For whatever reason that comment has stuck with me
and making this great will allow me to continue
enjoying the show knowing my voice was heard.
Thanks, Tom.
Hey, thanks Tom and very brave of you to sign it.
Well, I'm sorry that gripe stuck with you.
I have no recollection of it and I apologize for making it
because I truly don't feel that strongly about it,
but I will say in my defense,
you've been married for 23 years.
So 23 years ago, I feel like I knew,
a lot of my older cousins were indeed getting married
around 25 or older, younger than 25.
Certainly people out here in Los Angeles,
get very career focused and sometimes put it off,
but I don't feel that strongly about it.
I feel like the reason I may have said it at the time
was I have known a number of people
who have gotten married before 25
and I also have known a good amount of people
who have married by 25 and divorced a short while later.
So that might be where I was coming from
or I just saw something from back from my hometown
where I was like, oh no, they didn't last, that's sad.
Have you considered that love can transcend
while the stuff is supposed to transcend?
I don't remember what he said.
I can, I do agree.
Yes, I do believe that love can transcend established norms,
but that is fighting against the human brain.
At this point, they've figured out the human brain
is still growing until about 25.
So I think there with all this stuff, there's a give and take
and congratulations to you guys on your anniversary.
Hey.
Yeah.
I will say, I bet there is a case of this a lot
where we said something in an episode
and somebody's like, I still remembers it
and we have no memory of it.
And it was a very casual joke.
Yes.
I'll just blanket apologize.
I think we're all pretty like goofy about like what we like
with I'll make fun of stuff I love.
There's goofy stuff everywhere.
So if we're making fun of stuff,
we might just be having fun.
I think 99% of the time we're having fun.
Yeah.
So I, you know, well, I'll make fun of journey
into your imagination, but if I'm at Epcot,
I'm going on everything.
Of course.
All right.
This is kind of long.
Let me see.
Maybe I'll only read a little part of this.
This is, this is a, was, had a title to this gripe.
Whoa.
Oh.
Sanrio Laura.
Oh, this was going to be one of mine.
So yeah, you can, you can.
Okay, great.
All right.
Great.
This is correcting the record regarding a few things
brought up in the podcast episode, Scott's Tokyo Top 10
from April 26th, 2019.
Around, around, I love this, around two hours
and nine minutes into the podcast,
you suggest that Bats Maru,
I believe it's also right.
Bats Maru is depicted gambling
on the Sanrio character boat ride.
This is incorrect.
The penguin depicted in the diorama to the right
when entering the cave section of the ride
said in the casino is actually Bats Maru's father
whom is given no name other than Papa.
You can tell it's Papa and not Bats
because he is blue instead of black,
has a cigar and a top hat.
He also, he also has a mustache above his beak,
similar to that worn by Charlie Chaplin.
Ron Male of Sparks
and a few other notable historical figures.
Papa is a Yakuza boss with a gambling addiction.
Papa is also the penguin drinking in the party scene.
Although official Sanrio materials have depicted
Bats Maru consuming alcohol as well.
Accompanying him in the diorama are Panda,
Pandaba, is that right?
And Hanamaru, which is a little strange
since they are supposed to be
his elementary school classmates.
Pandaba Panda is a tough girl who loves hip hop
for whom Bats Maru harbors a secret crush.
Hanamaru Seal is a Bats Maru's friend
despite being a goody goody tattletale.
Hanamaru's name refers to a spiral shaped mark
Japanese teachers give when a student is incorrect,
or is correct, excuse me.
When Bats Maru is named after the X mark
for when they are incorrect.
You mentioned there being a scene of Bats Maru
spying on a woman in a dressing room.
This is also false.
Wow.
The pink character is also a penguin, not a cat.
She is Bats Maru's,
and then I wait, hold on, it cut off.
Oh, I have it.
She is Bats Maru's mother, Mama,
being teased by a hiding Bats Maru
and thereby distracted from her exercise.
You can see him performing the Akanbe in this scene,
I've said that wrong, I'm sure,
which is a childish gesture usually made
to display insolence towards a parent.
Bats Maru is said to live in gorgeous town USA,
which is said to be somewhere in Hawaii.
He said, oh my God, okay, so it goes on.
At the end of the person says he's also,
who the designer of Bats Maru is,
who is also the designer of Hang Yodan the Fish,
who is one of my favorite personal characters.
I would love to talk about Hang Yodan as well,
but fear that I am reaching the end of my allotted time.
And I just jumped over a bunch.
This is great, love this.
There's a couple in the gripes list
that were incredibly long,
and sometimes the incredibly long is a sign of,
a bad one that we don't wanna touch.
Most of the time, the longer it is, the better it is.
And in this case, amazing.
Yeah, there's so much context to go through here.
But yeah, I thought there was a character
who's a bad penguin who's shown gambling
and then getting spanked or spying on a woman changing.
And apparently in both cases, a parent was involved.
This was mistaken identity on my part.
I guess I just don't know the Sanrio world well enough.
I'd say I certainly don't.
I loved this ride so much, Sanrio character boat ride.
There was even, we never did an episode
about Sanrio Pura Land where Mike also went.
I think there was talk of,
my wife Erin maybe wanted to do an episode about it.
And then I started reading her this and she's like,
oh, thank God we didn't do an episode
because I would have been wrong on all of it.
Me casually liking Sanrio when I was 12
would just result in me putting my foot in my mouth
with all this mythology.
And thanks for taking the time.
Thanks for correcting the law.
I'm really curious about all of this.
It still is a ride that includes spanking and gambling.
So it's still weird.
It's just maybe weird in different ways than I thought.
Right.
Yes, thank you for this.
This is a great gripe.
Great gripe.
It's a great gripe.
It does bring up a gripe for me
for the Google Forms developers.
You need, you should have the spreadsheet
this information spits out to automatically wrap text
in the cells that in the column
because the spreadsheet looks so insane
when we first pulled it up.
They need to upgrade this.
Google certainly does.
I also have a gripe with Google, I agree.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, the length thing will become an issue
I think in the closer.
I have a really short one before that though,
which is, unless you have more about Sanrio.
We never taught, we did never do Sanrio.
I loved Sanrio Pure Land.
I would love to talk about it.
We do have to do that.
That's a huge.
It was something, that was one of the most delightful days.
That's one of the last times that Energy Scott
reared his head back in April 2019.
But here's a really quick one.
Stop bringing on that unfunny defunct land guy,
sincerely Kevin P.
We can only assume that that Kevin P
is the defunct land guy, and I won't use that word
that he used.
I think there was a kerfuffle on our Facebook page
where somebody was, I don't know if you call it ratioed
on Facebook, but somebody just really took a swing
that everyone agreed that they don't like Kevin Berger.
And he was, everybody really piled on him,
which yeah, hey, Kevin's great.
We have Kevin on whenever.
Right.
In the groups, on the internet, but also, you know,
guests enter at your own, you know, enter at your own,
your private Facebook groups where things you've created
may be discussed.
Oh yeah.
Tread lightly.
Well, we've learned that in this episode,
just trading lightly with feedback in general.
really quick, I'm just gonna list these out.
People did say like topics that they wanna hear,
and that's a welcome gripe, we'll always take that.
I'm just gonna say a couple quick ones.
Yosemite Sam Gold River Adventure at Six Flags Over Texas,
which is a boat ride with animatronic Looney Tunes.
Would love to, that sounds great.
That sounds awesome.
Please always send us ideas
that you're passionate about.
Silver Dollar City, for sure.
Busch Gardens Williamsburg, Carowinds, absolutely.
These are two that come up a lot lately,
and maybe there's a good chance to address them.
Stu Leonard's.
Stu Leonard's is a grocery chain.
The one that this guy mentioned is in Yonkers,
I think there's a bunch of them.
It's in the northeast of the country.
It's a grocery chain with a lot of animatronics,
and probably everybody's thinking,
well, this is similar to Fry's, like odd amount of theming
for being just a regular store.
I think we do have to do this, and I wanna go pretty bad,
and I just don't know if I'm gonna go.
I don't know if we're gonna end up in like Yonkers, are we?
Jason, you end up, are you anywhere near a Stu Leonard's
when you're visiting your folks?
I don't think so.
Wait, this isn't the one with the monorail outside?
That's a different one.
There's also, I don't know if it's the monorail one,
there's also Jungle Gyms, which is a similar thing
that I think is in Ohio.
I wanna do all of these.
I just would love to go, but how feasible is it to go?
Obviously not at all right now.
If you're fine with us doing these topics without going,
then we'll do it.
I don't know, are you guys as enthusiastic
about these animatronic grocery stores as me?
I'd like to go.
A couple people have said it to me,
of like, do you know about Jungle Gyms?
Like, yes, I think we've talked about Jungle Gyms before.
Maybe briefly.
I think it's come up.
Maybe with Doug Jones.
We look into a live, we could look at it,
we will do a live show again, fingers crossed.
We can always try to see, oh, we're gonna do it here.
Maybe it's not too far out of the way.
Let's look into the locations and see
if it even seems possible, and then we'll decide,
oh, maybe we'll just do it.
Maybe we'll find a guest who has been and we'll see.
Maybe somebody has to have been on the ground.
That's a good rule.
I have a couple that have been sent to me recently
that I think are, one we could go to at some point
in the future that's close.
Fran Comstock sent this to me.
The Capri Room, there's a buka in Encino that.
Buca di Beppo?
Buca di Beppo.
I'm just calling it, there's a buca.
We got a buca.
There's a buca that shows, it becomes a plot point
in The Real Housewives of Beverly Hills,
because one of them invests in this location
or becomes a part owner of this location,
and there's a lot of Robert Earl in these episodes
because he is that Real Housewives' son's godfather,
I think, and that was very funny to discover,
to learn about.
And the other thing that we have been sent to us
a few times that I have to go back and watch this,
because I think I watched it when I was kind of
falling asleep one night, is the,
I think it's called the Mouseketeers Go to the Magic Kingdom.
It's on Disney+.
Yeah, oh, that's one of those great,
it's awesome that they started adding stuff like that
with the commercials.
It's a real TV special.
Yeah, yeah, sure.
Love to talk about that.
The other big one, I've been seeing this a lot lately,
Casa Bonita, which famous from the South Park episode,
it's in Denver, I believe.
I watched a video, inspired by that,
I watched a video all about Casa Bonita.
It looks like it rules.
The people who work there seem great.
I hope they're doing okay in the pandemic.
I'm concerned about it.
That one, I feel like I can't,
I have to go to Casa Bonita in person.
And if you don't know what we're talking about,
this like amazing restaurant with gliff divers,
it's just some of,
I think it's my literal favorite South Park.
It's just such joy from Cartman,
who does horrible things to get to go there.
But cliff divers in Black Brides Cave,
and would love to do Casa Bonita.
I've just been seeing it enough,
I wanna say we're not ignoring this request.
Right, yeah, no, I would like to go as well.
It's obviously, it's more themed,
but it's almost like there's some elements of it
that remind me of Clifton's Downtown LA.
Yes.
Which is probably an episode,
if you've been there before.
Clifton's great.
Walt loved it.
Yeah.
They refurbed it a few, what, years ago at this point?
Yeah, yeah, it's really great.
Yeah.
Yeah, well anyway, I would love to do all that.
Hopefully do it in person, but else I gotta,
boy, there's a lot of,
I'm gonna go broke with travel after this apparently.
Well, do we close with the big one?
And also, how much can we possibly do?
I'm already ashamed.
I feel like most of it, by the way, is reading it.
I'm embracing myself.
But I think it's the reading more than the answering,
although you guys tell me,
because you're on the hook more than I am, obviously.
Do we spread this out like a,
do we assign each other parts, like a table read?
Do you all have it?
Oh, that's a good question, yeah, yeah.
Let me look.
Yeah, let me get in front of me.
Do you need me to send it to you if?
Oh yeah, maybe let's do that.
I have it here, but maybe I'm gonna make sure
I have all of it, because apparently it wasn't copying well
from those Google Docs.
Damn Google Docs.
I could put it in the chat also.
Maybe that's the way.
Yeah, throw it in the chat.
That's how much, this is quite a tome
that we're dealing with.
Which is not much better,
which is also not the chat feature on Zoom.
No, it's not, it's not letting me copy it even.
Too long.
Here, maybe, here's what we'll do.
Oh, I can't copy this either.
Yeah, I got it in front of me.
Mike, see if you can find it.
I'll read up through point one.
Jason, you take over at point two,
and Mike, if you can get to it by point three.
All right, here we go.
Yeah, I've got a gripe regarding the Lucy attribute episode,
and it's about the myriad of factual errors
presented present in this recording,
as well as the lack of apology for spreading such falsehoods.
Scott, you're excused from this,
because you knew barely anything throughout this whole episode.
Ah, phew.
My expectations for you were low here, and rightfully so.
These righteous complaints are unfortunately only
for Mike and Jason, who billed themselves
as the I Love Lucy experts of the podcast.
This, by the way, is the understood the assignment gripe.
Mike stated within the episode
that his mom would have the most corrections for this episode,
so I'm sure she already lectured you boys at length
about these mistakes.
Nonetheless, I feel compelled to address them again,
and I'm sure Mike's mom would agree
that these need to be addressed on air.
Thank you in advance to Ms.
Carlson for taking my side.
Mike, Jason, you said you'd apologize via YouTube
and issue retractions to the false facts in this episode,
but I've yet to see anything of the sort.
Well, I don't think they knew, and now they will.
With that said, this person's grievances are as follows.
Number one, approximately 15 minutes into the episode,
Mike says he knows the longest studio laugh break in history,
which is when Lucy is secretly holding eggs
and they get crushed.
Mike falsely identifies this as taking place
in a Lucy-Desi comedy hour.
Michael, he means business because he uses the full Michael.
This was in a regular 30-minute I Love Lucy episode
in the Connecticut season, and they're not in her apron.
They're hidden in her shirt because they're trying
to sneak eggs out to the chicken coops
to make Ricky and Fred think the hens started laying eggs.
Deep down, you know this, I know this,
your mom surely knows this.
Jason then goes on to say,
and then someone gives her a bear hug or something,
and while I'm disappointed in Jason
for getting this fact wrong, I'm more disappointed in Mike.
Oh my God, for not correcting him
as he brought up this scene in the first place.
The eggs are broken when Ricky asks Lucy
to practice their tango for the PTA show,
and she spins into him, crushing all the eggs
in one of the most iconic scenes in comedy history.
Mike then says, I did not relook this up,
it's just something I have in my mind, my memory.
It doesn't seem like you do, Michael.
Well, I did partially in there.
It was partially in there.
Intermission, do you wanna address anything
in the before we move on?
I mean, look, this person is 100% correct.
It was not a Lucy Desi comedy hour, which they made,
and I'm about to say more facts, and now I'm just,
I'm gun shy here as far as, I was gonna say they made
like nine Lucy Desi comedy hours,
which are longer than the Lucy,
than the I Love Lucy episodes.
I think that's right, I apologize ahead of time
if I'm wrong.
I do remember the tango, I do remember that is 100% correct,
there's nothing I need to correct here, I can't clap back.
All I have to say is that I apologize,
and I'm gonna be saying it a lot.
I'm gonna be saying a lot during this one.
Mike, I don't believe, I'm pretty sure
you don't have daughters.
If you do and I don't know about it,
feel free to blame them in a Ted Cruz-esque manner.
Your daughters were distracting you
from having proper I Love Lucy knowledge.
I won't use the excuse yet, I think when we get
even into worse things that Jason and I possibly did
or said about Lucy and Lucy history,
that I might blame some anonymous daughters, yes.
Jason part two?
I'll use this intermission to do a real quick gripe
within a gripe, because I see right under it
the spreadsheet I'm looking at, it says,
how the hell could you not have Griffin Newman
on a Fast and Furious episode,
that's a podcast felony in my book, boyos.
I thought the same thing, but then when we last talked
to him, he said he had not written Fast and Furious
Supercharged in Orlando, so I did not think it was,
you know, quite right to have him on the episode,
but I'm sure once he gets back to visiting Orlando
like the rest of us, he will give us his full opinion.
Seems like a perfect time for a full redo episode.
It seems like it, that's how we roll.
More of that, oh man.
That's right.
We roll like this.
All right, we'll discuss that later, part two.
Part two, is this me taking over?
Yeah.
Okay, this is the bullet point number two.
I don't know, it starts with later in the episode,
Jason, Ike.
Yeah, I see it.
Here, let me just make sure I can see all of it.
Again, ashamed, shame.
Let's see.
I can do it if you want.
Oh my gosh.
Okay.
Yeah, here, switch.
Okay, later in the episode, Jason says that at some point,
Fred and Ricky went into an egg business together,
and it's casually mentioned that Fred is now the manager
of Ricky's band.
Jason, Fred was Ricky's manager throughout the entire
Europe vacation season.
That's why the Mertzes got to tag along.
That's why Ricky tried to fire Fred when the band ended up
in the wrong town in Switzerland,
leading the gang to having free time
to go hiking in the Alps.
This was not a casual mention,
this was a full blown plot point.
And at some point, they went into an egg business together.
Jason, they dedicated at least two whole episodes
to the chickens right at the beginning
of the Connecticut season.
One of these being the egg tango episode
that was previously addressed.
It was thoroughly explained.
It seems to me that you need to rewatch
the Connecticut season,
because the errors here are astounding.
That's quite a punishment, Jason.
I'm sorry, but the man has spoken.
Well, there's a little more for me though.
Oh yes, yes.
Okay.
Furthermore, Mike then expressed confusion
over the Connecticut plot point of Fred and Ethel
leaving New York and didn't know that Fred had
Mrs.
Trumbull's sister manage the apartment building
after they moved.
Though to Mike's credit,
he did apologize for not knowing this.
I can appreciate the courage it took
to admit he didn't know this crucial fact
about a beloved character, Mrs.
Trumbull's sister.
From Jason, no apology.
Wow.
Well, I'll start off by saying I'm sorry for that.
I think you have to say what you're sorry for,
because I got lost.
What's the specific?
I'm sorry for, oh God.
Yeah, what is the specific?
All right, all right.
You're supposed to apologize for not knowing
that Fred managed Ricky's band for a long time,
that it was a main plot point.
Wait, it's Mrs.
Trumbull's sister is what he wants.
Yeah.
Well, that's for me.
That was more for me.
Oh, okay.
But I apologize for not knowing ahead of time,
so I'm in the clear on this paragraph.
I will apologize and say it's very possible
I was doing an allusion to the creative
energy of the Connecticut seasons
when everyone was checked out.
And I also haven't checked out.
Well, this isn't gonna help.
Now you're dissing the Connecticut season.
No, no, no, no.
Jason, you're making great this worse.
We're gonna get four, five, and six next round of grapes.
Oh no.
All the I Love Lucy people were just done with each other
by the time they're like,
I guess we're in Connecticut now.
I'm sorry.
You know, it's, it's sometimes they say stuff
very offhandedly in those shows to, you know,
rejigger people's memory.
And some of them made very far apart.
I think you're making too many excuses.
All right, I'm sorry.
I dropped the ball on the Connecticut season specifics
and also the European outing specifics, okay?
I will, look, they weren't calling on an apology,
but I will apologize for not remembering
Mrs.
Trumbull's sister, a character that I am now
immediately who's been refreshed in my brain,
a big fan of Mrs.
Trumbull's sister.
Now I was about to say,
did we ever see Mrs.
Trumbull's sister?
I don't remember.
And this might be opening me up to a future paragraph
of complaints that there will, yes, of course,
we saw multiple episodes about Mrs.
Trumbull's sister,
but I don't know.
So I apologize.
There is one more little chunk.
Jason, do you want to take it?
Do you have it or?
I have it if Jason doesn't have it.
Yeah, Mike, you read it,
because I think mine got cut off somehow.
I'm having a tough time.
Okay, and finally, number three,
Jason says that Ricky sings the theme song,
title of Lucy, when Lucy tells Ricky she's Spectin.
That's a different episode, a birthday episode.
In the pregnancy episode,
Ricky sings the classic song,
we're having a baby, my baby and me.
The lyrics to the I Love Lucy theme
are not at all about how Lucy is expecting.
It would be entirely out of place here.
And now the sum up.
Boys, it's hard to be mad at you about these errors.
You love William Frawley as I do.
We come from the same world, you and I,
but when a man's wrong, he's wrong and he should say so.
Am I a crazy person with an encyclopedic knowledge
of I Love Lucy episodes?
Yes, yes, we'll say yes.
I know that.
Do I expect everyone to have
the same knowledge level as me?
Of course not.
I know I stand above the rest, alone in my craziness,
but Mike and Jason, I did expect you to rise to this occasion,
to rise to the tribute.
To the co?
Please apologize, to me, to Mike's mom, to the world.
This hurts, folks.
Boy, this was the dark mirror that you were worried about
staring into when we proposed this.
You did it to yourself, Mike, Michael,
the full series name.
You know what?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry to you.
The song, I think I remembered when I got in my car
and immediately felt like, oh my God, I hate, God damn it.
But I appreciate that you came to us
and that you looked me right in the eye,
when you did it, when you plunged the knife in,
looked me right in the eye and made me feel a fool,
as opposed to the Muppet people
who will snipe me from a clock tower.
Oh God, oh yeah, yeah, don't.
We gotta search through Muppet stuff in these grapes.
We're in a lot of trouble.
filter out Muppet.
I will, again, formally apologize to this anonymous griper,
to my mother, to the world.
For the things I was inaccurate about
the difference between Lucy Desi Comedy Hour
and the regular I Love Lucy show, Connecticut Seasons.
So I deeply apologize.
I will try to watch more I Love Lucy
to make sure all of this stuff
is a little bit fresher in my mind.
And yes, you, whoever you are,
I think that we have a lot in common
when it comes to William Frawley.
And I would like to just say
that I will listen to William Frawley's album tonight.
Sings the old ones.
Bill Frawley Sings the Old Ones.
I think that's the name of it.
If it's not, I apologize again ahead of it.
And I would like also commend you
for my favorite gripe on this list.
Yeah, you nailed it.
Person one, he won, but also,
I think you guys nailed the art of the apology.
There's a lot of talk of people not nailing the apology.
And I think you manned up and you did it.
You acknowledged many of the specific bullet points.
And this was a lot easier for me
who was let off the hook hours ago into this gripe.
I just really got to sit back and relax.
So thank you also to this person
for expecting nothing from me.
Yes, here's what I'd like to say.
I'd like to make Jason feel better at the end of the show
by revealing a piece of information
unrelated to gripes that I think will make him feel better.
I'm not worried about myself.
I'm very selfless.
But Jason, I would like to say,
and this has been a real roller coaster of information,
but I have been given recently some information
about the Jim Belushi story you told.
Oh.
Now we believed this to be an incorrect story
because we heard it was actually about the show Cougar Town.
I am now being told that both stories are correct.
Whoa.
Oh my gosh.
And that your Jim Belushi story about angry crew members
throwing DVDs into his car is accurate as well.
The source was initially confused has confirmed
that both incidents, possibly one inspired by the other,
happened.
So you were correct.
Whoa.
On a positive note, you were correct.
Oh, wow.
About your Jim Belushi story.
So we have come full circle here and you were correct.
I wanted to make you feel better.
Jason wins in multiple ways.
And the big message, if you're making a movie,
you're making a TV show, you always be nice to the crew.
That's right.
You always be nice to the crew.
You make sure they first,
you say thank you on the way out.
Always be nice to the crew.
Yeah.
That's right.
That's why we're nice to,
we have to be especially nice to Mike,
who counts as the crew of this
because he edits some of them.
That's true.
I could add, you know what?
I could really, I could cut up you guys saying stuff
and really make it sound bad.
I could cut up that I Love Lucy episode
and make Jason's facts even more wrong.
Oh.
And if you.
I could just insert like the name Frank Nelson
in a spot where he said Gail Gordon
and then it would make you sound so foolish.
No.
And if you were.
I just got my emotions under control.
If you were really mad about anything that we had done,
you could take, really to either of us,
Jason just gave us a Trump Plaza,
a deck of playing cards that's still on the desk.
You could take each playing card
and slide it into our car until our car was full
and that would send a message.
But you don't do that.
So thank you, you get to eat first.
When we're done here.
All right, thank you.
In our separate places of recording, you eat before us.
Thank you, yeah.
All right, good, thank you.
And I guess with that, we should wrap up the group.
We'll just stand down for now.
You know, not so bad.
Well, that's easy for me to say
because I got taken off the hook at the beginning of that.
But do you, this wasn't, I think,
I think this was fine.
I think that it, I think we let people know
kind of what we're looking for in a gripe.
And I don't know, I guess keep them,
do we wanna leave it open
or do we wanna bury the gripe box?
Should we make a, well, maybe let's just make a,
if we do it again, maybe let's make a whole new form
so we can clear this.
Get this our fresh.
Let's make it like a cute Earth, like Valentine wishes.
Yeah.
I said your little wishes to podcast the ride.
And.
Hey.
Put your name and social security number for the FBI.
Well.
Send Amazon wish list for podcast the ride.
Wait, no, the wait, they're sending us their Amazon?
We're making a wish list that they can.
Yeah, we make a wish list.
Oh, well, I like that.
Yeah.
So now they gotta give us presents
instead of gripes to make things even.
Well, yeah, I'm just saying,
these are ideas I'm floating.
I don't think we have to decide on anything right now.
Hey, you guys are the ones
who are all about doing topics again.
Why doesn't gripes count as one of those?
Don't you think that we've exhausted gripes for now?
It just feels like we've really gotten to the meat of it.
And it's like, what are we really gonna even say
on the second one?
What is even there left to say?
Well, for now, yes.
You survived podcast the ride, McGrew edition.
I don't know.
We will, obviously the form will be there if you find it.
Will we ever open the box again
or will it be put up in an infinite room of shelves
like the Ark of the Covenant may be?
That remains to be seen.
We hope you enjoyed it at least.
We got a lot of really important stuff straight
and that's the important thing.
Yes.
And as always, thank you for listening.
That's what's important.
And thank you for your support.
Absolutely.
And we say that now,
especially that we're more scared of you.
That's right.
Humboldt.
All right, on that note, McGrew out.