Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast contains annoying seafood, bankruptcy, and animatronics that are very divorced.
In order to listen, you must redeem 150,000 tickets.
Jamie Loftus returns for Chuck E. Cheese 2 on today's podcast, The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the podcast about theme parks that won't let in any listeners who don't pass our patented weird adult check.
I'm Scott Entertainment Gardener, joined by Mike Entertainment Carlson.
I am here, I'd like to say hello and thank you to all of the little Cliffords listening out there.
The new name for our listeners, Cliffords.
I'd just like to say thank you for listening and your support.
Seems like everybody was fine with it.
As fine as I was hearing it.
The idea that our fans are now named after the Martin Short movie about the creepy man child Clifford.
It's fine, it's all fine.
Hey, and of course we're also joined by Jason P. Pieplate.
Hello Jason.
That's right.
Now everyone will please make sure you have the identical hand stamp, the matching hand stamps.
We can continue with the recording.
We discovered Jason playing drums on pie plates in a kitchen.
That's how we started this whole podcast, is we heard him rhythmically drumming.
And that's why.
So that's why we didn't know he was a perfect fit for this.
I can distinctly remember Mike like holding his hand up to his ear going like, hey, do that again.
What was that? I said.
I think he really got something there.
Yeah. So that's the origin story.
Marvin Berry kind of moment.
Right.
Look, this is very exciting.
We're returning to the world of Chuck E. Cheese, one of our favorite topics.
It's been two years since we talked about it and now it's Chuck E. Cheese 2.
It's been an interesting two years, you would say, for Chuck E. Cheese.
You might say horrible.
You might say disastrous.
There's probably a lot of things you could say.
And we're so excited to be joined once again by our guest from the previous episode, I guess, resident Chuck E.
Cheese expert and also great comedian, writer, podcaster from the LIDA podcast, Jamie Loftus.
Jamie, wait, Jamie E. Loftus.
I think that legally I need to end Henny because there can only be one.
There can never be one.
Jamie Henny.
What an ugly name.
It's so I mean, not that I guess I guess Helen Henny is no better thought out than any of the other character names.
Except Pasquale, which I Pasquale P. Pie plate is pretty brilliant.
Helen Henny. It just feels so half-assed.
Yeah, well, like we were talking the last time you were here, we talked about the other female characters that they just threw away.
But they had more fun names like Sally Sachet.
Yeah, they had good ones.
Actually thought out ones. Yeah.
I learned a little more than I had previously about Dolly Dimples.
Dimples is a lot of fun.
She's like kind of a I guess sort of a Mae West type hippo in kind of a sort of a clown wig is what the hair is like.
That sounds safe.
Yeah, yeah.
I feel like they've introduced a new female character in the last year named Bella.
What is Bella? I don't know about Bella.
Bella is new. I can't tell.
So what there's a lot to unpack, but like I can't tell how like where you go to find out what is currently canon because no matter where you go, it seems like you're operating on a kind of a different level of canon.
Bella is a bunny.
She speaks Spanish.
She's friends with Helen Henney, but she exists solely on the YouTube channel.
She's just only there.
She's nowhere else.
Right. We've talked a little bit about this.
They produce still to this day so much content and they put it on YouTube and there are just like long running parodies they've done on YouTube.
They put full albums on YouTube.
They put new dances on YouTube.
And I also came.
I don't know.
There were new characters I was finding when I went through and I was like, is this a one off?
Is this something that's are they part of the magical whatever five that we know now?
They interviewed Michael Pena like last week.
Yeah, I want to talk about that.
I would love to talk about the Michael Pena interview because it came out.
I checked.
I checked. It came out the same week as the Meghan Harry Oprah interview.
And I feel like it really got, you know, kind of swept under the rug because there was just another big ticket interview and no one was talking about Chuckie and Michael Pena promoting Tom and Jerry from his house.
Yes, because we're like in the this year's promotion is named the four C the celebration of the four seasons of fun.
Which for spring, the spring celebration is a tie in with the Tom and Jerry movie.
And he does interview Michael Pena.
And now it is can and seemingly that Michael Pena is Chuck E.
Cheese's favorite actor.
Yes, he says he says in the top of the interview, you're my favorite actor.
And that at the end, I love your work.
I love World Trade Center.
I don't know how well, uh, command.
What is the what is the Seth Rogen mall movie?
Observe and report.
I don't know that it's age well, but I bet your performance is evergreen in it.
You really commit it well to the character.
I loved how in because you could tell.
I mean, I guess I would assume and maybe I can't tell if I'm being like truly like out of my mind here, but I'm like, I'm guessing that it wasn't actually Chuckie on the other end.
It was just some guy being like, and then Chuckie will say this and then Chuckie will say this because I feel like if were I Michael Pena, unless he's just a really like smooth operator, I would have had bigger reactions to what was going on on the other end.
Like if Chuckie cheese told me you are my favorite actor, I love your work.
I would be crying like he was just like, oh, okay, thanks.
Like he didn't seem very into it.
It was really stiff.
It felt extremely space ghosty in its level of disconnect.
So like, did they properly explain what was going on?
Did they repurpose like a just an affiliate feed from a Kansas City news station and make it Chuckie later?
It's I'm glad we all caught this.
This was a very strange event.
Okay, Michael, Michael, stand by the bowling for soup guy is coming on the line.
And now he's not the bowling for soup guy.
When he talks to you, he's Chuckie cheese, but you probably know him as the bowling for soup guy.
Is Michael Pena more likely to know Chuckie?
I don't know how old he is, so I don't know if Chuckie cheese would have been a big thing for him.
But I wonder if he's more familiar with Chuckie cheese or bowling for soup just personally.
I think that says a lot about who you are.
Yes. How would you if he if he were to rank them in terms of how much he liked it?
Yeah, yeah. If now if you if you before the voice change, we're already a massive Chuckie cheese fan and a massive bowling for soup fan, then there was a certain day 10 years or so ago that was like better than a thousand birthdays.
This would have been it.
I guess we should say I mean, I would suggest the listener go back and listen to our first episode probably before doing this, because this is we're really throwing you in the deep end here.
Chuckie cheese, of course, in the last 10 ish years has been voiced by the lead singer of the rock and roll band bowling for soup.
I just want to do some filling in in case you're starting here.
You're starting on the Empire Strikes Back of Chuckie cheese podcast, the right episodes.
We are throwing you right in.
We'll try to Cliff notes things here and there.
That's important info.
The thriving YouTube channel is important info, which was news to me the last time we did an episode.
There's also something from that YouTube channel.
This came up on our Patreon, but not on the main feed.
And I well, Jamie, it seems like you like catch the YouTube channel pretty frequently.
I'm sorry.
OK, then you probably know this was this is back in September.
So you you you've very well probably saw this, but we discovered around the holidays that Munch is now a DJ with sort of a dead mouse marshmallow vibe.
And we were pretty into this.
Really? This is our favorite move in a while.
I forgot about this.
Yes. And I also liked that the comments are turned off for that video for some reason.
Yeah, very deflective of any criticism that who would be mad.
I DJ Munch rules.
I love it.
Super cool.
The the comments were also turned off on a video I watched right before we started, which I ended up on the forums, the forums that are really devoted to all this, which is called the forums are now called Retro Pizza Zone.
And I saw a thread that was about what is the worst Chuck E.
Cheese show video, I guess, like, OK, the videos that played behind them and songs, the combos or whatever.
People were trying to say was the one they like.
They disliked the most.
And there was somebody really adamant about January 96 is the worst of all time or January 96.
Number two, I'm still mad about it.
And I watched it.
It was just kind of a confusing piece about Helen trying to be a cheerleader and auditioning to be a cheerleader against like 11 year old girls, like much younger.
It was just baffling more than anything.
But somebody really hated it.
And the comments were turned off.
And it made me wonder, did the retro pizza zone crew all come and attack the comments and the user at, you know, nip all that in the bud?
There's a lot of rage, apparently.
I'm questioning if we should even be doing this again.
I don't I don't want to incite anyone's anger, but I that that sounds like more of a them problem.
That sounds like a perfectly fun tape.
Watching it, watching a gigantic costumed hen in direct competition with a real human child.
I have no problem with it.
Sounds great.
I mean, go to the school like worried.
Does she even qualify for this?
Does she is?
How do they know each other?
School.
I thought she works and is in a band.
So if she's 12, then that's weird.
I was unclear how old they are.
Yeah.
How does any of they all dress like they're 12?
Like original Rat Chucky is probably older than little boy skateboard rock and roll mouse.
Yeah, it seems like he seems like he's 56.
Yeah, he's an older man.
He's like he's in the Friars Club and he's an older man.
And then, yeah, the mouse version seems like he could be 15.
Mm hmm.
Yeah, it's unclear.
And they're all kind of like children now, like the puppet versions actually all feel like they could be like nine.
Yeah, I like the puppet versions, by the way, in general.
I like it a lot.
Yeah, yeah, I think so.
They satisfy like that they aren't creepy.
I can see why a brand would want to be not creepy these days.
I think like, I don't know, I could see kids liking these little puppet and maybe like never even going to the restaurant.
Maybe Chuck E. Cheese is all digital now.
Well, especially, yeah, if they're doing school at home, they have a run of videos called like Daily Afternoon Break.
They only update them like every three weeks, so they're not quite daily.
It was a good reminder, though, of a very strange YouTube feature.
Like a big thing I use for the show a lot is the save button on YouTube that adds it to a watch later playlist.
And for some reason, that is disabled for videos for, quote unquote, for kids.
But sometimes people will just tag stuff that's been ripped to YouTube for kids, I guess, so it doesn't get copyright strikes.
So there's just some you can't.
But I don't understand why that would protect children is turning off the watch later option.
Yeah, there are a lot of feature.
I don't know.
This is how interesting this is, but there's a lot of restrictions on the Chuck E.
Cheese videos.
I was watching on my phone yesterday and you can't minimize the video and search for another video while you're watching.
It'll turn the video off for some reason.
There's some feature.
Yeah, I don't know.
Like I wanted to minimize the video on the YouTube app and then search for another Chuck E.
Video while I'm watching the one in the little tiny window.
No, they will not let you do that.
That's off limits, too, on the Chuck E.
Cheese YouTube.
They're very specific, particular about what they're allowing for some reason.
I don't know.
That's yeah.
I was like, what are they hiding?
What's their end game there?
So you can't stop watching their their stuff.
Also not. I mean, no offense to our boy, but not many people are watching it.
You know, it's like they average less than 10 K a video.
I mean, is it are they trying to crush dissent?
Are they trying to stop negative discourse surrounding as a is it a freedom of speech thing?
I mean, possibly.
I don't know.
I'm just are they trying to hide?
Are they trying to hide five children missing from Chuck E.
Cheese? Did everyone come across that hoax from last year?
I don't remember this hoax from last year.
There's a lot of stuff we teased at the top.
We'll talk about this as far as the recent years.
We should probably start with that.
What's been going on?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah, yeah.
What's been up?
I guess a lot has has been up.
We can start with some some of the more famous things.
And we know we've talked about this a little and this really got out there.
But very early in in Pandemic 1.0 in the first generation of this never ending thing,
there was this strange story about people getting on Uber Eats or Postmates or whatever
and seeing a pizza place in their neighborhood they've never heard of before
that is called Pasquale's Pizza and Wings.
And then once it gets there, maybe doing the math and putting together that this came from Chuck E.
Cheese for people who didn't know all this bullshit.
They didn't realize maybe they know people did not recognize the name Pasquale offhand.
But we, of course, saw what we would have known as soon as we saw.
Yes, regular people, it seems like, don't know that he's Pasquale.
So that was a big that was a big early spike in the recent past with of Chuck E.
Cheese oddity.
Yes.
Well, and it had the big story that kind of broke it was in west of Philadelphia where there is an unrelated
Pasquale's Pizza.
But now in later Pandemic, they are full on advertising on the Chuck E.
Cheese.
And then they are like, Pasquale's Pizza and Wings available on delivery.
I love this pivot.
I think it's genius.
I love it.
I agree.
They've leaned in so far.
It is based on I almost last night I almost like took the challenge and was like, oh,
I'll order one pizza from Chuck E.
Cheese and one from Pasquale's and see what happens.
But then it was like, I will almost definitely have two inedible pizzas.
I've done this before and people have done it before.
I looked it up on YouTube and my boyfriend and I found a channel called Big John TV.
It's a family channel.
They've done it.
It's definitely the same pizza.
It's made at the same location.
They said that Pasquale's Pizza might have more sauce, but that could also just be at where they are.
But it's the same pizza.
I think it's so fun.
And they say like on the website as featured in the New Yorker and Newsday.
And so I was like, what did the New Yorker say about Pasquale's Pizza?
And what they just said is that it exists.
They said this new brand is the latest example of Chuck E.
Cheese Entertainment creatively adjusting to meet the needs of consumers in a unique way, allowing for more variety and convenient options available for delivery.
And that's just quoting a spokesperson from Chuck E.
Cheese.
They also said that Pasquale's uses different ingredients from the standard Chuck E.
Cheese pie to produce a more premium pizza experience.
That's all the New Yorker said.
They didn't say it was good.
They didn't say that they'd tried it, but it was technically featured in the New Yorker.
So, yeah, they weren't lying.
It feels the whole thing feels to me like like an afterthought.
Like, Jason, you're saying suddenly they're embracing it.
Suddenly it's on the site.
But when this all happened, it was just a weird Reddit discovery.
And then all of a sudden once reached for comment, they had all this stuff to say about it.
But then why didn't they say it first?
Why was there no press release about this?
It seems like they got caught and then had pulled together corporate claptrap and pretend like this is always the plan.
Right.
It was a trick.
It was started out as a trick.
This is like some old Chuck stuff.
And there were other like there are other restaurants doing it.
I don't I didn't check if any other restaurant has just really made a spin off company to instead of admitting they made a mistake.
But I don't know, because it was like I think Chili's had done it.
This whole this whole I went down the the Big John TV rabbit hole because this was a series this family was doing of ordering like one from the actual restaurant and one from like the fake name the restaurant made up.
But it was like Chili's had done it.
Applebee's had done it.
Smokey Bones had done it.
But Chuck E. Cheese were the only ones that got really brutally called out for it.
There is a big price difference.
I think Shakey's pizza.
Oh really?
Yeah.
Shakey's didn't?
Huh.
But these things don't have IP.
They can't like like what is it?
What's the fake Applebee's called or what's the fake Shakey's called?
Do we know?
Well, Shakey's was selling like Shakey's chicken sandwiches and Mojo potatoes.
I keep getting Instagram ads of these disgusting looking chicken sandwiches with just like a inch of mayo on top and bottom of the chicken.
And I'm like Shakey's what the hell man this sucks.
Applebee's was called Neighborhood Wings.
Oh, yeah.
I think it's like the knockoff Halloween costumes we talked about a little while back.
Like what word soup can we do that reminds you of our name?
But why are they avoiding their own copyright and yet trying to evoke their own themes and characters?
What is this entire operation?
I think they're trying to hit like multiple markets because obviously there's people that love chain bad chain restaurants.
And then there's people that are like I'd rather order like locally with stuff that I feel like is better.
It's not just mass produced chain restaurant crap.
So they're trying to trick.
It's all an elaborate trick of having multiple.
I think there was one.
I forget which restaurant that was doing.
They like four different names on an app.
So they were trying to appeal to like four different types of people.
Like your person that might like a chain restaurant and the person that wants like just like a mom and pop pizza place.
Like so I think they're just trying to it's a trick.
It's an elaborate trick to just market to different types of consumers.
That's what I think.
Yeah.
Early in the pandemic, too, I didn't really know what a ghost kitchen was.
And now I feel like I know everything about them.
Like I think I've ordered from like three different ones that most notorious, the flavor town kitchen being run out of the city walk.
Wait, really?
Oh, yes.
Yeah.
Because Robert Earl and Guy Fieri have an existing relationship with their chicken guy endeavor.
And so, yeah, if you if you look up flavor town, you can order from the city walk location or the Encino location.
And he shared kitchens out of the book.
I still find it baffling that you say just book.
I feel does anyone else on earth only say book?
I cannot.
Well, I feel like I'm family when I'm there, you know, and I also cannot remember which one I'm supposed to say.
Oh, it's so you don't have to say the right.
So I don't have to say Beppo or Peppo.
I cannot remember in this moment, as usual, which is the actual one.
If you had to guess which one it was, though, which one is it?
I think I think it's Beppo.
It's the one that's the alliterative one.
Yes, it is Beppo.
You're correct.
Where did Peppo come from?
That's just I don't know.
Just said Peppo and we roasted him pretty hard the first time.
Yeah.
Now it's in his head and we've ruined his.
There's a lot of things we've we've ruined in his brain.
It's just ruined.
And someone ran the literal translation.
One of the incorrect one, I believe, translates to Beephole.
Oh, yeah.
All I just think about is Beephole.
We're trying to reach for this word, this name.
This was the first Christmas Eve in like five years that I didn't go to Bucatabeppo
for my Christmas Eve dinner.
Oh, that's right.
Geez.
Well, then you're on a first name.
You should just do Bucca.
Yeah, we're pretty close.
I like to pass the picture of Buzz Aldrin eating the gigantic meatball.
Give it a high five as I pass.
Is that a back at home thing or are you going to the City Walk or the Encino or something?
I would go to the which the one at the is it the Grove that has one?
I think it was the Grove.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
OK. Yeah.
And I just I never went home for like my first five years living here.
I didn't go home.
And so my my other friends who didn't go home would meet at Bucatabeppo.
We would get we would buy the pictures and everything.
It would be it was a blast.
Is there a there's like a is it a pope?
It's a pope room at City Walk.
Is there a pope room in each Bucatabeppo?
I've only ever gotten sat on the balcony, which I don't know if that is like a compliment or an insult.
But they they I've only been.
Yeah, I've been sat at the same place over and over and over, which maybe is just where they sit when no one's there because it's Christmas Eve.
And that's the only time I've ever been.
But they sit you next to this gorgeous statue of a naked lady.
And she's in the picture.
And and it's and it's a blast.
All right.
We have five years worth of these photos.
That's great.
That is great.
We have to get to all the locations at a certain point when we do a big book Bucatabeppo like Saga, I think.
Yeah.
Like figure out.
Which one's the best nationwide?
All of them.
Did you guys do the the pope room at the time?
We toured the I toured the pope.
I didn't sit and eat there.
It seemed like this was a range like we had to know a guy.
Yeah.
When I say tour, we walked around the table and took pictures and giggled.
That's basically what we did.
We have photos from the pope room.
That was the only I've only actually eaten there once.
It was that time we did a couple of years ago.
Yeah.
When we're all vaccinated, we'll have to reserve the Capri room at the Encino one, which is the one that a real housewife of Beverly Hill designed.
And it looks like she just bought every piece of all the branches and fake lemons from a Michael's Crafts and just filled a room with it.
So good.
That's high on the list.
Yeah, it genuinely is, really.
Yeah.
OK, so the other if we're talking about big things that have happened that have been Internet prominent, I bet, Jamie, you're probably like us and got tagged in this 100 times with this story.
This bizarre thing where I think this was also a Reddit find this frightening post apocalyptic photo of the dumpster animatronic.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like rotting away in a landfill, looking like it had been shot in the face and several other places.
And this is the drama of it being in the desert.
It felt like very, very Mad Max or very Breaking Bad.
End of Casino.
Oh, yeah, yeah, absolutely.
Is there any clarity on where that was?
Because I feel like this picture has had a few different rounds of life.
I've been tagged in this picture a million times, like two or three different times.
I can't tell how old the picture is.
I can never tell where the dumpster is, like where the landfill is.
There's no I can't trace a history.
Well, yeah, I don't know the place, but I know that it's safe now.
That I know.
If you look a little further, like somebody bought it so that it isn't they didn't just die or get.
Oh, wow.
Burn up.
It didn't get Toy Story three.
It does.
So Chuckie lives.
I don't know if it's restored or anything yet, but it's basically.
Oh, that's what I found.
I didn't know that.
Yeah, apparently.
Yeah.
I only get tagged in the dumpster picture five million times.
There you go.
Oh, wow.
This is from a dumpster.
Oh, this is from a Newsweek story said that, yeah, someone bought it.
Someone restored it.
And this is supposedly the Instagram account of the person who got it and restored it.
And as you can see, the description is account is closed.
Please stop requesting.
Follow requests will be blocked.
More weird.
He has one phone.
He only allowed one.
Well, one person.
And that is in error.
Instagram shows one in error.
Are you talking about maybe should have said, I think we all guess because there's a side by side.
There's the one rotting away in such a sorry state.
And then there's just a fully restored the kind of like Latter Day version with a big C on his shirt.
I mean, it looks brand new.
It looks right out of the factory.
I demand a process video.
I want to know how it was done.
Right, right, right.
Otherwise, like, are we sure?
What if that's a fake?
That could be any check.
I saw a check like that last night.
So you did go in, but you picked up.
You didn't deliver.
I picked up the first of all, because the prices triple when you get delivery.
It's like ridiculous.
And the pickup, they desperately want you to pick up for some reason.
It's weird because it's like the restaurant is not open.
You can't sit there.
There's obviously no outdoor dining.
You can't touch the games are covered in germs.
Like, I don't know why there's but the carry out deals are pretty like they're like so good that it's kind of like suspicious.
They had like a four.
You could get like four large pizzas for twenty dollars if you wanted to.
Oh, like, which I don't want.
So I just wanted to to go to the pickup counter for a few reasons.
First, because I was excited to record this today.
Second, because I found out about a new menu item called the unicorn churros that are a part of the springtastic celebration that I wanted to try.
And third, because I was hoping that I would be able to buy a Chuck E. Cheese toy truck that I've had my eyes on without paying for shipping.
And I was able to accomplish all three.
It was a great, productive trip.
Geez. It was great.
So do you have the truck?
Can I do use a truck nearby?
Let me.
My I was trying to figure out where to display it.
And I don't know where my boyfriend ended up deciding.
I was like looking around for it.
I have a picture of it that I'll send in the chat.
It's a good it's a great truck.
The unicorn.
I wish I could say the same of the unicorn churros.
They're not very good.
They taste like Froot Loops in a bad way.
They're very, very, very sweet.
The truck was there.
It was only three dollars.
And I had to I felt bad because there's like two people working at Chuck E. Cheese right now.
There's a cook and a manager and there's really no need for anyone else.
And so we were standing there for the longest time.
I'm thrilled to announce they have not gotten rid of their single animatronic yet because some places have during the pandemic.
So I was I was just taking it all in.
And then like the manager came out from like desanitizing the games for nobody.
And she was like, oh, you you must have ordered the unicorn churros, meaning that no one else has ordered anything recently.
She's like, oh, unicorn churros.
OK, I'll go get them.
And I I was not I was being a coward.
I made my boyfriend ask if we could buy the truck.
I was just like standing there humiliated.
And she we it just took a while for us to communicate to her that like she just kind of couldn't believe that we wanted it.
He was like, hey, could we actually could we buy something for behind the counter?
I'd really love that truck.
And she's like, there's no truck.
And we had to be like, oh, no, it's like on the far left, the truck.
And she's like, the truck with Chuck E. Cheese on it.
And we were eventually able to get the truck.
I was at the Eagle Rock Mall.
They seem like they really have one person ordering a day.
I don't understand why it's open, really.
Yeah, that's a good question.
I wonder if there's any sort of income being made.
Is there any like maybe there's some sort of organization they send like pizzas to in the morning or like there's some like is there anything maybe like because obviously what you're saying has got to be true where there's probably not a lot of people ordering take out a Chuck E.
Cheese at the moment.
So who?
Good question.
And no one's buying because what you're saying is you bought the truck from the normal ticket redemption area.
Yeah, yeah, which you can't access because there's like tape.
You cannot get there.
You just have to ask if if those things are on sale currently and they're like, yeah, no one's bought any of this in 18 months and they're happy to sell it to you.
But you really have to ask because they will not believe you when you say that you want it.
I have a feeling that procedure too is probably like location by location.
Like maybe some won't sell it to you.
I have had recently where I like if I'm going by a drug store, I go in and go to the pharmacy and go like, so what are you folks doing with extra vaccines at the end of the day?
Because a medical professional told me to do this.
Like, hey, you know, there's a the best way to get a vaccine right now to start going around and asking what they're doing with their cancellations.
You're you're saying the extra vaccines are very similar to getting to just buy with cash a toy from the Chuck E. Cheese Prize redemption counter.
Well, getting to buy like, yeah, getting to buy.
Yeah, like some places might sell you that outright for cash, the truck or some might go like, oh, we give them if there's people 65 and older in the store, they get it.
If our employees do not want it.
Yeah, they get the truck.
So it's possible if you ask for the truck, they would say, well, LA County isn't allowing you to buy the truck right now.
But you look at this list of 50 different things you could possibly have in addition to also maybe just having a doctor's note that says you should get the truck.
Then, yes, we will sell you the truck.
So it all could be exactly like that.
I get that sort of case by case.
So if I had taken that same energy into a vaccination site, I could have done something far more useful with my night last night.
Yeah, yeah.
Hey, could I get sorry to bother?
Could I get that that vial right over there?
Well, that vial.
No one wants this.
This is the this is the AstraZeneca vaccine.
Oh, well, you know, I like the attitude, Jason.
You're coming in with feels like like Chuck E to me a little bit.
I'm just pairing this because that's the topic.
But so what are you doing with those extra vaccines at the end of the day?
Well, I feel like a maniac asking, but literally like someone's like, oh, just start asking about the extras.
And of course, it's been working, it seems like it's worth.
Yeah, I know someone who got it from doing that trick at a Ralph's.
So then I called a Ralph's with a pharmacy and they were like, oh, employees get it first and then 65 and older at the end of the day.
And I'm like, OK, so that's a totally different policy from this other Ralph's pharmacy.
Got it. Thank you.
I said Dodger Stadium shut down early yesterday because not enough people like were getting the vaccines.
It's like they're I'm so confused by a lot of like narratives to going around.
Yeah, yeah.
Where it's like somebody says something and then like an hour later you go, oh, that's actually not a story.
That's a game of telephone.
So it's just so much going on with that.
And it's same thing at Chuck E. Cheese, I'm sure, you know, you're getting.
Well, that's the true relevant question is should Chuck E.
Cheese get the vaccine on camera and what it I think it would help.
I think yeah, I think he's a hero, at least to the rest of the band.
I think it might help convince like Jasper's probably a denier Jasper's not sold on the vaccine.
I also have the other because Chuck, I mean, everywhere has their like cursed pandemic merch, but Chuck E.
has sold some masks.
I know because I have I got one for my birthday this year from my from my boyfriend's mother.
Because she lives in Wisconsin and I, you know, she believes in the vaccine,
but she's not afraid of walking into a Chuck E.
Cheese in the middle of a pandemic.
So she contains multitudes.
But she wanted to get a mask.
She marched in there to get me a Chuck E.
Cheese mask and a birthday balloon.
And, you know, I'm eternally grateful.
I was worried for her, but apparently no one I mean, no one was there.
The updates I got, it was like the updates I got about the Chuck E.
Cheese in Racine, Wisconsin, because she she like gave this stuff to me.
And then I just had a million questions for her about what the interior of the Chuck E.
Cheese is like since I was last there.
And she was like, I don't know, it's still a Chuck E.
Cheese. It sounds like it's changed quite a lot, though.
So she would have been there in August of last year.
The last time I went, they still had the full, full, full of the stuff.
They still had the full TV parody stuff, the movie parody stuff.
They had Chuck Feld.
They had like a Saturday night pizza slice.
I forget.
But now it's all gone.
All of the old decorations are gone.
They seem like they've followed through with this like big refurbishment they were talking about a couple of years ago of getting rid of all of the animatronics, not even a Chuck E.
And it's just a wide dance floor for nobody because it's because no one can go.
And and there is still a costumed character who she said came out to dance for just her when she was purchasing this mask.
Pandemic. They still sent out a.
They still had a costume.
Essentially.
Wow. It's I guess it's the safest role in the restaurant.
You got a mask on at all times.
Right.
I wonder how state to state it is because I would imagine that like Chuck E.
Cheese's in Wisconsin might be might have been a little more open than Chuck E.
Cheese's in Southern California.
I don't I don't know.
I don't think in Southern California, I'm pretty sure they were just totally like you could do pick up.
And that's it.
There was no there was no cost of character.
Right.
I think so.
Yeah. It's yet another one of those like COVID confusing case by case is the whole chain shut down.
Seemingly not.
There are enough open that there's like as we've read about there.
Yeah. Here's the spring event and here's the Halloween event and here's how we can do it.
COVID safe.
But then some places you can't go whatsoever.
Boy, it must be confusing to to work there or to manage it or to be the to be the CEO, to be new CEO.
David McKillips must be a pretty tough job.
We we have not mentioned the like what a newspaper would consider newsworthy about Chuck E.
Cheese, which is that during the pandemic, they did declare Chapter 11 bankruptcy and I believe closed a number of locations or are going to close a number of the locations.
I have a story about that.
I've had a big Chuck E.
Year in spite of never leaving my home.
Yeah.
So they did they close as they closed the location and it was like I forget they closed the location an hour or so from here.
I'm trying to remember the name of it.
But a tipster DM me an auction website because they were auctioning off a bunch of Chuck E.
Cheese stuff.
And like I was kind of nervous about it because I was like, well, I don't you know, who knows how safe they're being who but they were like, no, you just meet them outside and they give you your wares.
So they were selling off stuff for fucking dirt cheap.
It was like it was seaside.
I forget if we were I had to like ask a friend with a pickup truck to to to take me.
It was a whole project.
But but the result is that I now have a ticket muncher in my home and I also in my in my shed because it turns out there's no room for this in my apartment.
But I have one of those kid check like podiums.
Wow.
Oh, I can so visualize the podium.
That's a great item to get for $18.
There was no one wanted it.
No, I got I got the ticket muncher cost me $33 and the podium cost me $18.
No one wanted this shit.
They're like, if you've got a pickup truck and $50 will give you whatever you want.
It was incredible.
You could have bought like the whole showroom for $300.
Yes.
Wow.
Yeah.
It was good.
It's good.
We didn't hear about this or that pickup would have been a lot more like a rat race mad mad mad world.
We would have been like driving you off the road, Jamie.
We were trying to like trying to get there.
Cannonball.
I was kind of ashamed of it at the time.
It was like I was I was pretty ashamed because I was like, I think this was like July, like late July, early August.
And I was like, this is just not this is not how I should be using my time, money, energy.
So I kind of like secretly bidding on it and then went to collect it in in shame.
But I don't regret it because every morning I wake up and I look directly into my ticket muncher didn't work was one of the issues.
But fortunately, there's no need for it to and it's now a bookshelf.
Wow.
Cool.
Yeah, we we've spent there was an episode recently where we spent like 20 minutes just fantasizing about owning McDonald and Play Play stuff.
Oh, which is all expensive on eBay.
It's like I mean, it's not expensive if you're rich, but still it's like maybe 10 grand.
I'll send you the auction site because I'd never it was like a very HTML.
I don't know how the person who sent it to me like knew it existed, but everything there was just like I think it was places that were closing abruptly that were selling off large items.
Like it was just a very they would have made a killing on eBay.
But fortunately, I don't think that they had the time or ability to to care because I've paid so much like I've paid more for Chuck E.
I've paid more for Chuck E.
Cheese items than than that.
Like it's ridiculous.
That's crazy.
Yeah, I wonder.
I wonder what's left.
I mean, obviously, like the big ticket stuff for us would be like bowler hat Chuck.
I mean, is munch is much on the ticket muncher that you have.
Yeah.
OK.
And it's like newer munch.
I assume it's the new.
Yeah, it's the new.
I guess these would be the machines from the past 10 years or so with like the cartoon T shirt wearing munch.
I was hoping it would be an old one, but it was all I wonder the one thing that they weren't selling off.
And I asked the lady when I when I got there, I was like, so what happens to the animatronics?
And they're like, we were told that that's like not none of our but they were like, we were told that that's a whole other thing.
Like they they they weren't even brought into the discussion.
They were just selling off the skee ball machines and the and the random shit.
I was in a bidding war with someone over the bathroom signs, but it was it didn't work out in my favor.
The black helicopters and the black vans are coming from the animatronics.
They're going to whisk them away to the warehouse from the end of Raiders of the Lost Ark.
I'm so curious where they're all going, because that was that was I was waiting for confirmation from somewhere that they were like not being sold off to other places.
They're being brought somewhere or they're being like brought to they're being repurposed in some way, but it's not it's not a people facing issue.
They said, don't fucking worry about it.
Well, they're going to be examined by top men.
What happens top men are on the case.
I did see one of the locations I was closing pictures were going around of like all of the rides and arcade games like were in the like trash yard next to they had like cleared out the building.
And we're just kind of like dilapidated carousel like next to, you know, which again, like it makes like, of course, you'd want to get it.
You think that you'd want to get it, but it is that it is the physical moving.
It's the shit and like real remembering.
Oh, right. I don't have an eight bedroom house.
It does not make any sense to have this gigantic ski ball machine or whatever it is.
Yeah, it's convincing the person you live with that this will be a positive addition to our lives to look at every day.
Not just like hit you in the knees when you're trying to get out of bed.
Yeah, I was like, oh, we're going to put the we're going to put the Internet router in it.
So it's kind of more think of it as a shelf and functional.
You know, speaking of that, I was thinking about looking this up in preparation for the episode and I didn't.
But now I just went to eBay and I found a pretty good item.
Do you guys would you guys be interested in doing a quick, sudden souvenir smackdown?
Of course, with something that you talk about stuff that you want stuff that you're you're driving to a Chuck E. Cheese that is closed.
The big ticket stuff. I'm going to show you a big one.
You you, Jamie, already name checked essentially this thing.
This is one of the old CD covers from the wall.
Wow. Saturday Night Retriever in its frame with a Chuck E.
CD at the bottom and kind of a glass bricky pattern.
It's it's it's by the artist, the Bee Cheese.
It's it includes more than a wolfhound and straying alive.
Do we do we want to go?
Let's let's get some some guesses on what this is going for on eBay.
Can I ask, is it a buy it now or is it an auction in the starting price or are there bids on it already?
This is a place bid currently.
And starting somewhere. OK. Yeah, it's been up for you.
You got six days left on this.
OK, size, I don't know offhand.
I'll see if I can get it. But I mean, we know you it's all right.
Six, six feet by three feet. So it's big. Yeah.
I'll guess two hundred and forty nine ninety nine.
Jason, I'm going to go five hundred. Jamie.
I'll go I'll go three fifty. I'll split the difference.
The winner of that is going to be Jason at four forty nine.
Wait, is that right? Wait, five hundred.
Yeah, it depends if we're doing prices. Right.
Yeah, right. Jamie wins.
I went over. I went over.
It's not closest. It's over.
You don't want to do. OK, got it.
Well, now when we do this again, I know the rules.
I'm glad this is a good reiteration for me.
All right. So that's so much money.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
I don't care that much. I don't know.
So the size really is a problem there, too.
That's such that's going to take up a whole wall in your home.
Which, again, like how much wall space do people really have?
Do you like this enough for it to be like such a facet of your personality?
And not just Chuck E.
Specifically, do you want this Bee Gees parody?
Do you like Saturday Night Retriever enough to have it be the main art in your house?
Can I bring up real quick? I have to search on eBay just out of curiosity.
Let me just show you something that you can purchase.
And here you go.
Oh, this is a inside the head, like the mechanism inside of, I guess, a Chuck E. head you can buy for sixty dollars.
Oh, the eyes. And it is horrifying.
It's like a big like just kind of black bracket mechanism and then a weird like red.
It's weird knowing what's in the head now. A big red plastic piece.
It's probably some mouth piece of some kind.
And then just unpainted eyes with like listless eyebrows halfway down or eyelids rather.
They have six of these, apparently, and it says animatronic head kit, showbiz pizza, Chuck E. cheese's, Colorado animatronics.
So I guess you could just buy your own like material felt or something and construct your own Chuck E. head around this exoskeleton or not exoskeleton, the skeleton, I should say.
Yeah. Is this aftermarket though?
Is this like when your mechanic is like, well, do you want the part made by the manufacturer?
Do you want the aftermarket like made by third party?
It's like a third of the price, but it is less of a warranty.
It looks like it might be a knockoff. Yeah. A knockoff. Yeah, I agree.
It doesn't seem like it might be authentic, but that's maybe just an option for us.
If we're looking for something cheaper, we make our own Chuck E. head.
Well, that's a way more efficient way for us to start manufacturing our own animatronic at home.
That's always been the end game, right? Yes.
I mean, yeah, that's probably where this has been going.
Yeah, for sure. Talk to him, get advice from him.
Give him a hug at the end of the day and say thanks for being there for me, Chuck.
Yeah. Aaron Fector, the the like creator of all this stuff, who there's also a bunch of like stuff that's happened with him in the past year that I don't even want to get into because it's really fucked up.
You don't say that guy. Oh, he.
Everything about him is so fucked.
I was like going through my old emails with him and I was like, this guy's just really fucked up.
But he used to be selling like a make your own animatronic kit on his website for like $10,000 or something.
Absolutely scam artist ridiculous.
I don't know. But but also, like, what is a reasonable price for an animatronic?
I have no idea. Right.
It could be. Yeah, that could be anything.
Yeah, it could be like $100 with the way the world currently values animatronics, which is not very much.
Aaron Fector, there's a little Cliff notesy thing.
Yeah. So he yeah, he kind of kicked off the entire trend and he specifically is the creator of not the not the Chuck E.
Cheese characters, but of the Rock of Fire explosion, the other set of characters that got sort of bought out and replaced.
But this guy is still going as this documentary that's largely about him.
He once employed 200 people at his factory in Orlando, and now it's just him.
And there seems like there was some kind of chemical blast at this facility.
So now, which was decrepit when they filmed the documentary and now it's just full of chemicals everywhere.
And he's been maybe this is one of the things you're referring to is that he's been there's there's a very populated YouTube channel that just is him.
Yeah, he's putting out a lot of content.
There's been a lot of quarantine content from Aaron Fector so much.
Yeah, I have not been keeping up with it because I I mean, he was my perception with he was he was always like kind of bizarre on YouTube.
And I didn't really I couldn't really watch too much of his content without being like, I don't like it here.
I'm leaving. But it seems to have really taken a turn, which made me go back to I was trying to interview him at one point.
And I didn't mention this on the first episode we did, maybe because I still thought there was a chance I would interview him at this point.
I wash my hands of it. But I like almost three years ago, I reached out to him to interview him.
And he kept bailing on the interview at the last minute because of like an emergency.
And it would always in the last I read the last like true cancellation he made because I tried again a year later and never heard from him.
But this was in from December twenty eighteen.
And it's a long email that I barely read at the time because I just read the first sentence and was like, well, he's clearly not going to do this interview.
He keeps canceling for these like confusing reasons.
But I read through the whole email and it's like it sounds like he has he said that two of his dogs died very close together.
And it sounds like he was like doing holistic medicine on his dogs against the advice of his vet.
And it was a long email about that.
And so I just don't like him.
I don't trust him and I don't know.
Fuck with him anymore.
It's really like raising my blood pressure to even look at it because it's been like it's like a weird font.
And it's just a lot.
I can I can imagine what the font looks like.
And it's like what four points too big for a normal email.
Yeah, it's like Ariel size 22.
I tell that unmotivated.
You could have said just the font and I would have gone, oh, yeah, OK, I hear what you're saying.
Shiver.
I get it.
I get what you're saying.
If you're let's be careful.
All of us with our blood pressure, because I have I do have more air infector material that I've this is not all recent.
This is like from the last 20 years, some of which I came off of showbiz pizza dot com, which thanks to them for archiving so much stuff.
One step of the air infector saga I didn't know.
So his his characters, the rocket fire explosion, who were mainly associated with showbiz pizza, they all kind of went away.
And the whole story is he held on to the IP, which became essentially worthless or not worthless, but just not enough to mine a whole empire out of.
What I didn't know is that he tried to start new restaurants with the rocket fire explosion.
Like he yeah, he attempted to like put them into other places, which some of which only had a couple of locations.
One of the rocket fire characters is named Looney Bird.
So he started a restaurant in deep Orlando called Looney Birds.
He just named it after one of them in a Pasquale fashion.
I found some literature about Looney Birds.
That's all very much like your email.
It's very like come to Looney Birds.
We got pizza.
We got fun and games and we have the rocket fire explosion who are famous all over the world and they are world renowned and they are they are characters who are valued by many, many people.
It's like this.
We did not vaccinate them.
Are you going to know?
I also found a Looney Birds newsletter where he talks about the success of the first taping of Live at Looney's, a local Time Warner show that he was making from the restaurant.
The hook of Looney Birds is that the famous rocket fire explosion, which is the word famous, is thrown at you so many times.
You yourself can be the lead singer of the band.
You can sing karaoke and they are your backing band.
So he made it.
It's a karaoke situation and he made a TV show out of the karaoke and the newsletter says the taping was a big success.
And based on the feedback of the people in attendance, we will be installing air conditioning before the next taping.
In Orlando.
Yeah.
Now, look, it's fine during the day for the regular restaurant.
But when you bring in the TV lights, that's what we didn't know.
The TV lights really just heat up everything.
And so now we know.
So the next time.
But otherwise, it was great.
Everybody had a great time.
So don't say they didn't.
The other factor thing that I discovered, and I'm sorry to do this to everyone.
I know what a bummer I'm about to click on.
Do we know the fact about him that he was, according to his story, at least, the inventor of the Whack-a-Mole and that it got sort of taken from him?
Or he's just not credited such.
Well, there's no question if it's in question whether he invented the Whack-a-Mole.
He we absolutely know that he invented a cousin of the Whack-a-Mole called the Bin Laden basher.
Oh, no.
I see.
Yeah.
OK.
God.
Seen this for any reason?
No.
I've never seen this.
I came with like five new reasons to hate Aaron Fecter and this was not even one of them.
Wow.
Yeah, this is something.
Strike a blow for freedom, it says.
Bizarre.
A bizarre photo of, you know, it's like it.
Yeah, it's a Whack-a-Mole, but it's Bin Laden.
And there's a guy with an American flag patterned mallet and he is in jean shorts and shirtless.
Why?
That might be Aaron Fecter.
Like that.
Yeah.
I had that question.
I was wondering.
I'm also Florida.
Yeah, extremely.
Can I read?
You know, I said to my wife, like, where are you going to end up where you are shirtless
with a Whack-a-Mole?
And she said Florida.
The answer is Florida.
Wildwood, New Jersey.
Yeah.
Seaside Heights.
You have to rip to get to start it.
You have to rip the shirt off, though.
You can't just take it off.
You have to pull your shirt off and destroy it before you play this game.
Yeah.
And let out a yell.
The machine's activated by the yell.
So you use the Mallet of Freedom and you find Bin Laden.
Smash his ugly face, it says.
And then special bonus, Hitler's also down there.
Hitler's in it too.
Oh my God.
Why?
What?
Hitler's hiding with Bin Laden?
Hiding with dirtbag Osama Bin Laden is none other than history's most evil scumbag.
Let them both have it.
Wow.
This is wild.
These are all correct villains.
Look, they're all bad, but it is funny to me.
Absolutely bad.
Osama Bin Laden, that guy's a dirtbag.
And Hitler, I'll tell you what, he's a scumbag.
It's kind of like what you say about some guy on the street you don't like.
Not like these awful.
Saddam.
Saddam is also there by special request of the president.
What?
The president of what?
The president of Dick's Last Resort?
Did President Bush get in touch with Aaron Factor?
Aaron, you gotta help.
How do we get the message across to the fine?
Aaron Factor was in the cabinet.
Doesn't everyone remember?
I don't even know.
My brain has stopped.
What?
Yeah, yeah.
I know, there needs to be a come down from this.
Yeah, Aaron Factor was hired for the actual military.
The plan was him going around Afghanistan shirtless with a mallet of freedom.
In jorts, yeah.
As this marketing material says, perfect for military rec rooms.
That's big business, baby.
Those military rec rooms, you know?
Yeah, those.
In size 22 aerial font, kind of his thing.
Yeah, wow.
He got, there was, I didn't even dig too deep into it because I'm like, Jesus Christ.
But there was another, it seems like a peak in Aaron Factor YouTube commentary content
in early 2020, like pre pandemic 2020, of like a lot of racist stuff that he was putting
on his YouTube channel.
And that I guess it just, I can't even speak to it because I barely engaged with it.
But it just, since we last spoke about Aaron Factor, there's just been a spike in how many
fucked up things that he's done.
He does seem sort of primed for the current, like the kinds of people who've been prominent
in the last year.
Yeah, yeah, he's well qualified.
I would be, it's probably a good thing that he doesn't have like nationwide restaurants
and a robot show because God knows what he would be programming those robots to say and
play at this point.
I would, maybe I'm wrong, but it feels like they would have some speeches to give to the kids.
Chuck changes his initial from E to Q.
Chuck Q cheese.
You can look at the basement of our restaurants.
You can inspect the basement and see there's no sicko stuff.
Pizza places.
I guess there's a whole like toxic Facebook group surrounding the rocket fire explosion
that Aaron Factor is in charge of that.
Like some people have done the deep dive on it.
I don't care to even know.
I'm glad that Chuck E. Cheese has washed his little mouse, now canonically mouse hands.
You did Mesa.
You don't have to do this too.
That's too many things to infiltrate.
Maybe do we go, we obviously still have to deliver a showbiz pizza episode to the listeners
one day.
Yeah.
So maybe we have to get in the mud at a certain point.
But now we don't.
Now we don't have to go on the Facebook page.
I have something lighter.
I have some good news.
Oh good.
Dear God, please.
I know.
It's so dark.
This is a Little Shavers update.
If everyone will recall, the Little Shavers are a barbershop quartet that was featured
in the short-lived restaurant, the Ice Cream Emporium that existed two locations in Florida,
one in Texas.
A set, a full Little Shavers show has been restored and is on display at the Volo Auto
Museum in Volo, Illinois.
Mike, can you pull up that video I sent you?
Yes, I can.
Here it is.
And if you want to play that.
Whoa.
No, the barbershop.
These guys are adorable.
Very muppety.
Very noisy.
OK, that's good.
Man, the clacking of the robots.
Pretty loud.
Very loud.
But that's good.
I'm glad they're back.
Yeah, so they're back.
Supposedly the only Little Shavers preserved in the world, but this place, the Volo Auto
Museum has its own pirate show.
They have exhibits dedicated to pizza theater restaurants.
They have one of two operating the Beagles.
The Beagles.
The Chuck E. Cheese Beetles who are dogs.
And the King.
They've got the King.
And King Cat.
The Michael Jackson King.
How did they do that?
And you eat in a little pizza cafe in the museum.
Man, that's great.
Where's Volo?
Volo is about 40 minutes north of the Woodfield Mall.
So Mike.
What?
Yes.
It's just north of Chicago.
This is right by where my parents live, where I grew up.
Wow.
That's wild.
Well, Mike, I know you haven't gotten back there in a while.
So when you get back in town, I want you to go straight to the Volo Auto Museum and then
anything else or anyone you want to see in the Schomburg area, it's up to you.
But yeah, I'll go straight there.
Yeah, first.
Yeah.
Don't invite anybody with you.
Yeah, no, no.
Yeah.
Well, what do we have any more current stuff or awful air infected news?
Do we want to go some retro?
Let me just say I'm not going to say it, but we do.
There was we got too dark already that I don't want to even say the other things that I learned.
So so yeah, I honestly we're cutting on the fly.
OK, all right.
So Mike, feel free to take whatever you want.
I just want to break.
I mean, there's all these clips are fun except for one one dark spot.
I really quickly I want to highlight one of like Chuckie's signature songs that we didn't
talk about.
He's been singing this song forever and I assume we've all heard it.
But I really like I saw an old video of it and I just want to shout it out.
This is something I like.
This is just I don't want to make fun of it.
I just want to say I like this song and you probably know what I'm talking about.
And it's an old this is this is the old version.
They do do a new updated version with Bowling for Suit Man, but that's not what
exciting new musical review with your merry making master of ceremonies.
Chuckie Cheese.
That's me, Chuckie Cheese.
Your host with a most.
But even with this star behind me, I'm not the star of the show.
You are.
Magic only happens when we all get together.
We can feel the magic now that you're here.
Together we'll make the good times right here.
And when it comes to keeping up room.
Keeping up room.
We might just make believe that we're going to make a move.
We've got it together.
We've got it.
We've got it together with you.
We've got it together forever.
The fun has just begun.
This band is number one.
Together we've got it.
We might just make believe.
And then he sort of he shouts out all the members of the band.
I can keep playing, but that's the gist of it.
Together we got it.
And they still do this number, apparently.
And I remember it now when I found the video and I was like, this is just good.
I like this song.
Helen Henney was a belter back in the day.
Yes.
Yeah.
They all get their little moment to shine.
I like that about this song.
It's a nice introduction to the band.
And yeah, this is the old version, but there are new Bowling for Soupified versions of it as well.
Geez, I'm so glad it's around.
I love it.
That's so nice.
Because especially recently, I was trying to figure out if this was like something that happened post
Pasquale's pizza fiasco or if it had been happening for a while anyways.
But it seems like they're getting like they're slowly edging Pasquale out of the main crew on Merch.
Like that truck I got yesterday, not a Pasquale in sight, but the other four are there.
Really?
It's strange.
Yeah.
It's just it's Chuckie, Munch, Jasper and Helen.
No Pasquale.
And I don't know if they were.
I just wonder what's I feel like Pasquale is the most beloved in a way.
Yeah.
In some circles.
Do they think is he not cute?
Maybe like it's hard.
It's harder to cue.
I think the puppet.
Is it that he's a man?
It's unclear.
Maybe it's human.
A human thing.
I think he's in the there is a puppet one you were saying because like he's in there's a game show sketch they shot recently where they sing a song trying to figure out what Chuckie's middle name is.
And they're just naming off different names.
And at one point they say, is it evolution?
And they show what he used to look like.
Here's new Chuckie, but in the bowler hat.
Oh, cool.
And I think Pasquale is in there.
But yeah, I know what you mean that it feels like they're edging out Pasquale.
He's still like YouTube canon, but I don't he's not on a lot of the he's like not on the website.
Really?
It's confusing.
I don't know.
Is that do they want him to maybe is the voice to cartoonish in the twenty twenty one?
Maybe is there maybe are they trying to transition like maybe a young Pasquale in that's more authentic.
Maybe he's impossible to because they do seem to have like kind of like child of find the other the other characters.
And maybe just because Pasquale has a full goatee, they can't they can't get him there.
I don't know.
Yeah, maybe it's odd to have like an adult pizza chef hanging out with these children.
Right. Yeah, it seems a little.
I'm a kid check and it's fine.
Let me let me bring up another character.
I don't I didn't catch that.
We talked about him last time.
Maybe we did.
And you forgive me if we did.
We did not talk about Munch Jr. last time.
Right.
I don't think so.
No, no.
And Munch Jr. was and this is a clip I found on YouTube.
Munch Jr. was sort of hidden on certain stages.
And the reason he was only in certain stages is because he was a reskinned version of a rock of fire character named Chu Chu.
So they had to already have like a little robot on the stage kind of hiding in a garbage can before for the necessity to re-theme that character.
Oh, a little critter who pops up.
Yeah, there was a lot more of that kind of thing with with rock of fire.
Right. So like you see this clip, the clips on the top left here, Munch Jr. would pop his head up.
And I found a clip made by a child called Rest In Peace Munch Jr.
Wow.
And I just want to play a quick clip of it here.
In this video we will be finding out what happened to Munch Jr.
So Munch Jr. is a very old prop from Chuck E Cheese in front of Helen.
We're in between Helen and Munch.
So this is Munch little brother or little cousin.
People say, mostly people say that it's Munch's little cousin when it's really his brother.
So it's his brother.
So yeah, he would pop out in an air vent.
Here's like a video right here.
He would go up and down out of an air vent.
He would go up and then down an air vent.
So yeah, and he would usually pop out during like the songs to beat with the music like Chu Chu.
But here we finding out what would happen, what happened to him because he was being vandalized by kids.
I don't know if that means like he was not working properly or he was not working at all.
Because kids kept messing with him and breaking him.
That's the reason why.
And so yeah, that's what basically happened.
That's what basically happened.
And there's a little more to that video.
I want to shout out Ian.
The YouTube channel is Ian Cool Guy and the video itself is Rest In Peace Munch Jr.
So everyone go over here and support this video.
There's a little more information about what happened to Munch Jr.
But apparently children were vandalizing Munch Jr.
And they had to remove him.
I'm going to take this kid as the information.
I'm not looking into it.
I'm taking Ian at his word.
Exactly.
Yeah, we're all going to be working for Ian Cool Guy in a few years.
So this the like the passion about Munch Jr.
The knowledge and the quiver in the voice when thinking about vandal kids.
This, folks, is a good boy.
This is a very good boy.
I appreciate his passion.
But I love Munch Jr. immediately.
I wish Munch Jr. would come back.
I haven't seen Munch Jr. appear on the new Chucky things, but why not?
He seems like he'd be ripe for the YouTube channel.
Such a simple puppet.
Very simple puppet.
You probably also could just like like Martin Short and Clifford,
shoot him like smaller down below the same puppet,
but like smaller and do tricks to make it look like it's a different puppet,
but it's the same.
And there's just making it look like he's a different size.
There's some great pictures of like this picture here of Munch Jr.
Squat one tooth in a little beanie.
Oh, this is it.
This is new Munch Jr.
I think.
Oh, he is.
Whoa, wait.
Wait, click on that wiki.
Maybe it'll say.
Okay, all right.
Hold on.
Oh, I'm getting ads for wrestling figures.
On Fandom.com.
Okay, Munch Jr. in the mid 90s.
I don't know.
It doesn't say that he's been in it recently.
Munch Jr. puppet.
Remember, they were doing puppets though still in the 90s.
Puppets aren't new on the YouTube.
Wait, he was still in Wilmington, North Carolina until they closed in November 2020.
Oh, Munch Jr.
Still a Munch Jr.
I apologize to the audience for getting their hopes up that Munch Jr.
is still around.
So far, Munch Jr. has not returned.
There is a private collector who shows his Munch Jr. at Chuck E. Conn,
according to this fan.
That doesn't sound good.
It doesn't sound good.
I think Jamie should get in contact with him.
Maybe.
I've emailed Chuck E. Cheese people for the last time.
It's been probably nothing but pain.
That is.
Meet your, well, I don't want to say heroes.
Never meet anyone, I guess.
It's the long and short of it.
Yeah, don't meet new people.
You'll be just fine.
Yeah.
That's fine.
We're done with that this year.
No one's met anyone new.
In a year.
So it's worked out great.
Right.
Do you, does anyone else have, I mean, I have more things to share.
I can keep going if anybody else has something they'd like to talk about.
I have something, you know, this might, your clip might dovetail nicely into mine
because it also features a young boy with a charmingly like unprofessional voice,
a very little kid voice.
I'm really excited about it.
I feel like this might, when I saw this, this rang a bell to me and it might for you guys too.
I'm curious if it does because this was a television commercial that might have been late 80s,
late 90s, might have been early 2000s.
I feel like I remember it being on TV and you think that once you're in like skate Chuck era
that the fun is done.
But then I saw this, which is a very, very good clip.
I feel like I remember it being on TV and you think that once you're in like skate Chuck era
that the fun is done.
But then I saw this, which is like, honestly, one of my favorite pieces of Chuck content I've ever seen.
And this is a commercial that's at least on, by this YouTube user is dubbed,
They've Got Crabs.
And here now they've got crabs.
They've got music.
They've got...
Crabs!
Chuckie's got music.
They've got...
Crabs!
So let's start midway through check in.
Yeah, this kid has ended up at a crab restaurant instead of at Chuckie Cheese where he wants to be.
There's fun being had at Chuckie Cheese.
They built a giant mouth that a slice goes into.
Then he's at a lame plate with a big crab.
Then Chuckie Cheese gets even more fun.
And then a lemon gets squeezed and it shoots into the kid's eye and he says,
Crabs!
And then the crab is like alive on the plate and mocks him.
Like he did it on purpose.
And then worst of all, then Chuckie Cheese gets as fun as like a Vegas montage from a 60s movie.
And then the kid's worst nightmare because he yells,
Crabs!
And then he's in the darkened kitchen and a gigantic crab bursts into the kitchen after him.
This is a surrealist...
This is like Kafka.
Is this just like a Red Lobster call out commercial?
Like who are they calling out?
Seafood in general?
Yeah, I don't know.
These are prob...
I never thought of seafood places or crab places as being like stuffy or specifically not for kids.
But apparently they're a child's worst nightmare.
Or directly competitive to Chuckie Cheese in any way.
Yeah, yeah.
Who would ever be considering one or the other?
Do they have crabs at Chuckie Cheese?
Well, you know, back east like fish houses, like, you know,
soup, salad, fish entree, dessert, like all included.
Still very popular.
But usually there's an ample kids menu for like, here's fried shrimp or chicken tenders.
And here's like, you know, worms and dirt for dessert.
But yeah, I mean, I guess could be a little stuffy.
Maybe back in the day when everyone is still like smoking their way through a meal,
it was a little more dour.
Yeah.
And maybe back in the day, a giant crab would come to life and hunt you into the kitchen like the Jurassic Park raptors.
That's true.
This is...
Now, let me keep going with this, because if you were worried about the Quabs kid, it does work out for him.
Oh, good.
So for the listener, he's backed into a corner.
What's he going to do?
Well, a hero swoops in last minute and Chuckie Cheese with a net.
Suddenly, he's at the crab restaurant, unannounced.
Hi!
Oh, my goodness.
So, yeah, I mean, I think that's a good thing.
You know, I'm not a big fan of...
Suddenly, he's at the crab restaurant, unannounced.
Ha!
Look at that open mouth.
That's a great frame.
Ha!
Be gone with ye!
Throws a net over some of the crab, which fells him immediately, high fives the kid.
Very little Scott kid.
And then a graphic where Chuckie is flying in a spaceship.
A little one-mouse-sized spaceship.
This is a work of art.
This is a great short film.
Wow, Chuckie came to the restaurant to save the kid.
He caught wind of the child.
Beginning, middle, and end.
That is incredible.
Right.
And Chuckie, like, beats...
I guess he beats up a crab.
I mean, he doesn't beat the crab up, but I assume that's what happens off screen.
If a crab gets a net on it, it's like a turtle ending up on its back.
Like, eventually, he will suffocate.
He'll go to the ground and he'll die in a few days.
So the crab is dead.
See you in hell, crab.
Tell the devil, Chuckie says hi.
That's incredible.
Chuckie, it was a nightmare.
There were quabs.
Please, tell me that your restaurant has no quabs.
Good news, kid.
I'm going to talk to your mom and dad outside, too.
Let them know what for.
You take this kid to another restaurant, you'll never go to another restaurant again in your
life.
Jasper and Munch hold up the parents while Chuck punches them in the gut.
Helen, get the other net.
Mom and dad are getting netted.
You don't think I got another net, you got another thing coming.
You know old Chuckie was like a mobster connected guy.
Yeah, like Casino.
Yeah, he was.
That's his whole persona.
And it's a deliberate media narrative to frame the crab a very particular way and make you,
you know, to start you against the crab.
You're not, you're never given the crab's perspective.
Where's the crab coming from?
The crab's about to die, you know?
It's like no wonder the crab is upset.
The crab's about to be consumed.
But Chuckie is just unequivocally our hero.
He wants the crab to disappear.
Guess what?
He has the ability to make that happen.
Chuck is never in a position where it's he himself, Chuckie Cheese, that's going to be
eaten.
A rat is not desired to eat, but a crab is.
They're coming from different places.
I like this because it's like, you know, it's that scene in Breaking Bad when Gus kills
Victor himself.
He's been letting other minions do things for years and he actually finally like does
the really awful thing himself.
You know, we actually get to see how scary Chuckie could be because until now he's just
friendly.
It establishes him as a definitive predator.
Exactly, yes.
He's not the prey.
Right.
And this is probably part of why they had to rebrand maybe because of the aggressiveness
of this old Chuck.
Yeah.
Be the crab to the ticket muncher.
No one will find your bones.
Yeah, it is funny because I was thinking about the old Chuckie.
Definitely like if this person ran a business, you would go, oh, we should.
He's stealing money, skimming money off the top.
He's not paying the workers very well.
I'm getting ripped off somehow.
Like, you wouldn't trust that type of personality to own a business and let your kids loosen
his house or his restaurant.
He's really pivoted.
He's quite the empath these days, our Chuck.
Yes.
Yeah.
The crab one is very lovable.
It is weird that it came from.
He's sweet.
Yeah, yeah.
I genuinely, yeah, you know what?
I do think current Chuck is cute and you can make fun of that bowling for soup voice and
that they did that.
It is very silly, but I think that guy does a good job.
Sure does.
Yeah, I agree.
As opposed maybe to just while we're on the topic, I've also, I saw footage I'd never
seen of original Chuck.
This is from 1977.
And just to get a little hint of the earliest Chuck and in general, the puppets are amazing
to watch.
Um,
Honey, won't you be our birthday one?
say yes, don't say no.
And we'll tell the world.
By now, it's probably no surprise to anybody.
We got a birthday number coming up here.
What's the surprise to me?
We got a birthday coming up.
He's fucked up.
He's fucked.
Yeah, he's drunk.
He's really drunk.
Please.
He's got a cigar.
He's got a stoke.
Oh my God.
He's got his right hand is a human hand for some reason.
The eyes blink at different levels.
He's got one human hand.
He's got a giant cigar.
A skew bow tie.
A skew hat.
The hat's tipping off his head slowly.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
It is truly beautiful evolution from like a middle aged alcoholic uncle to a to a teenage
boy who couldn't be nicer.
To a teenage boy that like there was a recent video called Spring Break Break Dance and
it's just Chucky like dancing and there's kids dancing and of course they all have masks
on but they're not really like they're just having a good time.
They're making the best of a tough situation and that's very different from like this Chuck
who's like, yeah, I grew up downstream from the Silent Spring from the DDT water and my
eyes aren't so good but what are you gonna do?
I've been blind for years.
Scott, I'm assuming you pulled up this freeze frame of this video because you've noticed
like I just have that the employees would wear bowler hats.
Yeah, they all wore the hat like Chuck apparently.
Wow, I didn't realize that actually.
Yeah.
No, I didn't either.
That's pretty cool.
I was just trying to find one more Chuck line.
I think there might be another.
Let me see.
We slowly are.
So come on ladies, hit it.
Birthday one, honey bun, won't you be our birthday one?
Birthday one, honey bun.
So far there are six with three more under construction and another three on the drawing
boards.
The idea has already spread to Japan and it's only a matter of time before Chuck E. Cheese
makes his debut in Australia.
His debut.
I've never heard that in an accent.
I don't know.
I think it's Australian, not British but is that?
I feel like this guy's putting on a show.
I don't think that's right.
I don't think it always says date boo.
But there's one more odd thing.
Then you meet the real Chuck E.
This guy's the president or the CEO or something and he's like a 70s vested, you know, like
Keen and Wynn character with big sideburns.
He's pretty scary.
But he talks about the audience they're trying to hit.
Imagine that this company now is like for, they have like a skateboarder as their mascot
and it used to be like this old, this like, there will be blood man running it.
But there's this crazy bit of narration.
Let me see if I can find, they justify like who the audience might be for Chuck E. Cheese
and this is very grim.
I guess this was the, this is the world of the 70s apparently.
Chuck E. Cheese researchers say the idea is very popular with workaholic dads who are
suffering from what they call Y.E.G., Young Executive Guilt.
Drive dad into taking the kids out.
Guess who decides where they'll go.
In this country is Y.E.G.
This is an Australian like news show like with an anthropologist going like, this is
how Americans live.
Y.E.G.
Wow.
Young Executive Guilt.
So if you're on the road all the time, you're always on like you go in hotels and doing
deals and then you come home and you feel like, ah God, I guess I have to see my kid.
Well, where can I take my kid where I don't really have to talk to him and answer questions
and show that I don't know anything about them?
I know.
I'll plop them in front of a robot show and some video games.
That'll be that.
Then I won't prove that I don't know if they're in second grade or eighth.
That'll fix everything.
It's worked for generations.
I'm so damn tired.
It's 1974.
It's viewed as feminine to drink water.
I just have to drink coffee all day long.
I haven't slept in a decade.
And this was back when you could they really wouldn't like cut you off if you were if you
were if you were a drinking dad suffering of Y.E.G. at the Chuck E. Cheese, you could
be like tossing them back all night.
No, it's a paradox.
They would just keep serving you.
But there weren't fights until like the 90s and 2000s where like they'll cut you off.
But then there's fights because everyone's angry.
They cut you off.
It's true.
Is Y.E.G. a suitable reason for getting the vaccine?
Is that a preexisting condition?
How is that considered?
You need a note from your CEO.
And if you have that, then you can get the vaccine.
Adam Curtis of the BBC wrote me a note saying I have Y.E.G.
and that something has happened.
I'm working too hard at Halliburton all day.
Is young podcaster guilt a thing we could get from our various networks, our presidents
of our podcast networks?
They could write us a note.
That's right.
Yeah.
Hey, Brett, Brett, write us a note and says we have Y.E.G.
Brett, write us a note, Brett.
We need it.
Wow.
And then we in the last episode we talked about, there was like on some other with mom
and dad rooms.
Specifically, right?
Yeah, yeah.
So proper rooms and sports rooms to separate everybody.
Yeah.
And I think I'll repeat the joke I said last time.
And there'll be like stag films playing in the dad room.
Well, you know, you're not that far off because later in this Australian news report,
we get a little glimpse at Dolly Dimples, who I talked about earlier.
Yeah.
Oh, wow.
This is his dad.
I forgot what she looks like.
Yeah, she's she's something big, big, doily as a collar, big clown wig.
Clashing aesthetics.
Yeah.
She also you like sit at a bar to see her.
That's something I didn't really pull up a seat.
Drinking.
Close up.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's like the close up room at the Magic Castle.
It's very, very interesting.
Yeah.
And then you get to see the other kids.
Close up room at the Magic Castle.
It's very, very intimate.
And it's a room that says cabaret on the outside.
This is that weird?
Like most of the pizza time theater is at a separate cabaret room.
And then the narrator says this.
Dimples, the singing hippopotamus, is powered by a computer system
capable of handling 450 instructions per second.
Dolly has a repertoire of more than 20 medleys
and a bosom that rises and falls with compressed air.
Oh, wow.
Oh, that one goes out to her second husband, Eugene.
She talks about her second husband.
Yeah.
Wait a minute.
We need to hear about the second husband.
Yeah.
Wow.
My second husband, Eugene, who used to ride with the Texas Rangers.
He's a long tall Texan.
He wears a tan jacket.
Sounds like Eugene as young executive guilt too.
Yeah.
What a divorce hippopotamus that they put in this separate room
with a heaving bosom.
And you're like a foot away from her face.
You're so close to this animatronic while you're eating.
And it's only room for like four people at that bar.
This is a great idea.
The robot goes haywire and knocks your drink over.
Yeah.
Come see Dolly Dimples sing I'm Still Here from Folly.
Come see the song that Elaine Stritch made famous.
I just like that.
I mean, this was I would have to imagine unless the world was extremely
like even more different than I understood it to be.
This was just like before they were like testing anything of like,
does anybody want this?
They're just like, people probably want this.
It's good.
I can't imagine Dolly Dimples testing well, but I'm glad she existed.
Yeah, it's a dark room.
We're going to compressed air bosom, hear about failed marriages.
It's all.
Yeah, it's before you.
Yeah.
It's before like money.
People would come in and be like, we only are getting four people in here
to view this show up close.
Maybe with this is a waste of money and maybe this woman's story is a little
depressing for a child.
I would imagine that that like that suit guy would think Dolly Dimples
I bet she would crack him up because she would remind him of his wife.
That's true.
And that would just be enough.
And then you just put 500 of them in production.
We we sent a mystery shopper to the Dolly Dimples cabaret and it seemed like
the only other person in there was a young executive doing key bumps while his
kids played space invaders.
Dolly, you're the only one who understands me.
I think that Chuck E.
Cheese executive did, I think, put it in to like be mean to an ex-wife.
Like she's probably like a fine, like, like completely nice, attractive woman
who is like, let's put her in like a big, doily dress and give her a clown wig
because she she looked crazy.
Like it's all like it like probably the name was one off of Dolly and like
how can we character assess it?
And like how can we character assassinate my ex-wife with a robot?
Something out somewhere.
It could have been his mom.
Who knows?
Something was going on.
I will say I do appreciate that they were like thinking of this place for all ages.
We talked to God in the last episode a lot about how we wished they were
catering more to us adults who want to find it acceptable to enjoy a robot show
while working.
So I do appreciate it.
I feel like we could have easily strolled into a place like this and worked in the
dad's room or something and gotten a little robot show, drank 10 beers each
and then we would have had a great time.
Like it seems like that would have maybe been appropriate back then, but not now.
Yeah, I feel like you would maybe you would maybe saunter into to Dolly's
Dolly's cabaret after a couple of Blue Moons and sure.
And just strike up a conversation and kind of hear her story.
I can see that being very rewarding.
Yeah, yeah.
We rewatched some of the training videos the other day and I caught on the like
menu board, like the ordering set that was just like under like, you know,
soda salad bar.
And then it just there was one line that just said Bartles and James.
So you go in, you get Bartles and James, the cheapest wine coolers, I believe
imaginable.
And yeah, you just Dolly, you just tell Dolly your troubles.
Yeah, she seems she seems like a really nice lady.
Yeah, yeah, you could like, you know, you could leave that room feeling like you
have no problems compared to what's like at least compared to what she's been
through.
It sounds like she's been through quite a bit and she's got such a great ad.
Right.
Yes, she can smile through it.
Why can't I?
I think there is a robot bar in Nashville that like opened right at the start of
2020.
Like there is some sort of thing, but I don't I don't know how they're
currently doing.
Yeah, I went to an arcade that had some old school animatronics in it in
Chicago like two years ago and surprised and I met a listener of the podcast
there.
I was standing watching an animatronic show in an arcade and somebody's like,
excuse me, are you?
And I was like, well, that's of course, of course, you're here.
Statistically, yes.
Yeah, here and I am here.
Wow.
I didn't think I'd see a Clifford here.
Yeah, fellow Clifford was next to me.
You know, on the top, I'm sorry, I'm kind of hogging it, but there's like
there's these they're all flowing into each other nicely.
I think the there is something there was something at the top of the
there was something at the time that is sort of it feels like an entire place
that was like Dolly Dimples.
Have you guys has anyone ever come across a place called Gadgets?
No, Gadgets seems to be an early 80s thing.
And for the second time in the episode, I'll reference Brett from Forever Dog
and the producer of Double Threat with Tom Sharpling and Julie Klausner that
talked about Gadgets recently.
This was new to me.
So thank you, Double Threat.
This is an amazing news report about what?
Yeah, it completely seems like an adult
sort of TGI Friday, his type Xperia Fern bar.
This odd term I learned.
But with with robots, just this is the whole thing.
Oh, wow.
Nothing else around Gadgets, Gadgets, the only girl in town.
He's Sammy Sands and he's a robot.
Really grotesque animatronic piano player here.
Oh, my God.
Long Island.
There's just about everything from airplane propellers to washboards
and everywhere you look, the moving objects get your attention.
It's a combination of antique amusement park and high technology
all rolled into one.
And Candice Adams with Warner Leisure Company,
which is responsible for Gadgets, says she expects.
Let me also skip Candice Adams, but you just got to see more of the
because it's not just original IP like this, the piano player guy,
but the the the well, you'll see it.
There's also a very special action for the kids and the kid in all of us.
It's a robot cast of Looney Tunes characters and the Looney Tunes
will take you back to the mean an animal.
Wow. A Long Island restaurant with the Looney Tunes.
Three.
The folks up north will see me more when I get to that small store.
And then there's the food and the executive chef Mike Huffler
likes to think that his dishes make a gadget of a difference.
This is what we call our giant nacho platter.
And it's in a giant basket made of a flour tortilla
with taco chips and chili con queso sauce.
I don't know how to describe this listener, but I mean,
congealed.
Yeah, this looks like like the innards of some.
This looks like like maggots or something like this is what ends up
in a body after a death.
Mike, honey salad looks like we've got notes.
I mean, everyone was smoking 24 hours a day because this is what food
was at the time.
Macaroni salad mixed with the broja salad.
Enjoy.
That is really fine.
I think a kid would be afraid of.
Yes.
Oh, God, that shrimp salad came to life.
Oh, that cheesecake looks that tableau looks depressing.
The color quality of the film isn't helping.
Yeah, that's true.
It all looks a little gray, but yeah, but still, when are these wet
leaves on an orange going to be what you want next to your like spotty
cheesecake?
Wow.
Oh, that's cheesecake.
OK, I know I couldn't really tell you.
I think I was wondering.
And a chocolate dipped strawberry.
Yeah, I thought it was just a piece of cheese that wouldn't be
make sense.
Right.
That could be a cheese, a piece of cheese from a cheese block or
something.
Could you go back in?
Donald Duck is dressed like Angus Young from ACDC, right?
Daffy Duck?
Daffy.
Wait, you're right.
Oh, my God.
Oh, the.
Whoa.
Yes, he's dressed like a Daffy Duck is dressed like Angus Young,
who wears like a schoolboy outfit and ACDC little shorts.
He doesn't have a hat on, but that is the reference here.
Playing a guitar.
Even though wait, yeah, even though they're doing a medley of like
old timey Hollywood, he's dressed like ACDC.
I guess that's something for the dads in the audience to enjoy.
For everyone.
I mean, Gadgets is what I mean, the food looks horrible, but Gadgets
seems like if Gadgets was just suddenly up and open, I'd go.
Absolutely.
Especially because you get to the maybe I'd eat before, but then you
get to the bar.
And look, this is like this is like Oga's Cantina in Star Wars land.
Like it's a bunch of beakers and like, you know, weird like weird tubes.
And yeah, I would love to go here.
The way the way this reporter wraps up the story is pretty great, too.
That one of the specialties of the bar is something called a Sammy's
whammy named after that guy over there behind the piano.
And believe me, after you've had one or two of these, it doesn't matter
whether he's human or humanoid.
I'm Lynn Brown, Independent Network News.
Oh, the consummate professional.
Wow.
Is she saying she would go home with the robot?
What is this like?
Is that what she's saying?
It doesn't matter if he's a human or not.
Close enough.
Hey, I've had enough Sammy's whammies.
Wow.
It doesn't matter.
I carry you the one ton man I just met up the stairs to my apartment.
Removal your tubing.
Look, pal, it's a long, dark winter.
I just want someone to light my cigarette with.
I don't care if there's metal or bone inside of you.
I brought eight pieces of orange with wet leaves to go.
The ultimate aphrodisiac.
Wow.
Then there was only one location of that place?
There might maybe one more.
It didn't go far.
It didn't go far past Long Island.
Yeah, I was only open for two years, too.
That's it after all that?
Yeah, 82 to 84.
Oh my God.
Work out your The Warner Brothers licensing.
Oh yeah, that would have been right.
What year was it again?
82 to 84.
Wow, that's crazy.
A wonderful time.
You know it's aesthetically fantastic.
Lots of brass.
You know this is not for children.
I don't think you see one kid.
Is this for dates?
I think so.
Well, let's see.
Our food costs are 30%.
Our operating costs are 10%.
And then the other 60% is just Looney Tunes licensing fees.
We don't know how to balance this.
Wow, that's wild.
That's gadgets.
I don't know how I missed that one before and all the extra-factor restaurants.
I don't think we're even part way through all the animatronic restaurants that exist.
But I guess let's stay on Chuck E. Cheese and if somebody feels free to take the baton.
Well, go ahead, Jamie.
Oh, I just had one more current last year thing,
which was that Chuck E. Cheese had a brief tenure on Twitch.
He got into esports for...
It looks like he did a couple broadcasts.
I always meant to...
Because he would tweet about it,
assuming that Chuck E. Cheese sends his own tweets.
I don't know if he as a representative do it.
He was...
The puppet was going live as a Twitch streamer several times.
My guess, I don't have proof,
but just because I've seen screenshots is that they decided maybe it wasn't worth it
for the amount of really fucked up comments that the streams were getting.
But he streamed Animal Crossing in, I think, April or May.
And then he later streamed Fall Guys.
And he was blocking people in the chat.
He was replying, he was talking to people.
And as of last night,
because I was like, oh, I wonder if he's still in the game,
is he still streaming?
He hasn't streamed in four months.
I think that they figured it was maybe not worth it.
But there were a few stories about...
I don't know.
I mean, this past year has just been like attempt after attempt to keep Chuck E. relevant,
keep him on the cutting edge and keep him generating a profit.
I think the Twitch thing was maybe a bust in the end,
but I admire that he tried.
I can't name another mascot that was streaming on Twitch in the last calendar year.
Yeah, that's a lot of work.
We did a few Twitch streams and I did too.
And I was like, this is a lot of work.
You got to stick at it.
It's too much.
Yeah.
I am interested.
There's Lisa Frank, the property Lisa Frank with the folders and notebooks
with all the colorful, you know what I'm talking about, bears, whatever.
They have recently...
We were reading an article, Lindsay and I,
and they're popular on TikTok now because Lisa Frank's son has put the brand a little bit more on TikTok.
So you'll see like Lisa Frank character Hollywood bear dancing on TikTok now.
That's great news.
The Lisa Frank story is so wild too that I'm just glad she's doing okay.
I don't know any of this.
Oh, we got to do a whole Lisa Frank episode.
There's a whole factory, like dream factory she had that was only around for a few years
and then closed and it's now abandoned basically.
And in Arizona, it's like gigantic.
There's a whole story about her coked up husband slowly taking over the company and destroying it.
And then she broke up with him and then he started a Christian t-shirt company.
It's just like...
There's just so...
Yeah, the Lisa Frank hole is deep and rewarding.
Yes.
But go on TikTok and follow Lisa Frank to see Hollywood bear dance with Instagram and TikTok dogs, like real dogs.
They like do a branding thing.
Yeah, anyway.
I have to get on TikTok now?
That sounds awesome.
Yeah, you do.
You have to.
Let me...
Here, let me just...
I have a couple more things.
I mean, God, there's so much and there is still so much left.
This is not the end of our Chuck E. Cheese episodes.
Well, we'll let more disasters happen in the world and then talk about how Chuck E. Cheese dealt with them.
We'll be back.
Let me find...
This is a best of show.
I think it's from around 2012.
So it was not in my prime going to Chuck E. Cheese time.
But I really like it.
This is another thing where I'm just showing you something I like to show you what they were up to at the time.
This is a parody starring, I think, my favorite character Munch.
And you'll see what it is pretty quickly.
So Munch is singing into a spatula.
Green lasers behind him.
Yeah.
And he's got like a silver shirt on.
And he's got like...
He looks extra sleepy.
Yeah, his lids are all like...
He looks kind of tired.
He got drugs from Conrad Murray before this to get him up for the performance.
Oh, wait.
I just figured out what was happening.
Not a restaurant I associate with grilling.
Yeah, and he's like barbecuing.
It's got like a sparkly grill.
And he's got a little bit of a...
How can you not like that though?
So that was his little homage to Michael Jackson?
That's a Rock With You parody in the year 2012.
Wow.
Yeah, this is like a whole...
I found like a whole hour loop of whatever show they were playing in there at the time.
Oh, yeah.
And he's like, I'm going to go with the show.
I'm going to go with the show.
And a whole hour loop of whatever show they were playing in there at the time.
The disco ball grill was fantastic.
Yeah, the grill was good.
The shirt was good.
Again, I'll say this is not a restaurant I associate with grilling.
I literally went through my notes from the last episode and I have the sentence or the
phrase, hot dogs cooked in the pizza oven.
So...
Right.
Yeah.
That's bizarre.
Wonderful little gifts I left myself in that.
Like, make the garlic sauce using liquid margarine.
Pasquale filmed at White Settlement, Texas.
I think it's just the name of a town in Texas.
I don't know if it's still called that.
It might be.
Oh, that's a perfect segue for something I have.
Oh, cool.
Oh, wonderful.
I can only admit.
You'll never know.
I mean, it's going to come out of a strain.
You won't know where it's coming from.
Here, let me quickly do this.
OK, so this is a loop from 1991.
And it says Canada only, but I recall this type of thing playing.
This is Prime when we were going or when I was going, at least.
Yeah, yeah.
So this is a loop that they would play inside in between like robot shows.
And this is just a great logo.
You'll see it.
We'll post some clips of this.
Cyber star.
I like how he catches the spark.
I love that.
Yeah.
So very quickly, this is...
We talked about how on these videos, and this is still a thing they do to this day, it goes
back and forth between the robots and suited characters in the same piece of media, which
was jarring as a kid and I think is still a little jarring.
So this will set up with the premise of this whole 15 minutes is, and I swear I will not
make you all suffer through this 15 minutes.
Loving this.
We're supposed to sing a medley of disco hits by John Philip Sousa, but Larry...
Our technician.
He isn't playing our music.
Chuck E. look in the control room.
That's not Larry.
Chuck E. Cheese and his friends are about to take a musical detour into a past dimension.
A dimension not only of sight and sound, but of commercials.
A journey into a wondrous land whose boundaries are that of fringe reception.
That's the signpost up ahead.
Your next stop, the TV Zone.
Okay, so the TV Zone.
It's okay.
This is 1991, first of all.
Think about this.
Okay, so they're going to go into the TV Zone.
What would you think they're going to do?
Parody, cheers or something, right?
They have to be doing that.
Sure.
I would...
Yeah, I don't know.
I would probably...
My first guess would be like a swarthy Rod Serling puppet.
Well, that was the Rod Serling puppet is what I'm saying.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, that's what I probably would have done.
I probably would have done that.
Yeah, really like, yeah, a tired, drug-looking Rod Serling puppet.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, so what...
Yeah, based on the Michael Jackson homage in 2012, it's safe to assume they're operating
at least 20 to 25 years behind at any given time.
Now, yes, that's...
You're onto something here, because would you believe that the second parody,
I've skipped over the first one, but the second parody is of Car 54, Where Are You?
There's a highway in the Bronx, Brooklyn's broken out in vice.
There's a traffic jam right next to it.
What's that?
It's backed up to Jackson Heights.
There's a scout troop short of child, who's just still at Idlewild.
Car 54, Where Are You?
Oh, Francis.
Yes, Munter?
I think I cracked something.
Your brain?
No, I cracked a case.
I had my head on...
Your brain.
Okay, so I assume most people don't even know what Car 54, Where Are You?
is or was.
It was an old cop show.
It starred two of the Munsters, Al Lewis and Fred Gwin.
And it's a show I never really watched.
I think it was on Nick at Night a little bit, which is maybe why it's in this parody.
This whole reel.
So I think this whole thing was done.
This was totally done for the parents because this is 15 minutes of Nick at Night parodies
in 1991.
This is not for kids.
So bizarre.
And they go everywhere.
They do Adam's Family.
They do the Patty Duke Show, which is when Helen gets to shine.
And now it's suited Helen, not the robot Helen from the start of the video.
It's suited Helen dancing around to like a badly drawn backdrop that says hot dog stand.
And she's like just kind of shaking, like doing a lazy twist.
Let's not brush past the lyric.
A hot dog makes her lose control.
And that is a real line from...
Who Among Us.
That is a real line from the opening of the Patty Duke Show and a real line that Jason
thinks about every day.
Yeah.
You get Gilligan's Island here.
You get, let's see, you get the Chuck Van Dyke Show.
Chuck Van Dyke.
Now that sounds good.
Let's specifically parody the moments when Dick Van Dyke is at his job.
Don't have Chuck fall over something.
We want to see him at the office.
They're all playing like Buddy Sorrell and the character side characters.
Mel, Alan Brady's assistant Mel.
Robots can't trip over Ottomans.
So that's what they had.
Yeah.
So this they do all in the family here.
They do the Jefferson's.
Some of these are so ubiquitous.
How do these characters do the Jefferson's?
To the East Side.
A tea-loved puppet in the sky.
Wait, they just sing the song?
I guess they just sing the song.
Yeah, I guess that's why I didn't flag or something.
All right, so they do little inserts or Alfred Hitchcock parody.
Alfred Hitchcock presents.
I like that.
F-Troop.
Then they hit Leave It to Beaver and they introduce puppet characters.
To Beaver.
Gee Wally.
I think I'm really going to get yelled at.
So now they have like different characters playing Wally and the Beaver
from classic television.
So they throw this in at the very end.
And many loves of Dobie Gillis.
I'm sure anyone younger than us has turned off the podcast at this point.
Okay, so they do I Love Lucy, of course.
Lucy, honey, I'm home.
And they just have puppets of Lucy and Ricky.
Yes, and there's puppets.
They're not the characters playing anymore.
Your new guest star has been leaping into your arms all week.
And she pats and drools whenever she sees you.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
That's right.
And I brought her home to meet you.
You did?
Sure.
My new guest star is Lassie.
Okay, so that's Q Lassie.
That's what the joke is here.
Now here is when I almost fell out of my chair.
And there's a reason this happens.
But here I'll just play without interruption.
Away, away, away.
No, the Confederate flag has appeared on the screen.
Oh no.
Johnny Huma was a rebel.
Okay.
Oh my God.
Oh man.
Here is Munch singing the theme to an old show that I've never seen before.
And I'm so excited to be here.
I'm so excited to be here.
Here is Munch singing the theme to an old show that I've never seen.
What is this?
The Rebel Johnny Huma.
I've never, I barely know some of these.
That one just zero idea.
Why are we doing this?
That was so jarring.
So jarring.
Holy shit.
Filling the whole screen, forming one star at a time.
We had scarcely a moment to prep.
Yeah, I mean some of these shows were so ubiquitous with syndication and everything.
But I don't think Doe B.
Gillis and like Patty Duke show were necessarily quite as re-aired as like Twilight Zone and
Beaver were.
What even is this show?
The Rebel Johnny Huma.
I had to go back and look this up because I don't, was this even on Nick at Night?
F Troop was on Nick at Night.
A lot of these, Doe B.
Gillis, that was all on Nick at Night at the time.
I saw a little bit of that as a kid.
But not even Dukes of Hazzard.
Like the big one, the more obvious choice.
The more obvious Confederate flag show.
Yeah.
So anyway, so they do Green Acres and they close it out and that's the big loop.
Well that I like.
Sure, of course.
Guess what I have a chunk about.
Ooh, the Rebel Johnny Huma?
Well, Libby, I will keep this quick because there is no, we do not want to spend much
of our day dwelling on this.
Oh, I know exactly what this is.
1979, this is footage from 1979.
Here's the gang opening their frames they used to live in and then you pan across some
flags waving robotically and what do we have?
A Confederate flag.
This is why, this is why.
Is that like Jasper Jowell's cannon?
That's why Jasper's going away is because we're uncovering these clips of Jasper and
the Confederate flag flying next to him in the old clips.
It's been canceled.
We're canceling Jasper.
You've also got, this is from an annual report from the early 80s.
Here's Chuck in a white suit like Boss Hogg waving a Confederate flag.
In Florida.
For Florida?
Yeah, Florida's not the most like Confederate.
And a thing that I self-censored earlier because it was too dark for the room we were in.
Aaron Fector once made an entire animatronic show for a theme park in Tennessee and the
show was called the Confederate Critter Show.
Oh my god.
They're deep Confederate, they're deep Confederate ties to the Chuck E. Cheese.
What a dark episode.
What a bummer.
I'm so, I'm sorry to say all that but there's, look we can dovetail that.
It's just bizarre that, Mike I wonder if you were thinking this must be the only instance
of the Confederate flag in Chuck E. Cheese lore.
Scott I wasn't thinking that.
I wasn't.
I wasn't a thought I had.
You started smelling a rat as it were.
So the, I can get us to a lighter place though.
Are we sort of winding down or, because this might be a fun place to sort of stop.
I have, there's one last thing that I will say for next time because it's a 20 minute
clip of a game you could play where Chuck E. Cheese you would call him.
You would pay to call Chuck E. Cheese and he would like ramble at you for about a minute
and then always go, well call me back.
So call me back.
And like it was like, it felt really needy but it's too much to do.
We'll do it next time.
I'll save it.
Okay.
I will, this has motivated me to like, cause it's been, it sounds like something that I
should have done in, well the pandemic was really going but I do have like a vague mission
to at some point watch all the available show tapes.
Oh yeah.
Without pee breaks if possible.
We should have contacted you when this all began because it would have taken like a year
to get through it all.
So you have a year to prepare.
And hopefully we don't have another year in which you, hopefully you are now watching
show tapes instead of reuniting with friends and family.
Yeah.
I hope to use it as an excuse to never see my family again.
It's just this project.
Oh, sorry.
I have to go talk to these three guys about this.
Well, it's called Chuck E. in the galaxy 5,000 and oh boy, don't get me started.
Does an email to my parents.
It's Hollywood stuff.
It's a meeting.
General.
Generally about Chuck E. Cheese.
I'm amazed I didn't brave the full galaxy 5,000 perhaps for the next one.
I watched it yesterday and just I watched yesterday.
The whole thing.
Yeah.
And I was like, I, I, we probably won't get to this, but I'll have the notes for the future
and I need to watch it again.
Do you?
Unfortunately.
Yeah.
That is I say that.
Sorry, Scott.
You're 100%.
But coming soon.
Maybe in the future.
Yeah.
Well, plenty more meat on the bone.
Obviously this, this might be a fun, just, you know, a light one, one that you can't,
you can't hate on.
This is again, so much more nineties than I thought I would find.
And this is from 1998.
It actually is, I think, current relevant topical, but still as fun to this day.
Here's this.
Oh, man.
Wow.
Glasses and a blue suit with some ruffles.
Chuck E. Cheese, international mouse of mystery.
Wow.
And this is just some good fun for everyone.
They do the full opening credits of the first meat on the bone.
And I'm like, I'm going to go with this one.
I'm going to go with this one.
They do the full opening credits of the first movie.
Wow.
Like a Bobby comes up, glares, but then they all danced together.
It's all just all the jokes and beats.
What would I choose?
I, yeah, you know, the, the models that I'm trying to think any other moments.
I mean, it's just every, this, it's the full thing.
Wow.
And in the bit, like they do the full dance.
He gets a little off sync.
Oh yeah.
Because he's a mascot.
Hey, let's, God, let's see this.
He's an amazing dancer.
They're doing pretty good.
Yeah.
And what a start.
I mean, imagine the show that must have followed that.
Um, it must have been one of the great show tapes.
Wow.
Just a delight.
Imagine having that on your directing reel.
Just being like, look, I can do a lot.
Yeah.
Man, I would love.
I would love to handle this Marvel.
Well, let me flip this answer the question.
And save the best for last.
So good.
Well, you know, we, we uncovered some skeletons in the closet, but, um, you know, this, this
reinvigorated the brand for me.
I feel great about it.
Um, I feel great about the future.
They've kept the content coming.
The YouTube channel has been great.
Um, I don't know.
Do we think they're going to turn it around?
Will there be a Chuck E.
Cheese for us to do an episode about, uh, again?
That's a good question.
I don't, there is still the one right over here in Burbank, um, that is still operating
with takeout and stuff, but I, I don't know.
I feel like they're going to make it.
I feel like, you know, they're like, well, much like rats can survive anywhere.
They can, they can, you know, they're vermin.
They can last, you know, humans can be wiped out and rats are still on the planet.
I feel like maybe Chuck E.
Will find a way.
Is it going to be a way we love and would want to go?
Maybe not, but it'll exist.
I think it's going to make it.
I think it's going to make it into its next metamorphosis.
Yeah.
I, it's not going to be my dream of the doors being flown, flung open, him in the blue suit
going, do I make you cheesy, baby?
But, uh, you know, I think they'll be bad.
I think they'll, I think they'll, they'll manage.
Yeah.
Hopefully.
I agree.
Yeah.
I mean, it's like they, they have made it very clear that they are willing to exhaust
every possible option before calling it quits.
They're not above tricks.
They're not above scams.
They're not above e-sports.
They're not above anything.
And they will continue to try until, until it's literally no longer possible.
I mean, what they should have done during the pandemic is restore a show of animatronics
and program it to top like hit songs or like parodies of hit songs, upload those videos
and go after like, you know, the youth.
They should have a drive-in show with a full band that you could pay to go see.
I don't, I can't even imagine that.
Yeah.
But probably what they are doing is figuring out if they could rent out half the restaurant
to like a local electronics store.
Like that's probably really what's going on.
Well, can we make it smaller?
Drone repair, iPhone screen repair, vape juice.
Oh yeah.
Vape.
It's a Chuck E. Cheese slash vape store.
Slash everything, everything repair store.
Yeah.
That's probably what's happening.
So anyway.
Yeah.
Well, I hope they keep plugging away.
I hope there's a great, a bright, beautiful future for them.
Jamie Loftus, You Survive podcast, The Ride, Chuck E. Cheese 2.
Thanks for joining us once again.
What a blast.
Thanks for having me.
It, it always feels good to talk about Chuck E. Cheese for two hours.
Sure.
Of course.
Yeah.
Thank you.
I'm glad that's the case.
I feel like some people might not be able to make that statement, but I'm glad you're,
I'm glad you would.
Like say the accountants of Chuck E. Cheese.
Indeed.
Let's exit through the gift shop where you can purchase items that are normally won through
games.
Is there anything that you would like to plug?
There, if you want to listen to something really dark, you can listen to my new podcast
called Lolita podcast.
It's about, it's a complete taxonomy of the history of Lolita.
Or if you don't want to be upset, you can listen to the Bechtel cast on I Hurt Radio.
It's a feminist movie podcast that comes out every week and is only occasionally sad.
Like this episode with its confederate context, but otherwise pretty delightful.
Yeah, that's fantastic.
Love my ear in Mensa too.
Oh, thanks.
So yeah, check out everything Jamie does.
And for us, check out our social medias.
And if you want three bonus episodes a month, you can subscribe to the podcast.
We're at the second gate at patreon.com slash.
And if you want to see more of our podcast, check out the podcast.
To the podcast, we're at the second gate at patreon.com slash podcast.
The ride.
Well, fellas, let's close the curtain up or else or if there's no curtain, just stop moving
entirely for at least 15 minutes.
Yeah.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a forever dog production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Baum, Joe Sileo
and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts,
Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.