Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to what I'm sure will be an extremely comfortable episode of Podcast the Ride, the
Second Gate as we discuss the miracle of birth, the miracle of life as shown to us through
recently, constantly on the podcast, Martin Short.
I'm Scott Gardner, joined for this
day of miracles by Jason Sheridan.
Never been more comfortable in my life.
And Mike Carlson.
I'm here, I watched the thing we're talking about today through my hands, with my eyes
kind of peering out through my fingers.
I just, I didn't know what was coming and I
didn't want to be traumatized by it.
But I think I'll be okay.
If I have to excuse myself
or if I faint, I apologize.
You are describing my exact state of mind about this film, this Epcot Center film that
I had at the time and I thought I wouldn't have now and yet in a way, I guess I don't
know.
This is weird.
Here's a question.
Did everybody see this movie at the time?
Did
anyone watch this in person in the place that it was in the Wonders of Life Pavilion?
I cannot remember.
I feel like if I would have, I would have had a lot more questions.
And I would have gone into seventh grade health class a lot more prepared.
I don't remember.
What was the refresh?
What's the, how long was it there again?
I have it written down somewhere.
Now I don't know where it, I don't know when it left honestly.
I have it.
Was there an opening?
Yeah, Jason.
Okay.
October 1989, it opens and it closes with the rest of the Pavilion January 1st, 2007.
Wow.
What a run.
What a great run for it.
I, it's weird.
I don't have a memory of seeing this, but it is possible that I did because it's very Epcot Center.
And as we said before about Epcot, a lot of experiences of Epcot blend together, especially when you're remembering something from 25 years ago.
But this one, I think this stands out.
This is an impossible one to blend.
It's very unique.
I for sure.
Yeah, I, you know, we were talking about the making of me an original movie for the wonders of life Pavilion starring Martin Short.
And, you know, I don't, I don't think of this.
I think of this moment a lot, but there's there's a funny or die video made by past guest Nick Weigert called Gungan Style.
And it features past guests of the show, Ryan Perez, and in it he has a wonderful delivery of the line.
So why are you doing this?
And that is how I thought about like reading about this ride.
I was like, why did they do this?
Yeah, yeah, because if you don't know it, if you never got to experience it, it is a it is a film about
the miracle of life, about birth, about the reproductive process.
Basically, you know, long story short, this is a Disney sex ed film.
This is a sex ed film that you could watch on vacation exclusively in Epcot Center.
This is crazy because I don't think like the Marvel characters are allowed to like kiss that much anymore.
Like I think that they're so afraid of certain things that might be like uncomfortable that like the company now is would never, ever, ever know something like this in one of their theme parks.
It's odd to do it back then, but I can at least see like their thought process of like it's this is going to be a very educational day at Disney World for youngsters.
So I guess we could also like we're doing body wars if we're explaining how, you know, fossil fuels work.
I guess maybe we should explain to the kids with a friendly, friendly Clifford man how reproduction works.
I can see their logic, but it is very funny to think about it now, especially in the context of what they're comfortable with.
Yeah, I hadn't thought about this that how like the are their bread and butter in the recent past Marvel and Star Wars, whatever you think of these franchises, they are the unsexiest franchises you've ever like.
No one would ever describe anything in any of these movies as sexy.
Not that making a me is supposed to be sexy.
It's just in the in the, you know, the argument of them getting anywhere close to even the topic to even saying the word.
There's animated sperm, you know, there's animated sperm and animated sperm at Epcot Center is the headline.
If you didn't know about this cart cute cute, I will say definitively cute cartoon sperm at Epcot Center for years, years.
Definitely cute, but then they're like they talk like they're sort of like Brooklyn guys.
There's a race going.
We got to make a baby.
We got to we got to go get that egg.
I'm a cute sperm.
I don't you think that's cute?
Well, I don't think the voice is necessarily cute, but I think their design is visually design wise.
You take the personality out of it.
Just purely aesthetically, I do find the cartoons sperm cute.
That's very I'm shocked by that.
I thought you would be pure discomfort with every step of this.
So now to hear that you find the sperm cute.
Well, I'm a theme park journalist and I can separate myself sometimes from my own personal beliefs and feelings.
Obviously, I believe no child should ever learn any of this stuff.
I think that this should be blind until wedding night.
And then you sort of had a pamphlet from a priest and you quickly do what it says in the pamphlet and you hope that that's the one time you get pregnant and then you never talk about it again.
Never have to remotely revisit.
Hopefully you have hopefully you have triplets also with that one intercourse.
Take care of it all at once.
Yeah.
Children really exist as scars as proof that you had to do the dirty, awful deed.
But you got through it.
Hey, that actually to that end, this was part of what inspired doing this topic.
I I feel bad roping him into this after the creepy discussion so far.
But I have been a dad for a year now.
I am a year out from having experienced the the miracle of birth and I thought this could be I thought this would be fun to talk about.
And what I didn't realize is how much would plunge me back into like if I ever saw this at the time and I'm not really sure.
But it just it did plunge me back into just feeling like, well, you'll never you'll never do any of this.
If this is your comfort level with learning basic, un-graphic information about where babies come from, then you know, you don't have to worry about ever going there.
The lights you go to an interminably long dance and then the lights go down.
At some point, there's a wedding and you get a phone call.
You know, there's a brief water skiing interlude.
There's a water skiing interlude.
There's a second dance, a honeymoon dance and different kind of dance.
It sounds like a lot of planning and a lot of work.
I.
Yeah, this this is it's it's extremely strange.
And like I said, I thought I'd be comfortable watching it now.
I was like so shocked by that.
And and I watched it with with Aaron, who I did the baby with.
And she was mortified.
She was mortified through this entire thing.
Like, yeah, you would think two people who have who have made who have made a me there's a me out there made by us.
You'd think we'd be comfortable with this film.
But, oh, my, it's like it's utterly creepy to both of us and everyone.
It's very chase and like unnervingly.
It's perverse.
But it's also very ambly.
It's very like ET soaring music while they're talking about some of this stuff, which is I find an odd juxtaposition as well.
I mean, I get that like making a child like, you know, that's such an emotional experience.
But like before that, like the nuts and bolts of it, like it's supposed to be like, wow, the sperm and the egg.
Wow.
Yeah.
I guess it's a miracle.
I guess they're also like tiptoeing from what I read.
They were concerned about like, OK, first off, we don't want to get tied into the abortion debate.
And it's like, oh, OK.
And I feel like they go out of their way to have more.
They don't they don't like say like here Martin Short says like, this is me at three months and now me at six months.
But he doesn't go like this is a person like, you know, this is a thing they do.
You know, it's very obvious, very hetero hetero normative in the like there's two types of people, lady kind and mankind.
Yes, I did note that.
And and that, you know, I they science knew there was more kinds back then.
You know, society took a long time to catch up.
And so I, you know, but you can feel them like sometimes you can feel Disney try not to be political.
Like the pictures in the Carthage Circle bar and restaurant where Walt is like they have Photoshopped a cigarette out.
It's like, OK, this just looks like you.
You've created an unreality in your attempts not to offend.
Yeah, don't put yourself in this situation.
Don't go anywhere near the arena if you don't want to deal with the subtlety.
I think you like why no one made them do this.
As far as I know, did MetLife, the sponsor of the Pavilion, I think, require.
Look, we've been really meaning to get some sex ed info out there.
So that's our one stipulation.
Yeah.
Parents were like coming to Main Street going like this place has everything at the help desk or whatever.
This place has everything except I would really like it if like somebody could teach my kid how to make a baby here.
That would be the one thing I would have as far as a suggestion is concerned at Walt Disney World.
Yeah.
Well, just like it's a one stop shop.
You know, Dad can golf and Mom can shop and the kids can enjoy meeting cartoon characters and going on rides.
We're taking care of so much.
So can you help me avoid the talk while we're here for six days?
Can Ed Grimley describe sperm to my young child?
Please.
Can it be a man known for his main lot in life is playing creepy characters?
Can it be the king of the creeps?
Yes.
All his famous characters are the creepiest characters and on Nerva young child.
Can he please explain about where they came from?
I like this might be one where it might behoove us to go sort of in order because I think a lot of people have not seen this or have only the fuzziest memory of seeing it.
If they did, the YouTube copies are pretty roundly terrible, despite ones that say remastered.
That is still filmed from the back of the weird small theater that they have this thing in.
They're functional.
But remember, filming, filming project projected film with like interlaced, you know, VHS is not going to look great.
You know, it's all very stroby and potentially seizure causing.
So if you have made a me, if you're expecting, I think maybe don't watch the YouTube version of this because you it might be unhealthy for your for your child.
For your me.
You've recently made a me.
You recently made a me.
Yeah, it's somewhat.
Sometimes it's interesting.
I'm always so curious, like how is there a perfect pristine copy of Captain EO on YouTube from like the original reel or something?
And then there's certain things that are like this.
Like, I don't know.
How do people get copies of certain like pavilion movies and then others are not.
I'm always so confused by how that happens or why.
I mean, everything's like did any did did someone is it just like, well, someone liked this one.
So they saved it and no one cared enough to save the making of it.
It's a good possibility.
That's the case.
Not a single person was interested in archiving this bizarre movie.
Very possible.
Let me set the stage a little bit here.
So, yeah, we're in the wonders of life pavilion.
We've talked.
This was a later addition to Epcot 89.
We have talked about Cranium Command where you're in the brain.
We will at some point talk about body wars where you're in the bloodstream.
So it's generally about your body and life and health.
So, you know, we got to go see.
Got to see the nut.
You know, I feel like that that literally feels like a pitch in a conference room.
It's like, Mark, take it.
Take a 10.
Get some air.
I mean, man.
Well, obviously, that what if they wanted to address this area,
it should have been a ride where you go into the night and where we all get.
Yeah.
Where you get ejaculated.
Like, clearly, that's a launch coast.
That's a lot of first launch coaster before Disney started doing it.
Sixty miles an hour launch.
And then you'd get to really like understand it like you wouldn't have to have someone explain it to you.
You just know, oh, I get it now.
Yeah.
There's only one place you saw some vague like tower like at an incline.
You would understand.
Oh, OK.
So that's what you're.
All right.
I understand sex now.
It really it's you know, it should be a really a lot like,
maybe like Superman, the ride at Six Flags, a shoot off and up.
Maybe I guess you come back down, though, that doesn't make any sense.
Although I don't want to actually get into the physics of that and what that would actually represent.
I think it would have to be like the Space Mountain in Paris where there's a launch up
and then there's a whole like world that you get like you would have to you'd end up with like blinding white light.
And that represents like that's the moment of conception.
Can I I think that's absolutely correct.
But I do think that you would have wanted still like the start of rock and roller coasters launch.
You would have to have a Steven Tyler scream to start it off.
I think that would also be really good.
It's just like I thought you were just going to say muffled like,
you know, mixed tape playing in the background muffled, jaded playing in the distance.
Or you could have like a radio announcer like, check out Steven Seiler's new hat.
And then you ejaculate.
Yesterday, by the way, yesterday was Aerosmith Day in Boston in case when recording this on the 14th,
but the 13th in April is Aerosmith Day.
It was declared by a mayor or something.
I just want to let everyone know that.
Obviously, you don't need to go through basics on this podcast.
You could have said the sky is blue.
That's not news to anyone.
That's true.
I apologize.
I want to pander or I want to maybe we we all celebrated.
We all put on scarves for Aerosmith Day.
Yeah, I know.
I know you guys did.
So happy Aerosmith Day is all I wanted to say.
We put we put pics in the yard for the baby to find to go on a on a peri pic hunt.
Joey Kramer.
First of the words.
OK, so anyway, in setting the scene, basically what I'm trying to say is like I loved Wonders of Life so much.
We talked about Kramer Command, love Kramer Command.
I loved all these.
I love that.
That's the most like, you know, 80s mallish pavilion.
And not only that, I wanted to do everything that there was to do at Disney World the first time I went.
And I had the Burn Bombs guide.
I don't know if we've talked about Burn Bombs guides that travel.
But I read this thing on the on the flight over.
I read it front to back.
I knew everything there was to do at Disney World before we got there.
And I just remember reading about this one like, huh?
Well, we'll see when we get there.
It sounds very bad to me, but I do want to do everything there is to do.
And then I got to the sign that is outside the the attraction, which I think bears reading.
Dear guest, the making of me explores the sensitive subjects of human reproduction and birth.
This film contains spectacular images of fetal development as well as live footage of the birth process.
We ask that you use discretion when deciding whether you or your family should view the making of me.
Thank you.
Out.
I was out turned around.
No, thanks.
This this you're going to I don't think I know the word fetal at this point.
And hold on.
I'm going to learn something about sex and see what babies are like inside that with my mom.
I'm going me and my mom are going to walk in and watch this together.
I don't think so.
No, thanks.
One more body wars for me, please.
Did you like a cartoon like pull out a picket sign immediately and start walking up and down outside to picket it?
No more filth.
Yeah, because I would imagine like Madonna or any of the other controversial people.
Oh, yeah.
You were like probably fired up about it.
God, right around the same time that they're willing to do business with that cone broad.
Or lit.
And then they're willing to promote the idea of people having sex.
I mean, they were really.
Yeah, they were.
They were mired at the time.
I do wonder, did like Limbaugh or like Morton Downey Jr.
like pick up on this one, like because that's the thing I was reading about.
Fox News does now they just like hone in on some, you know, you know, seminar at a community college or like a weird like local government like, yeah,
a thing or they just like the world is ending if a library does, you know, drag queen story hour and they just blow it out of proportion.
Like this is the end of society.
Everything is collapsing.
Like I did anyone I didn't really find any like controversial stuff.
I think there was one newspaper article.
It's like, well, this is certainly interesting.
Yeah, I don't think this was so popular.
I don't think this was popular enough.
Yeah.
Warrant controversy at the time.
That's a guess.
But yeah, there was no Richter scale whatsoever.
Like nothing.
The needle did not move.
Right.
Yeah.
So that was the oh, what do we got here?
Oh, there's the the outside.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
This scared me.
These puzzle pieces.
Yeah.
The puzzle pieces are certainly a choice.
I have to say I do like that it is a building within a building that's appealing to me.
I don't quite know why.
I just kind of like that.
And I like the color scheme.
You too.
That's why this broke my heart to not go in and building in a building.
I like what you're saying.
But then like just just made it like, all right.
Well, it's colorful, but it's still like a shack where I'm going to watch a sex movie with my mom.
No, thanks.
I think I was mostly interested in getting a turn at the stationary bike
with a screen that made it look like you were peddling through Disney.
Is that is that right?
Yeah.
Am I imagining that?
OK, that is real.
Love that thing.
Yes.
Yeah, that's like why was that so exciting?
Conan's desk bit.
Yeah.
Which, yeah, I think the faster you peddled, the faster the footage went to.
Yeah, it just seemed fun.
Can I can I real quick get in a do you have memories of
because I have one very specific one, a memory of watching something that was really uncomfortable
because you were watching it with your parents?
My mind, maybe I said this already in the other episode.
It was Ace Ventura, Ace Ventura.
There's a very comic sex scene in that movie and we saw it in the theater.
And I just remember feeling like I wanted to die.
It felt like it lasted for like 15 minutes.
And I remember my mom like looking at my dad because he like had decided
that we were going to see Ace Ventura because he wanted to see it.
And I just remember like, oh, my, how am I ever going to get out of this movie?
Like, how am I ever going to get out of this situation?
You you did this.
You did this to our family.
Yeah.
Yeah, that is right.
That's my recollection of it.
Maybe they don't think it's like that, but we'll see.
I'll hear about it.
I have one which is that we we did watch Seinfeld a lot and I watched it as a kid
despite there being sexual scenarios and they would just always be ready to to pounce or to change the channel
if they thought that anything was getting dicey or to just avoid me asking questions about like,
what's a diaphragm or whatever that might come up?
What is mommy?
What is Spongworthy?
I boy, I think they they completely just whiffed it on that.
They just like talked about other things and spun their way out of the room to avoid it.
But I don't know.
Is this even in the same episode?
I don't know.
There's just a there's a thing where a condom is being fumbled with.
And it's just a close up of hands in a condo.
But I just I just remember like both parents like leaping across the room to cover my eyes for what never.
To be fair, they didn't know what was coming.
But also it's it's like NBC.
Like, I don't think they're just going to like.
All right.
Now we tilt down and see George's George's erect penis.
But I just remember like and I didn't understand like what what's and then when I caught glimpses of it,
I'm like, that's like a little balloon pack.
What's the problem?
I can't I see that.
Yeah, that's that seems right.
I don't know that my parents ever like did a superhero action hero dive across the move to change channel.
Excuse me, Jason, what do you got?
Anything I I've got to that they're both kind of like have asterisks.
But I remember watching with all of my family.
We ran it.
The Shining, just because I think we could all we weren't big on horror.
You know, we liked everyone in the family could agree on.
Are you afraid of the dark rolling right into Alfred Hitchcock Presents?
And at a certain age, I started becoming interested in movies.
I was like, can we rent like The Shining, Stanley Kubrick movie?
And I don't know that my brother would have watched it,
but I think we're all definitely sitting around and, you know, there's certainly nudity in the one, if not two sequences in that.
I think the abject horror is kind of overshadows it.
So I don't I don't think we jumped as much.
I don't know.
Another memory I have is being at like some sort of summer camp or like maybe it's on a cruise ship,
some sort of like kids like teens group like preteens and teens like hang out in its movie time.
And the movie they chose to show was The Rock.
And that has a very funny, like a very strange sex scene like a like a sex scene where they're like having a conversation and like played for laughs.
And that was just very weird to watch with other like 12, 13, 14 year olds and a couple of adults in the back of the room.
Yeah, I get that.
I don't remember this Rock.
And then my real quick, my sorry, my remember though, my mom loved that old 60 1968 Romeo and Juliet movie.
And you see Romeo's butt in that.
And she showed us that.
But she liked it, I guess.
So it was fine.
A scandal, scandalous at the time, I believe.
I think so.
Yeah.
Yikes.
Wow.
So I don't know if my mom liked the scene.
She was fine with it, I guess.
She didn't like my coarseness of Ace Ventura, I guess.
My mom took the the MPAA ratings very seriously as if they had been like around for a while.
Like if not himself had assigned the rating.
Oh, yeah, I was that way too.
My friend Luke could watch R rated movies.
And I think the first R rated movie I saw was South Park in the theater with my dad.
Yeah.
And the movie theaters near me were pretty strict about checking IDs.
But then I realized like a blockbuster video will rent you anything.
Sure.
I.
And you know, especially if you're a young, young, nerdy little little preteen who is very interested in hacking his way through the A.
F.
100 list.
That was a big deal when that first came out.
And yeah, they're not checking if you're here bringing an R rated.
They're just scanning the box.
Do back in three days.
Roman Holiday, please.
I suppose there's not that much R rated.
There's a few later movies, you know.
OK, so so the film.
All right.
We.
And again, I don't I really don't remember if I if I saw it at the time.
So so watch it recently.
It begins with Martin Short in like a black void initially.
And he says, how do you know it happens to everybody?
Just all of a sudden one day you wonder where you came from.
And we get to hear his story.
It becomes not a black void.
He's in the hallway of a delivery ward.
And he goes and he points to his dad in the room where there's a bunch of babies all at once.
I don't know what that's called or what it is because I had a baby in Covid era.
So this was not familiar to me whatsoever.
There was no lots of baby's room.
So so so now we've established is going to be like a this is like a time hopping thing.
He's going back to see the early days of his parents.
Yeah.
And he plays his own father.
Yes, which is we got to high school.
Realize he's playing his own father.
There's a pretty awkward cut in there because I think we go from dad is baby.
And he says that.
But you know, but before my story can begin, he's still got to meet mom.
Let's check in on her goes to see mom at like age five, six.
I'm not sure.
She's like playing with perfume that she shouldn't be.
And her mom stops her.
So she's just a little girl and she's going to be punished.
We don't want to see that.
So let's get out of here.
Let's go check on dad cuts to dad in high school played by a grown man.
And I don't know what they were intending.
I think there's a jump in time.
But the way the jump happens, it makes you go.
Wait, so the mom's six and he's like 17.
What's the it's a reverse Padme Anakin situation.
Maybe they could first meet when they were wildly different age.
I mean, they're always going to be at same age, but it was an appropriate age, I guess.
Maybe.
But I think that I think there's a time jump.
That's how I interpreted it.
But I know what you're saying.
It is confusing.
Yeah.
There's also a moment I don't want to skip over this.
It's very quick.
You have to pause it to try and catch it.
But the mom, before she plays with the makeup and stuff as like a child,
she's walking down a hallway with a baby carriage.
And the quick shot of the doll in the baby carriage is one of them.
It's it's upsetting.
Like, like, what the fuck, man?
What is this?
I don't care for this.
And I had to keep rewinding it to go like, is that like,
did they superimpose Martin Short's fate?
Like, what were they trying to account?
And I think it's just a very strange doll.
Mm hmm.
But that's a like you just described the perfect part for Martin Short to play.
Well, now maybe that was wishful thinking on my part.
There's still time.
Yeah.
Come on, Marty, play a doll.
It's on the subject of Martin Short.
I forgot to say, too, I said this an episode forever ago, that Martin Short is in four Disney theme park films,
not even attraction, not even like yours.
There's a pre movie before a ride.
It's all films.
There's this there's the monster sound show from when Disney MGM opened.
There's something that's exclusive to Disney's work.
The worst park Disney's Hollywood Studios is that what Disney Studios Paris in Europe called Ciné Magique and Oh Canada,
the Circle Vision movie.
So he's been in two Epcot movies, four theme park things overall.
It's a it's a rough filmography.
He's like number one, I think, Paz, besides like the voice of Mickey Mouse and increasingly Chris Pratt.
But he's been in so many things and it's all a pretty like like is anyone super fond of any of what I just listed?
I'm trying to think it's like the most popular one.
Oh Canada, I guess.
Just maybe like Canada.
I've never seen it.
I like it.
Yeah, I like that one.
What was the other there?
There's the Paris one.
This was the fourth monster sound show with Chevy Chase.
That was that where it was a thing where you made the sound effects, I believe.
Oh, yeah.
OK.
Yeah.
I don't I don't remember that super well, but I I mean, I loved all the binaural audio stuff and the little booths.
And so I think that probably would be what I would choose to prefer.
I know there is some good quality copies of some other videos went up, Superstar Television and the Mel Brooks, the Mickey's Big Break, not the Mickey's Big Break.
We talked about that.
There's another Mickey's Big Break.
Jim and Lett had been talking about it recently.
Oh, yeah.
Where did that play?
Well, the Mickey's Big Break that we were talking about was from the like the late 90s or 2000, the one where with Go Soak Your Head, Fresh Boy.
But Mickey's Big Break with Mel Brooks and like a bunch of other stars, Carol Kane, I think shows up in it.
That I believe they said was in MGM Studios as like a bridge attraction, like something is closed.
We need to fill some time.
And they just shot this thing and put it up real quick.
Yeah.
Faintest memory of that.
Not totally sure.
Yeah.
Anyways, odd filmography, this being perhaps the oddest entry.
So he's in a high school classroom as a chalkboard.
And I think it says on the chalkboard next week, the reproductive process.
So that gives that gives Martin, our Martin, not dad Martin, the the in to turn to us and use the chalkboard to demonstrate some stuff.
We have the I'll just say the line verbatim.
Oh, yeah.
About growing up.
Very important for people who want to have babies because most of the baby making equipment doesn't begin to work until you mature.
This is this is a line you could see on your vacation.
The baby making equipment doesn't work.
Baby making equipment.
Like work.
I mean, it does some stuff.
I think it's the other stuff that comes later, I guess.
It's part of it works and then it could work earlier for some people.
And then I yeah, the tap of the prescription, the tap water.
Maybe it doesn't work all the way.
If you know what I'm saying, they can't intellectually.
Yeah.
But I'm comfortable with every word said everything remotely close to this.
So I imagine this was all, yeah, like, you know, going over with a fine tooth comb at the time to be like, we have to explain that this the penis doesn't work yet in the way we want.
But we have to say it in a neutral way.
Yeah, we know 80s and 90s pop culture.
The motto may as well just be sex sells the most.
But suburban madness tells you that don't it just it's all it's awful.
No, no, no, no.
Yeah.
How do you square that circle?
And yeah, yeah, this movie does not not have the answer, I wouldn't say.
But before we can talk about baby making or body parts or any of that, we have to talk about people.
This is when there's the very stuck in the past.
There's two types of people.
That's it.
And that's it.
No more questions.
We only got 15 minutes.
That's a perfect amount of time to cover everything.
All the issues that this opens up.
So he goes in his little sex ed lesson and then we see a diagram and what we see on the chalkboard, I would have to think is the only iteration in a Disney park of an intentional depiction of a penis.
Maybe in any theme park.
I hope I hope that there's not a lot of like maybe on if you're going for like an Italian statue sort of vibe that would still possibly be allowed.
Is there like a French or Italian theme park called like Penisland or Dickland or something like there is like a gross out park.
Yeah.
I'm not sure what it is.
It's got to be something like that.
Yes.
And as far as a mainstream American park.
Yeah.
All the penises are subtle if they exist.
They are subtle.
They were put there by horny imagineers who were doing it for a gag between them and their other imagineer buddies.
Typical Hollywood sickos.
Yeah.
We've seen the boxes of Disney animated releases and the priest with the boner and little mermaid.
Those animators, those pervert animators.
You will see arguments about that kind of thing like today.
Like in the in the panic of like Q world, they'll say these Hollywood sickos and you know, the priest gets a boner and little mermaid.
Did you know that?
Like, yeah, you mean from over 30 years ago?
Is that what you're talking about?
Yeah, it's probably a knee anyway.
But this there's no mistaking because it's a diagram.
Let's look at it together.
There's the penis.
As well as, you know, the tubes, the lady, the fallopian tubes.
Yeah.
Calpers gland over on the right and sure.
I feel like any any time like a health book needs to portray like a reproductive system, but it doesn't want to make it like sexual.
There are me like, OK, lead with the fallopian tubes.
You know, put a drawing of that in there.
Not sexy probably.
I don't think that's there's like a specific appeal in the fallopian tubes like your intestines or something.
I just just got so many handouts at like public school education, public school health class of like like just sheer boiled down to like these are different kinds of anatomy.
There are blanks next to him.
You know, when there's a blank on a worksheet, you got to fill it in, fill it in.
And I don't I don't know what that purpose was serving.
Looking back, what did barely comes up?
Look, we had a baby.
We had and I still don't like remember what all the various parts are that come into play.
It's like, you know, it's like when you go to a you go to another country and you learn enough language to get by and then you forget it as soon as the vacations over.
I've already jumbled as to what all these body parts are.
I yeah.
And the medical field does not seemingly prioritize a lot of people's health.
And it wasn't until I was much older.
I learned about like, yeah, there's a lot of ailments specific to stuff.
And it's like, why didn't this come up in health class?
You know, what I want to learn about ailments when you were well, you know, you just look I just feel foolish when I'm older.
It's like, well, they they never I don't yeah, like stuff never came up, I think, until people like had to actually deal with it either.
You know, they had it or a family member had it.
I don't know.
I had public education.
You know, yeah, it's a real roll of the dice.
I had a great school, but there was definitely some questionable choices.
Hmm.
Right.
Well, look, if you want me to, I'll explain to you what the Vaz deference does and what the cowper's gland does off air, though.
I don't want to.
I don't know what the cowper's gland is.
I wrote I looked up what the cowper's gland does for a bit that I had Jason disgustingly do about seven years ago on stage.
And I have forgotten.
I will be OK.
Yeah.
But we have them to all three of us have cowper's.
I hope so.
I mean, I haven't I haven't had one removed.
I didn't like my cow.
Yeah.
Gland didn't like burst.
You know, if you had an aftermarket model, if you had gotten something replaced or swapped out synthetic cowper's gland.
Yeah.
Has science perfected this?
Maybe.
I mean, those like, you know, your any of your characters on fiction have a synthetic this like Winter Soldier have a synthetic cowper's gland.
Do we know they haven't gotten it?
They see they're not going to get into that.
Maybe in the 80s.
Yeah.
Maybe in the 80s they would have been certainly not now.
Despite this might be a zone where I know we're getting off of the movie a fair amount, but I was like, I can't resist asking if any of us have specific memories about.
How we did learn where babies come from.
Yes, I have absolutely know exactly how it went down.
Mm hmm.
And my memory of it is I might be combining two different explanation dumps by my mother in one conversation.
So I have a memory of asking two specific questions.
I don't know if I've said this in the show before.
Two questions in one two things that were bothering me that I didn't understand both at the same time.
I remember my mom sitting on the bed and explaining this stuff to me.
And the two questions were how am I you say like I'm related by blood to dad.
If I just came out of you, how do I actually have a relation to that?
That doesn't make sense to me.
How how would I be actually blood related to him if I just came out of you?
That doesn't make that question to Santa Claus doesn't actually.
Does not go bunch out at one ring toys for everyone.
Right.
That seems wrong.
Like my memory is both of those getting knocked out in one conversation.
I think they are probably around the same time in third grade that I come upon both of these.
I don't know if that's that's earlier than I got to any of this.
That's to either one.
I think it's their great could be third or fourth.
I think third or fourth for sure.
And yeah, my mom was like, I'm saying we're Santa Claus because I think I've said this on the show before.
My mom had to start retconning stuff after I was asking questions like I go, Mom, wait a minute.
If people don't have money, if they're poor like Santa doesn't does he bring them things?
Why wouldn't he just bring them things and then they wouldn't be poor anymore?
My mom's like, oh, we we have to pay Santa.
What?
I was like, oh, OK.
Like that lasted maybe another six months of my logic where I go, oh, OK, that seems odd.
It kind of takes the magic away of Santa leaves a bill after it's a service.
It's like Amazon Prime.
Yeah, yeah.
But I think that lasted that kept the fantasy alive for at least another month, few months.
But then that's a crazy one.
Then I could answer.
Good question.
Good answer.
You know, he was thinkers in the Carlson House.
Yeah, pretty good.
Pretty good lie to keep that ruse, the fun ruse going.
And then the other one was I just because my mom would say your blood, there's blood relation and then you can be related through like marriage and like you could have a step brother and you don't necessarily you're not related by blood.
So when she when introduced that concept, I started thinking.
And then my memory is she said, well, when you have a baby, you have the man puts his penis in the woman's vagina.
And she didn't explain sperm.
She didn't explain anything past that.
She just said that happens.
And then a baby, that's how a baby's created.
And I went, oh, OK, got it.
Oh, went for it with the with the words didn't even dance around.
I believe she said the words.
But yeah, she didn't say.
And then like some New York voicing like New York speaking sperm shoot and then like an egg that's all dolled up.
Lots of competing Brooklynites.
Yeah.
I didn't do a race in uterus city.
Yeah, you have sperm.
They're very overeager and they're very aroused and they all work at the docks.
They're all longshoremen sperm.
They're yeah, longshoremen and stevedores.
And yeah, I think the wow, wow, that's crazy.
That's a real like end of innocence all at once.
Yes.
Yeah.
You were said, were you asking where did I?
Yeah, I think I was slowly piecing stuff together throughout middle school.
And then I had OK.
So so my school had seventh grade health class, eighth grade health class, nothing in ninth grade, tenth grade health class and seventh grade.
Looking back, it's a lot of the food pyramid and a lot of calculating cholesterol and blood pressure, which I don't know.
I would just get good at doing the worksheets.
I wouldn't retain the knowledge.
I still I know my blood pressure is usually fine if not low, but I anyway, unless it's laundry week.
Well, you know, I hate it.
I hate I hate cleaning.
I do.
So eighth grade health class, they're like, OK, sex, penis, vagina.
It was coed for one thing.
Like it was boys and girls in one class in fifth grade.
I believe the the girls were taken out of the class and had a presentation about like your body is changing.
And then they came back and we were all like reading magazines and playing board games.
It's like, what was that all about?
There was like, don't worry about it.
And then in tenth grade, that's the that was a class where the like kind of intense gym teacher is like, you have to use a condom, but didn't like like and with with
you have to use a condom and here are all the diseases you're going to be tested on that you could get.
But didn't say here are condoms or here you can buy them anywhere at any age with just money.
Like, I don't know.
Like they were weird about it.
They were they were prioritizing strange things.
So I need to know a condom dealer.
I kind of now finding out the logistical factors, the horse racing channel and cable would switch from horse racing to much more entertaining footage at about 11 o'clock midnight.
Most evenings.
So you are scrambled.
You're watching scrambled porno.
And that's how you figure out worse channel.
The whole channel once once trotting.
Once the trotting races ended, were they humans or horses?
Huh?
No, they were humans.
OK, huh?
So so you're saying that's you learn through scrambled porn how babies are made?
Well, no, I knew the logistics.
But like, what were you when you learn the stuff?
I think like 1314.
OK, wow.
The fun stuff.
You mean like when I would watch like a scrambled porn channel and it was like a woman in underwear, like posing on a couch for 45 minutes.
This is my recollection of what I was scrambled on our TV.
Now, it's well, look at this.
It depended on if you got the Playboy channel, which was softcore or the spice channel, which is disgusting.
It's just very it was like comically graphic.
Well, we're trotting after dark.
The night is to add that sometimes it would just be horse racing all night or it was Gilbert Godfrey's up all night when he would show a movie that was like beach party.
Aliens or something.
And it was like just an excuse for everyone to be like somewhat naked.
But as far as USA would let something out that air.
Right, right.
I so my my story with it was, I believe, fifth grade.
I like one of the strongest memories that I still retain was I was like beginning to put some pieces together and then some kid, some like jerky kid came up to me.
It was like, hey, check this out.
And he had a twig and he had a nut, not a nut like a peanut or the nut that Jason was referring to earlier, but like a, you know, like a nut and bolt nut.
And the nut has a hole in it.
And he took the twig and went back and forth.
Wow.
And then he ran away.
And I don't know why this was done.
But I like was just that was probably at lunch.
And then for all my classes, the rest of the day, I was like, wait, hmm.
There had to be you don't just do that.
That's got to mean something.
And by the end of the day, I sort of had maybe pieced it all together.
So when I got home, I said to my mom, hey, is sex when the guy puts his thing into the girl's thing?
Wow.
And then and she was not prepared for this.
She was frozen in her tracks.
And then it was like, give me give me a little time.
And then the day passed.
I did my homework.
Dinner passed.
And then Scott were ready.
And both of my parents were in what I were.
They were on what I call the serious couch.
It was the couch where we prayed, where we did the rosary.
Wow.
Where I where we went when I was in trouble.
And now for for this discussion.
And there was a book that they had had ready in case this were to come up.
And I don't remember much about that presentation.
It confirms what I thought about things, about things and things.
And mainly, I just remember the veneer of it being so creepy that I was like, well, I won't be going anywhere near this anytime soon.
Goodbye.
It was just that.
I don't know.
It all the serious couch.
It just like it mucked up my brain for a while.
But I was the twig guy really, really did it for me.
Thanks for spelling it out.
A very helpful diagram like in the CEPCOD movie.
Was your explanation clinical or was it more like what I got where it was like, these are the broad strokes of it?
But I think that I have blacked it out 100 percent.
There's no way to know.
You know, when you're getting the sex presentation from super Catholic parents, you you get red in the face as I'm getting again, even describing it.
And there's a lot of warnings about Opus Dei in there.
Strange.
I feel like my mom got away because I had asked about it early.
She got away with not having to be very detailed about it.
So I could know the gist, but I wasn't old enough to know, like, experience any feelings that were complicated.
So, like, I had the basic knowledge and then I could slowly understand it just on my own versus like asking when I was in seventh or eighth grade when, like, all of a sudden hormones are firing and I have to, like, navigate my own feelings in relation to it.
It's got to get more specific because you're like you're getting getting closer to something.
Yeah, a little a little kid, you would just have to explain the very basics of it.
But if somebody was like, yeah, fifth, sixth, seventh, eighth grade, I feel like then you start to have to go.
And now you might feel certain ways.
And here's what you do with that.
And here's that being said, I never got any of that from either parent.
Some of that would have been nice if I if I think about it.
But I think most of our parents probably don't want to do it because it's uncomfortable.
And I get that.
But yeah, well, I want to steal from how your mom did this whole like giving you clues.
And then letting you go off and solve the mystery because I'm going to have to do this within the decade.
I need a plan at some point when the when the boy comes to me asking questions.
You've got a movie here, though, on YouTube.
You got a movie.
Yeah.
That I think might be perfect.
Oh, boy.
It is an option.
I think after my wife's reaction to it, I think there's no way that the making of me will be involved in the talk.
All right.
Well, when when making of me on Disney plus the new six part season one premieres in a few and a few years, maybe that'll be like perfectly timed and ready.
A new generation of making of me.
Maybe making of me is tied into the Ronald Moore see somehow.
Martin Short's character is a member of C.
That's my dad.
Barnabas T.
Bullion.
Yeah, that's yes.
The prospector.
Yeah.
Well, Disney updated.
Give me something.
Give me a movie.
You know, I'll play for a lifetime pass if you give me something to replace the talk.
I remembered one of the ways I pieced it together.
I think.
Oh, yeah.
I was very when I had to do papers in school.
I was a real I was a real encyclopedia kid.
We didn't have them at home, but I knew like I had to do a paper.
This is easy.
I'll just start with the encyclopedia.
And if not enough there, then I'll go to books.
But then sometimes you grab the, you know, the S encyclopedia and you just see like what's under here under sex or what's under here under penis or vagina.
And, you know, and that shit like that happens.
You just become a podcaster, you know, eventually you were really getting away with something there.
I mean, we all look at Brown on cycle.
I think we all looked up words in a dictionary, you know, see what's in their dictionaries were good to again all of this very cold and methodical.
Yeah, yeah, sure.
This was just I just I felt like we couldn't resist the, you know, the listeners have come to know us pretty well.
And now they know how the good boys or maybe why the good boys didn't graduate into good men.
Why there's stuntedness.
Oh, and down to the river to pray.
Yikes.
OK, well, back, back to the film.
So now we got to get the we got to get the parents together.
And that's when we cut to where they finally meet and merge as a couple.
And it cuts to a fifties dance in full effect.
We're outside the gymnasium and there's people in big poofy dresses and there's a fifties car.
And we get into a scene where the fifties people are at the dance with different people and their future son needs to get them together.
And their future son is a floppy haired Canadian TV star who's worried that he won't exist unless he pushes his parents together at the fifties dance.
This is all I can't put my finger on it, but it's like this was trying to evoke something familiar.
I agree.
I couldn't I didn't know I have any.
Yeah, I didn't have any guess what I was imagining it was like seeming like.
But yeah, I hear you.
Yeah.
Very bad.
Hey, shout out 80s late 80s.
Martin Short had a heck of a head of hair on him.
That's true.
Yeah, yeah.
Pretty styling.
Absolutely.
Yeah, I did find a quote confirming that that Disney wanted this to think this thing to feel like a cross between Back to the Future and Nova.
Strange, strange things to cross.
Well, while you'd want to.
And in fact, the the fetus footage that comes not long after this spoiler is from Nova.
It's from the series Nova.
Disney did not commission specific other Disney branded fetus footage.
They just, yeah, reuse.
That is a little disappointing that they reuse the fetus footage.
Yeah, knowing it's a rerun.
Yeah, it is a bit of a let down.
So another thing with Disney trying to like skirt issues is that they're like, wait a minute.
So the whole thing this is about like these people are going to have a baby and we want to have this this dance scene.
But now that's high school and these we don't want to get into how are these people when they conceived and what have you.
So that is why this is not a high school dance.
This is a college dance.
You know, a college dance.
Those things that happen.
I rebuke my college, my sophomore college dance that I remember so well.
Yeah, I I'm sure they existed, but I didn't go to a college dance.
Nor do I recall that even being an option for me.
Perhaps in the fraternity sorority world, which if you can imagine that I, the good boy, was not mixed up in the fraternity world.
I was not involved in a fraternity either, believe it or not.
Shocker of shockers.
No, Ithaca had outlawed fraternities after someone died in the 80s and Cornell was rife with fraternities despite the fact that someone dies once a year.
And in fact, the one or two frat parties I went to over at Cornell, sure enough, did feel like hell on earth.
Yeah.
Not my scene.
So we got to get the we got to get the couple together.
We got to get mom and dad together.
They they're dancing with with partners who they don't really seem to care for.
But then they notice the other from across the room and then and then slowly push their dates to the center of the room and are dancing close enough to see the other in this very creepy tableau of the like unwanted other partner.
Just being ballast getting in the way of the eventual birth of Merton Shore.
It's a very strange sequence.
Yes.
So before your mommy and daddy make you there will be a thing called dance cuckolding that goes on where you you dance with the one you came with.
But you are furious that you have to do that.
But you try to do it while locking eyes with somebody else who is also there with someone else.
That is the decent thing to do.
It's what they do.
And you smash cut to it at a top hat wedding.
I like that choice.
The top hat wedding.
I think, you know, Martin's character from Father of the Bride.
I was thinking about Frank throughout because Frank's involved in the in the delivery later on and been Father of the Bride.
Right.
Yes.
And Frank to come in if we're going to have Martin's shirt playing multiple characters.
When is the first Father of the Bride?
Is it around this time?
Around here.
I mean, that makes sense that he's in the family like the Disney family when he's doing all these different Disney things.
Is he in Atlantis maybe or one of those one of those late era the ones that killed the animated movie?
Father of the Bride is 91.
So this is before it.
Oh, yeah.
So Frank was just, you know, a gleam in his eye at that point.
I have this idea.
I don't know where to put it.
Just waiting for the right film to come along.
I mean, he's Jack Frost in Santa Claus 3.
Mm hmm.
Of course.
You know, he is in a lot of different Disney stuff.
Yeah.
Do you think that when he's making the making of me, is he like probably Clifford is in the can?
Is he like super cocky about it?
Is he talking about it every time they cut on making of me?
Is he like, yeah, so just wait on that release date.
Orion should be getting back to us any day now.
And I think it's look, it's my peewee.
What can I say?
It's my peewee.
I can't wait to be able to see it.
It's a good question.
There was a quote, I feel like, and maybe I'm going to get it totally wrong after he was on Malaney, the one season Malaney sitcom.
And like Malaney was like, yeah, I talked to Martin Schur and he was like, look, kid, you do some of these.
Sometimes people like it.
Sometimes they don't.
I feel like maybe he's got his just like a working man philosophy when it comes to people liking things.
I don't know if he had it back then.
Maybe Clifford broke him.
I'm not sure.
Brought him down a peg.
Yeah.
I also don't.
I want to make it clear.
I love Martin Short.
I'm not.
I'm not goofing.
Oh, yeah.
But he's played some unnerving characters of all time.
And I just remembered another one.
The clip when he's in Mars Attacks and he's the horny presidential aide.
And he gets I completely forgot about this scene.
And I remember this.
I go, oh, I saw this with my mom and it made me uncomfortable in the theater in 1996.
Oh, I remember this.
The other was like a couple of weeks ago.
And I was like, oh, yeah, because he's hitting on the Lisa.
I think Lisa Marie's actress's name who plays the very tall like Martian.
Tim Burton's wife or girlfriend at the time at the time.
Maybe.
Yeah.
Possible.
And then, yeah, he takes her in like the secret.
This is obviously very Clinton.
Bill Clinton influenced like a secret sex room in the White House.
And then he gets murdered by this Martian.
Yeah, I remember I was having flashbacks to like, oh, I was sitting with my mother.
One of the first PG 13 movies I was allowed to see in theaters and 96.
I would have been 11.
So that was probably an argument, like at least a minor fight of like, just let me see.
Like, Dad's coming.
You know, it's fine.
Like it's a commercial.
It's silly.
Like, you know, it's kitschy.
It's self-aware.
We really funny.
And my mom was like, all right, now that you've seen Mars attacks, we want to talk to you about how it really goes down.
Now that you've seen Martin Short and the Martian, now we want to explain to you what he was feeling and what he was, you know, what you might eventually uncomfortable.
Did you did she have to have a talk with you about Jack Frost?
Like, so does just so when Jack Frost tries to if there's no Santa Claus, then when Jack Frost tries to freeze Santa Claus, he can't deliver toys anymore or or something or whatever.
That's what I assume the plot of Santa Claus three is.
Yeah, I think I think almost every Martin Short movie is a learning a chance for learning about sex in some way.
You can apply it.
Learning about something learning, you know, like how our audience had to learn that they are all Clifford's.
Right.
And they love it.
The audience loves it across the board.
They we've gotten a lot of great feedback.
They are.
I wouldn't be.
We're the biggest Cliffords.
Let's let's be true.
We're the biggest.
Well, that was the swing that Mike took.
You said we're Cliffords.
And then suddenly you made the leap to bring in thousands of other people in on.
I saw the opportunity because for so long people haven't I don't think we've not decided on like a catchy little name.
And I saw a really good marketing opportunity, I think, because I'm just that's how my brain works.
I'm honestly think of a marketing opportunities.
So it's got people talking.
The socials are a buzz.
They love it.
Yeah, they love it.
I assume all good.
It's not 50 50 for sure.
It's certainly not 50 50 love and hate.
Certainly not.
OK, so let's see.
So all right.
So we get the we get the couple together.
They get they get married.
They have the top hat wedding.
Then we got a little montage of what they're doing instead of having the baby rather water ski than have me.
Yeah, they say.
And, you know, so they have to go so the roads.
This is a montage that for Aaron and I would be approximately 14 years long.
Sorry.
My apologies to the child.
You got to do what you got to do.
Go to theme parks a lot and then have a baby.
So then they get together.
Now we're in the bedroom, but we don't get to see any of that.
We tilt up to the magical Amblin indoor sky where OK, so Mernchardt is being conceived.
But now adult Martin Short is up on top of a roof.
He's giving them their privacy.
So instead, he's just hovering above them.
But he can hear.
Yeah, unless they are very unless they're very quiet, unless they're doing it very gingerly.
And maybe that is maybe that's the case.
They just don't make any noise during it.
But still, you're so close.
If there was a window even cracked open, he's he's listening to some unpleasant noises at the very least.
Well, it's a character played by Martin Short.
So you know that the sex is like pretty, you know, loud and insane.
I would have to think.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, boy.
Oh, there's some mugging happening during the sex.
Yeah, for sure.
It's kind of high kicks and like crossing the line very quickly.
A live performer for God's sake.
I just watched a clip of him do a Frank Sinatra song with a Paul Schaefer orchestra from a couple of years ago.
You know, this is like kind of an old time showbiz guy, too.
So, yeah.
So imagine him in the bedroom.
He's got panache.
Yeah, of course.
This is interesting.
It's really like he's he's seeing it all at once.
You know, he exists while he's being conceived.
It's like what's Jason, our favorite writer, one of our favorite writers, Grant Morrison.
I talk about a lot.
He talks about the hyper entity, which is if you could stand out of space and time and look at it all at once, you could see everything where everything came from.
It was just this one long like this giant snake monster, this big rat king.
Oh, yeah.
Like a big, long comic strip.
Yeah.
And this is sort of what Martin Short is doing right now.
He's he's existing all at once.
He's seeing the past, present and future.
That's pretty trippy.
I mean, why are we focused on actually birth is kind of boring and it happens all the time.
I want to know how he got to this juncture where he has godlike powers.
Very good time magically.
Yeah.
Well, look, Lauren pulls some strings and magic happens, you know,
Lauren, some ritual, some fraternity ritual.
Lauren was there and he he like made a deal with some sort of a demon.
So Martin Short could travel through time and see everything.
If you're in the SNL elite.
Yeah.
Lauren gives let you in on the secret of how you live for 5000 years, but only the you got to like more than four seasons.
You got to have a couple of hit characters.
Five Timers Club.
They make it in there for sure.
They get to be immortal.
Yeah.
You get to glimpse upon an elder god, an ancient one.
Cursed.
But you can't look too long or you will be driven insane.
Right.
Danny.
Danny's in the group.
Billy.
I guess as a Roth Cthulhu.
They have to fake kill some of them sometimes like Buck Henry.
But that was a false death.
He that's just to throw people off the trail.
But yeah, he's off.
He's in a he's in a castle somewhere.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
You got that power.
Yeah.
So we'll be we'll be in it.
He's still going to look like he still look very youthful even at 500.
Yeah.
He then says I'm going to recite some dialogue here again.
Remember the sperm we said my dad had?
I don't know.
No, I don't.
So it's something I can't imagine a lot of people say in casual conversation.
Then let's read this all.
But the truth is when two people are in love, one of the loveliest things they can do is be as close together as possible.
They might kiss.
They might hug.
Another way that mature adults express their love for each other is to get so close that the man's sperm actually enters the woman's body.
Yes, I also took note of this phrasing because, again, very careful to say so much and not anything at all at the same time.
It's yeah, it's like really trying to make sure that like if you're little, it goes right over your head.
And it's it's that thing.
If it's me, third grade, that's going over my head.
But you guys, when you learned you might have maybe figured that out a little more.
You could piece it together.
You had the memory of like, I know where it comes from, so I know where it has to go.
So that's not to jump ahead.
But if you haven't seen this film, they do.
There is not then a scene around the corner where they show a penis thrusting into a vagina.
It doesn't become scrambled trot channel after dark.
Not two horses going at it.
No, there's no horse racing into like a sequence of scrambled of like a guy like high fiving like, yes, dude, no, guess what?
It's not the Simpsons fuzzy bunny joke.
Oh, yes.
Yeah, yeah.
One of the best children.
She's faking it.
So they don't really.
Yeah, they don't get into then then what happens.
But I think something like I think there is something about the ambleniness and the creepiness of all that.
Like it was around this point I turned to Erin while watching with her and she was a gas.
She was pale white.
Someone who is not uncomfortable.
I look like I've had sex with her as we have baby again.
There's not a person who is too.
I've found to be uncomfortable with these areas.
I don't think I've ever seen her so offended by something as this.
She was just so creeped out by the general veneer of this film by the by the dancing, the loveliest things they can do.
I think the lack of suggestive language around this point, she called it filth.
She said this is filth.
This should have never been anywhere in an amusement park.
I don't remember the bit, but there's a pat and I was a bit about how like cleaning up filth makes it way creepier.
And I don't remember the details of it, but he likes it.
He takes like dirty material and then he like puts in like network censored words for things.
Oh, yeah.
It's so much stranger and more bizarre and creepy.
Yes.
Yeah.
Similar, I feel like to this where it lets me know that if I had said, you know, a little while ago, you know, Aaron, when two people are in love, one of the loveliest things they can do is be as close together as possible.
If I had said that verbatim as a pickup line, that is what happened.
There'd be no baby.
Do you want to do?
Do you want to do a lovely thing?
The making of a divorce.
Oh, man, baby.
I want to get as close to you as possible.
We might kiss.
We might hug.
I second hug second in the list.
I know we might even hug.
I learned everything I know about sex from this one video Epcot Center.
I got to get close to you.
Very close.
Super close.
I saw that when I was a kid, but now I'm a mature adult and I want to express lovely love.
You know, I was saying my dad had all that sperm.
That's sperm.
My dad had.
I got it.
He still has some, but he doesn't need it as much as when he needed it to make me.
And now I've got the sperm and it's lovely.
I just got the captain now.
I just got to get very close to you.
How close?
Well, that's close as we can do.
And I still because all my info is from this.
I still don't know.
All right, let's do it.
Let's get close.
Here we are.
We've kissed.
We've hugged.
I assume that some sperm is now in you and I'll see you at the delivery room.
Wraps that thing up.
The delivery of you remember the sperm?
My dad had it.
It said so offhandedly.
It sounds like I think like if you're like padding your pot, like do you have a lighter?
Do you have a light or like, hey, do you have a quarter for the meter?
I thought it's not one of the ones that takes credit cards.
Yeah, it's very casual.
It's a very casual.
Yeah.
It's odd.
I don't.
I don't even want to throw it out to somebody on the street.
If you're, you know, like socializing is going to be weird once we're out of quarantine and we're going to need icebreakers.
We can't just talk about did we get Pfizer or Moderna over and over again?
We need new stuff to talk about.
So, hey, remember before all that were two years ago, I was talking about that sperm.
My dad had.
A good book story quarantine.
Do you ever remember that sperm?
My dad had.
That's a week.
We could all in a way like I don't know, like there could be a photos of us that say underneath the sperm.
My dad had like we we are the products of the sperm.
I want an egg as to get.
So you have to include that, you know, we all equal the sperm.
Our dad had and the egg.
Our mom had.
It's really lovely when you think about it.
Oh, yeah.
When you say it like that, it's lovely.
I think this is one of the loveliest episodes.
It's one of the loveliest.
It's one of the nice music under this too.
Where it just be so nice.
Such a nice thing to think of.
Well, it's a shame.
It's just so crass.
And like again, like learning the true name of God, like you start to unravel a little hearing it because it is the sort of phrase that it's like that is such an odd phrasing.
We'd love to put it on a T public shirt.
You know, we haven't had a new shirt in a while.
That'd be good.
But just far.
No, no.
You know, I'm going to say no.
I'm going to veto that on air.
It's a retro.
I've got mania out there.
People love every little bit.
They want a shirt with smart one.
They want a shirt with figment.
I'm sure that says remember the sperm my dad had a little cartoon Martin Short on a roof.
If they could, you know, cut at the gardens, the galaxy cosmic rewind is going to have nods to old Epcot.
Then maybe there's a place for it.
There is.
I will say this now that I'm thinking about it.
There is a sperm joke in the first Guardians of the Galaxy movie.
Well, a black light joke.
I mean, it's a black light joke.
I've seen it about 50 movies, but there is there.
So it is appropriate for the level.
So maybe we could get a little nod to making a me, you know, as it maybe it launches.
Maybe it's a little bit of a launch.
I think it launches backwards.
In fact, that's what I heard is a rumor.
Time to launch you like the sperm my dad had.
I was telling you about that sperm my dad had.
Here's a cosmic rewind for you.
The sperm my dad had.
Look, kid, tantric stuff takes a lot of practice and you can do it, but it's not a joke.
Oh, man, you got get it in there.
People are dying.
There's oh, people are clamoring for the sperm.
The sperm Martin for its dad had.
That's right.
Imagine it hasn't opened yet.
Let's get it in.
So then I was going to say we moved into like into the cartoon.
But first, there's a lie.
And the lie is all of us came to be because their parents made love, allowing the sperm and the egg to meet.
Lie.
That's not true.
There's fertilization.
There's lots of there's people who then the parent is out of the picture.
There's so is it.
There's so much going on.
What do you mean all of us came to be?
That one.
You can't let that slide.
So with the lie is a transition, we go into the wacky sperm cartoon when it began.
Erin had the question, is this John Kay?
And thank God it's not John Kay, because, boy, we delve into even a deeper, darker territory.
The cartoon I looked up, it was it was done by the animation director was Bill Croyer, who's the director of Fern Gully,
The Last Rainforest, and also the animated intro sequences of both Christmas Vacation and True Beverly Hills.
Oh, wow.
Now, like you said, you called the sperm cute.
I did.
I do think the sperm sequence is cool.
It totally has that vibe.
Like the thing that doesn't happen anymore when the live action movie had the animated intro, I tended to like those a lot.
And I there's like a real spirited vibe to those.
And I feel that in in this a little bit.
Is this the best part of the whole thing?
Hmm.
I'd say so, because we're not having to watch the parents bring their bodies close.
Yeah.
There's no no magical, lovely skies.
It's nice to see a cartoon after all this.
I think maybe it is.
Yeah.
Maybe that's the best part.
But pretty insane that this is a Disney attraction that has a sign that says uterus city limits.
How in the world would they ever allow this now?
I bet this really is so funny.
Because I even at the time, it would seem like it seemed we really seem insane to put this in that somebody go, what is Jason said?
Like, what are we doing?
Why are we?
Yeah.
Why?
Why would you?
Why would you do this?
But I guess I guess they really wanted to stick with the mission of like educating the youth.
Yeah.
And what it is is that a ball your sperm gear up for a race to be the to be the uterus city champions.
You get they also they all get going.
And the winner gets to make a baby.
What happens to the losers?
And then like a like a kaput.
Yeah.
Gesture.
So now everybody knows.
Well, this is it is like, you know, you do kind of like the sperm.
They're they're fun.
They're hopping around.
Mike even called them cute.
So to think that these are probably the quickest dead Disney characters in history.
the precursor to minions.
He's making me sperm, I think.
Yeah.
Now, Universal will not be doing a making of minions movie.
But thanks to the wonders of the Internet, you can find all about.
I would like to know.
I think the minions as your guides through the reproductive reproductive process would be a great way to learn.
It'd be very I just figured I'd teach the teach the kid.
Great.
But OK, so the race is on and then it pans over to the to to Miss Egg.
Hello, Miss Egg.
She is sexy.
She's sassy.
She's got a ponytail.
She looks at her watch like what's the trouble, boys?
Why aren't you here yet?
Very again, really odd.
This Lady Egg character.
And then when they all get close, when they finally like it, like a lot of them are dropping off along the way,
they're they're expending their energy too early.
And this is a marathon.
You have to like be in it for the long haul.
So like we're losing them.
And then you got to they got to get up over a hill.
And she finally sees some sperm cresting the hill.
So she puts on an apron with a target on it.
What did you miss that part?
I am in the moment.
I'm forgetting it.
Why does this all this whole sequence is like, OK, when the sperm meet the egg, it's like a USO skit that they would see on like on the deck of an aircraft carrier.
That's the sketch that Al Franken did when he was in the US.
Oh, geez, geez.
Oh, man.
All right.
Sorry.
Maybe he wrote this.
We don't really know who wrote it.
We don't know him.
The well, that we die actually do know who wrote it, but we'll talk about that later.
Oh, great.
OK.
Oh, I forgot that the first step of the race is having to pick a tube and their labels left fallopian tube, right fallopian tube.
A lot of them a lot of them lose just by plowing right into the middle, not making a decision quickly enough.
But she's put on her target.
She is ready to get plowed into by a sperm.
It's really crazy.
It would be like showing a porno in there.
You'd be like, this is fucked up.
But OK, I OK.
Well, it's a clinical understanding of how this happened.
Yes.
As long as there's not too much goofy setup, as long as it's straight out, just straight.
You just want to read like there's something to you about the unadorned nature of a pornography film that would be more acceptable to you.
Well, it depends.
It would have to be like a soft lens and maybe it's one of the ones where people are married and there's no shenanigans.
You know what I'm saying?
You hate those porno shenanigans.
Yeah, there's just a lot of shenanigans.
You try to find one where they're playing a married couple.
The nice thing.
I want all the porns that I watch.
There is a screenshot of the marriage license at the beginning so that I know.
Me too.
The sperm knows that he's the way like he looks back.
There's no competition.
He kind of hops over.
He doesn't even bother with the cutting the ribbon, the ribbon that's there before target apron egg girl.
He just hops over it and he knows this is his time.
He's going to do it.
He sprays his breath with little breath spray and he just collides in and they both explode into smoke.
And that is how that's how a me is made involves breath spray, a target apron.
Here's a list.
Here's a list of supplies.
If you want to make a me, I'm trying to think.
I mean, I, you know, plus it up again.
We shouldn't be plus thing.
This probably is not going to come back.
We should probably burn it down.
But if I have to plus it up, maybe it's like a sugar rush from Wreck-It Ralph and all the sperm are driving little cars maybe toward the egg.
And the egg is the victory like the victory line or whatever you call a finish line.
Yeah, I like I like that.
And look, all the there's all these Pixar movies, all the P doctors are all about like different metaphysical.
Here's the representations of things in your body.
Why not do let's bring the let's bring the sperm.
The full sperm's back.
Let's do the full sperm's movie.
I think that's right.
I think that then they own it.
You know, it's not a stretch.
They love I.
P.
They love reusing I.
these days.
So I think I would like a movie that's all about like because a lot of the Pixar characters are dealing with like, you know, but I want to be more than I know I have this purpose that I'm stuck to.
But I want to transcend that and see what else is out there.
So you like really get to know the plight of sperm and you follow him to the day and then there's the race and there's five million other ones and he dies.
Yeah, and that's the end of the movie.
Yeah, it goes 60 miles an hour and head first into a goddamn diaphragm or something.
Just like a leader of the pack.
Oh, where oh where can my baby be?
The Lord took away from me.
Oh, no.
Head first into a condom.
Tied on impact.
So that's that.
And then we get our our majestic fetus footage courtesy of Nova.
The the you see them go to a movie theater where everyone is laughing nonstop, not waiting for jokes to laugh at, but just laughing and laughing straight through while everyone in the theater is smoking a cigar.
This is a very bizarre theater.
Yes, they're extremely distressing in Koba times to watch this like so much smoke flying around the room.
The baby's coughing Martin Shurtz.
Like, get me out of there, Mom.
And they do the day the dad wants to stay.
He wants to keep watching this nonstop polarity and choking on 100 other people's smoke.
But he agrees to leave for the sake of the baby.
I don't know what I feel like when Martin Shurtz would have been gestating, doctors still would have been recommending like four out of five doctors would have still been recommending Chesterfield's for your T zone.
Like cigarettes is good.
I don't know that that feels like a very 1988 89 thing of like secondhand smoke.
Not great.
You know, that's slightly new.
It's revisionist.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, they're like, you know, your baby's hair is going to be longer and thicker.
The more smoke it gets straight into the womb.
So they so they leave.
And then pretty soon, I think we're at we're at delivery.
The baby is delivered.
I mean, this is like I could certainly could not have handled this at nine years old.
I'm seeing the like because it's a pretty realistic depiction of the baby coming.
This is not the sitcom version where I have like perfect year and a half year old is handed to the mother.
You know, it's a it's a it's a graphic sticky display.
It's like a gross baby.
Right.
Am I like that's like an extra.
It does seem like like a baby xenomorph or something.
Just the way, especially because of the like bootleg nation, the bootleg nature of the video as well.
I can't quite see what it looks like.
So it does look like it's like a baby alien or something.
Maybe on a fully restored print.
Maybe it doesn't look that crazy, but it's like this baby is pale blue.
It was very.
Yeah, yeah.
It's like a little avatar baby or something.
A little not be God.
Yeesh.
And you know, this also like Aaron is watching this aghast.
She's just like, Jesus, they showed this and I'm like, you know, we did this.
This was we had to do this.
And we both agreed watching this in this movie was more unpleasant than doing it in real life.
The baby looked grosser.
There's also something about when it's yours.
You're like, you know, they warn you that the baby is going to be gross when they come out.
Not in our case, because our baby is so great.
It was adorable to us.
You see photos later like Jesus.
Oh, my God.
Well, imagining the walkie talkie chatter on like the on the set of just like, Hi, Glen wants more goo for the baby.
OK, flying in the goo, flying in the placenta goo.
Flying in.
How do they do it?
Sound like is this is this a baby that is has things has goo applied?
How do they do newborns?
Is it a good up for month old or is it a an animatronic or just like a still baby model?
They shake a lot to convince you that it's alive.
This one looked pretty real and I think has a credit on IMDb.
Oh, yes.
Maybe.
But the actress, though, like when then it then she's a little bit grown and visits Martin Short in the hospital, bringing the loop to a close.
Or did that baby have like a two month period where it worked a lot like it had like 30 credits for two months?
Well, actually, can I ask, are we getting to the end with the the is the next thing the girl in the hospital?
I think so.
Yeah.
Can you explain to me?
This is where I lost the thread.
Like I lost the timeline.
Is this the mother child mother traveling forward in time to see her future child Martin Short as a baby?
Is that what's happening?
Yeah.
So the movie began with Martin Short seeing his father as a baby, which is the beginning of his story.
So now we've looped around and it's the beginning of the girl's story.
She says, here's my dad as a baby.
It's it's all set one generation back.
Well, but she's starting a new making of me that we don't get to see all of.
Thank God.
So that's Martin Short's movie daughter seeing.
But so we haven't met that daughter before.
Oh, wait, that's right.
Yeah.
See, this is where it starts to get confusing.
And it's not Martin Short's actual daughter.
I looked that up.
No, no, it's yeah.
No, we're just jumping ahead to.
But it is the same order of events, right?
It's just it's a kid now instead of a grown Martin Short.
Right.
Yeah.
But she's seeing her own father as a baby.
If we're really following the pattern, though, she should be an adult woman saying.
Correct.
That.
Yeah.
OK, that's what I think.
That's the confusion, right?
If it was a little confusing to go from a baby to a kid.
And then that's not the because the baby is Martin Short and the kid.
And it would have been so much more clear if Martin Short had just played the seven year old girl, too.
Obviously.
Oh, well, that yes, that is what we all want.
Child Martin Short should be a child doll.
A fetus.
It should have been.
Why did they do?
Why did they use this Nova footage?
Why wasn't it Martin Short?
Oh, like wrinkled up.
We know he's a contortionist.
He would have eaten up playing a fetus.
Yeah, it would have been a lot like Ace Ventura, too, with the rhino or something like he's just like gooey and like trying to climb out of something.
Yeah, Martin Short is the baby covered in goo like the rhino.
Yeah.
Every and he should have been the mom, too.
He should have been clearly should have been everybody.
He should have definitely done an Eddie Murphy, a nutty professor in this.
Yeah.
And there's still time you could still.
He's not doing play.
JPEC.
We're redoing Epcot Center now.
We're redoing Epcot.
And, you know, there's an opportunity here somewhere to get this back into the park.
You know, I just heard that Club Cool is returning.
It was taken out.
It was taken away, but they're going to put it somewhere else now.
I don't remember.
I don't quite remember what Club Cool was.
I don't know.
I guess this is not of important.
It absolutely is an important.
It is important.
Oh, man.
This is not fake.
I swear to you, this is not fake.
Then what's Club Cool?
Convince me.
Club Cool, it's one of the few free things at Disney World.
You could sample sodas from all around the world.
I know it's that.
I know about that.
With Beverly, that horrible drink, Beverly.
Ligenberry soda, right?
Yeah.
Lincolnberry.
Ligenberry.
Thank you for the right pronunciation.
I knew there was a thing where you could sample foreign sodas.
I didn't know it was called Club Cool.
And I have just condemned myself to an endless episode of Club Cool.
I know how this podcast works.
People are going to be fucking psyched for Club Cool episode.
Trust me.
I like people being happy.
This is not like us doing a Patreon about the Aerosmith Pink video or something.
This is what people are excited about, I think, Club Cool.
Fine.
Club Cool is coming.
Okay.
But so, yeah, we're at the end of the film.
We've closed the loop.
Jason, you were saying that the makers of this film.
Yeah.
Okay.
So writing and directing credit goes to a guy named Glenn Gordon Carone.
He was a producer for Moonlighting and Medium.
Created these series.
That's crazy.
I didn't know he was the same creator of both of those shows.
Bull.
He's a producer on Bull.
Currently on the air.
He directed numerous episodes of Bull.
He directed the pilot for Medium.
And I may have said this before.
If you direct the pilot of a TV show, you get money every time they keep making the TV show.
Right.
One of those coveted jobs in Hollywood.
And he has a written by credit for an episode of Taxi.
Geez.
Nice.
Career.
Yeah.
Wow.
Cool career.
And don't forget, he rakes it in from having directed the film Wilder Napalm.
You know, Wilder Napalm with Dennis Quaid, Deborah Winger and written by Vince Gilligan.
You know, Breaking Bad Mania caused such a reverse swell backwards into Wilder Napalm.
Of course.
Yeah.
We're still in the crater of it.
He also, I think, though, maybe sucks because he, this director, because he fired Eliza Dushku in a sexual harassment kerfuffle with the star of Bull, Michael Weatherly.
Oh, no.
Do you remember anything from this story?
Yeah.
I didn't know that was that show.
I think that's this.
Yeah, it's Bull and it's this guy maybe.
And I like he was on tape saying bad stuff about her.
This guy didn't harass, but he took the harassers side.
And I believe Eliza Dushku sued and got a lot of money.
I think I might be getting some facts wrong about that.
So, look, I don't know.
These are some good shows and everything.
That's going to taint my feeling about this movie forever.
This magical film that perfectly summarizes the loveliness of body closeness.
Yeah.
I'm going to remove my half awake description of quite a career and replace it.
That's still true.
We just did.
That's true.
Unfortunate.
An unfortunate arc.
I don't like I feel like maybe you guys don't share my I don't want to sound like I'm like this is like some sort of moral panic thing for me.
I just know, boy, watching my wife get a gasp at this film, I don't think I've ever heard her call anything filth the whole time I've been with her.
She was very, very upset about this.
I don't know.
There's a but maybe that's not where you guys are landing on the.
I mean, it's just odd.
It's odd that there was an attraction where, like, if you were dealing with sterility or endometriosis or any number of other issues, you're like, oh, great.
I went to Disney World.
I saw this little movie and yeah, it made it was I got depressed immediately.
Yeah, I'm not like horrified by it being there.
It is just confusing, obviously, like watching it in, you know, whatever year this is, 2021.
It's like, oh, I think we're like we're ready to have a more nuanced conversation or a more elaborate conversation about all these topics.
But it's just like, how are you going to do that at a theme park?
And yeah, that's what I understand.
Just don't get anywhere near it.
You don't really have the time for it there because there are a lot of things.
There are a lot of things I would tell a hypothetical son or daughter about all this stuff.
And it's like you can't cram it into a nice a nice people eater attraction, you know, for 15 minutes.
You with your considerations to hitting all the quadrants that a theme park attraction has to hit like it's too.
It's too ambitious is my feeling, especially in this day and age.
Yes, I like it for the ambition in a way.
I like that they, you know, you talk about Epcot being weird.
This is really weird.
It's weird that they did so weird.
Yes.
Yeah.
Is it good?
I don't know.
I also don't feel like the audience was thrilled in the copy that I watched.
Martin Shirt was explaining things at the chalkboard and then just midway through a sentence.
He just heard this really like interrupts the whole thing.
So they were they were enthralled.
I feel like if dads went on University of Energy and then straight over to this thing, it was double nap time.
It was.
Yeah, that was it.
Just sleep right through it.
Can I I have something I found the touring plans, the old touring plans page.
Oh, yes.
Great.
With this.
And they show both sides of the argument, you know, because they are the touring plans, you know, reviews and rundowns of rides, you know.
They they have a father of two from Connecticut weighed in with this opinion.
The making of me is very well done, but I find it an odd juxtaposition.
How many people decide a vacation at Disney World is the time to explain this stuff?
Show this in health class.
Yeah.
Now, that said, they add a gentleman from Cheshire, England, who believes correctly in our view that Americans are sexually repressed rights by the standards of sex education programs shown to English children of ages eight to nine.
The making of me seemed almost Mary Poppins ish in tone.
Certainly other Brits found your warnings over content quite puzzling.
I got a you know, I I think I lean closer to that second opinion of like, yeah, this is this is probably just another way Americans are kind of insane, you know, compared to much of the rest of the world.
I think my my take is that he's I think he's right.
But like like you should if you're going to let a movie do the work and explain some of this stuff to a kid, the movie should go further.
The movie should like, you know, show a little more of what it is and what like it should tackle stuff a little more.
But that movie should not be shown in Epcot Center.
Well, correct.
So if I'm feeling like harumphy about it, it's not the like the film is very tame.
Absolutely.
But for the setting, it's just so bizarre.
And it gets you into this area of lovely bodies.
And when lovely bodies want to be be lovely on each other, they shoot their lovely sperm.
I think that's where it's just to just either go one way or go the other way and and pick choose a choose a tube.
It should be like a 10 hour seminar that you had to go to like the hotel, like a hotel ballroom somewhere.
Like if you really want to do this with your kid, let's let's go do it.
OK, it's 10 hours.
There's many different movies.
It start with this like cleaned up version.
Then there's like hours on consent.
There's hours on the fact that you can have sex and it's not for procreation.
There's a lot in there.
There's a bit like let's do it as opposed to this.
Yes, Mary Poppins, like Puritan American version of like and then a little bit of whimsy will create your future child.
Like we haven't gotten it.
He calls himself a sprite.
Yes, yes.
The man who plays Clifford when he is getting coughed on by a hundred people in a movie theater, he says,
but cigars and drugs and alcohol are not good for this little sprite.
Weird, weird.
This is why I understand audience.
Why you don't want to be called Clifford's.
It's really a good man who calls himself a sprite.
When you think about how backwards, you know, things have been when it comes to like teaching people about sex education.
This is a beautiful illustration of of yes, what the American psyche was at the time and still to some degree is
when it comes to like how comfortable you are explaining this to children.
All right.
Right.
It's a day.
Look, this video damaged a lot of minds.
It really.
Oh, yeah.
A lot of kids up.
I'm sure of it.
I maybe I saw it and I just blacked it out like you're talking about your sex talk.
It's possible.
I should have.
You know, I really should have asked my mom is any memory of this because it was there long enough
that I would think that there was a good chance we did see it, but I have no memory of it.
Is there any chance I saw it in like 2003?
Did I just say like, it's a weird thing.
I'm bored.
I'll do it.
I because it did feel a little familiar.
But it's a good idea.
It's familiar in that Epcot center of its time way to where you go, did I see this or did I see the Canada Pavilion?
And I'm just remembering Martin Short from that.
Yeah.
But I mean, there were no sperm in the Canada movie.
So.
Yeah, well, bizarre, interesting to revisit.
I guess you survived podcast the ride.
And what can I say?
It's, you know, keep it lovely out there.
Obviously, if you have a talk to give to somebody, you know, to a child, you know, be aware that that the discussion of man of dad's sperm could enter into it and make it easier.
And just remember, you know, during this last year, these trying times, you know, people's memories might not be as as good as they they once were.
So, you know, be patient with the people around you if they don't remember that, you know, that friggin sperm.
You remember I mentioned that sperm?
You know, you got to smoke.
Can I buy my smoke?
If you have to remind people about your dad's sperm, that's OK.
That's what Jason's saying.
It's OK.
Yeah.
Go at your own pace.
You know, it takes a little while.
Just get nice and lovely and say, yes, I remember the sperm you said your dad had.
Yes.
But but stop before you start screaming.
I remember I remember everything.
I can see everything all at once.
Yikes.
Yikes is correct.
Yeah, that's a yikes of an episode.
But thanks for thanks for listening to it for potentially less yikesy episodes.
We got three a month here.
So keep it.
So long.
So long to all the wonderful me's out there.
Goodbye, me's.
I'm glad you got made.