Forever.
Dog.
Warning.
The following podcast contains a savory pastry with cream chicken, feather-based lockpicking,
and the revelation of life's greatest treasure.
It's Sinbad's Storybook Voyage with returning guest Lindsay Katai.
There is no map, there's no chart.
It's Podcast the Ride.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, the theme park podcast who seeks great adventure by following
the compass of their hearts.
Wait a minute, I made a mistake here.
The podcast who seeks boring information about Six Flags Great Adventure.
Sorry about that.
My name is Mike Carlson, joining me as always, Jason Sheridan.
Now there are a lot of interesting stuff about Six Flags though, because first off that's
one of the Six Flags with Big Body Water next to it.
Of course.
It's got a drive-through safari.
Scott Gairdner, do you also have some information about Great Adventure?
Oh yeah.
There's people out there who've been to Great Adventure and also had Casamigos tequila.
They've also drank the tequila that is extremely common everywhere.
What?
And so that's pretty interesting that you think the same people have been to the theme
park and also had this very common tequila.
Oh my gosh.
I just realized somebody had sent me Casamigos is expanding their brand into hot sauces and
different flavors, which is very exciting to me.
But we can't take up the episode talking about that.
Is that true?
That's insane if that's true.
I have a graphic of it.
I'm not exactly sure what the products are.
I was just given this graphic by a friend of the podcast, Dan Grissom.
But again, I can't get derailed looking at this right now because we have so much exciting,
positive, uplifting things to talk about today.
Follow the compass.
Yeah.
Exactly.
Follow it to positivity.
But let's welcome the guest who's very psyched about this topic.
You know her from Infinity Train, the podcast Teen Creeps.
She's a podcast, the right favorite, and she's the Sarah Davis to my Uncle Martin Daniels.
This is Lindsay Katai, ladies and gentlemen.
Hello.
I don't know what that means.
Well, it is.
I'm not sure.
It took me a sec.
Oh, I know.
Jason.
Well, Jason, you please explain the reference.
Well, that that's the central love story at the heart of the classic film Clifford.
I see.
You're like fighting for the whole movie.
I mean, it works out and they get married.
It's a bad like, I don't think this is something you want to be.
Well, sometimes when you follow the compass of your heart, there's some swells, you know,
there's pirates.
Yeah, things, you know, love is love can be a little bit rocky sometimes, but they end
up in a good place.
That's why I said it.
Yeah.
You know, I wasn't trying to be negative.
I just need a nightmarish nephew to teach you Jason to make you a man.
And then the fighting will stop at some point.
Yeah, Jason.
That dinosaur ride incident.
That's Jason.
Yes, yes.
For some reason, I refuse to recognize the antics of this small man child and just be
a big pain in the ass.
That's my whole vibe.
Yes, exactly.
Why doesn't she?
Why is she so blind to his high jinkery?
It's kind of inexplicable.
Yeah, yeah.
Because he's off.
Like, even when he's being nice, he's still like a weird little man in a suit who talks
to a dinosaur and uses 1910 phrases.
Like, yeah, there's no reason she should just go.
She's maybe the true villain of the piece.
That's a good take.
Yeah, I hear you.
I'd have to rewatch the whole thing to see how that lines up.
I've been watching Clifford from the little bits I've watched and that I have been piecing
out just little bits of Clifford.
Clifford has really come to dominate the podcast in 2021, which is a good development for some.
And some listeners, this might be the last straw.
Yeah, some people are upset about all the Clifford talk.
And I just made it worse.
I just threw more wood on the fire.
But we can get off that.
We can start talking about the actual topic that the episode you see in the title right
now.
We should.
Well, let me let me acknowledge one thing, which is that Lindsay's not been on in a long
time and this is the like, I don't know, how has it been for a year and change not having
this podcast interrupt your breakfasts?
Surreal.
Too calm, maybe.
the days unless I have a 25 part podcast on the history of the wood used at Disney California
Adventure Pier and ranking each plank.
Like how how do you pass a year?
Yes.
And yeah, we got to do just wood because when you get into nails and bolts, that's a whole
other.
That's not really what you hear.
Apples and oranges.
You can't write them together.
Yeah.
And also each bolt affects the plank.
So so they have you have to cover them separately and then do an episode about them working
in conjunction.
But yes, but you guys did get featured in Vulture for that 25 part series.
So congratulations.
Thank you.
I think well, I mean, it being that it is so essential.
Yes, of course, we we had to get the right up, obviously.
So essential that you guys were considered essential workers and you all got vaccinated
before in August.
Anyone else? Yeah.
In August, we've been like pretending like then we get to have an episode where we go,
hey, we're vaccinated.
We're back in the parks, but that ruins the I'm sorry.
I pulled back the curtain on you guys being basically health care workers.
Many months ago, we're going to have to cut this whole part out.
It's all unusual.
I'm sorry.
That's OK.
Complicate your editing duties, Michael.
It's fine.
So yeah, I go being the Sarah.
What's her face?
Just needlessly complicating things.
Sarah Davis, of course.
I'm surprised you didn't remember that because I've been calling you that for weeks since
we watched Clifford.
I just tune you out.
I just do.
OK, every time I just go, there's probably some fucking Ninja Turtles thing or something.
And then I just stop.
Yeah.
Yeah, love means love means occasionally saying, yep, got it.
So that one already, I think.
Jason just wrote a Ziggy.
Yeah.
I wait, I wrote a Ziggy, not a love is.
Well, they could maybe both be.
Could it be a Dilbert?
I don't know if it can be a Dilbert.
Dilbert doesn't have a lot of love in his life.
Yeah, you're like circa ninety five.
But modern Dilberts are a lot edgier.
It's such a lack.
Oh, a lack of experience that it's all of the right.
Yeah, I was just going to say, Jason, maybe it's a lock horns.
I think yeah, lock horns might be good.
I think you just, you know, rework it a slightly and then you can send it to all of them.
You know, yeah, just send it.
We'll we'll submit it just to King Features Syndicate blanket and they can use it in whichever
one they want.
So that'll be good.
You put us where you want us.
Yeah.
Can I say to can I say two quick things before we get into the meat of the episode?
Because something occurred to me and I think this is, you know, what we're going to be
talking about is one of the most like positive, optimistic, uplifting experiences in all of
Parkton, which I'm so happy about.
And there's two little optimistic things I want to acknowledge to go along with that
and ramp up to it.
As people are listening to this April 30th, this is the day that this comes this episode
comes out is the day that Disneyland reopens.
Like we've started to see, you know, cast members and people who know cast members who
I'm very jealous of starting to trickle in.
But today is the day that it's back, which it felt like I was worried there were times
that I was worried it was not going to happen.
Like the thought crossed my mind.
Like, what if this kept going so insane that Disneyland closed entirely and this became
condos? Like, that's very insane.
But I was worried. What was that?
I said that really would be something I can't I I wasn't worried simply because I can't
imagine a world without Disneyland.
Yeah, yeah. Well, and they were like, yes, yeah, yeah.
And they're like they would have like personally, they just would have like firing squatted
Gavin Newsom themselves in public and people would have been like, yeah, do what you got
to do. OK, so we're back in the back in the green zone.
Cool. Yeah, they would have.
I mean, at the worst, they would have had to like sell to Tesla or something or sell
to any of these big brands.
And then Tesla would be running Disneyland.
Finally, more fires at Disneyland.
And Elon, Elon would have just take he would, you know, he would say like the rides are
good now, but they're really going to be awesome sauce after we take over.
And he's going to he's going to be like, whoa, whoa, this this Haunted Mansion ride, who
made this? What were they smoking?
Huh? He would have been like so random.
Yeah, he would have had all these comments from his his mind, his genius level mind.
What do they call it? Disneyland, even though some of it is water.
Like like 300000 likes on that for some reason.
Yeah, but he'll he'll do some of this material soon, I think.
I think he has a platform coming up.
Big New York platform. Yes, that's the last.
That's another one more bit of positivity, but not yet.
We got to wake up, wait another week for that.
The other thing I wanted to say, and this is just not a personal thing, really quick,
I had to share this, but just as things start reopening, going to places has opened back
up and I've been able to do some really fun stuff with my baby son, increasingly less
babies over a year. I don't know if we even call him that now.
We got to go to the zoo, which is very magical.
And, you know, animals, sure, whatever.
But the main thing is I now have been on a ride with my son.
This is a big deal.
I was so happy.
And now we haven't now we should say we're all probably not going to get around to the
parks for a little bit.
I think it's coming.
But, you know, you'll hear us update you about that.
Hey, we're back and we did it and it was cool.
So it wasn't one of the big league parks was very special anyway.
There's a place called Travel Town.
Have you all been to Travel Town?
You're all in this neck of the woods, kind of.
Are people aware of Travel Town?
I know it, but I actually have not made it over there.
Yeah, got to do it.
Meet us there sometime. It's great.
It's just a place with a bunch of parked trains.
And that's and that's all it is.
Here's a bunch of trains sitting around.
There's a train that where the Beach Boys took a photo one time.
So that I was happy to see in person the famous Beach Boys train.
But there is famous L.A.
landmark. But there is also a little train that tools around the park.
Very like classic early Walt Disney style.
And we didn't think it would be open one day.
And then we went and it was open and I ran over to it
to a speed that was maybe dangerous to the child.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. A ride.
We did it. Huge smiles.
Big smiles. Laughter for the entire first lap.
Second lap. He kind of freaked out and got bored and then cried
as soon as we got off of it.
But there was one very successful lap of a ride with my kid.
This felt like just a big moment
for for me as a dad and a ride aficionado.
It finally all came together.
So I just wanted to share that. Wow.
Congratulations. Congratulations.
That's big. That's early. I have been there.
I have been there because we went for Owen Dennis's birthday.
My boss, my former boss, the creator of Infinity Train.
We went to Travel Town for his birthday and we sat in a little car.
Did you not get on the train, though, to celebrate Infinity Train?
Wait, what?
I'm saying there's a train there to celebrate Infinity Train.
You should have ridden the train with there.
Well, I think maybe I did.
Or maybe it wasn't running that day.
I forget. But there was there was a little train
and there were a bunch of trains and we rented a train car.
OK, to have his birthday meal in.
What? Wait, I don't think I know about the rental of the train cars,
which I'm thinking someplace else entirely.
Where is this place?
It's in it's in Griffith Park, like not that far from the Disney studio.
You can see it from the from the 134 freeway.
Yeah, I think probably. Yeah.
Confusingly, there's some other little train place
that is not affiliated with Travel Town, but next to it.
So maybe it could have been that maybe I was at the unaffiliated train
the other one, which who know I don't know why they are like,
did they get along or are they enemies?
It's weird that there's two train parks next to each other.
They were started by a pair of brothers.
Yeah, there's fierce competition.
Two brothers.
They just their difference was like, should the train go clockwise
or counterclockwise?
Mm hmm. Fight over that.
I believe at Halloween, they they turn that little train
into a ghost train and then they just fill it with like kooky,
spooky stuff the whole route, because I saw that
I went to a few years ago.
L.A. Haunt, Boney Island set up right next to Travel Town.
And it was awesome. They went all out.
I saw a number of listeners at this event.
And as I was leaving, I was like, oh, wow, that ghost train looks awesome.
But it was Halloween and was sold out.
It was totally booked.
So hopefully this year they're both back.
You know, all this kind of like fun little cute stuff.
I am so in on every bit of it this year.
I haven't done any of these Griffith Park trains in the recent past.
And it's boy, this is going to be the whole rest of the year is little trains now.
Wow. Five years as little trains made me so about trains.
That's that's great.
A train podcast now you can get him ready for haunts, you know,
get him ready for haunts at an early age, which will be nice.
So he'll be he'll be like vaccinated against train like a haunted train stuff.
And by the time he gets to our age, he's going to be like the king of haunts.
Well, yeah, if I could have a kid, if I could like kind of thicken the skin
so that he's not like me slash us.
And it doesn't take him decades to never to get comfortable with.
I want him to be ahead of it and be like a bully,
making fun of kids who are afraid to be young me, his young dad.
Yeah, that's that's that's where I want to go.
So far the other direction you want to like a boy named Sue him.
Oh, no, that doesn't sound good.
I don't remember all the ins and outs of those lyrics, but it's probably not.
Really, he just he named his son Sue so that he'd have to fight his whole life.
I think that's it.
Well, that's it.
Hmm. I guess if I really wanted this trajectory.
Yeah, I could have gone with Sue.
I didn't go with Sue.
But look, a lot of trains in the future.
Maybe just a could be like like a lot of full train podcast.
Or maybe I just need to spin off into a little trains podcast.
I think Jason's going to come along with me.
Oh, little trains.
That's good.
Good title.
I would have I would have put a hundred dollars on Jason doing the first one.
I know I got to look through all the trademarks I've registered
to make sure I haven't already secured little trains.
Scott's going to have to buy that from Jason.
Yeah. Domain squatting.
Oh, no. Little trains dot train.
Barely used. Yeah.
Suffix. Wow.
So that's anyway, magical stuff.
I thought that's how that news would fit into an episode about even
more magical stuff, which I'm so happy to talk about for a while with you guys.
Yes. So we are talking today about a ride you can only experience
at Tokyo Disney Sea.
And it is top one of our top favorite top three favorite rides.
I don't know. It's called Sinbad Storybook Voyage.
And it's something we went into called the Sinbad Storybook Voyage.
And it's something we went into completely cold.
We didn't know a thing about it.
Again, podcast friend Andrew Grissom said, you got to do Sinbad.
We went on Sinbad and it was as magical a time
as like going on a ride for the first time when you're a kid, like a child.
We felt like children being on this ride and discovering what it was,
you know, as it went.
Yeah. So we've all three of us have been on it.
Jason has watched YouTube videos, I assume.
Yes, I watched it a number of times this morning.
And I have to say it is one of the rare rides where it's like,
oh, this is moving just on video.
This is, I mean, an emotional year and a half or so, you know.
So kind of primed for it was a little worn out
going to two grocery stores yesterday, like a little like,
so I guess I was kind of in the anything can set me off these days.
But certainly this in a good way did.
Yeah, I completely agree.
I don't know that.
And this we've talked a little bit about like weird,
like weird times when you go like, am I am I getting emotional with this?
We've we've done a little bit.
Like we talked a little bit about it in the frozen episode at the Let it Go part,
which I think, yeah, I agree with Scott on that.
But like this ride, I think it was the second time we wrote it.
We're like in the soaring part.
And again, I'm getting I'm all over the place.
The song itself is unbelievably good.
It's an Alan Menken song.
There's a soaring part that makes it the song.
Yeah, the ride. Yeah, 100 percent.
The ride is very good on its own.
It's a cute, fun little time.
But that song before the the singing even starts.
Yeah, I had me. Yes.
And there's like a soaring part of the song.
And I think it was the second time we wrote it.
I think we wrote it like four times, maybe the soaring part of the song.
I start to go, oh, my God, it's like I have some like sense memory
or some memory from being like six and going on this ride.
And I'm like, why am I so moved by this?
The room where the like giant is playing the bass.
What is this doing to me?
But yeah, there's something about that song
that makes this thing like extra special.
Yeah, I just watching the YouTube videos this morning.
And then because I cried because of that, I was like,
oh, I bet that Tokyo Disney Resort
35th anniversary theme song still makes me cry.
And so I went and listened to that and it makes me cry even more
because now the lyrics take on this extra poignancy
because of the last year of lockdown and not being able to go to the park
because it's it's all about like, hey, hasn't it been a while
since you've come on down and played with your friends?
And I'm like, it has.
Yes, I totally agree.
We had a very nice magical time at Tokyo Disney.
And that was the anthem playing like maybe immediately
as we got to their main street.
Yeah, it was playing.
It's playing in the monorail area.
Even I don't know.
Do you guys know we played that song for you?
Yes. Yeah. OK.
I think I don't.
I don't remember if it was.
I don't think this was going by the time I got there.
And I think this may have been retired.
I mean, we should probably play a little snippet of.
I don't know what the rules are as far as how much song we can play, really.
But we've broken those.
We like hear about that in the moment.
Yeah. Yeah.
Things all the time. You are correct.
You know, we'll just take it down nicely.
Just two little, two little.
This is the song Lizzie's talking about.
Brand new day, I believe, right?
Yeah.
It's a it's in the second verse where they said, like,
hasn't it been a while since you played with your friends?
But all right, I can I can.
We have four.
The difference between this and the song and Sinbad, though,
this is in English.
Compass of your heart in the ride is 95 percent or more in Japanese.
Yeah, they only say compass of your heart.
In English. Yeah.
Here we go. It's ramping up.
One, two, three.
This is where the listeners think this is insanity.
Yeah, probably. Is it? Or not.
I mean, if anybody is not going to think it's insanity, it's your listeners.
Yeah, I well, I mean, yeah, if you wandered into this podcast today,
you're probably like, these are for lunatics.
What's like? What is like?
These people need therapy.
And you're right. That's all.
Yeah. And that's like that song.
Like you're like, I guess it's OK.
It sounds like I don't know.
Was it even recorded very well?
I don't know. It makes me cry.
It makes me cry every time I hear it.
And it really makes me cry when it gets to the chorus.
But then when I was listening to it today, it the lyric is, I think.
Like it's.
I mean, all right, here, I'll just play it.
Hasn't it been a while? Like you?
You. The world is.
Sure, yeah.
Here it is. Here it is.
I know you haven't come to party in a while.
In a while. Right.
Come to party in a while. Right.
It's too applicable.
That's a that's one of the funny of the moment.
Cultural differences, I think, is like saying like come and party,
I think is much more of an innocent fun thing in Japan
versus here where it sounds like you're going to go get loaded at Disney.
Like, yeah, more of your body lyrics that contain nothing,
not one sliver of an offensive word.
Well, I'm saying already. What is this filth?
I mean, like I am certainly offended by the use of it.
I'm just saying I think it's maybe a different a different word usage there.
So, yeah, that's that's one of the things.
And I think it's partly that's that's burning our brain because, yeah,
it was like literally we got into the Main Street
and there was like explosion of like confetti in the songs playing.
We're like, oh, man.
People ran to see it.
Yeah. So anyway, that's that was again, you can go back and listen.
We did an episode about our Tokyo Disney trips, both Lindsay and I,
and then a different episode with Scott.
So well, let me say that because so you guys did a Tokyo episode
and I was I was too strict about spoilers and I physically left the episode.
That was the plan. It was not a storm out.
I think you were just strict enough.
I think, well, I'm glad I was because it was it is the rare occasion
like to get to go on rides where I truly don't know what's going to happen.
Now, the Sinbad thing, I think, because Erin, my wife, did listen to the episode.
And when we got to Sinbad, I sort of knew what I knew that Sinbad was
full of animatronics and a boat ride.
I wasn't going in totally blind.
But she said, yeah, I think the thing is, there is this song,
there is a song in it, and the song is very emotional.
And I was like, we'll see.
We'll see how emotional this song makes me.
And I think as soon as the boat took off, I was tearing up.
I don't think there was one lyric yet.
And somehow I and then watching the video just did it again.
And we're just going to have to analyze why, because I think, you know,
to some listeners, it might be inherent.
It might be you might.
But I do think that the experience is part of it.
And I have theories as to the what is so emotional about all this.
But we can get into it. Right.
To Mike, like maybe a minute into the ride.
And I was like, have we is this song from something?
Why do I feel like I've heard it before?
So my theory is just having that all of us having been raised on
specifically the Disney music of Alan Mankin and Howard Ashman.
We are primed to like connect to the musicality.
Yeah, I mean, that's that's got to be part of it.
That it's like it's, you know, it's in this.
It's got the same DNA as the stuff we were raised on all the Disney songs.
For sure, that has to be part of it.
But yeah, there's an extra little X factor here.
We'll play a little bit of it so you know what we're talking about.
There's there's like piece, there's different pieces of it.
And this is like this is what you hear kind of right when you get on the boat.
Here we go.
I can see Scott's like I could see it affecting him in a little window.
I don't want to look at the wind.
I don't want to see what I'm doing.
I don't want to see what you guys are doing.
It's too vulnerable.
Yeah, I'm a I'm the nerve.
I don't want this to be an episode involving tears.
I could see it off our cameras.
Yeah, really, I can see it.
So like that's that's what happens right away.
And I think immediately you're kind of like, this is a big deal.
Whatever is about to happen is a big deal.
This is important. What we're doing here.
Weeping and an epic and majestic.
It's just it's true.
It is the beginning of something.
Yeah. You know, it does it for me.
Horns in general, like there's so many uses of horns that will just
have some physical effect on me and the horns.
I feel like it's French horns, probably probably a mix of things.
But that when that little
I think that takes you back to the beginning of Beauty and the Beast.
And it is like what you never get to experience again for the first time.
You can only have seen Beauty and the Beast for the first time once.
And this is almost like it's a new beauty and the beast unfolding.
And you had to come into a specific place across the globe to see it.
And you're exhausted and worn down.
And it's in Japan is such a crazy fun adventure to go do.
But it's not relaxing in any way.
It's like an agitated go, go, go, holy shit kind of trip.
So by the time you get here, which was like towards the end of the trip for me.
And it's all been so magical.
Boy, there's there's a lot feeding into it.
The yeah.
I just want to shout out those who like those who
who those who's something about those are like very spooky, but like uplifting.
That, I think, is another one of the main components of like this making
like chills from time here's fine.
We're going to say so many embarrassing things in the next so many minutes.
I'm realizing now I I mine and Kelly's podcast
is maybe like more emotional.
Like, we're probably like, I don't want to get super like stereotypical,
but we are two women.
And we're maybe a little more open and vulnerable.
So I've cried a fair number of times on a teen creeps episode.
Like we read Never Ending Story and we were reading some passages from it.
It's a very touching book.
And I like couldn't get through it because it's crying.
So for me, I'm like, yeah, it's totally normal.
We're just going to like cry over us in bed song and we all get it.
Well, we're three tough, stereotypical men
who are trying to have an aura of, you know, of like strength.
So we're going to try to maintain that hard asses.
Three traditionally are in men.
Three hard asses.
What's on your head right now?
As you say this, Mike, you describe.
I am wearing what is it called, Jason, a gator?
It's a I think it's a gator, right?
Yeah, this is for this is for like athletes, Scott.
You got to know this.
I'm wearing a brawny, strong, emotion free athletes.
My hair is very long right now and sort of to keep it up.
I've been wearing this gator given to me by my friend John, who was on Survivor.
And it says Slam Town on it.
Well, slamming is pretty masculine.
It was not much more masculine than slamming.
Yeah. So all right.
Pumped up the testosterone here.
No way. We're not going to cry in this episode.
What do you mean? No way.
It's not going to happen anyway.
Back to the song and everybody just like just like grimaces and tries to grit.
Really? Like I rewatched the I rewatched Alan Menken's performance of it.
Oh, I have a D23.
That one makes me just weeping because everybody in the audience is weeping to.
Scott, you've seen this clip, I assume, right?
I have. I don't want to go against you.
There is something I the Alan Menken performance does not do it for me as much.
And I think why is that I love first of all, I love the singing voice of Sinbad,
the protagonist in the ride.
And I think I prefer it as much as like an acoustic performance, you know,
should do it for me.
I think that switching it back to English kind of undoes the mystery.
I sort of like not knowing what the words are of this song
that's making me so emotional.
Like I think because you can like almost apply anything to the to the Japanese
lyrics, which I don't.
If you speak Japanese and you can't apply anything to it.
But I don't know what they're singing about until they say compass of your heart,
which has some like innate power to it.
I like that it's the only English.
And yeah, I don't I don't disagree with that.
But I think that what I'm responding to actually even more is that he's playing it
at a Japanese D23 in, I think, 2018.
And he says he's never performed it before.
And they cut to the audience and people immediately are like freaking out.
And then gasping, their hands are going up to their face.
And he's playing it.
And there's just like women are like sobbing.
Everyone's like you can see like this is real.
This emotion is real.
Yeah, there's a shot of one person and they're just like serenely smiling
and nodding along.
And then you realize they have a sorcerer Mickey like propped on their lap
like a sitting child.
And you can just tell it's the happiest moment.
And it yeah, you can feel the energy.
I think the lyrics in English are very beautiful.
But I agree. I understand that, like, oh, yeah, there is a certain mystery
in the fall. Yeah, I hear what you're saying.
But but hearing the lyrics in English for me had the opposite effect.
And I did feel like, oh, I've been hearing this since I was a child.
This is making me feel like I felt when I was a child.
But I was 36 when we went
and heard this song for the first time.
I would never I would never take away the emotion that you guys are experiencing
this for whatever reason.
I don't get us on board. But yeah, yeah.
But we can all play.
We all get something.
Yeah. Do you want to play more?
And then we should play. Yeah.
I don't think we said what the hell the right.
I know. I know. We got a song.
We've been focused 100 percent on the emotions the song evokes.
Well, I mean, I think the song is a big part because this ride is kind of new ish.
Like this version of the ride only dates to 2007.
And that's when you get the song.
It's when you get a lot of the cute little stuff.
We haven't even mentioned Shondu.
Yeah, yeah. I mean, I think we'll play this song just so everybody
who doesn't know anything about this has sort of the vibe in their head.
And then we'll start describing sort of everything.
Yeah, there's two key parts.
Just real quick, I want to play.
This is sort of the start of when Sinbad starts singing.
And then I want to play that thing I mentioned, the soaring part, which just
I will hopefully not lose it.
I believe in the.
You see, there's a cute banter.
He's talking to the people in the village.
He's talking to Shondu.
And that's great.
I believe at this point when we were on the ride, I'm sure I said this last podcast,
I think I turned to you, Lindsay, and I said, man, I really like
I like this Sinbad guy.
You were just like, I'm really like, I like Sinbad.
I like his energy kind of a statement.
Yeah, I like it just seems like a good guy.
Yeah, I was like really like immediately charmed by him and his attitude.
I was like, I like this guy.
There's something about this guy.
And that's definitely captured there.
And then this this is the later in the in the ride.
This is sort of the soaring part I'm talking about.
The land to be found.
The right.
So.
See.
Yeah, so I got like little bumps on my arm listening to that.
Oh boy.
Man, it's crazy.
It's crazy, ladies and gentlemen.
And now that I know the English lyrics, I like definitely remember what it is he's singing
at that point.
Sure.
So yeah, so that's the vibe.
That's what you're hearing the whole time.
It's looping around.
There's one other little section that's like when they're in like the jungle, that part
is the least good part as far as music is concerned.
No offense to it.
It's just like kind of nothing.
It's like the instrumental part.
Yeah.
Just a lot of like drums and so.
But it's it's it's a small world style and maybe the rare thing.
Maybe I can't think of anything.
Maybe since it's a small world, it's brought that back where there's a song looping for
the entire trip.
Yes.
Where it's a it's a boat ride with, you know, seven to nine big set pieces, big set pieces,
as we can say.
And the it's it's a seamless transition in and out of different parts of the song.
They've just like queued it up really perfectly where you're always somewhere in the bed of
that song for this very long attraction.
I feel like this can take, you know, 15 minutes depending on the speed of the boats.
Yeah. And it's like the difference, even even your best classic dark rides, I probably.
Like I might get a little like sleepy in certain sections, but because of the song, I feel
like there's not a part of the ride where I'm like, man, this is the weak part of this.
I do really I think I don't know that they could like put any sort of animatronic, any
type of ride over this song, but it's possible they could have done like a just put like,
I'm trying to think like a peer level attraction with that song.
If they put this into the the new journey into imagination where he where the figment
farts or whatever and the toilet on the ceiling.
But you hear like, oh, it's the greatest.
Like, yeah, I think you'd be like, well, that doesn't make much sense.
But I feel really good.
This is making me maybe it is the toilet on the ceiling that's making me feel really good.
I don't know.
I like this figment guy.
I just think he's got a good heart.
Life is the greatest.
That might do it.
That might ruin it.
If Figment was singing.
If he's saying in that.
Yeah, I think yeah, I think probably the song would be affected by the person singing it.
But if Dreamfinder's singing it, maybe I can see him having a Kenji style voice.
Sure. So that's that might possibly work.
The singer of Compass of Your Heart.
There's a lot of crossover, I think, between this ride and original journey into imagination
and the way people feel about it, where it is this specific thing in this specific location
never got cloned in another park that people just have really special heartwarming feelings about.
And it's and where there's like a little critter is a little critter who's really popular
in the merchandise and deservedly so from this one specific ride.
Yes. Yeah, there's for sure the parallels there.
That, of course, is Shandu.
We mentioned him earlier.
Well, let's say he's a little baby tiger with that little baby tiger
wearing a little baby turban.
Yes. And a little bell in the front.
This door is so, so cute.
This is the cutest thing.
That's a lot of the emotion to instant lovability.
I was taking photos of him just in the queue.
There's just, you know, like drawings of him up in the queue where he is.
You're getting a hint at the kind of thing that he does, which is mainly, despite being very cute,
keeping bad guys in line.
So somewhere in the line, there is him like pulling kind of like biting the fabric of somebody who's
up to no good and like, OK, so he's cute, but he's also feisty.
This is good.
He's the enforcer.
The most adorable little enforcer you've ever seen.
He's like, yeah, he's like Mike.
I'm breaking bad.
He's the cleaner.
Who do you have sweet emotions for as it goes?
Yes.
The OK.
Cliff notes the ride, not like scene by scene, but just basically,
you know, Sinbad's off on a journey.
He like leaves his port town and goes to all these different little islands and on
different little quests and then returns triumphantly a hero, having done hacks,
acts of heroism throughout his journey.
This is all conveyed via like 150 audio animatronics, right?
So many.
Yes.
Great movement.
These things really move.
Yeah. Yeah.
No, it's a small world in that regard.
Yeah, extremely.
Mixed with gigantic animatronics, which I'm sure that we will highlight.
But like you think that, you know, you know,
you think you get what it is.
OK, it's a little it's a doll ride.
Like it's a small world.
But then you round some corners to see some of the most jaw dropping
animatronics ever built, just massive in scale.
Yes, it's it is like I'm trying to think.
I don't know if that was done on purpose, but yeah, you you it throws that surprise
at you because as far as like scale is concerned, it's very rare.
I feel like the parks were like they really you turn a corner
and it's like, oh, wait, they can do this with the OK, I got it.
I mean, I guess you get there's a bird
that's pretty big earlier than than the scene you're talking about.
But mostly, yeah, mostly.
I mean, it's kind of like approaching Ursula in Ariel's.
What is it called? Undersea Adventure?
Mm hmm.
But that was, of course, built after the Sinbad, right?
Yeah. And Ursula Ursula is obviously very impressive, but Ursula's probably
no ogre, seven feet, seven feet tall, six feet.
She's also like she's further from you.
She's not moving as much.
She's not as expressive.
You go under that.
That is jaw dropping, like getting to see kind of all angles of it.
It's really cool. Yeah.
So it's sort of this like it's this
like very heartwarming boat ride about a guy going on journeys all over the world
and being very supported by the people back in his town.
They're so excited for him.
Yeah,
I mean, like not to we could seen by seeing it a little more, but like,
that's, I think, where the emotion comes in for me is the like, OK,
so we know that Sinbad is going to go on an adventure.
Is he going to be we don't know what we're going to encounter.
What does that mean?
Do we see like one solitary boat and this guy's piloting it around?
And instead of what we see is this vibrant
community where everyone is so happy and everyone has their purpose.
Everyone has their role.
And these people are bringing food to other people.
And these there's entertainers and people
making shadow puppets and people operating the lamp to help the shadow puppets get
made, but they're all united in wishing Sinbad good luck on his journey.
And maybe you have to be there to understand why this notion is so emotional.
It's just so everybody's just
because he doesn't really have a mission beyond just I'm going exploring.
And of course, these are based on like very old stories.
In which it was not heartwarming, they were just adventures and he was kind of a
dick and his his crew was a bunch of assholes who were just like trying to steal
treasure and of course, there was an earlier iteration of the ride that was a lot
closer to the original tales and and in the original ride,
it was just a community that was just where he was from.
And it showed the people of the town.
And then when they retooled it with the music, then
it's a the whole dang town is celebrating Sinbad and his amazing adventure.
They're just so happy for him to be going out and seeing the world.
And it's not like he's.
It's not there's not an aspect to the story where it's like Sinbad's going to
save us all or like Sinbad's going to find the answer and we're all depending on Sinbad.
It's just like, hey, do you hear Sinbad's going on a boat with Shandu?
Cool. Let's go out and see him off with a bunch of banners and singing.
It's just so delightful.
Well, what they realized and if you read any blog post or wiki or any sort of thing
about this ride, everyone makes sure to mention it's like, OK, first off,
you need to know one thing.
The greatest treasure, it's friendship.
OK, that's the starting place.
And that is kind of like the thesis of this ride.
And I think why it you know, the vibe just changed so wildly.
The song was added.
Chon Du was added.
And like I was saying before we started
recording the original ride, which opened with the park, Sinbad 7 Voyages.
Everyone, everyone just looks is just unhappy to see you.
Everyone's pissed.
Yeah, because Sinbad, yeah, he's like him and his crew are trying to get treasure.
Like and in this he's helping everyone and he's making new friends.
He teaches a bunch of monkeys how to rock, you know.
Yeah, that's the thing is the song becomes his his ticket into every community.
He encounters.
Yeah, mm hmm.
Like it's a beautiful message.
Yeah, there's the like the juxtaposition between the two versions,
the original version and the newer version.
It's like in the original version,
the mermaids were like luring them to the rocks to like kill them.
And then a very traditional idea of what mermaids did.
They were, you know, sirens.
They sang and they were gorgeous to try to entice ships to two rocky areas.
So that they would die.
Yeah, in this version, not in this version, they're friends.
They're just more friends in this version and they tell you where to go.
Yeah, it's very funny that that
is kind of was kind of universal across the ancient world and that it shows up
in the Iliad, it shows up in one thousand and one nights.
But here we flip it on its head and it's like there's just more friends
telling you what's your direction to go, you know.
Everyone's a friend.
Just nothing but making friends on this ride.
I love all that about just supporting the journey.
He's going on a trip and we have to be we should all be happy for him.
And on a personal note, I might have said this before when I came back from Japan,
I don't recall, but how I felt because I had this unusual experience of like,
no matter what, going to this park that I dreamed of going to for so long was going
to be great and doing it with my wife and like it was this was there was this was
always going to be wonderful.
But then I would like post pictures throughout the day
and then I would get feedback from our listeners cheering us, cheering Aaron
and I on, wow, go Scott, nothing but positive, like so insanely positive.
And I'm like, that's the that's the town.
The town is cheering me and my journey on it.
And not only that, the other thing that
occurred to me about why the whole the city supporting each other kind of vibe,
that's Japan that from my experience over those couple of weeks of everything else
in Japan, Japan is as nice and friendly as Sinbad's town.
So you've already been living in that love,
like the kindness of strangers for 10 days or whatever.
And then you get this little like depiction of it.
That I think that's why the the town, the supportive town resonates so.
Yeah, that makes sense.
It's it's I'm trying to think like, yeah, you're you compared the opening to Beauty
and the Beast and I'm trying to think like Beauty and the Beast is really
beautiful and it's fun and the town looks nice.
But everyone's like being real dismissive of Bell for the most part.
Like, oh, look at her, that weirdo.
Like, there's none of the.
It's not pretty. Why she got a read.
Oh, come on.
Enough with the reading, Bell.
Like it's so beautiful.
But like there's some negative, there's a lot of a lot of negativity.
Also, it finds her people like here's like here's the bookstore guy.
And here's the people I get along with and they get me.
But it's not everybody.
Some of the other people are nice, but they don't get me.
And that's a little more, I think, what America is like.
Maybe you got to watch out, watch out for these people.
But then there's some of the best, nicest people you're ever going to encounter.
But whereas like, yeah, maybe Japan and Sinbad's town.
Maybe it's like I should assume this person's a friend.
Easier to assume, maybe.
Yeah. So that's yeah, there's it's like, I guess there was a, you know,
maybe like a note in your head of like, oh, it's like make it like
beating the beast, but not so negative.
Wow. You know, yeah, they fixed the one.
I have a criticism.
Well, you don't need you don't need conflict in an 11 minute ride necessarily.
I was just about to say it's like I look, I love a story with high stakes
and conflict and darkness.
If you've seen Infinity Train, you know that about me.
I write, I wrote a show for children that was like scary and upsetting.
But sometimes you just want a story where everybody likes each other
and has a good time and sings a song.
Yeah, it's just that is that
a positive adrenaline shot the whole time, like the whole ride.
So like, yeah, we're kind of going scene and scene here.
Like basically, like you're coming kind of coming in at the end of adventures
a lot like it's almost like the adventures, like kind of wrapping up.
Sinbad has one.
He's won people over.
If the bad guys are bad guys, they have something comical has happened to them.
Like there's a scene where one of them is in like the talons of a giant bird.
Another one like fell upside down into a giant egg.
Yeah. And his little feet are kicking around.
Yeah. So it's like this this guy is like he's just he comes into a situation,
he fixes it, and now he's celebrating with his magical song.
And that's sort of the format in most of those scenes.
Yeah. And yeah, you know, to explain the difference between the two versions,
which we have a little bit,
you know, you know, there's no difference in the locations.
Like the locales never change.
The basic places that Sinbad goes, we go to this island
where there's big birds and we go visit a giant.
But the dynamic shifts in every single one of them,
they are all about making friends as opposed to a lot of the scenes
seem to be about bad stuff is happening and you're going to narrowly escape
the bad stuff.
And in that way, it's kind of an awkward mix of cute figures.
Like it's a small world.
But if they were all doing bad things to each other all around the world
and that's where you left it like, oh, no, Italy's on fire.
Can we help them? No. All right. They're on their own.
We came in just as Hitler was invading France.
And we're like, well, see you. Best of luck with that.
It's a little cute doll, Hitler, but still, it's still the stakes are real for them.
Yeah, cutest Hitler.
And another another thing like it's a lot of the same audio
animatronics, too.
And if you if you go back and watch the one that was there from 2001 to 2006,
you like and then you watch the current one, you recognize all of them.
They may be some changed entirely.
I don't know. But you seem to you kind of go, I know that guy.
I know that guy.
Mostly they just took away facial hair.
Yeah. We haven't talked about that one in a very Disney
classic fashion before the new rules.
Yes, they made Sinbad remove his facial hair.
The old world order.
Yes. Walt Walt's ghost came to the Imagineers
and he said, I know what to do to fix this, right?
Take the boy's facial hair away.
Bearded animatronics are evil.
That's the rule.
We all know the goatees are of the devil.
The devil has a goatee.
Sinbad shouldn't have one.
The way the presidents with beards are all the evil ones.
That's right. And the ones without hair are all good.
Nixon didn't have a beard.
He takes credit for fixing the ride.
And everybody is like, well, I think it was more the song.
And he's like, no, facial hair.
Only 100 percent that evil beard.
But they also like something that I don't think is acknowledged
and I don't have tangible proof of this, but I do feel like you guys talked about
the animatronics moving very, very smoothly.
And I agree with that.
And I think if you watch the old one, they're a little jerkier.
Like maybe there's more going on.
They actually might be like more advanced animatronics in that way
that that Johnny Depp moves a little more or Trump moves a little more.
And I just listed two of the creepiest animatronics that exist.
You really went for it.
We're probably applying our feelings about the real life people to it a little bit.
But I, regardless, I'm like, yeah, maybe a little too much movement going on.
And I think that was maybe true of these old some of these older characters.
And one place that I notice it is like belly dancing,
there's belly dancing going on through kind of at the beginning and the end.
And for some and I watched the original version, I'm like,
why is this like creepier to me originally?
And then they still dance in the new one. Why is it not?
And I think it's like I think like the dancing is just like more manic.
It's just like a crazier dance.
And then they're just surrounded by people
just staring down at the belly dancer's body.
Whereas now it's like the person's dancing, but they're kind of on their own.
They're just like they're off having a they're just like, it's less like spirits.
It's less for the male gaze, perhaps
than it is just for the celebration of dance.
Yeah, I think so.
I think they just want to dance.
And there's no there's no odd little crowd like too close.
Like they gave they gave the dancers some space.
And I think that's good.
But just truly and we'll get to it with the monkeys, but big time,
the monkeys are like crazy in the old one.
Right. And they've kind of toned it down.
It's probably also just that the you know, they're newer animatronics.
And maybe you can be more subtle.
You know, you know what's like a very realistic animatronic, but that isn't.
Well, it's a little creepy, maybe.
But the the shaman of song, the shaman of song is smooth.
The movement doesn't freak me out about the shaman.
Maybe in general, the shaman is a little creepy, but it's
but there's fluidity for sure.
So wait, Scott, you're saying you like the shaman?
I don't know if I'd go that far.
I guess technically.
Oh, man.
Well, you've really backed yourself into a corner here.
Do I like I've I've been I've been hiding at this halt.
I love the shaman.
All right. Thank you.
It's been my desktop this entire time.
You can appreciate the shaman of song while still feeling like kind of an uncanny
valley feeling about the shaman.
Well, you know what it is?
Actually, it just occurred to me.
It's the it's the big stuff in small rooms.
It's that thing rearing its head as has as it has in many episodes.
I think if the shaman of song was open air,
just like with the sky above it, that'd be fine.
But it's a very tall creature, not a problem in Sinbad.
I mean, there's big characters in Sinbad, but most of them are extremely small.
So, oh, man, I can't wait for you to ride this new ride.
Everyone's talking about and we'll get some real good feedback on that.
I'm sure you'll be on it soon enough.
Pets. Yeah, pets. Pets.
Yeah, there's a big there's a big pet.
Oh, boy, you have no idea.
Wow. Jason got to see the big pet before us.
I'm very jealous of Jason.
Yeah. Big pet.
Oh, man. Yeah, that's interesting.
I will. I want to make a quick comparison, though.
And obviously, it's not quite as good as the song here, though.
But I will say the Na'vi shaman of song song
is similar, kind of haunted our vacation, much like Sinbad.
Haunted is true where it's like that.
That's a new song you just heard.
And maybe it's just me, but I constantly was singing both songs
the rest of our trip.
It became one of the other an additional theme
of the trip. Yes.
So I will say I have zero emotion ascribed to the shaman song.
Same song.
I did not. Yes, I did not cry about the shaman of song.
And it doesn't do the same thing. But it did become a theme.
But it definitely wormed its way into my head and it
I was using it as a weapon the rest of the trip.
That's true.
Every time I would forget it, it got brought back.
I don't know. Oh, God, I'm so sorry.
This song I kept to just like, yeah, like just like getting
going to the airport and getting on the plane.
I just kept like anything that felt like part of a journey.
I would do this refrain, even though it was the opposite, where like
I think Sinbad was kind of happy to be going home because, you know, like
he had a good thing going back there, even though all the adventures were fun.
We were so sad to leave Japan.
Dear God, that was not I did not feel the joy of this song leaving
leaving Disney. Right.
And yes, that was not not the same as you leaving Orlando the last time.
Thinking of the shaman.
That was the refrain that was supposed to like, keep me back.
That was supposed to like, no, no, no, don't go.
Yeah, it didn't didn't do the trick for me. Right.
Neither did. Well, maybe.
Did you have the same effect, though?
Did the the Baja men, did the Baja
were they like, was that like a siren song for you
calling you to stay in Orlando forever?
I mean, kind of. Crash yourself on the rocks of Orlando.
The sirens, the Baja men calling to me
enticing you from a shirtless on a rock.
Just the idea.
Yeah, just the idea, just the idea that you can see that list of bands
that plays Epcot every year in Orlando does make me go,
wouldn't be bad to live 20 minutes and head over here a couple of times
a week and see, see the bomb and see
third eye blind and smash mouth.
And yeah, you can't see Sugar Ray anywhere else.
They're very that's the rarest appearance that you make.
Even though we have seen them two times.
This was this was a revelation in an episode.
Lindsay, you too. You've also seen them twice.
Oh, yeah, we went to to the first one was
Summerland or was that the second one?
I can't remember which one was which.
The Summerland tour and.
We yeah, we say we remember the name of the next one, but
it was sugar the first year was Sugar Ray.
It was Everclear.
It was lit.
It was the Wallflowers and then one other band.
Marcy Playground, Marcy Playground, who opened
Marcy's Playground. No, Marcy Playground.
Marcy Playground. Yeah.
My mother's name is Marcy also.
So that's where it was a big thing in the house.
Yeah. When that band was around.
It was a great time to be on Marcy. Yeah.
And we yes, that was what over 1997, 98.
And I think we were like, oh, Marcy Playground, good.
Then lit hit the stage and we were like, whoa, lit is good.
Yeah, I was like, oh, I forgot that I really liked lit as a teenager.
They were just like, you know, people were trickling into Greek theater.
It wasn't even like it was full yet because it was a big festival of music.
And lit was bringing it like they were really like they didn't care
that they were playing second on the bill.
And we were like, oh, that's pretty good.
Wow. And you would say, yeah, lit was lit.
I would say that.
And and then Sugar Ray closed that time.
And Everclear, not so good, like audio wise.
They were not bringing the energy.
Sugar Ray, however, sounded fantastic.
And Mark McGrath, a very charming band leader,
like just really he like he knows what he is and he played it to perfection.
Hmm. Like a 90s mic.
Like self-effacing, like funny.
Making fun of himself and Sugar Ray.
It was a good time.
I'm scanning the I'm scanning the sincerity irony meter
and I'm landing at sincerity.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No sincerity.
He was he was like making fun of himself and him being like,
he said the fact that this tour existed.
He was like, he goes, yeah, you're here to see like douchey Sugar Ray.
And yeah, and we were all like,
we are here to see douchey Sugar Ray.
Thank you, Mark. We're all thank you so much.
Those singles are good. I maintain those singles are good.
I like how you call Mark McGrath a band leader as if he was Xavier.
Uh huh.
His name is Brown.
I mean, can you argue with his?
No. Yeah.
So then we then we went back the next year and Smash Mouth was on the tour
and I believe they closed.
Well, of course. Yes.
And Gin Blossoms was there and that was fantastic.
Both years, I believe.
Oh, OK.
I believe we've talked about this repeated.
Yeah. But they're yeah, they got the they got those fastball was great.
Fastball was there. Yes.
Couple of songs I like a lot of as far as best.
All right. The audience wants to hear.
And you guys, you two, you guys went to Sturgis, right?
Last year to see Smash Mouth.
You went to the Motor's.
Mm hmm. And it worked out great.
The sacred spreader event.
You stand up.
Everyone stayed six feet apart wearing masks.
It was really a safe, just like welcoming.
It was like it was like the town seeing everyone off, seeing Sinbad off.
Seeing Sinbad off.
Yeah, yeah, it was good.
I think I've said before on the podcast that my old lady,
Lindsay, jumped into the sidecar on my hog and we headed out for Sturgis.
And it was really a hell of a time.
Yeah. You brought back a lot of memories and a lot of covid. Yeah.
Tons, tons of covid.
But we we had a great time in Sturgis.
Let's let's have more stuff on the ride.
Do we not talk about Shondu enough?
That's the other big.
So, yeah, there was no there was no Shondu before.
It was it was just this this bearded mercenary band of sailors.
Killers. Yeah.
Stealing treasure, getting greedy.
Get that they're the reason they were attacked by birds, whereas in the new version,
they are pirates that Sinbad is fighting instead of the men he hired for the journey.
Yeah. His guys.
Yeah. So now now instead of those jerks, he's got a cute little tiger cub.
The cutest tiger.
Oh, my God. If you have never seen this
chandu and I'm sure it'll be on Twitter as we do this.
I boy, what a heartwarming.
Yeah. We have our is it cute arguments all the time.
I would like to meet the monster who does not find Shondu to be cute.
Yeah, I don't know. Yeah, I don't need I don't need to know.
I don't need to know that person or their minds.
100 percent. If we did the poll, I'd like to know who's responsible for Shondu.
Yeah, you know, there's not a lot of like kind of in-depth,
imagineering interviews and stuff about this attraction.
I was trying to find some.
Yeah, I mean, when you have this much of a retool, you shouldn't.
There should be.
I want to know the oral history of the Sinbad retool.
Oh, sure. It's interesting.
They don't do stuff like this a lot and they don't do it like unless there's
there's a lot of change outs that involve in putting in new IP,
but there's not a lot of like the rides not working.
Let's fix it. But in like a in a screenwriting way, let's do like
there needs to be a journey and a better hero and a music
musical arc that tells you who the character is and a fun little sidekick.
Locations can stay the same robots change, stay the same go.
Well, I'm very curious as to what the new Snow White ride is going to be,
because it's no longer the scary adventure. Right now, it's the enchanted wish.
Yeah. Enchanted wish.
What's that going to look like?
Yeah. What does that phrase mean? Yeah.
You know, because most wishes not that enchanted.
This very enchanted most wishes for the prince to come wishing for.
Right. So that's her wish is the prince.
And maybe and now they have a moment at the end like the prince things resolved
a little better in that they have a kiss.
The wish is for a kiss and she has an enchanted kiss as per her enchanted wish.
I think maybe that's what it is.
I mean, Snow White's I Wish song is literally about wishing. So.
Yes, she's wishing well appropriate, but still like not.
Doesn't really indicate what the changes are going to be. Right.
Well, I mean, well, sooner today, people know.
I think there's people already posted videos.
I'm going cold. Yeah, I don't want to change.
Well, that wish I wanted to know.
Yeah, I want it to be like Sinbad.
I was thinking you were saying like,
like a retooling like could could could Alan Menken.
And I want to mention Alan Menken wrote that song with a guy named Glenn Slater as well.
Oh, yes, he should be credit.
I believe he wrote the lyrics to the song.
But could could Menken and Slater have saved Superstar Limo with a song?
Maybe, you know, because like you leave the animatronics in and you leave what was there.
But yeah, maybe like you didn't have to put Monsters Inc.
And they could have written a song about Hollywood that would have saved the ride.
And now we would have been enjoying the beautiful Superstar Limo song to this day.
We just feel as money for me.
It'd be about coming to Hollywood.
Drew Carey.
Perfect. Soaring epic.
Boring and epic.
City of stars, sea of shining just for me.
Right. It wasn't.
Yeah, I get you. It wasn't out yet, though.
Yeah, I know. To put that in there.
But that would have been a that would have been a good show.
They should have tried that.
I mean, I like that one song from earlier in the really quick song that
I can't remember the name of, but it's very jaunty.
And there's a lot of costume changes in La La Land.
Took me a while to remember the name of the movie.
Probably not a great sign that you would put in a ride.
I don't know. Is that is that more of a sign of your mental state or is that?
Oh, yeah, it's yeah.
My memory has definitely deteriorated.
I definitely need to take some more supplements and interpretation.
I'm not even sure why La La Land came up to begin with before he produced the title.
Oh, jaunty Hollywood song.
You were talking about that.
That's the song. Yeah, it's from La La Land.
Yeah, yeah. Stars. Yeah.
City of stars.
I'm sure there's we should be advertising some sort of supplements for brains,
you know, like the Joe Rowan podcast does.
Yeah, some sort of a new tropic, new tropic.
If we could, yeah, if we could put that out into the world, we're willing to
advertise for some sort of brain supplement.
Have we in the way of weird.
Hey, Lynn, Lynn over it forever.
Don't get us a brain supplement.
Yeah, get us that sweet brain supplement sponsorship.
I want to get in touch with big brain supplement.
Yeah, we need Jason.
We can get Jason on these pills ASAP.
No, I won't take the vaccine, but I will take any weird pill
or powder that gives money to this program.
A tincture. If you got a tincture, I'm all about it.
Yes, that's right.
Let me say another thing about Chandu, which is that his popularity
and his cuteness is such that there is a snack in the park based around him.
And I thought that I knew I thought I could picture what this was.
I thought maybe I'd even seen it or had it, but I clearly didn't have it
because I'd remember this because the actual what the Chandu Tiger tail is.
If you look at it, it looks very pastry and it is orange and black.
Odd, odd little like question mark shaped pastry piece.
But what's inside, it is referred to as a chicken cream bun,
which sounds awful to me.
However, there were a bunch of things in Tokyo, Disney
that sounded not the best and then were the best.
So maybe I would be a fan of this chicken cream.
Well, I think I think it's like a bow dough
with like a chicken pot pie kind of filling, and it's just not described.
So you can imagine that.
Yeah, it's a savory pastry.
We didn't, Lindsay, we didn't eat Chandu's tail.
It sounds really might have now that I'm thinking about it.
I think we did. Maybe I think we did.
I think it was raining and we had it. Maybe.
Pretty sure.
I don't know. I should look through the photos.
Yeah, we ate Chandu's Chandu's tail from each end.
We were, yeah, like Lady and the Tramp. Yeah.
Romantic. Did you guys see they sell a key?
Oh, sorry, go ahead.
They sell a key chain of the tiger tail.
Wow.
A key chain of the tail and the rapper, the tail comes in.
That's so Tokyo.
Yeah, that was the kind of thing they'd get fixated on.
It's great. The rappers at Tokyo, maybe we didn't say this
on this other two episodes, like food rappers are like fully themed.
Like art in a way they're like not like you don't even want to throw
the rappers away for their like quick service chicken sandwich or something.
Because like I think the first place we ate was over in, I guess,
Frontierland and it was like fully themed to the junior woodchucks
and Huey Dewey and Louie on the rapper.
And I was eating like an OK sandwich with this like beautiful piece
of like artwork essentially.
And I'm like, I have to throw this away.
Like and the same with such care goes into everything.
Chandu has like his tiger tail, but then the pack is like,
his tiger tail. But then the package with a tiger tail comes in
is like themed to Chandu.
And it's you find that everywhere, which is fun.
Little extra bit of theming, which we do not have out here.
Oh, yeah. Such attention to detail.
That's directly related to what I was going to say, which is we were very
disappointed by the lack of Sinbad merchandise, much like country bears in Florida.
Well, yeah, it was mostly Chandu focus.
There was a good amount of Chandu stuff,
but we wanted like a Sinbad doll or something like I want him playing
like his little I don't know if it's a mandolin or guitar or whatever.
Best friend. Yeah, because I again, I I he won me over very quickly.
And I was looking for like a whole all of the figures or something.
All of the characters, especially that belly dancer figure I was looking for.
Yeah, you wouldn't shut up about that belly dancer.
You're either singing the song or some of that belly dancer.
I just like her. Yeah, yeah.
But yeah, we were yeah, we were sort of disappointed in the range of stuff
you get. It was just mostly tiger focused.
Not the quality of the merchandise itself, but the.
Yeah, the lack of additional merchandise.
It was also Chandu focused.
I just always want more.
I want more, more, more all the time.
More. I was super satisfied with the amount of Chandu stuff,
and I bought a Chandu puppet and it was and which Aaron
and I both agreed would be good to have.
But there is to keep being corny in an episode of cornyness.
We and we confirm later that unspoken we were buying the Chandu puppet
thinking I hope that this is for a baby.
And then that is what ended up being the case.
We would have been happy to have this tiger puppet regardless.
We have plenty of toys as it is.
But we're but I remember that specifically.
I was and you're and you're so heartwarming by the ride.
We were just kind of like, all right, see you back in America, dude.
And then and now on to the next generation.
Yeah, thought Michael has never had.
This is for a child.
No, absolutely not.
I have the opposite for me and for me.
Yeah, I have the opposite feeling like I will not let a future child
see like touch this.
They will not be allowed.
We're like, this is for a child.
Me. I will undercut it by saying that he has no interest in plushes of any.
Shandy was a bell, which is good.
The bell helps something that makes noise is good.
So that puts it a notch above other stuffed animals, which he doesn't care about.
So that all punctured that nice little fantasy scene.
But still, it was nice.
There's still time.
I mean, you can get he'll get into plush.
We'll get it. We'll make it.
You brought over some you brought over fantastic plushes, a DeLorean and a Doc Brown,
which he did immediately go for that DeLorean.
So he has a need for speed, probably.
He's going to be at Sturgis in a couple of years.
He loves autos.
And Sammy Hagar, the iconic music from BTTF to he's going to be on.
He's going to be watching Jay Leno's garage in a couple of months.
Oh, hell yeah. I'll take him to Jay Leno's garage.
He has trains.
And now I'll find it's probably not that far from where we live.
I'll just go knock on the door.
He'll probably be like, yeah, sure. For a kid. Yeah.
Yeah. And love modes of transportation and cartoon character.
Jay Leno. Mm hmm.
They love his exaggerated chin.
That's right. He does like, you know, he yells.
The baby yells a lot when he sees a big truck, and that's essentially Jay, too.
It's like the enthusiasm of a six month old.
Ah, wow.
I'm trying to split the difference between Jay and baby.
Scott compared Jay Leno to a street shark on a episode a couple of weeks ago.
Like body wise, is big.
He's just so top heavy in his head is big.
He's like a human street shark. Yeah.
So, yeah, kids, kids love street sharks.
OK, so oh, wait, so so trying to do this can take us into some scenes maybe.
But I wanted to ask this question, just knee jerk.
And does it do people have a favorite
Chandu moment because you see him in all of these scenes,
these scenes that were very like mean and joyless before.
And now there's some way that this cute tiger is undercutting it all with cuteness.
And I think there's a lot of great tableaus.
But do you have a knee jerk? What's your favorite moment of him?
Well, the first one that occurred to me was him on the
the water spout coming out of the whale's blowhole.
Yeah, yeah.
Spinning around. That's great.
Yeah, it's hard to beat that one.
I feel like I like him with all the bananas a lot.
The bananas is cute.
The very end, he is like taking a little nap.
Sinbad says goodbye to you.
And then Chandu like lifts his head up and kind of goes like, ah,
like that was kind of cute because he hadn't really talked
the rest of the ride, at least from what I could tell a video.
Just a little little moments.
You hear it in the in the clean audio of the song, but little like
it's great. The little you get is plenty.
Yeah, I like when he jumps on a drum, too.
That's what I was going to say. The drum he's being
that's the door now.
Oh, yeah. He's being carried by like four guys and a big drum.
And he's like he's on top of it like he's a conquering hero, which is really great.
That was another moment that that jumped out to me
because I think when the drum sound effect hits of him jumping on it,
I imitated it with my mouth.
He's in it goes, boom, boom.
And so that I went boom, boom, just because it seemed fun.
So that was the other one that stuck out to me.
I am sure that I got home and picked up the cats that I hadn't seen in several weeks
and who were over with the with their grandparents.
And I'm sure I picked one up and made them go boom, boom, boom.
I ascribed a lot of chandu to the cats.
Yeah, I recommend it with Edwin. Give it a shot.
He hates being picked up. I don't think that's it.
All right. Do not think that will go well.
Didn't work with the cats either.
He has some cat
tendencies, but is not a cat.
Yeah.
Standoffish sometimes wriggles away,
wriggles out of potentially cute situations.
Yeah, I was trying to think, like, is there a way to get even just a chandu
presence in some part?
Is it like chandu, a member of C Society of Explorers and Adventures?
Isn't there a way?
I, you know, I do.
Is Sinbad.
Well, sure. I mean, yeah, this is the thing.
Like I and maybe this is a more of the end of the conversation of the episode.
But like I do like it that it's only in Japan.
There is something really cool about this.
Don't clone it.
It should just be in Japan.
That being said, couldn't we get a little reference somewhere
just for the big Sinbad fans?
Yeah, just like incorporate them into the family a little more.
Yeah, I don't know.
Maybe it's adventure land, like Fortune Teller machine, like we did the.
Yes.
Is there some little you just put a coin in and and
Chandu bounces on a drum.
Yeah, that would be something like that.
I would love something like that, because, yeah, there's no.
I think really what your question, Scott,
like the question you just posed proves there's like really probably
not a bad Chandu moment as long as it's involving Chandu.
Is he tying someone up in the in the cave scene
where they're bringing the Uyghur? That is very cute.
I have to say, I think I really like watching the footage of this ride
is that scenes, stuff is set up or like stuff calls back previous scenes.
Like when Sinbad unlocks a giant lock with a big feather from the Bird Island.
Yeah, it's so.
And then that's so sweet to me.
And then you come around the corner and him and the giant Uyghur are jamming together.
It's it's just so nice.
It's just so like heartwarming.
And then later, like music is acknowledged is a big part of this, because, yeah,
he teaches the I think I saw it referred to as the residents of the Monkey Kingdom.
He teaches them how to play instruments.
He is, yes, he is spreading the song.
He is spreading the love and the knowledge of music around and playing.
And yes, as you said, that my favorite scene is that scene where he's playing with this Uyghur.
And as we alluded to earlier, the animatronic feels like it's 40 feet tall.
I'm sure it's not.
But in my memory, it's like the tallest thing I've ever seen.
Yeah. And it's so great.
It's right by or excuse me.
It happens like right during that soaring part of the song as well.
And I noticed that scene for particular.
I would start to go like get emotional again when we rode over and over.
Yeah. And the Uyghur's voice is so deep.
Yeah. Yes.
And he said he is very deep and Sinbad is much higher.
But they fit together so nicely.
There is harmony.
They are such different types of beings and the power of song brings them together.
It's so beautiful.
This is really the core of what this redo was from this kind of abrasive ride to the friendly
or warming ride that we love where it's is it a giant?
What do we call? I kept seeing it as the cave of the giant.
I think it's called a giant.
I just think of him as an ogre because he's green.
Oh, sure. Yeah.
I think, yeah, because he doesn't he's not like he doesn't have human form exactly.
And so giants, I think of as being just like big old people, people.
But he's not people.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Another weird and bulbous and yeah, has a particular color.
But so he in the original one,
it's it is sort of the midpoint of the ride and it's this very same grand vista
where you round a corner.
But in the old one, he is holding up to people like by their clothes or upside down,
dangling by their legs and kind of torturing them.
Might be people who deserve it, who are trying to plunder his riches.
Nevertheless, it was still like this is your centerpiece as a giant.
Oh, yeah. And then Sinbad's got his sword out and is like clearly about to go to battle
with the giant ogre.
That yeah, that scene with the original scene with the giant ogre,
like with the people in his hands reminds me of the Robert Smygall Shazam cartoon
where Shazam is like a genie, but he's like the most mean,
petty, petty, like, hurts people and like,
there's too much like, yeah, like the could just kind of like embarrass them once,
but instead, like, like punches them into the ground and makes them eat manure.
And then and then punches himself because he hates himself the most.
Yeah, yeah. It's a it's a very funny cartoon.
But this it does remind me of this where I'm like, man, that that giant can like
really do some harm to these people and like, fine, if they were bad.
Yeah, do some like throw them over to the side.
They were trying to steal his treasure after just trying to steal all those bird eggs.
But I just picture. Yeah, I picture him like making those guys eat manure
after the after after the boat is cleared, then the giant does something really cruel to them.
Chewing them kind of as slowly as he can.
Like, how can I get their meat off but still keep them alive?
What's the slowest I can eat these people?
He's going to torture you.
He seems like such a jerk.
You know, not it's not this harmony, this song, this beautiful moment.
Sorry, Jason. Good.
Oh, I was just going to say that talking about the original version of the show
reminds me of some stuff I pulled up of in America.
It is very popular every now and then to dig up
and do a Sinbad thing because it's extremely in the public domain.
And this the current version of this ride could not be further from,
let's say, this short lived 90 syndicated Sinbad.
Or is this hunk? Yeah.
From 96.
I don't know.
I also don't know who this like man who's got a real like sour look on his face.
Oh, that's Shandu.
That's human Shandu.
And then there, of course, is the 2003 Forgotten Dreamworks animated film
Sinbad Legend of the Seven Seas with what I am predicting is the most expensive
voice cast I have ever seen.
Brad Pitt, Catherine Zeta-Jones, Michelle Pfeiffer and Joseph Fong.
And then, of course, at Universal Florida, there was a show
I always really liked, the Eighth Voyage of Sinbad.
Not a lot of merchandise from that either.
But I found this on eBay a while back.
And I kind of know if this was the logo they were going with,
why they didn't sell a lot of this.
He is ripped.
Yeah, it's yeah, he's jacked. Yeah.
And mean, but like these are everyone looks mean.
Yeah. The female friend looks mean.
The little guy looks mean.
The mean crew. Really?
Yeah. Jason, you know, you bringing all this up.
I also found a few different versions of Sinbad that might be of some quick interest,
just because, yeah, this is obviously this character has been around forever
and been used in a lot of different ways.
And let me just some of the quick, quick highlights real quick here.
There was a Fantastic Four Sinbad crossover in 2001.
Chris Claremont wrote it. I have not read anything about it.
There was something called the Freedom Force TV show in 1978,
which had a super team, much like the League of Extraordinary Gentlemen,
with Merlin, Sinbad, Super Samurai, Isis and Hercules.
And then one of my favorite.
We're going to get the we're going to get a really expensive,
really miserable movie out of this six years.
Yes. And then one of my favorite topics,
junkie Anna Barbera cartoons.
There was something called Sinbad Junior and his magic belt.
And I'll just play a little just a snippet of this.
What that?
OK.
So, yes, Sinbad is Sinbad Junior is white.
And he has a he has a character named Salty the Parrot, which is a sidekick,
which is, of course, Mary Oceaneer's parrot sidekick's name in
See, the Society of Explorers and Adventures.
So I don't know.
They ripped. Disney ripped off Hannah Barbera
with a very classic show that everyone knows.
Sinbad Junior and his magic belt.
I think he just set off a corporate corporate war by stating that.
Yeah, I did. Yeah.
It's funny you mentioned Adam Barbera, because I was convinced
there was a Fox Kids or an ABC Morning Sinbad cartoon.
And then I I looked and what I was thinking of was a Hannah Barbera
cartoon from 1991 called The Pirates of Dark Water.
If you recall that area, yeah, which remember that features a character
named Niddler voice in the miniseries
premier by Roddy McDowell and later in the show by Frank Welker.
Oh, wow.
Jodie Benson's in this.
What's that little mermaid herself?
Jodie Benson is on this show.
I believe so. Yeah. As Tula.
That's interesting.
I have to I was about to say I have to go back and watch that.
But you know what? I don't.
The designs.
And Conk and the Lug Brothers.
You know what?
I think it's really good to draw the line.
I think like we don't have to watch everything.
We can be discerning.
A plea from the person who lives with Mike to Mike.
Oh, I'm the one who watches things.
I'm the watcher in the house.
She is the watcher in the house.
I am the collector. I'm Tana Lear to Vaughn.
She is watching the watcher.
And I'm Tana Lear to Vaughn to use Marvel characters.
Yes. Can I quick?
Let me make a point about the ride and the changeover.
I feel like there's I'm sure there's, you know, a good way to do a Sinbad ride
that's scary and more like the original stories.
But I don't think it's like a small world, slow moving boat ride.
That is, I think, where they went wrong, where it's like you want to do
something like scary and intense.
I think the ride system needs to be a little bit more intense as well.
You know what I'm saying?
Like, yeah, if you've just got a dark ride, but it's not a ride,
it's like you're just watching these intense adventures
instead of feeling like you're in the experience.
Yeah. And it's a mix of, I think, the slower moving ride
plus the small world style doll animatronics.
Like if it was fully pirates level, like human sized animatronics
mixed with a slow moving boat, right.
I think that's a different story.
We might be going, there's this very cool Sinbad ride
that's dark and creepy that's in Tokyo.
But I think that is why the first version of it really didn't work so well.
We associate boats with relaxation
and maybe even with cuteness or at least niceness.
But if it was like, even if it was a haunted mansion style,
it can be slow and scary, but it can't be a slow boat and scary.
Yes, that's what I think.
I mean, I can't think of anything that's contradicting what I'm saying that works.
But like, I feel like that's what it is.
It could be a slow boat, then where there's a big drop or something
that's all building to something bad happening.
Right. That's OK.
But like, but maybe that original ride had this air of malice.
Like we're going into worse and worse places and more dangerous situations,
but then it's not building to a drop or something.
Right. Exactly.
Like if you took if you took like Small World and you like put
like a weird like took the song away and then made it like it would immediately
be weirder because they're like dolls and toys.
I mean, it's already a weird ride that we all like.
But yeah, if you took the song away
and put this original Sinbad song in there, it would be odd.
It would be odd.
Or like, if you know those things where you take out a sitcom's laugh track
or something, if you just like hit every sound effect and there was no song
and just a bunch of mood drastically.
Right. Yeah.
Well, then you then what you've got is the gripping film Escape from Tomorrow.
They finally. Oh, man.
Small World is twisted, man.
Yeah, that's right.
It's hard to tell if I like Dismaland better or Escape from Tomorrow.
I'm always doing that sort of battle in my head.
Which one is more outrageous?
Which one more like cuts to the core?
Which one really gets to the truth of the matter?
It makes a question that we like this stuff.
Like, have you ever thought about that?
It's all a bunch of like
just like corporate crap shoved into our brains.
We're being fed, thought stew by a corporation by head chef Mickey Mouse.
Who was like, you know, wall was like wall, like literally
what like did hate crimes, he was like the worst man.
And he's frozen.
He's frozen. And he's frozen.
You know, he's got a head is frozen.
It's like under the gets deep under the castle.
It's hundreds of feet under the castle.
And he like friends with Hitler, too.
Like he was he was like a doll.
The room when a lot of that happened.
Also, I'm 14 and I just discovered the concept
that like adults don't always have the answers.
I just download a bunch of Bill Hicks, MP3s.
It's really it's all making me think, man.
I have a stepdad now and it's changed everything.
My yes, you know what?
If I really think about it, my complaint with this, all this stuff
is that these people don't know Disney well enough to know exactly
what to make fun of and think is bad.
They yeah, they're they need.
They need to listen to the podcast.
They need to hear from us if they want to do their real awesome
piece of satire, you know.
Yeah, that's what like I'm really most.
I'm really most upset with them just not knowing a lot like like not proper
ride maintenance or that actually what was a little too chummy
with Lenny Reif and stall.
But, you know, mostly let's get a union busting.
Yeah, the real stuff.
And head. Yeah.
Yeah. Saying these are not these are the surface level pair.
Say they're the real stuff and then you can use that tone.
Yeah. And then we'll talk.
Yes. Then we'll talk.
I mean, we won't talk. I don't want to.
I don't want to talk to you.
Any of these people.
We already know this.
Much like you find it out and then talk about yourselves.
Please don't say the phrase NFTs to me.
Yeah, I'm checked out on the whole thing. Absolutely.
I think maybe the one place that we haven't super visited
is the land of the monkeys,
which is also a pretty dramatic shift from the original to the current one.
Where OK, I think we all agree that this is maybe the most out of place
and the one where you feel the most like, all right,
so you feel the old ride in this one.
It is a happy scene, but the song stops.
We go into like a full percussive jam
and the monkeys are all mostly like drumming
and banging on stuff and shaking sticks.
And it's fun in the original.
They are bloodthirsty.
They want their terrifying you in the boat.
They're the first characters you feel like notice you
and they want to pounce on you and put holes in your neck.
It's really they're so crazy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, God, the monkeys have seen us.
It's really then they like it.
This is a little creepy.
The sullen teens we were just impersonating might think this is weird
that they do.
They kept all the monkeys the same, but they switched them from like
howling, scary faces to big old smiles.
And I think successfully, I think the monkeys are kind of lovable,
but they're pretty cute.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But boy, that monkey sequence, I was genuinely scary.
It's just like we was nuts.
All the monkeys mad at you.
I was reading that like part of the reason they changed is because children
were scared.
And so I'm watching the original ride through and I was like,
I guess is it like the fact that the like the giant ogre is big or something?
I guess I see it.
And then it gets to the monkeys and I was like, oh, no, thank you.
None for me.
I don't like these monkeys at all.
They're scary.
Yeah, yeah, not to redeem.
If we had all grown up in Japan, we'd be all of our podcasts would be about
being freaked out by these monkeys.
Yeah.
In the new one, though, you know what I really like in this sequence is how
Sinbad has a pretty jaunty, fun air for the most part.
And I think the most serious he is anywhere in the ride is banging on
drums with the monkeys.
He is so focused.
He is taking this jam seriously.
Very serious about his music.
Yeah, he's no Mark McGrath.
He doesn't have self-awareness.
He is there for the craft and there is no down.
He's a shoegator.
There's no pattern.
No, no, no.
Keep it down. I'm working.
Mm hmm. Yeah, maybe that's not one of his main instruments either.
Maybe that's one where he has to focus a little bit more like our mandolin.
Now, yeah, yeah, he can kind of do whatever while he's playing those.
But this one, he has to really sit and keep keeping time with the beat.
Yeah. Like if someone asked Sinbad, Sinbad, can you play drums?
The response would be, I can.
But, you know, like he's like, I'm just I'm warning you now.
You know, it's not the first instrument I learned.
Like I just picked it up like maybe like six months ago.
Right. Yes.
Yeah. If we're just having fun, it's fine.
If we're just having fun, but if we're putting down tracks,
you might want to call someone else.
Should do it. Yeah, someone else should do it.
In the wrecking crew.
Don't like, yeah, I'll jam, but yeah.
There's a quick I don't know, maybe that maybe I'm crazy about this.
If you were to sort of take the one at some of the animatronics of Sinbad,
does he look a little bit like some of these like directed DVD Pinocchio's?
Yeah. Oh, like a little bit like the Jonathan Taylor Thomas one.
Yeah, a little bit Disney style. It's like.
Yeah, it's like capitalizing off Disney releases.
Yeah. Maybe it's just because he's a small animatronic
and I'm thinking of Pinocchio, but if we didn't like him
and we didn't like the song and everything surrounding it,
would we say he was like almost getting into like ventriloquist dummy territory?
And not really. Not that I wouldn't necessarily go that far.
But you know what I mean? He's like. It's in the family.
I mean, that small world dolls are in the family of ventriloquists.
Yeah. Yeah.
So I think comparing it to like knock off straight to DVD releases is very accurate.
I think that's a fair assessment of the art style of the animatronics.
Yeah, it's not fully like Roberto Benigni Pinocchio boy,
but it's it's yeah, there again. Yeah, it's close. It's close.
But that's it's flirting with that. Sure. Sure.
But I think it makes it through. Yeah.
Oh, you still end up you still end up loving the guy.
It's weird that we aren't more creeped out by the the animatronic style.
Like this would be prime to be a little like scary.
But I think we love all his friends and neighbors. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. And all the other creatures like there at the end, there's the it's a whale right at the end.
I believe so. Yeah. Yeah. And that's cute.
That's cute. And it's it was sort of unbelievable to me.
I thought it was just going to be the silhouette.
And then you round the corner and they do it to you again.
You turn the corner and on your right hand side is a massive thing.
And it's like, I can't believe in America.
I feel like the the money people would just be like, you got it once.
Do we have to we have the second one?
We gave you got King Kong at the end, can't the recipe screens?
But here it's twice. It's unbelievable.
Yeah. That's one where I was watching the video and going like, this is this is grander in person.
I feel I think like, yeah, I think the darker the lighting is in a ride video,
the less it translates.
And this I just remember that room being super magical.
And it's kind of the last big thing before you return home.
But then the home, there's so much going on at home, too.
Like you're you're scarcely done after the whale.
It's still so. Yeah.
It's like I wish I had taken a notepad on the ride with me for when we eventually did this episode,
because, yeah, you can't in the ride views, you the ride throughs, you can't like see every it's like there's so much stuff going on.
And there's little details I'm sure we're missing that are very nice.
But, Jason, when you go to Tokyo soon, you know, you will have to point out that stuff that we've missed.
But yeah, I mean, they just shut down some theme parks there in some cities.
I don't think Tokyo, Disney, but Universal.
I'd say tomorrow.
No, no. But hopefully.
I'm just trying to get them to break the rule.
I think the intention was to save a lot of Tokyo until we all did it.
But like now, like there was a world where you you might have gone, you know, in 2020 or 2021.
But obviously, that hasn't worked out.
And yeah, I hope you get the shot.
Oh, for sure. Yeah.
Now that you have the shots. Yeah.
I phrase that on. Right.
But I mean, it worked since August. Yeah.
Yes, it's August. Yes.
Yeah, we all have for a long time.
The last scene is what you know, I think I declared this, I don't know in what ride.
But I think one of these little theme park recurring things that I've decided
I like is indoor fireworks.
I really like fireworks up on the ceiling in any case.
I, you know, in the Mexico ride and Epcot.
And there's so many here.
The return home is so great.
And then it's yours back to like that good luck on your journey.
And then how was your journey? Good.
Oh, wonderful.
Glad to hear it.
I think it's funny that when he gets back, they're like, congratulations.
I.
On what?
I would say that no matter what happened, even if he didn't rescue some some bird.
He could have come back
with a totally empty handed and they would have been like, well, those hands are full of friendship.
Congratulations.
That's right. This town loves each other.
And it's wonderful.
I yeah, it's it's just it's so grand.
Like how much of it is back in his town and it's all still it's all memorable
and compelling and I and boy, so long.
That is really the benefit of the boat ride that they can just go and go.
Yeah. And you don't get tired of it.
Mm hmm. And yeah, it's the boat ride.
Yeah. The nice thing about your small, the slow moving boat ride is you can pack stuff in
to be seen because it's not going to like you won't be like, well, they're going too fast
to be able to pay attention to all these details.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, what have we not called out?
Are there other details that we've that we've missed?
I mean, yeah, there's a there's a scene we didn't really talk about
that just seems to be like a nice exchange of vases
in him and a, you know, Sultan.
They just kind of like, here you go.
Good to meet you.
It's not like as dramatic as the bird one.
But in the original, right, I read that that was
that character was warning Sinbad about the dangers to come
with the monkeys because the monkeys are next.
Right, right.
So that character is like, beware, there are
scary creatures and you're heading into the unknown.
And then monkeys.
And then it like gives him time to form a plan.
Yeah. And instead, in this one, it's like, hey, Vase, teach me this song.
We want to just absolutely fill your boat with treasures.
Just everywhere he goes there.
The monkeys, by the end of hanging out with the monkeys
and teaching the monkeys the song, they're like, take
the biggest boatload of bananas you've ever seen in your life.
That's how much we appreciate our time with you.
To the point where when I was rewatching it, I was like.
Did they bring bananas to the monkeys?
No, the monkeys are giving them a boatload of bananas
out of the goodness of their heart.
That one hadn't occurred to me. That's wonderful.
That is nice. And I do get to a ton.
He gets that.
I was about to say, I really like the look of the fake bananas, too,
before we started talking.
Yes.
They say like, you know, those fake bananas look great.
Something fake fruit on rides, I'm sure like not always like.
Attracted to the fruit like I am to these bananas.
I found these bananas might be a good if we're if we're doing fake final fours.
That's an interesting one.
What's food on a ride?
Noted. Oh, yeah.
Oh, Horizon says all that future food in it.
All those combo fruits.
Yeah. And then there's a gingerbread house on Mansion Holiday.
Yeah. Rare thing that was in the smell and then it can be in the food.
We may have it. I think you guys got to do it.
That's pretty good. Yeah.
One. So I don't know why fake is always part of it, but.
I like it.
It's the artistry.
Yes.
The art.
Admiring the craft. You're praising the craft.
Absolutely. Yeah.
Well, I mean, if that brings us sort of around the bend and the journey's ending.
Yeah, that is the question.
If like in some bizarre version of events where they add a bunch of extra Disneyland
or California Adventure over where there's hotel parking currently and like, why not?
You know what? We have the space.
Let's put let's let's do Sinbad.
Maybe America will like it.
I can't see this happening, but would you be happy because you can go to whenever you want?
Or would it be less special in a way?
It would be less special, but I'm not.
If it was the same ride, I couldn't be mad.
Yeah. And I think it would be too elitist
to be like, no, don't bring it here.
People should have to go to Tokyo to experience it.
It's like, well, not everyone can go to Tokyo.
Let the people know the glory of Sinbad and become acquainted with the compasses of their hearts.
Yes, exactly.
Yeah.
That's more important when it comes down to it.
Much like Sinbad travels the world, the Sinbad ride should travel the world and teach more people
this song.
I agree.
And there's some truly fucked vibes in parts of Orange County.
And I think if they all could learn about the compass of your heart and the true treasure
of friendship, like that might help.
Yeah.
I don't know, help some people chill.
Get that Aryan nation on into Sinbad.
And I think they're going to shape right up.
I think it's a heartwarming story of like American and Japanese imagineers coming together
with a great musical talent of our time to tell a folktale of Arabian and Persian origin.
And yeah, I'm assuming they would think that too, you know, some of the weirdos in Orange County.
Maybe we could at least get to the children.
Yeah.
I'm just imagining, like all the things that are bothering us in the recent worlds,
like that you see like up and off in the distance, you see like a Q save the children rally,
and then you round the corner and everybody's dropped their signs and they're just,
and they're singing with Sinbad.
We'll be amazed at the movement of the animatronics,
like hitting their palms against their foreheads going, I can't believe I was that foolish.
What was I thinking?
Sinbad is personally texting people's like mothers and uncles and aunts.
Like, here's why, here's the proof that it's wrong.
Mr. Watson, Mr. Watson, it's wrong.
Here's a scene of Sinbad having a conversation with his family off Facebook.
Wow. Sinbad needs to tour.
Sinbad needs to go everywhere, I guess.
Yeah.
Every state put a Sinbad ride in every city.
Wow.
Yes. Okay. I've been sold on that. Nevermind.
Yeah. Yeah. I actually know what needs to happen is that yes, a separate ride is built in every
state, a freestanding Sinbad ride.
It's its own park now.
I think before you know it. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
It's an embassy.
Sinbad embassy.
And it's like, there's four Sinbad rides in each embassy, the same ride, exact ride.
But yeah, you build one at just like, without telling him, build it
somewhere on the grounds of Mar-a-Lago. There's plenty of space.
Oh yeah.
And then Trump goes on at once and now he's like offering heaps of bananas to everyone he encounters.
He's the most generous man now.
What a world. Can you imagine? A Sinbad world, a Sinbad influenced world.
Life is the greatest adventure.
It sure is. It sure is.
And well, and on that note, Lindsay Katai, you survived podcast The Ride.
A super sentimental one, a nice one. I thought it was great.
And let's exit through the gift shop. Is there anything you'd like to plug?
Well, it was a pleasure to be on the podcast. Thank you for having me.
And if people have not watched it yet, the Cartoon Network show I wrote on,
Infinity Train, all four seasons are now available on HBO Max.
That is the end of the show, sadly. The fourth season is the final.
Please, please watch it. Very proud of the work that we did on that show.
And you can also check out my podcast Teen Creeps, where
me and my co-host Kelly Nugent talk about YA pulp fiction of the 80s and 90s,
such as Arl Stein, Christopher Pike, etc.
Check both of those out. Infinity Train this season features a, I don't hope this is not a
spoiler, but a large pig baby voiced by J.K. Simmons. And it's delightful.
Wow.
That's just that's a specific I want to say. There's a lot of great.
I was yes, Lindsay wrote that episode and I just wanted to give everyone a little treat.
Much like Pig Baby demands a little treat.
Yes, there that is. It's a very strange episode.
And I feel like listeners of this podcast would like that one specifically,
but the whole series as a whole as well.
You know, it's just refreshing to hear the phrase Pig Baby demands a treat,
and it's not referring to me for once.
I modeled him after you.
Oh, thank you so much.
But that my real I don't know.
Get some of that Oscar winner juice.
Yeah.
Hey, as for us, you can follow the compass of your heart to us on all the socials at
podcast the ride as merch available at our tea public store and for three bonus episodes every
month. Check out podcasts, the ride, the second gate at patreon.com slash podcast the ride.
That was fantastic. Everyone enjoy Disneyland.
If you're there now, someone might be listening to this who's there now.
If you're going in the next week or so, have a great time.
We're hoping to go as soon as we can.
Lindsay, hopefully see you soon in person and do a podcast.
That would be very nice.
Yeah. And interrupt your breakfast again.
Yeah, I really miss sneaking into my kitchen and getting some cereal and then
scooting back upstairs. I really miss it.
Well, in the inner in the interjects, they're like,
hearing us say something wrong and correcting.
Going the world needs to hear me on this.
And wait, so the final thing has to be I don't have it at my disposal.
What is that? What's the nice message of this ride that has to be the end of the episode?
About friendship.
Oh, the greatest treasure of all is friendship.
Yeah. Wow. That was beautiful.
Wow. Big baby.
All right. Well, let's say that's the first and last instance of that.
You brought that on yourself. Nobody replied it to you.
You know, I thought it was done. I thought we had moved on.
And sometimes you can't predict a callback. So fair enough.
It wouldn't help to juxtapose that awful phrase with the nice one.
No, let's think about the nice one. Friendship.
Think about that.
Thanks for listening. All right.
Bye.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson,
Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.