Forever.
Dog.
Warning, said the Lord to uncharismatic creationist Ken Ham.
Thou must recreate Noah's Ark in Kentucky and make it full of dinosaurs, depressed animatronics
doing chores, and unlimited soda refills.
If thou faileth, the earth shall be smoten, and lo, Ken built this ark, and it was bad.
Today, the Ark Encounter on a special Easter podcast, The Ride.
A most mournful Good Friday to everyone.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, a show hosted by three very good men, much like Noah's sons,
Shem, Ham, and Japeth.
We're the Shem, Ham, and Japeth of podcasting.
I'm the Shem Scott Gardner.
I guess, I don't know.
Well, Japeth is closest to Jason.
So Jason is Japeth.
You know, I thought I was a given for Ham, but I guess-
Oh, what am I saying?
It was right there.
I was right there.
We've been doing this podcast for years now and you didn't?
That's the lowest hanging fruit I've ever heard.
That's a good Ham.
There's an evil Ham today that's gonna come up a lot.
Oh, that's right.
Maybe you don't want to be associated with Ham.
But that's the Easter, that's the traditional Easter feast, you know?
Yeah, well in two days, all of us will want to be associated with Ham as much as possible,
including Mike Carlson, who I guess has shifted to Japeth.
I am Japeth, but I like to think of myself as a Ham.
I know we're three Cliffords and our listeners are all Cliffords, but for this episode, we're
three Hams.
They love it.
Three Hams and our listeners will be known as Hams, just for this week, this holy week.
That's fine to me.
Whatever definition you want to take, but maybe yes, maybe not a Ham in the way.
We're certainly not related to Ken Ham, the guy who figured out the evil Walt of today's
park.
Just to be clear before we get into it, this is the beginning of Easter weekend and last
year we kind of started a tradition of talking about religious theme parks.
Last year we talked about Orlando's very bizarre Holy Land experience, a place where there
are crucifixions on the daily.
And I didn't know if it could get more bizarre or maybe more contemptible.
Contemptible is the word that I have written down multiple times.
I stole that from you.
You said that before we started recording and I really liked the word and it's a correct
word.
That's the Ark encounter, a place where you can see Noah's Ark in the exact proportions
that it was built in Noah's time, which as we learned from all this was what, like 4000
years ago?
A couple years ago.
Really?
Yeah.
Right before the Pilgrim times.
This definitely didn't happen in a, well, no, maybe it did happen in America.
I'm not sure where that lands in the whole creationist mythos.
Maybe Noah's Ark actually did happen in Kentucky.
Oh, that's yes, that's a very good chance.
There's a lot of, I kept writing down the word retcon in my notes while watching interviews
with Ken and for just a little context, I'm sure we talked last year, I had virtually
no religious teaching as a youth.
Jason is similar?
Yes.
No, we went to church most Sundays.
We went to like a very chill Protestant church, although it was Presbyterian and there's some
kooky branches of Presbyterianism.
A lot of it going back to I think the origins of Calvinism, which is, I believe, the idea
that when you are born, it's already predetermined whether you are good or bad.
And I didn't get any of that shit.
I got like what the Simpsons got, you know, going to church.
So that's okay.
Yeah.
Simpsons stuff seems like, yeah, Simpsons seemed like a pretty like passable, you know,
that's a kind of religious, you could be and be fine.
Yeah.
I mean, the thing that I always bring up when I talk about it is like a lot of pastors who
would start a sermon by trying to be relatable to the crowd of like, you know, I was at the
mall this week and I saw a group of teens goofing around and that reminded me of the
Apostles.
You know, they would just make very tenuous connections of like, I was watching America's
funniest home videos and so pretty harmless stuff.
But I know a lot of people who have the worst, much worse story.
In some ways, the original Biker Mice from Mars were the three wise men.
That's a pastor who really studied TV Guide.
He actually did the deep dive.
Yeah.
He wanted to really relate to the kids.
So yeah, I mean, I, we would go once in a while to church and, but I didn't go to any
sort of religious school.
I vaguely, I knew probably religious most from the Simpsons and the things.
Yeah.
Oh, wow.
Wow.
That's an interesting context for it.
Yeah, completely.
Yes.
Raised hardcore Catholic, which again, on the scale of things is not the hardest of
core that there could be.
And all this was making me flash back to what did creep me out when I would come across
it because there's not enough, like I was pretty comfortable with Catholicism, but then
you were always right around the corner from ickier stuff and there's not like, there's
not enough full Catholic media to avoid the ickier stuff.
Like you'd catch little glimpses of it.
My parents would do their best to say, well, that's not really what we believe, which I
appreciated because boy, as we'll find today, there is some, some big time icky stuff.
The other thing that I was flashing back to is that, yeah, I was full Catholic for not
my elementary school, but my middle school and my high school.
So a lot of Catholicism in the education, including that my high school theater program,
which Joe Rody is a graduate from, he got his start painting sets for my, the school
I eventually went to.
We did, and I say we, I wasn't really part of it.
I was the crew that filmed the play and there was a play that was done called Noah and nobody
Maybe don't know the play Noah and that is because it was written by the theater director
of my high school.
This was an original production and like a big long play with lots of numbers and you
know, the way they have to cast that stuff, Jason, you know this where it's like, all
right, we need a 90 parts because we got to fit everybody in.
So this was a massive sprawling production where you aren't even on the arc until act
two.
Like you have to go through the creation of man.
God is a character in the show and you have to see first sin and a song by a sexy snake
who's in like pleather pants in sort of like Brittany era, early 2000s.
It was, he was seducing man.
But when, in just in thinking about Noah's arc, I was flashing back to my fondness for
Noah, which really was an incredible production and which I wish made it past my high school
and was something that all high schools had to do, especially because there, you know,
you know what wasn't on Noah's arc were animals that are made up like unicorns, unicorns,
not on the arc.
And this is addressed in my high school play because there is a song where the unicorns
are late.
They didn't get to the arc on time because the wife unicorn was fiddling around with
chores at home.
The husband was there on time.
Women love to sacrifice their own well-being to do chores?
To do, yeah.
Even in the face of the biblical flood, of the big flood, the woman, the wife is still
like tidying things and they address this in the scene.
Where were you?
I was straightening up at home.
But the flood is coming.
I don't know.
Habit, I guess.
Where is the arc?
The arc has left already.
And then it's, I would post this if I didn't want to like embarrass the people I don't
know who are in the production, but I have tapes of it because I filmed it.
I was media crew.
So there's this incredible song and boy, I would love The Arc Encounter more if there
was something as creative as this on it.
This great song where the character of God's favorite dove swoops down and sees how sad
it is that the unicorns miss their chance to be in the arc and get saved.
So she has a new plan and the plan is to make them live in the realm of imagination where
it's like here you will be in our dreams.
You may not get to thrive and reproduce, but you'll be in the hearts of man forever, which
is conveyed in a song that is mainly ripped off from Lucy in the Sky with Diamonds that
even has lines about tangerine sunsets and stuff like that.
And then it's a dance done by two human unicorns with like big plastic horns glued to their
heads.
Oh my goodness.
And you can't just blur all these people out and post this for us?
It would take a while.
This would be a process.
Maybe.
Yeah.
So if I could get it to a post studio, what I can do is recite from memory the thing that
the dove says at the end of the when it's time to do our part for the unicorns.
Let me make sure I think I knew because this is this was in 2001 and it's still burned
into my brain.
So let me just see if I can do this.
Okay.
Angel friends come now it's time from the floodwaters they must climb.
This is a part I don't remember very well.
From this realm they must depart.
Lift them high high up in the human heart.
Place them in their destination in the realm of imagination.
And then the song is like you'll be always and forever till all the stars have been wished
away and then some psychedelic stuff.
Wow.
I know this so well.
I've thought about this like nonstop since almost 20 years ago at this point.
That almost sounds like the Phil Collins Hercules soundtrack.
Yeah.
Tarzan you mean.
I'm so sorry.
That's the yeah.
Excuse me.
A little bit.
Well it's that like son of man.
There is that that grandeur to it.
I feel like if only roadie had still been around.
If he was still checking out the alma mater maybe he could have seen it and then got it
made in the part.
He this would have been a shoe in I think for Animal Kingdom.
No alive right after Tarzan's done.
There had to have been.
I mean obviously they want to Disney wants everything to be very secular but what a great
idea.
Well Disney they did know in they've done know actually several times they did know
in Fantasia 2000 where the animals marched to the graduation theme which was distracting
to everyone.
And did you know that there was a Tony Danza modern version of Noah done by Disney for
the wonderful world of Disney in the late 90s.
Oh my God.
This is unfindable.
There's not even clips on YouTube.
No one is bothered to archive this.
Wow.
It's like only barely there that a record even exists much like biblical texts.
It's gotten erased to the sands of time.
And Mike the angel who tells Tony he needs to be a modern carpenter that he needs to
build an ark Wallace Sean.
No way.
Yes.
Wow.
How does nobody know this for it being as an angel named Zack.
Wallace Sean is the angel Zack.
How did you come upon this then or did you see it when I saw it in a dream.
God himself spoke to me.
No I was just looking up like depictions of Noah and there besides the weird there was
a look at was it Aaron off schema Aaron Austin and I'm Bren Evan Almighty.
Obviously Crow.
Yeah.
By the way this arc experience taught me I think Evan Almighty lied to me about some
of this stuff.
You know it wasn't a funny weatherman.
Yeah.
Being betrayed by Evan and Evan Almighty.
That's wild.
I mean I guess no I mean I knew the story of Noah.
That actually I think I guess as I was saying that is like kind of been secularized to some
degree.
I mean you leave out all the other like I mean God tells Noah what to do.
But other than that as a kid it's just like oh there was a lot of water and he saved all
the animals like that story is fine.
Like you don't have to necessarily.
There's nothing terribly and you and we'd grow up watching I think you could be non-religious
and end up seeing the Ten Commandments or even some amount of Jesus stuff.
Even Disney made Jesus.
There's a thing about the called small one about the donkey who's there in the nativity.
Yes.
So like Disney wouldn't avoid it.
I think today they would but 80s 90s they'd still go there.
People who even aren't religious can acknowledge like there's some good stories.
There's a reason these are like inspirational stories creationist stories.
But then sometimes they take a little bit of a wrong turn.
Look I my feeling with a religion I take the Kevin Smith dogma approach.
I happy but everyone believe what they want to believe as long as it's not like you're
not starting a war you're discriminating against people like that sucks.
That stuff sucks.
Yeah I don't disparage anyone their faith but Young Earth creationism.
Get the fuck out of here man.
Get out of here with that shit like and the fact that you are trying to this place the
Ark encounter is trying to use it as like elementary school kids come learn the real
truth like I feel like that is such a fine.
There's a real slippery slope from the earth is 6000 to 10000 years old to the vaccines
got 5G chips and Donald Trump gonna be president in August anyway.
You know this is exactly what I was leading into this.
Yeah I think you know in considering my religious upbringing and what I object to about it and
this was not my parents.
There was no trickery going on with my parents but you'd run into trickery you'd run into
like here this is a nice thing we're going to tell you about and then it's fire and
brimstone and something even crazier than fire and brimstone.
I was recalling a thing where my mom seeing that I was getting into CDs found me a magazine
called breakaway magazine and this was a cool magazine.
There's a surfer on the front you know like I like and she gave it to me and said this
is for young people this is there's actually they talk about some of the albums you listen
to I thought oh no kidding well then I must check this out this magazine and there was
there was in fact a review of the Beastie Boys Hello Nasty potentially my favorite album
at the time which just throws the whole thing under the bus because of the one line I be
smoking roaches in the vestibule so therefore the Beastie Boys are damned for all eternity
how dare they befoul vestibules but then I kept going then I like what that well I this
isn't I don't want to read about why my album is bad what's this thing who made breakaway
magazine focus on the family.
There it is.
James Dobbs said yeah and you know that that's like I can't remember the specifics about
but that's like that's horrible hateful bigoted like an awful organization.
That guy and the Catholic League if you remember the offshoot of the Catholic Church the Catholic
League who I think pretty much the Catholic Church washed their hands of a long time ago
that was the guy who was most mad at things like dogma or any popular culture after like
1950 you know.
Yeah.
Yes yeah did I say last time we talked about religious stuff how much I remember it wasn't
my church but I go on a vacation and then the other church we didn't go to the preachers
completely upset about dogma and about maybe the movie kids I remember that wasn't the
same year but I remember a sermon about kids I remember a sermon about powder.
Powder.
Yeah something wrong with powder I don't remember why.
I think powder is a creepy movie.
I think he embraces the supernatural phenomenon right like he's got some powers but they're
not necessarily from God.
Did he have a problem with John Travolta's phenomenon?
No I think phenomenon is wait no phenomenon is.
Michael is the angel John Travolta will be.
But phenomenon is supernatural stuff.
He like makes a spoon like float.
Phenomenon is not Michael.
Michael and Michael is not powder.
And neither of them are K packs.
Neither of them are K packs.
No.
What could be.
I was saying before we started recording that it's a very funny week to be doing this episode
because we're coming off like the satanic panic of the Lil Nas X Montero music video
where he grinds on and then murders Satan and takes his crown.
And there's like a sneaker sneaker customizer doing a limited run of like these sneakers
each have a single drop of human blood in it.
And every maniac right wing swab came out of the woodwork just be like I stand on guard.
I stand on guard against you and the devil.
And meanwhile Lil Nas X is just having the time of his life giving them the business
of being like here's the storyboards we made.
I use the screen grab of SpongeBob and Patrick to inspire this.
Like he's just just having a ball.
And while every weirdo freak hungover from the Trump administration is just like worried
about the devil.
Silent on multiple shootings in the country.
But this video that's like the South Park movie.
Yeah. Like Halloween Horror Nights makeup.
I've hit miniature golf balls into more realistic demons mouths like.
And it's fun. He's having fun.
The guys have a fun like.
I'm going to watch this video.
He's I'm not you know like I'm not in the age range to where I should be.
Like I'm not watching a lot a lot of Lil Nas X.
But boy it seems like he's having a blast.
Just everything.
Dancing around those kindergartners all singing the song with him.
He's just he's he's having the time of his life.
Yeah. Well, yeah.
Still this kind of thing.
But while Satan is an ongoing issue and fear, you might not realize the ongoing the biggest issue,
which is all of us thinking that the earth is more than six thousand years old, which is apparently
the primate we've all been indoctrinated.
I assume most listeners to this show.
Maybe you think that the earth is very young.
I'm not sure.
If if if if you're a younger creationist, then maybe you already stopped listening after Jason said to fuck yourself.
But get out of here.
Probably probably stop listening now.
That's what what this whole thing comes from.
And now I didn't know any of this going into it.
I think maybe a couple of listeners had said this arc encounter thing is funny.
And I you know, you got to assume that if something has a lot of money and a theme park gets made,
that it's probably a little more fundamentalist.
But I did not know the whole agenda here.
I'd maybe heard of Ken Ham in passing, but I'd never married all this.
And now I know how it all works.
And maybe I wish I didn't.
Yeah, it's yeah.
I was hoping that when we did this, it was going to be like, and it is a big boat.
And here's the like most dry, basic like.
And then he put all the animals on.
And there you go. Isn't it fun to see the little robot animals?
And it's a lot more it's a lot more.
What is the word I'm looking for here?
I kept thinking about like loaded.
Sacrilegious. Oh, yeah.
Like, you know how like they were so obsessed with Star Wars,
Galaxy said with Bato about the narrative and making sure everything fits and timeline and whatever that is.
It's that times 10 only with real world implications.
Yeah, yeah.
And if you deny one ounce of this, then you burn for all eternity.
Right. But also they can make up whatever crap they want.
But also, yes, that's also a part of it as well.
Yeah. Yeah. And they can get tax breaks from the county and state.
Yeah. Which happened when I came up with the Holy Land experience, too.
This is a good way to get it.
Disney might want to consider getting more religious because they're proposing all this new stuff across the street.
We talked about it on the Patreon.
And if some of it was religious, maybe I definitely Orange County would pay for it.
There's a crystal cathedral down the five.
That's a good thing.
Or I think they'd be psyched for some Disney religious park.
I think, you know, if if at this point, Disney is its own religion.
And a lot of this anger that people have had historically over religion,
I think, has moved into places like Disney or Star Wars, The Last Jedi.
I think it's a different it's moving there.
That's where we're headed, I think. I think you're right.
Yeah. Well, because the tales everyone grew up reading are less and less the tale of Shem, Ham and J.
Pitt, more, you know, Iron Man and Black Widow and what have you.
Methuselah died at age nine hundred and sixty nine.
I learned that on the sign outside.
But like how old was Seg L Superman's grandfather when he died?
Like we should know this.
These are all the same.
We're all playing in the same ballpark here.
It's just, again, these characters have real world implications.
Yeah. Yeah.
I almost think the Holy Land experience is a little better because not better.
That's not the word.
Less less egregious.
Yeah, less egregious, because it's just like this is what it was like back.
This is what the Bible talks about.
I mean, I'm sure there was some weird stuff there.
But yeah, there's a lot more like hook them while they're young stuff at the Ark encounter,
where it was like prosperity gospel like grifters.
Maybe I'm just I have a soft spot for that because that's a very American con.
That's like a very American to con people out of their money
with the promise of like snake oil and like good luck or whatever is very American.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We've sort of we've said so they built this giant Ark.
He built this giant like, I guess, accurate maybe to a scale.
Well, the cubit cubit.
Exactly the cubit.
Yeah, they had to choose what cubit, which version of cubit.
And then they settled on cubits aren't even the same height.
Right. Well, yeah, no, it's not.
It's not clear depending on which book you're reading or whatever.
I saw it was six hundred eleven miles of wooden boards used
where if you laid them all out, they would go from Kentucky to Philadelphia.
Yes. And it's like in some parts, it's seven stories tall.
Some parts, it's five stories tall. Yeah.
One and a half football fields wide, I believe, is what Mr.
Ham said. Yeah.
And divided into three three levels inside with different.
I hesitate to use the word exhibits, but I can't think of a better word.
Well, almost cubbies.
Cubbies of propaganda.
Even propaganda feels too big to use.
Sculpture cages.
There's cages where sculptures have to live.
Some of what caught my eye and probably a lot of people's about all this
was the headline from from Vice.
As with the Holy Land experience, these things exist for vice people to go
and be mad at and which say, thank you guys for going.
So we don't have to
their headline.
This one hundred million dollar Noah's Ark theme park is a boring homophobic mess.
So sounds great. Sounds like a blast.
And if it did, we not say Williamstown, Kentucky,
which is probably the closest major city is Cincinnati, Ohio.
And if you're looking it up on a map, it's it's on one Ark and counter drive.
That's how you know you got a lot of money.
Yeah. When you get the street named after what your themed attraction is,
it's like, OK, you either spend some money or the state gave you a lot of money.
Yeah. Yeah.
Um, we did. Yeah.
I'm a big guy. Yeah, we really did.
The so the the man behind this, the the the
Bizarro John Hammond, I guess, is is Ken Ham.
A little bit of the name in there, too.
Ken Ham is an extremely vocal creationist.
And what is creationism?
Well, I mean, his specific thing is that
it's very anti evolution, first of all, and that is because he is a Bible literalist.
He is the the kind of Christianity.
And this is like the heart, almost the hardest core in a way,
where every bit of the Bible is exactly true, and especially the book of Genesis,
which is the the formation of the world and man and everything.
And his organization is called Answers in Genesis.
So it seems like a lot of it's almost like mainly those first couple books.
He is just down to the word.
All of this is exactly true, which has a bunch of implications,
one of them being that the earth is only six thousand years old.
And why? Because there's no date in there.
Well, it's because there's all of the so and so, baguette, so and so, so and so,
baguette, so and so.
So from that, they're able to determine how far back it goes.
And this takes you to Noah and this takes you to Jesus Christ.
But it's all bizarre because that ends you up with, yeah,
a bunch of people who are like 500 years old or 900 years old.
Yeah. So why did people stop being 900 years old?
Do we have an answer for that?
There's a lot of tenuous justifications, like Mike said, retcons, where it's like,
OK, so after the flood, everyone stopped being thousands of years old.
And now they're just hundreds of years old.
And of course, the Tower of Babel splintered language.
And that's why we all speak different languages.
And and there's a lot of this stuff.
And it it I asked my dad, my dad went to Catholic school, too.
And I was like, did you encounter a lot of this, like sort of literalism in school?
He's like, no, his teachers were all mostly like Jesuit priests,
like the keepers of knowledge or people from the neighborhood.
And like he told me about one teacher who was like,
if you believe everything in the Bible happened literally, you are an asshole.
Like, that's the education he got.
Like, like, you know, you got to be a little blunt to get people's attention
in Northeast Philadelphia.
So, you know, they were pushing like this is to inspire you,
this is to teach you to be a good person, teach you the lesson.
Like, you're not supposed to track this exactly literally.
Yeah, it would be like tracking Batman's 80 year history and going, OK,
this all did happen to one man and I know all of it and it's in here
and I can explain it to you and I can explain it to you how it works.
Like any sort of long, not thought out as far as being a giant piece
of like multi-year entertainment was committed completely to memory
and you couldn't deviate from it ever.
Like that's watching videos of Ken Ham walking through here,
which I've watched several at this point.
He has it's it's cool.
It's funnier than any like comic book nerd you've ever heard
talk about anything he likes or any any different piece of trivia.
Like he knows exactly how to justify it.
And some of it seems like maybe he's just bullshitting in the moment
because he hasn't figured out like it's impossible to justify everything
as being truly everything that truly happened.
But he's did everybody watch Bill Nye walk through the arc with him?
No, no, I know this exists.
And I think this is why Ken, I think Ken Ham is
what is more well known because of these two Bill Nye
debates that he has done.
I think Bill Nye seemingly on the opposite side, wanting to challenge him,
completely raised the profile of Ken.
Yes. And that's maybe not a good thing.
And I think on this show, I've once in a while been critical
that I'll watch Bill Nye and I go, I don't know that he knows
that much about what he's talking about.
He just says like seemingly a basic information, basic knowledge.
But Ken Ham apparently was a science teacher.
Which is funny, which is very funny.
So weird. They had some sort of debate.
I did not watch that.
They had some sort of creationist versus science debate.
But then years later, Bill Nye came to the arc and walks.
It's like a two hour video.
A walking debate, they call it a walking debate.
And Bill Nye is just upset the whole he's perturbed from the get go.
And Ken Ham is like he's a he's a soft spoken English
English gentleman, I believe, right?
Australian, Australian, excuse me.
Can I read a quote about him for context?
I this credit to the reporter, which this is the Atlantic, I believe.
Ham is Australian, a rare, rare sort of Australian
in that he is religiously devout and completely humorless.
That really good like sums up the vibe because, boy, this is a dry
just like non
like doesn't project, does it like isn't like giving you the bit?
You know, if he's the Walt of this place, they need, I think,
maybe somebody with some higher energy to be a hype man,
because this is a very sleepy Walt to be their Walt.
He's like he he's like dead inside.
He's truly like so like there should be Bill Nye is looking at something
that says that the earth is six thousand years old and something about glaciers.
And he's like, it's like, how do you know this?
Why why do you think this?
What what is the justification for?
And he's like, are you just come here to be upset?
Let's just talk like let's talk.
And he's like just like even keeled and Bill Nye's just like,
I don't understand this.
He's like, well, how would you know how old ice is?
How would you know how old ice is?
He goes, he goes, is it dated?
And he goes, yes, it is dated.
You can look at it.
You look at molecules, you can look.
There's a way to tell.
And it's just he's like from the get go, very upset with him.
And it's very funny, honestly, I was enjoying it.
I need to watch the rest of it.
It's like two hours long.
Yeah, I saw him saying that there are obviously the entire arc is fraught
with errors, but he said the third floor has not one correct fact anywhere.
Not a drop.
My favorite part is I zoomed to the middle and there's a part where people
start gathering and like ganging up on Bill Nye and it's just people are like,
hey, do you do you have a soul?
Do you think you have a soul to Bill Nye?
And he's like, I don't know.
I'm not sure.
I don't think.
And then, and then finally, Mr.
Ham, Ken Ham is he good.
He just goes, he goes, okay, so you, he goes, you believe that when you die,
that nothing, nothing will happen.
There's nothing after that.
And Bill Nye goes, yeah, that's, that's what I believe.
He goes, okay, what do you care then?
What do you care that we're doing this?
Like, it's just literally like he hits his breaking point where he's like,
just give us our fun.
What?
Who cares?
Like that's his, that's ultimately where Ken Ham's argument ends up where it's
just like, just let us do this.
Why are you mad at us?
I mean, that there's like a kernel of truth there.
And it was like, yeah, it was just a private experience for you and your weird
little creep friends.
But then this guy is like, you know,
the started getting heat from politicians of like, you're not inviting.
Are you encouraging elementary schools to come to this?
And he's like, yes, elementary schools should come to this.
And it's like, OK, no, no, stop it right now.
That's a good line. Yeah, it's starting to regard it as a as a museum,
especially because here's one that I was deep on the website for the Arc Encounter.
I found the tab overnight adventures, looking for the perfect group
adventure or youth retreat.
Spend a night aboard Noah's Arc.
This behind the scenes opportunity is especially popular with youth groups
and Christian schools.
So not only inviting children, but inviting children to spend the night
spending, spend a night in the Arc.
Noah did 40. Why can't you do one?
And also the Arc kind of sucks.
So who cares? Like, that's not even that fun.
Completely sucks.
Like it's really drab in there.
Really boring in there.
There's some like, yes, static animals and a few robots.
But like I could see a situation where like, you know, it was one of the most
hateful places, but I'd go, well, at least the animatronics are good.
You know, at least.
Yes, right.
Um, yeah, which if that was the case, then,
yeah, sure. And you go and you laugh.
But hey, they put on a good little show.
But this is different here.
And let me just jump somewhere into the middle of the park to help make this point.
You guys might have seen this, that there is something.
You know, we're saying that it's drab.
Well, it's not drab over in the part fairy tale Arc.
It's fairy tale Arc.
This is what you imagine Noah's Arc to be like.
It's this big molded plastic sign with a bunch of really friendly
elephants and monkeys and giraffes all poking out of various corners
and the top of the Arc.
And this is the Noah's Arc we remember from cartoons and from books.
And you look inside and it's a children's library.
And there's a it's it's a bunch of Noah's Arc books in there.
It's all kinds of, you know, a little piece of literature that tell the tale of Noah.
But it turns out that once you actually go under this friendly cartoon
Toontown sign, that it's just a thing saying all of these books are
evil because they don't show the reality.
Noah's Arc was not fun.
It was arduous.
And these cartoon elephants and giraffes, they undermine
this serious this seriousness of the oh, jeez, Jason.
Oh, this is what you've pulled up.
The seven D's of deception, one of them deceptively cute.
Discrediting the truth.
This is you've shown us like this is for two year olds.
This is an even more simple cartoon.
This is there's like a bad bar on there, like really simple,
cute birds and giraffes who could hate this drawing.
I guess Ken Ham could hate the drug.
How confusing.
So it's like cute animals and stuff.
No, not cute animals.
That's evil. No, don't make it palatable and understandable for children.
Make them stare at this plaque that says, why does a loving
God allow so much death and suffering?
Now, that's a cool field trip.
I yeah. What parents?
You'd you'd you'd want to think that there's a lot of parents
who went to this were imagining a fun cartoon thing that kids might like
and were upset at what they found.
Like people that I would hope that there are parents who agree with all this
and went and said, this sucks.
And Mike, you brought up the thing that has not come up yet, because
I it seems to me that with
taking Genesis literally and all of this bizarre.
All right. So people were 700 years old.
Yeah, that's right. And I used to only 6000.
OK, sounds good that all of this bizarre pretzel logic seems
at the end of the day to all be supporting an anti LGBTQ bigotry.
And why? Why is that the case?
I guess because in Genesis, like I've never understood why the Bible is anti.
It feels like there's like four things in the entire big, thick Bible
that you could maybe construe, but not really as being that
bitch can only be men and women.
Like, it's such a stretch to me to still like go further
and say that it's anti homosexuality.
But like this whole thing seems to be about.
OK, so if we say that there were dinosaurs on the ark,
maybe that'll teach some kids that they shouldn't kiss a boy.
Well, and it goes back to like different versions, like interpretations
of different versions of the Bible, because like there's
there's something there's a line of like, do not lie with another man.
But like earlier editions, earlier translations say, like,
do not lie with a child.
Yes. Yeah, that's good.
Yeah. Use that. Use that phrase.
Like focus on that one. Yeah. Don't do that. For sure.
Wait, that was the same thing. One change to the other.
It's just there's so many of changes like that.
There's so much like
from generation to generation.
It's almost like people use it to scapegoat.
Yeah, for sure.
So do you mean like the thing that they actually think themselves?
They use this big complicated, well, if you look in the book.
Sometimes it's that sometimes it's just they want to raise some
some millions of dollars for their shitty church.
There's a lot of shitty little griffs.
Yeah, they're shitty. They're bad pseudo theme parks.
So let's because almost I'm not sure that we even justified
why we're talking about it on the show.
But like as far as I knew before we started looking into it,
you know, I figured there wasn't much more than the Ark.
But I definitely saw it quickly being described as a religious theme park.
This is a theme park centered around Noah's Ark.
But then you start looking and like, I don't know, is it?
I don't think it is.
I think there are plans to make it more that have not really come to fruition.
Like, in theory, the Ark is just the beginning.
But I like it's just going to be part of a campus.
But yeah, I don't know.
I don't I think they have stopped way short of it being an actual theme park.
Yeah, I mean, there's a VR experience that exists.
Yes. Now, I was going to build to the VR experience.
I'm tempted to talk about the VR experience right now.
In order to get us on more fun ground, because the VR experience is something.
And this this does make it more of a theme park.
Right. That's the closest thing you can point to, I guess,
for it being sort of a themed theme park.
They do have annual passes. I checked.
Oh, you can get a go to this more than anyone would want to do this more than once.
You can get I think your entire family, you can get like a five
hundred dollar pass for all of them to go for a year.
Mm hmm. So that's there.
I'm not sure.
I 60 bucks, by the way, between admission and parking.
That's what that's where you're paying.
I mean, that's high.
That's it really does, especially because.
All right. So what else makes this a theme park?
All right. There's a VR thing. Cool.
With a petting zoo. OK.
Yeah, that's kind of something almost zip lines.
There's zip lines. Sure. That's a ride.
I mean, we've never talked about zip lines in hundreds of episodes,
but OK, close enough.
All right. One zip line, please.
All right. At least 50 more dollars, if not more.
Yeah. Thank you.
Well, it's an upcharge.
It's not even part of that 60 dollars you spend.
Yeah, that's wild.
So, yes, it's it's high.
I mean, look, we you know, we did these drive through experiences
that were close to that, but that's because of covid.
That's because of the cost.
You know, that's a one year thing.
People making the best of a bad situation.
Right. Building up from scratch, too.
Which I mean, this had to do.
But the petting zoo is very funny because you can't.
Biblical, as you can't Bible's eyes, the zoo,
you have to feed these animal zoos are regular.
There's a certain.
I mean, there's some wonky zoos in America, but by all accounts,
like there's a certain level of care, like you thought.
Even if you have like animal wrangler zookeepers,
they still have to know what they're doing, even if they're religious.
Like you can't just feed a tortoise
only millet or whatever they would have been eating back back.
Only what Noah would have fed the tortoise.
Yeah, that's an old family expression, too, right?
From your family. Oh, you can't.
Can't just feed a tortoise millet.
Yeah, you know, you can't.
Judaism feed Methuselah only ancient grains, the very old tortoise
Methuselah, which is pretty good.
I mean, I got to give them credit credit where it's due.
That's pretty good.
Yeah, I'm also just a bummer to me that like this ostrich or whatever
has to live in rural Kentucky.
Let it let these animals.
There's a there's a kangaroo.
The kangaroo has to live in this field. Are they?
They must all be jealous of the animals in animal kingdom.
They're like, well, at least let us go to Disney World. Come on.
I think so.
But then Ken would say, now you listen, it's that's a place of ill virtue.
So be happy here next to this this cafeteria.
I really can't under say how how uncompelling Ken Ham is.
Like, how is he this firebrand?
How have we ever heard of him before for him being the most listless?
Like, I'm sure all of our dads are far more dynamic in every like,
this is the sleepiest man.
Yeah, I I'm building I'm waiting.
I'm building to a Ken Ham thing I found where I was like, it's
it's obviously not the most egregious thing he's ever done.
But it's like you son of a bitch, like just insult to injury on top of anything else,
because he's just such a charisma black hole.
And let me say, by the way, I don't want to give any airtime
either to the atheist and skeptic community.
There are also fucking creeps.
No, I know.
I've watched a bunch of stuff like in trying to find
what where do you get footage and stills of this thing?
Yeah, I've gone down some atheist YouTube rabbit holes and like,
oh, God, these guys, that's the most annoying voice.
This guy's got a big ponytail.
Geez, these atheists. Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, I'm with you.
So but let's you know what?
Let's try to judge this as we did with our fake theme parks.
Let's try to judge some of the experiences.
Of course, the philosophy is abhorrent,
but maybe there's something fun to do in this arc somewhere,
somewhere on on campus.
After all, it was built by a guy named Patrick Marsh.
And Patrick Marsh was one of the leaders on the Jaws
and King Kong projects for Universal Studios.
And he worked on Sanrio Puroland, which I liked very, very much.
So they had a theme park world ringer.
So surely he must have pulled off something amazing.
Do you think the arc itself, do you think do you imagine that you're
driving up, you crest the hill and there is I mean, we love our big
our our big spectacles, our castles and our
Hallelium Mountains and our radiator springs.
Do we do we think at least we look at this arc and go, whoa, how about that?
I got to gram this.
It is impressive in its size.
And it does like I would see it and I would say, oh, that looks like Noah's Ark.
I would think I wouldn't think that before knowing where I was,
if I was just transported there.
So I think, yes, I think if you were assessing just the outside,
you'd go, oh, very impressive how big this is.
Could it be better? Yeah, it could be better.
It could look better.
Yeah, I could use a little more character.
A little, I think so, which I guess is this petting zoo thing.
I get not petting zoo, the children's arcs like maybe like if it was like
a charming Disney boat with that sheen that the Disney would has,
that'd be nice, but it's pretty like it's just drab.
It's extremely drab and accurate,
except that then if you look around the back, then it's just like a building.
Like there's there's just a stucco building attached to it.
So they didn't even go full tilt on that.
It's like an actual bark.
The whole well, but the the HVAC units on the roof are period appropriate.
You know, they are two thousand year old heating and air conditioning.
Ham keeps telling Bill Nye how accurate it is.
And then Bill Nye asks, well, can it float?
And he's like, no, so
it's not accurate.
It can't be accurate unless it's floating.
And it could like, you know, take the weight of all those animal
every animal species on the planet.
Yeah, I mean, there's definitely a lot of design flaws.
When I think this is a good example of this is what happens
when you have no gay people on your design team.
Right. There's just there is no character.
Artists. Yeah, this is like when straight people try to do camp.
And it's just like, oh, man, this sucks.
All right. However, they have.
OK, now, yes, again, you can't avoid it.
This place is extremely anti-gay.
If you want to work there, even seasonally,
you have to sign a statement of faith that says that you go to church
and you view homosexuality as a sin.
You can't even be part time or you would have to, I guess, like
you could sign that and go, yeah, I do.
If you all homosexualize, but I am homosexual.
So who cares? Get away from me. Sure.
But you do. Technically, this is in the.
But that's not to say that they haven't worked.
They haven't had homosexual employees before because they
at the same organization as a thing called the Creation Museum.
That happened before the arc encounter.
And they made a movie about Adam and Eve.
And it was running there for several years before somebody figured out
that the guy who played Adam was the owner and operator of a gay porn site.
Nice. And just did it as a like acting gig.
You got some slow gigs, you know, in comedy.
Sometimes you do a prank show.
Sometimes you do like some sort of hardcore porn.
Yeah, sometimes you do.
You know, it's something you got slow years, folks.
You got so years.
That's what happens in gigs where you can.
Anyways, so well, so that's the outside.
There is a little bit of imagination in the queue.
And by that, I mean that the queue is big enough to fit a thousand people.
But typically on you will on a typical day, you'll only see about 10.
Yeah, that's yes. I think maybe he was optimistic.
I mean, I think with a lot.
Anytime you dig into any of these religious theme parks,
whoever put them together has a fantasy that this thing is going to be
so inspirational that there will be thousands of people lined up.
And I have yet to see evidence that that can happen.
I don't think that's maybe there is a place right now that's going
and it's the best religious theme park.
But maybe the Jim Baker one got close, right?
The Jim Baker theme park from the 80s.
But that seems like a better theme park in a way.
It at least had it doesn't, you know, they didn't exactly have any
radiator springs racers there, but they had like, you know, a merry-go-round
and like a flume ride and a water slide.
So do that stuff and like tapings that that kind of thing helps.
I think maybe they aren't doing like the periphery stuff to make you want
to make thousands of people want to keep coming. Right.
Well, Jim Baker was a he's a bigger celebrity than Ken Ham.
Maybe it's him needs to up his profile and become more of a of a charismatic figure.
I don't know how I should make a response video to Lil Nas X.
Yeah, he makes a response video, starts selling buckets like Jim Baker sells
now of MREs and dehydrated food for the end times. Of course.
Oh, yeah. Weird buckets.
And then Lil Nas X can like tweet at him like, hey, can Ken Ham is daddy or something?
Stay mad, daddy.
If we all if we all just talk about how Ken Ham is hot.
That's that's ethical, right?
We can he won't like that, but I like it, but it would keep him.
He should like stir up.
He should know that controversy is good for him. Yeah.
Well, I mean, we talked about, you know, former Disney CEOs getting it,
quote unquote, but can Ken Ham get it?
I mean, I don't think I don't think I'm going to say absolutely no.
I think so. Ken Ham do not show feet.
Thank you very much.
So you get into the thing and then what do you see?
Then you see, all right, well, here's where all the animals live.
But again, it's against the rules to have.
Here's the giraffe head poking out and you could barely squeeze into the cage.
It's just like a bunch of cubbies.
And you look inside through like slats and you see like a non,
but mostly non animatronic animals, mostly like in the dark.
Yeah, it sucks. It's like, go to Disney.
I see you like can't go to Disney and see what it looks like to go on a decent
ride with some robots like it sucks ass.
It's like it's really it's it's really bad.
I know the Vice article, I'll steal this observation from them that
they pointed out a room that is full of like charts on the wall and numbers.
And they're like, yeah, you know, there's a ride at Epcot and the ride is called
Test Track. And when you're in the line, there's a lot of charts and numbers.
But then at the end of all the charts and numbers, you get in a car and you go
65 miles an hour.
The arc encounter is like if they didn't do that last part.
Yeah. The top floor is all like museum.
It doesn't even look like an arc from the shots I saw.
Maybe there are parts that still look kind of like arc like.
But the pictures up there made it look like it was a cheap ass museum.
Yeah, I watched a walkthrough by what I quickly learned
was a family with four children and they live in an RV.
And they just kept talking about how like, this is so amazing.
This is so great. There's so much information.
They said that so many times.
There's just so much information here.
And I beg to differ.
I don't know that there's much besides like the parking lot is that way.
Uncle Leroy's fudge is that way.
That, I think, is the only information.
You know, do we were we able to find any reviews of the fudge in our encounter?
I've got fudge material. Don't worry.
Let's you know, let's let's go out of order in order to just to keep the fun
flowing. Yes. I'm uncle.
What do we know about Uncle Leroy's?
Well, OK, so there's a 36 minute long video
called Ken Ham Becomes a Fudge Expert that you can find on YouTube.
And so it's 36 minutes long because it was the live
stream video from New Year's Eve 2019.
And Ken Ham goes to the fudge.
There's this fudge counter in the Ark named Uncle Leroy's fudge.
Uncle Leroy is there. He's a guy.
He said he's been doing this for 45 years, I guess, making fudge for 45 years.
And very quickly, you realize this video also sucks
because Ken Ham is a charisma black hole.
He will not let Uncle Leroy talk.
He keeps cracking the worst jokes.
There's another guy there and they go, this is Cody and Cody is along for the video.
There's no explanation of who Cody is or why he's there.
The fudge looks competent.
It's more of the loaf shape kind of fudge.
Oh, interesting. I don't know if you guys are more partial to square or rectangular
square, man, but I'm interested in this.
The different shape actually makes me more intrigued to have it.
I don't know if that doesn't maybe make any sense, but I'm intrigued because maybe
the process of making it is different.
I'm starved for fun now, so I'd gladly grab a vanilla pecan fudge loaf.
Yeah. Yeah.
Devour the whole thing.
Jason's being negative, but let's be honest, he would get baptized by Ken Ham to try
some of Uncle Leroy's fudge.
Oh, look, the fudge looks good.
Uncle Leroy seems like a pro.
I believe it's his son is making the fudge like in the video.
I did not watch all 36 minutes of it because I wanted to hear about fudge making and see
how he did it.
But Ken Ham kept fucking interrupting him.
I do have to say, unlike the fudge, M.
Zara's buffet, the all you can eat buffet looks like some of the brownest,
most underseasoned food I have ever seen.
That macaroni cheese doesn't look like it's melted very well.
No, no.
Mostly cheese. Yeah, it's like straight out of the bag of shredded cheese.
I yeah.
Ick cinnamon. Those cinnamon rolls don't look good.
Some of these just big like whipped cream type trays.
I don't even know what's in it.
What is that in the middle?
I think in the middle.
I don't know what that is.
That's mashed potatoes on the right, I assume.
But what is that thing next to it?
No, I think that's tapioca.
I think this is the dessert trays, which has.
Oh, you're right. You're right.
I thought that was mashed potatoes. I apologize.
It's got the most sinister energy coming off.
It really does. That's evil food.
Yeah, this is terribly underseasoned.
And M. Zara's buffet, the buffet next to the Ark,
is one of the largest restaurants in the world, capable of holding 1500 diners.
Unbelievable.
I saw that fact and I confirmed it on a listicle of the biggest restaurants
in the world, and it's buried towards the back because most of them
are more interesting than this.
And then they're like, yeah.
And then for some reason, the Kentucky
Ark encounter is the biggest restaurant.
And to me, it seems like, is this a mistake?
Like, did was this a reverse of the spinal tap Stonehenge
where the little like inch marking was in the wrong place?
And so make sure you can hold 150 people. Got it.
And then somebody read something as a zero that they weren't supposed to.
Like, when is this ever needed?
1500 people.
Then like Ken Ham has found something that he can tie it to in one of the chapters
in Genesis to say, well, we all should be dining with
1499 of our close friends at all times.
It's got to be something he's figured out.
Let me ask. I'll show you guys this and I'll post this so people can see.
Can you identify any of these items?
Oh, OK. All right.
Uh,
there's brownies on the right.
Those are brown. OK, good. All right. OK.
Yeah. OK.
Oh, which maybe puts it all in dessert.
That helps me because there's a big there's a bunch of balls
that are like different shades of brown.
And I was thinking falafel.
But if it's dessert, then it's not falafel.
And maybe edible cookie.
I thought maybe it was like ball versions of the Cheesecake Factory breads,
the two types, the brown bread and the regular bread.
But I don't now.
Now I don't. I actually don't know.
Besides that, it's I think those are blondies maybe next to the brownies.
Yes, possibly.
I think these look like maybe like munchkin, maybe like donut holes.
Oh, yeah. Maybe or maybe a little bigger.
Chespie squares on the right.
Yeah, like a custard pie.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Or banana cream.
But it's like a big mess like the the the
it's it's like a slop made up of individual slices.
You know where one begins and the next ends.
Yeah, it's a yick.
It's it's rough stuff.
I mean, I've been to a I've been to a buffet in my time.
I've been to my family, went to Amish smorgasbords in Pennsylvania.
And very kind people.
There are nice people, again, food pretty under season.
But there's a lot of it, certainly.
But the nicest, again, the nicest people
working those places, not trying to convert you at all,
not like the answers in Genesis crowd.
Yes, the whole point is to
the can I say two facts really quick?
One is that M Zara is the name of Noah's wife.
Yes, apparently.
But that's not I don't think in the Bible.
I think that's pulled from other stuff over the years.
But more fun fact is that I'm looking at a sign
that's right outside the actual arc that has some soda cups
branded to our encounter.
And it does inform you that there's the possibility of a flood of refills.
See, that seems like that's too much fun to be had. Yeah.
I think it's the only fun thing on property.
And it's just because Ken hasn't seen it yet.
They're like steering him away from the sign.
Don't let Ken see.
The gift shop.
Do we look at this?
Oh, I don't know. Yeah, no, I missed it.
OK, so the gift shop.
So we're talking about fun.
You're talking about how, you know, they do that
misdirect with the cute animals, and that's not what this is about.
Don't think that for a second.
You go into the goddamn gift shop. Excuse my language.
No, do it. And the episode.
There are cute animal plush everywhere.
It's full and under it on a headline, it says equip children.
What? Why?
Why is it said so formally for with a equip children with a little
stuffed camel? Yeah.
And we barely even talked.
I didn't realize dinosaurs run Noah's Ark.
That's news to me.
Well, I mean, that's kind of the corner that you're around.
Yeah, like that's the big secret of the place in general.
Yeah, is the presence of dinosaurs, which does get us into fun a little more.
That's not what they intended.
I agree. It would be more fun if like also the mighty Akron was on the Ark.
That would be even better if we could get some other fun character, fun animals.
So we'll focus on this gift shop. There's a couple more things here.
So they got the cute plush and the cute.
So that's already go spitting in the face of Ken Ham's idea.
And then on the left here, I love there's a lot of books
that say stuff like Inside Noah's Ark, why it worked.
Oh, it's so obsessed with like practically explaining.
This is so funny because there's like videos where it's like explaining
how the Batmobile would work in real life.
No one cares. It's a fucking story.
Like Batman isn't real.
There's no reason to explain.
Because we are I don't think we're a fan of any of the Neil deGrasse
Tyson type stuff.
It's like, actually, that wouldn't have been is not very realistic.
It's stories. Shut up.
Did the point of the story work?
That's true of movies. That's true of the Bible.
I've said it. I'm sure I've said it on the podcast before.
But Grant Morrison, our one of our favorite comic book writers, was saying,
he goes, when you show a kid a movie with a talking crab,
the kid just goes, oh, the crab is talking.
But when an adult gets a hold of it, they're like, well, why is this crab talking
and why the kid knows it's fake?
The kid knows it's made up.
But adults, for some reason, have this bizarre thing where it's like,
we must explain.
And it's like, it's so boring. Who gives a shit?
You can also get a book called A Flood of Evidence.
Forty Reasons Noah's Ark Still Matter
or Noah's Ark Still Matters or an S at the end of that.
Ken Ham wrote this book, folks, with Bodie Hoge.
Bodie Hoge or Hodge.
Bodie Hodge.
That's probably Hodge.
I'm choosing Hodge just to go with Bodie.
Bodie Hoge.
In case you want more books that that have evidence in them.
How about this? The flood evidences combo.
There's more books with evidence.
Imagine going to a gift shop that's just here.
Take a book full of evidence.
Format, pack, technicality, layman, ages seven and up.
Oh, so my seven year old will like Echoes of Eritat.
Oh, man. Evidence.
Flood of Evidence also is three hundred and thirty six pages long.
Yes. But but but back to the cuteness stuff, too.
If you look on this page, here's Noah.
He's a cute cartoon man.
This is this is not what Ken Ham was talking about.
So I'm surprised he's allowing this, but I'm also not because he's probably
raking in money from it.
Yeah, I also just don't think he's paying a lot of attention
and that'll come back into play when we talk about the virtual reality stuff.
I don't think this is a Walt in charisma or in obsession with details.
I think he is not obsessed with details.
I think he wanted his arc and he ignores a lot of other stuff. Yes.
I would. I'm always curious about exactly how deep these guys go
with what they're saying as well, because like as evidenced by him
just being saying to Bill Nye, what do you care, man?
Hey, I'm done arguing with you.
What do you care about what we're doing?
That feels like maybe you're out of you're out of evidence.
Yeah. Perhaps.
Also, you invited me here.
You're getting content out of this just like I have.
Why are you getting to that point?
I did see the one gift shop thing I saw was a yarn
beard and cap so that you could be a little Noah.
His famous cap and his beard.
All right. Can we get that for you?
Oh, yeah. Not from not from here.
We can get a separate Etsy yarn beard, but that's yeah.
We're not supporting this place.
Yeah. Can somebody make is there a different, more secular character
like the mascot for a beard beard papa?
Yeah. Oh, Jason is beard papa.
Can we have somebody on Etsy make us a beard papa outfit for Jason, please?
Sure.
And if the post sizes somewhere, just DM us, we'll give you sizes.
Let's talk about dinosaurs,
because that's what they're anxious to do.
My exposure to the notion of creationism
and dinosaurs or religion dinosaurs going together
was the cabezon dinosaurs.
Apologies if I'm saying that that name wrong.
Cabezon the that, of course, being the dinosaurs that are on the way
to Palm Springs, probably on the way to other places.
But I think of them from the Palm Springs Drive.
They're famous from Pee Wee's Big Adventure.
You pass by him on the side of the road, maybe once in a while.
People go, I'm going to get out and take some photos of that
scene of my whole life.
Obviously from Pee Wee, they've been there since the 50s or 60s.
And finally, like one time going to Palm Springs with Aaron, like,
all right, we got to go.
We got to go check this out.
I didn't know that in the recent past that there was a change
in ownership to the cabezon dinosaurs and it had become a creationist museum.
So they took the fun dinosaurs that Pee Wee hangs out with
and they built a whole little thing around it with smaller dinosaurs.
And there's this whole little maze that you walk around.
And I don't know if it's still like this.
I think it may have changed ownership again.
I was when I went there.
So did you go into the thing?
We didn't pay for the thing.
We just pulled.
You can just pull over and park next to the Burger King
and take your picture under the big dinosaurs for free and then leave.
And that's what we did.
But it seemed like mostly the thing they were pushing is come in.
There's a petting zoo and get soft serve ice cream and like dinosaur cones,
like the fish, the fish, soft serve ice cream codes.
Unfortunately, you had to pay to get past the entry to get to that ice cream shack.
So we. But there's other ice cream.
Yeah, there's you needn't pay that fee.
So yeah, you can still get your pictures taken there for free.
And that's what we did.
And then got in the car because the winds were knocking everyone over.
It was so windy.
Oh, yeah, it's so crazy.
Well, there's that whole feel the windmill is not far past that.
But so at least whenever we went in there, totally surprised,
totally got the smack that this was a religious museum.
And and but religious, however, with in that there's like a T-Rex
attacking a medieval knight.
That's the kind of crap that's in there.
And I'll tell you, way more fun than the Ark encounter.
This may be a separate thing to be done about the Cabezon dinosaurs.
Pretty like clever of some group to come in and say,
hey, people know those dinosaurs and they know Peewee.
What if we we have a message around it?
And all the little tableaus of us like a scared knight
holding up a spear like, what do I do?
Like as a velociraptor, that shit.
Pretty fun, stupid, wrong, incorrect.
But anyway, that was my exposure to all of it.
And I didn't know there was this whole strand of thing that there
and that is very kid baiting, like, well, kids like dinosaurs.
And maybe they don't know that God created dinosaurs
and on the same day that he created Adam and Eve.
That was news to me in researching this episode.
And I was like, wait, so it does it say in the Bible
God created dinosaurs and then he created man?
No, it says created the land animals, created all the land animals
and then created man.
So it's still a leap to say dinosaurs.
They're pulling. There's no dinosaurs in the Bible.
They're pulling this out of nowhere, which makes it extra bizarre.
When you walk around here and you see signs that say things like,
did you know up to 85 kinds of dinosaurs were on the Ark
to Tyrannosaurids to Stegosaurids?
What are you talking about for being Bible literalists?
How are you getting that there were two Stegosaurus on there?
That is made up.
This is kids making up rules on the playground.
You don't get to say how many Stegosaurus were there.
The gremlins may as well be on the Ark.
Like it like you may.
It doesn't it doesn't make any sense.
You said Mighty Akron, you said this is the way this is how they get me.
If all of the great creatures from literature,
if the xenomorph is on there, it's created the xenomorph kingdom.
If they put the beastly kingdom in.
Yeah, that's right.
There's minions.
God created the minions, created Stuart.
That's game over if you get minions in there.
That's God created the biker mice from Mars and they're on the Ark.
Do you is Ninja Turtles sinful in this viewpoint
because it was a mutation?
Well, no, no, no, because God created the turtles and he also created the ooze.
And then an accident combined these two things.
So the mutation that that just happened, that was,
I guess, eventually part of God's plan.
Yeah, for sure. That's yes, the turtles were part of God's plan.
That's what I always that's the most religion, by the way, I had as a child.
That was your religion.
Yes, it's still going into some degree.
But the dangers of Eastern religion, you know, the spirituality and
and discipline that comes in the art of the ninja of martial arts.
The ninja. Yeah.
And I have to reconcile like how in the movie,
Hamato Yoshi is a man who is killed and his rat becomes splinter
versus in the cartoon Ninja Turtles, where
Hamato Yoshi becomes the rat man.
It's different.
So I have to reconcile how that works in my brain.
And I I don't have a great Ken Ham explanation for it yet.
This is like King James and different like, yeah, it passes through different sources.
So how do you reconcile?
How can you be a literalist when there's
original Ninja Turtles, but also Ninja Turtles meet Batman and Robin? Right.
How does it all work together? Yeah, it's tough.
And I got to maybe talk to a Ken Ham like guy
to help, you know, make it my faith straight, my turtle faith.
Yeah. Also, what does it do to one's brain to run the Twitter account
for Ark encounter where they post like, check out this animal,
like the statue of this animal, which went extinct a long time ago.
And all the replies are like, yeah, went extinct two million years ago, asshole.
Just got to ignore sinners, haters. Yeah.
On on the dinosaur front, though,
just this this twisted philosophy because you well, you start going like
like those Twitter people poking holes in everything.
Well, how could there have been dinosaurs on the Ark?
Because they're big. They would have eaten everything.
Well, no. God thought of that.
He put small dinosaurs on.
You see, they were smaller, so they wouldn't go and they were caged.
So don't worry about it.
But then there's this whole other.
I mean, part of the Noah story is that there was so much sin on Earth
that God decided to wipe it and, you know, start fresh.
And only the pious Noah and Ham and all of them were going to make it.
So this the Ark encounter has exhibits that show you what was that sin,
what was going on on Earth that was so bad.
And apparently it was mistreatment of dinosaurs.
This is probably the most prominent tableau.
I'll zoom in a tiny bit where
there's a gladiator pit and people like like gladiators or whatever.
Warriors are being made to fight a dinosaur while other people cheer and holler.
And then I don't know why over here on the left,
giants come into the mix.
We also got giants.
Dinosaurs fighting giants because you shouldn't be gay.
Right. That all ties there.
Giants. OK, like what?
I guess look at this.
This is a sign on the wall to giants Genesis six four.
And you look it up and one out of 10 Bible versions use the word giants.
The rest, it's some made up term.
But they're from that they're convinced the giants are a major
part of the Bible story. Huh.
Are giants bad?
I guess they are in this context.
Well, also, humans were much smaller in the time of the Bible.
And they might think Mike was a giant.
You know, that's a good point.
I could be a giant. Yeah.
Let's call me Ken Ham.
If you came poking around Ken Ham with questions about the Ninja Turtles,
would he go, ah, giant and runs run screaming
or his half hearted version of screaming?
Yeah, he yeah, he would not.
He can't. He runs like one mile an hour and his scream is like, ah, ah,
oh, don't eat me giant.
Also, isn't this a perfect
isn't this a perfect opportunity to retcon dinosaurs
out of the actual timeline that they probably existed in?
Just say they were killed in the flood
and Noah didn't have time to collect the dinosaurs and then that wiped them out.
So you get rid of the problem of them existing far longer ago
than 6000 years away. Yeah, that would be easy.
Well, there's a whole wipe clean.
Why did Noah take dinosaurs? Right.
Because then they stopped existing. Right.
You have to explain then why they stopped existing past that.
There's it's such an easy I mean, he's really got to talk to Jason.
Who are like the best
like crisis on infinite earth is a DC event where they like
took all their continuity and it was so heavy that they just like stripped it away
and got rid of characters.
He's really got to talk to somebody who who.
Marv specialized.
Yeah, well, you should.
Comic book writer Marv Wolfman should really be involved in this.
Or even just script like like Robert McKee, like Robert McKee.
Help me help me simplify this this story.
That said, I think like not to be Pat and be like all this stuff there.
Like, you know, they complain about is cool. But
the statue they made of a priest delivers a human baby
into the belly furnace of a snake god is pretty bad ass.
What this is this is nuts.
Yeah. Now this is like psychedelic.
No, it's like H.R. Geiger.
This is cool. Yeah.
Now I would in a flood at that, I would just be pissing off that snake god.
And, you know, I don't want any I don't want beef with snake gods, you know.
There was a snake god or is that a statue?
Oh, that's a statue.
That's a false idol. It is a false idol.
OK, so there were there weren't big snakes running around, but there were giants.
No, but there are eventually after the flood.
Eventually, you get to modern history and there are pagans.
So I don't know quite know how they square that circle.
Also, other world religions, I'm sure they're not fond of them.
Well, mainly because they don't fit in the narrative very well. Yeah.
There's also there's on the dinosaur front.
Oh, another weird thing is that,
again, with that gladiator thing, this apparently was a very common like,
all right, what are the sins of man?
What are they doing that are bad?
Apparently, there's artwork all over
showing humans at the time being bad to dinosaurs.
There's like a first sacrifice.
It's a real thing in the Bible.
They just make it a dinosaur in this.
And they just show other like, I don't know what it is exactly.
But I think like, you know, I guess they know God had to wipe out all of humanity
because people were like kicking a dinosaur in the butt.
That's that seems like a simplification of what the message was, was it?
Wasn't there like a bigger message?
Forgive me not knowing anything about religion, but wasn't like, yeah,
I don't think it was just like it wasn't just like yanking dinosaurs
tails or like making them do stuff for you.
Take me to school.
And mush. It's it turns out it turns out it was not a living.
The way that humans were misusing dinosaurs.
That was exactly.
That is exactly what I was about to say.
Is the is an easy retcon just showing old Flintstones footage
and them using like an old dinosaur as a garbage can?
And then you go, oh, yeah, humans misused dinosaurs.
They did. They were abusing them at this time.
And this is our actual can and would say like this is actual footage from the past.
There is one accurate text.
There is only one piece of true media in filthy vile Hollywood.
And it is this from the fire center in Barbera.
You see the these sinners were using
elephants as showers and pig dinosaurs as garbage disposals.
Some kids like, oh, I saw them meet the Jetsons once.
He's like, no, you didn't.
No, you did not.
That was because God created a time machine.
That is what happened.
Yeah, I mean, there's so many easy pop culture ways, you know, to get around this.
And I feel like Ken Ham did a shit job.
And easy, real easy.
Just just have a room in your not fun museum.
Have a room that just plays Flintstones episodes all day.
That would make this 10 times a better theme park.
If you need to edit it to scary music and put like, you know,
filters on it to good, then the and these heathens would when it was
they would ride a dinosaur all day for work and then
yell a celebration word that was nonsense
and slide all the way down its tail.
Here you can see them committing the sin of gluttony, eating a far too big rib platter.
God. OK, so God was watching the Flintstones and he said, this must stop.
And he told Noah to build the ark and get all the animals there.
And then after he did that and then the flood went away, God said,
All right, now I will kill the dinosaurs forever.
I will wipe them out.
Good news. I saved the dinosaurs.
All right. Good.
Thanks for saving the job for me.
Now I like the lightning bolt.
And he gets no now.
He now God in heaven is using
dinosaurs as record players and as garbage cans
because he's brought them up to his kingdom.
And he stole our idea.
Yes, Flintstones idea.
He is abusing the dinosaurs now.
That's what's happening.
And it's it's that sort of, you know, for forward thinking
usefulness that would make him a great hire.
It's basically Sprockets company.
No, it doesn't. Oh, no.
The the pterodactyls holding a cloud up with God sitting on it.
And the pterodactyls, of course, say it's a it's a holy living.
It's a holy.
It's a pious living.
I like the idea also that in the aftermath of the flood, that you as somebody
would be digging for fossils and then find the perfect fossils of Fred and Barney.
Like short, weird, stout, early man.
I mean, yeah, tiny early man looked like height,
stun it by those, you know, lucky strikes.
OK, so there's all that.
There's also the fact that so there's a documentary about all this
called We Believe in Dinosaurs, which is mainly notable for a part
where they show a Ken Ham lecture where he's talking to a bunch of children.
And he says, so what do you say when somebody says that the earth was old,
actually, and a bunch of kids all say, were you there?
And then he says, and what do you when somebody talks about dinosaurs,
what do you say that they are called?
And they all say, missionary lizards.
What? Yeah, never heard that one in my life.
A great improv team name.
If you're looking for an improv team name, you could do a lot worse.
Of course, improv was wiped out by the great flood of 2020.
Yeah, I don't know that it needs to come.
The great plague, I guess.
I don't know if that needs to come back.
Much like dinosaurs.
God told God told certain people to put it on their boat,
but they actually had paid too much for the boat and they had to sell the boat
because they had made bad business decisions.
So then they didn't have a boat to save it.
It's a very sad. You will build a great.
Yeah, imagine a great arc, two stories with classrooms and a storefront.
Should I fill it? No.
Yeah, I put a business in there.
That's not my plan.
Imagine Noah built like four boats, two at once.
And like maybe the demand wasn't there.
He is not listening to Ham or M.Zara.
He's listening to no one who came after him.
He has these meetings and it's like, why are we even having the meetings
if M.Zara is not going to get a word in?
Yelling at the dinosaurs?
The two boats, the two boats were like a cash cow, like Noah was living good.
Yeah, off those two boats.
But then the four of us.
Stupid new vision.
The two more boats.
Ken Ham's lack of charisma does prime him
that if this endeavor ever goes under, he he could easily be a comedy teacher.
Yeah, Jason and I, we were younger.
We would pay Ken Ham four hundred dollars for eight classes of comedy instruction.
He told me we needed a boys band, too.
All right. The first rule of improv.
Yes. And unless you're not straight.
Well, and now that is leave right now.
That brings up a good I don't think we've talked about this.
This is on top of everything else.
The lamest thing he can ham did in December 2016.
The they lit the arc with rainbow colors,
with the idea of reclaiming the symbol from the gay rights movement.
Oh, for God's sake, that's soft.
Oh, like that's so bad.
It's take back the rainbow.
Take back the rainbow campaign.
That's catchy, isn't it?
Yeah. Yes.
What a what a good use of your time.
What a wonderful use of your time.
Yeah. Planet Earth.
Heal the sick, heal the sick, feed the poor.
No, no, no. We got a we got a culture war bullshit about rainbows.
Is he mad? Is he mad at Skittles, too?
Does he want the rainbow back from Skittles?
Does he not want you to taste the rainbow anymore?
It's coming for the Christians should have Skittles.
Sherman, Sherwin and Williams committed sins by making this many paint colors.
Only Brown, only arc brown, like the delicious meals
you can get at M.
Zara's Cafe, which unfortunately has been converted back to a cafeteria
due to this covid hoax virus.
That's something we haven't talked about.
They still have to adhere to the basic safety
tenants of businesses and theme parks.
Like CDC regulations.
So they have to have mask enforcement.
They have to have like like limited seating at M.
Zara's, and I'm sure it's killing them.
Oh, because if it was just if it was like zoned as a museum,
then they wouldn't have to do it because it is a museum.
But because they made it, they said the word theme park.
Now they're stuck under theme park rules.
Oh, I think just just it's Kentucky.
I think just basic Kentucky, like most states.
I don't know. I'm sure they've scaled stuff back.
A lot of states have.
But like it's just basic common sense stuff of hand sanitizer and all.
And it's like how much are they like pissed about that?
Right, right.
Before we leave the arc, I want to nod to the Noah animatronic.
You got to like that.
There is an animatronic.
He talks in that history voice that all history animatronics
talk in like Ben Franklin and Mark Twain.
He answers a lot of bizarre questions like,
why don't I look 600?
What do you mean?
This is what all the 600 year olds I know look like.
But not my wife.
She doesn't look a day over 400.
Yeah, yeah.
He also it's also canon that Noah hates woodpeckers.
What they ask, what's your least favorite animal?
And he says, they're all wonderful in God's eye.
But why do question why Shem put that bird that knocks on wood all day
next to the living quarters?
And I'm just I'm out of this room by the time this is over.
I love robots.
What else is going on in the news today?
Airplane food, huh?
I'm sure we're going to do a little plus up, but like here, live it up.
Throw Woody Woodpecker in there to like pestering.
Yeah, pranking.
He's like bothering Noah.
He's like Noah's figment, you know.
Oh, Woody, I guess it is you.
I do despise you sometimes,
but it is part of God's plan that we spar.
And then he does his noise that we all can do an impression of.
Right. It does that.
That's fine. That's fine.
You know, we can't assume just because we're all so bad at Donald's
that we can't do at least that you can't do, Woody.
That was very good. Thank you.
Jason, you want to try it?
Um.
No, I can't.
I can't.
A little bit better than Donald.
Yeah.
You would recognize.
Schako.
Yeah.
Sure.
OK.
And then and then Ken Ham, you go, ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Yeah, that's about right.
He does a great Donald, though, I bet.
Broadly perfect Donald.
Oh, yeah.
Donald, though, I bet.
Broadly perfect, Donald.
There's also an animatronic of Jepeth's sad wife sweeping up the floor.
Oh, man.
Does she talk?
No.
Is Jepeth's wife?
What do we know her name?
I didn't write it down because I was going to butcher the Helen.
It's probably no, it's way you could.
I have the names.
Wait, well, here, I'm going to share this from Wikipedia, which is where I learned about
the.
Oh, here we go.
Thing.
It's got an apostrophe at the beginning.
What is that? How do you pronounce that?
Not Elta Muck.
That's a guess.
No, that's Ham's wife.
Jepeth's wife is of course.
Yes, of course, it's Jepeth's wife, who is added added to the.
Tenis is that a tennis.
Well, we've got we are trying to say Shams wife's name, old names.
You know what? Shams wife.
It's Old Testament.
I don't know. Some of these people might be very holy in the Torah.
So for the sake of proper religious dignity, which this place has none of,
I will not attempt these.
Shams wife. Yeah, that's for the best.
How would Woody Woodpecker say one of these names is the question.
Second to say, said it said a telebab.
Yeah, there you go. Yeah, I think it actually helped.
Yahweh will allow that. He will allow what he a little more chill.
Yeah, so let's we're winding down, but we got to talk about this.
Now, here's where it becomes a theme park.
Everybody is the VR experience.
Now, this I like.
I I got way more excited knowing about the VR experience.
Why it's called Truth Traveler.
That's right. Strap on your goggles.
It's time for truth traveler.
Let me find the description.
Get seated in the truth traveler time machine and journey back to the time of Noah.
Well, again, more in our immersive virtual reality experience.
A flood of reality.
More floods.
And here we go.
Finally, some catnip pod, the lovable robot.
We have a character.
It's pod will be your guide as you witness the building of Noah's Ark.
Experience the flood, venture inside the Ark with the animals and some surprises,
some exciting surprises along the way.
We can't see a ride through of this because this is a VR goggle experience.
But I did learn what one of the exciting surprises is.
And would you believe that the first exciting surprise
is that you were greeted in this VR attraction by a hologram of Ken Ham?
Oh, man.
Hello, it's me, holograms, all this time.
Welcome to. Yeah.
Wow. I did not realize that, like much like on star tours,
you get a Princess Leia hologram here.
You get the Ken Ham hologram instead.
Oh, man, am I going to get Leia?
Am I going to get a Yoda?
Oh, I got Ken Ham.
It's such a perfect, like disappointing name.
Ken Ham and Ham again.
How is John Ham the most like dashing name?
And Ken Ham is just the saddest dipshit.
Yeah.
Scott, you know what else makes this place a theme park?
Grand expansion plans.
Oh, yeah, there's yeah, yeah, yeah.
There's a huge map of unbuilt stuff.
Yeah, they want it.
They want to make this a whole complex.
The Ark alone seemed to cost a hundred million dollars,
and that's with like private fundraising and state incentives and stuff.
But they also were including a
a model of the Tower of Babel and replicas
of an ancient walled city and a Middle Eastern village.
And yeah, if this is your proof of concept, the Ark, I wouldn't.
Like, I don't.
First off, I don't I don't want to meet the people who live in that village.
I'm afraid of what they're going to say.
Mm hmm.
Yeah, sure.
They did almost build there or part of the plans
have included a thrill ride about the 10 plagues of Egypt.
But I guess they've if you can believe that they have scaled back those plans,
there will not be this now.
Now, what does thrill ride mean to them?
That's my question.
Um, I don't know.
I mean, look, it's just to go back to the truth
traveler really quick because I watched a video where Ken Ham does a walkthrough
of the truth, travel experience.
And if this is their idea of a thrilling experience, this
is the saddest thing I've ever seen, where this is like older man in a mask
and like the most wires on a VR setup I've ever seen.
There's so much more than the void or on an Oculus.
I mean, he looks like he's like undergoing surgery.
This is like like he's going to be here for 10 hours
and it's going to be really invasive.
This is so this is such misery.
But then you get to like
you go around the boat, you know, like you get to do in reality.
But instead with goggles and you're in like it's it's a it's a row of four
40 X chairs, basically, that move around in unthemed rooms.
And everything here, that's just like black walls
with just like the your headphone shelves or just right above your head.
This is but then you but you do see dinosaurs.
There's there's there's pod reacting to a dinosaur.
You come face to face with a baby T-Rex
because there were only small T-Rex is on the arc.
So as opposed to other dinosaur theme park attractions,
you get the tiniest dinosaur.
The graphics look like GameCube, Nintendo GameCube graphics.
Yeah. And this is a newer experience.
So it feels like they didn't maybe put so much money into it.
Maybe not.
At least the character is there, though, I'll say that.
Yeah, he's British.
So he's got sort of a Ken Ham vibe himself.
Did you get any sense of do we like pod?
Well, it's pod is pod anti LGBTQ, because that might I assume he is probably.
Is it a hate monger robot? Yeah, I don't.
Probably. He seems nice.
But some people, you know, are nice, but have hate in their heart.
I did read the former
the former head of Hirshend Family Entertainment,
which runs Dollywood and Kentucky Kingdom and Silver Dollar City
consulted on this project.
And to them, I ask, what did you do?
What did you contribute?
Have a couple different restaurants like
you're going to have no proof of.
Yeah. Theming here anywhere.
No. You know, you know what I would love?
And maybe this if I do we have anything else before like
really fast, here we go.
I was just going to say my absolute favorite Ken Ham video
is him being taken around this facility of truth traveler.
And the best moment is he's going around with like another total dullard.
And the two of them walk in and Ken's like, OK, looks good.
So this is the lobby.
And it's going to be more it's going to be more themed.
Eventually, you're going to put up more stuff.
And the guy says, oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, you are. Oh, yes.
He just did like the minimal amount to get it open.
Yeah, exactly. So it's going to be so it's going to be like, yes.
No, we're going to do the theming. OK, good. Good.
And then he then they leave and he does it again.
You're just like, why did they publish this?
Him scolding his own employee.
And then they then the guy says and so the thing kicks off actually with you.
It's a hologram of you. And he's like, oh, right.
Me. That's oh, yeah. OK.
Like he's in the ride and doesn't even know he doesn't know Pod's name.
He's so checked out.
This is like, what's he doing?
If not this, if we had our own theme park, it's all we would think about.
Yeah, no, he I at the most.
I don't know. It's obviously worse if it's this is whole.
It's just a cynical exercise on his part to rake in money, which it might be.
I don't know. I'm not sure.
But yeah, of course, you'd be like very excited to.
He built a giant arc like you should be at least excited about that.
Yeah. But nothing does it.
For this guy, apparently.
Yeah. Well, how do we save this play?
Like what if it changes hands like the cab is on dinosaurs and it gets.
Is there something fun you can do with an arc?
Well, I think and I'm not sure what connection it'll have,
but I think it should change hands.
And I believe it should go in the hands of hard rock park creator John Binkowski.
I. Hell, yeah.
I think you give, you know, go back and listen to our hard rock hard rock
park episodes.
But you got to give you got to give a guy with that passion,
with the creativity that's exploding with ideas like Winston,
the punk rock dog and the bare metal family, original characters.
He knew what was fun.
I believe that was a failure of a park because of advertising and location.
And I don't think it was for lack of creativity.
So I think turning over to somebody like a Binkowski.
And now we're now we can get something going in here.
Are there any famous big boats in rock history?
We just make this hard rock park.
That's exactly what I was trying to figure out.
What is a big boat in rock history?
That boat.
There was a movie with Philip Seymour Hoffman about the pirate radio stations
off of the coast of England.
That's true. Yeah, that is true.
Well, is it called pirate radio?
Is it called the boat that rocked?
Was it one that had like different names?
Hmm. I don't remember.
Hmm. There is, of course, I'm looking at famous songs about a boat.
And there is a Jimmy Buffett song called Something About a Boat,
but that might not be so famous to do.
Come Sail Away, a famous Styx song, of course.
Well, if we're going to make this Styx land and now Styx is the river in hell.
So, you know, that would really be against the wishes of Ken Ham.
But what better way to stick it to him
than to give it over to Tommy Shaw and John Binkowski?
Well, and then you actually make the river Styx.
You'd be like, oh, yeah, water red.
It's a blood red river.
Styx playing all day.
All right.
Bunch of robato's walking around serving you.
Get your two coins for the pay the river man to put over your eye.
I don't think I get that one. Wait, what's the river man?
Oh, you when someone back in the day, when someone died,
you would put a coin over each eye.
And those were the two coins to pay the river man
to ferry you across the river Styx to the.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Oh, to get past to. OK, OK. Yeah.
I'm into this.
If it's not the arc, it's the come sail away.
Yeah. Paint it white.
Yeah. Like, sure.
Get a coat of paint on that thing fast.
And what's inside?
You know, we don't have to limit it to sticks.
Other bands can.
Well, and that's what I was going to say.
I think you need another business minded musician in there.
Maybe someone with royalty, you know, royal prestige, like a knight,
a knight in Satan's service.
And I'm talking about Mr.
Gene Simmons, the restaurateur.
You know, you get him involved.
He's not going to like sharing power.
He's not going to like sharing attention, but he could bring a lot to the table.
Of course, he does bring a lot to the table.
But the Kiss, I don't believe has any songs about a boat, unfortunately.
So Scott Garner's favorite band does
have a song about boat and all references to other boats.
How about the Beach Boys?
The Sloop John B. What about that?
Oh, make it the Sloop John B.
It's a it's finally a
exactly accurate recreation.
This was the size of the Sloop John B.
These stages are where these cages are, where people were when they
wanted to go home because they felt so broke up.
That's exactly right.
And there's books that you wrote that are 500 pages long evidence
about the Sloop John B.
And it's where you explain how the Sloop John B could have existed.
And it did.
And it's yeah, well, it's all convincing.
It's converting people to, you know, Brian Wilson Beach Boys
ism as opposed to it's about converting people away from love ism.
Right. Because it's in Kentucky.
There might be more Mike Love supporters and people who would still go see
the Beach Boys. And now, look, I'd love to ride a roller coaster with the guy.
But I think he's using that name a little wrongly these days.
And I don't like that he's going around to Trump events. So
yeah, that made a difference.
Mike Love did not save the campaign ultimately.
And then also.
And what's interesting, too, is that there were dinosaurs on the Sloop John B.
Yeah, leave them.
The lyrics don't say there were dinosaurs, but there were.
And it explains it all here at the Sloop John B.
That's the was not was deck.
That's where Walk the Dinosaur plays.
Yes, that's the name of that song, right?
Yes, yes. Great, great.
Well, all the best music is going to be at.
So do you just call it maybe you just unify it?
Obviously, Sticks Beach Boys was not was all the best bands get involved.
But and Kiss Kiss is in there, too.
But is this is it Hard Rock Park to
Hard Rock Park?
Is there a biblical way to like like
what's when Jesus comes back from the dead?
It's the resurrection, the rising.
It's the resurrection.
Hard Rock Park Resurrection. Yeah.
Oh, that's good. Yeah.
The rising is, of course, Bruce Springsteen song.
That's who the boat that rocked.
Hard Rock Park Resurrection, the boat that rocked,
which was the official name of in America.
This movie was called Pirate Radio with Nick Frost and
Philip Seymour Hoffman and Bill Nye about the pirate stations in England.
Oh, weird. OK.
Well, yeah. Then the whole thing is Hard Rock Park.
What do we like?
Hard Rock Park rising Hard Rock Park.
Wait, what's the resurrection?
Yeah. Hard Rock Park Resurrection.
I mean, either one. Yeah, I think either one is good.
I don't know. I don't.
And then it's the boat that rocked within that.
Both that rocked. Yeah, that's good.
That could be the simulator ride.
You're like, we've got to get offshore.
We've got to get to the oil rig where we're broadcasting the kink songs.
And then there's a hologram of John Binkowski that appears.
It'd be why don't we save pod the robot reprogram him,
right, make sure that he doesn't have any bigoted views.
So we'll say we'll save him. Right.
And what if like every because there's 12 rooms in that VR experience,
they're all programmed to different things and just offhand.
It's all stopping rocket disasters.
Like we're all going to go in the time machine to save the plane.
Right. Buddy Holly.
Don't get on that plane, big buffer and Buddy Holly.
I'm pod. I'm here to save you.
Not in the religious way, right?
No, like your life. Oh, yeah, baby.
One of the rooms is pod convinces Stephen Page not to quit the bare naked ladies.
Oh, there. Well, yeah, one of the major one of the big major stories in rock
that shake the world.
Yeah. Stopping John Denver from going skiing.
Yeah. Pod yanks him off the slopes.
Wait, was he skiing or a foot? Wait, Sonny Bono.
Sonny Bono was a yeah. Denver was a plane. Yeah.
All right. So we'll pull him out of the plane.
We'll pull Sonny Bono away from the skis.
And that's great. Yeah.
It's a lot of missions of getting people not to get on planes.
Mostly planes, largely planes.
I mean, this is yeah, it's unlimited.
It's unlimited. And also you'd have
I mean, there'd be so many so many just opportunities for walk around characters.
And it would just be it would be full of life.
You could really do a ton with it. Yeah.
Would it be cruel to keep the animals at the petting zoo,
but to paint them kiss colors?
No, not at all. No.
As long as it's safe, we'll make sure it's whatever we're using is safe for them.
Yeah, we do need to branch out a little more than Hard Rock Park.
And that's why you have a walk around like Drake character.
And he sings God's plan.
His big hit song. OK.
Well, that's still in the day.
Religious roots. We do honor them.
Yeah. And a big mascot, Drake.
That sounds pretty good to me. Yeah.
So that's I mean, kids stay awake.
Actually, maybe not.
We saved it.
We saved it. But it's going to take a couple of years for this to have.
This place has to fall apart slowly.
I think it is being burnt to the ground for insurance money slowly.
And yes, well, can Ham learn a lesson from all this as humanity did from the flood?
Perhaps not.
But I hope maybe some Kentucky land will be going for real cheap soon
and we can grab it on behalf of John Binkowski.
I think that's a great idea.
And when we eventually have Binkowski on, we'll float this idea to him.
We really did. At this point, we really got to talk to that guy.
Yeah, that's a good that's a good goal for the near future.
But for now, we close out.
You survived podcast, the ride Weird Easter Edition. Amen.
Thank you, everyone, for being here.
Follow us on the socials.
We'll post pictures of weird dinosaur giant fights over there.
And for three bonus episodes every month, you can check out the second gate
at Patreon.com slash podcast, the ride.
Everyone have a very happy Easter.
Have hopefully the last holiday for a little bit that has to be done
in a weird, careful, bad way.
And next Easter will finally be a rager.
I can't wait.
I'm going to go as nuts as all those pagans did before the flood.
Oh, my gosh. Dying.
I'm going to die so many eggs every year.
Every honey baked ham out of like location is going to just be a full on bacchanal.
You know, I will say I'm going a little crazy right now
because I'm going to go to a grocery store pickup.
And I did order some fruit punch flavored peeps.
Wow. So that's pretty wild.
That's so bad.
Peeps, the notorious.
It's like cliched to say how bad peeps are.
And you added fruit punch to the mix.
I am. Well, I did not create the candy, but I am a longtime fan of peeps.
I believe peeps, people saying peeps are bad or slander.
I was loved peeps as a child.
So we'll see. Maybe they're out of them.
It also looked like one of those niche items where sometimes I add it
to the order and they're like, we don't carry this.
What are you doing?
So we'll see.
I guess of all the things to get wrong in your mobile grocery orders, that one.
But I don't know. Maybe maybe this one you throw a fit.
Yeah, no, I've never thrown a fit at one of these pickups yet.
But I might today if I don't get my fruit punch flavored peeps.
Well, please report back.
Let us know how they are in a post Easter episode soon. Sure.
Everyone else, see if you can find them in your hometown.
And we'll talk to you after Easter.
So long. Bye. Bye.
By following us on Twitter and Instagram at Forever Dog Team
and liking our page on Facebook.