Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, The Second Gate,
where today we discuss a true pillar
of the Universal Studios experience,
the possibility of seeing a guy
who kind of resembles Doc Brown.
I'm Scott Gardner, I'm Great Scott Gardner, right?
Sure, and Mike Carlson joins us as always.
Yes, I was, we were just discussing
how we're gonna start this episode.
I would have just been like,
Great Scott, this is the best I can do.
And then we would have segued into that, so.
Bernie Sanders showed up on the record.
Jeff Garland.
You know, it's a hard impression to do
was gonna be my teaching moment out of trying to do that.
It's a hard character to play, I think,
exactly how the original person did.
Anyway, Jason Sheridan.
It is, and I think that's good to know at the beginning
as we discuss, you know, I guess in general,
like walk around Doc Brown's at Universal Studios,
because the temptation will certainly be
to make fun of the lack of accuracy.
However, like, could any of us do it?
I don't think we could.
I think we would not pass that audition.
We should try a few lines here and there on this episode,
but I don't think, I mean, I didn't spend weeks on this,
but yeah, I think that it's a very tough thing to do.
I also think there's a problem
when you're doing a character
that's been so, you know, burned in people's minds.
It's so iconic.
Rarely do you get like a Carl Urban,
McCoy Bones from Star Trek, where you go,
oh my God, he's doing the exact voice
and the exact attitude, and that's perfect.
Wow.
What to, Carl Urban?
Carl Urban plays Dr.
McCoy in the J.
J.
Abrams Star Trek.
Oh.
And I think widely regarded as like,
whoa, he really got the essence of the original character
of DeForest Kelly's iconic performance
as Dr.
McCoy on Star Trek, but it's hard.
It's very hard and often impossible, I would think.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Yeah, it's very specific.
And I think that's sort of why we landed on doing this
as an episode is just that it's funny
when Universal Studios has had things
where, you know, you do associate this part
with a specific person, the person who played the part,
that's why, because a person played it,
and how willing Universal has been to just have like,
I don't know, a guy, which is a wig, yeah, sure.
Of course, yeah, a wig.
Could it should be a nice wig?
No, I don't know, that doesn't matter.
That's fine.
So it's like white hair.
That's like the easiest kind of wig to do.
So just grab whatever you can find
and throw somebody out there.
Should be tall, doesn't have to be, it would help,
but old, young, doesn't matter.
They should be older than 20.
If we have a 20-year-old working here,
put him in a Shrek suit or a bob, a minion.
But, you know, so like a little bit of, yeah,
they should be, you know, older, north of 21.
Yeah.
That's, yeah, so the book, yeah,
there must be so many different bullet points in the book,
in the Universal book about Doc Brown,
and they're all what Scott just said,
plus five more pages of just what, yeah.
And if this is, and if any of that stuff doesn't apply,
that doesn't matter.
Let a child do it, we don't care.
Yeah.
Let a seven-year-old do it.
We kept throwing back and forth between us
the phrase off-brand Doc Brown,
but like technically on-brand in terms of this
is the corporate intellectual property holder
doing this and giving the okay and paying for the materials
and hiring the person to do it.
But off-brand and like this execution seems off
in a way that like, you know,
kind of Jack Sparrow wandering around Hollywood studios.
It's like, well, anyone can kind of do the like,
oh, hello, lovely, you know, whoever can do that.
But with Jack Sparrow,
anytime I've seen him or most of the times I've seen him,
and it's not a lot, it hasn't been in Disneyland in a while,
the Jack Sparrow costume they give the performer is good.
And the makeup.
That does a lot of the heavy lifting.
Yeah.
The makeup is pretty good.
As Scott was saying, the difference here is it really feels
like the Doc Brown just went to the Dollar General
and found a lab coat and they like spray painted
like the shades, the sunglasses.
And then they're like, all right,
did you work on the impression?
And the performer said, a little bit.
And they go, ah, fine.
He's loud, right?
Yes, you're right.
He does not speak softly.
This just don't be like Steven Wright
and this should go great.
Yeah.
I think there's a, I think that, I mean, it is harder too,
because Jack Sparrow obviously has like a butt
and beard mustache, headband.
There's a lot of stuff on the face.
So there is something funny just seeing Doc Brown
and you like squinch and you go, oh, it's Doc Brown.
And then you get closer and you go, ooh,
that's not Doc Brown.
Like, is this guy, did this guy wander over
from Hollywood Boulevard perhaps?
You don't know.
There's something funny about it.
Now it's tough because Disney has cartoon characters
and then they have human beings play them.
And that's an easier thing, I think,
for our brains to handle.
It's easier when you see a fun performer
who's playing Gaston.
He doesn't look anything like him.
He doesn't sound like him, but he's got the attitude.
He's got the vibe.
And he's having fun with, and he's got the vibe.
That's a lot easier because if, you know,
if Doc Brown was initially just a cartoon,
I think maybe we wouldn't be doing this episode.
I don't know.
Sure, sure.
And it's why we landed on this as opposed to,
Mike, you threw out like,
is there a universal walk around character
who might be worthy of an episode?
Because this is a thing we haven't talked about a lot
is the presence of, the perennial presence of,
your W.
C.
Fieldses and your Groucho Marxes
and your Lucies.
I guess we've discussed Lucy a little bit.
But, you know, this is a fun part about Universal Studios
that classic characters of yore who now,
if you're a child in 2021,
these are probably 100% unrecognizable to you.
You like, undoubtedly have never seen W.
C.
Fields
on here, not even like in a documentary about old things.
Cause a documentary about old things now
would be about less old things than that.
Yes.
I can't even imagine being a kid and like going,
who is that performer dressed in a suit?
And you're like, oh, it's W.
C.
Fields, son.
And then like, you have to explain that.
I mean, that doesn't even happen.
I probably doesn't even register to a kid
that that's like somebody I should be excited about.
C.
Fields also seemed like would be a lot of work
because I'm sure there's lots of weird stuff we would find.
No, he was perfect.
He was perfect, Jason.
I'm sure, you know, don't look into it.
Oh no, I'm not even concerned about scandals
and that sort of thing.
It's just like, no, there's gonna be some fun oddities.
Like there's gotta be a movie where it's like,
oh yeah, remember he was like the King of the Pigeons.
Remember that movie?
It was like the biggest movie of 1931
and now we don't remember it at all.
More along those lines.
I see, I see.
What I was thinking of.
Well, you will, whenever you have children,
you will definitely teach them about King of the Pigeons
as one of the first lessons
when the kids are able to absorb.
I would show the kids,
I think a lot of the Marx Brothers stuff does hold up.
And other than that, I think you have to go
for like physical stuff.
Charlie Chaplin, Buster Keaton.
Don't look into that either.
Don't look into that history either.
Anyway, yes, I hear what you're saying.
The equivalent now,
like let's look at some old entertainment.
Let's watch the Friends, I think,
is like what Universal should have now
is Joey and Chandler walking around.
I mean, that's now like, oh yeah, remember the past?
Even some of the office is old enough you could do.
Like by the time my kid is seven,
the first year of the office is gonna be a little old.
So to have a Michael Scott stroll in.
I still want everybody to have a cane and twirl it around.
Like, is that okay?
I know that's not what Michael Scott did,
but I would like to retain that
from the old studio characters.
Yeah.
Well, and here comes Emily from Emily's Reasons Why Not.
And she's got a little cane.
Samantha who?
Bumbling down the street.
Oh man, Michael Scott walk around is really,
I don't know why they haven't done that.
I guess, I'm trying to think like,
would Michael Scott or Chandler and Joey,
would that actually be better than Doc Brown in some way?
Cause they would just like,
Chandler would have to wear like a weird bowling shirt,
like a late nineties bowling shirt or something.
And you go, well, that's Chandler.
He looks exactly like him.
And then Doc Brown was next to you.
You go, who the hell is this white lab coat weirdo?
I don't get it.
I don't know.
Maybe it's easier to pull up.
If you like really lather,
remember how Michael Scott initially was less
of a human being and had like, jet back,
like he'd a lot of grease in his hair.
If you went really far with that,
and then like, again, let's just keep,
let's stick with the rules of WC Fields.
And he has like caked on pale face makeup.
He's just, he's kind of like a,
he's a Kabuki of Michael Scott.
Maybe that way you just have to like push it really far.
It might, you might be able to pull it off.
Well, what if it's like the fairy godmother,
which I know they just updated the face
where a fairy godmother in Disney has like a plastic face.
Even though she's a human-ish looking character,
they have like a plastic scary face for her.
What if there was just a plastic Michael Scott
Halloween mask that the performer could wear?
Maybe that solves the problem of even Doc Brown.
Maybe they should switch completely to plastic
Halloween masks for everyone.
I mean, that fairy godmother, yeah,
the Cinderella fairy godmother,
it's really insane that what they were doing
in the park for so long,
that is a truly ghoulish character.
You would see it and think,
oh my God, it's Cinderella's wicked fairy godmother.
You would immediately reclassify the character as evil
based on the walk around.
Like some-
The fairy godmother of the purge.
The doll-faced fairy godmother,
the lifeless doll-faced fairy godmother.
Oh no, she's been cursed again.
She Adrena-chromes, so that's why she looks like,
from all the Adrena-chrome,
she absorbs the power of little doll-faced children
and that's why she looks doll-faced.
Yes, so Universal has not gone the doll-faced route.
It is funny, because I kept trying to crack this exactly.
Lucy, I have a video, my mother and my sister
and I went to Universal five-ish years ago, six years ago,
and Lucy was sitting in the performer playing Lucille Ball,
was sitting in a director's chair.
We made my mom go over and sit next to her
in the seat and talk to Lucy.
And I was like, this woman's pretty good.
She's playing Lucy.
It's really like, it's working for me.
Obviously I know what Lucy looks like.
I know this isn't the voice, but I was like,
I don't know, pretty close, pretty good.
But with Doc Brown, it's just never quite there.
It's definitely, yeah, it's always iffy.
And I might vote if you guys are cool with this
with diving into one of the things
that inspired this episode,
which is that we, so we just did this episode
about Nickelodeon Studios, which was a lot of fun.
And one of the things about Nickelodeon Studios in Orlando
was this time capsule that moved.
It now is in Burbank, kind of close to us.
We got no leads, not a lead was gathered from the episode.
Unless do you have, was there a lead?
We had someone message us actually.
Really?
Oh wait, I missed this.
Oh, wow.
Okay.
I forgot even to mention it.
Yes, we do.
We have a little bit of a lead, I think.
There's a way that we could go see this lid in the ground
that I'm so excited to see.
I get to see this lid.
In an office building, no one has stepped foot in
in one year over one year possibly.
Yeah, it's not like an immediate thing or not a guarantee,
but there's one person that seems to think it's possible.
There's a possibility for making it happen.
So we have one lead, yeah.
This is unrelated, but something I like.
Did you guys see this on Twitter that we, from that episode,
got a shout out from Moe from Guts,
whose daughter listens to Podcast The Ride evidently?
Yes, fantastic.
That's great news.
Love Moe.
We love Moe.
We didn't talk about Guts enough.
I mean, Guts really loomed large,
but it's a theme park podcast,
so we're trying to hit all the things.
I was listening back and I was like,
oh, we didn't talk about any of the shows enough.
We didn't even mention about, my brother and me,
we didn't even mention Goo Punch, which is a fantastic.
Oh my God, do you remember Goo Punch?
You don't remember Goo Punch?
It was when Goo was fantasizing about having his own drink.
This is like Ivan Ooze when he was selling the Ooze.
Oh my God, I have to do this.
I just want to see if it brings your memory back of Goo Punch,
because I was bringing it up to a couple people
and they reminded me of Goo Punch.
And then I said it to my sister and she goes,
oh, Goo Punch.
I mentioned that we talked about my brother and me
and she goes, oh, Goo Punch.
And I was like, why didn't we say Goo Punch?
And here is Goo Punch.
Here's Goo imagining if he had a drink.
He's on a sparkly R&B stage now.
Yes.
A big top hat.
One plus one is always two.
I'm a goo with a drink for you.
My Goo Punch goes with any snack.
So get back to check, because it's a goo attack.
Goo!
Oh, Goo, you're all that.
I am and I am.
And so is my Goo Punch.
Come on, everybody.
It's a big can, like the old Juicy Juice cans.
It's a massive can.
Bright king.
Goo Punch.
I mean, Goo Punch, fantastic.
Probably the best moment in the whole series.
Goo!
I, boy, yeah, again, what happened to Goo?
Why didn't Hollywood embrace Goo the way they were supposed to?
I don't know, Goo was so funny.
So yeah, we should have talked more about all the shows,
including Guts and Thank You Mo for that shout out.
That means a lot.
Honestly, that would have, as a kid, you'd be like,
Mo is gonna like say something nice about me?
Or just even say I exist?
Mo is gonna acknowledge I exist?
She, the integrity that Mo lends to Guts,
where you suddenly, just by virtue of Mo's accent,
you're like, well, this is a global event.
This is an international, I know what the Olympics are like.
I've seen one of those on TV at this age.
They have British accents, there's accents.
So clearly, this is like, there are stakes to Guts.
Right.
This is not just like something happening in a soundstage.
This is gonna change lives.
This is gonna go in an almanac.
It legitimized hooking a kid up to a bungee cord
and making him jump off of a two story set of stairs
and throwing a basketball in a hoop.
Yeah, no, it was very, very exciting.
Yes, it felt like important.
Guts felt important, for sure,
when we were watching it, I think.
Yeah, it felt the same as the Olympics.
Yes.
I saw Barcelona and like, okay, and now Guts.
All right, so these are as crucial.
Yes, 100%.
Yeah, yeah.
So anyway, love all the Nickelodeon stuff.
Excited about this lead.
But the burial of the Nick Studios time capsules,
we're here to talk about a reminder.
It was buried in 1992 to be opened in 2042.
And the ceremony was overseen by host of Guts, Mike O'Malley,
sudden appearance from Joey Lawrence,
who showed up to put in a hat that says, whoa, 92.
And then they're about to bury the big orange time capsule.
They're about to put it in the ground.
And then a familiar face shows up.
I'm gonna play maybe a little more of this
than often we would play as a clip.
You guys just raise your hands if you wanna stop it
and talk about something.
And I'll stop it as well.
But I think this is a wonderful scene.
And maybe one of the best examples
of what an off-brand Doc Brown can get themselves up to.
So here is this very crucial moment.
Yeah, put that on right there.
I want you to do the honors of pressing the button
and lowering our time capsule into the ground.
Crane man, are you ready?
Okay, beautiful.
All right, Mike, we go.
Go ahead, press the button, man.
We're all set.
Whoa, who's that?
I have no idea, Mike.
It's a DeLorean.
A DeLorean.
Who is that?
Is it Michael Tate Fox?
I don't know who it is.
He's driving around here.
This guy looks familiar.
Actually, ladies and gentlemen,
it's Dr.
Emmett Brown from the Future Institute
of Technology here at Universal Studios in Florida.
It's kind of wrong.
It's not the right name.
Dr.
Brown!
Told everything!
Go bury that time capsule!
Doc, what's the problem?
What is it?
Michael, joy, thank goodness I got here in time.
Terrible news, just terrible.
What is it?
Well, I was working on one of my new DeLorean prototypes.
When I actually crossed-
That, by the way, felt like,
that we were like worried that if we were cross paths
with Michael Malley, that he would yell at us.
That's how that, I felt like he was yelling at the actor.
He was like, get it out!
Spit it!
Now that he's out, let's just say,
today you still see Doc Brown's in the park.
The wigs are not this bad.
This is an Albert Einstein wig.
This is not even what Doc's hair is like.
This is like early Mickey in Disneyland
where there were holes in his face for no reason,
or seemingly no reason.
He was all carved up, yes.
Okay, so Doc's here.
Shot 50 years into the future,
and that's when I made the discovery
of catastrophic proportions.
What's the problem, what's the discovery?
By the year 2042, there'll be no more GAC in the world.
No more GAC?
Exactly, so for the sake of future-
Kind of like forgetting stuff as he goes.
I got the liners, it's all right.
Okay, we have real Joey Lawrence,
like recognizable celebrity, good get for this thing,
and then Doc Brown comes out,
and it's just a guy we've never seen,
and probably will never see again.
What else was I gonna say?
Oh, and also the GAC, the fact that now we know,
now everything's so siloed by corporation,
and we know that, all right,
and Peacock's over here, and Paramount Plus is over here,
and like never shall they meet,
but that Doc Brown, a universal property,
is dealing with GAC, a Viacom property,
it's all just like, nobody's keeping track of who owns what,
nobody cares, there were no lawsuits,
none of this mattered at the time.
It's very interesting, yeah,
that Doc Brown was just treated as like,
if you wanna use him and you're in universal, go for it.
It doesn't matter, well, you don't have to,
I mean, Bob Gale signs off on literally anything
that comes across his desk,
but it doesn't have to even go through him.
Just use Doc Brown however you'd like,
and who, anyone, pick anyone to play him,
it doesn't, go for it.
Yeah, do you wanna look it over,
make sure we got her now, okay, that's fine.
Only two years after the last movie,
not even two full years after the last movie.
Right, and do we talk about on the Back to the Future
episode, the actual Christopher Lloyd special
with Universal Florida?
I can't remember.
We didn't really touch on it,
but that's pretty fun, that special.
Where he goes there before the park is open,
he's like, it's for potential investors to like,
Doc Brown goes forward into the future
where the park is now open.
Right, so like, yeah, it was like, Doc Brown,
the real Doc Brown, Christopher Lloyd,
had been involved in the park as well before, yeah,
I don't know how many, was it a year before it was open?
I don't know, something like that.
Something like that, I mean, in 1989,
I think they were filming like Double Dare or something,
some Nickelodeon game shows were shooting
in Finnish sound stages next to a massive,
empty construction site, which is funny to think about,
that that is like, you were driving through
a construction site, like, no, I'm not working
construction, I'm going to the Finnish game show
sound stage, that's where I work.
Yeah, two years of filming Double Dare
with nothing else around it.
Yeah, something like that, yeah.
Okay, so.
Some gack into that time capsule,
otherwise the future is fucked.
Doc, I understand what you're saying,
but you know, I mean, I don't know if I can get some
on such short notice, I mean, these things take time.
Wait a minute.
I have a suggestion, I think it's time for the Gackmeister.
That's a good idea, Joey.
Gackmeister!
Gackmeister, right here!
You got the Gackmeister.
Then this guy runs out with a bunch of splats on his jacket,
that's how you know he's the Gackmeister.
Now, I think this is more interesting, appearing to me,
like, I want to see the Godzilla versus Kong,
Gackmeister versus Doc Brown.
Oh yeah, do you think they get along?
Is Doc, does he believe that Gack is a pseudoscience?
Yeah, that's possible.
Does he need the Gack to power the fusion,
whatever it is on the top of the future,
the future DeLorean, like when he dumps trash in
at the end of the first, back to the future?
Runs on Gack now!
I have a Gackgeiser that's for my private use.
I thought it was Hocum, I was wrong, I was wrong.
Now that's your Doc Brown,
that sounds a little like your Dompardo.
Oh yeah, I mean, any sort of like, this guy is really,
he's, when you're doing an impression,
you hone in on like one sentence or one thing
to try and turn it on, and he's really going for the nasal.
The nasal kind of twang, like, nobilians.
There's, I found in every Doc Brown, there is like,
yes, a couple words where I go, oh good, that's it.
And then it's gone for a couple sentences,
and then it comes back, and that's including me.
That's including me, probably with even less good,
like less accuracy on one word or one phrase.
The longer you have to talk and perform a full scene
with Joey Lawrence, it goes in and out.
Right, exactly.
Hey, we forgot to talk about Joey Lawrence
on the Nickelodeon episode.
I did a what's he up to now search,
and the answer is he is more willingly
in the Roe versus Wade movie that Jamie Kennedy
did not bother to read the script for when he signed on.
Oh no.
Man, of course, God, they all go that way.
Yeah.
Joey, you're gonna be in a movie.
It's gonna be very bad, and try to set society back.
Many years.
Yeah, he runs out here and said like,
we have to stop Roe versus Wade.
Yeah, you're right.
Stop the signing of that awful legislation
that destroys all the, kills all these babies.
No, the making of the film.
Whoa.
The film that has holds a record
for being the quickest to be free on Hoopla
and every other streaming platform available.
You're gonna work with Jamie Kennedy, Joey.
We have to stop it.
He's an up and comer, right?
No, he's like, he's in for good.
No, he's weird now.
He's weird and sweaty.
Okay, everybody's in the scene.
We're gonna need that, and this Gax has got to last 50 years,
so make sure, get it in there.
Okay, thanks Gax Meisner, we can always count on you.
Always count on the gate cluster.
Make sure that thing is sealed tight.
We don't want Gax all over those CDs and stuff like that.
Okay, get that thing back on there.
Well, we have averted future catastrophe once again.
Thanks a lot, Doc, appreciate it.
No problem, Michael, don't mention it.
Hey, actually, while we have you here,
could you possibly tell me
who's gonna win the World Series this year?
Great Scott, I'm not gonna get into a mess like that again.
You know what happened the last time?
I'm just kidding you, Doc.
Oh look, I'm gonna get back to the Institute
of Future Technology and more time travel volunteers
here at Universal Studio waiting
to try temporal displacement.
Michael, good luck with your time.
Doc, thanks again, man.
Take care.
You always say hello to Blossom for me.
All right, thanks Doc.
We'll see you all in the future.
Bye bye.
Doc Brown, everybody, Doc Brown.
See you later, Doc.
He's a crazy cookie man, man.
He is a cookie guy.
Okay, hey, Vicki, did you get all that on camera?
Then they cut to the most upset girl.
I think I did.
I feel so much pressure having to film this.
Why does Doc Brown know Blossom?
Why does he have so many friends who are minors?
This is all pop culture, we're friends.
They all knew each other back then.
Now we think it's a big deal
when things are gonna cross over.
Everything was just crossing over always when we were kids
and it was not a big deal.
It was due to writer laziness.
Yes, and in that Doc Brown special from Universal,
and I don't know, that might be a different episode
at this point, but Doc Brown goes
and sees Ghostbusters and he gets a proton pack
and he goes, Ghostbusters.
And I'm like, holy shit, this is fantastic.
As a kid, because I think I've said this before,
and it's partly fueled by the fact that I have these toys
made by this company, NECA, that are all on the same scale
and I have them here to demonstrate.
You have your Marty McFly in the same scale as Toca
from Secret of the U's.
And as the two toys are sitting on the shelf,
my little brain, my little kid brain now is going,
man, you know what, that would have been good
if they made a bad Back to the Future
Ninja Turtle crossover with Toca and Razor.
I go, man, that would have been fantastic.
And then this Doc Brown clip
where he puts on the proton pack and he shoots Stay Puft,
I go, that's a piece of it.
That's a part of my fantasy imagined at the time.
And you go, yeah, wouldn't it be great
if you know how they make,
everything's just like IP garbage now
and it's all mashed up and we like some of it
and don't like some of it?
Wouldn't it be great if there was all of that in the past
and there were 10 Back to the Futures
and half of them were crossing over?
Like, and it was mostly trash,
but you look back and you go,
yeah, there was that one fun scene where like Doc Brown
had to try to like help Toca and Razor
mutate into something else or like make different Toca
and Razors to fight Toca and Razor.
Wouldn't that be great if now we could watch those?
I think yes, it would be great.
He goes back to the 30s or whatever
and helps the League of their own.
He helps them win the game.
Fantastic.
He makes a new bat for them.
He invents a new bat that helps the League of their own win.
Yes, wouldn't that be fantastic if we could see that?
And you go, did you know there's a weird
Back to the Future movie where he goes
and meets a League of their own and you go, really?
And you go, yeah, yeah, it's NHBMX, you should watch it.
And then we all like post about it and think it's crazy.
What a dream.
What a dream that would be.
They should, you know, if it didn't interrupt
the original continuity, if they were made kind of
of the scale of like that weird last,
Honey, I Shrunk the Kids, Honey, We Shrunk Ourselves.
Ourselves, yeah.
Actors could change, like, you know,
that movie doesn't like invade or ruin the experience
of the first two, Honey, I Shrunk the Kids.
It's its own thing.
Yeah, there should have been 10 weird
straight to video Back to the Futures.
Rory works with people from other movies.
Yeah, it's like, oh no, the Gremlin's stowed away.
Yes, any, it doesn't matter what the movie is
they cross over with, it's just the idea
that they're crossing over is good.
But it does have to be the old, it has to be in the past
because the next 10 Back to the Futures that will happen
when Zemeckis and Gale are dead,
those aren't gonna be the fun we want.
Those are gonna be a different thing.
It'll be like that total recall remake with Colin Farrell.
And it's just like, oh, this is really dry and serious.
Again, we're talking about a devil-may-care attitude.
They're like, yeah, we gotta film this thing for Universal.
And it'll be a preview on NBC at 9 p.
m.
on a Friday.
And then we're gonna put it on tapes for investors.
And so, yeah, have Doc Brown with the Ghostbusters.
And now it would be like, okay,
if Doc Brown's gonna meet the Ghostbusters,
we have to get some writers rooms together.
We have to get different teams of lawyers together.
The marketing people and the merchandising people
have to get on a call.
It's just so complicated.
Yeah, it's dry.
In the past, it would have just been like,
Marty, the little giants are stuck in ancient Rome.
We need to rescue the little giants.
Come quick!
We got to make sure Gomez and Morticia meet.
The Addams family will be destroyed.
Can you imagine that the two Lloyds meet in the movie?
Oh my God, Fester and Brown eating up.
Two of the most legitimate best characters of all time.
I'm not even being funny when I say it.
Big time.
Christopher Lloyd is a fucking genius who deserves,
give Christopher Lloyd an Oscar, first of all.
I've said this before.
The guy has been in enough movies
with playing wildly different characters that are perfect.
And it's unbelievable.
Anyway, yes, imagine this.
Let's ask it to the listener.
What movie from 30 years ago do you want
Back to the Future to cross over with?
And give us a little piece of dialogue from the movie
and we'll retweet some of the fun ones.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's a great idea.
And it's a weird request.
We don't want them to happen now.
Not now.
The way things are remade now, no, no, no.
I don't wanna see a poster with like a really,
oh, the huge brawny humorless Australian playing American,
big grizzled guy as the new Marty.
This is, I don't want this.
I want, yeah, let's imagine these all happen.
We're banged out haphazardly in 1993.
Right, like, let's see.
What was the-
Three men and a baby need our help with the baby.
What's the Michael J.
Fox weird presidents movie
or like he's like like Mike.
What is that?
What am I thinking?
No, you're-
Life with Mikey.
We have to find, we have to help life with Mikey.
Mikey's life will be destroyed.
We have to fix.
No, it's not about your life, Mikey.
It's about life with Mikey's children.
We have to make sure Clifford gets on that plane
or he'll never meet uncle Martin.
And uncle Martin will never, after some travails,
prove to his fiance who looks like my fiance
that he can handle children in his life.
Yes, these are perfect.
All these are perfect.
And you give us your version of perfect, please.
So with that, you have to like the sort of devil
may care spirit of the, you know, yeah,
some guy who doesn't really look like Doc Brown
makes Blossom part of Back to the Future canon,
makes Gack part of canon.
And yeah, I don't know, you know, it's good.
I think that I've quickly landed on it's good.
It's good that they did this.
And I don't know, I hope that actor, you know,
hey, maybe there was a part for him in Roe versus Wade also.
I hope that's true.
I assume was produced in Orlando probably.
One of the rare movie sets that are taking walk-ins.
You're willing to, we can film you
and you know what this is, right?
We've got scripts.
This is the fourth lead.
Are you sure you want this?
All right.
Now, can I play it sort of like as a Doc Brown type?
Yeah, sure.
We don't care.
This just has to get these words have to get filmed.
Look, the Mercer's just want it done, okay?
You know, I wanna, I was being a little negative.
I do like that this is how they've,
Doc Brown exists in the parks.
I've been a little bit negative and I'm, you know,
I'm trying to be, I guess funny here,
but I do think the way they're doing Doc Brown now is good.
And I like it.
I just wanna say that on the record
before we go forward with more.
Yeah, yeah.
I agree.
I mean, so this is the most fun one, I think,
that they just like, they had Doc Brown's hired.
Oh, we have to do this.
We had this idea for this beat in the Nickelodeon special
and this guy has the costume already.
He fits in the costume.
So we give him an hour to prep, kind of look at a script,
but you know, they'll wing it too.
And then it happens.
But there's, yeah, there's been this, you know,
in the park since the nineties.
I mean, I have various clips.
here's one guy, this is from, you know, I mean,
the big day for these people was October 21st.
Was it the, is that the day?
2015, which was the day depicted in Back to the Future 2.
That is the future that they went to.
So there was a lot of videos from that day.
That's Back to the Future Day.
So everybody wants a moment with Doc Brown on that day.
And this guy, this is like one way,
we're talking about how do you do this voice.
And here's, this guy gave it a shot.
He has an interesting angle on it.
I don't know if it is the angle, but let's just,
let's hear him.
There's a lot of competing sound, but here we go.
Quite how we predicted, but not to look.
Because of course, your future has been written.
But the best advice I can give you is,
your future's what you make it.
So they get a good one, okay?
Thank you.
Okay.
He like, his key is like a little wobble, okay?
Ha ha ha ha.
Which is, what does that remind me of?
That's like Jimmy Fallon doing Barry Gibb.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's a little bit high pitched.
It's a little more high pitched.
I can see.
From the state of Sydney, okay?
I could see where he got there from.
I could see where he's get, I can see it.
But I don't know that I would have heard that and gone
without the context and I don't know that I would have
heard it and said, oh, Doc Brown.
He was saying different lines.
He wasn't already saying the future's what you make of it
to make it a good one.
Right.
Yeah.
If he was saying park over here, $20, 30 for valet.
And you were just thinking.
Here's your coffee token.
Here's your token for your free coffee.
The machine doesn't work today.
The machine is out of order.
Bonnie, the machine is out of order.
Bonnie.
A warning from the future.
The coffee token does not work.
That was the day that in another part of the country
at an out of town series of Jimmy Kimmel tapings,
the actual Marty McFly and Doc Brown,
Michael J.
Fox and Christopher Lloyd showed up in a Delorean
for that episode of Jimmy Kimmel Live.
For a segment that I watched a minute of
and then I saw it was nine minutes long.
And I was like, I'm not, I don't need to watch all of this.
I watched all of that at the time.
Yeah.
You know, yeah.
I roll my eyes at like viral talk show moments,
but I love it back as a future enough, but I'm like, yeah,
yeah, it's long.
There's probably some trims.
It's a little long.
I don't disagree with that.
You know what was great though is that he had,
Jimmy had like Letterman people for that week
cause it was in New York.
So there was a line about like,
I have to warn you about Biff.
And then they cut it was Biff Henderson,
Letterman's stage manager.
What a good tie together.
They have the second most famous Biff,
Letterman stage manager.
Yeah.
So I liked that.
Now I'm not saying, look,
the times when Christopher Lloyd is on some show
next to a DeLorean,
I feel like it happens about three times a year.
I don't know.
Like he's on some discovery show now where they're like
trying to find a DeLorean.
I'm not sure what it is.
I just saw an ad for it.
So I'm not saying I necessarily watch all
of the DeLorean content.
But I do think that one was at least,
that was at least fun in a different way.
Sort of an elevation.
Better than when he came out in the,
I mean, we all think about it and talk about it.
The Funny or Die, Art of the Deal,
the film that they made where Johnny Depp is Trump member.
We all, you know, you know,
and you know that Christopher Lloyd is in it
as a pseudo Doc Brown.
He's like an off-brand Doc Brown in the movie.
They'd never say what he is.
The wig isn't very good.
He has weird goggles that are not the spray painted goggles.
Although as I say all this,
I'm reminded of a better Funny or Die Doc Brown thing.
Did I already say this in the Back to the Future episode
that I, there was this video that they did.
I didn't make it, but I was there when it happened.
This video that was like an ad for hover boards are real
and they're cool now.
And I was invited down to the set.
Like Christopher Lloyd's going to be there.
And I got to go watch him get out of a DeLorean,
which my heart stopped.
And then he hit his head on the door.
Oh no.
Oh man.
I mean, but also that was cool.
I mean, what a weird moment to see.
I bet it happened on the set of the films all the time.
That's a very difficult.
He had to like run in and out of the car.
So that felt like, I like that little slice of life
and like puncturing the childhood heroism of these people.
He seemed cool.
I didn't meet him, but he seemed cool.
There's a number of those.
He cameos in a million ways to die in the West.
Oh yeah.
Doc Brown in that, right?
Where he's Doc Brown, like don't worry about,
don't look at this.
Like when Seth MacFarlane walks into a barn.
And then there's a commercial
for an Argentinian electronic store chain
where it's like 2011.
Everyone's got smartphones with decent video around there
starting to get them.
And it's like a found footage kind of like
people are walking along the street
and a DeLorean crashes into the front
of this electronic store.
And he pops out and he's like, what year is it?
Where am I?
God.
Yeah, he's done it a lot.
There is a lot of other media where he's Doc.
I mean, it's related to the film,
but I really liked the music video for the power of love,
the Huey Lewis song that has like so much extra stuff
before the song starts.
Just like two minutes of rambling documentary
paced dialogue of Huey talking like,
hey, we haven't been around in a while, but here we are.
And it's a new song from the movie.
Like, why is all this in the cut?
And then Doc is improvising with a bunch of like,
he shows up at the cool rock club
and a bunch of rock rats all show up
that are poking around the vehicle
and he's clearly improvising.
And some guys like, what's that?
What's this?
Like pointing at some doodad and he says,
it is what it is.
Just a weird little Doc Bratt.
He like clearly could not invent in the moment
what the actual item is.
I like it though.
That's a good, that's an oddly eight minute music video.
Yeah.
I'm trying to think there's, he's like kind of Doc Brown
in Piranha 3D.
He's like kind of an old, like a crazy old scientist guy.
Wow.
He's been playing Doc Brown a lot.
So maybe really just like pay his day rate
and get him in the parks.
You know?
We could, oh, just have him, you just Christopher
and Christopher Lloyd is here always.
Like if he's not doing anything,
pay him his day rate and have him play Doc Brown
in the park for a couple hours.
Why not?
Like Wally Bogue, you're saying.
Like Wally Bogue would actually perform
at Disneyland quite a bit.
Yeah.
At the Golden Horseshoe.
Yeah, of course.
He seems down.
He's just like, he's a workhorse actor.
So point me to a place and I'll go.
Yeah.
A Doc Brown residency.
Yeah, they should do that with a.
Like Joe's pub, yeah.
Yeah, I think that's a good idea.
And you can have other like newer characters too.
You know, you could have your Steve Carell residency
at Universal Hollywood, you know?
Yeah.
Great idea.
They'll do some hits and you know they're gonna wanna sing
some standards or they're gonna wanna croon or something.
You know?
Well, you're just, you have McFarlane on the brain.
I got McFarlane on the brain.
Yeah, get him in the mix for sure.
I don't wanna tell a story out of school,
but in this, when I alluded to meeting Mark Summers,
he, and I don't remember the details,
but he seemed to imply that,
cause I asked like, was it like being down in Orlando
and being at the theme park?
And he was like, yeah, they kinda like wanted me
to be there always.
I think they wanted me to do Double Dare in the park.
And I'm like, guys, that would require a fight.
You don't have to pay King Kong and Jaws.
You would have to pay me to do the same thing over and over.
That's outside of the TV contract.
But don't quote me on that.
I think there was something like that.
Sure.
I have a series of just like photos here real quick.
I have some clips too.
So yeah, this is another Doc Brown wearing,
I guess, big khaki pants.
And he's holding Christopher Lloyd's arm in the air,
the real Christopher Lloyd,
who's just sort of in a polo shirt.
And that's pretty fun.
Christopher Lloyd looks pretty happy-ish.
You know, he amused by that.
I feel like anytime I've seen him like interacting,
he seems to honestly like not be that cynical
about anything, cause certain people, you know,
kind of are like, I don't want to be this character.
I don't want to be remembered just for this one thing I did.
He seems like he's cool and like, yeah, this is great.
You like me because of this?
Yeah, I'm good in that.
I'll show up to this day and let this Doc Brown.
Yeah.
Well, that was the closing of the ride.
They did a big ceremony where they had to wear,
and Bob Gale was there, if you can imagine.
They got Bob Gale.
Somehow they got some of Bob Gale's time.
And they like, it's a weird ceremony where like Doc makes
them connect the wires, you know,
like in the climax of the movie and like,
I think you know what to do with these.
And then they have, they connect them.
And then a bunch of fireworks go off.
And then there's a countdown clock that says
when the ride's going to close.
And then a really sleepy guy, the universal executive,
like now begins the final month.
Now we can send this attraction out in style.
Come one last time to say goodbye to our fair moments.
But it's just a weird like, hurry, Christopher Lloyd,
help me, Doc, close this.
There's, this happens a lot.
And we're going to, we have to do more special,
like episodes about specials where opening and closings,
because we've talked about the Benicio del Toro appearance
for the opening of Guardians, where he's not the collector,
even though he plays the collector,
he's there as Benicio del Toro.
And it feels like they wanted,
like they probably wanted Christopher Lloyd to be Doc Brown,
but he ends up being Christopher Lloyd,
which the reality I'm not sure of.
And like saying with Benicio del Toro, it's like,
he's here, but he's not, to put him in an outfit,
make him the collector and say, welcome to my collection.
Why, like why not?
But these, I think all these actors play it right
with their half commitment,
because there are technical errors like every time.
You're timing out pyro, like clearly these are not plays
that are rehearsed for weeks and weeks.
It's like, oh, well, I hope for the best.
I mean, remember the Galaxy's Edge one,
where it's like what's intended to be a huge soaring moment
where Harrison Ford says, this is for Peter,
for, and I have this right, for Peter Mayhew,
for like he's dedicating it to,
Chewbacca just passed away.
And it's interrupted by like,
the thing goes off at the wrong time
and he bangs it at the wrong time.
It's like, they're so fraught with errors always.
I feel like, if some of these,
some of the greatest actors ever committed more,
I think they would end up looking the fool.
Wouldn't it be funny though,
if he was dressed as Han Solo when he said that?
I would know, of course, for me, yes,
but we'd be laughing at him, you see.
I think he's, they're all smart to not.
the actors are smart to not,
but I would prefer if they forced,
an 80 year old Harrison Ford into the outfit one more time.
Put it on, we've got the prototype of the real lightsaber.
It does hurt people, we will hurt you.
Put on the outfit.
This is how they're making Indy five happen by the way.
Yeah, Josh Demaro has the saber,
he will slice your arm off Harrison.
You don't wanna make Josh Demaro mad,
Disneyland president.
Do not want to cross him.
Yeah, so this is, yeah, the video is fun.
I did, I watched a little bit of the video.
This Doc Brown also looks a little like Darryl Hammondish.
Sure, there's a Hammond-esque look to him.
He does look older though,
the Doc Brown from the Nickelodeon time capsule one
was so like lean and lanky.
Like it kind of, yeah, he definitely-
Like a younger mad scientist for sure,
but like not quite Doc Brown.
That guy was like Beakman.
He was like a different color haired Beakman.
Yeah, I liked Beakman as a child.
I will be on record as saying I was a big Beakman guy.
Oh yeah, but Beakman isn't Doc Brown.
Right, there's a younger, I found a guy who looks younger
too in the 1997 Doc Brown.
I don't know if you guys saw a 1997 Doc Brown,
but he's different.
I do have that in my search.
You have this guy?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Should we get a taste of him?
Is he audible?
I've seen him about five years.
Keep those dancing.
Hello there.
Oh hi, Doc Brown coming live from University of Florida.
Of course I'm coming live.
And that's like, okay-
This guy's got like a drifter vibe.
He's got like a five o'clock shadow.
He looks like he's like in his thirties.
Yeah, he looks like he's been hitchhiking.
He's got the voice part,
Dr.
Brown, da da da da.
He has like that cadence.
And then it sort of like goes away.
Oh, you've got the pattern.
You're from Scotland.
I've been there.
I just got a head start.
I was there about three and a half weeks ago.
And then he kind of just like,
it just starts talking to like this guy.
He's like kind of a little bit more like this.
I learned on the age when he hit about six times.
I'll never drive in Scotland again.
Next time I'll take a train.
Take care.
I don't know if he does have the pattern.
I know, yeah, driving in Scotland is a tough-
The first time, the first thing is Jason saying,
I feel like he has his way in with the cadence at the top
and then it sort of goes away.
Then he sort of loses it.
Yeah.
I think they need to,
one thing I think they could do
is switch up the outfit sometimes
because Ian Park, Doc Brown,
always has the pseudo graphic printed button-up,
aloha shirt with the, is it the train?
Is it the time train on it?
I think so.
There's a couple different shirts,
but it's, yeah, the ones I have here are the time train.
Yeah.
It's like a, if John Lasseter had a
back to the future time train shirt,
that's what it would look like.
Which he probably does.
He probably bought one of them.
Which a hundred percent he has one of these train shirts.
Yeah, I know what you're saying.
Cause it's like, why don't we have just like full
kind of like white jumpsuit,
like shopping mall back to the future one doc ever.
Why is it this?
I guess he's at the Institute
cause he works at the Institute.
So it's connecting to that mythology.
But the Institute is gone now.
So he can wear whatever he wants.
He could wear whatever he wants from any time.
He could have the red and yellow, you know,
from the future.
Well, I mean, Jason brings,
you do bring up a good point
because when we went to the eighties night at Disneyland,
a big draw was Mickey in his jazzer size,
like mouse, excuse me, mouse her size costume,
which is just like yellow sweats.
And everyone is flipping out.
And the same thing with totally Minnie.
Minnie was in her eighties outfit.
And that was such a big draw.
So I do feel like, you know,
Doc Brown has several iconic outfits.
The cowboy outfit, he has the future yellow outfit
with the jacket and the tie,
which that toy is coming out in a few months,
very excited about it.
But if Doc got in different outfits,
I feel like that would be a draw for the audience.
If you know like, oh, you know,
Doc Brown's got a new outfit today.
Let's go find him.
Let's go take a photo.
Do you think that,
or do you think that most of the people
at Universal Studios are like in a haze
of like three massive beers
and barely remember what the movie was?
Well, okay.
Well, I think.
There's us, but then there, you know what I mean.
It depends how big the audience of us is.
And it's specifically Universal.
Cause I would say almost any Disney night,
yes, a hundred percent.
That 80s night was sold out or close sold out.
And I'm sure a lot of people in there
were very excited to see Mickey wearing a sweatsuit.
So if-
You're combining us and back to the future fans.
That like, there is a rabbit fan base.
Back to the future fans are out of their minds.
Yeah.
So I do think, and again, it's not dad.
It's not your average dad going down there.
That's like, oh, we're going to go see Doc
wearing a different shirt, huh?
I spent this much money to go see Doc in a different shirt.
Like that's, yes, you're right, of course.
And is it 90% of people like that?
You may be, but that 10% still a nice chunk of people
and they're going to be very excited.
Do you think that there's,
Universal is going to make a profit
that would even pay for the new clothing to be made?
Do you think enough?
Like, are you going to make a trip up that you hear
that Doc Brown has a new shirt or new type of goggles
and you're going to go, you will go just for that.
Hook me to the lie detector.
If they said Doc Brown was wearing his
back to the future two yellow outfit,
I would be excited and absolutely go up there
and go see him just for that.
Obviously he'd go on another ride, have something to eat,
but absolutely I would go up there just for that.
And I swear on whatever you'd like me to swear on.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
If it was old West stuff, would you like that?
Or is that like the,
I like that.
Well, we don't care
about the old West as much.
We don't care about the old West as much.
I like that.
And if I was going up there,
I absolutely make a point to do it.
But if Doc was wearing his back to the future two outfit,
I will make a trip.
I will plan a day around it.
And if Doc was wearing Mickey's
jumpsuit.
Jumpsuit.
Sweatsuit, that I would think definitely you would go.
Definitely I would go,
cause it would be very confusing.
The marketing would be interesting too.
I would be like, gotta see what this is all about.
Is this like a shots fired at Disney thing?
I don't know.
Yeah.
So yes, I absolutely would go up to see that.
Is there, I mean, is there a Doc Brown outfit
you guys would want to see him in at the parks?
And you could be not in the movies either.
It could be in one of those fantasy crossovers.
He could be wearing a Ninja Turtle outfit.
You could be wearing Splinter's robe.
That's pretty good.
Pretty good.
How about just like a full like,
how about like vanilla ices jumpsuit
from the ice ice baby video.
Ice ice baby or, yeah, that would be good.
You would absolutely go up if you, if they said,
oh yeah, Doc Brown's wearing vanilla ices clothes today.
You go, what the hell?
Why?
Clearly this is, I think now we've opened a straight.
Universal, obviously what you have to do
is put Doc Brown in other people's clothes.
It's right there.
Why aren't you doing it?
You know, Disney is smarter.
Disney is smarter about a lot of this stuff.
And we've talked about the marketing from the merchandise
to certain events.
And yeah, Universal's got to listen to this and take this.
They're catching up.
They've got walls of retro merchandise.
I did see this.
I did see this and they're getting there.
They're definitely getting there.
But again, until they make Scott's genius idea
for a drink for the sugar, Mr.
DNA in a drink,
I'm not going to think they've arrived.
I think that's still the greatest idea.
No, they got to up the drink game, as I said.
I, yeah.
Giant gigantic sleepy beers is what I associate with them.
Yeah, they should have.
They gotta space it up.
Like they have the Tiki, the Nautilus Tiki thing,
Tiki drink that I have.
What if there's a DeLorean Tiki,
or a DeLorean thing you drink a bunch of rum out of,
a DeLorean cup of some kind?
Well, you know what, like, you know,
being that the Mr.
Fusion is something
that you just throw a bunch of stuff in and mix it up
and somehow it makes fuel,
if there was a bar that you could go to
where there was a Mr.
Fusion and that was the blender,
and it was a bunch of disparate ingredients,
but somehow it works and makes a great drink.
There you go.
Another million dollar idea.
If the Institute of Future Technology had to go away,
but it became the Institute of Future Mixology.
Oh, come on.
Yes, that make a little,
like we just scaled back our efforts,
we got in too much trouble with time travel,
so we're going to a less risky science.
And then there's a little, it's Doc Brown's bar.
This is free money.
This is free money for them.
You know who founds it?
The kids, Doc Brown's children.
Oh, Jules and Lur, yeah.
Jules and Byrne.
Are there going to be scumbags?
You know from how they are and when you see them quickly.
No, they got into apothecare,
they got into like, you know, the old west,
there was all this sort of a, you know, snake oil
and pharmacy, early pharmacies where soda fountains were,
and then they traveled to the future
and found out about craft cocktails
and the explosion in tiki culture in America in the 50s.
And they're like, we're opening a bar in a theme park
with tiki drinks based on our father's like cool stuff.
So they got, I'm sorry,
they got the best ingredients from all across time
and we're going to blend things like weird old,
like things that would make you go blind in 1870
with drinks that haven't even been invented yet.
This is a great bar idea.
Oh man.
This would be perfect.
And I like the idea that the bar is run by like a 10
and a 12 year old too.
That's pretty good.
That's a fun angle.
Constantly pointing at his crotch.
Yeah, right.
Yes, the iconic scene.
Truly, sometimes we stumble into legitimately good ideas.
That one's, that's really good.
Yeah, that's a fantastic idea.
And Doc Brown would wear different clothes
in the bar sometimes.
Yes, you'd cycle through outfits.
You can run it all like a food trail.
Like it's all like made out of a Deloria.
Like you do make the drinks up on top of it.
That's great too.
Yeah.
That's kind of cool.
Yeah, I mean, there's a lot, I mean, yes, there's that way.
There's the making it look like future Hill Valley
or whatever, or whatever.
Look, when the contract for Simpsons is up
and Disney pulls the plug and somehow the fan obsession
of like, bring it back.
Yeah, we are actually going to do it this time.
We're gonna do a Hill Valley street
and then we'll do a Back to the Future ride.
The Doc Brown Tiki Bar, you know,
the Brown family Tiki Bar.
Sure.
Yeah.
Well, we're talking about an area
where there was a Doc Brown dining establishment.
And we talked about this a little bit
when we did Back to the Future a couple of years ago.
But this is also is one of the most prominent uses
of off-brand Doc Brown,
that you would go to Doc Brown's chicken,
which in general, why did, we talked about it last time,
but once again, why did Doc Brown have a fried chicken place?
I think the theory may have been that he has white hair
like Colonel Sanders, so therefore they are similar figures.
And so why not throw these things together?
Doesn't quite add up, but I don't know.
A lot of people, I think, like Doc Brown's chicken.
I can remember a time when it was good.
I feel like maybe not the last time I went,
but maybe like when they opened it
and they were like actually paying attention to the food.
I think I remember thinking,
I like Doc Brown's fried chicken, that's worth a trip.
But it's gone, not there anymore.
Yeah, it's the same though.
Apparently there was a restaurant real close to there.
They've been serving chicken there,
well, I have it 1915.
There was a chicken restaurant there.
So there's a long history of chicken in that location,
which I assume is why they were like, well, I don't know,
Doc Brown has a chicken restaurant, I guess.
And then now they're still serving the same chicken,
but it's Cletus's Chicken Shack
in vaguely the same location at the Simpsons land.
So the chicken, the line runs through the chicken there
for about a hundred years at Universal.
And I've never loved the chicken.
My memory of it was like, okay, all right.
It was funny to go through the line.
I like that line to see the pictures.
Well, which that, so we talked about this and this again,
sort of the bizarre lack of attention to detail
that Universal's lately they're more on their game,
but in the 90s again, I don't know, whatever,
to go get a guy who fits the Doc Brown costume
and go take a bunch of pictures with him.
And there were all these great photos of him
visiting world landmarks, but clearly just,
and you're like, this is a pretty narrow hallway.
So you're right next to these photos.
So there is no question that this is some guy
and not Christopher Lloyd.
Do you guys have some of these photos?
I have them, I could bring them up.
Oh yeah, you go for it.
I have a video of a person taking the picture
or taking a photo or video,
but yeah, you go for it.
Yeah, it's better if it's photos.
Let's see.
So this is, let's just like meditate
on a couple of these photos.
So we got, here's one big tableau.
Here's, all right.
So it's Doc Brown.
He always has fried chicken in the photos somewhere.
He's holding it up or he's pointing with it.
So here he is, time traveling to the Eiffel Tower
and Stonehenge and next to the British guards
at Buckingham Palace.
But like, you could go to all these now.
This isn't time travel.
That's most of these.
Do we know that he actually time traveled
or did he just travel, did he get on a plane?
Do we know?
We don't necessarily know.
I guess they don't establish that.
I would just think like, why not put him in,
you know, what's clearly the Roman Empire
or some crazy future place we don't recognize.
Like marching in the French Revolution
or something in Paris.
To make you know it was a different time.
This isn't quite time travel so much
as just international travel.
Yes, yeah.
Plenty possible.
That's not special about Doc Brown, except right now.
Nobody can do it right now.
You know, here is the Taj Mahal.
That's not, you could go there now.
Statue of Liberty, yes, yeah.
Like what?
I kind of hadn't thought about it before.
But then you jump way ahead to the moon.
Now he's on the moon giving an astronaut
a piece of fried chicken outside of the suit.
Except wait a minute, oh, this is a little joke.
If you, I didn't catch this.
If you look in the reflection,
this is I think a faked moon landing
is what they're implying.
Is there's a bunch of stuff in his helmet.
Oh yes, right.
So Doc helped fake the moon landing.
Doc was part of the conspiracy to fake the moon landing
and he fed the crew too in addition to helping fake.
He helped, he was like doing, he was crafty.
He was doing catering.
He catered for Stanley Kubrick's shooting
of the moon landing.
Right, so.
They were friends.
I do like, by the way, I do like what that says.
I like that addition of canon there.
Yeah, yeah, that's pretty good.
But then you start getting into, well like now he's showing
up in, here's a little more of what I want.
Cause here he is with Gerald Ford.
Who is Gerald Ford with?
Does anybody know better than me?
They Russian.
What is he doing wearing like Russian hats?
So I'm not sure.
Is that Khrushchev?
Could be.
Much smarter people would know.
Here he is storming the Capitol.
He was there a day early.
Dang, I missed it.
Oh well, just enjoy a drumstick then.
Holding up his chicken.
But then a couple of them are just a real decrease in stakes.
You know, if you're going to all the best places
in the world, you gotta go to the Hard Rock Cafe
at City Walk.
He's pretending to rock out in front of the big guitar.
He's, okay, real quick, a quick note about some
of the portrayals I would find on YouTube and these pictures.
They make Doc Brown like a real like goofy, fun, loving guy,
which is not the right character.
Like he's dancing in Universal.
He's not like a cut loose kind of guy here and there,
but he was pretty uptight in the movies.
I know that's-
He's pretty neurotic.
to City Walk, he would play air guitar.
No.
It's a bit out of character.
It looks foolish.
Yeah, absolutely.
Would he go in front of the 3D Hulk that was long
on the theater marquee of the movie theater up there
and make a face like Hulk?
It doesn't feel, that doesn't seem right.
That doesn't seem like the Doc Brown I know.
Yeah, yeah.
And again, why are we just, well, I was going to say,
like when you can go anywhere in the world,
why are we just going to City Walk?
And yet that's a mistake we've made for many episodes
in a row and we'll continue to make outside of the podcast.
That's true.
He wanted to travel to what, like 2002 era City Walk
to meet Eric Bana at the premiere.
Is that, does that line up?
That's the hope we're looking at, I think.
Maybe, yeah.
Yeah, he wanted to, as would, I mean, God,
if we had a time machine, if we had a DeLorean,
we would certainly go to the greatest moments
in City Walk history.
We'd go see Kevin Sorbo riding a horse around
to the premiere of Crull the Conqueror.
Boys, boys, we have to go back.
We have to go to the third story of wizards.
We must see all the flaws of wizards.
Boys, boys.
There's no wizards in the future.
The future has no wizards.
Well, yeah, that makes sense.
Kind of a weird business model.
Seems like kind of the product of its time
and probably wouldn't make it.
Boys, boys, I'm getting weak.
I'm getting weak.
We've got to stop the restaurant group behind Country Star
from stealing my chicken recipe.
Let's see, so, and then just,
we got Doc Brown's beverages.
Oh, yes.
Really scary, like,
I mean, that looks like the CGI Orville Redenbacher.
Yes, it does.
Yes.
Holding a Coke.
That's really, that's very frightening.
I also just, while I have this open,
I, you know, in terms of other off-brand Doc Brown moments,
here's, apparently, there was crossover.
I think after there was all the accident on the tram route
and King Kong burn up, then they had a big event to say,
when they rebuilt all the New York sets,
say the trams back, it's better than ever.
And they had Doc Brown handing out balloons,
tying them to the tram and who else but Clump.
Oh, wow.
What's his name?
Sherman Clump?
Yeah, yeah, Sherman Clump, yeah, the Nutty Professor.
I've never seen that walk around.
Never.
That's a good walk around.
Yeah.
I have never seen a Sherman Clump walk around.
Wow.
No.
I'm not sure they ever did it again.
That might've just been that day, but what a mistake.
And of course, Doc Brown is also a Nutty Professor.
So it makes sense to pair these guys up.
And here they are, giving each other a big chest pound.
How great is this?
Wow.
This is another perfect crossover
that we should have gotten.
Yes, another.
Absolutely.
Right, and this is what?
What is Nutty Professor, 98, 99?
You're still a few years before the cutoff.
Yeah, this would've been perfect.
I mean, yeah, Doc Brown and Robin Williams' Flubber.
The doctors, like a league of extraordinary gentlemen
of doctors.
Dr.
T and the women?
All the doctors from the 90s.
Cinema's best doctors.
I mean, that's the C, yeah.
Get all of the, what isn't possible
when you get all the crazy doctors working in one bit?
Maybe working, well, or what if the Institute
of Future Technology is one outpost
and they are enemies of the thing that kind of rips it off
in Epcot lore with Eric Idle?
What is that?
It's the Inventors Institute.
Imagination Institute.
The Imagination Institute, yeah,
the Imagination Institute and the Institute
of Future Technology are in a bitter war
and they engage in chemical warfare.
They attack each other.
They try to like, all right, Einstein invented the bomb.
So he's on ours, Einstein's gonna help us out.
He's gonna build a bomb to blow up
the Imagination Institute.
Well, we got the guy who made the hydrogen bomb,
whatever else it did.
They're like deploying history's greatest weapons
manufacturers to hurt each other.
That's great, yeah.
There is a chance we almost could have gotten
something like that because the Dark Universe movies,
in the Mummy movie, Russell Crowe's Mr.
High, Dr.
Jekyll,
was the head of a secret organization
and in the Godzilla Kong movies,
there's this organization, Monarch,
that ties them all together.
So like Monarch versus Dark Universe,
you could have had Kong versus Godzilla
versus Dracula versus Mummy.
Oh man.
That's good.
I mean, I would have preferred it in the early 90s,
but yes, you're right.
That would have been, I would have been happy with that
and we'll probably still try to get there.
Versus Abbott, Abbott and Costello meet Dracula
and Frankenstein and Doc Brown and Dark Universe and Monarch.
And they tie together because they're all like
theme park walk around type character.
I guess it's Laurel and Hardy in Universal, but whatever.
They're all friends, they hang out.
TikTok Laurel, like Laurel and Hardy 2.
0,
there's a couple of TikTokers,
have a couple of TikTokers have tried to license
like Laurel and Hardy.
That's the plan with all these old IP.
We're just gonna have a new Laurel and Hardy
and they live, they do their physical comedy routines
fully licensed on TikTok now.
Well, look, I mean, I don't want,
this is a whole nother episode,
but as you gentlemen know,
I accidentally stumbled on the owner of Laurel and Hardy.
Oh yeah, wait, and who's that and why again?
Well, it is Larry Harmon Productions.
Larry Harmon owns Bozo and Laurel and Hardy.
And I am very intrigued by it.
And there's like one phone number and like one fax number
you can call to contact about licensing
for both of these properties.
The Laurel and Hardy property,
which of course were two real men.
That's right.
Two men that existed.
But if you wanna license them,
you have to call Larry Harmon Productions, I guess.
And also, oh, of course, Bozo was the,
I forgot it already.
They also own a property about like Bozo's like clown babies,
which is something I think Scott would be a big fan of.
Oh God, clown babies.
I'd have to find the exact wording of the property.
Oh yeah, I was correct.
It's Bozo's Clown Babies,
which is something that you cannot find
a lot of information about on the internet,
but here's like a rattle you could buy
that says Bozo's Clown Babies on it.
And here's one of the clown babies right there.
Jesus, awful, awful.
Why would, okay, there's two options here.
Either these are babies who are made to be made up
like clowns, which you can't do.
I've got a baby, he wouldn't sit still
to put a bunch of makeup on, and it probably would be toxic.
I can't glue a wig to his head.
That would be awful, it'd be torture.
So the other option is that like clowns are freaks.
So they're like born that way.
And so if these are like,
if these babies are genetic clowns
who came out of the womb looking like that,
then that's too horrifying of a thought to even get into.
Whatever the episode we were talking about,
Cliffy the Clown, the what, Smacks mascot?
Was that the cereal?
Yeah, one time Smacks mascot.
That's right.
Cliffy the Clown.
I believe we sort of figured out at the end
that perhaps some of these clowns hatch out of clown eggs.
So maybe Bozo's Clown Babies did hatch out of clown eggs.
And again, this is gonna be, I'm gonna dive into this.
We haven't done Bozo, I'm a big Bozo fan.
We of course, we'll get to Billy Corgan appearing
on the last Bozo show.
I watch Bozo a lot as a kid.
So we'll get to the Bozo's Clown Babies in Bozo
and Mr.
Professor Andy, his musical director
and Whizzo the Magician, all of the cast of characters
that I love so much as a child.
I could really use an off-brand Doc Brown
to run in and rescue.
You've got to come with me.
There's gonna be a terrible episode
all about scary clowns and being hatched out of clown eggs.
We have to stop it.
2016 Doc, or 2017 Doc Brown shows up at your door.
It's like, Scott, you're gonna get an offer
to do a podcast, don't do it.
You will be.
Talks about rides and theme parks and stuff.
That's all stuff I like.
No, but it's gonna be about all these other things.
Horrible clowns and creatures that aren't cute who pee.
And a name you'll never forget, Randy Kerber.
There's gonna be so much about this tequila company.
Is there anything like inherently funny
about the tequila company?
No, there's nothing funny about it.
It just keeps coming up for some reason.
And you'll be like, oh my God.
And you get in the car with him and I guess you kill us?
I don't know.
You think you might murder us?
I think that that's gonna be the plan.
And then like, okay, there you are.
Here's the gun.
What?
I have to kill myself?
That's the only one way.
How am I here now?
If I did, if I killed my past self,
I don't know, we'll go find another one.
We'll find another juncture in the space time continuum.
But here's the gun and get to it or else I'll do it.
No, I guess I should.
It is me.
Sorry, boy.
Turn around, think of a good place.
Think of a field.
And then after you're done, he's like,
but now we are going to see the little giants.
Okay, now next plan.
Okay, the mystery, man.
We have to take the little giants,
put them in a DeLorean and have them go play
against the rookie of the year team.
I'm gonna go combine all of the 90 sports teams
into one thing.
The small soldiers need your help.
All very good, all movies perfect.
They would be perfect movies.
Yeah, yeah.
But the star of them could only be not the best.
Not Christopher Lloyd, but just some guy.
Which now I'm immediately convinced that,
like early in the episode was I convinced
that this is a good thing.
They shouldn't be more accurate.
I like that they're weird and off.
May this always be part of the fabric of Universal.
Get Klump up there too.
Oh yeah.
This photo I'm looking at where they're chest bumping,
this is immediately iconic.
Get Doc Brown and Klump chest bumping every day in the park.
Then I'll be back up there.
Get everybody wearing different shirts all the time
and then Mike will be back up there.
Jason, do you have a specific request
of what you want from Doc Brown in the future?
I want him to assemble all of the old,
yes, the old big comedians we were talking about
that maybe young people have forgotten about
to hold an in-park Algonquin red table
where Groucho is there, Lucille Ball is there,
Stan, Laurel Hardee.
The Grinch.
You know what, we can start adding anyone.
Walk around Grinch.
Let's get a walk around Dorothy Parker in there.
Just everyone in there.
Okay, so do what?
To discuss their work?
They just, they just, yeah, talk about their work.
Maybe people toss them topics.
They're like, what do you want to hear us talk about?
It's just gonna rip a panel.
Like Donkey.
They're gonna riff on the news maybe?
Yeah, it's like, yeah, riffing on the,
yeah, a little more Saul, but it's each one.
Maybe they're all kind of puppety.
Maybe it's like 12 of those Donkey Shacks in a row.
Whoa, whoa, you've introduced a different element
to this now all of a sudden.
So they're like robots or?
Well, they're, no, I guess they would still be
like face characters.
They would still be impressions,
but they can, they just open the curtains around the table
and then they'll interact with you.
They'll take pictures.
So it's wagons around a table now.
A bunch of waffle carts.
12 wagons, there's 12 wagons around a table
on a Charlie, around a Charlie Rose table.
And then you shout out headlines in the news
and then they just give you their thoughts on it.
And where does it take place again?
Maybe, I guess you'd have to build like,
well, you'd have to build the table.
You'd have to build the Algonquin round table
and some recreation of the Algonquin Hotel.
Like not the whole thing, but a little bit.
The budget keeps growing on this project.
But people want immersion, okay?
People are gonna be hungry for immersion
as the world gets back up to speed.
I just want Doc to wear a yellow jacket.
That's all I'm looking for.
Seems easier.
Yeah.
You set the bar high
and then, cause you know, the budget's gonna get cut.
You're gonna have to scale back.
So I'm going big to start.
All right, I feel that's fair.
Hey, I'd like to see it.
I'll go see it if they, again, I will,
if they say we're doing the wagon thing with the table,
I'll go up there tomorrow.
I wanna see it.
Like a kind of austere, like Dick Cavett-esque setting
where all of history's greatest actors
discuss their lives out of conjoining
or next to each other while at a table.
And maybe like, oh, this isn't sort of meshing well.
Like just have them all say it, like, you know,
I wouldn't wanna be in any club
that would have me as a member.
You know, they all just start doing the hits, you know.
Well, you don't want the guy who says that line.
No, that is Groucho.
That's misattributed to Woody Allen.
Oh, okay.
Oh, that's good.
All right, well, I'm happy to salvage that one.
That's nice information.
Yeah, that actually, actually,
and there may have been someone who said it,
like H.
L.
Menken may have beat Groucho.
There's a million people it's credited to,
but I think Groucho is the one that's pointed to most often.
Okay, well, these events are gonna,
this waffle round table is gonna set the record straight
on all of this.
You just want waffles involved, Jason.
Come on, let's be honest.
I mean, that is the disappointing thing
is that donkey's not,
his waffle setup is not a full service waffle stand.
Right.
You know, you're right.
If that would make that thing 10 times better, I agree.
Yeah, he should take your order also.
Yes.
Well, I guess we covered all that there is to cover
about people who aren't Doc Brown,
who aren't Christopher Lloyd playing Doc Brown.
You Survive podcast, The Ride,
off-brand Doc Brown edition.
Keep it tuned here for three episodes every month
here on the second gate.
And hey, the future's what you make of it, I guess.
Yes.
Yeah, great.
That works.
And I said it with about as much commitment
to some of these Doc Browns.
Hire us to play Doc Brown.
That's my last request.
We're not gonna put any work into it.
We just wanna do it for a day, please.
Hey.
Yeah.
There, that was my audition.
Yes, so just hire us.
We'll each do a couple hours on the same day.
And it'll be fun.
If we all, yeah, we all trade a part all day in the part,
that sounds pretty fun.
Tag.
Now you're in.
What if we all switched off?
So like one, I'm playing Lucy for a couple hours.
I'm playing Doc Brown for a couple hours.
I play Grinch for a couple hours.
I guess the makeup on Grinch is maybe not easy in and out.
But I think that would be great.
We just, yeah, tag off, tag out.
That would really tune up the performing skills.
Like to be able to,
and you'd have moments where you'd screw up
and you'd be dressed as Lucy, but talk like the Grinch.
But you'd learn from those moments.
Those would be teachable moments.
Teachable moments.
And yeah, you'd just say like,
oh, I got a frog in my throat or something.
Mr.
Mooney.
And then you just call me back Mr.
Booney.
Yeah, exactly.
Perfect ad lib, Jason.
Yes.
Thank you.
Please.
Cut out for the parks.
Yeah.
Please let us do this.
All right.
Cool.
Thanks for listening.
See ya next time.