Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to podcast the Ride the Second Gate where after today's episode you will say flawless
victory.
My name is Mike Carlson joining me as always, Jason Sheridan.
That sounds right to me.
Scott Garner here as well.
But you'll always say that after every episode of course.
That's true, yes.
You're, you're, we're always, maybe like it's a hundred percent perfect of an episode.
I can't think of an episode we did that wasn't perfect.
No, no, it's the rare podcast that is never missed.
So today will be no exception.
Yeah.
We're in.
Yeah, Jason.
You'll be saying.
Oh, we're missing.
Oh, no, no, no.
This is the first time we've ever made a mistake on the show.
Wait, hang on.
Jason will save it.
What was Jason going to say?
You'll be holding, you'll be holding your sides so much.
You'll be in stitches.
You'll be calling for a loved one to get over here so you can share it with them and then
they will say finish this please.
We have to go.
Not finish him, finish this.
Finish this.
Which is finishing a meal or you're finishing an argument either way.
That's a good way to say it.
We're talking Mortal Kombat today, but more importantly, the Mortal Kombat, what is it
officially called?
It's called Mortal Kombat Live Tour.
Mortal Kombat Live Tour.
It's catchy.
And it, it started, it was in 1995, debuted at the Radio City Music Hall, September 14th,
1995, the same year as the Mortal Kombat movie came out and Mortal Kombat 3, the video
game came out.
Yes.
Big year for Mortal Kombat.
They were trying to do the turtles, the Ninja Turtles sort of model of let's take this very
popular thing and we'll tour it around the country to a bunch of kids who are going to
eat it up and their parents will have to go take them to see it.
But it did not go quite as well as the coming out of our shows tour.
No.
Nor do I believe it went as well as Mighty Morphin Power Rangers Live, which was another
very big live show.
Which even though they're, they put up quite a challenge in the commercial, they're pretty
upfront.
They, they in several commercials and press kits seemingly include a kid saying it was
way better than Power Rangers Live.
Yes.
I just said that it was way specifically.
He says, I loved it.
It was way much better than Power Rangers Live.
And it gave me a flat of like, is this, was that husky boy me?
Is that me?
Because there's a slightly taller kid next to him who looks disgusted.
And is it possible that was a young me and Michael who crossed paths at one point?
Were you and I not aware that we were together at the Mortal Kombat show that we've forgotten
about now entirely seeing?
Yes, it's possible.
Yeah, because I forget one of the because the the there's a commercial with that kid.
And then there is in the press kit, there's testimonials with him.
Yeah, I'll play.
He goes much further.
He keeps going like, it doesn't get much better than this, folks.
Like he's really hamming it up.
I love him.
Just to get a little flavor.
I'll play the commercial for this.
I think this is the one you're talking about.
Good call.
Yeah.
So let's see if it's you guys.
I loved it.
I thought it was way much better than Power Rangers Live.
Mortal Kombat, live on stage.
The best family show of the season.
USA today.
Rowan Oak, Civic Center Coliseum.
The show's great.
It was great, man.
The New York Times calls it an action fantasy spectacle.
Prepare yourselves for Mortal Kombat, live on stage.
It's coming for one performance only.
February 22nd at Rowan Oak Civic Center Coliseum.
Tickets now.
I mean, it's the monster truck rally voice, which is really great.
Doesn't that take you back the seeing the end screen with too much information, like
the phone number and all that.
It feels like a real sign of the times.
It was definitely a real sign of the times.
And in hindsight, it's really funny because we didn't have DVRs.
Like there's no way, were you like screaming at your mom to get a piece of paper or did
you always have a piece of paper next to the TV?
Because like how would you ever jot all that down?
Oh, yeah, right.
It's on again.
Get in there.
Write fast.
There's two paragraphs of information that's going to be on the screen for two seconds.
We got to write fast, mom.
Get the camcorder or the film camera and we'll convert it.
We'll develop it and then call a number.
I did.
OK.
Well, I think I think the thinking is that if you load it up with information, someone
will remember one kernel of it.
And from there, you can somehow get a ticket master ticket.
But I did write down once like when Fox Kids would run Power Rangers contests, I would
keep paper and pencil by the TV to write down where I was supposed to send, you know, a
self-addressed stamped envelope, you know.
Did you ever get anything?
No, never.
Oh, man.
There was, I mean, there's a history of now that I'm thinking about it, this is tied to
a very problematic figure, but there would be there would be reasons I would have stuff
right by the TV.
There was a thing called picture pages, which, of course, was hosted by Bill Cosby.
But a status side, it was a booklet and like a thing like a pencil you would have by the
TV.
So there were reasons I guess I would have like things ready to go if I was watching
television.
Yeah.
I also remember I don't think I tried to enter it, but I an early contest I remember is another
problematic person like a hang out with Michael Jackson on the set of Remember the Time.
I remember how much I wanted that.
If I could be there and like, wait, but how did I know what it was already?
If I feel like I saw clips already with Eddie Murphy and Michael Jackson and stuff or Magic
Johnson and stuff, but if they already shot it, I don't know.
The point is, it's probably it's really good that I didn't win that contest.
Yeah.
Yeah, that is true.
That is a good point.
Not winning the contest was a victory.
Was actually winning the ultimate win.
Yes.
Yeah.
So, yeah, I guess I guess, yeah, they would always dump all that information on screen,
no matter what it was, tickets, phone number.
And I guess you just scream at your parents and hopefully you would figure it out because
I mean, it's you really sound old when it's like you remember what it was like getting
tickets.
But it is crazy.
Like I was waiting in like a jewel at 9 a.
m.
to get wrestling tickets on like a Saturday or Sunday in line with a bunch of like older
degenerates.
Like that's the that was the experience of getting tickets to anything
at that point.
But now you're you getting wrestling tickets is like the most high pressure diffusing a
bomb situation I've ever seen.
Well, that's no easier for you.
It is not.
Could you reload this website for me?
Could you also check this browser?
I have enough browsers open, but it's so it's like it's turned into a different thing.
It's turned into like I'm, you know, Ving Rhames from Mission Impossible.
It's turned into a different kind of a thing, a different kind of high pressure situation,
I guess.
It's more of like a hacker thing in a van versus, I don't know, standing and
feeling like you're going to get into a fight with an older kid.
Yeah, I mean, we would we would always go to either the department store, Boscov's, or
I think Sears or Penny's.
Someone had a big ticket master counter and you could pretty much find whatever you want
it there.
But like Power Rangers Live and like Ninja Turtles Live, there's plenty of
seats like you didn't have to rush.
You could get to it on the weekend.
But I'm sure it was a little more relaxing than, yeah, having a million browser windows
open because at least afterwards you're like, well, I can go to the candy counter.
I can go to Orange Julius or something.
Well, right.
And that would have been a great treat after scoring some tickets.
Oh, for sure.
This kind of thing, by the way, the kids live tour, I feel like I didn't do as much of it
as when I was a kid as I wanted to.
I definitely did some.
I remember doing like ice capades or Disney on Ice kind of stuff.
I didn't see Ninja Turtles.
And it's going to be a while before this kind of thing is back.
But me having a kid now, like and it's like so much less like time commitment than going
to a theme park.
And who cares?
You could leave if he freaks out.
I could like the tickets aren't that expensive.
I could just be gone in 15 minutes if it goes badly.
This I I just don't know when these are going to come back, but I want to do all of these
things so bad because I want to go to these things like Mike, you and I separately before
we knew each other went to Batman Live and you're just a creep at Batman Live.
Like, it's weird for you to be there.
But now that I've got a baby, I could go to anything always.
I can see Paw Patrol and Baby Shark and all this stuff that I probably don't even want
to sit through, really.
But I think it's going to be fun anyway.
I'm just like dying for these to come back.
I don't know when they will.
Right.
There's nothing when you have a baby, there's nothing that's going to set off a
red flag for you to go to these places that we all want to go to, but might feel a little
I mean, we still probably would have gone to them.
We would have just been like, oh, God, all these people with kids are like, what are
these older, older kids, older kids doing?
But, uh, yep, I've got unless somebody recognizes me and knows who I am and go, wait a minute.
He does have a baby, but also he gets some weird other satisfaction from this.
So it is smiling awfully big, far too big than just seeing the gleam in his child's
eye.
He keeps telling the baby, I know you're not enjoying this, but I am.
He keeps scolding the bad.
It's really odd.
You got to watch this.
This is 5,000 years of civilization.
These tickets actually cost quite a bit compared to the other thing we went to.
This is for daddy, not for you.
Yeah.
Zip the lips.
You're going to explain to me what this Taruk show means later when we get home.
I want you to write a book report as soon as you can read and write.
Oh yeah.
Any and all Avatar.
Well, some of these avatars are about Avatar babies, right?
So they'll love that.
There's got to be an Avatar baby life tour.
Babies love content about babies.
That's true.
I guess it's kids, not babies, but there's probably some Avatar babies in there who I'm
sure will be very cute.
Half the well, the Etsy models say otherwise, but we'll see.
Yeah, those are that is hideous stuff.
Yeah.
Should we talk real quick about Mortal Kombat itself?
The video game.
Yeah.
Looming large in my arcade brains, because for me, it was a big deal.
That was a big deal because it was bloody and you could kill your opponent.
And for whatever reason to, I mean, I guess I liked Ninja Turtles because of fighting,
but I was not an aggressive kid for whatever reason it was like.
I have to play this bloody game where I could rip another man's head off.
Yes.
Yeah.
Good boys played Street Fighter.
Bad boys played Mortal Kombat.
And as a friend of ours has said, sometimes it's good to be bad because I don't think
I was supposed to be playing Mortal Kombat.
But if you're at a friend's house or you're at the bowling alley for a birthday party,
I don't know.
I was just playing.
I just had quarters.
That was the only machine working.
That was the only machine that didn't have a live.
So I played it a little, but I think I was more aware of the it's funny.
We're doing this like right after the Noah's Ark episode because it's like these Hollywood
sickos clowned on Noah's Ark, but they love this violent video game.
Why is this hedonism?
We portray accurate giant and dinosaur battles and yet you mock us.
But I well, this might align.
And during that episode, we discussed how much more religious my upbringing was than
you guys, which maybe aligns with that.
I don't know anything about Mortal Kombat.
I have never seen one of these movies.
I have never I do have not played it.
I don't know the characters whatsoever.
I haven't seen the new ones.
I don't know who people are.
When I look at a poster, I know nothing.
Complete cultural black spot for me.
So you couldn't name you.
I mean, through this research, like before this research, because you have named one
Mortal Kombat character.
No, no, I don't even like vaguely recognize.
I know this.
I know the music.
I know the yelling.
And that might be all that I know.
I don't think still it's Johnny Johnny Cage.
I was going to say Rage or Sage or Stage.
And it's not one of those.
Johnny Stage would be good because he's an actor as a performer.
Johnny Stage would be a great rock star name.
game where it was like kind of monsters fighting like gorilla, like kind of like a
more Godzilla kind of fight.
But it was also bloody.
That was bloody.
I think got away with it.
There was less uproar because it's like King Kong versus an alligator.
Yeah, this was Mortal Kombat.
Yeah, was much more.
Yeah, you would rip a man's skull out of his body and his spinal cord would be
hanging off the skull.
And that would be the end of the that would be the fatality, they would call it
where it which was the big deal was you would you know, the character would be
Uzi because you had beaten him and then you would put in a special code on your
controller and then you would have a unique murder to your character.
That's that was the idea of the game.
And they eventually changed it in future games.
They made like friendships where you would do something nice instead of killing
your opponent and they would also have some friendships.
Yes, they would have friendships.
And I'm by the way, I only know the first couple of games.
I got the new one, but I don't know it.
I don't know all the lore.
There's a lot more lore.
I don't know.
But yes, they added friendships to like you would open up one of the characters
would open up their hands and a rainbow would appear and it would say friendship.
So you wouldn't murder your opponent.
You would do something nice for them.
Yeah, you still got the victory, but it was it was a little more pleasant.
World Combat was they were pretty good at like teasing the, you know,
the the censors, the satanic panic crowd.
But it kind of single handedly led to the creation of video game rating systems
like a year before this all happened.
That big year for Mortal Kombat happened.
But that only made it more valuable.
Like it only made it like telling kids they couldn't play it made it
just made it more exciting.
It is crazy.
Yeah.
The first game came out in October 1992.
The most recent game was April 2019 and they were at Mortal Kombat 11, 11.
And they didn't.
I think they have subtitles sometimes, but I love that.
They just keep the numbers going.
I admire through multiple systems and everything.
There's never been a reboot of the numbers.
That's great.
Yeah, there's been like different like MK3, ultimate.
And there's been like additions of the game, but they still have kept
like the series going as far as I know.
The characters change.
I mean, I mean, I'm sure they add a lot and everything, but
is it still like a base?
Is Johnny Cage still
well, ignorant here?
Johnny Cages around there.
Died in storylines.
Oh, yeah.
He can just die entirely, like besides in a match.
Also, he had a child with Sonya Blade and you could play as that character
because she's a teenager at this point.
And I think Sub-Zero has like an ex apprentice.
Like there there's legacy characters.
Right.
Sub-Zero is he, you know, the guys with the blue, Scott
yellow and blue masks.
Yes.
Yeah, that's what Sub-Zero is.
So, yeah, Sub-Zero is the blue one.
Scorpion is the yellow one.
And then Reptile is the green one.
And I know there are more, but I'm again, OG.
I'm old and I haven't kept up on everything.
I know there's a bunch more characters.
So, yeah, I was obsessed with it.
Super Nintendo is what we had.
So the Super Nintendo version, number one, did not have blood.
Super Nintendo did not allow them to do blood.
So, again, that made me want to play it even more with the blood.
I don't know what's wrong, because I've talked about this before.
We're like movies that were rated R.
I thought these are not for me.
Too scary, too violent.
I can't handle it.
But for some dumb reason, as like this video game, I was like,
I must kill.
I must play this game.
You need a little juice every now and then.
You got to release the steam valve to let some of the hate out.
It's good.
It's good in little doses.
That arc episode was so cathartic to just like,
wow, an episode where we can just roast the thing the whole time.
We'll get back to things we like.
Here's something.
I think this show would have been awesome.
I didn't see this.
I bet I would have had a great time.
Yeah, I mean, it's tough, though, because maybe this is a good.
I'll play a clip.
So the movie Mortal Kombat was one of the first.
It's PG-13 movie, but one of the most violent movies I ever saw in the theater.
And I went with a friend and I will say I was terrified the whole time.
It was 1995.
I was 11 years old and I had never seen a movie in the theaters
that was like this dark with the promise of this much violence.
And my friend recalls that I did not shut up the entire time.
I kept like asking him questions that would basically was just like nervous.
I was just nervous.
So I had to keep talking to feel OK.
And I don't know what I was.
Do you know an example of that?
What do you mean?
Well, like, do you think?
So do you think that things will settle down soon or is it going to keep being like this
for a while or I think I was probably like think like, oh, do you I think
you think Johnny Cage will beat Scorpion here?
Like, do you think?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, well, this is this is cool.
Like, and I because I was trying not to be scared.
You know, my recollection is I was just sort of like doing running commentary
and then like asking questions about like, oh, who's who's that?
Oh, what's this going to be?
What's this going to be all about?
Talking to get through it.
Well, and my friend, yes, describes it as very annoying.
And he remembers that from when we were 11.
So the live show co-star, I mean, the live show was a lot of
dance fighting, like pole punches.
Oh, yeah.
The co-stars were lasers and fake fog.
Like the live show was much more gentle.
Yes.
You know, for sure.
But I do say I did like the movie a lot.
And Scott, I think you would like the first movie a lot.
It is it is bad, but has enough fun stuff in it.
Enough is well done enough.
Like because like the fighting is not bad.
It'd be they'd be unwatchable if the fighting was bad.
Yeah, I'm taking a guess here.
Well, the fight, some of the fighting is funny and some of it is pretty good.
But it's like the whole thing is pretty absurd.
I like I'll have a clip here.
I do think it's funny because we'll get to the actual live show
and a big basis of the marketing or big like kind of talking point
is that the Mortal Kombat live show is not about violence.
No, it's not.
Which is the one of the funniest things I find.
You find it over and over again in all these different press kits
and interviews with people involved.
This show is not about violence.
Now, this couldn't be more bullshit
because Mortal Kombat is all violence.
That's the whole thing about it.
Why you've heard of it.
It's why you know about it.
And I use this clip to even just to illustrate.
And this is absurd violence.
But so this is Johnny Cage.
This is the movie Johnny Cage for Scorpion and a very cool, by the way, set.
And they're fighting violence, violence.
And let me skip to the front here.
Oh, he's got a skull in the eyes are glowing.
Conveniently placed shield.
Well, Gurpeen is shooting.
And then here we go.
And this remember, Mortal Kombat is not about violence.
Remember while you're watching this, Scott.
OK.
I mean, can you call this violence?
Oh, orange blood from a big ear.
The skull got split in half.
And then explosion.
Which he was surprised by another explosion, another one.
And a hand came off his bottom jaw.
And then an autograph photo of Johnny Cage.
Yes, Johnny Cage leaves behind an autograph photo in his fatality
because he's a movie star, of course.
So, oh, OK, OK, gotcha.
Yeah, I mean, that seems so fun.
Funny.
Yeah.
So you should watch that movie.
Christopher Lambare is in it.
Highlander.
OK.
He just like with his whisper voice the whole time.
And it's great.
And he's got a obviously I'm a fan of Paul Anderson's other films,
Boogie Nights and Magnolia.
That's right.
Phantom Thread.
So if this I'd say he started in a very different place.
Yeah, but you can see the promise.
You can see the promise.
Yeah.
And and John Bryan score in Mortal Kombat is really good.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, did he do the dinner?
Yes.
Brian.
John Bryan, the Immortals, techno syndrome.
Syndrome is the name of the song.
Oh, John Bryan's one of the immortals.
Yeah.
Fiona Apple or the Immortals.
That's right.
Yeah, that's right.
And we are about 10 days away from a new
a new Mortal Kombat movie coming out, the Red Band trailer,
which I was like, oh, and this is one of the most violent trailers
I have ever seen.
And it does like that thing that every movie does now.
Like, oh, look, Sub-Zero froze Jax's arms.
And that's how Jax gets the cybernetic arms.
I'm not ruining everything.
This is the first minute of the trailer.
Yeah, there's a lot of like, oh, now we're going to go back
and see how a character got a cool eye patch.
We did that.
It's it's prequel.
It's learning stuff.
Kind of.
It does have what you I mean, it does have someone say Mortal Kombat
does have someone saying, get over here.
It has like the stuff you want seemingly.
But I think this was a very hard fought movie to get made.
I think they did some sort of web show a few years ago.
And like they kept trying to get another Mortal Kombat movie made.
Yeah, I mean, it's a very the game series is still insanely popular.
So yeah, it makes sense that they've been trying to do this forever.
I have seen Mortal Kombat Annihilation, which was the second movie,
but it is not as good.
It's it's it's kind of a little bit too bad.
It's like too bad.
Like the first Mortal Kombat is just the right amount of bad.
If that makes sense.
Right.
How does it compare contrast to Street Fighter, which to me is a masterpiece?
More aesthetically pleasing overall Street Fighter.
But I was a Street Fighter movie.
Yes.
No, no, the film.
Yeah.
Because I like Raul Julia, I think is one of the greatest performances
of the decade.
His last performance.
It really like cheers me up.
I think it is.
Yeah.
Or one of the last.
That's a good question.
I haven't watched Street Fighter to appear.
That might be more.
Fun bad than Mortal Kombat.
Yeah.
I mean, like more more my speed potentially.
Right.
But there's enough.
Well, a double feature.
When movie theaters get up and running, hopefully this
Street Fighter and Mortal Kombat at the New Beverly.
One of my first destinations.
Original.
Yeah.
And Quentin and Paul stop in to see Paul's move.
One of Paul's movies.
Got to support their buddy.
Yeah.
So yeah, check those out.
And hopefully I'm just worried the new one is going to be too like.
Realistic because that was not realistic, but I like to less
gaudy, bad 90s fun, I guess.
I will guarantee you that Sonya Blade is definitely a girl boss.
I mean, she's always been a girl boss, but this one is going to tell you
that she is a girl.
She is going to slay is what you're saying.
Absolutely.
Yes.
That's true.
I do believe that you're right about that.
So, yeah, I didn't even I didn't as a kid know this existed.
I mean, it didn't last very long.
Mortal Kombat, the live tour.
I have to.
But yeah, it was not on my radar at all at this point.
And I'm sure I would have been excited to see it.
But yeah, there's no live,
especially because they were marketing to young children.
There's this didn't come close to what kids liked
about Mortal Kombat, which was insane,
over the top violence.
No, I think a candy booking, though, because like, again, this is
this is a year of all all all hands on deck for Mortal Kombat,
because the movie is out this year and Mortal Kombat three
and this live tour.
In addition to that, there's a directed video cartoon
and the producers in the press kit.
Make sure to emphasize.
And we've got a CD rom.
And I don't quite know what was on the CD rom.
I should have looked up the CD rom.
Yeah.
But whatever fixer they're got, they got they're like, all right,
ride the controversy and go hard.
Like, let's make some money.
There's in the promotional video, they are like in
maybe I would call it insecure about Mortal Kombat,
because they have to keep explaining how popular Mortal Kombat is.
And there's a funny you guys probably saw this.
There's a funny way they decide to put it here.
Erica's top selling home video game of all time.
Consumers in the United States have spent more of their dollars
playing Mortal Kombat than watching Jurassic Park.
What?
Why do they have?
Why are their dollars playing?
What like when once you add in like coins?
Yeah, right.
Doesn't cost me any coins to watch Jurassic Park.
Right.
And I don't know why.
I guess they were like, well, dress parks very popular.
Let's figure out a math equation to make it seem like Mortal Kombat's better
than Jurassic Park.
Well, no, that's a trick, isn't it?
Because a movie ticket back then would be five or six bucks.
But a video game has always been.
Oh, I guess 50 bucks.
I guess that's true.
You know, it's funny you say that because I just saw
and I have a lot of different hashtags I follow on Instagram,
and one of them is I believe toys are us.
So one of the pictures I just saw that somebody posted
was an old Toys R Us ad for video games and toy and turtles.
And like Ninja Turtles toys are four ninety nine or three ninety nine.
Video games are sixty dollars, which that's the same price they are now.
Yeah, but action figures are like those Marvel Legends are like 20, 30 bucks.
Yes, everything else toy wise has gone up except for video games.
Yeah, which I think is interesting.
Anyway, that's a side.
I guess they've always been like higher tech than other things that are available.
They are the highest end tech that you can use in your house.
Right.
But yeah, I was like, oh, wow, that's the exact same.
But yeah, like a regular action figure now is 20 bucks.
Where is so on that on that hashtag, then do you also see like fan art of Jeffrey?
Do you see is there like are there like sexualized drawings of Jeffrey the giraffe?
Have I seen Jeffrey in like hot pants or something?
I don't know if they've been sexualized.
I definitely have seen Jeffrey.
There's definitely, you know, Jeffrey stuff for sure.
But we haven't I mean, if somebody wants to Google sexy Jeffrey the giraffe right now,
I'm willing to do that in the back.
OK, great.
Yeah.
And then Jason and I both tune out completely.
Mike's like asking questions, right, guys?
Right.
No response.
There's a lot of chat.
Toys R Us chatter again.
And this happens, I think every will happen every two years
because Toys R Us was sold to some other awful company, probably.
And there's there's more talk of like we're bringing it back.
It's going to come back.
But why do we need that back of all the things?
It's not going to Jeffrey's going to look different.
They're not going to it's not going to be the same type of floor and wall,
which is mainly what I'd be after.
Yeah, they probably won't do the same floor and wall.
But for a toy collector, it'd be nice to have another option.
That's all I'll say.
Oh, sure.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Because where do you get things?
Is it all online or just like you have to help that individual
comic stores have things you want?
I could do a whole 90 minutes on the difference.
It's all with all the above is correct.
There's exclusives to Target, to Walmart, some are online.
It's a it's a real nightmare, you know, to try to sort all that stuff out.
So right, right.
Toys R Us, it would be a little bit better, a little bit centralized.
That would be good.
But we'll see.
I don't think it's going to happen soon.
Yeah, yeah.
But Jason, any luck finding any good?
I'm not finding any luck, Scott, if you want to take a crack.
Sure.
Rule forty three, is that the term?
Yeah, yeah.
Mm hmm.
I mean, it's for the best.
I don't think any of us want to see this cute giraffe in a compromising position.
No, that's not something I need in my life.
So, OK, yeah.
So this is this is this live tour promotional video.
I guess real quick, we can take another quick detour
just because it's in the video here, and I'm sure you guys found this.
One of the the main producer is a guy and you know what I'm talking about, right?
You know where we're going with this?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The guy who organized the live tour, who put on a lot of other live tours before this.
Yes, and I'll play a clip of him.
His name is David Fischoff.
And I was as I was saying earlier, here he is defending,
putting a very violent thing on the road that's going to be marketed to kids.
Here we go.
Interested in developing a Mortal Kombat live tour.
At first, he too questioned the violence, then looked into it and jumped on board.
This is martial arts.
There are more kung fu and more martial arts schools
opening up every day in every community.
Martial arts is discipline.
Forget the violence.
The violence is in the game.
We're not you know, we're not going to teach these kids violence.
Right.
There's a KTLA interview to one of the performers.
I mean, we'll get to that.
We'll get to that for sure.
Let me just do a little more about David here.
Oh, yeah.
Because it's do you know about this, Jason?
Do you know why?
But what's important about this guy?
I I actually don't.
I think I watched a different set of promotional video.
There is a lot of Jason Jason Jason artifacts for this.
But who's this?
Who's this creep?
I guess I don't know.
I don't know that he's fine.
I think he's fine.
All right.
David Fischoff.
The way you're winding up.
No, no, no.
He's I mean, honestly, he's more of a hero to me than anything.
If you go through that video and man, was this a nice surprise.
If you go to 620 in this video, all of a sudden, it changes from just your standard
like, hey, in Mortal Kombat Live, blah, blah, blah, isn't this great?
And it changes to a little bit about David.
David Fischoff Presents Incorporated is responsible for producing
some of the most original, successful and exciting live shows in entertainment history.
Over the past 10 years, over 20 million people have attended David Fischoff
productions like The Monkeys 25th Anniversary Tour,
Classic Superfest, The Dirty Dancing Concert Tour,
Dick Clark's American Bandstand Tour, Ringo Starr and his All-Star Band for three tours,
the American Gladiators Live Tour and many, many more.
David Fischoff Presents also represents well-known professional sports figures
such as Phil Simms, Lou Fenella, Randy Meyers and Mark Bavaro.
So my friends like Mark Bavaro.
David Fischoff is responsible for the All-Star Band for Ringo Starr's All-Star Band.
Yeah, he named it.
He had the idea before Ringo and had approached Ringo about something before,
and he couldn't get all of them.
He was too busy.
A couple of years down the road, he gets ahold of Ringo and says,
here's this idea.
What if you go out on the road,
the All-Star musicians call the All-Star Band and Ringo's like, that sounds fine.
I'm doing nothing.
I'm doing a lot of nothing.
He truly for years was just sitting around.
There's an article where David's being interviewed and he's like, yeah,
Ringo and Barbro were doing nothing.
They were right out of rehab and they were doing nothing.
They were up to nothing.
So I said, so many times.
Yeah, it's like really aggressive.
And you're like, oh, you don't have to.
They were going through a hard time, maybe, David.
I don't know.
Nothing.
I just sit for days at a time.
I'd blink and the whole day had passed.
So his concept was Ringo goes on the road with an All-Star lineup of musicians.
And he was, I think, a sports agent before this.
And this got him into concerts and live shows.
And he put it all together.
Because before that, he had done those other tours.
We're a predecessor, the Monkeys Tour and the Dirty Dancing Tour,
which is really bizarre that several years after the movie,
a bunch of dancers from the movie got together.
And I think artists from the soundtrack would pop up on the tour like Eric
Carman, Eric Carman's around on the tour.
Seeing hungry eyes live on the Dirty Dancing Tour.
Mm hmm.
What a time.
The so yeah, this Ringo thing
came out of the Pepsi approached him and said, hey, you got any ideas for us?
After all, it is the 25th anniversary of the Pepsi generation.
How does that mean?
Of what?
Of you thinking of that term?
So therefore Ringo will.
And then, Mike, did you see that story about the the fight backstage?
I have the video queued up.
Oh, boy.
Well, then go for it.
You are already familiar with Mr.
Fischoff coming in is what you're saying?
No, no, I do none of this.
No, no, no.
OK, I got Ringo had the genius idea for the All-Star Band on his own.
I had no idea there was like a mystery man.
Oh, yeah.
He parted ways with Ringo no longer in the Ringo Folds,
but he got the the amazing ship off the ground.
And yeah, this backstage thing birthed this whole other David Fisher.
I think we have to pursue everything David Fischoff worked on.
Any setting the stage here to do, Mike?
Well, I guess so.
So the original lineup of the All-Star Band was Clarence Clemens
from East Street Band, Nils Lofgren, East Street Band and a solo artist.
Joe Walsh, Leavon Helm from the band.
Who am I?
Dr.
John.
Thank you, Rick Danko.
Rick Danko.
So I have a video here where they decide to play a little prank on David Fischoff.
And this appears in almost every article I found about this.
So I guess it's really hard because so to set up,
it's going to be hard to hear what's going on.
So I basically will just set it up.
What happened?
So they basically faked a fight between Joe Walsh and Leavon Helm
to scare the shit out of David Fischoff.
And they had fake blood in a broken bottle.
And Joe Walsh was holding a knife, I believe.
Mm hmm.
And they recorded it because they were just some goofy rock stars
trying to have some fun.
Scott, anything else of my leaving out here?
I don't think so.
Does the clip?
I feel like the clip doesn't even then they reveal it was a prank.
Yeah.
And then they just like put their arm like Leavon and Joe
put their arms around each other and then stick their tongue out at David.
And that's it.
And he laughs and laughs.
But what this turns into is that he's thinking about how much fun
all these rock stars have backstage.
And what if I could reproduce that fun for everybody?
Right.
And that's when he had the idea for Rock and Roll Fantasy Camp.
This is the guy who thought of Rock and Roll Fantasy Camp in general.
This guy, yes, we need to do a lot more on the things he's created.
For sure.
Yeah.
And we all obviously need to go to Rock and Roll Fantasy Camp
when this is all over.
We got to hang out with
Billy Squire or whoever the hell
whoever you can get fantasy camp now.
Mm hmm.
So I'll play this clip, but it's going to be hard to enjoy.
Joe and Levi are pretending to fight.
Here comes David.
You fucking guys.
Hey, man.
Jesus.
Come on.
Now, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Levi hits David.
Stick out their tongues to tease him.
And he's clowned on the suit.
Yeah.
Prank the suit.
Oh, then they trap him behind a door accident.
Yeah.
Dr.
John is in the corner loving it.
There's Pepsi everywhere.
They're living the lifestyle.
Clarence, Clarence laughing it up.
This is the Pepsi generation.
This is the fun they would have.
Yeah.
And oh, how they laughed.
The Pepsi generation that defined their laughter to find that generation.
So that's the gist of it.
So David is a character I did not know.
And going forward, he body.
All right.
He's a hero to me.
For sure.
Rock and roll fantasy camp is is there's this thing
where people fall backwards into like a themed experience,
like making a themed experience like I I watch the.
Did I talk about this recently?
I don't know.
We might not have gotten to it, but there's an episode
of Modern Marvel's and the history channel YouTube from like
theme park era Vegas.
And everyone is talking about designing these themed hotels and experiences.
And they're using the language of themed experiences
and they reference Disneyland as a, you know, a point of reference
a couple of times.
But then they're so blunt of like, and by the way, these aren't monuments.
These are going to be ripped down in 20 years at best.
Like this stuff isn't going to stay.
So it's very funny when this sort of theme design comes up in odd spots.
Right.
Yeah, the framework exists in odd places.
Yeah.
Where they fall backwards into it.
Right.
So, yeah, when COVID's over, we'll go to the rock and roll fantasy camp and,
you know,
whatever else David's up to, whatever else other live show
he's producing this this year or next year.
They're going to do they're going to wait and do Phil Spector's funeral,
I think, at rock and roll fantasy camp whenever they're allowed to.
They're just leaving the body around.
The COVID will be gone hopefully by then.
And they'll embalm it so it doesn't smell too bad.
So you we all us and,
you know, Melissa Etheridge can be the ball bearers for
Phil Spector's Vince Neal's going to put him in the ground.
The ultimate rock and roll experience.
I understand why rock is
going to be gone soon, having a rough time.
It'll be extinct.
I will say I will say that's the other.
There's another little rock and roll tie to it that I'll bring up
a little later as well.
More rock, more rock and roll to do.
Yeah, rock.
OK.
Well, what do we know about this show?
What there's not a lot of evidence of it.
We're sort of talking peripherally.
Yeah.
What do we know happened?
Well, I know the story a little because in the press kit,
there are nine slides that explain a very cumbersome,
complicated battle taking place.
This is so long.
I saw these.
And imagine me not knowing the characters at all.
I don't know what the hell's going on.
Yeah, it's gibberish.
Wait, just read the last one or like the second to last one.
The encoded order of the amulets is revealed to our heroes
through clues that are dropped by Lord Raiden along their journey.
Raiden is a big character.
He's kind of the big like protector of Earth sort of character.
And his counterpart would be the villainous
Shao Kahn.
Yeah.
And there's a tournament.
There's a fighting tournament called Mortal Kombat.
That's kind of what you need to know.
Well, the producers insist that, like, you know, we started
looking into the story of Mortal Kombat and we found there's a lot of
there's a lot of story there was to tell.
There's a lot of story.
And they meant to say money.
There's a lot of money to make.
And in fact, the fight choreographer did the turtles and enter the dragon
and karate kid.
And he's like, yes, this Mortal Kombat is going to be bigger
than all of them.
I forget what's the guy's name.
He was trained by Chuck Norris.
The guy Johnson.
Yeah.
So there's like a pair of these people that made this stuff are all like
like big time professionals in their field.
Right.
Which is funny that they made
a turd of a live show.
But was it the do we know that do we know that this was not all like?
OK, so there are clips of the show.
And I think that me from what I see, I've seen basically all I could find
were people talking about their memories of it, essentially.
Right.
So I think people were just saying, well, it's a lot of like,
you know, kind of like dance fighting.
As Jason was saying, there's like not much contact going on.
And there weren't like original songs or anything like the Ninja Turtles.
I mean, there was music, but there wasn't like, you know,
Raiden sings a sad song about living in the sky or something,
which would have been great.
We would have been doing this.
We would have done this episode way earlier if there was a Raiden
singing about the living in the clouds.
Yeah.
Johnny Cage singing about the the perils of being a movie star.
I mean, this is money they left on the table.
I mean, I guess there's still time if somebody wants to.
Tie it into the new.
If Fish-Off wants to come to us
and we will write the songs for Mortal Kombat Live.
Yeah.
As long as he brings his rock and roll fantasy camp buddies in on the deal.
As long as Alice Cooper will work with us.
Yeah.
Maybe the other Hollywood vampires.
Some of them.
They don't invite all of them.
A couple.
I read a review that was from the era that was not very satisfied,
but this is a stodgy adult.
Maybe a child would have a great time and disagree.
But this is what Entertainment Weekly said about Mortal Kombat Live.
The 90 minute show I attended was a spectacle of a neftly choreographed
fights and incomprehensible plot developments
enacted by a troupe of martial artists lip syncing pre-recorded dialogue.
So there that's why now we know that.
And I really like that.
I love the lip syncing the dialogue.
It doesn't happen enough.
It's kind of a trope of theme park stunt shows, but we don't see
too many people are allowed to do their own dialogue.
It should never happen.
I always lip sync.
It's the best.
All set to a techno industrial beat loud enough to induce sterility.
Good guy.
Liu Kang held up a magic amulet and accompanied by a Philip Glass style
motif, asked kids in attendance to raise their own amulets
and help defeat the forces of evil.
And by the way, seven dollar amulets are on sale at the concession stands.
D minus.
I also so so yeah, so real quick,
I found like a more of a truncated version of what the plot was.
So Shao Kahn has come to Earth to use, I believe, his bride Sindel's resurrection.
That's correct.
OK, thank you, Jason.
To steal to steal souls from the Earth realm, essentially.
And they need to collect the amulets, put them together to close the gates.
So Shao Kahn cannot steal souls.
So the kids would have amulets.
And then I guess in the show, the show itself, they would have amulets.
But apparently in one or two of the performances, the souvenir
amulets were not ready yet for the kids to buy.
So the big part of the show where it's like, oh, the kids are how you're helping
because you have an amulet.
That was not an element that they got to enjoy.
Oh, geez.
You know, I got it from your kids.
Don't worry that a similar thing happened to me as a young adult.
I went to the Pixies reunion tour in 2004
and they brag that we're recording every one of these shows
and you're going to be able to go to a stand at the stadium, at the arena,
pay for a CD of the show,
which you will be able to pick up or get mailed to you at the end of the show.
And at the show in Philadelphia,
everyone thought I was insane.
And then later on message boards, I found out that the CD company
was dropped and a new one was eventually found.
But there was like four shows where you could not buy a CD,
even though that was part of the marketing blitz was like they're back.
And you're going to be able to buy the show when you leave this show.
Oh, geez.
You fell into the black hole.
CD burner logistics.
That's right.
That was a big thing with rock shows around that time,
because I bought a few bare naked ladies shows that I saw, you know,
and it was like, you could collect the whole tour if you want.
And then in like a couple of years later, you're like, I don't need all this live.
No, I bought one at a record fair, like a few years later.
Yeah, it's not like I'm on the tape.
It's like I'm not on the recording in any way.
Unless you're very disruptive.
Right.
So if I was, yeah, front row heckling, maybe.
So, yeah, there was problems with the amulets, but the amulets,
that was sort of the device for, yeah, for the victory,
I guess, for the characters to win.
And I have a picture of the amulet.
Did you come across this?
No.
I'm sure it's very cool.
But let's see for sure how cool it is.
Very cool.
Oh, that's pretty good.
Oh, and it's autographed by the characters.
Yes.
And it looks like how would you describe this?
Like.
It looks kind of aggro, craggy.
It's like a belt buckle.
Yeah, it looks like, yeah, kind of an odd, misshapen silver belt buckle
with an Immortal Kombat live tour logo with signatures on it.
Closed in the dark.
And it closed in the dark.
Ten bucks.
Pretty good.
Maybe I'll buy it.
Yeah.
So that was yeah, that was like
I'm trying to think if there's a Turtles version,
they threw pizzas into the styrofoam pizzas into the audience
are coming out of her shells, but I don't think you could buy them.
Well, a lot of glowing plastic swords at all these live shows.
Oh, yeah, that's true.
Yeah.
Everyone would wave, sometimes would be prompted to wave, you know.
So smart.
Yeah.
And basically, yeah.
So so what we know is I was watching another YouTuber
and he said, I went to this and he was like very excitedly talking about it.
And then he goes, I don't remember a lot about the show.
I don't remember much about it, but I was really excited to go.
And yeah, so and I was like, OK, well,
it seems like no one really remembers.
It seems like the show itself was fairly unmemorable.
I guess so.
I don't.
Yeah.
Or just nobody bothered.
I thought that I had a potential way to figure out some some stuff about it.
And that is that I ended up on a listicle of the weirdest things
that the franchise of Mortal Kombat ever did.
And this was on the website Games Radar.
And there was a reference made.
So like the way they said the weirdest thing they ever did was this live tour
and that somebody in the office actually got to go to it.
And that was Henry Gilbert.
And I was like, Henry, yep, yep, yep.
Wow.
I also we both had had the same move here.
So got a PM Henry Gilbert.
Oh, we got a we lit up.
We saw a name that we knew.
Henry Gilbert is from Talking Simpsons, a great podcast
that we've been on in various configurations.
He wrote for this site 10 years ago and he went to Mortal Kombat.
Well, sounds great.
Maybe he can give us some info about what this thing was like.
Did you get the full story, Mike, as well?
I did.
He first said, ha ha ha.
Scott messaged me an hour ago.
I thought I was going to have an exclusive scoop here.
But when you're dealing with such a little information,
it's a premium on info here.
So at least his version of it to me was that,
you know, really excited to go.
We lived in near Jacksonville, Florida.
He'd seen Disney on ice.
He'd seen Sesame Street live.
So his mom was like, it's a new version of that.
Sounds great.
He's excited all week.
Oh, my God.
Here we go into Jacksonville.
Time to see Mortal Kombat live, pulls up to the arena or whatever it was.
And just the gates are closed.
There is no ability to park in this place.
And they quickly determine, wait a minute, this is canceled.
And they didn't even bother to let us know
there was no reaching out to the customers.
Maybe never.
Henry seems to think that his mom was not refunded in any way.
So this is a wild west of a time where nobody could throw a stink on social
media.
They could just cancel shows willy nilly and not explain it to anyone.
That is so funny and would be so heartbreaking as a kid.
Like, I can't imagine I never had anything similar happen like that.
But that's like the that's like vacation.
That's like Wally World.
Like a situation where you just I would be devastated.
I would have been devastated.
I I had something similar happen, but I was older,
but I was similarly devastated.
I was supposed to go see Kevin Smith speak at Villanova University.
Oh, man.
I'd be so mad if anything interrupted that.
And it got canceled last.
And I think there was I think someone passed.
And so we had to cancel last minute.
So it's very sad.
And thankfully, Villanova wasn't that far away from where I grew up.
But we did show up and they were there like, we're sorry.
Your money will be refunded.
Well, at least that's good.
Henry Henry claims he doesn't even know if his mom got refunded.
Oh, man.
He doesn't even think that happened.
But he did go get pizza in Jacksonville and play some arcade games.
And you have to wonder if one of those was Mortal Kombat.
And you have to wonder if that's the better choice of an evening anyway.
Well, sounds pretty good.
And I had a blast.
Yeah, I just went and saw Ocean's 11 instead.
Pretty good.
Yes, but pretty good.
But with the tweet, who needs to see Kevin Smith speak
when the tweet pays dividends year after year?
It's more exciting than any live speaking engagement could ever be.
You know about his wife.
You're right, Scott, you're right.
But it was 2001.
You know, it was different.
We had a different time.
It's probably T.
We.
Yeah.
Wow.
Why would anyone even want to see him speak before that?
He hadn't done his finest work.
He'd only made these movies.
That's true.
Well, you know, you need to build to the Sistine Chapel.
You don't paint it right out the gate.
The tweet needs to be its own movie.
Why is he bothering to make all these bad sequels to the movies
when he should obviously be doing sequels to the tweet?
Yeah.
Yes.
Put the flicks on the shelf, Kev.
NFT, the tweet.
Oh, they seem like they're a menace and I don't really understand them.
But it seems.
Wow.
Yeah.
What a great idea.
Oh, man, that would be insanely valuable.
Like generation after generation of Smith would be set for life.
Yeah.
The most expensive NFT of all time.
So what a mess.
We can't like it's people who are so excited to go
and then don't remember anything.
And then Henry went and then didn't get to go.
And there's press kits, but nobody
it doesn't really show you what the show is like.
I guess really what you're left with, the only way to really know
and these the cleanest footage that you have is from KTLA
one sunny morning in 1995.
That seems like the best way that this thing lives on.
Yeah, there's a video that says that's called Mortal Kombat
live tour, 1995 stage show that has some clips from the show
and then leads into that KTLA.
So that's the best illustration of what it was.
But yes, the KTLA footage, I think, will live the longest.
Mm hmm.
So the whole gang showed up on a morning show
with a host who I remember because he was my local guy
who is kind of like it's like if I had to do it.
He doesn't know who anyone is.
And he cares a little.
He cares enough to get through it like me with this episode.
He certainly cares a little more at the end when Sonya Blade steps up.
I will say that.
Oh, yes.
Sonya beats his interest.
Understandably.
Yeah, let's let's let's check out a little of this KTLA classic.
So, yeah.
So if you haven't seen this, there's there's a little of like
the kind of dance fighting going on in a KTLA studio.
Everyone is dressed in what looks like slightly better Halloween costumes,
maybe not even slightly.
And then the actor playing Shao Kahn or no, excuse me, Shang Tsung steps forward.
Copious face paint kind of on a lot of people.
Pretty tough crowd you hang with.
Yes, they are.
That is just a preview of the show that you'll be able to catch.
And it is coming into the Southland.
It's called Mortal Kombat.
Let me first of all start by having you introduce yourself
and the cast of characters behind you here.
My name is Shang Tsung.
All right.
And starting over here.
So to my left, Kano.
And Corpien, Sonya.
I must stress, no, I'm sure these people are very talented martial artists.
They all look like like me in a costume dressed as Kano.
Like theme park face paint, theme park face paint, like just thin clothing,
like thin costumes that look like, you know, you like cut up a T-shirt and.
Costumes that are meant to be viewed from a stage far away,
not from a television camera 10 feet away.
Right.
The Scorpion costume looks like he's wearing like a cutout body stocking.
Like looks like, you know, a Jabberwocky body stocking or something.
Uh, Raka and Kabal, tell us a little bit about the show and and what do you expect kids to get from this?
I mean, the video has already come under a little bit of criticism for some of the violence.
This is a pretty wild act.
You lied about the video.
The show is based on a martial art aspect of the video game, Mortal Kombat.
And it's already been to movie.
And now we're doing the live tour.
It's been under the violence has always been around.
But what martial arts show Scorpion is all positive messages.
What sort of positive messages?
What helps children be able to be concerned about violence and the difference between martial arts and violence.
It helps them to be positive.
It helps them to be able to to be able to overcome any obstacles,
which is in their life and be able to attain goals.
It helps them to commit to good things in their lives.
OK, so going to some people, good future in politics, dance, fight on stage for an hour and a half will make kids finish their goals, complete their goals.
They'll make them concerned about violence and how to make them want to avoid it when they see it.
The guy behind him and the guy in the background with a little sliver of face paint over his eyes looking down like, don't ask me anything.
Don't ask me anything.
Yes, this guy playing Shang Tsung seems miserable.
He is trying to remember the talking point they've given the talking point that David Fishoff, like, drilled a new one before this.
Like, it's positivity.
Kids will get a lot of out of get a lot out of this and there's nothing to do with violence.
Going to a show where people kick each other in the head is not about violence.
Do not say that.
I mean, this is the height of the suburban martial arts fascination.
Where did you guys do karate lessons after school or any of.
Jason, that is a very good question.
The answer is yes, I did Taekwondo.
OK, and I did it with my friend Luke and we got scared after a few classes and I quit and never did it again.
I respect that because I did like a few sample classes or like if instructors came and taught a class to the like the church youth group.
But I did not want to commit.
I think I was already doing like Cub Scouts and Little League and then eventually the plays.
So I was like, I don't want to take on another.
This is too many things.
But also.
At the kids who really committed to martial arts classes, I feel like really committed to it hard,
and I think it is good for like discipline and physical activity, but I just could not sign up.
Yeah, well, I I remember the teacher.
He was an older guy.
He could have been 31 at the time and I didn't.
I thought he was like 65.
There's no telling when you're a kid, but I remember his name was Mr.
McNulty and he was like a Chicago guy wearing the full like outfit, the white outfit.
And he was like, I remember he wanted to be to like kick him in the shins and I was like,
I'm going to I'm going to hurt you.
Artie's like, you're not going to hurt me.
And I'm like, but I can't.
So like I lightly kicked him and he was like, no harder.
Mr.
McNulty, I can take it.
I was like, but I don't.
And then I was like, Mom, I don't want to do this anymore.
And she was like, OK, good.
And she probably like held me and was like, I won't we won't ever do anything like that again.
I'm sure it was a situation like that was like, you'll never have to do anything
mildly out of your comfort zone again.
Don't worry.
You're leaving now.
That was only that was a minute and a half.
You paid for two hours.
The knock on my door.
Hey, get out here.
I know you're in there.
Come back to me.
Kick McNulty.
Mr.
McNulty.
I'm coming.
I'll fight you in your driveway.
Come on.
That's not going to hurt me.
What do you see here?
Unbruised shins.
You got to fix that.
I'll be at your door tomorrow.
Pretty far removed, you know, the suburban martial arts.
Just just as Mortal Kombat is removed from actual martial arts tournaments.
You don't think Mr.
McNulty classes are a little far removed.
McNulty kicks some ass in his day?
I'm sure he did, but probably at like an argument at the jewel
as opposed to like at a ancient temple.
I beat up another father at the jewel, Asko.
There was one Power Ranger toy left and I was getting it.
It was a dispute at the pharmacy.
I pulled the farm at the pharmacist over the counter.
Over the counter.
That white coat is red.
I kicked his ass.
Then I did a big spin kick and knocked all the pill bottles off of the shelf.
I cooled down at Portillo's.
I went over and I ate seven hot dogs.
I pulled the guy who was taking my order over the counter as well.
Then I made the hot dogs with my feet.
I karate'd that teenager right into the trashcan.
And I drove through the drive-through,
pulled the drive-through worker through the window over the counter.
Well, that's the only way anything used to get done at Chicago, you know?
Yeah.
Maybe he did work for like Mayor Daley.
Oh, yeah.
Busted heads for Mayor Daley.
And he didn't want to do it.
Part of his karate squad.
Mayor Daley's Karate Squad is a very famous tough guy faction.
Yeah, they would come in there.
Let's see this guy bother Sonya Blade.
OK, so so so basically he here.
Let me see.
I should have done a better job.
Also, they were either raising money or raising awareness for the MS foundation.
Yes, they threw a lot of like charity stuff in too.
So if you were like skeptical of the fact that this still sounds like it's going to be violent,
they're like, no, no, no.
Well, it's charity here.
Charity, charity stuff.
So you could go, well, it's for charity.
So I guess we can go.
Right now, the Mortal Kombat Live Tour, those are the places where it's going to be shown.
Can you give me a little demonstration?
Can I learn something here?
Are you sure can I call Sonya Blade up?
I'm glad you did.
Maybe not.
I don't know.
OK, are you going to hold on to the microphone here?
OK, now all I want you to do, I look at that.
That is the ultimate six pack of a stomach.
All right, man.
Cool.
OK, she is not happy with it.
It's so easy to see.
She just has such contempt for him immediately.
So here we go.
OK.
And this is what happens when you try to go for her neck.
OK, try to reach for her neck and grab with both hands.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Well, let you live.
OK.
Thank you.
I get to live this time.
You might want to check it out.
Like we said, it's coming to the pond.
It's also coming to show it like coming to the Great Western Forum.
There it is once again, Saturday, October 21st, the live tour at the Arrowhead Pond,
Sunday, October 22nd, one to five p.
m.
Tickets available at Ticketmaster two one three four eight oh thirty two thirty two.
You also in the show
reveal some secrets for people who are playing Mortal Kombat.
Basically, it says like you can get a cheat code for the video game.
If you go to the show.
That's a really good show.
A real good show, which would have worked if I knew about the live tour.
Special cheat code.
How long have you been doing this?
Because this is pre internet.
You didn't have cheat codes.
Yeah.
You love that they did the sound effects on TV.
Or what form?
He do you also think so?
So we'll post this clip.
The news anchor goes for Sonya Blay way too hard and fast.
Yeah, yeah, kind of.
I keep really like lunged at her, too.
I don't know if it was just he was in heat
and it was just an instinct or what.
But you believe she could kick his ass and I kind of wish she had.
But also like the directive of like go for her neck.
And it's like, did you guys talk about this backstage?
Like, did you her movie?
Her movements are obviously slower because she's not going to kick him in the head.
But he lunged at her neck.
I don't know what he was thinking.
Yeah.
Well, he was told to.
That was the plan.
True.
But like you would be like, OK, well, I get this is play fighting.
I'm not going to, you know, but, you know, I guess you got into it.
He was very excited.
He was very excited by her abs.
At least he didn't go for those.
That's the well, that's true.
The neck protected.
I believe this woman also was the model for Sonya in the video games.
Whoa.
Oh, geez.
You're seeing the real characters in a little bit.
Right.
Yeah, there was a lot of there was crossover in,
I think, with the movie and live show, some some other martial artists
and some of the fight choreographers.
Yeah.
So that is the most famous clip that exists and probably will ever exist
unless there's something particularly good in the show that hasn't surfaced yet.
I was trying to find a copy of it on eBay or something,
and there's a few like booklets like, you know, souvenir booklets from it or.
Yeah.
But I found this.
I found them.
Uh, let me try and find it.
A headband from the show
that someone is selling for over four thousand dollars.
I don't know why they think they're going to get that.
Hmm.
That's just like the the per inch cost is
pretty enormous.
Also, shipping says 80 dollars.
So I don't know if this is is this code for drugs?
Is that is someone just selling drugs?
This is some arbitrary item.
Yeah.
This exists to.
Jean jacket with lightning shooting out from the collar.
Yeah, like kind of awesome.
Yeah, that we could wear.
We could do that.
What was the the other jean jacket we wanted to buy?
The one from the parade.
White magic, light magic, light magic.
So we could have a range of different jean jackets from
theme themed in.
That's well, when we get to do live shows again and yeah, we all have different
themes, jean jackets.
Yeah, I think that will be very cool.
It'll remind people of what they've been missing for these many months.
I found a photo here of
Kevin Bacon with the cast.
Well, so the the six degrees of separation game
ain't too hard with this one.
Right.
And if you want, if you want this getting image, it's five hundred dollars
for a large.
That's another thing as well as video game prices remain high.
Getty images prices remain very high.
I don't know why they're such hot commodities.
Yeah, I don't know.
It's a small cost.
Yeah.
One seventy five.
Right.
Yeah.
Ron Galila runs the stock photo market.
The manifest.
Scott, he's OK.
Go ahead.
Well, you said you said you didn't know much about the game.
Do you know a trend with the newer games?
You know about downloadable content.
Sure.
You can pay an extra fee to get stuff like for a free game
or app and yeah, yeah, it keeps going if you buy more.
Yeah.
And so like for console games, this is like,
especially for fighting games, you can pay extra to get other fighters.
So you can pay extra and you can get like the T-800 Terminator
from Terminator Dark Fate or Robocop
or The Joker or Spawn
or Leatherface from the Texas Chainsaw Massacre.
Yeah, they have a lot of they've expanded recently.
So you can do a fatality with the Joker in Mortal Kombat.
Some of they have now they have all twisted fantasy has come true.
I know you love the Joker and now you can really experience
a lot of different Joker dying or Joker killing.
There's one.
Yeah.
Well, as an edgelord, this is what I
that's where I wish to do.
Yeah.
There's one where he puts like a bomb or it's a it's a jack in the box
inside the body and then it shoots the spring
knocking the person's head off through.
Yeah.
So that's pretty good.
That's pretty edgy.
It's pretty.
I like the sound of that.
Yeah, it's creative.
Well, this all star armada of fighters, this is like
bringing together all this great pop culture into one place.
This is like Space Jam, a new legacy.
Finally, well, that's all my favorite.
I brought it is conveniently owned in one place is not other not
no Disney or Paramount.
Finally, this specifically owned properties are together.
Yeah.
And Mike's right.
This is a Warner Brothers movie.
So the Mortal Kombat movie will be dumped on HBO Max.
And this is a good place where I would like to pitch
some downloadable characters to add to Mortal Kombat.
If hell, yeah.
Yeah.
Please.
Yes.
Since you mentioned the Joker, you know, it's
the Mortal Kombat Joker is kind of generic.
We talked about generic Joker on the Batman episode.
Right.
I would like the Jared Leto Joker in there.
I want the tattoos.
I want him mailing people, whatever rats or condoms or whatever.
I want to see the Noid.
I want to get the Noid in Mortal Kombat.
Oh, wow.
That's great.
Sure.
Do we know what's his finishing move?
I think he gives you a pizza and then he knocks your head off
so he can steal your pizza.
Mm hmm.
Yeah.
You've been on the wiser and also did.
Yes.
There's a lot of knocking heads off.
You can do who else?
Tony Soprano.
I think Tony Soprano.
You're the universe.
Yeah.
That's great.
What's his fatality?
Um, OK, this is complicated.
OK, there's an episode where him and Big Pussy are at a diner and
Mr.
Bomb and Saro gets a steak with fries and Tony gets
like cottage cheese and tomatoes or something.
And then he goes like, no, give me what he's having.
So I think Tony does like a scorpion move where he goes like, I want
I want him.
And then he he pulls you over and he begins to eat you.
I you know, that makes me think maybe they can add a different type of it.
And it's not a fatality or they have Scott, by the way, they have baby.
They had baby realities.
I don't know if they have that anymore.
Will you turn your opponent into a baby?
Oh, that exists.
Friendships.
Maybe there's like a serve him.
And then you get to just give them a meal at the end of the fight.
That's good.
That's a good one for my next one.
Captain Crunch.
Oh, yeah.
I would love to have it in there.
Flo, the progressive lady, Stephanie Courtney.
Sure.
American maniac recently deceased G Gordon Liddy.
Oh, you got to go out here.
Imagine what's weird.
G Gordon Liddy's finishing move.
Yeah.
Well, I can I can pitch on that.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
He obviously has to break in somewhere like he did at Watergate
into your rib cage.
He breaks into your rib cage and then he's unrepentant about it
because it was all in service to Nixon.
And he has like a disembodied, like kind of a ghostly Nixon
laughs above the arena or whatever.
Right.
And then it also can be scattered.
I don't know if you're aware of this, but G Gordon Liddy had a calendar
he would put out where women in bathing suits would have guns.
Really?
Why?
That's what he that was just a nice thing he did for the world.
And I'm trying to think, I think it was like last year
he was doing this.
I don't know if he had stopped.
I think he probably stopped recently.
I had seen a tweet or a couple of tweets about this.
I believe the calendars were called stacked and packed.
Yes.
They all had submachine guns.
Yeah, that's a pretty good fatality.
Like that is show up and open fire.
Mm hmm.
Stacked and packed.
Right.
You got liddyed.
And then my last character is Major Biden, the dog.
Well, they got to work out a licensing deal with Warner Brothers, I guess.
But they're probably they're probably all ears, you know.
Yeah.
But can he do this well in office?
I mean, Obama had to wait to make the Netflix deal till he was out.
But maybe the dog can be in the game now.
Yeah, yeah.
The dogs for they had those rules apply to the president, not the dog.
Yeah.
What do we know about Major?
Is he a rescue?
He's a rescue and they're often very nervous.
Yeah.
And Major has bitten two people at this point, I believe.
Yes, they're working with him.
They're working with him.
They have Cesar Millan for a newspaper.
He has Cesar Millan.
Like, what do you do about it?
Like, no, you just need to acclimate him to new places, you know?
Mm hmm.
Huh.
So what?
Well, then, I don't know.
Is it can he just bite people?
It's something that we don't want Major to be doing anymore.
What's what?
I don't know.
What could Joe teach him?
What would Joe's finishing move be?
That's a good question.
I certainly go ahead.
Go ahead.
I think Joe just starts telling you the corn pop story.
And while you're distracted, Major comes up behind you and bites your butt,
but your head off.
Yeah.
Like a yarn.
Biden's like thing.
He's like, it's a yarn ality, like a spin spinning, an old yarn ality
or something where he just gives you five minutes of a story.
And your head falls off.
Just from like your your your neck just gives up
keeping your head sturdy.
Yeah, you can't.
Bails on the responsibility.
You tilt back.
Hey, man, how come you can't find Moxie soda anymore?
And then you just explode.
Your brain cannot follow all the threads.
It's like it just quit.
Your brain quits because there's so many directions that the story is gone.
You don't know where he's he's trying to go with it.
So that's it's just too much.
And yeah, well, Major and Joe,
that's a great fatality duo.
Get them in there, get them in the new pack and send it out on the road again.
And I guess, I mean, obviously, if they were to do this again,
it would have to be bloody.
But why even do it?
I think kids now can handle it.
This isn't a fire.
This isn't a hot button controversy.
Joe Lieberman isn't having a hearing about the violence in this anymore.
So do whatever you want.
We should have it should be like Gallagher, where you show up with tarps
and you know there's going to be a lot of blood.
Spray.
I mean, there's yeah, I'm I'm that's that's a good idea.
I do think just maybe have saw if you're not going to if you're not going to do
that, just we need songs, we need all the characters to have songs.
Yeah.
And I think there's there's a character, Scott,
I think you'll like this character from the movie and the character's name is Goro.
Does that mean anything to you?
I've come across it in a little bit of research.
Yeah, but I don't know much about.
And have you ever seen what he looks like in the movie?
No, let's see Goro.
OK, because I think you're going to really like Goro.
Yeah, I think you're going to like Goro.
These are some of the monster characters.
Yeah.
Is he going to be a scary clown or something?
Am I being set up?
No, no, he's not a clown.
No, by the way, I just said it and it sounded like I'm setting you up for a clown.
No, no, I swear.
But no, he's not a clown.
He's like a robot.
He's like a here.
I'll show you.
They he's like a monster with with multiple arms.
He's like four arms.
But the way they did him in the movie, he is like a animatronic
and he is goofy as hell.
Here, this is where Goro gets punched in the nuts.
So that's I mean, first of all, that's the reason why you should watch the movie.
But I think Goro at that point should sort of like, you know, the giant is now has a
beautiful, like very high octave voice.
And he sings about how this fighting, you know, is something that he was born into and
how he doesn't need it anymore and how it's a positive message for kids and that they
should just take the lesson that your goals are achievable.
You know, you watch the movie and you're like, oh, I'm going to be a clown.
You watch me get hit in the nuts and you watched a bunch of people dance fight and now anything is possible.
What's the I'm trying to think of like the most plaintive song there is.
And maybe it's I dream to dream from Les Miserables, but it's my my my nuts.
Just my nuts got punched.
My my nuts got punched just right now.
Yeah, or something.
Yeah, I think that's good.
I think that's a good framework for the song.
Yeah, yeah.
And kids, your dreams, they are achievable.
You'll go home and accomplish whatever you want and get good things in your life.
That natural phrase that the man said on the TV show.
Yes, I think I think a Tony would be one if it all culminates in this.
So, yeah, bring it back.
Goro nut punchings and just to bring it back to the beginning, if I could share the screen,
a strand that we all forgot about and probably wish that we kept forgetting about.
There is a ton of pornography of Jeffrey the giraffe.
Oh, my God.
He's our.
Oh, it's awful.
The one that jumps out at me is this one where apparently there's like a three way
being headed for between Jeffrey the giraffe, Tony the tiger from Frosted Flakes and Scooby
Dooby Doo.
Oh, my God.
Come on, it's going to be great.
Scooby Dooby Doo.
And everyone has big, colorful, hard boners.
This is first of all, this is unethical because Scooby Doo is like a regular dog.
And Tony and Jeffrey are like half man, half animal.
Yeah, yeah, you're right.
Yeah, only if you're a hybrid, you can mix, I think, and it's less weird, but a pure animal.
Wow, this is just awful.
Yeah, then it then it happens.
Oh, no.
All right.
I won't I won't I won't scan down.
But yeah, disarming and alarming in every style of Jeffrey, like kind of the more clip
already version of him.
Yeah, yeah, some very imaginative notions about what his what his penis might look like.
So obviously, get them all into in this expansion pack, get Jeffrey, get get Tony and get Scooby
Do and their their fatality, I guess, is swinging their hard boners around.
And you get to make sure to post that in my notes app or my my insta paper app.
We're not going to post that publicly, but I'll take that.
Yeah, yeah.
So yeah, that's for the podcast, right?
Only fans.
But you're on the podcast, right?
Patreon, which you survived podcast, the ride, the second gate.
Keep it tuned here where I promise we won't talk about Jeffrey the giraffe's penis again.
That is if there's no better lure to get you to stay subscribed.
I think that's a pretty good one.
Look, I hated that, but I won't make that promise.
It's true.
Let me just say that we don't know where where conversations go.
And should we need to talk about it?
Yeah.
Let's not take it off the table.
I just don't want to get in a court case or something.
He says you made a vow on the show and then didn't abide by it.
Yeah, yeah.
OK, so yeah.
All right.
Well, then there you go.
Jeff for the direct penis might come up again.
And it's really the mystery that you're paying for.
So keep it tuned right here.
Three bonus episodes every month.
And yeah,
Mortal Kombat.
Well, how do you finish an episode?
What would be the way they would end the game?
Well, if you end the game with a murder.
Hmm.
Well, it's we're still over friendship.
We can do friendships.
Oh, let's do friendship.
We could do it because we'd each have our own special friendship.
So we could figure out what our character in the Mortal Kombat
would do as a friendship.
You know, what would be the nice thing you would offer your opponent
after you've beaten them?
Sure, sure.
Well, here's here's two very buttery Chardonnays for the both of you.
I would I would I would bring gelatoni.
I would pull gelatoni out my gelatoni plush, which is the cat.
Italian painter cat from the Duffy verse.
And I would have gelatoni, give them a big hug.
And that would be my friendship.
That's beautiful.
And Jason,
I would offer a freshly grilled hot dog and ask what you would like on.
How do you want this prepared?
What condiments would you like?
Chili and cheese, you know.
And if and if I had a fatality, I would pull someone across a counter.
And kick them very hard in the head.
That's how I would do it.
Then I would knock their head off with the.
Great.
Beautiful.
Everyone pursue your own friendships and fatalities,
and we'll talk to you next time.
Goodbye.