Forever.
Dog.
Whoa, warning, man.
The following podcast features fun, sun,
and surfing cave bed.
Grab your lotion or oil or your tanning butter
as we breathe along the Santa Cruz beach boardwalk
with guest Kelly Dugent.
Hey, cowabunga, man.
This podcast the ride.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, the theme park podcast
that today we'll try to focus on actual rides
and not a store called the Octopus's Garden Gift Shop.
My name is Mike Carlson, joining me as always
under the sea, Jason Sheridan.
Yeah, I mean, between the Octopus's Garden
and like all of the long gone closed stuff
and just the past, the past looms large
at this destination.
We're gonna try.
Okay, Scott, you're gonna hear as well?
I know, it's a good thing there's some very good rides
because it'd be easy to get lost in the woods.
I wanna know about this gift shop though.
I didn't previously, so we're gonna have to carve out
some time.
Anytime, the podcast dangerously veers into Ringo's
star obsession territory with me a lot.
And again, I'm trying, if you hear like me going,
it's like I wanna talk about Ringo and this gift shop,
which I assume he knows a lot about
and definitely gave his blessing to.
Personally approved.
Yeah, a lot of Ringo lately, a lot of Leno.
Obviously Buffett Beach Boys always around the corner,
we know the topic, we will stay
and there's such good rides here,
so we promise we'll be good today.
There's very good rides.
Of course, I did discover that the nearby Sun and Sand Inn
offers cookies every day from three to five.
But we'll get to the lodging if it comes to it.
There's only a couple.
Let's bring in our guest to prevent me from talking about
Ringo Starr's solo music career and all the songs
that I like that I feel like people don't appreciate enough.
So I will not do that.
I do myself.
Yes, that's your friend and I don't.
Bring the guest in,
this will make me not have to talk about this.
You know her from the podcasts Exile and Teen Creeps.
Ladies and gentlemen, it's Kelly Nugent.
Hey guys, thank you so much for having me.
Hey, thanks for coming.
Thanks for doing the show.
Thanks for talking about a place
that we all wish we could visit.
Ah, wish I was there, wish I was there.
I do feel bad because I know you were like begging
for anyone to give you a reason to not talk about Ringo,
but I did have a question upon hearing what you said.
I was like, is that an actual gift shop?
I looked at the website and it said,
that's what the name of the gift shop is called.
And I got very excited because it's a Beatles reference.
So yes, that is real.
I did not make that up.
I would, sounds like some place I would make up,
but I did not.
Okay, I don't mean to derail straight off,
but like, do we know what kind of product they sell?
Like, is it specific to Ringo?
No, it's not specific to Ringo.
I wish it was all Ringo star hats and shirts.
That would be incredible.
It says Santa Cruz inspired clothing, hats, stickers,
and gifts, as well as a wide selection
of sunglasses and sundries.
Yeah, all of the Santa Cruz Beach Boardwalk stores
seem to sell similar surf inspired items.
But if it was like surf Ringo and he was like peace and love
while he was on a surfboard in the water,
I mean, that would, the sales would triple, quadruple.
So we're throwing that idea out for these places for free
if they want them.
They got a Darth Vader and it says,
may the surf be with you.
So that's cool.
I don't think that's, why Darth for that though?
I guess it's not force.
So he, I guess he might say, may the surf be with you.
It's a little muddy, but whatever.
Hey, it looks cool.
Nobody's thinking about it that hard.
I shouldn't either.
Yeah, so yeah, not Ringo specific.
As far as we know, maybe there is a Ringo section in there,
but I don't know.
I'm hoping I haven't been-
I mean, missed opportunity, missed opportunity
if they don't have it.
Yeah, for sure.
At least obviously they would have cute octopus stuff
and it would be, you know, lines from the song maybe.
Yeah.
That's kids, kids, that kid could wear that
and not be beaten up at school.
Like a child, a young child would go with a Ringo Starship
and be like, this is the coolest.
Like if I had a son, he'd be like,
daddy says this is the coolest celebrity on the planet.
A 90 year old Ringo star.
And then the kid's just right in his stomach,
punch right in his stomach.
Well, I also just, I feel like it's such a,
because you know how you see all those like tweets
that are like, what if you old kids
don't even know who blah, blah, blah is?
Like, I feel like there would be such little context
that maybe this hypothetical son could fly under the radar
and people would just be like,
okay, man, I mean, whatever.
I think that's cool.
Yeah.
Who is that?
You're saying I'm, my references will be so out of it.
Yes.
By that point that the kids won't even know
to make fun of this hypothetical son of mine.
So yeah, he may be fine.
He may be, oh, okay, he's got that older man on his shirt.
That must be a cool guy I've never heard of.
Yeah.
So yeah, that's a dream I can hold on to at least.
But we're talking Santa Cruz Beach Boardwalk today.
Yes.
A place that none of the hosts have been.
I've been.
You've never been there?
I've been at the beach part,
but I did not have time to go to the amusement park part.
I know that it was beautiful and chill,
but I didn't know how wonderful some of these rides were
and a lot of the mythology and everything.
So I really wish I'd gotten to go,
but Kelly, you've been clearly.
Yes.
What's your story with this place?
Okay, I do feel tricky being the person
that wants to talk about this,
because I didn't grow up in Santa Cruz.
I don't have these childhood memories of like,
oh my God, me and my friends used to go to the boardwalk.
First of all, I was not allowed to do anything
when I was a kid.
So I wasn't, even if I lived near it,
I would not have been at the boardwalk.
You weren't allowed to have stories growing up?
Yeah, no.
No, I mean, my stories were like,
I sat at a dining room table
and like stared at a math book and was sad.
So.
What a story.
I was like alone.
Yeah, it was great.
I went there for the first time probably in college
because a friend of mine's family lived out there.
So we went there to visit it.
And that visit, I think I did the whole gamut of rides.
I did like all the different rides,
the big old roller coaster, classic giant dipper.
It's like wooden roller coaster,
shared lap bar with the person that you're sitting next to.
So if you are someone who's smaller like me
and I was sitting next to someone
who was like six, four or something,
I did fear for my life, like going down the drop
because it was safe for him,
but it was not safe for me.
But also it's the boardwalk, so who cares?
Right.
But it's so safe.
I hate to say this though, this is an attraction.
It's been around for a long time,
so it's had a lot of opportunities to kill people
and it has killed three people.
So.
I hate to tell you that now, but you're off,
you're not on it now, so everything's okay.
But again, there's Disney rides that haven't killed anybody
but they haven't been around as long.
There's a century of opportunity for death.
So, and most of them were a long time ago
before there were better safety standards.
So I'm sure nothing to worry about now.
No bars maybe.
Simultaneously, a historical landmark
along with the carousel, the giant dipper,
a historical landmark.
In fact, the picture, I wonder if I can ever find it,
because they snap a picture of you as you go down.
I swear my jaw is like unhinged
because I was truly shrieking for my life
because I was suspended in air
and was just gripping with my hands on the lap bar
because I was like, oh, I will just fly out
of the top of this car.
Yeah, yes.
That would be interesting.
I mean, you should find that
because I would, there's like a newer Six Flags coaster
that like has like really strong restraints
and it still felt like I was flying out of it.
It was the Twisted Colossus.
And I would like to see what older technology
to restrain someone in looks like.
It's just a lap bar.
Yeah, it's just a metal.
It's just the shared,
it's like one, so you just pull it down
to whomever has taller legs and then hope for the best.
Yeah.
And by the time you realize it,
there's like a teenager that's like, okay, go,
and then it's just going and you're like,
oh, but I'm not, it's fine.
Yeah, the Santa Cruz teens who work there
are not so diligent maybe as far as safety.
No.
I assume also- At least they weren't
when I was in college.
Yeah, I bet they haven't changed.
Well, they do go out of their way on the website
to say they have four engineers every day
like checking on this thing every few hours.
Yeah. What?
Like on call, they have full-time like mechanics and stuff.
There's also a full medical staff on call
all the time for this ride.
He's listing all the things they have,
a defibrillator in case your heart stops.
The medical staff does,
they transport on the Skyglider though,
so it will take a significant amount of time.
They have to wait in line too.
They've got to wait in line and if it stops,
it could be upwards of 10 minutes.
Yeah.
Kelly, when you went on this,
is this one of those things where you were terrified
and you were like, I'm not going on that again,
or it was like right back in line?
Oh, I was never gonna go on that ride ever again in my life.
Got it.
Okay, so it was that kind of thing.
It was scary.
I truly was, it was one of those things where,
so I was in college at the time,
so I was like, oh, this is fun and scary,
and then we didn't go on that ride again,
and then for my Bachelorette trip,
basically my three best friends arranged
a spooky tour of the California coast,
and so we went to go see all these haunted places
and also went to the Santa Cruz Boardwalk,
and as an adult, I saw that ride and I was like,
I will not be riding that ride again.
Now that I'm in my 30s,
I don't need to do anything to anyone going to perish.
Interesting, so yeah, you were not looking to conquer it.
That was, you were done with it.
I was done.
Yeah.
But then we went on rides that I had overlooked
as possibly being babyish or boring
on the second trip that I went there,
and those rides, I mean, 10 out of 10,
Cave Train is amazing, amazing.
Yeah, my friends, Tyler and Kia,
who've spent a lot of time up there,
I asked them, what's the big stuff to hit,
and they said, just mainly Cave Train.
Anything else you get to, whatever.
Cave Train is the shit.
Make sure you get a lot of Cave Train in there.
I couldn't believe this ride.
This looks like a, I cannot wait to go on this thing,
and it's, I mean, it's not just Cave Train,
but some of these other dark rides that they have are long.
These are massive rides with so many animatronics,
fairly limited animatronics,
but you feel the heart and spirit in the making of them.
Yes. Yes.
Really good, yeah.
Haunted Castle goes under the Boardwalk,
which was very popular for a certain while
on the Jersey Shore towns, in the amusement parks there.
Now, on the East Coast, that's a real dicey proposition,
because while that is very fun,
you are subject to hurricane storm surges,
and every now and then, once in a generation,
Superstorm that does this to theme parks,
because this is in Seaside Heights, New Jersey.
So Santa Cruz Beach Boardwalk is built,
like the amusement park is built parallel to the Boardwalk.
On the East Coast, beach down parks are built
similar to Santa Cruz Boardwalk,
but just kind of in a patch of land,
or they're built on the piers,
which again, subject to storm surges,
sometimes hurricanes take those parks away.
Wait, explain that photo, Jason.
It's like there's a roller coaster
that's just not on the pier anymore.
It's in the Osh.
Yes.
So Sandy hit the Jersey Shore pretty hard,
and Wildwood and Seaside Heights,
two towns on different parts of Jersey,
they built their parks on piers going out into the water,
and the Seaside Heights park,
just the pier part of it collapsed,
and the whole roller coaster just plopped down
into the water.
Are you trying to put Santa Cruz on notice?
This could happen to you.
Well, I did find historical photos
where there are one pier that used to have
a water intake pipe on it that would fill the indoor pool
was partially destroyed by a storm,
but when you build the park further back
behind the Boardwalk, less chance of damage.
So you're saying Santa Cruz is better prepared for a storm.
You just want us to know about the storm
possibility. Yeah.
The storm possibilities before we start talking
about these fun rides.
Well, compare and contrast.
They were in the middle of talking about a fun ride,
and then like, but hang on, storm possibilities.
Yeah, no.
Also in the listed things they have,
like doctors on staff, they also have you on staff being like,
guys, this could go away at any time.
You're like a Doc Brown style, like, it's coming, it's coming.
Look at this photo from the other coast.
Get off the ride, kids.
For the sake of listeners.
You've got some interesting literature
underneath your seat.
And it's the picture.
For the sake of listeners, because my impression
of seaside Boardwalk is a little different than this one.
I mean, they were more popular on the East Coast
than on the West Coast.
Santa Cruz Boardwalk is one of the bigger ones
and one of the few still around on the West Coast.
Yeah, that's a miracle.
Oldest surviving one.
So let's hope, let's hope that Santa Cruz
so let's hope, let's hope the storm never comes
for these cute little rides that I like from the video.
This is also. Not a huge storm either.
No storms, not a capital storm.
I don't want any storms in this place.
No one's can, no one should storm the Boardwalk.
Oh, yeah.
No, let the cave people be.
Political.
That's right.
This is one of the older places we've talked.
I think Kennywood might be a little older than this,
but this park goes back to 1907.
Well, if the cave train is to be believed,
this park goes back to prehistoric times.
Yes. That's right.
You go to a world that has stayed intact
since prehistoric times that happened to exist.
It's a world that exists only under the Boardwalk.
It's a microcosm, entire other universe.
Which I. Perfectly preserved.
When you watch the video with the thing,
I really like the like casual narration.
You're looking at the phrase cave train.
Like, what does that even mean?
Like, is that a frequent thing that trains go into caves?
You have no real indication of what the premise
of the ride is going to be.
And then there's this folksy narration.
It's like, it's the funniest thing.
People were looking under the Boardwalk one time
and there was a whole race of cave people anyway.
So we thought that was neat.
Like, give you a chance to go see it.
It's just like tossed off in the amount of time
it takes to go through this hallway.
And then you do love that the name is kind of a misdirect.
Like, you don't know what if you because if you go on the ride
as I did, not knowing what was going to happen to me.
When you come upon the like scores of cave families and also
cave dinosaur families, because dinosaurs are also there.
Coexisting, they're all friends, coexisting, all friends.
Sometimes they're fun little enemies for enemies.
Sure, sure.
Rivals.
You're it's deeply voyeuristic in a way that's like different
from other rides that have like families of animatronics
like doing things because like.
They're. It feels very uniquely, and I don't know,
maybe this I was just experiencing something myself
when I was going to this ride, but like I feel like a lot of other
animatronic rides, it's like this is a show that you're going to see.
Right. But like there's so little effort put into like.
A show for the person going through, it's just kind of like these
animatronics exist here and you get to go through it
and you see what is happening and that's kind of it.
They aren't in other words, they aren't like, hey, you're here.
Welcome. They don't acknowledge you.
You're just watching them go about their day to day.
No, no, no, it is.
It is. They're not trying too hard.
You know, they're kind of just like, like, oh, we're playing cave volleyball.
Oh, did you know we have our own boardwalk?
Like it's gone back all the way since here.
We have a square dancing.
It's like there's a whole thing.
There's a drive in like it's amazing. Amazing.
It's like it's a very it's a crazy premise that. All right.
So you're going to go see underground cave world. Great.
What's what is that?
I'm going to see a lot of like bats or what is this going to be?
No, it's a bunch of cave people all with a really united,
specific style of drawing that are or not drawn, but design.
Wallace and Gromody, very totally.
Nation looking. Absolutely. Yeah.
I thought Rugrats a little bit, too.
Yeah, a little.
There's some Garfield, too, though.
Yeah, a little bit, a little bit.
But there's definitely some Tommy Pickles faces like throughout the ride
in the in the dance hall scene.
That's like a step up from the Billy Joel piano man song.
Like it kind of looks like the cave man version of that bar. Yes.
And I feel like there's also a lot of like no stakes,
like, oh, this thing's about to happen.
Stuff going on like.
Like there's like one where I'm trying to recall,
I think it's like a dinosaur is like hoisting up something
that's going to drop on like a cave person.
And yet I don't know how to put my finger on it,
but it lacks any of the urgency of like any other of setups of those kinds
that you see in like another
ride, you know, where you're like, oh, God, the dynamite's going to fall.
Or like, for example, in Pirates of the Caribbean, right?
When they're all like shooting at each other and there's like explosives
everywhere and there's that thing hanging above you.
I guess it's because nothing's ever hanging above you.
It's like to the side.
And it all looks like very obviously like paper mache.
And so you're just like, and if it falls on him, so what?
You know, danger is more casual in this time. Yes. Yes.
Yeah, it's a more brutal era.
Yes. It's going to happen.
It was brutal, brutal. Yeah.
They are similar to that.
There's a I think my favorite aspect of it.
Yeah. So it is like it's cave people who are also like beach dwellers.
They're doing the same thing that you're doing up on top of the boardwalk,
but they're doing it underground.
They're having like they're they're having fun burgers,
McBoulder burgers and dino dogs, and they're watching bands play and stuff.
They're having a fun seaside day just like you.
But there is a big sign that says sharkasaurus warning today.
So that feels like stakes a little bit.
Oh, it was going to be we're going to see a sharkasaurus
maybe at the end of the ride.
And then it's like 15 seconds later, there just is the sharkasaurus.
It's very big, but it's grinning.
It seems to be lunging at somebody, but you don't find out what happened.
And they're they're probably fine. I'm not worried about it.
No, exactly. No one's in peril.
Like you're just like, oh, I guess they're together.
There's also like interpersonal stuff happening between the animatronics.
Like you get to see kind of fun, like, oh, he's looking at her,
but he's with her. You know what I mean?
Like that kind of because they're all like swinging singles, like they're all
the vibrant, like Polly scene in the cave.
That's the brother.
They're Polly cave people. Yes.
And the big band era never ended, seemingly.
The big band era that once the big bands have played
the old coconut grove at the Santa Cruz Beach Boardwalk.
There's still cave people,
big bands in the ride, the clam tones.
You got the clam tones playing.
That seems like a good show.
There's a lot of good that might be on the like our fake final four
is like full animatronic bands.
That's a that's a fun and electronic band area.
And that not says that really good one in the log ride.
And yeah, shout out to the clam tones. Good job.
And with the clam tones, I do want to say here,
I think this kind of falls in the same.
Mm, joie de vivre of the name, where it's like the clam tones,
like of the name of the ride, the clam tones.
There's no danger that the clam tones are playing the music that you hear.
Like they are supposed to be, but we all know, like their movements,
like there's not any way that the music that they are creating
is the music that we're hearing.
Do you know what I'm saying?
They don't suddenly that is not a speaker that you pass by
that's playing music similar to the instruments you see them playing.
It's entirely unrelated.
It like I feel like the ride is trying to tell us like,
you believe that they're playing this music, right?
But like, you know, like, there's no way it would be.
They're playing a different genre or something you're feeling.
Yeah. And just like the way that they're moving,
there's no possible way that like their range of motion
would be able to even at all play that kind of music.
It's very nice. I like it.
A lot of suspension of disbelief. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That makes sense.
Should we describe a little bit just looks wise?
We're talking about this this cave ride like it's very like
I wanted to say kind of it's it's a better version of the Kiss Mini Golf
in Vegas color wise.
There's like kind of totally low neon blacklight.
Great blacklight. Right.
Like stuff going on.
But oh, it's low, low rent ish, I think, in a good way,
in a way that I actually feel like it gives it a vibe.
Oh, it's so super charming.
And the story that I looked up about it is that
they thought that this thing was kind of this was open in 1961.
In the late 90s, they thought this is decaying.
This is all right.
This was put in in Flintstones era.
Do people care about the Flintstones anymore?
Let's do something different here.
They were going to put a whole other dark ride in.
And then people started saying, but I love the cave people.
And I think the Santa Cruz Beach Boardwalk folks were like, they you do.
Like, I don't think they realize the cult.
And then they they talked about it and said, well, is there just a way
to like inject new energy in a new storyline?
And they got this dark ride company, R&R, to come in and revamp it
and make the effects better.
But it's all still the original figures.
So it's this like great it's 60s bones and kooky sub Flintstones characters
mixed with, you know, a 90s refresh.
And I think all of that, that it's a beach,
you know, that they're hanging out on the pier and
eating Brano burgers and all that.
I think that's all new in the 90s.
So I don't know.
It's so nice that this was like
it's 60s charm being saved.
Yeah. Due to a public outcry.
And crosses over with a different ride in this park
because there is a caveman on one of the ride vehicles on the Skyglider,
the shareless type.
Yes.
Ride that you can ride up and down the boardwalk.
Again, another thing that I was so excited to see one of these
because I feel like a lot of beach towns used to have these on their boardwalk
and then remove them partially probably because the upkeep is expensive
and the liability.
It really feels like you'd fall out of one of these things.
You definitely would. Yeah.
And it's always fun seeing that cave guy because there's, you know, a story there.
Right. Like, did he get out?
Is he stuck?
Is he coming back?
I like the idea of like this larger mythos surrounding these cave people.
Is he an Encino man?
Oh, Link. Yeah.
Right. Right. Yes.
Did he leave?
Did he somehow escape the time vortex that you go into at the beginning of cave train?
I also wanted to bring up like what's because I was just thinking about this.
And I don't know if this is real or anything.
This is just me postulating. But.
OK, so I was thinking about why a train, right?
Like, why are you in a train in the train, cave train, right?
Because and the train looks.
It doesn't look cave ish, it looks like a train,
but the boardwalk is right off of a set of train tracks.
So maybe that's like.
Like a like a world within a world, you know what I'm saying?
Like, so so you're saying like it's like in the narrative
of the boardwalk, you're using the same train that might have been on those tracks
in the real world that's transporting you to this magical cave land.
Yeah. And that's what people on that train, the real train,
are experiencing kind of like when they go by the boardwalk.
Sure. Yes. So like, look at this world of boardwalk people.
Oh, but then we're not talking to the people on the train. Right.
Then waving to them, maybe a little bit, you acknowledge them,
but not we're just going about our day.
And in the same way, the cave people are just living in their cave world.
They're not concerned about us on the train.
Yeah. Yeah. They're just like us.
Levels is really what it is. Yeah.
Yeah. No, I think that's I think that's right.
This thing is so cool.
I love that it's the whole time if you're up on the boardwalk,
you're doing anything on the boardwalk that you're above this long, long dark ride.
This entire time, it's such like clever use of the double decker space.
This thing is great. Everybody watch a video of cave train. It's great.
There's also OK, there's this other ride and I'm I cannot recall
the name of it right now, but it's right across the way from the cave train.
And it's like something like waves or something.
Anyway, you go in, it's under the boardwalk, but it's like a concrete space.
OK. And it's just.
A nothing room like this, the walls are like they look like temporary,
like rigging. It doesn't even it's like no effort put in. Right.
But it's just a bunch of like, I want to say, like wave runners.
Like you just sit and it's like a bunch of them on like a series of little
carousels that all each spin and they all all together all spin.
But they turn out all the lights and each of the wave
runners that you're sitting in has headlights and you're just spinning
like crazy in the dark with these lights that are just like.
And it is the most transformative experience, like once those lights go off
and they have like, you know, neon like lasers and like music.
It's like, and you're spinning in the dark.
The difference from before the ride starts
and while the ride is occurring is phenomenal.
Well, really, nothing happens except for lights.
Mm hmm. Can't find what this is called.
It's it's not wave writer because I looked it up and that's a slide.
There's no dark light.
I think it's called Wipe Out.
Wipe out. Yes. Wipe out.
That ride is so fun.
It really whips you around.
And it's a transformative experience of some kind is what you're saying.
Yeah. When you walk in, you're like, what is this?
But it only costs, you know, X amount of tickets.
So I guess I'll do it.
And then you do. And it's very fun. It's.
Yeah, it just like really takes advantage of that,
like centripetal force kind of thing.
There's a whole like like tilt.
Like I think some people I'm a guy who likes to be spun around
fast in a circle.
I like it. And you love that tilto world that they have.
I like a tilto world. I like a gravitron.
I don't think it's a sensation everyone likes, but it's I'm a lights guy
and I'm spinning around in a circle, guys.
So I'm looking at this now and I do.
I see exactly what you're saying.
It seems like it seems like you're doing like cosmic bowling
or you're playing laser tag. Yeah.
But you're being spun around like twice, essentially at the same time.
Double spins and it looks like it looks like darkness.
I was going to say it would blow my mind as a kid, but let's be honest,
it would blow my mind now.
It blew my mind now.
I went on that ride for the first time two years ago and I was changed.
I truly was like this ride, like because I was like, this seems so low rent
and so nothing, especially when you go in, you know, the in between
everybody get off and everybody get on all the lights are on
because they bring on all the lights. I swear it's like
fluorescent bulbs, like like so no magic.
Nothing. Terrible lighting.
It looks it looks odd and it looks like let me hear.
I'll bring up a share a screen real quick just to show everybody
how odd it looks with the lights on.
Here it is. Yeah.
Very industrial. This like I see what you're saying.
Like you walk into this.
You just see the machinery and the wires.
You don't think you're going to have a great time on this. Yeah.
Oh, also. OK, so you see how that the blue shirt child is tilting.
So you can control your.
Oh, wow. You really want to.
Yeah, if you really want to whip around, you just have to put your shoulders
into it and you'll really get whipping.
Wow. It does.
It looks like if you walk in a Broadway theater,
when it's just rehearsals and they have fluorescence on
and then you turn on all the show lights and turn off the audience lights
and you're like, oh, my gosh. Yes. Yes.
How it's so fun.
How is this not everywhere?
It's it's so, so, so fun.
I was cackling the entire time on this ride.
Yeah, because because there's so much going on and the lights
and then the controlling controllability of it.
It's very like Miami Vice.
Like the vibe is very.
Yeah. I guess you're on little speed boats.
Yeah, I guess.
Or I think they're like hover. Are they hovercrafts?
They look like they're hovering.
Well, so what you don't see is that the decor not in here is very like ocean theme.
Right. So that's my only.
So you're on like futuristic boat.
Yeah. See how the lights are turning on.
It's so cool.
Or you're on the boat from Thunder in Paradise or something like a futuristic boat.
Mini version, the children of Thunder in Paradise. Right.
Mini. Yeah. What's the name of the boat?
Thunder. It's the thunder, right?
And Thunder in Paradise.
Maybe some mini thunder.
Yeah. Thunder Juniors.
You're on a Thunder Junior.
A bunch of Thunder Juniors. Yeah.
This is delightful. I know what you mean.
Like, why is this not a standard type of dark ride?
So fun. Yeah.
Because you've got tilting and turning, which I really enjoy the combination of tilting and turning.
Yeah, boy, that's something.
I missed that one entirely.
Like we're so focused on on dark rides and original IPs.
You miss the simple thrills of Wipeout.
Yeah. And I only went on it because I had like a weird amount of tickets left
because how you do it there and I guess a lot of boardwalks these days is you like
you can get a wristband and then you add, you know, tickets or points or whatever.
And so like I had an odd number left and I was like, well, I could fit in a ride on this weird ride.
Also, no imagery about what this ride is going to be like, because there's just like a door,
like an open garage, basically.
And it's dark. And it just says.
What's the name of it? Wipeout. Wipeout.
It just says Wipeout. And you're like, what is that?
And you go in and if you go in while it's not going, you're like,
OK, maybe is this storage?
Is this a shed? Yeah, exactly.
Because it looks so industrial.
It looks like not for the public. Yeah.
But there are people going on it.
So I was like, fine, I'll go. And and and it was very fun.
I mean, there's a lot of that, like a lot of I like the mystery of this whole place in general,
which I don't know if it's all purposeful.
This sounds like they were just like, oh, we don't want to put up a sign on the shed.
But yeah, but the cause of that or what happens because of that is you have like
a very surprising experience because you don't get to see things.
And it's the same with cave or what?
Like you don't know the characters are in that ride.
You don't know. There's a lot of mystery to be had at the boardwalk, is what I'm saying.
Yeah. Maybe that's my thing with this place that I was near it essentially
and was like, I know what that is. That's like Santa Monica Pier.
I don't need to do that.
And I was wrong. I was completely right.
Like there's so I maybe I don't know.
I'm maybe not the biggest fan of the Santa Monica Pier.
It's a little like all off the shelf there.
I feel like. Yeah, I don't like the Santa Monica Pier.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
It's not great. You know what it is.
Yeah. You look at it. You know what you get.
Whereas this thing, like you wouldn't expect like
like rides with mythology and rides with surprises.
And you see the, you know, the wooden roller coaster like, oh, OK.
Yeah, I wouldn't roll by a beach. I know what that's like.
You wouldn't expect that it, you know, almost threw you out of it entirely.
Kelly, like there's yeah.
And that it's a historical landmark.
Like there's there's stories and surprises with everything here.
I feel. Yeah.
Also with the boardwalk,
there's like a discovery aspect to everything because they're not
like super streamlined and you know where everything is.
I mean, unless you go there all the time. But like there's like.
Because they kind of like don't bother to make everything super slick,
you're kind of just like finding yourself on certain rides.
And then you're like, oh, I guess I'll go on this ride.
And then it turns out like it's this huge dark ride
that's underneath the entire boardwalk, you know, and and and.
Yeah, there's kind of like this feeling that you discovered it.
Right. You know, yeah, that is that is the best kind of feeling at one of these places
is feeling like you've done something, you've uncovered something,
because it does happen even like if you're like, you know,
we were told to go with this ride Sinbad's voyage in Tokyo, Disney,
and we got on it and we were like, we had no idea what it was.
We loved it. It's one of our favorite rides.
But it felt like, you know what?
We kind of discovered that. Yeah, we didn't even.
It's really just your brain playing a trick on you because you didn't know anything about it.
But it is a feeling of like I did something here.
If there's nobody telling you this is an incredible classic.
So get ready and love this.
Like if you don't have any of that buildup and just get to experience it.
Following like a group of middle schoolers and you're like,
I guess I'll just go where they're going. Right.
And then afterwards, you're like, I have
something everyone could come around, gather around.
And then you're DMing podcast, the ride, and you're like, guys,
I have a really not well known ride I'd like to talk to you about.
Yes. Yeah, for sure.
That happens all the time.
I've looked up Wipeout real quick on just on YouTube to see if there's another one.
Wipeout apparently is in the very common name among a wide variety of rides.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Like you just look at you on YouTube and it's like one of it's just one of those
circle things that spins around one of its one of.
Yeah, which is not as fun.
One of them is like a weird arm with like some Kuka arm
chair kind of Harry Potter things.
I think it just spins.
So I guess Wipeout at this point, you can't.
Oh, yeah. Wipeout.
There's one where it's like a long chair of people in an arm.
It's like Wipeout is used for many things, but I cannot see another one
that looks exactly like that one.
So maybe that is truly unique.
Well, I've been to a million carnivals or fairs or stuff
that have like the bobsleds or the Himalayans.
Or and it's it's yeah, it's always one of two things.
But like, yeah, stuff that's generic that they can call
any rides, you know, the log ride, the log ride.
Yeah, it's not like an original character, say, like
my friend, my boardwalk card.
There he is.
I came across him, my boardwalk rechargeable card.
He's got a great attitude.
He's in the safety video for the giant tipper.
He so the I think I guess you pay for things at this park
by putting money on a card.
And they have in the in the recent past made their mascot
one of these cards with legs, with very scrawny little ant legs
and 3D eyeballs.
He's he's very strange.
The voice is strange. Yeah, yeah.
I was creeped out by the video I watched where he explains
how he works, which has a lot of odd double speak and like,
so just make sure you swipe me and don't lose me
because other people are going to want me and then they'll have me
and they'll have the money on me and not you.
It gets very confusing, this guy talking about you,
talking to you about himself.
But then it really did you see this one, Jason, where then he
suddenly it cuts in.
There's four of him. He multiplied.
No, I haven't seen that.
You was right.
I did. I did have the reaction of like, this guy's got a good attitude.
But what is he trying to hide?
And it appears multiple man powers is what he's trying to hide.
That reminds me of I was
there's this commercial that's been happening a lot lately,
which is like the Kologard commercial,
which they've also decided to anthropomorphize a like colorectal test.
And the like little box comes up to this guy on the beach.
And and he's like, I'm Kologard.
And the guy is like with I assume his wife and ignoring his wife
to have a full on conversation with like the box.
And he's like, I can tell you if you have like this and that and whatever.
And it just is a similar thing where you're like,
why did you make this a character?
Like you couldn't you.
You don't need to have it be a character.
Hey, buddy, don't look at her. Look at me.
Eyes on me. Eyes on me.
Eyes on me. Now put me up your asshole if you want to know if you're sick.
There is Kologard.
Kologard, I've never seen Kologard.
Here he is with a hat and a whistle like a referee.
He's blowing and he has little he has cheeks.
He has cheek puffs.
Wow. This is great IP.
Kologard has cheeks.
Oh, don't think just because he's a he's a box of of colorectal tests
doesn't mean he does. He can't have cheeks.
Wow. Well, we have to subject him to the podcast, the right test real quick.
Is Kologard cute?
No, Kologard is a criminal.
Hmm. How so? Why is he a criminal?
Yeah, he's trying to help.
I don't. That's OK.
The best villains think they're trying to help.
Mike, I don't do trust him.
First of all, why is he everywhere?
Why is he there? He's everywhere.
Why did he follow you to the beach?
I'm not bathroom.
I don't look. I don't know his motivations.
I don't know what's in his heart.
But if I'm judging him purely aesthetically, I think he's cute.
His face is a colon, by the way.
That's true.
But it's like it's blue.
It's shades of blue.
And it's a kind of you could just mistake it for maybe some sort of symbol.
Wait, is it is the weight?
The shape on his face is a is a colon.
Like, well, yeah, I guess down knows the anus.
Yeah. Anus. Yeah, I guess.
Yeah, I cute, though, I think, because it's not like
it's not cute because you know his nose is the anus.
I think he's cute despite the fact that his nose is the anus. OK.
Well, I mean, look, I'm not telling you you have to say he's cute.
I'm just judging my personal opinion.
I do think Colo Guard is cute.
I don't know.
Colo Guard, Colo Guard versus my boardwalk card.
One will fall like Godzilla versus Kong. Yeah.
I like Colo Guard more than my boardwalk card.
Cute. I'm not sure is the right word.
I think he's likable, but he's not like a child.
So I think it's weird to call him.
Yeah. Yeah.
A little a little too much like Clippy.
I don't think Clippy is cute.
I don't mind Clippy.
I don't know if I call him cute. What do you think?
I do think he's cute. Thank you.
Yeah. All right.
Yeah, I think he's cute.
And I love a practical.
I love I'm a practical guy.
You know, I this kit makes sense to me.
You know, the kit makes sense.
I just don't get why he needs to like follow you everywhere.
He seems to be a guy.
He seems needy.
He it's odd that he's alive.
It's like did a wizard and chant up Colo Guard box.
And you know, I came to life one night.
You're right. When you say he seems needy, he seems like the kind of guy
where like if you're upset about something, he's like,
but I need you to tell me that I'm doing a good job making you feel better.
Comforting. Yes. Yes. Right. Right. Right.
He's that he does something wrong and then it's like you.
But it's actually on you. Yeah. Me out.
Yes, I agree.
I mean, the Pillsbury Doe Boy, I think is cute,
but he's also one of the neediest character. Yes.
And so I think it's a similar vibe with him.
He obviously makes cookies and doesn't ask people to shit in a box for a side
for him and him. He says it's in him.
He's shooting in him. Yeah.
I mean, you're shooting in Colo Guard.
Wait, that's what the test is. You should in the cold.
You you you like drop off your stool sample and then they do a test.
Clearly, this is a test that I haven't done.
And maybe I need to maybe I need to get too dumb.
We're going too dumb. You're like, wait, this is what you do.
What I truly did.
I did not know until this time what a colorectal test involved.
I didn't know that you shit in a little box.
Well, you you don't go in the box.
You go in like, oh, you in the box.
You go in this little in this little plastic trash can that comes in the box.
Yeah. And you put that in the box.
OK, so you could you would take this little plastic thing out of Kola.
You don't have to open the lid of this box with a face
that we've all been looking at and poop into him.
No, no, no. He's like.
Um, he's like the outside of a porta potty.
You know what I'm saying?
He's like not the part that's holding the poo.
He's like holding the thing that's holding the poo.
Oh, right, right.
OK, I mean, it would be fun.
I mean, it would be fun if you were to put it in there.
And he goes, thank you.
Like in the box, we talk a little bit because if you take too long, he goes, I'm hungry.
Yes, I would be.
Ironically, yeah, that's just flavor.
Some of the food offerings at the Santa Cruz Beach Boardwalk
might be helpful to you if you need to use the look art in moving things along.
It's all like deep fried Twinkies and, you know,
corn dogs and yeah, nachos and that sort of thing.
And the you know, if you take a step back in time,
this struck me as potentially something, despite it being from 1933,
something that Jason might dig today, which is Winnie's turnover pies.
Yes. And where you can get hot chicken pie for 15 cents.
There is a substantial historical blog on the Santa Cruz Beach Boardwalk website.
And I read a long post about the ownership history of Winnie's turnover pie.
There's been a lot of turnover at Winnie's turnover, a lot of turnover and changing tastes.
I mean, a lot this park, you know, Seaside Park is always subject to changing tastes.
You know, there used to be the plunge, a massive indoor chlorinated saltwater pool,
which is now. Wow.
What is it called?
Neptune's Kingdom, I think it's called now.
And it's miniature golf and arcade.
Yes, that miniature golf is like blacklight.
Very good. Very fun.
Yeah, this whole place grew out of the of the bath, the big bath facility.
And the thing that I copy pasted right under that photo of turnover pies
is the phrase visitors could swim in the heated plunges and eat fancy turtle
soup at the casino grill.
Oh, man. Mass baths and turtle soup.
You know, that's what you do in 1895.
You are what you eat.
I feel like if you're sitting in a hot bath, you're like basically turtle soup.
And then you're eating turtle soup. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Any time. I mean, the shredder, the shredder would have loved it.
It would have been so all into it.
Sure. He said that a lot, right.
And he's going to turn him into turtle soup.
He said tonight. Well, it's I think the first Nintendo game is he says tonight.
I'll die tonight.
I dine on turtle soup, I believe is the quote from the shredder.
What if he did it?
What if shredder killed him and then ate them soup?
And that was the end of the Ninja Turtle.
And then it was like the end to do to do to do really fast credits. Yeah.
There's a very dark series happening right now,
and I have not read the second issue, but the only one it's the future.
And only one turtle is alive.
I've heard about this. I read it.
Yeah. You read it.
I've read the first issue so far.
I read both. Lots of fun reveals.
Yeah, really. So maybe that that happens.
Maybe there's a maybe shredder is got a bowl of something.
Oh, page splash of just him eating the bowl of turtle soup.
It's just lots of panels of the full pay.
Everything is a full page flash of shredder to tasting soups
with the comment like a mouth chompin
or wiping his mouth,
picking, picking a little flick, like a little bit of orange bandana
out of his teeth.
And, you know, that's Michelangelo in the second issue.
Spoiler alert. They do eat eggs.
So they might be building to a larger, more ornate legs.
Turtle. No, not turtle.
No, just like regular eggs, but they're hard to find in this.
They, you know, who do the turtles eat eggs in the series or to shredder?
Do turtles eat? I don't want to spoil anything.
These issues are hard to track down.
I asked at my comic shop if if they had issue two for Mike
and they kind of chuckled like, no, no.
Like it came out two weeks ago and they're like, well wiped out.
So yeah, it's almost comic book man thing.
Turtle eat eggs in real life, by the way.
Just looked it up.
Hmm. Yeah, like little Grogu. Yeah.
Hey, I got another
animal who eats unorthodox things right here.
Look at Leo, the paper eater.
This is a good idea. Wow.
This is a way this was a way to get people to clean up trash.
Is this thing made a sound like called people over and then made chomping sounds.
So it encourages kids to put paper in them.
It called people over like it.
OK, question. Was it like?
And you may not know this is my band fair.
Was it like pre recorded sounds just every once in a while?
Or was there a person like hiding with a microphone
that would like see people and call out to them or?
My guess is pre recorded.
I think maybe and then maybe when you put something in, it triggers.
Right. Chomping sounds.
Num num nums or something.
I don't like how round his mouth is.
I wish it were just that teeth.
More realistic.
It was like more mouth shape.
Like I just don't like.
I don't like how far I'd probably have to put my hand in to drop.
What are you know what I'm saying?
Keep going. Yeah.
Keep going deeper, deeper.
Touch my uvula.
Get your elbow in.
Get your elbow in there.
Uh, yeah, it is a little odd.
Yeah, it was just a trash can, though, at the base of its.
I mean, it obviously it's a disembodied head.
I assume it wasn't like a shredder.
There was on a paper.
Now I'm not talking about the shredder.
I'm talking about a paper.
Shredder. A paper shredder in there.
Jesus, I don't think so.
I don't think there's like a garbage disposal in this lion's been this cute
lion's mouth. Seems dangerous.
Do we think that lion is cute?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
We're all in agreement.
Unfortunately, he's cute.
Leo, the paper eater is cute, cuter than the color rectal box.
What have we what have we not talked about?
Well, in terms of these cool rides, you want to hit haunted castle.
Oh, it's kind of it's it's not quite the cave train, but it's pretty good.
Very good. Yeah.
I actually went on that before I went on the cave train.
And I had, you know, like zero expectations because,
you know, a lot of the outdoor rides just seem very carnivally.
Like the Tilted World that they have is the is the kind that they're
it's literally just like grating and you just lean against it.
And they just put a little chain thing in front of you.
And then when it goes up, you just hope you don't fall out.
So everything seems very like lo fi, very.
Like basic, I don't know.
So when I saw you see the sign and it just says like.
On a castle and there's like, you know,
sounds and you're kind of like, OK, this is just going to be what?
Like some cardboard cutouts or something and like not.
But it is a very long and be.
If you don't know that most of it takes place underneath
where you start out, it's quite delightful being like,
how far down are we going to go?
You know, oh, does it descend?
I don't think I could tell that from.
I think it does descend. Wow. Wow. Yeah.
There's a lot of, you know, again.
Weirdly, like a lot of like singular animatronics
that either like pop out at you or like are down a hallway
and you're like, oh, what's that?
But they also have like fun wigs and T-shirts on some of the animatronics,
like some of the skeletons are wearing like Santa Cruz boardwalk T-shirts.
So it's like, oh, someone from the boardwalk got stuck in the haunted castle.
Yeah, there's a lot of like creatures and skeletons and stuff.
But then at some point, there's a bunch of skeletons
who are all burying a Santa Cruz surfer dude alive.
It's really creepy.
And he says like, oh, no, man, I don't know what it is.
But like, you can sense his character big time.
The voice acting is superb in this one. Really good.
Yeah. Well, there's a lot of like notable characters.
You talk to you like the there's a there's a skeleton
who's holding his own skull separately from his body.
I remember that being a fun performance.
And then there's like a creepy British guillotine guy.
Yeah, because that's the end of your trip through the haunted castle
as you get guillotined and then it goes.
Then it's the bright light of your back outside.
And that's it. I think this this ride ends with your death. Yeah.
There's a you are dead.
A great effect where there's like an alligator or a crocodile in the distance.
And it comes towards you under a dock and every board on the dock like.
Yeah, that's really cool.
Splits down the middle.
That is so cinematic. It's really cool.
I was really. Yeah, that was awesome.
Yeah, there's a scary rabbit that's being cooked by a skeleton.
You got projections on bus, a la haunted mansion. Yeah.
This is this is great.
And I love like the genre of ride, like like the one that I'm
very nostalgic for growing up, the scary dark ride in Balboa Island,
in Orange County, that where you're if you're combining
different mythologies of scary stuff, if it's like
full knight's armor moving at you and then like a rat coming out,
but then also dinosaurs.
Or big scary snakes or like and ghosts and pirates.
Like how much just all the scary things all in one place.
That is fantastic.
Like mix them all up, you know, very confusingly.
I like I like a ride that feels very like cokey in its creation, right?
Because they're like, well, like what's scary?
Like skeletons, right?
But then also an alligator. OK.
And it's like very like genre mixing, because like
if I were thinking haunted castle,
first of all, I would think ghosts.
But there's like a billion skeletons.
And then there's also an alligator like that.
Aspect like there's like a whole swamp section that you go through, which is like.
You just wouldn't think, oh, haunted castle,
which I love that about that, like I love that they were just kind of like,
I don't know, let's throw a bunch of shit in there and like hope it's scary.
Like they got bored with the castle premise and are like, all right,
we need something else. It's a long.
It is a five minute ride.
We already made the sign.
We can't change it.
So yeah, but the haunted castle's backyard, it's Marsh backyard.
They got to go to whatever swan.
Yeah, they wouldn't have a feel bit of a swamp.
If you were watching like a movie version of it with this idea,
sometimes I feel like I'm watching a movie where I go, I feel like 45 minutes
and they ran out of the premise and they were like, well, what are we going to do now?
And then they like throw something wild at it,
which can go bad or less bad sometimes.
But like for this, for a ride situation, fantastic.
Bring it on. Bring it on.
They also simultaneously, they have a ghost blasters.
Did you see this?
I go on. I did not do ghost blasters.
Just because a listener tweeted out us about ghost blasters recently,
asking why the Nickelodeon Park at the Mall of America,
why do they have a ghost blasters?
And it's not like Danny Phantom or something to clarify,
to answer your question.
Ghost blasters is a pre like a prefab ride.
It's a design dark ride by the Sally Corporation
that parks can license and install and it's good to go.
And it saves money and time by installing.
It's like a bunch of unrelated parks kind of across the country.
Yes, a bunch of parks have ghost blasters.
And you can go to the Sally Dark Rides website and like look at the like,
you know, brochure like the digital.
Oh, we could buy that or Scott could get it and put it in the backyard right now.
Yeah. So are you allowed to add your own zest to it?
Or is it like is are there like licensing restrictions?
I think depending on your budget, you are able to customize to different levels.
I'm sure that you customize yourself, though, is what I'm asking.
Like, could you be like, oh, I want to make this not necessarily existing IP,
but like maybe I want to make this luau themed like, could I do that?
Or are they like, you're not allowed to represent our product?
That's a great question.
I bet they never check in on it again.
I bet like it's out.
Technically, if you ask the question, they'd say no.
But if you just did it, nobody would ever find out. Right.
Like if like, yeah, if we bought one of these rides, put it in Scott's backyard.
Could we change all the characters into like
like characters we talk about a podcast ride like Ringo Starr
or I Love Lucy guest star Frank Nelson?
Could we put those characters on this ride?
Colo Guard, one of my favorite characters in
could a ghost poop into Cola Guards top?
Yes. And would Sally Ride Corporation be upset
if one of their guests pooped in Cola Guard?
I don't know.
Cola Guard company might be assuming that you got the correct licensing for
for the IP that you're using for Cola Guard.
Yes. But we may have to do an analogous Cola Guard,
like call them like poop box or Mr. Poop Box or something. Right.
And then everyone would be like, but I know what you mean.
You mean classic Cola Guard. Right.
And then we just if we get sued, we say, well, this is parody law.
Yeah. This is a classic parody. Sorry. Yeah. Fair use.
I bet I bet there's leeway.
I bet there's leeway with it.
It feels like if there is licensing, it feels like I don't know
if Sally Ride's corporation is trying to make a Ghost Blasters TV show.
I'm not sure how precious with their IP they are.
I think they should at this point, because everything else
that's ever been in a thing is becoming a show. But that's true.
I bet if you talk to them, they're like, I do whatever you want.
I don't care.
I'm guessing, but maybe not.
So let's just gather the probably seven million dollars
it takes to buy all the parts of Ghost Blasters.
And then we can and then we can do whatever we want.
Yeah. You know, better to ask forgiveness than.
Absolutely. Permission. Yeah.
And that applies to Sally Ride's corporation.
In the coal guard, right? You're going to make.
Yeah, it's mostly it's by the way, it's mostly going to be the coal guard.
Yeah. Yeah.
With a little bit of the Knights and White Satin stuff
that we're able to get from their their other innovations.
Is this called the rectal blasters?
The only like the only laser game
with a score where you're also curing rectal cancer along the way. Nice.
Wow. Yeah, that's yes.
That's the that's the that's the ride. Yeah. Pretty cool.
If only were that simple in the real world, you just take a laser gun
and blast away the rectal cancer.
But it imagines a better world where that is what's possible someday.
Yeah. Yeah. And at the end, a generic animatronic
called like Rock and Roll Older Man says like, great job.
Peace and kindness, peace and kindness.
That's our generic rink that rock and roll older man.
Yeah. And then you get a child's t-shirt with his face on it at the end.
For your child. Generic rock and roll man.
There's been a weird history of IP at this place.
Do you know they had they were just using Popeye for a while.
Popeye olive oil late 80s, early 90s.
I was watching an old commercial and then Popeye and olive oil ran by.
Like, what are you talking about?
So just for like, I don't know, like a decade, they had Popeye
and now they don't.
Was he present at the park?
Yeah. You can take a picture of Popeye at the boardwalk.
I love that. Mm hmm.
Oh, that's stunning.
Popeye is weird. Popeye.
I mean, it's universal now.
And then there's the creepy island off the coast of Italy,
where you can hang out with the Popeye characters.
And at one point, they were also in Santa Cruz, California.
That's so funny. Weird travels.
There's also did you guys come across
what was in the haunted castle space long, long ago in the 30s?
A ride called Dante's Inferno.
Oh, I miss this.
I saw a headline about it, but then I didn't click it.
So they've always had this space for a scary ride.
And I think there was some iteration of a haunted.
It's mostly been haunted castle for a while.
I think the current version came in in 2010.
But when this space opened in the 30s,
it was a ride called Dante's Inferno sub headline, A Trip to Hades.
So this long before Mr.
Toads was an attraction, there was a trip through hell.
Wow. Yeah, yeah.
Pretty pretty. I'm assuming you probably die at some point
and then you're there.
Or maybe they're just like, welcome to hell.
Or maybe it's like cave train where you're just like, you're a tourist.
You're visiting hell to then maybe to scope it out,
see if you want to live there someday.
But I don't know any premise beyond that.
It's very weird and creepy, like seeing like 1930s
plaster representing the stalagmites and stalactites
that you would find in hell.
Like the facade is really fantastic.
But I don't know what happened once you were in there.
I don't know if it was either really tame or like unbelievably
morality tale terrifying.
It could go either way.
It could really go either way.
Yeah, bad. Yeah, it's too bad.
There's not like an old newsreel.
To talk definitions of hell were very different.
It could be like one room is just a bachelor in a studio apartment
and the next is an unmarried woman,
a 30 year old unmarried woman, a bathing suit in multiple pieces.
Couple in the same bed on TV.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, it's just like two beds, like being pushed together over and over again.
No, no, don't do it.
And then they and then it splits down the middle and they tumble into hell.
Oh, that's great.
That's a cool effect.
Beautiful, beautiful hospitalized regularly going on this ride.
They were so aghast that that band's not big at all.
It's a small band. No.
Get them on the cave train stat.
Curious.
Yeah, I've also got another thing in the realm of like
scary stuff and horrors that occurred.
So lots and lots of movies been filmed at St.
Chris Beach Boardwalk.
Lost Boys. Yes.
Us recently, Killer Clowns from Outer Space.
So lots of lots of varying degrees of creepy movies.
But I didn't know.
I have never seen the film Sudden Impact.
Which is a dirty, hairy movie.
So Clint Eastwood like starred and directed
this scene of that.
So the movie climax is at the Santa Cruz Beach Boardwalk.
And, Jay, this is also this is one of the you know,
we were just seeing a lot of theme park uses of theme park
or movies of theme parks for our fake theme park Final Four.
This isn't a fake theme park.
Boy, this is a great theme park scene.
You'll see. And he kicks it off with the the iconic line itself.
So buckle up for this.
Come on.
Make my day.
Scary guy holding a woman hostage on top of the giant dipper.
She punches her way out.
Dirty Harry shoots him.
Many times.
He falls off the coaster over and over again.
Yes. Electrified into the water.
Oh, look at that.
He falls off the giant dipper
through the glass of the carousel, lands on a carousel horse.
But it's not a horse.
It's he's very unlucky because it's a unicorn.
And the horn punctures him quite bloodily right through the chest.
Stunning. Cool, huh?
Stunning. Wow.
Yeah. What a little theme park action sequence.
I'm so jealous of it.
Really great.
And I love the Santa Cruz boardwalks.
Just. Devil may care attitude about being portrayed in this way
of like being a place where a person could fall and be impaled on their carousel.
I love that.
We don't give a shit.
Just give us the money and whatever you want to do, whatever you want to manipulate.
Go for it. I love it.
Yeah, geez.
You know, there was a movie in the 60s.
I might be getting this wrong.
40 Pounds of Trouble that was filmed in Disneyland.
I think Tony Curtis is in it.
And in that movie, it's just like a guy runs around.
He's chased by another guy and then everyone runs, but then they emerge safely.
And that's it.
It is the tamest action you've ever seen.
And that's what Disneyland would allow.
Cut to Santa Cruz Beach.
All of these horror films and crazy shit.
And then there's impaling.
And yeah, boy, it's devil may care.
They're taking risks.
In Lost Boys, the bridge that they're supposed to be on by the boardwalk.
So you can walk across that to get to the boardwalk.
You're supposed to walk on the side of it.
So basically, there's a railway, right?
And it's on this bridge with planks.
And each of the planks is about, I don't know, five or six inches apart, pretty wide.
And then to the side, there's like this safe part for the pedestrians to walk.
But of course, if you are a rebellious teen or when I was in college,
you can walk along where the railway is.
And it's pretty scary because once you're so far,
you can't really jump over easily to where the pedestrians are supposed to be.
So you're kind of like tempting fate by being where a train could hit you.
And you're very high above the water.
So if you're scared of heights, that's a river at that point.
It goes over a river that feeds into the Monterey Bay.
Yeah.
And would you believe I don't have any close by,
but very popular for engagement photos and influencer bullshit.
I'm sure.
If someone tried to propose to me on that, I would push them into the ocean or the river.
And they would fall or push them onto the carousel.
Oh my gosh.
Come this way.
Perfectly impaled.
What if we not talked about, Kelly, was there anything new,
any other odd memories of this place or things you ran into while you were there?
No, I guess I just want to OK, this is like I have to do this because I grew up in the South Bay,
which is Torrance, like not the NorCal South Bay.
And I have to give a shout out to the boardwalk I grew up with,
which is the Redondo Beach boardwalk.
They had this like really creepy like boardwalk area that had basically just like a little
tilt to whirl and which was clown themed.
And they had this machine that I will like never forget,
which is like you put in and that machine has been there since it opened.
You put in a quarter and then like marionettes dance for you.
And it's like a little scene of like some kind of drama, I guess,
between the marionettes.
And so they dance for you.
So I do have to, you know, it's now being closed and they're putting in condos there,
which is very, very sad.
Yeah, I didn't know that.
That's a bummer.
Yeah, I've been there.
That's really cool.
I love it.
Yeah, I love it.
So that I do have to say that was my first boardwalk love,
but the Santa Cruz boardwalk is so iconic.
Do you do recall when am I being insulting to this place that you love from my trips down there?
I recall it like stinking around there.
Yeah, it smells like shit.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It smells like fish because it's right next to this open air fish market.
And the way that it is set up is like it's not really that open air because like
it's like a like a C shape.
And so like at the curve or I guess a U at the bottom curve of the U is the fish market.
And then just right to the right is like this boardwalk thing with like
games and rides and stuff.
But it's all enclosed.
So like all the air just like goes into it just funnels straight into.
And there's a really like like no air escaping parking garage right there.
Yes.
I've written my bike through carbon monoxide parking lot.
Yeah, yeah, it's like really tight.
So yeah, carbon monoxide and fish all merge in this little blowing into like a Tilted Whirl.
That's heaven to me.
I mean, that sounds great.
I loved it.
I loved it, but it is going away.
So I'm very sad, but there's still the Santa Cruz boardwalk.
Yeah.
Can I mention the coconut grove?
We haven't mentioned that spelled an anachronistic spelling.
Of coconut with an A in the middle.
This is now used for like weddings and conferences and that sort of thing back.
We were talking about changing taste, but in the 30s and 40s, it would host big bands like
fronted by Benny Goodman and Artie Shaw and another reoccurring podcast,
the ride character, Xavier Kugin mentioned on the websites.
Well, of course, great.
That's great.
There's also a you're welcome listeners.
Xavier Kugin is back.
It's 2021 more save.
There's a portion of one of the buildings called the Boardwalk Historium
and where you can learn more about this place.
And I will push anyone out of the way.
If you tell me, would you like to learn about the history of this seaside town?
Yes, I absolutely would.
Hey, and one more little thing about the history.
This place, they had a ride about a ride called Autorama.
Autorama, I'm not sure, but it was a ride a lot like the Autopia
opened in 1961 and unlike the Autopia, it had a guard rail.
So Walt Disney heard about this place and heard that it wasn't constantly maiming children
like the Autopia was at the time, which was just Roman free, no guide rail.
So the company Aero built the thing and they built a lot of the early Disney rights.
They said, why don't you come check it out?
So Walt Disney in 1963 went up to the Santa Cruz Beach Boardwalk, checked it out,
looked around and was like, all right, we should probably do a guard rail.
I think we better do it.
So that's why there's a guard rail on the Autopia.
But his trip to the Santa Cruz Beach Boardwalk led to this photo of a bunch of people.
And in the center is Walt Disney smoking a cigarette.
Wow.
Right under the giant dipper.
Yeah.
Himself having a nice puff.
Nice crease in those pants.
You can tell he was sitting for a while.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, that's true.
Very wrinkly pants.
Very wrinkled pants.
He looks tired.
Tired.
Yeah.
Worn down.
Soon to die.
Dead in three years of this photo of smoking.
Well, yeah, the dang Lost Boys are creeping around.
They crave this delicious blood.
I cannot believe that the Santa Cruz Boardwalk influenced someone to make,
like through good example, to make their ride safer.
Because the Santa Cruz Boardwalk is very, you know.
Wow.
This very ride that he's under, you said, does not feel safe to you to this day.
And yet it inspired safety.
Yeah.
I mean, I feel like it's safe if you sit next to somebody that's similar in height to you.
Right.
So your plus it up would be maybe try to even out the size of people going on the giant dipper,
try to get those leg heights and widths in line.
But other than that.
I mean, here's the thing.
To this day, they might have changed their lap bars to, you know how some places now
do an individual, like they just slice them down the middle.
So it goes to, you know what I mean?
Oh, yeah.
So maybe they've done that.
But at the time when I rode in, you know, 2007 or whatever, it was one.
And I sat next to someone who was a good foot taller than me.
So I had a lot of space to fly away.
I need to find someone six three, possibly.
Hey, you could ride next to the guy that rode next to me.
OK.
Well, if you know, I'll hook you guys up.
Yeah.
Let me know.
His name was his name is Mike, too.
Two Mikes.
Well, we have we have two Mikes.
We have the name.
We may as well be best friends.
Wow.
And he knows a lot about Xavier Kuget, too.
Yeah.
Huge, huge.
They've had.
And now I'm on board.
I think we're all going to like this new Mike.
We'll we'll we'll hit him up soon.
But but but for now, Kelly, you survived podcast the ride.
Thank you so much for being here.
It's a delight to talk about this delightful place with you.
And let's exit through the Octopus's Garden
Esk gift shop.
Is there anything you would like to plug?
Sure. Check out my podcast, Teen Creeps.
It's the podcast where Lindsay K.
Tan and I talk.
Why Pulp Fiction?
Also check out Exile.
It's my narrative horror podcast.
It's out in its entirety.
You can find it wherever you find your podcasts.
Follow me on everything.
Social media, Twitch, all that.
Kelly Newgy, K, E, L, L, Y and UGEE.
Fantastic.
Cool, cool, cool.
And as for us, you can find us on lots of things also at podcast the ride.
We got merch available in our tea public store.
And for three bonus episodes every month, check out podcast the ride.
The second gate at Patreon dot com slash podcast the ride.
Well, you know, I don't know where to do it, guys.
But what I'd like to propose that we all try to go find some some hot chicken pies.
Might be more than 15 cents, but if we find a place, let's all meet.
I think Jason knows where the hot chicken pies are.
So if he if Jason could take a second out of from warning every boardwalk that their time is imminent.
He's so busy, though.
You know, climate change is very chaotic and, you know, just be careful.
I'm sure they're designing, you know, with with that in mind.
There is a pier.
There's not a ton on it anymore.
But, you know, be careful out there.
Yeah, be careful, peers.
Be careful, peers.
And good day.
Thanks for listening.
Bye bye.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts.com and subscribe to our shows
on Apple podcasts, Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.