Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast contains a retconned lamp, an anniversary treat for one,
the offensively boring and disgustingly unthemed tram roadway, and most exciting, discussion
of various protocols.
All this plus podcast the ride goes back to Disneyland.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, the podcast about theme parks hosted by boys who are so good
that not going to Disneyland for 14 months is their version of edging.
I'm, as an edgy joke, courtesy of me, the edgelord, Scott Gardner, Mike Carlson joins
me.
Oh my gosh, that makes me so uncomfortable thinking about that.
I kind of know what you're talking about.
Like, I kind of know.
I've heard it in a context, but is it ever, it's like what Sting does, right?
The singer Sting, the same thing?
That's related.
You probably put fancier terms on it.
That's a little different.
That's like pro level.
Well, Jason sure didn't hear what he was saying.
He was saying the difference.
Well, no, Tantric is like you go like hours and hours or like a day or something.
Yeah, but what?
But is it?
Yeah, I think I believe that edging could be just a matter of minutes.
Yeah, could be minutes.
Why don't you edge for a day?
I mean, I guess mechanically, yeah, it is kind of the same.
You're saying it is a more short term version of Tantric.
Yeah, the two of you, something.
You really swallowed your words.
You're dipping your little toesies into the spirit of Eros, you know, the spirit of the
erotic God.
What's the term for that?
What's the edging-esque term for dipping your toes into the spirit?
I think that I don't know.
That was just kind of off the cuff.
I'm looking at Eros here and I just want to determine is Eros cute?
Is the mischievous God of love?
There's got to be so many depictions of heroes.
It'd be hard to, you'd have to judge on an Eros by Eros basis.
Yeah, this image says Eros, or it's an article, I think, Eros, the naughty superhero of love.
And then that Kickstarter was funded to the tune of $200,000.
Wow, a new podcast, the right character, Eros.
The mythical God of love?
I think we're, I mean, he's public domain, right?
Eros?
So we could use him.
The naughty, ooh boy.
This can't be how anyone expected the episode to begin that is about our return to the golden
gates of-
I think we could go down the pantheon of Greek gods.
I think we could squeeze it in.
Determine which are naughty and which are just cheeky.
Yeah.
I want to know, this is about a moment that we have all waited for for so long, for so
many months, for over a year, moments, separate moments, because we did not all go together.
But separately, over the last few weeks, we have all made our return to the Disneyland
Resort.
Yes.
And we're very excited to share our findings.
It was fun.
It is kind of fun because we all went on different weeks, different levels of capacity potentially
and different operational things.
I had some very unique operational things the day I was there and I'm curious to see
if they're still carrying it onwards.
It's going to be a lot of operational talk today.
I love it.
We're going to go through how they're operating during this time.
Tape on the ground.
Galaxy's Edge specific bathroom markers.
Some days we're looking at the sky and today we're looking at the ground.
Yeah.
So here's the tease for my section of this episode.
First half of the day, I said, man, it's going to be a lot of operations talk.
It's going to be a lot of talk about protocols, how well thought out things are as far as
the pandemic is concerned.
And then the second half of the day happened.
And I'll say this, and this is not serious.
It's not as crazy as you might think.
The second half of the day, I visited the Disney doctor.
Oh no.
It's not as serious.
I don't want to hype it up to be something crazy, crazy, but I, for the first time in
my life, had to see the Disney doctor.
Let me just say that.
Oh my God.
Well, that's like, do we, do we ask more questions now or do we just put the pin in that?
Maybe with the pin in it.
The enticing tease of chapters to come.
That's very crazy.
And a first for every odd in any episode, let alone this one where health is what's
on all of our minds.
It's very embarrassing why I was at the Disney doctor.
I will say that.
Oh man.
Yeah.
Do something about Marriott.
Wait, what?
Like you, did you get your, you get your penis caught in a zipper?
Oh, I was thinking you meant I got something caught in my hair.
That could be that too.
Yes.
I should be more specific.
This episode is so dirty.
14 months of just infected your brains.
Twisted movies, like something about Mary, unrated edition.
I couldn't remember.
Yeah.
I was like, balls caught.
Yeah, that's right.
No, that did not happen.
That was not the problem.
That would, I would hype that up to the moon.
Oh, that would be an event.
I thought you said Marriott and I was like, something Marriott related?
That's like a, you know, there's like porn parodies of movies.
There would be like milder parodies of movies that you would enjoy.
There's something about Marriott.
Ah, yes.
A nice film about a hotel.
They lost my reservation, but then thankfully they failed it.
Hotel based parodies.
Yeah.
There is something about Marriott.
Free soaps, shampoo and conditioner to take home with me.
I'm trying to think of another, like a Sheridan.
Here, pitch on this real quick.
Sheridan hotels, uh, share, uh, share.
Hmm.
Share.
Something with den.
Yeah.
What's a movie with den in it?
I don't know.
I guess we'll come back to this.
Yeah.
Okay.
Or share a ton.
Uh, okay.
I can't think of anything with ton in either.
What a, oh boy.
Man, I really set us up for a failure here.
Yeah, that's all right.
I'm so sorry.
You know what?
You're still on the men.
You went yesterday, you know?
Oh yeah.
The home, the home woods sweetest thing.
There you go.
Yes.
Right?
Is this home?
Am I making that up?
Was homewood?
Did I just make up a hotel chain entirely?
Jason, is that a real hotel chain?
Homewood.
It is, right?
Uh, yeah.
Home.
Homewood sweets.
It sure is.
Oh great.
Okay.
And it's another Cameron.
Everything you need to feel at home no matter how long you stay.
Book today.
Mm-hmm.
And it's a, uh, it's a, uh, I'm trying to think it's another Cameron Diaz movie.
Uh, oh, that's right.
Oh yeah.
I didn't even remember what the sweetest thing was.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
That was a sort of, it was kind of a bomb.
Um, all right.
Well I'll come, I'll think about this.
I'll zone out during the episode and come up with a couple funny ones for the end.
Okay.
And homewood sweets has a mascot, Louis the Duck.
Oh.
That's another character discussion.
Yes.
Is Louis the Duck?
Well, you know, Greek deities, they're always turning into things.
Do you think Eros hides out on earth under the guise of Louis the Duck on occasion?
Is that naughty Eros?
Yeah.
Uh, Louis the Duck is cute.
Look at this.
This is Louis the Duck Saves the Day.
Whoa.
And he's got a rake.
They, they seem to put out, uh, books of this.
Louis the Duck Cleans the World.
It's Scrubbing the Whole Globe.
Mm-hmm.
Louis, thanks Louis.
Geez.
This, the homewood sweets duck mascot as a full toy line and book series.
Toy line.
It goes to Canada.
All right.
Louis the Duck is also coming.
Oh man, it won't happen to me later.
Yeah.
Um, but for now, Disneyland.
Disneyland.
Where is our destination?
We're back.
We went back.
And it's, it does feel, it, uh, I don't know.
Overall, everybody happy?
Had a great day.
Yeah, real good time.
I did.
And I will say that I, I, maybe you guys share this or I am a crazy person, obviously, for,
for some of this, uh, from what I'm about to say.
The first thing that I was like struck by is that, you know, since annual passes are
not back, um, is that, oh, okay.
My time is limited here.
I only have so much time to do so much.
And I'm, you know, spoiler alert, we'll be going, uh, going back for Avengers.
But after that, I don't know when I'm going back.
I don't know necessarily if it might be like by the time there's a new annual pass loyal
to whatever they decide to do.
So I felt like not scared.
Because again, that's, I'm not completely out of my mind, but I felt like that weird
vacation crunch that we always talk about when people say, oh, why do you like to go
down to that Disneyland so much?
Isn't that a big pain?
And you go, no, it's breezy.
It's a nice trip.
And you have a little drink in the middle of the day.
I felt this, this crush now also they don't have max pass, fast pass, single rider, all
of my tools.
I felt like Batman, you know, when they would strip Batman of his belt and his costume and
he just had his fist in his wits.
Just had his fist in his wits.
Like Rachel Gould takes all his clothes off and puts them in like a tent and fights him
with a sword.
That's how I felt too.
So I felt completely disoriented the first hour and also on top of it, of course, everything
is different because of COVID protocols.
So I was totally trying to get my bearings for how the day was going to go.
The wait times were like so high already.
110 minutes for guardians.
No chance of a fast pass.
I was like, I don't know what's going on here.
I don't know how to approach this.
I don't know what to do.
Huh.
See, I never, the week I went and I was the first of the three of us to go down, I didn't
see anything over 40 minutes.
45 minutes.
You were at a lower capacity day.
Yeah.
So, but we still felt the crunch to some extent.
But I knew I would be back for Avenger.
So I think I felt it a little less.
But we, I think I said this on another episode recently.
So I was like up at like 630 to get dressed and then start refreshing my phone like two
minutes before seven to get the rise of the resistance.
Sure.
Virtual queue.
And I got it.
I got it in like group 29.
By the time we drove down there and like we're exiting the parking garage, they're like,
okay, you have one hour to get here.
So it's like, okay, I guess we're, I guess we know what we're doing first.
So
Oh yeah.
It was, it was dictated for you.
Yes.
And it was also like a bit of a, you know, you walk from the parking garage through the
tram route.
You can do the bridge to downtown Disney by the old ESPN zone.
But I was like, well, let's see what the tram route is like.
Okay.
Walking the tram route is pretty boring.
There's not much.
Okay.
So yeah.
So, so it was Jason saying like, they're not doing any trams anymore.
So if you've never been to Disneyland, basically you park in now one of two giant parking structures.
Generally you just get in a tram and they take you right to the front to the Esplanade.
Yeah.
Cause security is all right before the tram now.
And by the time this comes out, trams could be back.
We don't know.
They keep changing stuff.
This is a slice in time.
This is a moment in time.
Yeah.
Certain protocols.
This will be an artifact that people will just study it for years to come to see exactly
where you could stand in the Disneyland resort.
So yeah.
So Jason, you alluded to this before.
I don't know.
Is it an episode that hasn't come out yet about how you found walking the tram route
so unpleasant?
You hate it.
Well, no, I didn't say I don't know if I hate it.
I was curious to see what it looked like, but it just felt like so long and it's just
like the undecorated backside of like downtown Disney.
And I think walking the length of downtown Disney, it's like Vegas.
It's like, yeah, your mind is kind of tricked because it's like there's a lot of lights
and sounds and everything.
And you can hear a little of the area music, but like not a ton.
And so Jamba Juice has a TV in it now.
So that gives you the energy you need to sprint the next half mile.
And a new name and look.
Oh, yeah.
They're just Jamba.
So by the time you've discussed all that, looked at the TV, thought like, is that 4K?
What kind of TV are we talking about?
You're almost at the gate.
But without any of those distractions.
That's right.
Yeah.
And then don't worry, I'll get to my downtown Disney experience because I patronized a number
of establishments on my way out.
Really interesting because we took the tram route back.
Did you walk downtown Disney Scott or did you walk tram?
Well, I had this whole other thing.
I did it in a different way because I not only was this my return to Disneyland, this
was my first.
This is my wife, Aaron and I's first overnight without our new son.
So, yeah, grandma was taking good care of him.
And this was so this was a little vacation for us.
And we decided to live it way up and spend the night at the Grand Californian.
Wow.
Which was so fantastic.
A ungodly expense, insanely expensive.
But we're like, but this is look, we've been cooped up.
This is a big deal.
Right.
We want everything to be as comfortable as possible.
And oh my God, if you stay there, you like now your security line is 10 people.
You're not hoofing it back and forth.
You're not doing the big walk for Mickey and friends.
Getting to do I stay there maybe once before.
And I don't remember if I did this then.
But that whole that you can just walk out of the private exit from California Adventure.
Oh my God.
Like in a day of mega walking and when we're trying to that was a lot of it, too, is just
like, can we not have all of this stress and worry and the day isn't just all about walking?
Because it's also a vacation for a one day vacation for us.
Right.
And Grand California.
Oh my God.
You are just right in the heart of it.
Yeah.
I want to stay there because when my family comes to visit, sometimes they'll want to
take like one night and stay down there.
And we were checking into Paradise Pier and somebody behind the desk went, Oh, excuse
me.
Um, would you, would you want to upgrade for free to the Grand Californian?
What?
And we were like, yeah, okay.
Yeah.
We're trying to save money by saying at the worst one.
It is if you don't know these hotels, if you aren't in the, in the LA area, yeah, it's
the, it's the lower of the three.
And still you would hear that and go, Oh, then it's probably affordable.
And then you will look at the price and go, no, yeah, yeah.
All these, they are gouging out all these hotels big time.
I am kicking myself that I didn't like years ago, like splurge more often because you would
use to be able to find the Grand Californian for like occasionally under 300 a night or
and the grand, the Disney land hotel, the same like, and, and if you want to splurge
like, okay, 300 night, but we don't do it that often.
And now it seems like, you know, all bets are off.
I don't know if they're especially gouging in this, like everybody's going to want to
come and you want to be in the heart of it, right?
I don't know if it's like even higher than usual.
Yeah, maybe.
But I would, but like, you know, once you get over that and you're there and like we
have a room and a room overlooking the beautiful kingdom of downtown Disney, we've got a little
upgrade.
I think supposed to be on a, with less of a view, but then we got a view of Napolini
and the new Sandal store.
I think we're right above Jamba with the new TV.
This is the heart of the action felt on top of the world.
So you could just like look out the window and see people walk by and go, look, the new
Jamba.
Like they were so many people were yelling the new branding of Jamba.
They were yelling how excited they were.
Yes, children and their parents weep, just drop to the ground like it's the wailing wall
and just breathe it all in.
Yeah, it's really beautiful.
Man, that's so great.
Yeah, yeah, it did rule.
So yeah, so we all we all had sort of different experiences then in terms of like the hassle.
I might take away admittedly was because we haven't really talked about how our little
days were.
Jason, we heard a little bit from you just before recording an episode and it was like,
that was Disneyland.
Oh my God, the walking.
Yeah, it was the first thing out of your mouth.
You're straight to.
So the walking, I didn't expect the group to get called that quickly.
Yeah, that was the pressure I felt.
That's OK.
So now, yes, now I'm seeing your stress.
I'm stressed.
You were upset about the walk, mainly because you felt a time crunch.
I felt a time crunch from there to Galaxy.
Because I kind of released I released, you know, gradually released pressure of like,
we've done a lot of this before, like, let you know, I was asking Jane what she wouldn't
do a lot because she wasn't sure when she would be back next because she had an annual
pay week, annual pay.
We'd renewed our annual passes like right at the end of like twenty nineteen, twenty
twenty.
And we're like, well, we'll come a bunch in twenty twenty.
You know, so that that was we didn't have reservations for anything.
So the only thing we had scheduled was that rise of the resistance ride.
And she had not done it before.
Yeah. So I wanted to make sure she got to have a good experience on that.
Yes. So that was the only thing.
And combined, I mean, I think we stopped to like use the bathrooms or have a drink of
water on Main Street.
But I looked at like the step counter, the mile mark in the phone after we went all the
way back, walked through the substantial queue for rise of the resistance, did the whole
ride, which involves walking when we got out of the queue at that point, it was a little
over three miles and less than an hour.
And that's a lot.
I'm not like I'm not like jumping out of my chair.
I know.
I feel like you.
But I've been up since like six a.m.
And I was like, this was not you're not going to get me on that.
Yeah, no, I don't think I don't.
We're not. We are not the same.
That is correct.
But like if if this were Orlando and this was a ride, an island of adventure,
you would not have a single problem.
You would have floated over to the well.
No, because with the luxury of staying on site at Universal Studios Resort Orlando,
you can take a boat or you can walk.
You don't have to drive the like one to one to the five to the.
Yes, that is true.
I kept saying while Lindsay and I were walking both ways, I go, Jason hated this walk.
I kept I kept bringing it up.
I go. I loved I loved walking through a lively downtown Disney that when the park
because park was at seven.
One of the best things you can do.
I think that you made a big mistake, though, because I'm really happy now
because I'm realizing I'm we're the only people who did this walk from the tram back.
And again, this will probably change this.
There'll probably be a tram in a couple of weeks.
But I think what happened, and this is totally a guess,
is that people were getting a little sleepy on that walk back to the tram.
And it wasn't like a lively downtown Disney because they were pumping music in
on the walk back that I I've recorded it because I was so intrigued by it.
This is like what someone would set up a folding table at downtown
Disney selling their own CDs and play hand flute.
This is like what they would be playing.
I mean, you might not be able to hear it that well, but that's got a that's a groove going
like, yeah, I was like, yeah, what is this?
And I was like, you know what I bet this is.
They were like, we got to find some high energy music
because people are like dragging at the end of the day because this boring street,
they set up a ton of benches throughout that tram pathway.
Yeah, like take a seat if it's a little long.
And now they're just like, please leave, please go.
And they put like some like generic up tempo disco music
to get people going like, yeah, yeah, that's going back to my car.
Modern fifth, the Beethoven.
Yeah. Don't don't don't don't don't.
Yes. So I feel like they were like, all right, we got to go into the archives
and find something that will make people like really excited to get back to their car.
And you think that this this this like
drum machine plus a violin is going to just get people's blood surging.
Here's well, I don't I would have picked a different song.
But my my rationale is why wouldn't they be playing like
done? Why would they be playing like a sleepy end of Disneyland song?
Yeah. So that I don't know why they picked that particular piece of music.
But that's my guess is they were like, we got to find some of the most up
tempo thing that wouldn't offend anyone.
OK, pull the opening promotional video for downtown Disney
and just rip the audio and let's blast that through the speakers.
It's 2001 all over again, folks.
Most generic turn of the century jazz you can find.
Well, if anyone out there walked to the tram at the end of the night
and they were playing a similar song, let us know.
I'm curious. Yeah.
Maybe they started with a sleepier Disney song and people were literally
falling over and falling asleep on the way back because it was such a arduous walk.
Can I talk about a little thing that, you know, this this this sort of
it's it's I guess like an end of the night thing as well.
But it was also the to commemorate the dawning of a new day.
There was this this event that happened before all this.
And I think we obviously have to talk about I'm sure we all watched it
with our loved ones, all the listeners watched it,
which was the the relighting of Sleeping Beauty Castle.
Did everybody see this online?
This was like, oh, yes, I did.
This is a seven minute live broadcast.
Is that right? Yeah, I did.
I did see this.
Now, I say that sarcastically and realize we did all see this.
But yeah, it was this odd sort of arbitrary little event
where you're watching it and go and then and it happens.
You know, that was it.
Yeah, I guess so.
It wasn't exactly like lighting the Rockefeller Center Christmas tree.
This is the they just turn the lights on. It's nice.
I'm happy that. Sure.
I think a lot of the I think the park has been unlit.
The one time I went down at night in December to a very spare
downtown Disney, it was really creepy seeing no lights on Ferris wheel,
no lights on spires.
So, you know, that it's going to be lit and stay lit is a good thing.
But then there is this odd I just want to play a second of this video.
Just the odd pomp and circumstance.
And I'm glad, you know, as an Eisner fan, I like that they make their officials,
their executives come out and do weird things like this.
But there's this.
All right. So this is the video reawakening of Sleeping Beauty
Castle at Disneyland. And this is what is he's the president of the resort.
Josh Demaro.
No, Ken Potrock is the president.
He's the wartime president.
He came in during very difficult time. Head of parks and resorts. Yes.
Oh, he's had it. It's not just Disneyland.
He's the head of all of it.
Yeah, he used to be head of Disneyland.
Now he's the head. He's Chapek's old job. All right. All right. Yeah.
And this is one of these. Yeah, people like, OK, I'm gathering people
despise Chapek.
People want to see him fall off a cliff.
They hate Chapek so much.
And yet, Josh Demaro, everyone is swooning over this man.
I don't know what happened.
Suddenly, everyone. This is Prince Charming.
We all, everyone united and loving.
Anyway, this is just this odd moment here.
This lamp is very special.
It's Walt Disney's lamp. There it is.
It is shown in his apartment on Main Street USA every day
as a symbol of the Disney spirit.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Josh Demaro, chairman of Disney Parks, experiences and products.
Thank you for joining us tonight for this special event.
Throughout the past year, Walt Disney's lamp has become a beacon of hope
and optimism that Disneyland will reopen.
Of course. Yeah, we all know.
So definitely. Yeah, we've all thought about it.
The miracle of Walt Disney's lamp.
There was no oil in it and yet it burned for 400 nights
while we waited for Disneyland to reopen.
Crazy nights.
Um, I just yeah, hang on.
Maybe if you work there, you know this, but I also think if you work there,
even if you like really like Disneyland and work there,
it's possible that you don't like.
And then at the end of the night, you go,
let me just go reflect at the lamp.
You know, that's Walt's lamp.
And if that fire can burn, then my fire of hope can burn
that all my friends will be back at home again.
I just do who's like this?
Well, this is I think they're leading on that apartment a lot,
because I asked Jane to send me some photos and she had taken a video.
And we rode the omnibus, like the double decker bus down Main Street.
And it was very cool.
And, you know, the characters all happened to be on the train station.
And so we were going right towards them.
And then as we passed the firehouse, the guy immediately
like stopped talking about Main Street is like,
and here is coming up on the firehouse, you know, on the second floor.
That's Walt Disney's apartment.
And like he had the Walt Disney apartment.
So they're leaning on that a little hard on the reopening.
Yeah. Huh.
I may be because that wall, like that that core and the love
and the personal touch, it makes you forget about that.
I guess we hate shape back a lot or that, you know, that they laid people off.
Like, well, forget. Look, look, look what it's about.
What it's about at the end of the day is this mostly nice man
and the lamp that he loved so dear.
He was he has to be buried with the lamp.
And but we said, no, the world needs the lamp.
And we went against his wishes, but for good reason.
The lamp is it is it magic?
Is it like the genies lamp?
Is it is it's just like that's that place where we used to crash, right?
When he was too tired to go home.
Yeah, there was a hot plate. You can make a grilled cheese.
I mean, I like I was very lucky I got to go up and see it.
And I'm like, oh, the lamp is not magic.
But if you make a grilled cheese sandwich in the hot plate
and eat the sandwich, that's a magic sandwich.
And you and your wish will come true.
Do not want you to make a sandwich with that.
I will say they don't want you to not touch anything.
I mean, no, maybe nobody ever will again.
Only like the most like the elite of Disney,
like like like at his height as Jack Sparrow, Johnny Depp got to make a sandwich
and his and his wish of a 10 million dollar raise for the next Pirates came true.
Do you think back in the day did Kurt Russell or like Suzanne Plushett
get a grilled cheese from that sandwich maker?
Oh, I think so. Yeah, I think they're regulars.
I think Dean Jones had his.
Jules for sure.
Keenan wins.
He came every day.
And that how many sandwiches did Annette get?
So many, so many magic sandwiches.
Well, Wally Boag, you know, he's pocketed, you know, on his way out
from doing a Golden Horseshoe show, he's like, well, he worked in the park.
I feel like there was a.
Oh, you think, OK, you got to really like be a profit generator.
Miley Cyrus. Yeah.
Had a lot of magic sandwich. Right. Yeah.
I will. You know what?
I think what you're getting at, if correct me if I'm wrong,
is that there's this bizarre sort of maybe retconning of this specific
lamp in the Walt Disney legend where you're like, I don't know,
do you really like the lamp or like is this even in the lamp?
He was literally like a like a tiny room he would stay at.
And it wasn't like, I don't like I think this is a little strange.
But you know what? Let's just add some more retcon to the Walt's legend.
Let's make up more fake stuff that's like so special, you know, to Walt.
No, absolutely.
Yeah. Did you know like
the concrete out front was his favorite concrete that he liked?
The wishing stone. Yeah.
Yeah. He would wish on this specific concrete that he liked.
And they would pour it. And you know that it was really special.
If you put your hands on it, you sort of can feel his presence.
Yeah. That's what's nice.
He left. He left his own fingernails.
Yeah. In the concrete.
His actual fingernails. Not his impressions.
No, his yeah, like like he cut the tips.
And then one full his full thumbnail he pulled off and put into the.
Oh, jeez. Yeah.
But he needed his essence to be in there.
Yeah. He needed. Oh, OK. He was also a sick guy.
Yeah. You can.
If you listen, if you put your ear up to it, you can hear him wailing,
you know, wailing like people don't want to work.
They make more money staying home right now.
We need to do something.
Yeah. Yeah. So that was that's all real.
There's a wall.
There's one of his mustache hairs laid
when they break ground on every new attraction.
And that's everywhere. That's all over the world.
That's Hong Kong, Shanghai. Right. Right.
That's the when they inaugurate the ships,
they like bash the bottle of champagne, but also rub it with one of the
the whiskers that's left.
He left. He had like he died with like two hundred.
And they have to be really careful about spacing those out.
That's why they're slow, slow with attraction sometimes.
OK, we're running out.
We're running out. Clone.
It wouldn't be the same.
Did you know that the Navi in the tank on in right
of flight of passage, all that water is wild saliva.
He would collect his saliva over the years and they needed it
for a special attraction later.
He knew he feel that they would have a special attraction.
Now we're starting to paint kind of a Howard Hughes and Vegas sort of image.
No thumbnails.
Saliva, he saved his hair.
It was all saved.
He cataloged it because he knew it would be important.
He knew he was important.
Yeah, and he has a big vault of his piss somewhere as well.
He saved that too.
The vault has a bunch of wall.
It's a little of it into the into the most each day.
Just a little magic.
Walt's magic piss makes our moat what it is.
His spirit is alive,
bubbling up under each Disney duck.
I'd love to see Josh tomorrow read that.
I'd like you to read anything you put on.
You can get a nice figure and wears a suit well, you know,
well-coiffed hair, you know, very stylish.
I'll listen to anything.
This is all fine.
Everybody having everybody thinking this guy can get it.
That's great. Enjoy it, everyone.
He is a handsome man. I just don't know when it happened.
This was my what I was zero to 60.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. All of a sudden, one day everybody is just freaking
like, who's the guy from the Bridgerton?
Is that the right name of the show?
Yes. Yes.
Yes, Josh tomorrow within theme park.
And then is that guy? Yeah.
Well, I mean, you know, sometimes if you any pop star, you know,
do you really remember it building didn't just sort of feel like it appeared
any of the big crazes? That's true.
Yeah, yeah, no, there was there was no Bieber and then there was Bieber.
Yeah. So like Josh tomorrow is a lot like Bieber.
If you really think about it.
Anyway, I did not see him yesterday when I went.
Well, OK, so stuff we are here.
Well, there's a question we know.
We know Jason's first ride back.
It was kind of enforced.
Did you choose your first ride back?
What did it end up being?
How do you after all this time?
What's the first what's the return?
Well, we did.
We ate something first and went to Flo's
and we ate something and then we went on in credit coaster. Nice.
That's and yeah, because we had to start because they make you start in one park
and we had California Venture.
Then you can hop after one.
And we started California Venture, did in credit coaster
because the weight was a little less.
And then that's when I kind of had a sigh of relief
because the weight was like 30 or 40 minutes on the app.
But it really took us like 15 minutes in the line.
And you know what?
Maybe all of these are going to be easier than I thought.
And then we did made way mania again.
15 minutes tops. Yeah.
And I go, OK, because I really was looking at that app and going
110 minutes for guardians, like 60 minutes for like I was like,
we're going to get three things done today.
Yeah, yeah.
And I don't ever want to tell people like that's a guarantee.
But like touring plans does a great job of tracking this stuff.
And oftentimes their experience of actually getting through the line
is a hair shorter than the. Yeah.
And they do supposedly they do this psychologically to make you feel like good.
Because if somebody tells you something's going to be 50 minutes
and it takes 40 minutes, you go, why?
What a little trick it is.
But this felt really like inflated.
This felt like double the time when you would look at the app.
So because like Guardian said like 60, 70 minutes.
And I swear we 20 minutes and we were on.
So it was way inflated.
Should we say the time?
I guess I don't I don't remember where you were, Jason, and the because.
And this is also a thing if you don't know.
And if you're in Florida, where everything's just been like, hey,
whoever all the time always anybody into the park.
California has been really spaced out in terms of theme park capacity.
And places are moving up tiers very slowly.
So I ended up being there on the last day that it could only be 25 percent.
Right. It changed in the morning.
We had breakfast at the La Brea bakery right next to the ticket booths.
And it was flooding with people getting tickets for that day
because they just immediately, you know, turn the faucet back on.
So that mean and that went from 25 to 35 percent, which is when you.
So you went with a 35 percent. Yes, I was there.
Thirty five percent.
So it was a little it was still, of course, not very crowded
when you consider the days we've been there before. For sure.
We know like a labor day or.
Yeah. The 24 hour Disney day we were there when I was like,
oh, we're going to get like trampled to death by people. Yeah.
I can almost can't imagine it being like like now that you've done it with less
people, it's going to be hard to go back.
Yeah. It's a first class situation when you have the leg room.
Yeah. How do you go back to coach?
Yeah. It's kind of how all this this felt.
Jason, how much was do you think was it 25 yet or was it down to the very slim?
Fifteen percent? Well, I went I think I went May 13th.
So that was less than two weeks.
It had been reopened. So I believe it was at 25 percent.
You texted me a day or two before and was like, you might get
the tail end or we might both get the tail end of 25 percent. Right. Right.
Which is pretty good. You feel it.
You definitely feel it.
There is it's not all day.
It's not like everything feels super spaced out, but there's certain
there were certain moments.
We went to Adventureland pretty quick and you really feel it there.
Because if you know Disneyland, boy, is it jammed over there. Yeah.
I'm trying to think of other Tomorrowland, too, because that middle
that Tomorrowland zone next between Star Tours and Buzz Lightyear
Super anything that's always stroller central. Right.
A lot less stroller central and just less people.
Yeah. Some of the more irritating congested areas of the park
were definitely a lot chiller.
I have to say the four o'clock crunch in New Orleans Square, though,
that was where I called it.
That's where I tapped out.
I was like, let's go to California Adventure and have a drink
because it was just it is.
It's so nice when it works.
It's so intimate and well designed.
But it was made in the it was designed in the early to mid 60s.
And the park has a lot more people go into it now.
So if you factor in that and you factor in
a lot of only entrance doors and only exit doors
and outdoor rope queues, it got pretty gnarly over there.
Yeah. Yeah.
Well, if I could say my first attraction,
I didn't really have a plan until I got in.
And then it just felt like, you know, why don't we do it sort of chronologically?
Let's like do the like you never end up doing that when you're crisscrossing
around with Max Pass and Fast Pass.
Let's just like go left as Walt introduced the lands on the show.
So go and left into Adventureland and then straight to the Indiana Jones
Adventure, pretty like epic first one back. Yeah.
And the ride's great, obviously really enjoyed it.
And you got a weird plexiglass and there's less space in the car.
And that's all good.
I brought I bring it all up partially to say this is one of the more unusual
line setups, because that's a question.
If you haven't gotten to go yet or you're not on the West Coast,
they are keeping it outdoor lines as much as they can.
There's certain spaces where you sort of can't do that,
but limiting your in your indoor time.
And Indiana Jones is very interesting because the Jungle Cruise is closed
currently. So a lot of the queue was the second floor
of what is usually the Jungle Cruise.
Oh, it's really weird to be waiting in a line clearly for a different attraction.
And then like, I know this is the Jungle Cruise line,
and yet it's going to take me into Indiana. Right.
Yeah, I will say we talked about this on Patreon.
Universally, you're like, OK, they have like markers six feet apart in line.
That being said, you're literally standing right next to a person
because they're in the line over.
So what is it? What's the point of this?
You still need distance there. Right.
And look, I don't know. I'm not a doctor here.
Yes, but I saw I see what you said. That doesn't make any sense.
I will say Disney put a lot more work into it than Universal did.
But can't you say this most of the time?
Well, of course.
Well, yeah, at least they're like in the line.
You're like, well, there's markers and the markers aren't next to each other.
When there's a line. Yeah.
I go, oh, yeah, this was like they took another couple minutes
when walking through and went, yeah, we should probably put these people
farther away from each other.
Did you have a virtual queue, too?
I did end up doing.
Yeah, that's another thing.
There's only two rides that you can get in a sort of Max Pass ish,
like like digitally reserve your spot in the rise of the resistance
and Indiana Jones, I assume, because that's one of the first
when this was all starting the whole pandemic.
I was like, that's like the most impossible one,
because that's a mega line all indoors.
How is that going to work?
So I guess supplementing it with the digital is part of it.
But no, we just walked in. You walked it.
OK. Yeah.
Yeah, we did the virtual queue for that, but just kind of on a lark.
Like I think we were we stopped after.
I don't know. We did rise.
And then we had a veggie Ronto wrap and blue milk
because Jane had not tried either of those and they were very good.
Blue milk.
I don't know if you can see this right now,
but they give you a little lead for it, right?
They're like a little paper lead to cover it.
Well, it looks like a coffee ground thing, but the opposite.
Yeah, it looks like a little top of your drink.
You got the bottom of like a cupcake, a little cupcake wrapper
or something flipped around.
Yeah. And I think it's again kind of like,
you know, psychological kind of COVID comforting.
It's a little bit, though.
Yeah, it was very pleasant.
And then at some point we did like three of the fantasy land rides.
We did Pinocchio, Toad and Alice and Wonderland.
And then we got popcorn and a soda and sat on the old boat dock
slash smoking section, you know, that little weird part by the water and be
in fantasy land, in fantasy land.
Yeah. Kind of where the it was the motorboat cruise.
Wait, yes. A long time ago.
Yeah. Not to Snow White.
Did you say Snow White?
No, I can do it.
And TFO was tearing it down the day I was there.
Brick by brick.
Thank God, because we all collectively as the left, certainly
we all discussed at the last meeting this Snow White ride and the kiss
will not stand. No, there's no way.
Face character was reading from the Communist Manifesto by Karl Marx,
which you can now buy at every Disneyland gift shop.
And we're all comforted for that fact.
And as soon as they started selling it, the light in Walter Perman went out.
It was just flickered. Yeah, flickered.
If you can, if a little flame can be considered angry,
I would call it that.
Oh, is Walt Walt is the flame. Hey,
do I look over to the happy place?
I live in the lamp forever.
I'm fire now.
I'll transform into another state and got Mickey's voice.
And Walt Disney and Mickey's voice and fly on the flame now.
We should explain this case.
The context is missing later that the,
you know, there's there's all of it because all right,
they're changing the jungle crews.
And some of that is you put in the umbrella of cultural sensitivity
or just updating things.
And obviously Splash Mountain is changing at some point, someday. Not yet.
If you have that question, is Splash Mountain running? Yes.
Is it not? Is it any less song in the South? No, they've not had to.
That whole thing was just like in their foot in the door.
It's going to be Princess the Frog someday.
Now when it opens, but don't worry about it. It's happening. It will happen.
Don't worry. Don't protest.
So there's all these things.
And then all these charlatans are writing stupid articles about Disney
getting to PC or whatever.
And then so there's this like this utterly fake
Fox News story about because they just redid the Snow White
ride and added a new ending.
And it involves the prince kissing Snow White to awaken Snow White.
And Fox News has framed this as well.
The left found a new target for their cancel culture.
Snow White and the lack of consent in the kids based on one article,
one blog, one one person who clearly has a quota
covers popular culture and likely has a number of articles
they have to post a week.
And I someone someone asked me like, did you see it?
I'm like, no, you don't have to. It's don't worry about it.
Like, and I'm sure like, yeah, this is important discussion to have with children.
Yes, but like not.
You mean about consent. Yeah, about consent.
But yes, absolutely about consent.
But like in the context of like a movie from before World War
Two, you're trying to apply twenty twenty one thinking.
It's a cartoon. Yes, it's a good.
It's a cartoon with magic in play.
And then I yeah, I don't I don't know.
And Apple is magical.
Yeah, I guess the apples are just poison.
The apple's not the apple's poison.
Poison an apple today.
That's as much as you could back then.
Yeah. But but and I'm sure Disney's like the Imagineers thinking was just like,
well, it's been a few decades of people saying it doesn't end like the movie does.
And they're like, well, let's try to nip this in the bud.
And and it created a whole new can of worms.
Well, but it was again, it's like I don't know that people were.
Yeah. Outside of like an article, I'm not sure.
Because also Tom Martins wrote an article about the Snow White Ride
I don't know if you read it yet.
Did it come out today or yesterday?
And today? Yeah, I saw he posted.
Yeah. It also talks about how every how much thought
everyone put in Imagineers put into like making sure Snow White
had like ownership over her story and wasn't about with the prince.
And they put all this thought into it. Agency and yes, agency.
That's actually the word I want to say.
And like at the end, they wanted to make sure that like she's hanging out
with her friends and the prince is in the distance.
But it's not about the whole thing.
Yeah, yeah. Now she lives with this man who bellows at her in a well once.
Right. That's why. Yeah.
So I think like, you know, they put some thoughtfulness into it
and trying to make sure that, you know, that but yes, you're to your point.
Yes. Like talk to your children about actual like consent
and what that means in the real world. That's important.
But also Fox News is blowing this disconnect to life lessons from popular
culture the most you can because they will be getting it constantly from left
to right. They will just be getting pop culture shoved down their throats,
like from every angle, you know.
No, just a weird fake controversy.
It's just one of those I have to keep clarifying to.
It's like a war on Christmas, maybe.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah.
That's the whole thing now is just taking like we found we found one.
If we like we found a needle in a haystack here, this sounds like a radical lift.
They're all mad about something stupid. Here you go.
Let's make this all we are talking about for four hours. Yeah.
Yeah. But it's a self-fulfilling prophecy because like, well,
this newspaper needs to have new content and this 24 hour TV
network needs things to go like absolutely apoplectic about.
And it's just they're just shaking hands.
It's just the two Spider-Man pointing at each other.
Did Gutfeld address this?
Oh, man. I don't know that we know.
I mean, yeah, I mean, all the good felt bits go viral.
And that's I just have a hard time keeping up with them because they.
Yeah, right. They are all the sewer,
you know, on the homepage all the time.
Sure. Yeah. So, you know, we'll go back and have have a good laugh.
You know, who else will have a good laugh is him who laughs at his own jokes.
Well, no one else is going to do it.
Who else is going to laugh at the people in the room with him?
These are like his employees, like the people who work there,
like and they're probably told not just laugh a little to support.
Yeah, it's like, you know, we do watch the old Tom Snyder show
and he'd have like one producer chuckle at him here and there.
And then that's it.
But that's a show that's like barely intended to be comedic.
That's true. Like the idea is that is to laugh and his own people won't do it.
Tom Snyder was not the comedian of Gut, meaning Gutfeld is.
That's for sure.
And now cowardly to go for it.
And now we've lost the children with Snyder.
Tom Snyder talk.
Yeah, I think that we have the good felt.
Yeah, yeah. We've got about kids love Gutfeld.
So anyways, yes, this brings us to a point which is,
yeah, oh, my God, they redid the Snow White ride.
There's some new rooms and some new effects.
They refreshed it.
Looked at that wait time for five minutes.
I don't look. I'd rather kind of go on the e-tickets in California Adventure.
Sorry. Sorry, podcast audience.
I can watch a video. I did not do it.
Jason did not do it. Mike, did you do it?
It is awesome. Oh, good.
It's so good.
I'll go back around.
It was just the clock was ticking.
It was only like exactly.
I don't see any chips.
It was that pressure.
I had we had no like I was like, oh, yeah, let's take a look at what they did.
And we were like, wow, look what they did in here.
They crammed so much good stuff in there.
And they didn't like it still because so it used to be the it was not
Snow White Scary Adventure, right?
That was the whole time losing my mind.
Yeah, Snow White Scary Adventure.
And like they were going to like the word was, oh, they're going to take
the scariness out of it.
And people were like, well, it's kind of sounds like that sucks.
Like it's fun to have a little scary.
Left wants to take the scariness and it's no one.
Hannity did 20 minutes on the scariness of the Snow White going away.
But you put so we're so well, we'll see what it is.
They just have like in the nooks and crannies of it.
And maybe we'll do a full.
There seems like there's enough to do like an episode,
at least a second gate on it, like all these little effects, new smells.
There's so that's what you don't get from videos.
I didn't know that.
Yeah, you're not going to get the smells.
And I'll do like there's one less witch.
There's two of the witch, like there's three.
No, there's actually four.
So I should say there's like two.
Yeah, there's like two less witch figures.
And they cram in a full like ending sequence.
So you have a real like sense of it finishing like a story wrapping up
because it used to be the dwarves were on the hill.
The witch was, you know, had the pride bar for the big boulder.
And then she falls to her death.
And then you're outside again.
And you're like, huh?
Yeah. And then like there was a book there, I think.
It tells you that it ended happily.
Right. It did.
And it's like it's confusing, like it's confusing in the way like Little Mermaid
is confusing still where it's like Ursula's just gone in their hat.
Now that that has the ending, but doesn't have what came between
the opposite in the margins.
Yeah, it's the opposite thing.
Like you see a little Ursula in the sea and you go, well, like you squint,
you go, oh, I guess she got killed.
So she died.
But this one, they give like they push the scene forward in the ride,
that final scene forward.
They do a different thing with it.
And then there's the prince kiss moment.
It happens.
It's a full new like forest you're in.
The thing illuminates and there's like a little magical moment.
Then there's another scene with Snow White hanging out with the dwarves.
And we got out and we were like, that was great.
Oh, that's nice.
Good. Like that like rockets that ride now to me up.
And like that's in the conversation for maybe one of like the best dark
ride in Fantasyland.
Great. Wow. Wow.
That's that's awesome to hear.
I yeah, it's funny how I feel like
you know, the imagineers would cop to that that was not ideal, that it doesn't
like there wasn't enough room really to do a happy ending.
We just didn't have the space to get one more scene in there to make it end up
and nicely.
And then I watched a side by side of what it is now after the redo and what it was
before. I'm like, they didn't have the room.
It's just like room after room of scary trees, weird,
like spindly alligators slowly opening their mouths like they're looking back.
I think you're going to cut a couple of cut some swamp.
I think when Claude Coates was putting together, he was just like,
kids hate these trees.
I'm going to put as many scary trees as I can.
But it's still like if I was a kid, I would still be scared in the couple
scenes that still have the witch, like the witch still turns around from the mirror
and stuff. And yeah, that's an iconic part.
They didn't change. Yeah.
And they were spoiler.
She doesn't she doesn't come out on the boat anymore.
That's been replaced by an image of the mirror and whatever.
So I don't know. I love when Snow White, when there's Snow White,
do you see her eating the apple? What is it?
And then and then the entire image shatters into glass.
That's what it is. Yes. Yes.
That's so hard.
That's like that's like from a 80s music video.
It's like it's like it gets like abstract.
It's very silly. And I like it.
Yeah. That's where the boat was.
That's what it used to be.
Now I'm hyping it up.
Many people will not feel like it was so good.
But this Todd Barton's wrote an article to I feel like he felt similar
to me, where it was like, whoa, hey, wow.
And then about everybody putting so much thought into it.
I was like, oh, yeah, it feels like they really.
Oh, that's good.
Because I saw detractors complaining that like, oh, they clearly just copied
some of the stuff from the seven dwarfs mine train in Florida.
But like, I don't know. Yeah. I'll give it a chance.
I just the clock was there was only open till 7 p.m.
the day I was there.
And we were trying to like, you know, I just crisscrossed the park.
I thought it was so important because we were at the park.
I guess I had to do it. OK, well, I guess you can.
I guess we just didn't feel the I guess.
I guess you don't want to realistic pressure.
Look, I spent half a Sunday
refreshing that reservation website to try and get a day
where I could start in Disneyland because we mostly wanted to do Disneyland.
When you say spent half a Sunday, do you mean you were eating a Sunday while checking?
I mean, I had some snacks in there to keep my blood sugar up for sure.
It turned out to be useless because they keep just if you're looking for a reservation,
just give it a day or so.
They might just unleash a bunch because they're unleashing a bunch anyway.
Yes. I mean, things are changing.
We may have we may actually when we go to Avengers, we are.
Spoiler, we're going together on a day.
We may have a we may have a guest with us also.
Somebody wants to go.
So I but I have to check for this person
because there's not reservations available.
Oh, so you would have to one would have to open up.
Yeah. And checking, I didn't get to do a lot of my checking,
but I did get to there was one thing I got to check for Carthy
for the Carthy walk up list.
Oh, that was that involved a list.
There's digital walk up lists at some restaurants.
That's the other thing.
Reservations are kind of hard to find for in-park food right now
because restaurant occupancy is limited and some restaurants just aren't open yet.
But stuff's reopening every week.
It seems sit down.
Stuff is not.
So you really got to be on those mobile orders.
One thing I'm seeing a lot of on Twitter is people like
big wait for the mobile appeal are being so bitchy about that.
Like I thought it was all maybe it's worse now.
I thought every mobile experience I had was fine.
Some of it took a sec.
But like so it takes a sec.
What do you do? Some of these.
You're at Disneyland again.
Yeah. Shut up. Flows.
I wanted to mobile order.
Flows was an hour after the time.
Well, it would have taken an hour.
And I was like, what is this?
Oh, yeah.
But if it tells you that, you know, like then you're you know what you're in.
We waited in line. Oh, OK.
Oh, OK. I see. Sure.
Gotcha. It was fine, obviously.
But it is funny.
I did not post about it.
Yeah. Yeah.
I'm self aware.
And you know, you know, the kinds of accounts that are posted,
the the Disney daddy's esc accounts that are
I turn into a Disney daddy a few times in the trip.
And then I revert back and go, no, no, no.
You're a reasonable man.
You're having a good
you know, it's kind of a Disney daddy moment for me.
I did not get a lot of sleep the night before.
I was kind of going off of not a lot of sleep a couple days.
Yeah. To this, which just meant and and then racing.
It was a lot of hassle and like getting the grandmas to take care of the baby.
Everybody good. Just like so involved me having to like I had to backtrack
on the freeway and give a key that I'd forgotten to like.
It set me back 30 minutes and we went down to just so much weird stress.
All this resulted in me.
Oh, my God, we're on the haunted mansion for the first time in a long time.
Also, we're sitting and it's dark in here and I slept through half of the
haunted mansion. Wow.
There is this. You are a dad now.
Congratulations. Yeah.
You know, are there cool ghosts? Yes.
Is it dark? Even more? Yes.
And I. Yeah.
Similar in Florida.
I took a nap on the Mexico boat ride one of the times that I went.
And it was so sweet.
It was such a good.
Maybe a ride nap is a little secret.
Maybe the baby ride naps are what you got to start.
You were out Sheridan Sheridan Sheridan.
I guess. Yeah.
Wow. That's Jason's lane.
You know, you become the teacher.
I've definitely fallen asleep on rides before, for sure.
Had you? Yeah.
Yeah, I think so.
Which ride do you think?
I know something in Florida.
You know, those like long, long Orlando days, especially when I was young,
like as a kid, like, yeah, I would zonk.
Maybe when I was a little kid, I would fall asleep.
But I've said this before, I never I've never fallen asleep in school or anything
ever. Like, I can't.
I'm always on guard.
Oh, no, I was just too.
Yeah. Too neurotic in school. Yeah.
Yeah. The games, the character games are now switch are switching here, you know,
because like sometimes I like I like, you know, sweets or something.
And that really steps on the game that Jason is the only one who likes sweets.
And now Scott's saying he likes to sleep on rides and is sleepy.
And that's Jason's territory.
So we're stepping on your like well-defined podcast character games.
Well, I you know, it makes me feel any better.
When I was talking to my dad on the phone the other day, he did.
I forget how he got to this point, but he did say the phrase like unprompted.
Well, don't forget your grandfather was a candy man.
And
as my grandfather used to run the the like third shift, like night shift lines
at the Whitman's Factory in Philadelphia and a candy man.
Yeah. Hershey.
I believe he said at some point Hershey tried to poach him.
What? Yeah.
And I shared a little that I've never heard.
No, I forget.
I forget it. But like every every other year or so, an aunt will like it's like
everyone got Whitman samplers this year.
Wow.
I am a candy man.
My father before me was a candy man.
My father before him was a candy man.
This is my son, Jay.
This is my grandson, Jay.
I'm sure.
That's a good Halloween costume for you two.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
And his son, Paul Dano.
And you just shave and slick.
Yeah, absolutely.
Yes. Get some dip ity do and slick the hair back.
Wow. Explain to my girlfriend, hey, you know, I said I don't really like Halloween.
I don't want to do a couple's costume.
I have you with Mike.
Thing is, I know.
Yeah, I know you're not.
I don't like it.
Yeah.
If you guys go to a party and you get lost and Mike, you could say, I remember I did
my hair.
I remember.
Mike, you could say I'm a man and my boy, my candy child, my candy boy.
Wow.
That is crazy.
I'm always blown away when there's a piece of Sheridan family history like that that
I have not heard because I've heard a lot of it at this point.
Yeah.
Father was a candy man.
What a candy man.
That's so good.
Geez.
Yeah.
Wow.
I think other things.
Well, you know, speaking of people have like shifting, you know, personas and tropes.
Again, we just covered this a little bit on the universal episode on the Patreon, but
there was the question of, am I going to reset and not be into thrills whatsoever or am I
going to go back full tilt?
And I'll tell you, there was a five minute wait, five minute wait for Splash Mountain,
which did not last all day.
You know what?
Why not?
Let's go back in.
It was the first time that I did not close my eyes on the drop.
Wow.
I stared down.
You just, you go up there and you're thinking, man, it's been, it's been 14 months.
Enjoy it.
Stare.
And I boy watching those steam jets come at me.
I mean, I still look terrified in the picture.
You never saw it before with your own eyes on a lift drop hill.
When we were at knots, did you keep your eyes open on the timber mountain?
Yeah.
No.
No, I'm keeping my eyes open on the children's rides now.
No, but it is a big deal for me.
And I, yeah, this was the first time.
And I always think that I'm going to do it or I think that I did it.
And then the photo proves that I did not.
It's like the dinosaur thing with me where I thought I was staring at the dinosaur and
apparently I was cowering in fear.
Yeah.
So yeah, I still look super scared in the photo, but man, I enjoyed it.
I just like locked eyes with the bottom, yelled happily was and like, I think I was really
enjoying especially that you get that's the one where you get a log into yourself.
How awesome.
I think it added to the pressure with me that I don't want to be like, I'm like nervous
and talking to Aaron like, I don't know, maybe I don't know if I can handle the drop and
there's other people around and probably kids now to have the thing to yourself.
You'd really do just feel the relaxing boat ride nature of it.
I felt that on Jurassic World too.
You're just people around and suddenly it's like you're taking a pontoon around that just
happens to have a drop at the end.
Because like if there was a kid on the log, you would have been like, this isn't going
to be so bad.
Don't worry about it.
It's going to be fine.
I'm going to be fine.
You're going to be fine.
No problem.
We will be fine.
So don't you're freaking me out, kid.
Yeah, I man, so great.
And I'm now like braver in credit coaster.
I was now just part of Lexica.
I just love them credit coaster now.
I can't even remember not loving it.
So that one's not even a big deal at this point.
But boy, did I eat that one up and the guardians.
I closed out the night with wow, which is only my second time.
The bravest.
I did it.
Now again, is alcohol involved?
This is the recurring thing it does.
It's like flying.
It just needs.
I need it to get rid of the jitters.
But boy, did I love you.
And you know what?
Now, after that second one, I think there was like the fear of the new the first time
I did it.
And then this one, there's just been so long.
I was so ready for it.
And now I like didn't freak me out at all.
I think it is now just in the lineup.
I think I will always do mission break at this point.
So I'm so happy.
Hey, that's great.
Yeah, it's it's so that was like I asked Lindsay, what's the one thing we have to do?
She goes like guardians.
I saw somebody post that the ride was bad or unpopular.
I think it's bullshit.
The guardians so good.
I just a tweet saying that like the outside was ugly or something like that.
Yeah, I don't.
Everyone came around to it.
Yeah.
Anyway, I don't.
Regardless of whether you like the movies or not, the ride itself is fun and good.
Yeah.
I don't know what.
And again, so weird.
Like we're going to take this.
We're just going to jam some IP in there instead of the original story of the Twilight Zone.
Like what was I?
The logic just isn't there.
And yeah, the thing is super fun.
I yeah, I don't know.
I just dig it.
And like, well, we were saying on the second gate how I was like sprinting to Silver Bullet.
Now I did at knots.
I have a more advanced coaster than I've done.
Now I'm just sort of a junkie.
And maybe it's an end of the night thing.
Like I only got a little bit of time.
Yeah, maybe I do.
Like the longer I wait, the more I think about it, I'll back off.
So I just got to like run to that thing.
Yeah.
Or I'll change my mind.
And it's that is, as I was saying, a hell of a ride to end the day and then to just
walk to your hotel room on a path with essentially no one.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
Such a relaxing, great end of the day.
See, we really did switch because I went over to California Adventure and we got a beer
and a margarita and sat in like the Canary Row, Fisherman's Worth area, enjoyed the sunset
and was like, OK, let's go back to Disneyland.
And then we walked back over to the other park because we like, all right, we have one
hour left.
What's the thing to do?
And we both agreed on Haunted Mansion.
OK.
And that was the right call because we were in line for Haunted Mansion.
And it was like a magical ending to the day.
We started talking to the person behind us.
She had a Haunted Mansion dress on.
It was her birthday.
She had the button.
And we were talking about like, oh, I saw some people there are letting some people
in through the like mausoleum, like the door there.
She's like, oh, yeah, have you done it?
I was like, no, I've never been over there.
I got a picture there, but I've never gone through that back entrance.
She's like, I've done it.
It's really cool.
And she and we get to the front of the house.
We get to the front door and they stop us and they went, are you guys OK with stairs?
We're like, yeah.
And they're like, all right, come on.
And they took us in the back door of the Haunted Mansion.
If you don't do this thing where they intercepted you and said, do you want to do it?
How do you get this see this other end?
That's a good question.
You just have to you just ask someone somewhere.
I think what's happening is they're just trying to keep occupancy down in the elevators, but
they can get lots of people downstairs onto the ride.
So they were running the stretching room, but then they're also taking people in the
back.
So there's a door, if you see like by the graveyard mausoleum crypt area, whatever you
want to call it.
They took us in that door.
First off, everyone was clearly like, OK, yeah, let's we want to go home.
Let's get these people in.
It was one of the steepest set of stairs I've ever seen in my life.
There are miniature versions of the stretching portrait just kind of hung along the walls.
And then you can see the lightning effects from the other side of the wall.
And then they open a door and you're in the middle of the portrait gallery walkway like
Q. Whoa.
And that was why I was like, oh, that's OK.
Because there's still stuff where I'm like, oh, that connects to that.
And then and then and then we got to see like they added those new like dressing room kind
of screens in the queue line.
And there's they added one more portrait back.
I think that had been in storage and it was great.
It was running great.
And pretty much everything I went on, I think, was running great that day.
Yeah, we got to do that same walk.
We got asked the same question, the mysterious question.
Like, are you OK with stairs?
Really cool.
I will say that the thing, the issue that was I was dealing with, I was dealing with
it during this Haunted Mansion trip, this ride.
So my memory is a bit impaired because of what I was dealing with.
Well, do we need to?
So I think we have to say, yeah, OK.
So just a little bit of context before this, just maybe I don't even need to say it, but
I was checking.
I got reservations to Carthay.
We were in Carthay.
We had some food.
This is just just for just because it's funny.
And this is the first time we've actually dined inside since being vaccinated.
That was the first.
Yeah.
Not to step on yours, but yeah, I didn't realize we would get indoors.
That's why we didn't want to.
No, we didn't want it.
We wanted to be outside, but they like seated us there and we're like, I guess we're vaccinated.
That's yeah, that's a hell of a first place to do it.
Yeah, absolutely.
Yeah.
So let it happen.
Oh, my God.
Like that was where I first texted you guys.
Like, here's the thing to show.
Having the Manhattan inside.
Yes.
Holy shit.
And that's so great.
Lindsay had her didn't.
Jill Jill had the dog distracted me, I swear.
A dill gin and tonic.
And I had my Carthay Manhattan like two older folks.
Your mother likes the dill gin and tonic.
We like California Adventure.
It's a slower park.
More to our speed.
You know your mother.
She likes the dill gin and tonic.
Yeah, made it well to do.
Mm hmm.
Yes.
So we got that.
We had we had some meatballs as well.
All the prices are three dollars more expensive.
Yeah, if I can.
I feel like I feel like Mr.
Chaypex snuck the price up on us.
Why does it tomorrow get the blame?
That's what I'm saying.
He's handsome.
Maybe he's the one pulling the trigger on all the prices.
You might be right.
Yeah.
As a wolf and sheep's clothing.
But he's just so sexy.
I can't imagine he would.
This is an anti-bald bias with shaping.
That's what's happening.
You might be right.
So when we were trying to get the reservations, you can put in like,
oh, is it a special occasion or something?
And like we're a couple of days away from Lindsay's birthday.
She was trying to she was trying to get reservations, too.
I was trying to get reservations and I was trying to go as fast as possible.
I wasn't even putting any of that in just to, you know, expedite the thing.
Finally, I did it.
It took me 20 minutes of checking.
Lindsay was luckily she wanted me to stop checking, but then she said,
oh, I want a coffee, so I'll go wait in line.
You can keep checking out on the bench in the 85 degree heat.
And I did that.
And she so I got that and she kept saying she's been yelling at me
because I haven't been wearing enough sunscreen.
This is another thing where I'm like,
yeah, I should.
I got burned playing tennis.
We all know I'm playing tennis again.
That's a whole thing.
That's a big deal in my life.
You like already were like your knees were hurting and you burnt.
You got sunburn.
Yeah, I got sunburn playing tennis.
But I'm just like, how many times?
Four, three or four at this point.
Playing again tomorrow.
Maladies already.
Yeah.
So she and Lindsay is big sunscreen person.
She's got the different types.
She's got the face one.
She's got the whatever.
So like before before during when I was checking, she's like, you got to put
we got to reapply, you know, every four hours or whatever.
So, OK, put the body one on.
I put the face one on.
She's got one now where it's like
almost like a deodorant stick.
It's for like your eyes because your eyes are different, like thinner skin and you
whatever you put it on there.
So she's she is made sure I'm not going to get burned.
I'm in the sun now checking because that's like that's the spot on the bench.
Do it. I'm checking, checking, checking.
Finally get it. OK, great.
We go over there.
We get seated.
We're eating and drinking and having a nice time.
And then Lindsay, I think, you know, she had a little bit of a drink.
Not that she's drunk or anything, but she's, you know, she's feeling a little bold.
She goes, hey, you know, would it be?
It's like birthday.
Like, is there anything for?
She also like throws in like, you know, it was our anniversary,
but that's like two months ago, but she's like, it's our anniversary.
There was some of that.
If you're celebrating, if you're celebrating, you didn't have a chance to celebrate.
They're not checking ID.
So she goes like, is that she's like, basically, does that do anything?
And I was like, I'm, of course, always very nervous any time, anything like that.
Even she's like, oh, shut up to me.
Oh, I'm the king of. She doesn't do anything.
She's like, oh, come on.
Or whatever. And she goes, did that do anything?
And the woman is very nice who was waiting on us.
And she's like, oh, maybe after June 15th, it does.
He's like, oh, I'm sorry. Whatever.
That's good. It felt like two minutes later,
they brought a giant chocolate milk, like milkshake Sunday
with a brownie sticking out of the top on the table.
So we're like, we're like, whoa, what?
Thank you so much.
And the thing with that happened is Lindsey is to ask that to
there were two women who were waiting on us.
And she asked it to the one who didn't know that she had a nut allergy.
Oh, oh. So I was at the Disney Doctor, though.
You think we think Lindsey's going to go in for another nut allergy.
Not the case. Oh, so.
OK, they put the thing there.
They put the thing there.
We ask about the nuts and they say, yes, there are walnuts in there.
Lindsey is allergic to tree nuts.
And then just because this is just like so it's such a nice thing
for them to have done.
Lindsey goes, oh, it's OK. I'll scrape them off,
which is not how this works, by the way, if you have a tree nut allergy.
Yeah. It's so sensitive.
Like one time I had walnuts like at noon and like we kissed at eight o'clock.
And she was like, did you have walnuts earlier?
You I stopped for coffee on the we were going down to the park once
and I got like a pecan twist.
I remember I was at Panera and I was like, oh, give me an extra one.
Because I got it from Mike.
Forgetting about the tree nut conundrum.
And I was like, I got you a pastry and you were like, it's.
Yeah. And so then you were like, well, now you have to eat a second pecan twist.
And I was like, oh, darn. Oh, darn.
Sure. We.
So what's going to happen now?
We there was no way we were going to send this back.
Ask for another one after it's this complimentary thing they just did on a whim
because they felt like, oh, we want to, you know, do whatever.
So I'm going to have to eat it.
I'm going to have to eat those whole thing.
And it is massive. We have there's a picture of it. It is massive.
We I once again back up to the city walks.
Yes, I say you do not have to eat the whole I making you eat the whole thing.
But they were so nice to bring it out.
We have to make a very sizable dent in it.
There's no way we are wasting more like half or more, half or more.
That's fine. Yes. OK.
It's not. And again, it's not a I mean, it's not as crazy as like that monster,
mini monster or whatever, or as crazy as the Liberty Tree meal.
But I said it to Lindsay while it was happening.
I go, I am eating a big thing now and I have to finish a certain amount of it
because I wasn't planning on doing that.
I was planning on getting my my patented to scoop ice cream cone in the end.
That's my treat from Disney.
So I was like, I don't want like ton of ice cream earlier.
My yummy treats are coming too early and free.
A free yummy treat that's not the same flavor of the yummy treat I wanted later.
You know, if you know, it's sometimes change is good.
You know, I'm delicious. Yeah. Delicious.
Yeah. So if a wild card treat appears, you know, a wild Pokemon appears,
you know, you got to go with it.
Hey, I completely agree.
So so I'm eating this.
Lindsay goes, how do you think I could just have like a little maybe
of like the milkshake part?
And she like tries to go, I go, do not.
What are you thinking? Don't do it.
I go, do you have your EpiPens?
She goes, yeah, I go, no, we don't want to.
I go, we don't want to go to the Disney doctor.
We do not. I said this to her.
I do not want to go to the Disney doctor.
And she goes, yeah, OK, you're right.
And I take a big like I take the spoon.
I went in and I go, there's tons of walnuts in the liquid.
It's not just on the top or on the brownie.
I go, it's very good.
You didn't take a sip of that.
She goes, yeah, yeah, you're right.
So I do. I eat a lot of it.
It's great. It was great, obviously.
It's obviously not a burden to do it.
It's just funny that that happened like that.
So I eat that. I had a beer.
I had just ordered a beer, too.
So we were drinking that.
So we leave there. I'm feeling good.
I didn't get a ton of sleep.
I'm feeling a little like lightheaded and I also didn't get good sleep either.
I went anywhere for a year.
Yeah. And I'm such a self-sabotager when I'm trying to get to bed
and wake up extra early.
My brain just sabotages me.
Bedtime procrastination.
There's articles about it now.
Left and right.
Yeah. Your brain screwing.
It's so weird.
It was happening just a couple of days.
Yes. It's so weird.
Why? Why? Why?
Our brains hate us like that.
I have a feeling I know where this is going.
But I am a nerve that you both absorb some of my qualities
during the quarantine time.
And we're recording in person again.
It's no, I think we got it recently.
Oh, OK. Oh, like through droplets and aerosols.
We caught it.
That's it. Back to Zoom.
OK, so I'm interested to see.
Tell me if I wonder if you do know where this is going.
So we get out of a car, we hit the 80 whatever degree heat.
And I'm feeling like good, but I'm feeling a little out of it.
I'm feeling a little, you know, you have one drink and a beer and I'm full of sugar.
And yeah, so I'm just like, I'm feeling fine,
but I'm feeling a little woozy or whatever, but not so terribly.
And we're walking and we're walking.
And all of a sudden I go, oh, no.
I think I think there's sunscreen in my eye.
I know. And I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, huh?
And this we've all had this.
You get soap in your eye, you get sunscreen.
I want some while you close your eye, you know, it tears up
and you wipe it on your sleeve and you get it gets out.
This that didn't happen that easily for me.
We're getting into Disney and we're walking down Main Street.
And I'm like, I can't see.
I like I this won't stop tearing.
It's bright red.
Did I scratch my cornea?
What is going on?
So we're walking through Adventureland.
I'm going, this is really bad.
And I'm not this doesn't happen to me a lot where I like
like I don't like I'm not like over complaining about like an ailment
usually, unless it's for comedic effect on a podcast, but not this instance.
I can't see very well.
I'm my eyes tearing. I'm closing it.
We're walking around.
I go, let's just walk over by like the Poo Give Shop.
Or something for a while.
Let me see if I can get this worked out of my eye or whatever.
And we're walking by the Poo Give Shop.
It's closed. I go, all right, let's go on Poo.
I don't care. I don't care about that.
You're still getting on ride.
So we got on the ride and I'm like, I'm like, oh, now I'm seeing heffalumps
and woozles and like out of one eye.
Oh, no, you're tripping out.
And I'm like, OK, there's not as much light in here.
So that's good. OK, good.
So like and so then I'm like, OK, maybe I'm feeling better.
I think I'm feeling better.
We get out. The light hits my eye.
It stings. It is stinging so bad.
And I'm like, all right, I got to go to Hungry Bear.
I go into Hungry Bear.
I start getting a handful of water and dumping them in my left eye.
Yeah. And that's you don't want to do that.
Well, that's what Lindsay was saying.
And she was like she was trying to give me she goes,
oh, take like a paper towel and dab your like eyelashes a little bit
like you're removing like mascara.
And I go, oh, and I'm trying to do it.
She's like, no, that's not how you remove mascara.
And I go, I've only worn mascara like for a play or something.
I don't know. Maybe it was just eyeliner.
I don't think it was mascara.
So I'm trying to do it.
Trying to get it off. It's not working.
I go, I got to like flush my eye out.
I'm in a hungry bear.
I'm waiting till people leave so they don't see this.
I am taking handfuls of water and splashing them on my face.
My mask is soaked.
My mask is like I just dipped my mouth in splash.
Do you want an eyelid wipe for next time?
Because I started carrying the this is the thing my eye doctor showed me last year.
Really? An eyelid wipe?
Well, you close your eyes and you.
You just pulled one out.
Yeah, I pulled one out.
So for the listener, you have this in your bag.
I went through all the samples and I finally splurged for a box.
You wipe your eyes.
The dirt builds up under your eyelid.
And so you wipe your closed eyes and then you rinse it off.
Or they have non rinse ones now.
OK, so yeah, so that is close to maybe what I did.
So we get out hungry bear and I think it's bad.
I think it was Gomer's Gentlemen's Lair, of course,
is the name of the hungry bear bathroom, the gentleman's bathroom there.
And this, by the way, you're avoiding people.
And this is the very spot where you refuse to take off your socks
before getting on splash man.
And that's why you'd rather do it in the log.
So public embarrassment in this spot is a true nightmare.
Well, yeah. And this is the last like these are the last remnants
of the country bears in Disneyland.
I mean, Gomer's bathroom, Gomer from the country bears.
You're going to be embarrassed in front of people walking by.
You're going to be embarrassed in front of Gomer.
Yes, I don't want to look like a fool in front of Gomer.
But I did. I mean, I was handfuls of water dumping on my eye, trying to like
I was like waterboarding myself with water in the bathroom when people were gone.
And I'd have to wait.
So I'd like kind of like linger in a strange way.
And then when they were out of the bathroom, I would do this.
And I thought, OK, like maybe it's getting a little better.
So I'd go outside.
And then like we were walking towards Hauna Mansion and I go, OK,
and then it would get worse again.
It would just be just as bad.
And I go and Lindsay's like, do you want to go to the doctor?
And I swear, like, of course, in my head, I go, it's going to be funny
if I go to the Disney doctor, because I'll talk about it.
But I was trying to be very authentic.
I was trying to be honest.
And I was like, no, I think it'll go away.
It's going to go away.
I don't want to force a doctor visit for this silly thing that's happening.
So we go on Hauna Mansion.
It's low light.
I'm feeling a little better on Hauna Mansion.
I'm closing my eye.
I get out. It's just as bad.
It is burning.
At this point, it's been 30 minutes or whatever of like burning my left eye.
So she goes, go to the Disney doctor.
And I go, yeah, OK.
She goes, I'll wait in line for pirates and you go to go go to the doctor.
So I go, all right.
So I walk all the way over.
Where is it? Where's the Disney doctor?
It's right by the photo.
It's off of Main Street.
It's right by Plaza Inn, right?
It's it's by the there's a baby.
There's a weird little corner that kind of just ends up going backstage.
I don't really know what's over there.
So the Disney. Yeah, I had never been to a Disney.
I was there once.
And I think it was because like I had a cut or like I had a bandage
that fell off and I needed a new one and they were able to give me a new one.
And I think we'll give you a you can buy Advil or Tylenol at most gift shops.
But I think they'll just give it to you there.
Like, I'm not sure you need to sign, right? Sign in.
So I again, I never been there.
Lindsay had to go there because she's like hurt her toe really badly in Florida.
But that was the Florida Disney doctor.
So I go in here.
There's no one inside.
There was a very nice calm man
who always felt like he was like I was pausing for him to finish his thought.
But he had finished his thought, if that makes sense, like rhythm wise.
Or he'd be like, all right, what's going on?
What's the problem here?
And I go, well, I have like a suntan because you have an eye wash station
or something like a sun. I have lotion in my eye.
It won't come out. I don't think I've scratched it, but it's possible.
I'm in such pain.
I'm in such discomfort.
And he's like, OK, well, what's your name?
And I go, OK.
And I he took like there's a form and the form looked like it was full of names.
And I look and there were people outside and I go, oh, I'm going to have to wait.
Like, is it going to be a big wait?
Like it's like the ER or not the ER.
Yeah. Well, I guess the ticking clock of the day, you're saying like
it's not annual pass on a whenever I'm right back.
And I'm going to lose some of it to sit in a big line of the Disney doctor.
Yes. So so he goes.
All right. Well.
Follow me back.
And I go, all right, because I was like, he was like, all right.
And I was like, he's going to say, like, go outside and I'll call your name.
I was like, follow me back and go. All right.
So I'm walking through and I can't see.
But I'm also because I'm a theme park journalist trying to go like look in the.
OK, how can I report on what else is here?
Lap coat Mickey Lapcoat, probably a lap coat Mickey painting.
Nothing. No, no.
Like, yeah, goofy.
It's not the most themed.
It's pretty white.
Yeah, it's pretty stethoscope or something.
Yeah.
Shoking themselves.
And we're like, goofy, misdiagnosing someone.
Ship making a makeshift splints for Dale.
Yeah.
Yeah, goofy filled out the wrong pill prescription for some old lady.
His eyes are exploding out of his head.
Or should I kill her?
Overdia.
So I'm looking through.
I saw a bigger room that looked almost like
like after some sort of disaster, like there were a lot of
cots or a lot of like it was a bigger room.
Wow. I mean, really didn't look quite.
Oh, yeah. He stroke. People need to lie down.
I think it was like for that.
I think it was like if Dad has had too much heat for the day,
maybe he had a couple too many drinks.
He gets to lie down in there.
But then he took me into a very small room that was very similar to like a doctor's
office room. They had the eyewash there and he goes, all right, let me.
And this is my I'm probably remembering half of it because I was still like so disoriented.
He goes, we have the eyewash station here.
But I don't know.
He really doesn't work.
So he goes, here's what you're going to do.
Here's what I think you should do.
And he has he goes he takes a towel and he goes, take the towel.
Turn the water and wet the towel.
You know, pull down your eye like this, like pull down the bottom of your eye.
Generally, you know how you get suntan lotion and you, you know,
you go in the pool and it still stays on.
That's probably what's happening to you right now.
He goes, plop pools in the bottom of the eye, pull the eye down,
take the washcloth and just, you know, go along the eye like, like,
like scrub the bottom of your eye.
And he goes and do that back and forth.
And I go, OK, all right.
So I take it and I do it like I do it like twice.
And I'm doing it badly, too.
And I go, is it like that?
And one is like approval.
And he goes, well, I guess I mean, if it feels better,
like I can't tell you what to do.
And I go, oh, yeah. And he goes, we do as many times as you want.
And I go, oh, OK.
So I'm like trying to like go back and forth a little bit.
And he he goes, all right, does it feel better?
And I go, I think so.
So he goes, all right, well, come back if it does.
And I go, thank you so much.
So I walk out and it still like hurts.
But it did work. It worked.
He was absolutely right.
It had pulled in there.
No water. It wasn't even it was just stuck.
It was just stuck on the bottom of my eyelid and re irritating it over and over again.
Yeah, it's the part I like.
Your lids are lubricating your eye.
And if there's dirt or some other substance, it's not, you know, doing it correctly.
Yeah. And I ran over.
Lindsay had just gotten in the front of the line of pirates.
And I just like immediate like jumped over in the line with her.
Oh, you still got on the wow.
I still got on pirates with her. Oh, yeah.
I don't remember the time right after that.
I was still like in some discomfort.
So I don't really remember even walking back.
It was all a little, you know, trauma blurs your memory.
Yeah, yeah. I remember getting back in line and then going, OK.
And then like 30 minutes later, I could feel it was not perfect,
but it was fine. And now I'm fine. Oh, good.
So I was like, wow, what a what a situation it really I mean,
obviously in the scheme of things, that's not a serious problem.
But if you ever had some stuck in your eye, you can feel kind of panicked about it.
Yeah, yeah. That's that's ruining the day.
Yeah. Mixed with the full tummy and.
Yes, yeah.
A bunch of like the the chill of Carthay, followed by the panic of eye pain.
Yeah, yeah. God.
Geez. Yeah. Boy.
When we say you survived this episode, you were going to mean it. Yeah.
It was a harrowing. Yeah. Yeah. That's insane.
Oh, my God. Yeah.
Well, let's we should start winding it down. Sure.
Let's just like let's let's, you know, call out some stuff. Yeah.
I had some other.
I mean, I did my Mark Twain.
I did a maiden voyage on Mark Twain.
I didn't do the train.
Here's what it was explained to me at the Main Street station.
I could board the train at Toon Town and then I could exit at any station,
but I could only board at Toon Town.
And when I went over to Toon Town, it was looked like a shit show.
And I was like, ah, skipping this one like that.
That was one of the outdoor lines that just seemed like out.
It was unclear where it started and ended.
So they reserving the train station for the distant character hangs.
Yeah. That's kind of what was like the steps where you would walk up
to get on the train and means that Main Street is where Mickey
and Minnie are hanging out and like a lot during the day.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Here's times are they out.
Here's Donald and. Oh, boy.
Yeah. And they really from up on their perch, some steps up.
They give you they do give you a moment.
Goofy posed.
They like I think the distant character hangs are good.
I agree. Yeah. A bunch of them.
It's really good for them that kids aren't harassing them and pulling on stuff.
It's probably makes it an easier job for that.
I think those things are really nice.
Kind of a more confusing one.
Here's Jack Sparrow on the second floor above the Pirates of the Caribbean,
kind of hidden by tree branches.
I looked from a couple of angles, couldn't really make him out.
I'm pretty sure you can only see him if you were directly below him.
That was a little weird.
Couldn't hear him either.
But Lindsay said because I didn't see Jack.
She said she saw Jack Sparrow walking back to exit to like go on break or whatever.
And she's got a kid goes, hey, Jack Sparrow.
And he turned around to like wave or say hello or whatever.
And then Jack Sparrow turned back around to go back to the exit.
And the door was closed and he smacked right into the door.
Oh, no.
I hope he's fine, obviously.
But it's a comedic situation.
I just want to prove I forgot.
I took a photo of my eye.
Here is probably irritated, right?
Yeah, here you go.
Yeah, it looks a little red from from.
G.
Rubbing. Yeah, fine.
That's like that would be the last frame of a movie.
Oh, yeah. But we're looking at your dead body and like, yes,
whatever horrors you've witnessed in the third act.
Yeah, the mask is soaked.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah. And your hair is like, oh, wait, I got a different one, too.
Look at both. Like.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yeah. Compared to the other one compared to the well one.
Yes. Yeah, yeah. Jesus.
I'll get I'll get you a bottle of OptiV tears.
That's what I usually carry on me.
It's kind of sensitive eyes.
OptiV gave me my OptiV tears.
And that is we met this crazy bird.
We were eating popcorn.
It was called him Eric.
I thought he looked like he wanted to kill me.
Jane thought he was friendly.
But that bird, that beak seems like a weapon.
So I don't know. He was mad dogging me a lot.
Now, I have a Disney bird question, which is we felt like we were seeing
a lot more geese than before.
I saw geese. Really? OK.
You know, this is to. Yep. What's going on with this?
Why are there more geese?
My guess would be that since there were a lot fewer people there for a year
that more birds and geese were like, hey, this is our home now.
And now that empty spot.
And now they're kind of stuck there because they're like, well, we were here.
Why are you all coming here?
Yeah, we saw a cat.
We saw a cat from the Haunted Mansion line.
It was on the big hill that the train goes above the mansion.
Kind of those little things really make you feel like we're back.
Yeah, we didn't see any cats.
We saw a lot of birds, a lot of ducks, like the ducks even bolder
than I remember them, where you're like you.
I almost ran into you.
Like you are not worried about me at all.
Like you were a duck and you are not concerned that I'm a human
and that you should get away from me.
Yeah, we saw that.
I'm trying to think we we had a Ronto rap, of course.
We had we did.
Yeah, as we said in our episode about it on the second gate,
I think it's a must do.
It's really looking forward to it.
Aaron loved the veggie one a lot.
And I think we're going to see on the second day
we all made Ronto wraps at home to varying degrees of success.
And the I think a big thing we missed, I think that I think the bread,
there's more going on than you remember.
It had been a long time.
There's you feel the grill of it.
There's texture.
There's more complexity to that bread than you recall.
And I think that's something that we all we all missed.
Yeah, I agree. Yeah.
But yeah, that was good.
That was sort of our last thing we had.
I did. Yeah, I had my free ice cream treat earlier in the day.
Lindsay's first time doing Rise of the Resistance.
Wait, all of our significant others are not done.
Why? We did not allow them to go with us the first time.
We went alone.
Boys Club. Yeah.
We're gatekeeping.
Yes. Yeah.
You'll yes, you'll get in a couple of months, you'll get it.
When the gentlemen say it's OK, when we deem the right acceptable,
we will allow the ladies to see it after hopefully a year later
over a year later.
That's weird. We all had that same experience.
I yeah, I don't know.
Did it let anyone down?
I Aaron was a buzz, super thrilled with it.
You know, I don't want to watch that happen.
Yeah, Lindsay was very.
Yeah, she really liked it.
She loved the reveal with the with the back ship.
You know, yeah, you forget at the end that that is a big surprise.
Like it almost wasn't one of the big things I was talking about.
And that was what lit her up.
Hey, and you just love him by then.
That was so excited.
Yeah, the little misdirect with the ship, with the door.
Yeah, yeah.
I yeah, it's still so great.
It was so nice to be on that specifically broke during the day.
That took up a lot of time.
And it is your.
Jason, it is way up in the corner.
If you're going to make the sojourn, it's like it's not the same as like
Star Tours is down. I will come back.
It's kind of centrally located.
You got to really commit.
Or are we going to walk all the way over?
And it did just take up an inordinate amount of the day.
Not really, because it is such a great ride.
But then it made us we had to gun it after that to get a couple major things in.
I since we got it at seven, I didn't try to do do it at noon.
But it was noon.
I had to do the new I like waited one millisecond and checked something like,
is that my pass number?
And I know you have to do it in the first 10 seconds or you're screwed.
It is. Yeah. You don't know about all this.
There's two entry points.
You do it before you get to Disneyland at 7 a.m.
Just let me try to get on and get a spot.
And then you do it at noon when you're at Disneyland.
I think it's the same for the Spider-Man.
It is. You cannot have both at the same time.
So the problem there is if we want to do rise the day we go,
is that it'll be we have to get the Spider-Man reservation before noon.
We have to use it before noon.
OK. Oh, yeah.
I only have DCA.
Yeah, I only have DCA to.
You're on your own.
He's going to for that as well.
OK, there in addition to a special special guest.
OK, the yeah.
But yeah, I did the noon and it worked, which got me on.
At five, but then it broke.
And so, yeah, it like did take over the day.
Stressful thing, but also funny, fun shades of when Rez the Resistance open
that first morning, your ultimate checking,
you know, events like you really having to nail it.
Watching everybody like with phones and getting happy or unhappy.
It is a funny like thing that happens in the park now.
A little mass phone event.
Yes. So she has she really had a good time with it.
I assume I probably like tried to tell her some of it,
but like it's been a year since, so I'm sure that's a lot fresher.
Yeah, I think I had said like, yeah, it's great.
It's like indoors and outdoors.
There's anti-parts and outside parts.
And she vaguely recalled me saying that, but could not picture
how that played out exactly. Yeah.
And also, it really it really is like you see pictures,
you see video of the ad at room.
I think she watched a video of that part.
I said, I'm not going to spoil all of it, but you guys see this.
And she's like, OK.
And then you do it in person and it's a whole other.
But why does that part not look impressive on a video and in.
It's just like scale doesn't. Yeah.
It doesn't translate all.
I mean, I'll take pictures of stuff that I think like, oh,
look at this big, crazy thing. And it looks like shit.
Yeah. If you don't have lenses or anything to support it.
Yeah. It really has to be like shot in a specific way to convey that, I think.
Yeah. Jane had watched videos, but she was like,
that Canon room looks a little scary.
I was like, yeah, it is. It is.
It's really you really think they're going to hit you.
And she doesn't like the stuff guys above her, you know, robots above her
and stuff. And there's a lot above you in that ride.
Point of view. Yeah. Yeah.
So so that was yeah.
So she was she liked it. Yeah, it was we had a good time.
Good. So downtown.
So downtown Disney.
I alluded to this earlier.
This is the most crowded I have ever seen downtown Disney
because the parks closed.
Both bars closed right at seven.
And then if other people were just coming in to go to downtown Disney.
But I didn't have too bad of experience.
We got ice cream and salt and straw.
I think I'd only ever been one other time.
And then I got a coffee.
I got an Americano at Starbucks for the drive back.
And for whatever reason, they're like, don't forget to use your 50 percent
off coupon. And I was like, OK, I don't know why.
I have this.
Like, I don't know what you're talking about, but I'll take it.
And then Jane got a roll of sandwich to go.
So no, the wait wasn't too bad.
There was just a lot of people.
Oh, and a lot of outdoor lines, because that's why it seemed probably crowded
because everything's out there.
They were staggering, letting people in the store.
It was like a 30 minute wait to get in the world at Disney.
Wow. It's like, yeah, we looked in Star Traders.
We stayed. Most of the new stuff were good.
You know, yeah, yeah.
Huh? Yeah, I'm trying to think.
Big other stuff with me.
The I really I was telling you guys off the show the other day,
I told Jason this, that like, I really think that I never felt more
like the the pandemic is over or like the worst of the pandemic is over
than being on Space Mountain, the most indoor ride that there is.
Yeah. The most iconic like you go to Disneyland for that
and you yell and you're so happy and it really felt like, wow,
this is it.
It really like came over me in a wave in Space Mountain,
like a good place to end up having that feeling.
Yeah, I think it would have we were hoping to have more of a triumph.
But when it's still dystopian mask world, I think we were still like,
it's great to be back.
It's like in six months, we'll be like, yeah, really.
Well, maybe I felt it in Space Mountain because you can't see dystopian space.
Well, that might be why it hit me.
And then you don't I don't remember.
I think they just staggered Rose.
I don't think there was any bizarre plexiglass going on,
which there's all that those things are interesting.
A little you know, the haunted mansion stretching room.
They give you numbers and spots to stand on.
You all hug the. Oh, it's yeah, it's weird.
I realize we broke COVID protocol in the Lieutenant Beck spaceship
because like I was like, we got to get right in front where the
we can see that. Yes.
And we were like right on this like railing.
And I realized like halfway through that there was a number
we were supposed to be in the they were supposed to shove us in the corner
in a different place.
And I was like, oh, no, we I didn't get any direction.
We broke. Yeah.
Well, we're trying to maintain the cavefabe of the ride.
Get in, get in.
Also, by the way, there's numbers on the floor and you need to correspond to that.
Because all the numbers rebel.
COVID protocols and by the way, resistance numbers, by the way,
covered in like the yeah, the
in the and the Star Destroyer, it's like, don't worry,
I'm going to give you a number of color.
It's red. You're going to go on the floor.
It's red. And I hate you because you're a rebel and bad.
Blah, blah, blah.
Like, but they're trying to shout.
They're trying to do two things at once.
And you know, shows are debating whether like we like Law and Order,
like they're wearing they acknowledge COVID.
It'd be so funny if like a Disney plus show like the bad Star Wars,
the bad batch is suddenly like and COVID-19 is really throwing the rebellion
for a loop like, wait, what did he say?
He changes every other term, but not that one.
Yeah, that'll be interesting to see.
Baby Grogu has to deal with it on that season of Mandalorian.
Yeah, it's a it's a big scary droid.
No, yeah.
One like Revis, Revis relative Loki knocks over one of Owen
Wilson's test tubes and all.
Oh, no. Mischievous Loki. Wow.
Ka-chow. Ka-chow.
You better say Ka-chow.
I kept saying, Ka-chow, what is it?
I go, it's like the Queen's catchphrase.
Yeah. Ka-chow.
Ask any child here.
Well, first off, don't ask any child, but they would be able to tell you
in theory what Ka-chow meant.
Yeah. It took me years after seeing cars to know that that was a catchphrase of.
Here, I tried to do the Avery Monson hat trick of fortune tellers.
Oh, right. And Fortune Red was out of commission or in a closed part of the store.
It was unclear. Yeah.
Like a tarp.
There's a person with a desk and then Fortune Red was behind.
They were counting people ins and outs.
So, OK. But Esmeralda and Shrunken Ned, both running.
OK. I forgot all about them.
Yeah. Next time.
So the details are going to.
Yeah. I mean, I did Big Thunder.
What did I do? Yeah, Big Thunder.
We had to do that.
We we actually did not step foot in Tomorrowland.
Wow. Just just time.
Yeah, we crossed through it.
That was about all we had time for.
And yeah, we didn't. Yeah, I don't know.
I think I think we hit the highlights.
There was it's being not having gone on a lot of these rides for so long.
I have to go back now and check because there was stuff in the Haunted
Mansion graveyard where I go, is that new?
There's a telescope up on the veranda.
I don't know. Was that always there?
Was there always a telescope?
I knew to me. Yeah, it seemed to.
Yeah, it was the first time I really noticed it, too.
There was like at the end of the graveyard.
There was a weird scene with like a guy, maybe with like a bell or something.
People are going to be really mad if this has been there
since the opening or something.
But we both were like, is that new?
That doesn't look like I got to go back and go side by side.
I mean, we'll discuss this, of course, in the Haunted Mansion episode
in three or four years, whenever that part of the ride comes up.
But I'll go back and do that.
But that's I just larger point just to make is that ever not after not going on
these, there's always a couple of things because there's so much going on.
We go, is that new?
Yeah. Was this hologram wall always there in Tomorrowland?
I know the wall was always there, but was it always like colored like this?
Oh, I think that's a fairly recent.
OK, that's recent.
I remember the discourse around that.
I like it. It looked great.
Good like Disneyland Twitter discourse always is.
I feel like there was I think like it was mostly accepted,
but I feel like there were some people that didn't like it.
It looked found a way to not like paint on a wall.
Yeah, sure. They will.
There's a will, there's a way.
It looked appropriately futurey, but it was clearly like, you know,
decorative landscape.
It wasn't like there was no Instagram spot.
There was no stand here for a picture spot.
So maybe that's why I was like, oh, that looks nice.
Yeah. Yeah.
Let me just say this greater arc of because like, you know, it was
there was the running guy and we had these great moments like,
do we have time to do this?
And I think, all right, we can't do Soren and Guardians.
So which one do we prioritize?
And we did pick Guardians.
It was so great to go out on that.
But we do have time for for a little mermaid because that'll be shorter.
So like doing all this math again was kind of exciting.
But we, you know, the time was a little crunch partially
because we also took a big long breather as guests of the Grand
Californian to chill out at the Craftsman Bar,
which is outdoors and by their pool.
And this typically would be open to everybody.
But we realized after we got the hotel, oh, my God,
we're the only people who get this.
It was so sparsely populated.
And again, any new parents just know the feeling of the first time
you get to step away.
This was the chillest thing ever.
The food there is fantastic.
They do a really good if you like the vibe of
of the whole Grizzly Peak area, it's like getting to just sit in that
for a while, that big tree trunk.
That's the water slide base over there.
It's just such a like we just wanted that resort thing to.
It's the Disneyland Resort.
We got our resort vibe.
Food's great.
We both ended up drinking a perfect day IPA.
And that's how we felt.
It really was a perfect day.
A like music guitar version of Warmth of the Sun,
which is one of my favorite, one of the best Beach Boys songs.
Kind of a dusk.
Boy, it was wonderful.
Then leaving from Guardians,
like taking that little stroll,
grabbing another beer on the way up, taking it back to the room,
to the balcony where we have a view I was joking about.
It's a view of downtown Disney.
And that's funny and silly, but also a view of the distant spires
of Space Mountain, right of Splash Mountain.
And it was just just after all this lockdown and all of the all of the
newborn madness that we've had to get to get to relax
and just have a beer up there.
Boy, we've just we've it was just so great to feel so chill.
You really took it in that night.
Woke up, got to have the leisurely wake up of eight
fifteen as opposed to what we're what we're usually doing.
Probably another new parent that you know that first time
where you don't have to wake up and immediately deal with stuff.
So relaxed again, I go out on the patio and just just take it in like, wow,
it's really feeling like we're turning a new leaf and it's over.
And we got to relax.
It was a perfect day, as the IPA said.
This is I just feel well rested.
I maybe could not have not felt better.
I reached into my hoodie pockets
and felt immense searing pain on my right hand.
Oh, no. An unrecognizable pain.
What in the world is there a like a barb from a barbed wire in there?
Wait a minute. It can only be.
And I kept digging through the pocket and there was a bee in there.
This was the morning.
The sweater had only been inside somewhere in the park
or at California Adventure, a bee stowed away
and stayed in the room the entire night and then stung me so hard.
Still see it. Still. Wow.
Still feel it a little bit.
What do you mean? I got stung by a bee.
So, Mike, you're telling your story of woe. Wow.
Jason, you had your immediate hike to have to do.
And I have like I'm truly it is like a movie moment of like deep breath.
Ah, life's pretty good.
Then I got stung so hard by a bee.
So I guess this was nice for everybody.
But we all got punished in our own ways.
Yeah, that's true.
You know, I had a number of conversations with people and and they're like,
you know, I feel a little myself included.
I feel a little overwhelmed by getting back out into the world.
It's also refreshing. It's invigorating.
It's nice to do.
But emotionally and mentally, like after 14, 15 months,
it can be very draining and very shocking.
So when it manifests in physical woes
that that feels like insult to injury sometimes.
The stress manifested into a bee.
Yeah. Stung Scott.
And yeah, did I make up the bee?
Was the bee just in my head like Tyler Durden?
You absorbed my anxiety just to manifest as bees sometimes.
Sorry, you got that too.
I've seen that happen to Jason, really stressed and all of a sudden
a few bees just appear.
Yeah. Stinging him repeatedly.
Yeah. And I psychosomatically like leaked
the like my body was like, I'm going to leak the lotion into his left eye
because I want in the same way that my body self sabotaged
any before by not allowing me to go to sleep the same way this happened.
So, yeah, you're probably right.
We've talked about spirits in the air and all this is possible
that the the sun, tan lotion in the eye and the bee
were both manifestations of Walt.
He was preemptively punishing us for that riff
that ran to the thing we did earlier in the show.
He's like, I'm not going to be happy about this.
Yeah, I'm not a flame.
I don't have a bunch of pee in a fact in a warehouse somewhere.
I rarely kept my toenails and thumbnails around or did anything with them.
This crass show that you boys do.
I'm not happy with it.
Is he part of it because there was a weird full moon this week.
One of the blood moons or some sort of blood.
Like something was going on with the moon this week, throwing stuff off.
Saying that Walt created a blood moon.
Does he is does that like the eclipse powers Imhotep?
Does does Walt come back?
Does he start to materialize like a happy heart?
Does he materialize?
Let me think about it. Yes.
OK, exactly correct.
Yeah, that's what happens.
So when the next time there's a blood moon, keep your eye out.
For for, you know, a beloved figure named Walt Disney,
he might sting the palm of your hand.
I'm going to sting you.
Make you go blind for half an hour.
I'm back. I'm going to sting you.
I'm going to ruin your eyesight.
I'm going to.
I'm not happy with all the changes at the resort, but boy, that Josh tomorrow
in one hunk, that's that's a looker.
He's got the Disney look.
He could replace a young Kurt Russell in one of our films.
I'd share a grilled cheese with him off the hot plate any day.
I bet Suzanne Plushet wants a date with Josh tomorrow.
So you two nudges them together.
Beach party movie and that and Josh tomorrow.
Write the script.
We'll get the boys on it.
Wow. All right.
Brothers writing a song for it.
The summer beach party.
Josh tomorrow.
Three piece suit at the beach.
Three piece suit. Yeah.
He's always wearing three piece suits.
Josh tomorrow. Oh, I see.
Yeah, I thought I thought it was a joke about Annette's one piece bathing suit,
which is of course what Walt insisted.
I'm just true wanted her to wear because a two piece was scandalous.
More pieces, more chase.
And that I want to wear cover up that I want to wear a three piece bathing suit.
I'm still so mad that Annette wanted to show skin
that I'm going to sting everybody as a bee for the next century.
And Walt, come on.
Yeah, cut us a break, Walt.
But look, we love your park.
It was great to be back. It was great to be home.
You you survive
podcast the ride away.
What are you doing?
What are you in for? Just do the plug.
Do the plugs. The plugs are if you want, if you enjoyed
if you enjoy this episode, please follow us on Twitter, Instagram.
Join our Facebook group.
This was our discussion of our return to Disneyland.
If you want to hear earlier in the week, we talked about our return
to Universal Studios. We're heading back everywhere.
It's felt so great.
And we talk about it on Patreon.com slash podcast.
The ride, the second game with its three bonus episodes every month.
Michael.
You said it, whoever this is.
Skylar Grace, Scott. Oh, of course.
We have to wait for the kick in, don't we?
I guess we have. Yeah, you got to wait.
Thanks for listening.
Be on the lookout for bees and
happy visits to the park, everyone.
Whoa, this is really energetic violins.
I feel like I'm walking the darkened frame path back to the parking garage.
Do we have enough photos between the three of us to make a little montage with this?
Oh, I think I'm going to be a good I could I only have.
Is this mostly my eye in the montage?
Well, that should be
flipping the photos zooming in on the photo.
I don't have the bee, but I'll try to find clip art of an angry bee.
All right. Great. Great.
Forever.
This has been a forever dog production,
executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner,
Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.