Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, The Second Gate,
a show that with the number of tangents
and off-topic discussions could be described
as a series of legendary journeys.
I'm Jason Sheridan, joined as always by Mike Carlson.
Yeah, you know, I like to think, that's good.
I like to think of what we're doing as like legendary.
Like, you don't often think about your legacy
when you're in the middle of forging your legacy,
but now that I think about it, you're right.
And what we're doing is going to be sort of
a Lord of the Rings style adventure,
the whole catalog we're building here.
So thank you for that.
That's true.
And like a Lord of the Rings TV show
where every episode costs like $20 million an episode.
Yeah, the budget of Podcast The Ride,
people don't understand, is very high.
Very high.
I like Lord of the Rings and Hercules and Xeno.
We are in New Zealand right now.
We do zoom over in New Zealand.
Scott Garner actually is on location elsewhere,
which is costing us a lot of money.
Yeah, it's an island that even you guys aren't allowed
to know the location of or which ocean it's in.
Is it Mushake?
Let's just, well, let's just say that there's a number
of very helpful monkeys around.
All right, it's Mushake.
I'll just say it's Mushake.
Okay, good.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Why do I dance around it?
Yeah.
Yeah, but it's, you know, the recording quality's great here.
The ocean air actually, it all like kind of cancels out
and just sounds like nothing.
Like you're just in a room.
Yeah.
People don't know that the microphones,
we throw away a microphone after each record.
That really adds up as far as budget is concerned.
Yeah, yeah.
And don't clean them up very often.
You just end up with a big old pile like a dorm room trash can.
Yeah.
Or he's daring each other to be the one to take it out.
We each have a room full of mics in our apartments and living spaces.
There's just a room full of unused mics.
We're waiting for somebody to pick them up.
Yeah, but if you bury down deep enough in them,
you will pull out like a fish skeleton with the head and tail still on.
Heathcliff style.
What, you're saying you've been eating fish in the room
and you've been throwing it in there?
Well, I need the, you know, it's the kind of good fats
in the Omega 3s and that sort of thing.
So you're saying it's almost like a junkyard that's mostly microphones
except for some remnants of fish like in a normal junkyard,
like Riff Raff and the other cats.
Yes.
Hector, my friend, my idol Hector would eat and throw in the junkyard.
Yeah, I slide down the junk microphones to get to my Honda Civic,
much like his red Cadillac would come out of the junkyard.
Okay, I get it.
I understand what you're saying now.
I'm not sure I want the tangent, but I don't think I know about your idol Hector from Heathcliff.
Oh, okay.
This is not a joke.
This quick side note here.
I hate to say, I really want to talk about the Xena show.
Hercules and Xena, wizards of the screen.
They're wizards of the screen and we'll get to that.
I think I've mentioned it a little bit on the show.
Maybe I haven't said it specifically.
I just said this to Lindsay three days ago when I put Heathcliff on,
because I said Heathcliff doesn't generally make any sense if you watch it.
Your memory of it is like, oh yeah, I kind of liked that when I was a kid.
The show doesn't, like, things happen and you're just really confused the whole time
because obviously nobody gave a shit.
But Hector, his look and his style, he was one of, there was a style,
like there were two cartoons basically, Heathcliff and then it was Riff Raff and the Cadillac cats.
And they lived in a junkyard.
They had a car that transformed and I was like all in on the Cadillac cats.
I didn't care that much about Heathcliff.
And Hector had a headband and a tie.
And I thought this was the coolest guy I had ever seen on TV.
And I don't know exactly why, but whatever reason, you're looking at him now, Scott?
I'm looking at him now.
Yeah, I guess, I don't know.
I mean, your style isn't dissimilar.
You don't wear a lot of ties, but he's got, you know, it's sort of shaggy hair as you currently have.
I was wearing a couple of weeks ago, I was wearing a gator on my head,
which I honestly should put on now because my hair is still long and unruly.
But I was wearing and I think I said to Lindsay, hey, I look like Hector from the Cadillac cats.
She's like, what?
Who?
I go, Hector, you know, Riff Raff's friend from Heathcliff.
She's like, oh, OK.
And I was like, yeah, he was like, I liked Hector a lot.
Well, good for you.
Yeah.
Very supportive.
A lot of people say after I shout information at them.
Well, I obviously was very fond of Riff Raff because he's a short guy with a real big mouth
and he had a jaunty scarf and a big hat, you know, a cat girlfriend that was basically had the body of a human woman.
That's true.
And taller than him, like my girlfriend, like anyone I've ever dated taller than me.
Yeah, this is an extremely sexualized in Google Image Search in various forms on your Deviant Arts, Cleo, the cat.
This is like people got a problem with boy, this goes and goes and goes.
So pages, I'm not sure I've ever seen this much sexualized animated animal art of Cleo.
I can't you can barely even find regular photos of Cleo.
I think it's very it must be because she like it's very like come hither eyes and then a ponytail and then like in very and like sort of like a big 80s workout socks.
And then the skin tone is just like kind of human flesh colored.
So if you like squint, it just kind of looks like a naked woman.
That being said, little too much Cleo, the ratio of sexualized Cleo to regular Cleo is like 20 to one.
It's crazy.
I guess that shouldn't surprise me.
I have not looked into this.
I was not when I watched Heathcliff.
I was not I had nothing dirty on my brain.
I was not I was not thinking of that way.
But if you see Cleo, you can imagine that like a bunch of messed up people that made an impression on them.
Maybe not messed up.
I shouldn't say that.
But just maybe they were at the right age and they were appreciating the human form via a cartoon of a cat woman, I guess, when when you say it like that.
And then, yes, that leads to all the deviant art that we should never speak of again.
We just had we had just nothing but respect for, you know, comedic icon characters like this fellow in a tuxedo pulling his tie.
It looks like kind of like a fancy like a cat skills comedian or almost Liberace.
And according to the episode title, his name is the Great Pusini.
I guess I'm putting that poose on it so that I'm not just saying Pusini.
But who knows?
I'd have to watch to find out.
There's no pornography, though, of this like cat Krusty the Clown-esque character, the Great Pusini.
There's a very cute drawing of Cleo in Riff Raff.
He's given her a rose.
That's wholesome.
Yeah, that's wholesome.
That's what we like.
But she's also like sticking her butt at him.
I think there's still this is still a sort of sexual.
It's just tamer than the other stuff.
It's just tamer than the other ones.
I think that you can see a lot of like animators and people who are designing things like working stuff out as far as their female character designs over the years.
And that's still continuing, especially their feed.
They're animal female characters.
And the big criticism is that like, you know, your Lola Bunny has the body of a human woman.
And then the other Looney Tunes are all just like little weird aliens, weird little animals.
Yeah, I wish there was more like idealized drawings or like exaggerated drawings of short King Riff Raff.
You know, it's a lot of Cleo.
Do you think Riff Raff has like a little cane?
He wears a Dom DeLuis kind of hat going.
Is this a thing, Jason, you thought about maybe one day acquiring and putting into your fashion rotation?
Any time as a theater kid, I was in the prop room and there was like a little cane in a bin with like, I feel like any theater prop room has like a bin of crutches, canes, umbrellas.
Like, you know, I was fiddling around with that sort of thing.
Or it would be like if I had a part in something, I was like, hey, could this character have a cane?
Could this character have like a fun hat?
Like, yeah, I think that's good.
I think you need.
Yeah, I think coming out of the pandemic, you got to do something.
Yeah, we put all the accessories right, right.
And I think maybe the riff raff is what you're looking for.
Yeah, I mean, I have the mustache.
I think I do need some more accoutrements coming out of quarantine.
Yeah, so cane, if you see a man with a mustache with a little cane and a Dom DeLuis hat, it's Jason.
It's not Riff Raff.
Yeah.
All right.
Well, today's episode involves some Jason performance.
Yes, it does.
I understand.
Yeah, that's what I understand too.
That's true.
Hercules and Zeno, Wizards of the Screen, a very powerful title for a ride that an attraction that limped along for about three years before eventually literally being condemned.
Yes.
I think it is notable among in my eyes as being one of the few theme park experiences where when they said, can we have a kid volunteer?
I, shocking my family, strongly raised my hand and volunteered to do it.
Wow.
So you are a star of this attraction, which I, you know, when I was a kid, I saw my mom do the soap opera show at Disney's Hollywood Studios or MGM Studios at the time.
But I was scared.
So you, did you even, let me ask you this, did you surprise yourself with it?
Because sometimes that would happen when I was a kid.
I would sort of surprise myself by doing something.
I think so.
I think it worked out where we were like, we were in the kind of in the front of the area when they asked.
And I had done a few plays at this point.
So like, I'm josing, josing for stage time for attention.
And I raised my hand and my family was like, oh, fuck, really?
All right.
That's what they said.
Oh, fuck.
The audience volunteering section.
That's right.
My, my famously profanity averse mother was just like, shit, man.
She was.
Yeah.
And, and I, I volunteered to be, I don't know if I knew what I was volunteering for even because this was like not a show that we knew we were like, oh, there's something new here.
I think we probably would have done it like summer of 98.
So it'd been going for a little while, but they used audience volunteers.
This was a big green screen and ADR kind of show.
And I was like a child centaur.
They, they take some audience volunteers.
They put them in like, you know, armor and head pieces and then blue screen from the waist down to be like the bottom half of you was a horse.
And you helped Hercules like shoot crossbows at bad guy.
Like you kill some people and then you waved like Hercules.
What does he say?
I caught the video.
There's not a, there's footage of this online.
It's really cut up, but there you can find footage of Hercules going like, uh, thanks centaurs.
He just hit the play.
They like throws to a little moment.
Yeah, from the audience.
Cause by then they know these are some of us and they're in the show just kill every time it really does kill in the footage online.
He literally says, Hey guys, thanks a lot.
And then goes about his business, gives them a look like these, these knuckleheads.
Hey, well, whatever, whatever it takes to get a 10.
So you're the, you were kind of the Ewoks of this, the like the odd creatures who get caught up in the battle and surprisingly, we were craftily resourcefully help save the day.
Yeah, pretty much.
And I'm sure there, there might be a quick picture, like a quick, like very dim picture.
Cause I think by like 98 or 97, we were like, we're not bringing the brick of a video camera to the theme park.
And we're like, we're good.
We don't need, and we don't watch these.
We take these videos.
We don't watch them.
So, and there's no purchase opportunity.
This wasn't one of those where you buy the $28 video of you as a center.
No, we immediately inquired about that.
Anytime I've won it one, there was not an option to buy not like Mike's fold, like karaoke spectacle.
But so there might've been one quick shot of like the, the point and shoot camera with some features right before we got a digital camera, you know, two years before we splurged for an early digital camera.
I've thought about this, like, cause there's, there's a lot of attractions like this where you go, oh, they should have had a video tape to be sold.
Yeah.
But it must just be because only a few people are chosen.
So the idea is probably maybe they'd only sell four like cassette, like VHS's after each performance.
And it doesn't make monetary sense to have that whole apparatus going.
You know what I mean?
A live quickly spitting out videos because if they only make $300 in a day, if that, yeah, why have an on staff, a tape labeler, tape cranker out.
Right.
Doesn't make sense.
Yeah.
Money wise.
Because like the Star Trek show, the Star Trek special effects show, that was part of the appeal.
It's like you buy it at the end or you can buy it at the end.
Come do it.
When we talked about like there was a Nickelodeon kind of game show audience participation show at one of the former Paramount parks, they really push that.
Like, and if you're in this game show, you can buy the tape of it at the end.
Like this was not the case with that.
Probably because it's hard to film like, all right.
And then these people are behind a green screen.
This guy's hitting wind chimes.
This guy makes an ugly face that they superimpose on like a goblin.
This boy is taking a wrench and just wailing on a pipe.
Yeah.
To make noise.
I mean, this show, there's a lot of screen like you are put into.
I mean, they did film original footage with Hercules and Xena for this.
And it is projected on giant standard definition screens at weird angles.
Another screen ride though from Universal.
And another like, yeah, like here's how you make a show.
But then the things in the show are real.
Probably the thing to say about it that we haven't said because it's possible people don't know these shows anymore.
These were like the titans of syndicated television in the late 90s.
Sort of sort of taking over from Baywatch like as Baywatch descended.
So Rose Hercules, the legendary journeys.
That's why you said that.
Right.
That's the name of the show and Xena Warrior Princess, which is a spin off of Hercules legendary journeys.
Yeah, there is something very special about this era genre.
And I don't want to say low budget, but kind of low budget shows because they were still like shows that had a, you know, they were at production value.
We had to have.
Yeah.
But Lindsay's been watching some Xena lately and I'll come into the room and I'll be like, look, I like watching Xena.
Some of these sets look like a porno.
Like there's just no, like she's in supposedly like a magical cave and it's just like a piece of like an obvious piece of like wooden backdrop stone and then like a curtain.
And I go, this looks awful.
This looks so cheap.
And I like that.
I really like that about it.
I like that about this sort of genre of show.
Maybe it's like they could have made like they had the production value and they went and shot this stuff in New Zealand.
That's the big thing.
So you've got the natural beauty of New Zealand helping you out.
But maybe they had the budget and resources to make like three really good episodes, not 30.
Right.
Like the amount of crank it out that syndicated required.
Yeah.
Maybe.
The history of like syndicated shows like Star Trek Next Generation is famously syndicated, I think.
But even though some search for Next Generation looks cheap is like I think a bigger budget show than most of these things.
But like there was so many we've talked about, of course, beloved show Relic Hunter.
We've talked about all these different syndicated shows that were sort of in the same like hour long genre.
Yeah.
Your Valerie Irons Protection Agency, VIP.
Of course.
VIP.
I think it was VIP.
I think it was.
Because of the name, it's Valerie Irons Protection.
Pamela Anderson is Valerie Irons.
Yeah.
And there was, which was Christopher Lloyd in Relic Hunter.
He was in another one.
Are you thinking, Jason, are you thinking of Christopher Lloyd and Pamela Anderson's sitcom Stacked?
No, I'm not thinking of Stacked.
I think there was another genre show.
I know what you're thinking of.
And I've mentioned this before.
It was a UPN show.
And it was, and I'm already, he was of course Sebastian Jackle.
Yeah, Sebastian Jackle.
And there was a Bruce Campbell one too that was kind of a squashbuckler show.
Briscoe County Jr.
Adventures of Briscoe County Jr.
There was Sinbad that came up on the Sinbad episode.
Like as, as like the morning kids cartoons block wind it down, you would roll right into Hercules and or Xena, especially if there was like no sports.
And everyone, I remember watching them kind of checked out.
Like I was, it was not appointment viewing for me.
My dad, I think, would watch them too.
We'd all be kind of falling asleep, you know, falling into a Saturday nap watching these shows half awake.
I mean, though, that's really maybe not the show's fault.
You know, Saturday.
If we eat a large hot breakfast, you know, and everyone's just chilling out, you know, taking it easy.
Large hot breakfast.
Excuse me.
I have a question.
Poor girl eggs, scrappling eggs.
They sit in your gut.
You know, how often would you have a large hot breakfast on Saturday morning?
Oh, often like that.
We didn't eat hot breakfast during the week.
Like my.
Sure.
Or if we did, like if my mom, we would microwave, like, you know, Jimmy Dean breakfast sandwiches before school at most or like the pancakes, the sausage on a stick wrapped in pancakes.
Like that was as elaborate.
I feel like the sausage content over the course of your entire life is twice as much as the person.
You know, I we got feedback on the people commenting on the Toronto Raps episode.
It's like, I'm shocked.
Yeah, I cook a lot of sausage, you know, in other parts of the country.
I think we got comments saying comments on the page.
See, yeah, I did see somebody who was was like, they've never cooked sausage before.
Yeah, people from the Midwest.
I think we have.
All right.
Do we have not cooked sausage?
A lot.
OK, OK, sure.
I'm trying to think if I've cooked sausage.
I don't know that I have.
I mean, I usually.
Right.
You think I know, but I'm not sure exactly.
I've I've.
If it's a hot dog, I reheat it.
If it's sausage, I feel like I always buy the cooked ones and you just eat them up somehow.
Boil it or put it in the microwave or grill it.
But it's already like cooked.
Do you think this may be a coast issue that as on the East Coast that your level of sausage consumption is average?
Yeah, East Coast and Midwest.
I mean, if you go to, you know, a real New Jersey, Pennsylvania, New York kind of diner,
you're if you order eggs and potatoes and toast, it's like a it's a list of what your meat is going to be.
Sausage, bacon, Italian sausage, hot or sweet, Scrapple pork roll.
I'm probably missing some corned beef hash, maybe a possible option.
I had a good amount of sausage in my life.
I'm just saying cooking it.
Yeah, for sure.
I mean, there's definitely a period where I was sausage over bacon if I was ordering at IHOP or Denny's.
So, yeah, I'm not trying to say, oh, I don't even know anything about this sausage.
That's not what I'm trying to portray here.
I'm just trying to say, yeah, I don't know.
You're not being one of those snooty I don't know about sausage guys.
No, I'm salt of the earth.
I know sausage.
I eat sausage, but I don't know.
Yeah, give me a truly raw sausage.
I'm a little I don't know exactly what to do with it.
Yeah, you don't want to get food poisoned.
I get it.
I keep it in the freezer.
It's something to have in the freezer.
Pull it down for eggs or you cook it, toss it in some pasta or something.
So hot breakfast.
What did you say?
It was a big hot breakfast.
Hot and hot was the large hot breakfast.
So you're just hanging out large hot lunch.
Well, hoagies usually cold, but steak, you know, picking up steaks, cheese steaks.
That's hot.
But I feel like these syndicated shows were to like, I agree.
Yes, absolutely.
That was the yes, I don't all of these shows I have paid attention to if I was watching them.
I was not like where I mean, I was way into Star Trek Next Generation.
Deep Space Nine would come on.
Deep Space Nine I've still never dug into, which I've been meaning to.
But that used to come on Saturday afternoon, which I was even if I was watching it, I was a little checked out until like Quark showed up.
And I enjoyed his antics.
Yeah.
The Ferengi, the bartender of Ferengi.
But this at one point was the number one show in the world.
Hercules, at least according to if you listen to Kevin Sorbo talk for the actor who portrayed Hercules,
he will certainly toss out that it was the number one show in the world that was part of this lawsuit that came up where he felt entitled to more profits from the Hercules series.
And part of that was the number one show in the world.
Why would I not be seeing more from that?
I don't really it doesn't feel right to me.
Maybe if you just it's like you I don't know if being everywhere in the world doesn't mean it's the biggest thing in the world.
He doesn't even feel obviously Hasselhoff and Baywatch loom larger for me because I like them now.
But you kind of felt like you knew that Baywatch that Hasselhoff was huge internationally.
Was Sorbo?
I'm confused how big Sorbo got.
That's a good question.
I mean, I don't know.
Maybe.
Obviously Sorbo in recent years has been a little bit more Christian, a little bit more annoying.
Yeah.
So to put it lightly.
But maybe maybe just because Hasselhoff had outside like in depth, like he was doing, he was singing.
We knew about his singing career even back then.
We knew about some of that all like and maybe Sorbo wasn't doing as much extracurricular.
And I will look up does Kevin Sorbo have an album right now?
Oh, that's a good question.
Well, while you do that, there's a premise that I want to introduce into this episode because, you know, this can't be an all Kevin Sorbo episode.
And, you know, I want to make it about, you know, I don't even want to I don't want to make it about the personal life and the fact that he thought that the storm on January 6th was all actors pretending to be right winger because he tweeted.
He said, these don't look like patriots to me with a photo of the QAnon shaman like he thought it was a leftist pose like ruining the name of the great patriots.
But that's that's his personal life and his Twitter presence.
I want to pay tribute to this man's body of work because he has been I mean his level of his acting credits are as long as sausages that Jason is fond of.
It's a massive list.
There's so much there.
And I just want to like, in order to make it not just about Hercules.
Here's what's going to happen in this episode every 15 minutes an alarm is going to go off.
And that's the sorbometer.
And when that happens, I'm going to read several of his credits from his IMDb.
And just as an example, because there's so many and the people might not know if you're if you're a heathen and are not versed in Christian cinema or just generally unreleased cinema, then you might not know some of Kevin's work.
So let me just read a few of the parts that he's played and in what films.
Actually, these are all just announced.
These haven't even happened yet.
Detective Chase Riley in Ghost Killer.
Larry Masters in Final Invasion.
And let's see, Dr.
Ben Riley in The Girl Who Believes in Miracles.
Those are all post 2021 what I just listed.
And now I will I will reset the sorbometer just so all of these great films get their get their day.
Also the name of Spider-Man's clone in Marvel Comics.
So that's right.
Yeah, you're not really supposed to reuse exact character names.
But I know it's kind of doctor in there.
You have a doctor that's transformative, that's transformative.
OK, probably.
Yeah, that's different.
Plays a lot of doctors.
He's Dr.
Robinson in Faith Under Fire.
That sounds pretty good.
Faith, the movie Faith Under Fire in 2020.
That's a hot button.
Tell a lot of people feel they're facing.
Yeah, I here's a shock to me.
Kevin Sorbo, not in the crazy Roe versus Wade movie.
That's right.
He and Jamie Kennedy like didn't bother to read the script or the title of the project he agreed to.
Has he maybe made already like five Roe versus Wade movies and he doesn't want to repeat himself at this point?
Well, I'm going to let I don't want to step on Scott's toe.
I know some stuff he's made that probably falls.
I have a look.
I have some of it.
We can go.
It doesn't have to be all off of the sorbometer.
You can throw Sorbo's out regardless of the sorbometer.
I'm happy to I'm happy to bow to the sorbometer.
Because God's not dead.
He's God's not dead.
Right.
I think so.
Yeah.
I mean, it's hard to find it.
It's a needle in the haystack of 144 acting credits, but he's at least in one of the is he like the yeah, he's the star of the big of he's
Professor Radisson and the first God's not dead.
He might be the liberal scumbag professor from like the he might be the encapsulation of those memes about Marine Todd going to punch out the liberal professor.
I hate to be lewd and bring up porno again, but it does feel like these are all like fake porno movie like act like character names.
And then he has the amount of credits that a porno actor would have as well.
Kind of like a hundred movies in a year.
And these sets were probably likely cheap rental houses deep in the San Fernando Valley that probably used for porno at some point after probably used for porno.
And if of course, if it's like something weird, if it's like a cauldron or even or even like a courtroom, if you need a cheap courtroom,
then you're either a Funny or Die sketch from 10 years ago, a Christian movie or a porno shooting.
I think we're like the doctor's office shares a wall with the courtroom.
And I've been in that I've been in that courtroom.
I've been in the bar set that's right by there as well.
One of them just closed a big one just closed where it was like it was all of those things.
Here's here's an airplane and a courtroom and all that.
And for some reason, the photo on the website was just like a like kind of a cheesecake style photo of the owner.
Like putting her putting her leg up like she was like, you know, posing on a bomb in a World War Two poster.
Wow, really?
I don't think I even want to shoot here.
Meet me.
Hey, Martha.
I don't know who it was.
Just like a Louse.
We got a deal out this dorm room set.
The Christians are coming tomorrow.
Get the UV out, light out.
You see how many stains we can find.
I like how she's like little Vicky or something like she's an old showbiz legend.
Yeah, I want to give credit to Lucy Lawless, who you can find footage of the opening day ceremony of the the Hercules and Zena show.
And she just immediately she's much funnier and charismatic than Kevin Swervo.
Like you can tell in the few minutes that they're standing next to Universal executive Tom Williams.
Tom Williams still hanging in there, still hanging out.
His current title is he he's like a big wig still at Universal.
I forget where I say we like our we know our Disney people a little bit.
I can't say that I really track the Universal executives.
Yeah.
So Tom Williams, I think, was like maybe the head of just this park.
Tom Williams, current title is chairman and chief executive officer of Universal Parks and Resorts.
And he serves on the NBCU executive committee.
So he's like he's like the Josh Demaro of Universal.
It seems that way.
But like, yeah, I think he was an executive when this this was open in 97 and now it's just like climbed the ranks and it's still still hanging in there.
Well, he's not the Josh Demaro unless like everybody's like getting wet for him.
That's been the we don't know what we're talking about.
There's this Disneyland executive who's like, I guess, kind of handsome.
And then just the day that Disneyland reopened, I just there was just all these thirsty posts for this guy.
It just really weirded me out.
Like, I just never seen it before.
I guess it just hit me in a wave.
Maybe there was like a lot of like discussion of this guy that I hadn't been privy to.
And then just I think something about the emotion of Disneyland's opening just then also it's just like in this guy, man, this guy.
I just want to like crawl up against his shoulder for a couple hours and just cry it out and he'll keep me warm with his strength.
It's so weird.
You just need two things.
You need a three piece suit and you need a tailor to fit it to you.
You know, and that's that's how you can do a transformative like reality TV transformation for yourself is get get a suit properly tailored.
Yeah.
And if I mean, if Josh, Josh, tomorrow when it took it to a new level, he could get a little cane and Dom DeLuis hat as well.
Oh, well, now now I'm on board.
People couldn't handle it too much.
Too much to be thirsty for.
Yeah.
Thomas L.
Williams is probably not in he's probably not daddy like Josh tomorrow is, I will say.
And no offense to Mr.
Williams.
I'm sure he's a very nice man.
To me, I don't know.
Bad looking guy.
He just looks like he's just a guy.
But Josh tomorrow is that nobody ascends to Josh tomorrow heights is what we learned.
We asked this question of can executive various Disney executives get it.
And I guess what we learned is he can definitely get it.
Are we going to do an episode of Josh tomorrow exclusively?
Maybe maybe the thing by asking the question, I feel like it becomes.
A guarantee you can, but I don't know this part out later.
I'd be sure I have no I have no problem with that.
It's because a name gets said.
Does it mean it has to be a full thing?
Maybe specific episodes for different people that were in the company at JPEG tomorrow.
Williams, we got a hit for a while.
Who's the new president of Ken Potts?
Potts.
Yeah, I thought it was Rock.
I could be wrong.
I've never rock is cool.
Rock is a cool last name, but that's that's the new president of Disneyland.
Man, that guy came on board like spring, like May 22, like first time to become the head of Disneyland.
He's a war time.
Wow.
Yeah.
So he's a war time president.
He's like, well, he's like Woodrow Wilson.
Yeah.
And FDR.
We were saying about Lucy Lawless.
I think.
Yeah, like I was just thinking about I forgot that that Zena spun off from Hercules.
And I feel like regardless of the stat of Hercules was the most popular show in the world.
I think Zena exceeded it in terms of pop culture relevancy.
And just, of course, everybody was so into her and into the character.
And he must have been so mad.
Sorbo must have been so mad that this spin off character, this woman even just takes the baton and just runs with it.
Like and then they're equal.
He's at that opening probably going like Hercules and Zena.
She's with Zena Hercules plus Zena.
If we have time, she was created from Hercules's rib.
She was taken out of just his rib.
She was lesser than Hercules.
Is that the same?
Is that one here?
Oh, OK.
Is that can?
Could be.
Let's say it is.
Let's say it happened in an episode.
They mixed because the bad guy in this attraction is Ares, the god of war, and Hera, I think that's right.
They're all just kind of mushing mythology with general fantasy stuff.
Well, there's in that to that end, I found an article saying that they there was a protest by a Hindu group that was upset because they just put Krishna in the show.
And like so like a whole here's this holy figure that's now just like, ha, it's me, Krishna.
Like, and I'm presented as like, you know, it's a cyclops and a giant and Krishna.
And there's the there was the quote in an article about this.
We are outraged.
How would Christians feel if a bunch of Hindus took Jesus Christ and filmed Zena punching him in the face?
Which I'm like, they shouldn't be mad.
Zena versus Jesus and sounds like the best episode ever.
I would be interested to watch that.
Yeah.
Obviously, Kevin would have been upset about that.
Oh, boy, boy, boy.
I'm sure he had a lot to say about Zena and her partner, Gabrielle, like a pretty I don't know if they intended initially for it to be a gay coded like characters.
But like by the end of the series, it's like they're all but saying it, which was kind of a big deal in the 90s because there wasn't that much representation.
You know, yeah, that was the I was reading this about I was reading about this Hindu controversy and I was like, yeah, that's not good.
They probably shouldn't have put Krishna in.
And then the article keeps going and like it implies that our faith is OK with homosexual relationships with Zena clearly is like, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Get away.
This is a 90s controversy where everyone is wrong.
All sides, all sides are incorrect.
Boo.
Yeah.
So I was thinking, too, about just like lawless versus sorbo.
Sorbo very much in the like wake of Schwarzenegger, where they're like, you know, let's take a guy who maybe and I don't even want this to sound like a diss on Schwarzenegger maybe isn't so versatile.
I do think Schwarzenegger is versatile in the way that like he plays himself, but he can go back.
He can do some comedy.
He can do whatever.
But he's a little limited, but it works really well.
And Schwarzenegger is great.
Sorbo doesn't really is not as good as Schwarzenegger.
Whereas like Lucy Lawless is very versatile, I think, as an actor, and she can pop up and you go, oh, she's good.
Yes, she was in Spartacus and she was in Parks and Rec.
And yeah, it was very funny.
Good on SNL, I recall.
Not to say they don't try with Sorbo, because this has come up more than once.
I brought it up more than once.
I'm jamming this fact and people just this thing where he, Kevin Sorbo, rode a horse through City Walk for the premiere of Call the Conqueror.
He did a full path, which you can look at in great Ron Gaia stock photos.
I just I just like this not knowing what Call the Conqueror is.
I like that you talk about like the natural like appeal of Schwarzenegger.
And then this guy, he's got like that brawny look, but then he just wears like boring golf shirts all the time.
He's riding a horse and yet he's just in.
He's wearing what Greg Norman would wear.
But I like seeing this horse pass by the Sun Coast and the most beautiful faces in the world sign and under King Kong.
And then there's another one of him also wearing a boring shirt at a premiere that he's outside of the Wetzel's Pretzels at City Walk, I believe with William Hurt.
Oh, yeah, William Hurt.
This is the only recorded instance, though, of Kevin Sorbo wearing a shirt untucked.
And he he shivers when he sees it.
The deviant lifestyle that I was once a part of.
Burn all the photographs, get the images.
Yeah, some of the other photos he just I've never seen a polo so like hard tucked into like pants.
And it's like, oh, man, like there's like clasps inside his pants to tie the shirt to.
Make sure it stays there.
He just seems so square and he seems like a guy at the office who's like really loud and someone told him he was funny once.
And it's like, oh, Jesus, that was the worst thing you could have done.
Whereas like Lucy Lawless just at scenes effortlessly funny and charming.
Who has Kevin Sorbo been on Huckabee or am I am I just wishing there is no way he has not been on Huckabee?
Probably statistically.
It's just a matter of if he just hasn't made the trip to Brands.
But are they doing have they been doing Zoom guests or not?
Or did Huckabee never shut down?
Do they just like maskless?
I thought you would know.
I sort of lost track.
I had a big Huckabee phase and then I sort of I lost track.
I need to go back and see what's going on in 2021.
And then God obviously distracted everybody.
That's that's the hot new show in town.
And I got you know, but Huckabee is the Carson.
You ultimately come back to Huckabee and I will, of course, here confirming that.
Yes, he has been on with his wife, Sam Sorbo.
Yes.
So I don't know that that clip has been I would I'll look at it later if it's worth watching.
We'll see if it's worth you know, I'm going to get ahead of the sorbometer going off so that it doesn't interrupt any thoughts since we're sort of in a sorbo run.
And I'll just read three other credits.
Detective Gullickson in Shadow Witness, Reginald Cash in Sam Steele and the Crystal Chalice and Drake Hunter in the Santa suit.
OK, wait a minute.
Now, imagine all those are pornos.
Yeah.
And I think it works exactly the same.
I think you go, yeah, yeah.
Shadow Witness is fine.
Kind of a sexy detective in that.
Yes, absolutely.
Reginald Cash and Sam Steele sort of like lazy, pornoy names.
Hard.
Yeah, like, yeah, you get it.
Crystal Chalice could be the name of an actress.
So absolutely.
Or a club like a sexual club.
A seedy club.
Yes, people could have sex in a giant Crystal Chalice.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
Welcome to the Crystal Chalice is what a character would say.
I also I don't think it would go against it to say to add another one, the movie Coffin, in which he plays Sean Justice.
Absolutely.
That could be perhaps involving fucking in a coffin.
Now that's a coffin challenge.
How long can you last in the coffin?
Well, the coffin stands not built for that.
So careful it could collapse on you.
That is absolutely, by the way, happened at a Six Flags.
I think we speculate it whether someone like killed some time by pleasuring themselves in the coffin.
Yeah.
But I mean, like, you know, like somebody snuck in like you had like a date who snuck into the coffin in the middle of the night.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
The 4 a.
m.
Yeah.
The shift change like, OK, quick, quick knock like a knock at your coffin door.
Hey, quick, let me in.
This breaks the rules.
I won't win that six hundred dollars.
No, I got to be in here for a week and get six hundred dollars.
OK, well, so what else about all this?
That's a lot of well, it'll be more sorbo.
But so I the one thing I like, I they the opening day ceremonies, they use swords.
They're doing the swinging sword thing again.
Lucy Lawless looks much cooler doing it than Kevin Sorbo.
Kevin Sorbo almost looks bored swinging his sword around with a kind of wrist motion.
And they unveiled the big sword sign, which looks pretty good.
But then I had a hard time finding the marquee for this attraction, like a good quality photo of it.
But it looks like they could not have spent less money on.
Oh, yeah.
Signage.
That is so trashy.
I remember I never saw this, but I went to the park around this time and I feel like the sign put me off like these.
That is a lot of clashy logo, like kind of low rent comic.
But those logos look like like logos from Christian comic books.
Yeah, that looks exactly right.
And that building, too.
I mean, they barely took like change the front of it from saying Murder, She Wrote Mystery Theatre to when it was close to closing.
I guess they changed the name from Murder, She Wrote Mystery Theatre to Murder, She Wrote post production, which is a real downgrade.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
But then they jazzed up, they jazzed it up.
They got rid of murder, sure.
And that boring title.
And they put this in Hercules and Zena, Wizards of the Screen, which is more exciting than a lot of what happened in their show.
What does it mean?
Who are the Wizards?
Hercules and Zena or the people or like the the ADR operator?
Who's the wizard?
Yeah, yeah, because everyone's kind of doing a bit like the director and the sound guy and the graphics guy.
They're all kind of playing like the kooky Hollywood versions of those roles.
Yeah, but why?
Yeah, Wizard.
Why not like Warriors of the Screen?
Because they're not they're warriors, at least in like Wizards isn't even a thing you truly associate with, like the post production crew of a TV show.
They're very good.
There's a lot of talent in that.
Of course.
Area, but Wizards, I'm not sure.
Yeah.
So, yeah, that is confusing.
Very strange title.
You know, even before we talk about what happens in the show, it might be a good thing to play.
Well, first for me to click away from some pop up ads that came from me trying to find if there was any riffraff porn hold off on that.
It was a little too distracting for me to not mention Cliffhanger for later.
But now let me play this Universal Studios ad.
And so here's what they framed this show as.
Here we go.
You control their fate.
You decide their destiny.
Universal Studios Florida introduces Hurtleys and Xena, Wizards of the Screen.
Come have a brawl at Universal's newest attraction.
And here's another new attraction for Florida residents.
Save $10 from now.
But the pretty dramatic.
You control their fate.
You decide their destiny.
And then I don't know if we're spoiling it by saying that by controlling fates and destinies, we mean you get to see what it's like to ADR sound for actors and create sound effects.
And you learn how green screens work is what they're trying to say.
You control their destiny from a post house in the way they are portrayed and heard.
You control their fate in terms of is your dad in a funny costume going to appear in front of a field or an outer space?
What will you control his chroma fate?
Because this is sort of a, I mean, it's basically like a reskin of the Murder She Wrote attraction, which as alluded to in that boring title was about post production.
There's a scene for Murder She Wrote where there is no sound and the audience members have to make the sound.
It's like the Harry and the Hendersons thing that was in Hollywood.
We just talked about all this with new friend Moe, Maura Quirk.
This is a show that she was part of, the Murder She Wrote version of what she did in the park.
And I don't, as I said to her, I don't remember that show very well.
We haven't done an episode about it yet.
But that's sort of the gist, right?
There's the like, hear a clang on this thing to make the sword banging sound effects and that kind of stuff.
Yeah, and that's what I saw what I was talking about earlier is there's a clip of this show, Hercules and Zena with a kid just banging on a pipe with a wrench just to make a noise for ADR, what ADR would be like.
Yeah.
And yeah, that was the same deal.
If they wanted like, I think I christened this area like Grandparents Rest Alley.
They really should have replaced the Murder She Wrote Mystery Theater with the Diagnosis Murdery Mr.
Theater.
Oh man.
Or the Marshall Law starring Sammo Hung Action Theater or something like that.
Like every Walker, Walker, Texas Ranger.
Yeah, we're Walker.
Like Hercules and Zena is pretty dynamic replacement.
A bit too, yes, a bit too lively, especially when things from the show start happening in the theater.
It gets a tad loud, I would say, when there's lightning and magic going on.
How are you supposed to take a nap during that?
Yeah, that's a good point.
I mean, I guess Walker was a little more high.
That was a bad, I should have said like Father Dowling or another one of an old sitcom and like an elderly sitcom actor solves murders every week, which is my favorite genres of shows.
Well, you know those theme park sinners are averse to anything stinking of religion, as Kevin Sorbo would probably tell you.
Sure.
That's a good point.
It's so perverse in Orlando.
Let me tell you, it's just a they've lost their values there.
They want you now you pay an amount of money in the morning and then you just get meals all day and that's gluttony.
These meal plans are gluttony.
Kevin Sorbo should reboot Father Dowling for a new generation.
What's Father Dowling again?
Don't do Father Dowling dirty like that.
Sorry, Father Dowling was what's his name from happy days?
Dad from happy days and I'm losing.
Tom Bosley.
Tom Bosley, thank you.
And he was like a priest.
The podcast where sometimes two people happily say in unison, Tom Bosley, I think it's Tom Bosley.
And that's shameful that I didn't know that.
I've said Tom Bosley like with no thought before on this podcast.
So I know Tom Bosley.
You're really owed.
I think for that we have to do one of those scolding.
Michael, we got to give you the full name to really make you feel bad about it.
I do deserve it.
And I will tell the priest about it on Sunday.
But Father Dowling would solve murders.
I mean, he was like a priest and he would always kind of get embroiled in something.
And a little fun fact, I lived in an apartment owned by one of the cast members of Father Dowling 10 years ago.
I forgot about that.
Which one are you allowed to say?
Do you remember the name?
Why can't I think of his name?
I got to look him up.
I don't know.
Should I say his name?
You don't have to say it.
It doesn't matter.
There's more fun facts.
I'll tell you off the air.
Sure.
That's for another tier of Patreon.
Learn who owns the building from Father Dowling that Mike once lived in.
That's an extra $100 a month, everyone.
You just get the name.
It's like John Grayson.
Okay, great.
Now I know.
Okay, so the show.
It is hard to find footage.
It is hard to find like a full run of the show.
It was one of those where you move from room to room and see different steps of the process.
It took me going really deep into it.
There's a very good video about all this made by Yesterworld, correct?
Yes.
In his sources, there's a video that's pulled from some family's entire vacation footage.
You have to go deep into that to see, oh, there was a thing where there was like a puppet.
A bunch of kids all manipulate a dragon puppet.
Here you do the eyebrows and you do the arms and you wiggle them around.
That seems fun.
It's a good looking puppet.
It's a good practical thing.
It seems like they pulled that part off pretty well, at least.
The puppet was good.
I remember I think I was standing in front of it at some point like this child that I pulled from a video.
And I kept looking back of like, I do not trust that puppet.
Although at the end, it's CG in the footage and it looks bad.
They keep cutting back and forth between the bad CG and the good looking puppet, I think.
Pretty awful CG throughout this whole series and that scene, yes.
It all culminates in a six minute sequence custom shot by the makers of Hercules and Xena.
Where everybody gives it their all and it's like the show.
I bet if you're a fan of the shows, then like, oh, this is an episode I can only watch here.
That's cool.
But that's CGI.
Oh my God.
I think that's what it was like in the show too, in the real show.
Yeah, that's why even like the bigger budget like Battlestar Galactica stuff, I always have a hard time watching.
Like really heavy genre TV shows because I'm like, oh, these effects are going to age really fast.
You're talking about like the Cylons and the newer Battlestar?
Like in the new, yeah, like any sci-fi on TV, like the stuff that imply that like Twilight Zone has aged better because they just imply everything or it's all practical makeup.
Right.
I see what you're saying.
Yeah, as opposed to Stargate SG-1, you know?
Yeah, it depends.
It depends.
There's a mixed bag.
There's like, there's sweet spots for CG where I feel like it was like good for two years and like the mid 90s and all of a sudden it's bad for four years.
And then you get like pockets and you go, oh, that looks pretty good or whatever.
Like, but you never know.
You never know what you're going to get.
Some of it looks at first Steven Summer's Mummy.
Yeah, it still looks pretty good.
Second Steven Summer's Mummy with the scorpion.
Oh man.
This is where they're like, oh no.
And it's like, oh geez Louise.
I forgot that the show we were referencing earlier with Sebastian Jackal was Deadly Game on UPN, which also had some real bad like CGI transformation stuff and it was like very internet bay.
It was like in the net.
You were going in the net.
Oh, well, that I love.
I love or if you're going, if you see the physical internet that I will give a million passes to the hackers kind of internet.
Yeah, fair game.
Let's let's talk a little bit about what you what you did and what like what you wore.
First of all, because you just pulled up a photo of some audience volunteers.
Can we describe what you're what you had to put on?
Well, yeah, it was like a helmet.
I think they gave you like a cap.
They gave you like an under layer, which was probably the only thing they washed like a white essentially white sheet and like a white skull cap.
And then they put a helmet on you and they put like like armor and chainmail with like fringe fur at the bottom.
And then you would stand behind a blue block in front of a blue screen.
So that way they could make your lower half a horse and make the background like the the field, the empty field where the battle is happening.
Now, how did that work?
Was it did you just have to stay very still?
And then there is a like how much is that bottom half really doing that?
Well, it's not that your bottom half is just hidden behind the block.
Like you didn't really have to do anything with your bottom half because the horses were on the screen.
But it's but it is like is it like a digital lower half horse body or is it on?
OK, yeah, it here you can see from this angle.
I'll share some of these pictures so people know we're talking about.
So you're totally obscured.
Very much like here's a big blue block or bench or something.
Yeah, they tell you in one of the videos you drape your little like your shirt or whatever over the block to make it look a little bit more realistic.
That that's part of you.
It like blends in better if there's not a hard break between the block in your body.
That's a little tidbit.
That's a good little special effects.
Sure, it was good.
And I think we were given or maybe one guy was given a hollow crossbow, hollow plastic like crossbow looking thing because it's fired in the footage.
And you're just he was just like holding it or we were all holding it.
And then they just want us to wave at the end and then everyone laughs.
Mm hmm.
Right.
Yeah.
So you remember Jason doing it.
How do you start?
You know, did you feel were you like this is awesome.
I'm a star.
I'm a you like a Mark Holberg at the end of Boogie Nights.
I well I was a 12 year old boy.
Right.
But so I guess the equivalent of that, I did feel like like I was clearly the most excited to be doing this compared to the the adult man and adult woman also doing it.
Hit to cut you off there.
We got the sorbometer going off.
You're all in it.
Make it fast.
These don't always have to be belabored.
OK, so let's read a few credits.
Pastor Dave in the sparrows nesting Pastor Matthews in Confessions of a Prodigal Son and Gojan Pie in Mythica, the Dark Spore.
I think it's a jolt of energy.
Back to his fantasy roots.
Mythica, the Dark Spore.
I think Mythica is a series.
I think he played Gojan Pie a number of times.
Well, you gotta see what he's up to, you know.
And a number of that was a couple pastors in a row.
Those were like next to each other in his filmography.
I'll try to find.
Oh, he's going to be in a movie coming up called The Pastor where he plays Big John.
Lots to look forward to.
Anyway, please continue.
It's reset.
I'll talk to you in 15 minutes.
Oh, OK.
Yeah.
So I mean, going room by room, I think they dress.
I don't think dressed us in the last room and we kept walking or they dressed us before the last room and we kept walking around.
But like they highlighted each technology individually of like, here's how we do sound effects.
Here's how we overlay someone's face onto a monster.
Here's how we'll put you guys in.
And then at the end, it all comes together.
Right.
And when you were seeing it was you were a kid who liked watching special features, I assume.
I mean, I guess that wasn't around yet, but like you were a kid who liked movie, the magic of the movies.
So was that like your first taste of like, wow, like this is what the lights are like and I can see how the sausage is made, so to speak.
Well, this is the first I think I got so close to it because I had been to Universal a few times at this point and I was the kid who it's like, hey, I got to I can't.
Can we make sure we're home?
There's a making of like face off that I really want to watch.
And that was like, I feel like I did not see a lot of I went to the movies pretty regularly, but I think I was pretty my parents were pretty strict about PG 13.
Right.
Like we would go to PG 13 if my dad came, but it was like, well, you're not 13 yet.
And I'm like, why are you buying that?
Like, what do you think's in this?
So but I would want any making up like I would always watch those.
So but yes, I was thrilled to be by like a C stand or like, right.
That's yes, that's that's what I was hoping an apple like my my dear set friend, Apple boxes, hollow wooden boxes that actors stand on to appear very tall that all actors stand on unless you're Mike's height.
Right.
Very well brought up to pretty sure you see a lot of Apple boxes for on guts.
Sure.
So yes, I stood on any sort of combination of like, get a couple more Apple boxes under him.
I always remember in these kind of shows that moment where it's when it's if it's somebody you know, then they disappear for a little bit and they come back in a funny costume, the nerves that you have while they're gone and the relief when they return.
But the mockery of the silly thing that they're wearing, this stuff always works.
These things are just caked.
It's a really good format.
I remember I remember when I saw my mom do the soap opera show, I was a little disturbed because I was like that.
Those are again, those like those aren't her clothes.
She is acting different and I know this isn't real, but I don't like this.
Thought she had been brainwashed.
Yes, is she maybe she's been like lying to me this whole time and she's actually like about to pull a gun like she's been a like a fur coat wearing gun wielder.
This is the real her finally.
Yeah.
See now this is the point at my age where I was like, I have to go backstage to get in costume and then I come out on stage in costume or right.
Mom, can we go to Blockbuster so I can rent singing in the rain?
I don't want to go to the beach today.
Sunset Boulevard is on Turner Classic movies.
Yeah, 98.
I would not have had the I'm talking about maybe early 90s when I was in that mind mindset.
But yeah, 98.
I would have understood.
I was in the seventh or eighth grade play at that point and I knew.
Yeah, and that was that was this is all a result of Universal Studios and MGM Studios warping my brain so that the one vacation ruined the rather summer vacations because they're like Jason's watching old movies again.
We have to go.
We have to go to a family party.
Come on, man.
The old that's what I don't get is how did you veer to the 40s and the 30s?
That does naturally happen.
I just love I love Gene Kelly.
I love Gene Kelly.
I love just big characters and Norma Desmond in Sunset Boulevard.
There's no one bigger.
And yeah, I even at that time, I liked like old detectives like old CD stuff, you know.
I mean, and also like you were born like mentally in the 40s, too.
I feel like there was some sort of like mix up that happened with like brains and the time based on continuum or something.
Well, the thing I realized when I was older, too, is that all the weirdos making children's entertainment liked these old movies and would find a way to do like a detective parody in like step by step or Ninja Turtles or something.
And then when I would get a chance to get the actual thing, it was referencing.
I was like, well, I'm already familiar with all of this crap, you know, and I love it.
Yeah, I get that.
Yeah, that makes sense.
We all had to sit through a lot of like jokes about dames and gams and the thing where like the the narration then like somebody hears the narration.
Like, what was that?
Oh, so you can hear that.
Like there was a lot of deconstruction of film noir tropes.
And I'm like, I don't know what the film noir I've seen 20 times more deconstruction than the real thing.
I mean, yeah, yeah.
By the time I got to it, I had seen a lot of deconstructions.
There's multiple Maltese Falcon parodies.
When I was six years old, like there's a Turtles episode called the Maltese Hamster.
And I think there's like a Ren and Stimpy comic I read and it was another Maltese Falcon.
And I was like, what is like I was actively like confused.
But later on, you're like, oh, OK, it's that 40 year old movie, which is funny because of those kinds of movies, the Maltese Falcon is very stiff.
Like it's very it's carried by Humphrey Bogart.
And is Peter Laurie in it?
I think like it's kind of carried by the actors.
But like compared to like out of the past or the big sleep, those are much more dynamic movies that seem more what we consider modern, I think, at least.
Peter Laurie is indeed in Maltese.
OK, yeah.
And that's another guy who's in like every other Looney Tunes.
There's a Peter.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like trope or character.
Yeah, constant cartoon Peter Laurie.
So yeah, I just said Ren and Stimpy and Stimpy, the Martin's voice.
Yeah, the Marx Brothers come up in a lot of that stuff.
Yeah, who I loved.
I love the Marx Brothers.
I don't care about the three stooges.
I never got into Laurel and Hardy.
But even as a kid, I loved the Marx Brothers.
Or I can't figure out how to transition other than to say, yeah, we can't get out of this.
Please, we can't get out.
I well, you want to talk about what it culminates in that now an episode comes to life like the fruits of our labor have had.
We filmed the Jason's as the centaurs.
We've got our pre-taped material and now we're going to drop it into an episode of Hercules and Xena.
But then the episode comes to life and there seems to be a moment where like things start happening in the room.
A bunch of lightning shoots out of the screen and then it's almost like you know, like you almost do with this at this point in universal history.
I want to say like, just don't even we know you don't have to say it because this one just really lays on thick.
They just say the line.
This isn't one of our special effects.
This is real.
You've been doing Ghostbusters for seven years now.
We know we know.
And you're also this is also a much lazier iteration of it.
We get something goes wrong.
I think one of the screens Hera is in the real with the real world.
And then she's like starts making things happen in the soundstage and you know, the sword falls out of the screen.
They got to toss back in the screen.
That stuff's fun.
It's fun to see here here.
Yeah.
An object goes from our world into Kevin Sorbo's hands.
I and yeah, magic affects people again.
It's like hard to there's not the best full.
Here's the here's a giant video of this, but you can piece it together.
Yeah, it's all it's all stuff that would have been like fun if I was little, but I think I would have been a little it would have been a sleepier show.
If I was, yeah, I don't know, 14 or 15.
I wouldn't have not enjoyed it, but yeah.
Well, and we're maybe at the point where do you just want to do a Hercules and Zena stunt show and not 100% like completely?
There was already that question maybe in the early 90s a little and by now by the late 90s for sure.
We want to just see action and not like so here you have to hear.
Let's queue up the tape and you got to splice it.
Make sure to splice that tape exactly on that at point you want.
Yeah, I think we talked about this before another show.
I'm sure is that like yeah, back in the 90s, there was still a little more mystery.
And now it's like you can edit a movie on your computer like so who like that's a the whole thing has been a bit demystified.
Yeah, and it's like now we're just skipping separate editing procedure.
It's yes, that's true, which so you know, mostly there's not mostly these sorts of things are gone.
I'm trying to think is anything else.
Is there anything oddly late that is teaching us about stuff that we don't that is no longer relevant in terms of that is a good question.
I haven't done the tram tour in a long time, so I don't really I don't really know what's going on in the trim.
I mean, the special effects stage is still in Universal Hollywood.
Yeah, and then like animal actors is like like kind of do like a behind the scenes, but there's action in it.
Yeah, they've kept the more practical stuff like light a guy on fire.
Right.
Bird of prey takes a dollar out of your hand like that stuff.
I think people always like seeing, you know, because you can't see it in your daily life.
Yes, but there's yeah, there's no there's no theater show where they show you what it's like to audition for a role in a movie or TV show.
Yeah, yeah.
I've seen it pointed out.
Was this a comment in our group or just somewhere in general like theme park chatter that if there's going to be this kind of thing like that, I feel like there are still the studio parks and at least within the world of Disney.
That like one of the few things that's come up in the recent past that genuinely is interesting like oh, that's how they do it is the Mandalorian and those crazy realistic.
We've those are cool.
And if there was a we have this theory, I don't remember this came from the idea that like if there was some show or they could replace something that was a little more ailing with, you know, here, let's show you how let's make a Mandalorian scene on the spot by just pulling up these backgrounds, changing the lighting and look.
It looks exactly like the like just yeah, these digital backgrounds they use genuinely.
I think that stuff is incredibly cool.
And there's maybe a little meat on that bone.
If they're if they were to ever do some sort of Mandalorian making of experience.
I don't know that we are.
We came up with that.
But that is yeah, if you've ever you haven't seen that go on Disney Plus and there's the making of Mandalorian and basically it's like instead of just putting a blue or green screen behind the actor.
It's this crazy like 360 theater that has like high def.
I guess it's an unreal engine, which is what powers a lot of video games basically.
But it can be real time manipulated and rendered.
So like almost everything on Mandalorian in the background is a screen, but it looks good because there's depth.
There's like an actual like depth between the screen in the background and the actor as opposed to green screen, which like if you watch the prequels, it's got like a there's a weird feeling in it because they're really like so close to the background that's supposed to like stretch out far.
And for the actors, they're able to actually be in the place, which which helps.
Yeah, it gives them a little bit of a vibe.
There's like practical pieces of ships and stuff when they're getting off things.
But like like armory swords get actual reflections of the lighting of why it makes so much sense.
It's very it's yeah, it's really cool.
And it's a shame only the most expensive shows in the world can possibly use this technology green screen.
We can do in our backyard.
The this is this you need a lot of money.
You need big.
Yeah, yeah.
All of my I feel like I know multiple friends who have a green screen and it's like shoved next to the it's rolled up next to the toilet or next to the toilet.
The washing machine in the unfinished basement or something like that's how cheap green screening is now.
Obviously, eight K or the K plus or whatever that kind of projection and real time manipulation is super expensive, which is probably why they haven't like duplicated it for three different theme parks or whatever.
Yeah, yeah.
But but so but so this thing, it's sort of, you know, it was like a relevant thing to introduce.
You can have your press event with Sorbo and Lawless and they're big right now.
And that's in 97.
But by 2000, it already feels a tad stale.
I feel like the tide turned quickly on this one.
I saw an article where a universal spokesman said to the Orlando Sentinel in 1999, quote, It's the kind of show you can change without the audience asking where it went.
Yeah, pretty cold.
Yeah.
Yeah, really?
And I alluded to this earlier.
So the building, it closed in February 2000 and then the building sat empty until Horror Nights 2004.
And then after, like at some point, the city came in and condemned the building.
They said, You can't do anything, but like you can't use this building.
Like, you know, I don't know.
But like, eventually it was demolished.
And that's where Transformers is now in Florida.
That was just that was some Hollywood canceling or some Orlando, some fake Hollywood canceling.
They just knew Sorbo was in there and they had them on.
This was early cancel culture.
Oh, okay.
But how often does like some of the most
It was called condemning culture back then.
Oh, and here we go.
Speak.
I said Sorbo again and that's Sorbometer.
Let me go to it quickly.
Okay, let's see.
Dodge Davis in Tommy and the Cool Mule.
Bird Tatums in an episode of Psych called Bounty Hunters exclamation point.
So that's more, he's not
That's actually pretty good.
Yeah.
No, Psych is legit.
He hasn't fully made the switch to his corner yet.
And Mr.
Phoenix in Bitch Slap.
Whoa, wait a minute.
That's bold.
I think that also he's maybe not fully
Yeah, he hasn't been kicked out.
Lucy Lawless is also in that.
Interesting.
That might be some like Cameo Fest put together like Movie 43 or something.
Well, he's elsewhere in his credits around this time.
Meet the Spartans.
He's in Meets the Spartans.
That's a movie movie kind of
And he's in An American Carol, the weird creepy right wing parody.
Sure, the Farley brother, right?
With the Farley brother as documentary filmmaker Michael Malone.
Michael Moore stand in.
Who's taken to ground zero by a ghost played by country singer Trace Atkins.
No!
Have you ever seen that?
Or it's like he's in a church and like, what's all this in this building?
Dust?
You gotta clean this place up.
No, it's not dust.
Trace Atkins opens the doors and they're at.
Oh my goodness.
It's a jaw dropper.
Kelsey Grammer is in it.
And that was like they had not yet figured out the bizarre like the Christian movie Closet.
This was like in theaters.
This was a
They made the push.
It's by a Zucker.
Right.
Aye, aye, aye, aye.
Yeah.
Well, I really quickly was the cool
What was the cool mule about?
Was it a Christmas story?
Yeah, let's check that out.
Tommy and the cool mule.
Yeah, because I know one cool mule who was like hanging out by a manger and then stuff started happening.
Yeah, that makes me think of the Troy McClure movie Gladys the Groovy Mule.
He kind of is.
He's a
He's our Christian.
He's our Troy McClure.
Oh my God, he's real Troy McClure.
He's just
But he's not as fun.
He's got
He's like Troy McClure with an agenda.
Is Kevin Sorbo bad for many aquariums?
Could be.
Maybe that's why he's not allowed in Hollywood.
It's not his political views.
Tommy and the cool mule.
Here's a really horrendous poster I'm showing you guys.
I like how these two actors aren't allowed to have their full faces shown.
They are mostly covered up by a mule head.
It says, not your average talking mule.
So we at least know that about it.
Ice-T is the voice of a mule.
Yeah, like my computer is not
Is fighting back against
Yeah, mine is also not
I'm looking at it on the internet, but for some reason it's not working.
I see it though.
Ice-T is in it and he's the voice of the mule?
Yeah, maybe.
Jackie A, the voice of the mule.
You know, I think this movie is a trick.
I think that it has a fun title and a fun cover and you think that it's a fun silly movie perhaps where a mule farts or something.
But then the description is, Tommy Braxton's father goes to war and never returns, forcing Tommy to become the man of the house and support his mom and sister.
That is not
That doesn't sound fun.
No, I think it's a serious
I think they canker-rejected it.
I think they decided to make it a silly animal movie in editing because it was too boring.
Well, here I wanted to show
I have
This is in
I found it in one video about this ride.
So this is a promotional item from Universal at the time.
And they used to be
In the Michael Eisner era of Disney, they would talk a lot about, well, our idea with movies
You know, as Disney was trying to get back on its feet, we got to hit a bunch of singles and doubles.
We're not trying to hit home runs or grand slams.
And it certainly seems like after the grand slam of T2 3D, you get
Here are the new thrills and all new excitement that Universal Studios Florida had.
Twister ride it out.
Hercules and Xeno, Wizards of the Screen, Universal Studios Islands of Adventure preview center.
So I'm going to go ahead and say the preview center was the most dynamic of those three options.
Well, to you, this was like
This was your church, the preview center.
Well, that's true.
But like that is the double, I think, of the singles of
I mean, Twister ride it out.
Certainly a much better experience than Hercules and Xeno, Wizards of the Screen.
But my affection for Hercules and Xena is because I got to do it.
You lived it.
Had you not lived it, how would you feel?
I wrote the movies.
You wrote the movies.
Yeah, we should say so this
Yeah, I guess the building got condemned.
They couldn't use it anymore.
So they couldn't even just put another attraction in this soundstage building.
They had to just tear it down entirely, which they did and replaced the whole area with Transformers the Ride.
So if you're in Universal Orlando now, that's what's there.
So look at it now and point out before you get on Transformers and have your adventure with the AllSpark, turn to whoever you're with and say, you know, once this was where the Wizards of the Screen rained and they will stare at you and consider leaving the park entirely.
But then maybe you'll just go in and have fun on the ride.
Is it Wizards because there was magic stuff in the shows?
I guess, but they weren't
They weren't
I'm sure they fought a Wizard or they befriended a Wizard on episodes.
Constantly, seemingly.
Yeah, but they weren't Wizards.
So I just don't know why
Not in this show.
There's not a Wizard.
Hercules is a God.
Well, the crew who makes all your favorite Hollywood TV and movies.
They're the real Wizards of the Screen.
That's right.
Look, I agree with that, of course.
That's what Universal was there to teach us and to teach them that those tributes are more important than watching a show that is full of kicking and punching and swinging around on ropes.
You need to learn what ADR stands for, what looping is.
I mean, in reality, they should have like, at the time, they should have been showing you how to use that, what was it called?
The Thompson's Guide, that old giant phone book size map that showed you every street in LA or whatever.
Or like, here's how a PA wraps a napkin around a can of Diet Coke to hand to this movie star.
Don't look them in the eye.
They hate that.
They should have done more PA tips, more tips for burgeoning PAs.
Yeah, well, that's how the real stuff
I cannot
I've lost track of how many people I've read about, like, and they love Diet Coke with a napkin wrapped around it.
It's like, what?
So their hands don't get what?
What the fuck, man?
This is another Jim Belushi tale, I think.
I think that's what it's about.
Probably.
There should be one where like, there should be a Halloween Horror Nights maze where you have to
The like, final room is that there's a guy playing Scott Rudin, movie producer.
Jesus.
And he like, screams at you and throws stuff, and it's like the scariest thing.
Just repurpose, like, if one of the King Kongs that got removed, just like, reskin it.
Keep, like, the giant speakers, because you'll need that to be the amplification of a Scott Rudin scream.
Yeah, exactly.
And he has banana breath, too, for some reason.
Really scary.
I think that was on the list of places that took interns when I was doing internship, like
And I was just like, on paper, it's like, well, they've made some cool stuff.
And it's like, oh, thank God I dodged that bullet, or dodged that binder hurl across the room.
Yeah, literally dodge.
Yeah, I think that's what the job would have been.
Closing thoughts, have we missed anything?
RIP, or Killy Xena?
Yeah, I
It was past its time for this type of attraction.
I wish it was more of a stunt show.
I wish it, yeah, ended up being like, more kitschy and fun, like some of the episodes, or most of the episodes.
But yeah, it ended up
It was stuck.
It had to fit into the framework of the previous murder she wrote.
And I feel like the IP of Hercules and Xena then wasn't done full justice, because it was trying to fit, you know, a square peg in a slightly round hole.
The lawsuits of them trying to get owed residuals or owed TV money kind of helped wind up a lot of Hercules and Xena.
There were Hercules and Xena walk-around characters for a while too.
Mm-hmm, right.
And yeah, so
And I'm sure they, by the way, they probably deserve that money.
Oh yeah.
Talked a lot of residuals.
A lot of talk about residuals.
And yeah.
Yeah.
So even despite Kevin Sorbo, he did get his money, right?
He got more money, I believe.
I think they probably settled the issue.
Yeah, I don't think they did.
I don't think it was a successful lawsuit, actually.
I don't think they got what they were looking for, but it might have gotten something.
So yeah, anyway.
Well, you know, I guess in the end, Hercules and Xena did not get one more round like the movie One More Round, where Sorbo plays Billy Jack Taylor.
But will there be other great attractions based on our favorite TV shows in the future?
You'd have to hope that there is, for such a thing, that there is a Hope Bridge, like the film where Kevin Sorbo plays Eric.
Hope Bridge.
Oh my God.
Can we, can there be like, can they make rides or experiences and put it in the Ark encounter for some of these movies?
Oh yeah.
That would be a great, perfect tie in and get a little more, yeah, get some new attractions going to pique people's interest to get back to the Ark encounter.
Welcome to the, oh yes, go ahead.
I was going to say, here's how we filmed this scene in silhouette.
So Kirk Cameron could be shown kissing a woman on screen.
That is actually his wife, not the actress he acted opposite this movie, because he refused to kiss anyone who's not his wife.
And that was okay.
You know, that wasn't a massive pain in the ass that goes against most filmmaking rules.
But okay, here's how we did it.
Majority of our budgets is to create false kisses between, to remove married partners.
And that's, and that's, that's what you've learned from the Bernie the Dolphin 2 Wizards of the Screen experience.
And good job to our volunteer Jason for his portrayal of Winston Mills.
Thanks for participating.
I was an allegory for Barabbas, the unrepentant, crucified.
He plays King Herod in something.
That's a good reel.
Yeah.
That's a meaty role to sink your teeth into.
In a list of otherwise, I think Italian actors.
I think this is, this is an Italy Italian shot film.
There it is.
Check out the Penitent Thief with Sorbo as King Herod.
You survived podcast The Ride.
Yeah.
So, so much homework.
You know, obviously go out and rent and buy all of the films that I mentioned and put money in Sorbo's pocket being that he's missed out on his residuals.
But if you have any left at the end of the day, keep it tuned here to podcast The Ride,
the second gate for three bonus episodes every month.
And oh, that's right.
I knew I had something to go out on, which will be the sounds of Mike and Jason reacting to a admittedly adorably drawn gang bang between Riff Raff and other members.
That's Top Cat.
Yeah, that's Top Cat.
Oh, it is.
But Riff Raff's over there.
He's over on the right.
Jason might say there was no porn to picture of Riff Raff.
Who's that woman that Riff Raff is making love to?
Oh my God.
Top Cat has his tongue out.
He's in ecstasy.
Oh God.
This is going to be a recurring feature, I think, where we are 34 something midway through an episode and go out on the shocking reveal, but not tweet the photo.
That's not what a cat's genitals look like.
That is not accurate to that.
I think a cat's genitals might be grosser though is the problem.
Yeah, you might be right about that.
I guess if these are like half man, half cat or anthropomorphic cats, maybe.
I mean, I don't know what their anatomy looks like, but I will say this is, I could do an hour on what's wrong with this.
But pretty accurate drawings though of Riff Raff and Top Cat's hats.
I would know the hat anywhere.
Credit where it's due.
Cover the bottom of it with your hands and then just look at the hats and then you've just got a well-drawn series of hats.
It is.
Look, I agree that the hats are well done.
Maybe we'll tweet that, just the top half of this Cadillac cat gangbang photo.
Swap.
I don't know.
Top Cat has his own gang of guys too that are not around here.
So it's like the two leaders of like a bunch of cats getting together and like swapping wives maybe?
This is a cat key party.
You think that's Top Cat's love interest?
Yeah, maybe.
Yeah.
I don't recognize her.
Why didn't they invite the Heathcliff gang and why didn't they invite Oliver and company?
The Cadillac cats?
Oliver's a child.
Yeah, yeah.
Sorry.
Dodger, maybe Dodger.
He's a dog.
He's been with Oliver and Company in 20 years.
Alright, let him grow.
Dodger is in the corner watching.
Licking his lips.
Oh, he's a
Yeah.
Oh, no.
And you know what he's saying?
Why should I worry?
Why should I care?
Well, he always says that.
It sounds like Dodger.
Alright, let's get out of here.
This is all I talk to you next time.
Goodbye.