Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the second gate, the entertainment capital of listener supported
podcast feeds.
I'm Jason Sheridan here as always with Mike Carlson.
I am here, yes.
This is the entertainment capital, for sure.
That's right.
And Scott Geradner?
Burbank, the podcast capital of us, at least.
That of course, phrase is a reference to Universal Studios Hollywood, the entertainment capital
of Los Angeles, a marketing term that they got and went with and went, everyone went,
okay, sure.
But Universal Hollywood, a place recently reopened that at this point in time, we've
all been back to, we've all returned to the entertainment capital.
Yes, we've all been back to ride the movies, as I was saying, on the main feed.
It was great.
It's great to be back.
Great to be back doing, great to be back going into Target also.
But I don't want to dwell on that element.
I feel like I'm talking too much about that.
I just want to say, yes, it's good to be back to the place where the bass is pumping, you're
on the starway, the Bart man is roaring in the speakers.
Hit songs from 2000 to 2005 are in the air, which is a more recent sense of pop culture
than Disney has, but I don't want them to necessarily.
Did Will.
i.
am do a song with Iggy Azalea that we haven't heard about?
Yes, I think so, but it's playing at Universal somewhere.
You've never heard it before, but it's there and it's 10 years old.
Universal exclusive, yeah.
Somehow it was number one for seven weeks, but you can't find anyone who can sing it,
knows it, knows a lyric.
It's called Come and Get It.
Will.
i.
am featuring Iggy Azalea.
Iggy Azalea and DJ Snake and Lauv.
Yeah, all those people are on it.
They're all on it.
They're other kids.
We've never heard it, but all of their children are going to go to college on the residuals
of Universal Studios Hollywood getting exclusive rights to the song.
Yes.
You know we got to come and get it.
Get, get, get, get, get, get it.
Yeah, that's a sample directly from that song.
That's directly, yeah.
So.
Grab a glass and wha-wha-whet it.
Ha!
As good as Will.
i.
am's raps are.
And also Plea, I don't know if it's been scrubbed from the internet with the essential death
of the company, but the Will.
i.
am Donald Trump rap from Funny or Die, one of the Funny or
Die greats, highly recommended.
Did you guys ever see that one?
I don't think I did.
Where he raps like, Donald Trump said, grab you by the wheel, and then it's a cat.
Rawr.
He stressed his trump.
And then he's like, you know, he's doing a cocky trump rap and then it's, and then like
record scratch stop and he steps out as himself.
All right.
I think it's obvious.
I do not look anything like Donald Trump.
But the other thing it's obvious, Donald Trump does not look anything like a president.
And then then he keeps going like that for two minutes.
Wow, really?
It's incredible.
I've never seen this.
I believe you that that is real, but I would also believe if you were doing a long con
on us and at the end of the episode, you told us like, hey, by the way, that I totally made
that up.
It's not real.
You never know when it comes to Funny or Die, plus helping Democrats win elections, any
things up in the air.
Win elections.
Any celebrity.
Oh, yes.
Right.
Trying to help Democrats.
Yeah, yeah.
I forgot how that election turned out.
That's right.
They lost.
Hard to remember.
Sometimes we've talked on the show, haven't we, about how I did also work for Will.
i.
am's
comedy company service.
Oh, yeah.
Dip Dive.
Yeah.
He had his own streaming platform for a while.
This is like almost a decade ago at this point.
Before Elon Musk tried to do an onion and then bailed on it.
Way before that.
Before this was cool.
There was a building.
I don't know.
They apparently had owned this building in Glendale for a long time, but it was the head
operation, head operational base of Dip Dive dot com, which I believe is not even.
Scott, could you Google that?
See if that exists anymore.
It just goes to rerouted to Will.
i.
am and then an ad for something called Zuper Mask
with an X.
Wow.
Really?
It's just the word coronavirus flashing over and over.
And then stay home, stay.
We're going to discover together what Zuper Mask is all about.
I think he's selling like a cool mask.
I think Will.
am using the valuable Dip Dive URL.
It says FU 2020, another clever bleep like the cat meow.
Wow.
It's taken a very long time.
Oh, it is a very sleek.
It looks like a Bane mask.
Oh my gosh.
He's selling Bane masks to fight coronavirus.
Will.
i.
am is selling Bane masks to battle COVID-19.
How much can you buy one of these with?
Let's find out the price for Zuper Mask.
Zuper Mask with a Z?
Z-U-P-E-R?
With an X.
Oh, Zuper.
That's even better, actually.
The X as Z pronunciation is guessed on my part.
Wait, but I'm clicking on Zuper Mask and then it's taking me to no more of a website.
What?
First drop sold out.
Go to ZuperMask.
com to find out when drop two will be released.
It's sleek black and white just like iPhones.
You are on ZuperMask.
com right now?
No, that's Will.
i.
am redirected from Dip Dive.
com.
Now I'm on ZuperMask.
Okay, when does wave two drop?
This is possibly.
I'm not sure, but they cost $300.
What?
Of course they do.
But we already have drop two of the vaccine.
That's a good point.
Don't they need to rush out drop two of the most expensive mask you've ever heard of?
I think that, yes, that should have been rushed out.
Old Navy and stuff and ordered pretty decent masks from both of them.
And now I'm getting a number of emails of like $2 for a three pack of masks.
So I think they're priced to move right now.
I don't know that this is the best climate for a $300 ZuperMask.
Well, I think I figured out the expense because it is also Bluetooth headphones.
Oh, and a microphone inside also like Bane.
Wow.
I don't know what technology Bane was using, but you'd have to think Bluetooth was involved
unless it was just super janky.
It was made like a 60s animatronic.
Yeah, that's a good point.
I mean, the Bane from the last Nolan Batman.
I mean, Jason, Bane's mask was to continue helping to inject venom into his veins, which
is like the steroid that Bane was taking.
But he's also venom separately.
Whoa, I didn't even think about that.
That's weird.
Whoa.
Tom Hardy is Bane who…
Tom Hardy is the epitome of like early 90s extreme characters.
Yeah, he takes venom, but Tom Hardy is venom.
Is venom.
Wow.
What an interesting start to this episode.
ZuperMask also injects venom slowly into your bloodstream.
So that's worth it.
It's the same thing.
And only two hours for a full charge.
So check out will.
i.
m, but we're here to talk about theme parks mostly, including Universal
Studios.
And wait, well, let's like, we can jump all around.
This episode is meant to be a catch all for our general Universal Studios thoughts that
couldn't fit in our Secret Life of Pets episode on the main feed.
But we're also here to talk about the big dog, the new dino in town, Indominus Rex,
new on the Jurassic World's ride, which opened two years ago with a different Indominus Rex.
It always, it's the same format of finale with a dinosaur fight, but this one can do
so much more.
Yeah, it's a full body dinosaur.
Yeah.
And boy, is it very impressive, is it?
Did they, I mean, I guess I'm getting out of myself.
They moved the old one.
That's what people seem to be saying.
Coaster 101, the website, has a good side by side before and after the major changes
to Jurassic World, because in addition to the ending dinosaur, there's an Indominus
that comes out before the lift hill and there's a new dryosphere where previously there had
just been bloody white boxes.
If you notice, I didn't remember what was there.
I missed the blood.
There was not really blood anymore.
And now there's the gyrosphere, which speculating that it's like, oh, I think they took the
gyrosphere from the picture car section of the studio tour and put it in the ride.
Oh, interesting.
Okay.
The gyrosphere being the weird glass ball that the kids get trapped in that has a Jimmy
Fallon ride video in Jurassic World.
Yes.
Which is subject to like any time there's a construction permit or patent filed at Universal
in Florida, everyone's like, all right, buckle your seat belts, gyrosphere attraction.
It's going to happen.
And it just never happens.
Oh, yeah.
I think there's, I've seen all there's patents, I think as well.
Like you go, it's like the gyrosphere.
I don't know that they've, I've, I've maybe I've heard this or maybe I'm making it up
is that they haven't figured out the technology to make the gyrosphere work like it should.
It's a rolling ball that also has like non rolling elements.
That's pretty difficult.
So I think that's obviously that would be in their plans to do something like that.
But it seems easier to invent a CGI version of it for a major motion picture as opposed
to make this science fiction real life.
Sure.
In five years.
Speaking of not figuring out tech and I don't want to just stay on this.
But of course I kind of do.
The super mask launched one month ago.
What?
It took him that much pandemic.
Like I don't know.
And they're probably showing him fake graphs like real.
This thing is going nowhere.
This virus will be raging out of control for the next 10 years.
If you corner the Bluetooth mask market, the premium Bluetooth mask market, you'll have
no competitors.
Wow.
Great.
Take as much time as you need.
Let's just try to get this thing out by 2025.
Well I mean global pan.
What was the last global pandemic?
1918 or something.
So it'll be ready for the next one hopefully in 100 years.
Although the way things technology speeds up, you know, hopefully, hopefully it takes
100 years.
You're always at risk with these things of being so 2000 and late.
I have found a number of Bluetooth masks on Alibaba for about $50 or less.
Bluetooth masks are a thing in general.
I think they are kind of a novelty.
Most of them are like displaying a little LED light show.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Headphone or microphone.
But yeah, I feel like.
Can you get a Bane mask?
Oh I wonder, can you get a Bane mask?
This is a yeah, that's a good idea.
A Bane looking Bluetooth.
This is a market.
They're appealing to no one because to want something like this, you have to be a douchebag.
But douchebags have been going out in public without a mask the entire time.
So why would a douchebag spend a bunch of money on the Google Glass of masks when they
don't want to, what they enjoy doing the most is coughing on everybody and pretending nothing's
going on.
Right.
I see what you're saying.
I'd have to take a look.
I am not looking at the mask.
$300 seems a bit steep, I will agree with you.
And seems like you could just use your regular headphones and regular mic.
But maybe, but if Will's, if Will Ams just trying to get like his 20 rapper friends to
buy them.
Yeah.
It might be, that might be priced to move if you have upwards of $200 million.
Right.
Well, he's at a high end.
It's a sharper image sold a mask.
That's what this is.
Yeah.
So maybe, you know, I do think I'll be wearing a mask on a plane forever or other spaces
that seem crowded.
So I don't know if they can show it off in a store.
If I can go back to the old office and there's a prototype.
Oh, the old, the dip dive.
The old dip dive office.
If that's back, we're making viral content for super mask.
Yeah.
So just any joke that you can think of that represents super mask in a cool hip light.
Superman, a character he created.
I wonder.
That's a pitch that could work for dip dive.
If you get your old job back.
Well, I've two point dip dive zoo point.
Oh, Superman.
Hold on.
Google Superman.
These episodes at higher risk of careening out of control.
I might connect it back by saying another good idea for a Bluetooth mask is one that
looks like a raptor face and that moves and it moves along with what you're saying.
Like if you had a full realistic raptor face.
Oh, yeah.
Like the Chewbacca mom.
Like the.
Oh, yeah.
Exactly.
That also a good idea.
Chewbacca mom masks that work against COVID as well.
That are just an old thing.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
We're also joining the Mask Innovation team on the downward slope of this.
Yeah, I don't think there's a Superman Superman character, but yes, soon, hopefully you're
ready to go with it.
Just get it out to him.
ASAP.
So the Jurassic World, the big finale.
Yeah, you guys both saw that.
Oh, right.
Because it was not running my return to Universal.
I went like six or seven days before it officially reopened.
It was the end of the taste of Universal event and they just soft opened like 70 percent
of the rides and they're like, have at it, folks.
Sure.
Some kind of dry runs getting them.
It's a little bonus for you guys.
Yeah.
We saw the tail end of that event.
You might have gotten to do it, but you were a little too early.
Yeah.
Well, I believe I was getting in the car in the parking garage and I happened to look
at Twitter and some maybe on the show account and there were pictures where it's like they
just opened Jurassic World.
It was like six, even six o'clock at night.
So they opened it for like an hour, hour and a half before the end of the event.
So you were still there.
I was still there.
Yeah.
You didn't go back.
I didn't know.
I didn't go from Jurassic Parking down to Jurassic World.
I'm ready on that.
I would go back.
That's that's as far as you could.
Well, Transformers, I guess, is the furthest that's technically furthest.
Yeah.
This is a big habit of mine.
When I've had a Universal Annual Pass, there's I've definitely like it's like a fifth of
the time I go to the lower lot.
I am too lazy to go to the lower lot despite having bought the annual pass.
It's a big haul as much as I was praising the Starway.
Love being on all those escalators.
Just a lot of time.
And it always I also used to live so close to the bottom of the hill.
And it was the started to have the effect of when Homer is stuck in traffic and then
all the way back in the nuclear plant lot and then that right to his house.
Sure.
It was kind of would feel like that sometimes.
I read.
Yeah.
The whole summer of Transformers, though, I had the annual pass and a couple times that
summer I parked down the hill, got on the tram, went all the way up, went all the way
down to the lower lot, did Transformers and then left.
Well, so, you know, solo.
Solo.
Yeah.
Who would do that with me?
People are calling this the best summer ever.
Summer of Crunk or whatever anyone's saying.
It's crunk is far too old of a word.
That sounds like it'd be in a song played at Universal Studios.
Yeah.
Ja Rule's Summer of Crunk.
Ja Rule, LMFAO.
From summer 2002.
So I guess I guess it worked.
Should we start with the Jurassic?
Yeah, might as well.
We're kind of in it.
Yeah.
How do we like this robot, everyone?
We saw it.
Jason didn't get the pleasure.
I watched a bunch of videos.
It's amazing.
It's so great.
It's really amazing.
Yeah.
And truly like, yeah, makes, as we were saying, and I'm assuming on our first Jurassic World
episode, we were like, it feels like it'll be better, right?
And yes, they wanted it to be better.
And now it's better, a lot better.
And the only gripe I would have with it is when I went on it, the timing was a little
off because so basically the old way that it would happen is that you're going over,
like you're being evacuated out of the building.
And then, you know, the shot that's in all the commercials, the T-Rex roars out of the
shadows right at your car and you drop.
So now you kind of do, now they've changed that whole top area into like a habitat, I
guess.
And there's some dinosaurs there.
And then you turn the corner, which would normally just kind of be dark and you see
the Indominus Rex and he's massive and he's just kind of like stalking back and forth.
He's like moving back and forth.
Yeah.
Turning that head, big turn radius on the head.
Very articulated.
This is, there's a lot of articulation going on.
And then the T-Rex comes out and roars.
It's a little unclear exactly what they're fighting over.
It's I'm not sure.
It doesn't, it's not like it seems like the Indominus Rex is going to attack us and then
T-Rex.
I think that's maybe the idea is that Indominus Rex is a threat to us and now T-Rex is saving
us like in the first Jurassic world.
Yeah, that's what I was going to think.
It's just mostly a nod to like the T-Rex inadvertently being the hero at the end of the first Jurassic
world.
Because you've got Raptor also involved in this.
That's the same kind of order of unveiling, which that Raptor is very great too.
The Raptor is not new, but it's pretty astounding.
Aaron had not seen any of these characters, I guess just the two, but super impressed
by the Raptor too.
This whole thing, I think with this piece, the Jurassic world plus up is fantastic.
I think this is a little hard to deny.
stop there.
They did go back and add the last little bit.
I think this bit too, this was the old like right before you went up the lift hill, you
know, there's just some scratch marks and a like fakey billboard.
And then they, you know, left the scratch mark, but then it's ripped through the billboard
and there's a little indominus head poking out trying to get you.
And that's a nice little touch too.
Yes.
So that's the original indominus head, I think.
That's yeah, that's why I saw a couple.
That was what was there before at the top of the hill when we went, what is this?
Is it?
This was supposed to be a big, massive dinosaur battle.
Remember the leaked photos of the two great beasts battling and it was like his head.
And then like the, he comes out and he goes, Hey, stop it.
And then goes back in the same one.
We know.
Yeah.
Just a head before and now you got that full body.
It's right over.
Yeah.
The full body.
So that's why I asked, I think on the last episode, Scott, if you were okay with it,
because it is giant and you do go under it, which is really impressive.
Yeah.
You get that scale, but the building is pretty big.
It didn't, didn't freak me out on that level.
I'm feeling very like fear conquer.
I have to say.
This is what I forecasted and you were saying you didn't think that would be the case, but
yes, I don't want to, I don't want to give it away of a future episode, but there was
some bravery that happened the other night.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
I don't know.
We'll get to that either.
Also like, like it was like Fast and the Furious supercharged.
Scott Gardner was so supercharged.
He was crisscrossing a theme park, like run out of time.
I got to do some rides, got to do some rides.
And I was like, oh, I thought we were finishing these free tasting nibbles.
Yeah, I know.
I was really, well, who cares?
We can talk about it.
It's the, we went to this Knott's event, which was so fantastic.
And I think just because I've been, I have been doing all the attractions that used to
scare me.
Yeah.
In this case, Jurassic worlds really enjoyed it.
Um, but you know, mummy, I'm launching, I'm back on that thing.
There's something, I maybe I just hadn't done a launch in a while.
I do wonder if that launch is slightly more intense than the Florida one.
Am I making that up?
I think it is actually.
I think the launch is more intense than in Hollywood.
Hmm.
Maybe that, maybe I had that one in my head.
If that is a slightly more intense launch than others, uh, maybe that's why it freaked me
But still did it, enjoyed it until the bizarre ending of that ride.
Yeah, of course.
Um, but then we got, we got to go to this Knott's thing and yeah, I was all hopped up.
I know I was like running around like a kid, like, come on, come on guys.
I think just because I just was assessing, I'm looking at this coaster, like I'm seeing
what this thing does.
I could do this.
I could do this and I don't want to second guess it.
And I'm so excited to be back in theme parks.
And I did the ride silver bullet and just really jammed over there.
Also subtext, a couple of drinks in.
Sure.
That's all I'll come back to.
Always a component.
Not 10 though.
No, no, no, certainly not.
They didn't give us that many pull tabs.
Yeah.
Um, but I, uh, yeah, I just had the confidence on it and I did it front row.
Uh, was so excited to do it.
I have not done a lot of, um, dangling coasters.
Um, that's not the proper term.
Suspended.
Dangling leg coasters.
Cause I am scared of it.
Danglies, dangly footsies.
Um, I, yeah, wait.
So, so I'm rushing you guys over there.
I only, it seemed like you were down in general, but did you have some trepidation over the,
the suspended element?
Uh, yeah, yeah.
I was like, oh yeah, that's the one with the legs.
I don't know about the legs.
I don't like, but, uh, but I can't, I don't think there's a scenario.
I'm trying to think of a ride.
I think if everybody wanted to do X two and we were at six flags, I probably do it for,
for, I, I'm not going to, I'm not going to be not doing it.
I'm not going to have a flashback to me as a kid.
Yeah.
That's a challenge.
Like you weren't meaning it to be a challenge, but you laid down a challenge and I said,
well, let's do it.
Let's, let's do this.
I did not sit front row though.
Sure.
I did not do front row.
I think I was, I, I would do front row actually again, though.
I would do it next time.
It's fine.
I love the dangling part.
It was that up to dangle.
I love it.
And for me though, the, I was not expecting, I guess, cause it had been a few years since
I had done a suspended coaster like that.
Maybe not since dueling dragons closed.
I think that's what the G forces.
I was like, Oh, my brain, like I can feel my brain stem.
Like I was like, Oh, am I going to have a headache?
And thankfully I did not just in the, in the like corkscrews and the loot did I go
like, Oh, that is new.
And then when we got off, I was fine.
Yeah.
That thing corkscrews the hell out of you.
And, and so, yeah, I, there was once or twice, I think I yelled to Mike.
It's like, I don't know what direction we're at right now.
You made a noise and it's the same way.
A similar noise on that is when we were sitting next to each other on hang time,
which we've talked a lot about on the knots, which is a terrifying coast where
you go 90 degrees to get to the top.
And then it's like stalls you at the top for what feels like a minute, but it's
five seconds, but did you just make like a noise?
Like there's a noise that comes out of you that came out of you on silver
bullet on the first, like, I think it was the first,
that on hang time on the lift hill.
I think it was on the lift.
Cause I like the hang.
I like the top of hang time.
Well, yeah, cause you're the itemizer.
Yeah.
You love it.
You love, you want to jump off the, which building in Vegas is Jason going to
jump off of?
Oh, what do they call it now?
The strat is it the, it's just called the strat.
Jump off a building.
He wants to one day, one day.
Yeah.
I will jump off a building of $20 a night hotel room.
Like the very notable historically designed building that now is on the
list of like, Oh, maybe don't maybe stay somewhere else.
Sure.
Like to look so it's like, Oh, maybe just walk through it.
You know?
Yeah.
But anyway, that came up, they, that came out during a quarantine that Jason is
down to jump off with a bungee cord.
To rappel.
I know.
Yeah.
It loves it.
Who knew?
So I'm looking up some stats on this thing just to see, because I did, I did
get off and like, I've never done a coaster with that many inversions.
Yeah.
One more than the In Credit Coasters biggest drop making that the biggest
drop that I've done.
Right.
I'm just feeling great.
I'm so glad to be on the other side of what you were guessing.
Can I guess the manufacturer?
Yeah.
Is it B&M?
B&M.
Nice.
Dueling Drei and Mabillard.
Yes.
How'd you know?
That, uh, I, well, cause I think they did Dueling Drei.
I think they've put in a lot of suspended coasters.
Oh, gotcha.
Okay.
If it's suspended, it might be that.
What is it when it says G-Force three and then no further, uh, the
word or qualification, what does that mean?
What does it three, what does it measure G-Force?
I think that's the number of moments where you feel G-Force.
Cause there was like three like moments where it was like being pushed.
Guys zero G-Roll, whatever that is.
Yeah.
I don't know what that is.
I checked after this cause I said right after, cause you were saying you weren't
sure you were going to do Velocicoaster and I said, I bet you could, if you
would this, if you did this and Velocicoaster I think is like maybe 10,
12 miles per hour faster.
Okay.
But that's not 30.
Well, that's what I'm, that's what I'm going to say.
Like this ride is like silver bullets, a little bit old and like that clunks
you around a little bit.
Yeah.
And I think, um, Velocicoaster distracts you with a lot of like sets and
landscaping and that kind of thing.
I bet Velocicoaster is just a smooth, fast, crazy ride, but I don't think,
I don't think it's, it's definitely not, I bet like twisted colossus or X2 or
anything where they, or hang time where there's an extra element that makes you
feel like you're going to shit in your pants.
I don't think so.
Yeah.
Bigger draw a hundred 40 is the biggest on that, but I'm getting there.
I don't know.
I'm not opening it up.
Yeah.
The drop is to me, the drop is not, I don't care anymore about the drops.
I used to be more worried about like drops.
Now I'm more worried about like on twisted colossus where basically the
sensation is they're only holding down your legs.
So it really feels like you're going to fly out of the car the whole ride.
Like there's extra stuff like that or X2 or you're dangling, but
flipping while it's happening.
We're like that stuff.
I go, I don't know.
Um, but yeah, with two velocity coaster, like you're nice and you're in there,
right?
You got the restraints.
Um, yeah, but I mean, I had such a blast.
I was so psyched on silver blum watching videos the next morning.
What's happening to me.
Wow.
Chillin out.
The one that what has to happen obviously is that we all have to go to Frightfest.
That's a different, I don't like that.
You don't have to.
That's so annoying to me.
You don't have to necessarily go on the house, but you can go on the rides while
we're in the houses.
But I ended up enjoying these when I'm like scared, but then I'm glad that I did
it just like Tony said about splash mountain haunts.
When we went to the one at knots, we went through one maze, which is not even
close to the most intense maze.
And I think Jason and I both were just like, ah, ah, ah, ducking the whole time.
And then like, few, we got out.
The joy of that ending is that it is over.
And we did the one where we were handed rifles, where we were handed
laser tag.
Oh, yeah.
Right.
You could shoot them away.
Scoot them away.
That's not on all of them.
Yeah.
And I will say, um, you know, though I'm, I'm putting on a show of like, yeah, I'm
doing these more advanced coasters.
Now I do.
I prefer it.
If there's a big, uh, puffy restraint that I can grip like a giant pillow, like
I can grip like mommy.
Sure.
That helps me a lot.
So that helped me on in credit coaster.
It makes me still more afraid of the tower guardians format because I just got these
little handles.
I got, I got no mommy to hold.
No mommy.
So if there's a, if there's a restraint mommy.
Right.
And so I, that's why I think the gun was good.
So you need like an anime body pillow to go through like the us house.
You need a, you need a waifu.
A really soothing, a soothing lightweight wife.
Five pounds or less.
You can do, yeah, you can do, uh, the twist of Colossus at six flags.
As long as you have a giant Lola bunny pillow that's as fixed to the side of the
car or like figment and dream finder.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, sure.
Yes.
Yeah.
Good, good friends or the soothing touch of a woman or woman rabbit platonic
support body pillow and emotional support body pillow.
That's the way nothing weird.
Okay.
Yeah.
Well, if they tell me you can't have that, this is a roller coaster.
I'll say, no, I need it for emotional support.
That's a weird doctor signed off on this.
That is never, they've never said that phrase at six flags.
You're right.
You can't do that.
I forgot where we were talking.
They don't care.
Yeah.
Just full multi-person sex Trist.
Sure.
Go for it.
Yeah.
There's cars one and two got out of the cars and are just having sex over the
rows.
There's been orgies on twisted Colossus for sure.
Well, it's pretty twisted.
You put that in the name.
Yeah.
You can't be responsible for what happens.
Uh, I think though, maybe not the fright fest, but I think six flags.
I think if you can do silver bullet, there's a handful of coasters at six
flags that are basically the same.
I was thinking, I think, um, I think Batman, the rides probably in my future.
Yeah.
Those are really similar.
I think Riddler's revenge.
You would do no problem.
It's the standup one, but you got a big harness and got restraint mommy,
restraint mommy.
Great.
So that one's fine.
And then there's probably one or two other ones.
Huh?
So maybe the job, maybe the magic mountain trips coming up.
Yeah.
Well, we got to go back to magic mountain.
And I've never done it for the first I ever did.
It was as a drive through experience watching darkened, uh, tin soldiers on
stilts, I dance around to faint music out of a car.
Yeah.
I was thinking we have to go back with obviously geo at fright fest, but maybe
we go back before without him or with him either way.
Yeah.
Let's just try not to go on the hottest day of the year.
Like I did one time and I had a pair of like flip flops or sandals or something
by the time I got home, like they, like pieces were separating.
It had been so hot.
Like I didn't throw them in the garbage.
It was like, Oh, these are a lost cause.
Uh, the Santa Clarita just destroyed them.
Hmm.
I think it's hot up there.
Yeah.
I don't, am I making up that I don't feel like there's like the most shade at six
legs that seems like a sweltering.
It depends where you are.
We went at more at night and that's really the only time I've been there
other than driving through it.
Hmm.
Um, so we didn't see a ton of like sun cover, like coverage, but there's, it is
so big and confusing, uh, I think there are like areas where there are like trees
and stuff, but I don't, there's a lot of stretches I think where it's just pavement.
Yeah.
Like by the hall of justice, there's no cover anywhere.
A lot of walking.
I'll bring this back to universal with the, with a lot of walking.
I feel like after you went to universal, you said I am not in theme park shape.
Yes.
Right.
And, and Carly, uh, was out.
I had also heard her say that I have certainly said that my body is definitely
atrophied during quarantine.
Yeah.
Uh, well, I, this is all odd to me.
It's like walk it.
You take a walk.
It's a lot of, I know, but I have like a recurring cramp in my right leg.
Now I have to get looked at.
It's on the coast.
There are crips and I was worried about, I saw the cramp and I asked about it
once or twice.
We were together.
Uh, usually if I take some excedrin or Tylenol or something, it's fine, but
you were limping at city.
Well, we went to see what the summer, there's a limb.
Yeah, I don't, yeah, I don't know what it is.
I used to walk a lot.
Do you not leave bed during the quarantine?
I have had days where I've left bed very little, but I'm working on getting
more active.
Like, wait a minute.
I work from, yeah, you work from bed.
That's like Robert.
You know, Robert Evans used to do that.
Yeah, sure.
Brian Wilson did for three years.
So I'm getting, I'm getting back up into theme park shape as well.
But the CDC never said don't get out of your bed.
Well, I, the CDC doesn't advise on how to deal with anxiety and depression
either, but, uh, so, uh, I'm working on it.
I'm working on getting back.
They don't have all the answers.
Yeah.
Uh, I, well, when I said that, look, I wasn't like, I wasn't
like, totally like wrecked completely.
I also started playing tennis again for the first time in 18 years or something
crazy, however old I am, maybe not 18.
Yeah, maybe 18.
Uh, so I remember just like, Oh, my knee, my, my old tennis injury is acting up
again, but then exacerbated by universal.
Uh, but I'm doing Disney what Tuesday?
Yeah.
We'll see if you're going to make you fall to the ground and vomit.
We'll see if nots universal and playing tennis three times.
If I'm ready to go.
Cause I, I'm, I, I can do a 8 a.
m.
to 12 to midnight day standing on my head.
No problem.
Yeah, I did do that.
Okay.
Yeah.
I had a moment or two yet where I took an Advil or whatever at Disney, but I
think I was there from 9 a.
m.
to like 8 p.
The other stepped it down to less hours and you needed medication.
Yeah.
No, I'm not saying I'm on his level.
I have to join him for one of these tennis outings.
You need, Oh yeah, we want Jason, but yeah, look at that leg first.
I'm a little worried.
Yeah, no, I know.
No, I'm going to inject you with venom.
Let's be honest.
I did do physical therapy on like my shoulder, my hamstring, like a couple
years ago, cause they were kind of bad.
So it might be one of that like flaring up again.
Sure.
So, um, so anyway, we'll be back.
We'll be back.
We'll all be good to go.
Yeah.
Moving around, um, my shoulder, my shoulders hang, hold it hanging in there.
By the way, I've gotten good again at tennis.
I just want to let everyone know.
I just want everyone to know the first time I played, I was bad and I'm good
again, second doubles conference champion, sophomore year of high school.
Ladies and gentlemen, that is a fact.
I'm not making that up.
You think I'm not an athlete.
You're wrong.
Schomburg city hall.
It says it in there.
Don't make your expose documentary and you're not going to like what you find.
Me and my partner, Jim Conrad.
Cool.
Nickle tennis.
Yeah.
Carlson Conrad.
That's right.
So you think I'm a nerd.
You're wrong.
The original bash brothers.
I'm, I'm an athlete.
You were after the movie bash brothers.
You're the tennis bash brothers.
I am.
Yeah, we were the tennis bash brothers.
Um, uh, anyway, whatever we said, whatever we said about this, you were
getting back into shape.
Oh yeah.
That's where I was.
We were, so well, what's because that we, you know, we could talk about other
universal things.
Is there anything to close out to this particular robot?
Well, it is one robot.
It's hard to fill an episode.
Well, yeah, the one robot is really good.
I would say that my, the timing of the robot fight was off when I saw it.
So that was forever ago.
You're talking about 35 minutes ago after tennis and Robert Evans or before,
excuse me.
Um, yeah, at the time it was a little off.
So it was like the dominance Rex T-Rex came out like a good solid minute before
we were close to jumping down the hill and then went back in.
And then there was like 20 seconds and then we went down the hill and it was
like, all right, wait, that's, I, that's, I looked at the thing.
That's not quite right.
So I had a criticism of this and even looking at what I think is the optimum
way it's supposed to perform by the criticism of it, it would be that the
prize fear is gone, which I think I've said this before on the show and we all
know I'm like afraid of dinosaur robots still, because we've in the dinosaur
episode, I always apparently look away.
I can't help it.
Even when I think I have my eyes like glued open looking, it's I'm cowering in fear.
Pretend it's a big tennis ball.
Just well, yeah.
Then I have the eye of the tiger.
Yeah, exactly.
Uh, and so you, it's up there.
It's too well lit.
And then you don't get that, that fear.
Cause I remember even like having gone on it after a while, the original Jurassic
world or Jurassic park ride and like thinking, Oh, maybe the T-Rex is broken.
And they really, when it's perfectly working, it is timed really great to just
get you on the way down to scare you as it's happening.
And even, even, you know, going on it a lot more in the last five or 10 years or
whatever, I would still always be like, Oh, maybe it's broken.
They'd wait to the last second to scare you.
And it feels like that per that was so perfect that it is missing that element.
Now it would be really great.
Like the maximum amount of fear on the, on the drop, whereas now it's kind of like,
even when it's working well, it's like the show happens, the dinosaurs were at
each other and then you go down.
Yeah.
The optimal thing I think, yeah, that is that that T-Rex barely makes it.
And there's videos where you sort of see that timing, but this has been recurring
even before the Indominus was there.
Cause I've watched videos.
I'm like, what's the, what are the subtle differences in the Japan one or the,
or the Florida one?
And, uh, there's there, yeah, sometimes there's the timing where you round the
corner and the T-Rex is just out already, just yelling for 30 full seconds.
And people, I think if you don't know what the time is supposed to be, it's fine.
Yeah, it's just very imprecise.
This is not, um, Indiana Jones and the Boulder where it's sort of the, it can,
only play out this one way.
It's very like, which I give them credit that it even syncs up at all because
boat rides are a little more, all right.
The stuff generally happens like jump scares and boat rides or, or like
particular moments or spin around and look at this all of a sudden.
That's just not the nature of boat rides.
It's like catch what you catch.
So it's like, it's, it's close, you know, am I making that up?
Like other, other boat rides where like, oh, that happens.
Well, there's a new, there's like the new, like Shanghai Disney pirates boat ride
where I think it's like wifi controlled boats and they can like spin and turn
very so precisely, but that's not the technology from the original Jurassic
park ride or like, yep, pirates of the Caribbean and Disneyland or Disney world.
It's like, you're the mercy of the current.
And it's like, I think the old ride was so dark that you could, like you would
see the boat in front of you, get the show scene and with the T-Rex before
that wouldn't happen.
So like that would always feel like a specialized thing that would feel like
the Boulder moment at the end of the Indiana Jones ride, but now that the
whole thing is brightly lit, I think I saw you turn around and you go, oh,
there's the boat in front.
Oh, there it got the show.
And now it loses the specialness of that feeling like it's just happening to you.
Sure.
So while it's an amazingly impressive, awesome robot, you lose.
And I'm going to say the word, the intimacy, the intimacy, the intimacy,
which we give you when we speak this close to the microphone.
Yeah.
Well, I'm doing the effort for intimate effect.
But yeah, you lose, you lose that thing of feeling like it's only happening to
you because now you're going like, oh yeah, it just happened to them.
It's going to happen to the people behind us too.
Yeah.
It's like a little show.
So it is a bummer that they couldn't have figured out some terrifying way to like
flash light up, oh my God, it's the Intaminus Rex.
Oh my God, it's the T-Rex.
Now we're dropping again.
I'm sure they've tried, but.
Yeah.
Cause I think they had that water effect in the big, um, you know, the tank that
you go by at the start, that is like queued to a music queue or a sink and it works so
well, like I love that effect.
That's yeah, there's a couple of fun water.
We said this before, or I said this before that I'm happy to get soaked on a
tri now universal in the tank.
Yeah.
The tank is one of the best water effects for sure.
And that's, yeah, all the stuff leading up to that end scene is perfectly synced
and fine.
It's not like you're losing out on a little moment or whatever.
Like, I don't think you can see that tank moment happen to the people in front of you.
No, no, not really.
No.
So like, you don't know that's coming.
I forgot, I knew it was coming, but I forgot it was coming.
I forgot it.
I got hit with the water and we go, of course.
So I ponchoed up so stupidly.
We post, I posted a picture on, on Twitter, but yeah, Aaron as well.
She was reluctant to go on this, not because of fear, but because of wet, not wanting
theme park witness.
She's on the opposite end.
Sure.
Like there's a little bit of landscaping trees by Jurassic world, but otherwise it's
a lot of concrete and asphalt and it gets hot down there and it gets crowded really
easy too.
That's the trick.
If you've never been to the universe, do this Hollywood, go to the lower lot early
in the morning.
As soon as you get there, you can knock it out in less than an hour.
Yeah.
So, oh yeah, especially in this limited capacity time.
This is a thing you're making me realize, like kind of a change in perspective from
kid to adult where I used to be at theme parks and think it is very hot.
I want the refreshment of getting splashed.
I will be so cooled down and I'll feel so much more refreshed the more soaked that I
get.
And I have not felt that remotely past 21 or so.
It's, it's akin to I'm so thirsty and I need some refreshment.
I'm going to have a big glass of milk.
That is not where I'm at anymore with that.
Like now I just don't even like, why did I think that?
And why, why only is a kid that I think that?
Well, technically milk is hydrating due to as many vitamins and nutrients and high
protein content.
The milk lobby.
But mentally it might not seem that way.
I think one, a part of that is that most water rides in California, the effects are
kind of turned down for much of the year because it's a little more mild in
Southern California.
If you want it to cool down by getting soaking wet and you happen to find yourself in
the lagoon lagoon, you're all set.
You're going to get soaking wet on Dudley.
I wouldn't want that.
You're not going to, oh, it's not going to be satisfying.
That's different.
No, a shower is going to do.
I just no longer.
I'm like, ah, great.
I feel so much better.
I'm soaked in strange water that has machine parts in it.
Yeah.
The strangers.
Your underwear is wet.
That doesn't like cool you down.
No.
Yeah.
That's fair.
It's like, ah, just some of my right buttocks.
It's wet.
And like an inconvenient amount on my shirt.
What it did now, I'm curious, would it dip in a pool or the ocean?
Yeah, of course.
Okay.
Yeah.
Are you asking these questions because you find going on Popeye like refreshing?
Sometimes.
I mean, I know you like get like soaked, but I know what it's got saying.
It was like, it's unpleasant to get like your socks soaked.
Obviously we know.
Yeah, it can be applied, but it wakes you up a little.
It's like getting a bucket of water thrown at you.
It's not the most sustainable.
I'll say that.
If it's like 95 degrees out and I'm wearing like short, like a very simple outfit,
shorts, a shirt or a tank, either one, then all right, fine.
It's going to be pretty quick to being dry.
But if I'm wearing pants or something, like I don't, even if it's 80 degrees.
Now that's fair.
If it's 80 degrees.
The day we all went to Islands of Adventure together turned out to be the coldest day
of our trip.
And I went on Dudley Do-Right at 5 30 PM and came off and immediately had to put a sweater on
and change some of my clothes.
Only cold day.
Yeah, the only cold day.
The hottest day, of course, was the day we went to Animal Kingdom.
It always is.
Yeah, it always is hot there.
That was my prior trip.
Yeah, it was just like sitting there sweltering.
It hurts my perception of the place.
I, it doesn't, even though I associate it with 90 degree heat, I'm still, I'm just watching
somebody walk through there and going, we got to get back to Animal Kingdom.
I think that's probably well served though by a reservation, by like going to Tiffin's or Yak and
Yeti and having a long break in the cold with a nice meal.
Sure.
But there's, there are places, there's places, there's a lot of places with not much shade.
Yeah.
You got to be strategic about it.
So I just want to, I'm not trashing this ride.
I'm just saying I do miss that really perfectly timed element at the end.
But I would say if you watch old videos, it maybe was not that perfect.
I've certainly had it not be perfect on the ride, but what they were going for,
I do miss that part of it.
I also don't know what that room is supposed to be up there.
It looks cool.
But is it fake outdoors?
Or is it like, is it supposed to be like a zoo room that is themed to night?
Like an interior habitat, like a reptile house?
Yeah.
Maybe that makes sense.
I think so.
Because the original narrative of Jurassic Park ride was you're being rerouted into the
building to be evacuated.
Kind of a water plant, like a water processing pipe plant.
And the dinosaurs were not supposed to be in there.
There was a raptor, there was a T-Rex obviously, but they, that was just, they had gotten loose.
Now I just caught a detail.
I think that as you're heading up to the lift hill, I think there is a sign that says
Tyrannosaur Habitat or Tyrannosaur Kingdom.
I think you're right.
Yes, you're right.
So it is completely, they are, there is a T-Rex up there.
Is the idea that you're being rerouted and hopefully you don't run into a T-Rex?
That's a good question.
Bryce Dallas Howard and Chris Pratt just told us to be careful and keep our arms in the
vehicle, I think.
And they told us that their names are Claire Deering and…
Oh, Grady.
There's an emergency, I have to act fast.
I better get on and say my name.
Right.
They wanted to make sure we know.
We do know, but we, they just want to make sure.
Well, the us, the us's in Jurassic Park world, Jurassic World world would know because
we know who Josh Demaro is.
Yeah.
Who I saw at Nass.
Whoa.
Yeah.
Wow.
Mm-hmm.
Now that's…
It's like seeing a teacher at the mall where you're like, what?
It's like when I saw, when I was in elementary school and saw my school's janitor working
at like Home Depot and he pretended he wasn't, he said, no, I'm not him to be funny.
And I was so confused, like in kindergarten or first grade.
Oh.
And I saw, yeah, he was like working at one of these stores and like, he like pretended
he wasn't who he was.
And I was just, I really didn't know what to do.
On top of just seeing a teacher care or a person who works at the school outside was
weird enough, but then having them lie to me, I barely recovered.
Peanuts distress, I guess.
Really?
Yeah.
So I'm getting very glum.
So yeah, so Owen and Claire.
Yeah.
They tell us just be careful, but they're not saying, oh, we're rerouting you into the
dinosaur habitat.
Be careful up there.
They don't really say there's just a sign that says that.
Yeah.
But there are supposed to be T-Rex's.
So I guess that what the idea was you're on the tour of Jurassic world and you haven't
gone off.
You haven't really gone off.
I mean, there's a section where it looks like you go off like, you know, in Jurassic park
where you're supposed to go one way, you go the other way that still happens here.
But then you go in a place that looks like you were supposed to go there anyway.
Yeah.
It's all, it's all good.
It all works for me.
I really like the lift hill with the Chris Pratt screens.
And I agree broken and torn out.
I think that's an improvement.
I think all of it is either an improvement or a lateral move.
You know, some things are much better.
Other things are like, I kind of like the old way, but like this doll.
Yeah.
I just, I think I said in the original, like I wish there was another, it's like we're
almost getting like the scope and the size moment at the end now as opposed to the start.
Because when you would see all of the dinosaurs, Jurassic park, look at this.
And now we're getting this giant stuff.
We're getting that at the end of the ride.
But does the endominus not reach, uh, shift that opinion?
Like, do you now feel like you get some grandeur at the very end?
I do.
I do feel that I'm just saying, yeah, yeah, that's sort of,
I still wouldn't mind that earlier, but I guess, yeah, you do get at least like feeling
like, okay, I can, I can know how big this thing would have been and I would be scared
of it.
I should be scared of it.
Sure.
So you're getting that at the end.
You get the, as just as when you went two years ago, you get the grandeur of the
screens, the wide, the wide short screens in the queue, which are so weird.
The aspect ratio of 32 by four.
We all know it.
We're all buying 32 by four TV.
I think there are gaming monitors that look like that.
Oh, sure.
I don't like on the, uh, like lining the walls of, uh, baseball stadiums to flash
when there's been a home run.
Right.
If you go to like a Sony store, a Samsung store, you know, if you're ever in a shopping
center or mall and you're like, is that a, is that a fucking Vizio store?
And like, they have like the $6,000, like next gen model or it's like, do not buy
this $6,000 TV.
It will be $500 in two years.
Yeah.
You know, this isn't the time to be around forever.
It's not the super mask.
No, it's not a super mask.
Yeah.
A permanent fixture in our world.
I, I got to see the full loop of videos, which I didn't before, uh, which I do
think are pretty well done and pretty like classic theme park tradition and the
actors are fun in it.
Here's one thing I will, I will say, um, for all of the effort that all of these
theme parks have made to do the social distance and the six feet, they do it
long ways, but not.
Yeah.
You know what I mean?
Like, like you're still like, it's, you're still next to people.
Like, what is the point of the six foot markers?
If it's only going up and down, left to right, you're still right next to a big
group.
Well, it's, I mean, I guess why are we getting our temperatures taken when
there's so much asymptomatic spread?
Like what there's a lot of phobia.
Maybe that the temperature does cut down on some people that might have a fever,
but there's a lot, but you could take a Tylenol, like you could get rid of your
fever taking a Tylenol.
Yeah.
A lot.
As I've said, they've called you COVID theater.
A lot of ways phasing out the temperature.
Why are they, why are they handing me my taco bell meal in a like rubber
tray tray?
Like, this is just, this is theater.
We, the, how you get it is well documented now.
Yeah.
Which this is maybe a way that you would get it is being just, I'd never more
than the Jurassic world line.
Am I like, I really got, I waited to be vaccinated to come here.
I'm glad this isn't like, I didn't even do like, I got a little bit to go.
I was fully faxed.
Yeah.
And you see lines like that and you're like, all right, I'd like some of what
you're doing here theme park, but this one, this is like a, this is a greenhouse
where COVID could grow masked, but you know, that's that one.
I was like, had a few days left when I was up there, but I was like, Oh, I don't
know that I need to wait 30 minutes indoors and switch backs with all my
closest stranger friends.
Yeah.
That's a whole doing a revenge of them up, doing like rides.
I had done a million times before.
So I felt plenty safe there the whole day, but I felt safe because of Pfizer
less so than NBC universal.
Yeah.
Look, believe it or not corporations, not always doing the most safe things
if they're allowed to do it.
But yes, I agree.
There's, there's a lot of that stuff where you go, well, why not here, but not here.
Yeah.
It's the same.
Why are we taking our shoes off at the airport?
But unless if you pay though, you don't have to, you pay a hundred dollars a year.
You don't have to pay to bring a bomb on.
Yeah.
I pay.
I came with a free credit.
I came with a credit card where I get to have a free pass that says I don't have to take
my shoes off.
It seems a bit silly.
Does it not?
Sure.
Yeah.
I have a weird little tangent about odd collusion between universal and strange elements.
So I started, I was with all of this, I was thinking about the opening of the universal
or of the Jurassic park ride in 96, which we definitely talked about on the original
episode long ago.
I remember watching the full E special of it and there's a lot of fun novelty, you know,
Spielberg and Goldblum are there, but also Tatiana Ali and Hasselhoff and a bunch of weirdos.
I was just like, was there any details of that opening that I don't recall?
And there definitely was.
That being that Steven Spielberg spent the whole opening hanging around with
General Norman Schwarzkopf.
What?
Who of course led the operation Desert Storm.
Yeah, I don't know.
Norman Schwarzkopf was there.
When you Google Steven Spielberg Norman Schwarzkopf, one of the only results,
well the only times this has ever really been noticed was by Zach Dunn, fellow comedy writer,
guy in our scene.
Like he tweeted about it a couple of years ago.
So big ups to Zach Dunn for catching this.
Apparently nobody else has ever found this weird.
But then there's, I don't know, there's,
there's articles, I guess they were doing some charity thing together or something like,
so it was like early zoom basically, but to be able to talk to sick children in hospitals.
And then I found this bizarre account of Spielberg and Schwarzkopf doing a proto zoom with a sick
child in Osby at this opening.
What?
There's the Jurassic Park openings happening and then you have to find,
reporters have to go follow Spielberg and Schwarzkopf to go talk to a kid.
And it was very awkward and there was a big lag.
And this is all spelled out in an article.
Spielberg and Schwarzkopf attempted a dialogue with a child in her hospital room.
Are there any questions you want to ask me or the general said Spielberg?
What?
Silence.
About ET?
Jurassic Park?
Silence.
The army?
Okay, yes.
Why didn't the coalition forces continue on to Baghdad and thoroughly end Saddam's regime?
I didn't quite hear you.
You asked about Hook, right?
Well, it was very challenging to do the fake food and the paint.
It's such a mess on the set.
Okay, I think you're cutting out.
Bye little girl.
And then it turned out that she just wanted to know how the ride was.
That's what she was after.
Anyway, this is bizarre.
Steven Spielberg asking a sick kid if she wants to ask about the army.
One of the weirdest things.
But then I kept going.
Oh, sorry.
She's like, oh, no, I just pointing out that.
So this was 96, you said?
So video conferencing was around, but imagine the devices.
They would have had to wheel into a hospital and wheel to Universal Studios Hollywood.
They're like, we have to get a satellite uplink going.
And it's going to look smeary, folks.
It's going to interrupt.
We're not going to be able to get the Tonight Show out tonight.
Like, oh, it's just going to be an hour of black reschedule.
Rosie and the bare naked ladies.
We're not getting into broadcast tonight.
This is a photo you can see of this is some of the first people ever to ride the ride.
The Goldblum, the kids, Mazzello and Ariana Richards and front row center.
Norman Schwarzkopf.
Hurray.
Which row is G Gordon Lady in?
General Schwarzkopf, do you have any guilt of funding, Saddam America funding Saddam in the 80s?
And now you're fighting him.
I didn't quite make that out, but that T-Rex is scary.
For that final splashdown, that's scarier than anything you experience in a helicopter.
OK, bye.
Nixon would have been at the opening of Disney World with G Gordon Lady, I think.
Well, he wanted to be at Disney World.
Yeah, we talked about that on some episode.
Yeah, he wanted to be at Disney World, but I think it was the middle of like
Watergate or the wind down in Vietnam.
The missing tape was all at the contemporary.
It was all in a sweet overlooking Discovery Island.
Yeah, yeah.
Anyway, a whole other weird other tangent.
Also on Getty Images, a picture of a ref from like not too long after that.
Here's the T-Rex with Newt Gingrich, who got just like an off ride tour of the attraction.
And I was like, why?
And I Googled Newt Gingrich, Jurassic Park.
This guy is a Jurassic Park.
Oh, really?
Loves the movie.
Loves it.
Talks about it all the time.
In 2015, tweeted Jurassic World is the best in the series since the original Jurassic Park.
Terrific script with constant surprises.
What?
Two months after the release of the film, Newt Gingrich weighed in on this.
There's lots of media where he talks about Jurassic Park, including that he said,
and I quote, why not aspire to build a real Jurassic Park?
It may not be at all impossible, you know, wouldn't that be one of the most spectacular
accomplishments of human history?
What if we can bring back extinct species?
Newt Gingrich wanted to build Jurassic Park for real.
The Speaker of the House, Newt Gingrich, why did he now push this while he was in office?
And why hasn't Pelosi weighed in on her?
What sci-fi does she want to make real?
Gattaca?
Just because she want to make a Simone.
Gattaca is my favorite movie.
Yeah.
Really strange.
And like, why don't like if you watch Jurassic, unless he bailed about 25 minutes in,
maybe he should have.
Wouldn't you think maybe you should not make Jurassic Park?
Oh, right.
He just saw the first 25 minutes.
So yeah, well, he missed the cold open of the he missed the
pre credits where someone doesn't someone get eaten before the credit.
Yeah, he also he arrived late.
Did I miss anything?
Just saw the technical rehearsals, but before and then went to the bathroom
when their jeep stopped in the rain.
And then he got a phone call on a massive old cell phone and didn't go back in.
So he thinks the technical rehearsals like our.
Hurry, if we act right now, we can keep gates out of the military.
Hurry, go.
I don't have time to finish this movie.
Yeah.
Now he's very busy.
Wow.
Interesting.
Yeah, weird.
And then just sorry, one more little thing.
I also he talks about Jurassic Bark and dinosaurs on his podcast, Newt's World.
Know what?
Everybody knows Newt's World, right?
And I'm sure we share a lot of audience with Newt's World, which is up to episode 250.
And then I'm curious, like, what else is what's what's he talking about on Newt's World?
And I pulled up episode 238, Biden's radical first 100 days.
And you're not unless it has changed since I left to come here.
And we could just edit all this out if so.
But here's what I heard on at the beginning of Newt's World.
Yes, you need to make the most of it.
Animal welfare certified pork ribs.
Oh, it did change.
OK, never mind.
I thought you were going to always going to say forever dog.
Like, huh?
Brett, what are you doing?
No, the wolf is dead.
This is not a good fit with the race chaser.
Yeah, I don't like that.
I don't like being on the same network.
What I heard was the first time I have ever heard this in my life, a podcast ad for Disneyland.
What for Disneyland on Newt's World?
Excuse me.
They do podcasts.
They do podcast ads at all.
And look, I'm sorry.
I just look, I know that they don't support us.
They don't invite us to anything.
Disney doesn't help us in any way.
That being said, you're going to advertise on the episode Biden's Radical First Hundred Days
and you're not going to advertise on a podcast where we talk about like a pseudo
pseudo crushes on your former CEO.
What do you like?
How are we dicey?
How are we a worse bet for them?
Look, the the the metrics of dynamic insertion of advertising is very complicated and they need
it's safer for them to put it in into the podcast where a chunk of the listeners probably think
Disneyland is the project of Hollywood sickos as opposed to us, a show where they're definitely
these three are definitely Hollywood.
They're part of the thing.
Yeah, just go cut out the middle man.
Go straight with the sickos.
Well, but was the ad was new doing the ad?
Was he like, do you like that one?
There is a place I got to recommend.
If you're feeling, are you feeling stressed out, tired, having trouble sleeping at night?
If so, I recommend Disneyland.
Add in the place to have a blast and forget about your troubles.
Add personal anecdote, it says on the copy that he's reading.
I got a chance to go there and I loved it.
Despite not having any Jurassic Park attractions, I did enjoy a dinosaur diorama that I got to see.
I was I left the park promptly after that, but otherwise enjoyed it very much.
So for 5% off your Disneyland ticket, type in new 20 Disneyland.
com.
Yeah, I, I hope it's dynamic insertion, but let's be honest.
Come on, Disney, just let us.
What are you?
We've spent so many hours talking about you.
Do some of the hours contain profanities?
Do we sometimes say that your old rides aren't good?
Yeah, but also we say so many nice things.
We are so in your spell.
We love you very much despite the complaints.
So who do you want?
Yeah.
Who do you want to reach out to?
Teenage influencers who are getting the Huntington Beach police called on?
You know, it's.
No, or the guy, the op-ed guy who's mad that Disney's changing.
That's who I mean, that's who that's or that Newt Gingrich had his for.
You don't, but you know what's happening.
All the people at Disney, they got their headphones in.
They're listening to hear forever.
And then the podcast, the ride intro starts.
And then when Josh tomorrow walks by, they got to quickly like hide it and turn the volume down.
They're all listening to us, but they can't, they don't want to get in trouble
because we're the bad boys of Disney press.
Theme park podcasting.
We're good boys.
Every another, every, every other avenue, but for Disney, we're the bad boys.
We lost them as soon as we said we like to get drinks and get drunk
is instead of adult life, but instead of dancing around it for a minute and a half.
Yeah.
I may have possibly indulged in a bit of sugar water that goes to the brain.
And yeah, we don't wear like cabbie style hats all the time.
Jason once in a while.
If it's cold.
Uh, but yes, you know, we don't have Jack Skellington, like denim jackets or anything.
We're not their typical good boy media.
Yeah.
We've never Instagram in front of the purple wall.
Right.
I may have Instagram from, I don't remember.
I've seen it.
Let's do it.
We got to get cuter.
You guys.
Well, you know what the answer is and Scott already obviously did the first part of the
daddy's are going to have to emerge and become the wholesome Disney news coverage that Disney
loves only positive, never say a negative thing about them.
They do not tolerate, uh, uh, uh, insolence.
Yeah.
So the new Avengers campus is a Marvel fans dream come true for Ant-Man to Iron Man.
You'll end everyone in between.
You're going to love it all.
The only thing that the only thing that will shrink at the pimp test kitchen is your appetite.
If you do that, it's okay to be just an absolute right wing psychopath on social media.
Yes.
Everything else can be awful.
Every woman who ever comments creep.
Yeah.
But as long as you're like, golly, g will occurs.
I thought I was launched into the stratosphere on that mission breakout.
I never want to break back in, but rocket's plan might go a little bit.
All right.
He may be called Dr.
Strange, but I call him Dr.
Fun show.
I really enjoyed the outdoor doctor, uh, Dr.
Strange show.
I'll tell you what, but I have three sons and I hate people that aren't like me.
He's that's the kind of girl.
That's the kind of person that they would.
We had my family at a great time at the park today, but nothing is more satisfying to me
than knowing Disney shareholders are completely satisfied with their financial fiduciary choices.
Thumbs up everyone.
Disney premiere is acceptably priced and honestly better than the theater experience,
but also go do that too.
I personally have seen Cruella seven times.
Cruella is one bossy bitch.
I mean, bossy bitch.
Hold on.
Massive strike.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
I just meant to say that she's a girl boss and that I think all the U S laws should
revert back to how they were in 1950.
Well, we love that first part and you cut out at the second.
I'm the star of Disney's media.
Of their journalists.
Walt wasn't really frozen in time, but we believe that all that that all U S laws should be.
66 was the time to preserve everything exactly as it is.
Except union membership.
We're very happy with the state of that.
Well, these are the Disney daddies folks.
Yeah, get used to them.
They're horrible monsters.
They're so bad, but look, just you'll hear us do that.
And you'll know that we're getting free stuff.
And podcast ad placements that make that get us $30 a week.
Is it worth it?
I say yes.
I agree.
Yeah, it's very worth it.
I can bring us back to universal.
Yeah, sure.
What have we we've been going a while, but what do we want to say about our universal trip?
Well, my I mean, my postmortem, I had a lot of fun at the taste of universal.
I did a couple of the not food festivals, too.
I think the food festivals were nice.
They were they were pleasant diversions from the awfulness of like the past 15 months.
Such blissful Oasis.
I think they did a good job.
It was fun to sample all the foods and eat outside.
I had a Korean what universal was calling a Korean corndog or Korean hot dog, which is just a
regular corn dog.
But it was at the end rolled in panko crumbs and sugar crystals.
And that was kind of neat.
I hadn't really had those, but I had never heard of that before.
But there is like a bunch of kind of crazy hot dogs all around the world.
So it was nice to get a taste of it.
I'm sure it's not the most authentic version of a Korean hot dog, but that was fun.
And I went to the I sampled the new Minions Cafe,
which is very cute.
It's over by the Despicable Me ride.
They put up a new facade on the old grew restaurant and there's a fun neon sign.
And they have little pudding cups, chocolate, banana, hazelnut pudding cups that look like
the minions.
They have little fondant minions.
Did you get one?
I did.
Yeah, it was good.
And no, no, no.
Chicken nachos, chicken, Tinga nachos, which were also pretty good.
Oh, and important.
We always like to see wax paper, restaurant specific cute wax paper.
That's great.
They had that.
Came to the movie.
That's nice.
I got the sense they were kind of stepping up their food game at a few locations that we ate at that day.
Got a little picture with the minion.
I think that's Bob the minion.
Oh, great.
Yeah, we got a selfie.
Yeah, I forget which one.
Yeah, I did not have such a great food day at Universal because I was running out of time.
I think I said in the other episode, I got there kind of late and I was leaving and we were going
to record and I said, well, I need to eat something.
I'm feeling weak again.
I'm not in theme park shape, but I need to get protein.
And I was like, I didn't know what to do.
I needed just something quick.
And I'm in Springfield and I'm like, do I wait in the chicken sandwich?
Maybe I do that.
But the line's kind of long.
I don't want a crusty burger.
Anytime I have a crusty burger, it's awful.
No, it's like fine, whatever.
So I go, oh, there's the hot dog place here.
I guess maybe I have a get a hot dog and I'm like, I'm walking along,
there's only two people ahead of me.
I look up and I'm like, it's how is it $12?
And all of a sudden, like they're gone and I have to step up.
So I step up and I try, I go, oh, you know what I'm going to do?
I'm going to ask because there's those Disney hacks where you go,
I'm just going to get the hot dog.
I don't want the combo and they'll give it to you.
Six dollars, seven dollars, you know?
And I go, oh, can I just get the hot dog a la cart?
And she goes, oh, we don't do that.
It's like same price.
I go, oh, okay.
And then I gave her a credit card, paid $12 for a boring hot dog and some chips.
And then like sadly ate it fast in Springfield and it wasn't bad.
It was just like that was serviceable.
Yeah, there was a hundred more fun things I could do than eating a sad hot dog
alone in Springfield.
Right.
We miss this, but these places, we've missed them so much.
Solo hot dog, solo expensive hot dog.
I made the absolute there's, I'm sure everyone has this experience in their life.
Sometimes where you go, I made, there were a hundred options and I made the worst
choice of all the options.
I could have done anything and it would have been better than this.
I would have like, it would have been better for money wise.
It would have been a better meal.
And I blew it.
I completely blew it.
It's like humiliate.
Those do stick with me.
I will be like talking about my wrong meal choice the whole rest of the night.
Aaron has long moved on.
You're still talking about this.
Yeah.
I was like, Oh, I had lofty goals before I could go city walk and grab something or
whatever, but I was like, no, no, I'm running out of time.
I need to do something quick.
Big mistake.
I got one thing exactly right, which is that am I getting braver on these things?
Certainly.
Brave enough to not need alcoholic assistance, not necessarily.
And this also just this being an outing after many months of pandemic newborn
parenting to be in a theme park and free and nice weather and vaccinated and all that.
We watched the gate on the Island new bar rise.
We were there at 1030.
As soon as we could possibly hit it, got some Mai ties, took them up to what I don't know
what it's officially called, but I am calling it Jurassic patio.
It's the seating area up above that restaurant.
Yeah, that's great.
That's really my God view of the, I mean, view of the hills, view of the ride, view of the starway.
The other way, it's just a lot of tropical plants.
This is the closest we felt to being in Hawaii.
This was a great little vacation for mom and dad.
At least that early, nobody up there.
So you're, you're the hack Jason of just get to that lower lot.
Definitely do that and get to Island new bar.
As soon as your stomach is willing to accept alcohol, get a Mai tie down.
And if it's also empty, Jurassic patio is, yeah, that's, that's my new pick of the park.
It's kind of game changer for that lower lot,
you know, new bar and I, they, I don't think the ice cream was running when I was there,
but I think they do the crazy shakes are crazy.
Do I almost did that too.
And I went, I may as well have said Michael, I don't mean to drive the knife further,
but one of the things they have introduced at a number of universal eateries is a hot
chicken sandwich.
And I know I at Mills and I think at the Hollywood and dine, they have that and they
beyond burgers now at a number of outlets to better, but they have that at the Pym too.
Test kitchen.
I know.
Okay.
Yeah.
A lot of plant based stuff coming to that Pym test kitchen.
I could talk about the menu for another hour.
Yeah.
Is that going to, maybe that's an episode.
Maybe we determine that.
Just pin menu.
Maybe.
There's a Schwarm a cart too.
Schwarm a cart.
Yeah.
Well, we'll try to get there soon enough for now.
This is the most recent newish stuff that we've done.
Have we, have we, have we missed anything about our universal?
I got to Jurassic patio.
I got my shout out.
Yeah.
Young people are wearing big pants again.
I said that in the last one.
They're wearing big pants that look like Jinko pants.
I didn't know about this.
This just sprung up on me.
It felt like overnight, but apparently it's been going on for a while.
And I don't know if I have anything else to say, but I go, Oh, it feels like I'm
young again.
I mean, I always want to feel like I'm young again, but I feel like,
Oh, this is what kids dress like back in my day.
That's a phrase I thought in my head.
Yeah.
That's what that's going to feel.
That's going to make you feel very useful.
Yeah.
Back in my day is occurring to you.
Back in my day.
Yeah.
So, um, that's true.
Oh, the thing we,
the thing we were talking about, we alluded to on the last episode is that
Optimus prime is now giving a speech.
Jason, could you find that?
Yeah, here, you know, maybe that's, is that the way out of the episode?
Perhaps.
Yeah.
Here.
Well, then let's start winding it down while we find it.
You survived podcast, the ride new and you survived the new
Indominus Rex.
Um, please keep it tuned here to patreon.
com slash podcast,
the ride for three bonus episodes every month.
m,
Uh, please go to, uh, will.
i.
in order to get to super mask.
com, uh, super mask, according to their Twitter,
uh, though the drops are sold out, but they, it is still the air Jordan of masks.
So it says in a tweet that gets a lot less likes than our tweets typically get, um,
follows super mask is looking pretty lonely at 636 followers.
So go support small business support
will.
i.
m and his artisan $300 Bluetooth mask endeavor launched, uh, right at the end of the
pandemic.
Yeah, that's a, yeah, we'll, we'll all do that.
We'll retweet a couple of super mask tweets.
You gotta help them out.
They give them a little bit of a signal boost.
They seem like good folks.
Um, Jason, have you had any luck?
I have it.
Yeah.
Um, do you want me to just play it or you want to play it later?
You set it up.
Yeah, well we'll play here and react to it.
Um, yeah, but optimist prime was welcoming
guests back to universal with a message that was very specific.
It was not just a general like,
yes, good to see you.
It was like these trying times have been different.
I mean, we'll hear it
Yeah, let's hear it.
This is Twitter user at cranky J.
This has been viewed 187.
9 thousand times.
Geez.
Super mask dream in those numbers.
It is so good to see all of you once more.
It has been a tough and trying year, but you know what?
We did it.
We did it together.
Fight is not over yet.
I can see light at the end of this dark tunnel.
I owe it to all of you for staying diligent, staying smart, staying safe, not believing the hype,
believing in yourselves and believing in each other.
We must protect one another if we're going
to make it on this planet.
And although we are built galaxies of art, in the end, you're just like us
more than it's the time.
I am Optimus drive.
I send this message to anyone who needs to hear it.
You're worth it.
You're part of the team.
I'm glad he got in like I'm Chevy chasing.
You are not.
I'm glad he got his taglines in there.
What about roll out?
You are one of us.
You're like that is such a funny speech.
It's so good.
It's kind of, it was kind of nice the day it went around like the internet and it was
like, oh, this is kind of nice to hear.
But then if you think about it too long, you're like,
there's some phrases he's not saying.
Like, like you can see the Republicans buy sneakers to cracks
through these companies.
What do you mean when he says don't believe that?
Don't believe the hype.
I don't know.
I don't know if that's like, I don't know if that's like a catch all.
They were like,
it's it can apply to QAnon, but it can also apply to like those weird Twitter doctors who are like
trying to scare everyone every day.
I don't know.
I'm not sure.
Maybe I think everything about it
was designed to be vague enough.
It's perfectly market tested.
Like we're all in this together.
Yeah.
Beware.
There are little decepticons in every drop of the vaccine.
You are being tracked.
You are, you are all now as valuable as the all spark.
You're being pursued to what end and for
what reason?
I don't know.
If you are vaccinated, watch out for evac.
He's on your ass.
He will punch you in the chest like he did to Megatron at the end of the ride.
There's one person who has all the answers that we're looking for and she's not talking.
Melinda Gates, I'm talking about you.
Tell us the truth.
What secrets are you holding?
Pretty odd timing.
Wouldn't you say divorce right after all this?
What does she know?
Autobots to little St.
James.
We must examine the evidence.
All right.
That's it.
We're out of here.
Goodbye.
But you made us proud.
We're proud of you.