Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcasts may contain graphic monkey jerk-off sessions, fake teenage
cowboys who want to murder for real, and a special appearance by a monster.
Chris Gether joins us for thrills and spills at New Jersey's Six Flags Great Adventure
on Podcast The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the theme park podcast to where the hosts are often referred
to as good boys, but today we're Jersey Boys.
I'm Scott Garner, joined by Mike Carlson.
I'm here and I'm gonna do like an attitude but not a voice.
This is an attitude, okay?
I want to make that a distinction.
I'm not doing a voice.
I just have sort of like kind of a different authority to my person today.
So the only that's a good move.
The only person probably with any legitimacy to a Jersey voice might be Jason Sheridan.
Hi.
Yeah, sure.
I spent half of my adolescent, you know, summers and then, you know, some other weekends at
the Jersey Shore growing up.
So yeah, I got closer than us.
And at today's topic, this was my home, Six Flags, a local Six Flags, because it's kind
of equidistant between Philadelphia and New York.
Right, right.
Well, yeah, this is great.
I think, you know, we'll talk not just about this, but, you know, some other great theme
park destinations in the Garden State.
And we're doing it with, I mean, I feel like a New Jersey expert, at least a New Jersey
native and a veteran podcaster and broadcaster, the star of the new special Half My Life.
I'm so excited.
Chris Gethard is here.
Jersey expert on hand for all your needs.
So happy to be here.
Thanks for having me.
Thanks for owning that.
That does seem like the case.
You are a champion of this place.
You didn't flee.
You aren't ashamed.
I went back.
I was out and I voluntarily went back in.
Yeah, I mean, I'm on a pretty open, self-proclaimed quest to try to become like the comedy Springsteen
where like Jersey people are like, that's our guy.
I would love that.
That would be a huge accomplishment.
So happy to hear happy to be here representing.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, we've done a little.
We found there's a Jersey Hall of Fame, I think we found recently.
That's where I was going to go.
Yeah.
Are you aware of the Jersey Hall of Fame?
I am.
Do you think you have a way to get in?
I would love it more than anything.
And I'm aware of it because when Springsteen got inducted, his speech, he said, just one
of the coolest things I've ever heard.
You're like, that's why he's Springsteen.
He had some line in his speech about he's like, I always love to watch boxing matches
with guys from our home state because you just watch their opponent.
And when the announcer says, hail in from the great state of New Jersey, you just see
their shoulders drop a little bit because they know what they're in for.
And you're like, oh, that's the coolest.
You're the coolest.
And such a cool idea.
What a cool thing.
That's so great.
Anything he says any time during especially that like Netflix special, you feel like it
was workshopped by like 50 of the smartest writers.
But you know, it just like came from the most brilliant, like poetic mind on the planet.
That Hall of Fame where we for some reason, we end up talking about Southside Johnny a
lot on the show.
So a lot.
When you say a lot.
Well, for like versus any other of these type of podcasts.
Once or twice.
Yeah, like a lot.
A lot.
Yeah.
Like Doughboys.
They never talk about Southside Johnny.
I can't imagine in what context Southside Johnny's coming up.
We do a lot.
We like we like your more obscure music guys on this show.
So he pops in here and there and he's in, I believe, the Hall of Fame as well.
I would be shocked if he wasn't.
Him and the Asbury Jukes.
Let's get the Jukes.
Yeah, let's get the Jukes.
Little Steven, I believe.
Of course, Little Steven.
He may still be trapped in the hologram booth at Newark Airport where it is it's unclear
what speech he's giving in the hologram.
I can tell you right there.
You out it yourself as having spent time in Jersey but not of Jersey because you said
Newark.
Well, my Jersey.
That's Delaware.
Because you're closer to Delaware.
Where is the Norc?
Yeah, my Jersey stomping grounds, besides outings to Six Flags Great Adventure, were South Jersey
Point, Ocean City, Atlantic City, Wildwood occasionally for comic conventions.
My parents met in splitting a vacation, a rental house in Sea Isle City where my dad
and his friends were on one floor and my mom and her friends were on another floor.
That's beautiful.
Perfect story.
Yeah.
It lasted for like 20 plus years.
Nice.
Pretty good.
You said Newark.
As soon as you said Newark, I said, OK, that's the Philly influence.
You also probably say Wooder.
I say, yeah, I do slip into Wooder.
It's been great with Mayor of Easttown because I can just tell people I'm from Delaware County
now and they understand.
There you go.
That's how I felt with Sopranos.
Sure.
We're talking about this.
Both, I'll ask this to Jason and Chris, like your favorite park growing up, maybe this
is obvious, maybe I even asking this, other than like Disney World or going like your
favorite park that was around.
We're talking about Great Adventure today, right?
I'd have to go with that just because, first of all, it's like it's the most it's the one
in Jersey everybody went to.
Not everybody went to Action Park.
Despite all the legends of Action Park, a lot of people stayed away and it was pretty
remote.
So everybody said we would have stayed away.
God, when we covered it, we're like, I can't I can't get into the mind space of this at
all.
I mean, it was heaven.
It was heaven.
It was like the floor to the flies.
It was everything people say.
Great Adventure had its own really macabre stories about it, too.
And I was there all the time because my father worked at Pfizer Pharmaceuticals and they
used to have their company picnic there every summer.
And if you went, you got to go for that day on the picnic.
And then they also gave you tickets to come back another day.
So we always went to Great Adventure twice a year.
But then there's all the smaller places, too.
You know, your Bo Crafts, your Wild West cities.
There's a lot of up and down the boardwalk.
There's all the all the different rides.
So a lot of a lot of places in our general area, Sesame Place, Dorney Park, Hershey Park,
also being in the Philly scene.
But and then Rye Playland up near on the other side of New York, Westchester.
But Great Adventure felt to me like kind of the.
The center of gravity with theme parks that I grew up around.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Jason agreed.
Yeah, I liked Great Adventure a lot.
And we would we would hit a lot of those places growing up.
I mean, my family was a big park family and and a great adventure.
Yeah, Dorney Park is just a quick shot up to Allentown.
And because we were in P.A.,
Hershey Park was about 90 minutes away, 90 minutes, two hours.
So that was our our other big one.
What about Sesame Place?
I made it down to Sesame Place a few times.
Once or twice I went to Sesame.
I remember going to Sesame Place and liking all of the water attraction stuff.
And but knowing like I am too old to be here, like I am like nine or something.
And I'm like, this is even at nine or 10.
It's like, oh, this is I am an old child here.
The last time I went to Sesame Place, I went with my friend Lenny's family.
We're all a little too old.
And I it just came back to me.
The memory that we we actually got in trouble at Sesame Place.
And I looked back at it actually makes me laugh so hard because Lenny and I,
we were a little too old.
That's like mostly kiddie rides and ball pits and stuff, you know.
And we went in the lazy river or probably like eighth grade at the time.
And one of us noticed that there was change on the ground.
So we started like diving down and picking up all the change.
And then we enlisted my friend's little brother and we just kept going around
and one of the lifeguards caught us and was like, you can't do that.
Give me all the money.
And we had like probably like 18 or 19 dollars between us.
And then we told his dad.
And I remember Lenny's dad was like, they probably just go through
and pick it all up at the end of the night themselves.
That's why they're pissed. Let's go.
And for some reason, my friend's daddy went back.
He went 11 of that dollars of that money was theirs.
Some of that money was theirs that they brought with.
We just had a million dollars worth of change in our bathing suit pockets somehow.
But watching my friend Lenny's dad get in a contentious argument
with a teenage lifeguard at Sesame Place, I have not thought about that one in many years.
Negotiation. I agree.
That's only fair.
And that's a beautiful Philadelphia memory right there.
You know, it's very that mixed.
The relationship between Jersey and Philly could you could write volumes on volumes.
Oh, yeah.
Hi, Craig. Yeah.
Hey, I don't know anything about it.
I know. I know. Wisconsin, Chicago.
That's what I know. You know, I know.
There's like a dividing line between the states and even between North and South Jersey,
where like you can see the shops start calling sandwiches.
They stop calling them subs and start calling them hoagies,
whether they call it Taylor pork roll or Taylor ham.
That's a big difference.
Sprinkles or jimmies.
And yeah, North Jersey suburbs are all kind of affiliated with New York
because a lot of commuters go there.
South Jersey is more Philly.
But then in general, it's funny because I feel like in the past five to ten years,
this has actually changed.
And Philly's gotten very artsy and it always had an art scene, but very much so.
But there was always a thread growing up of like the city,
like New York City people think that they're better than you.
That's why we don't like them in Jersey.
But Philly people, you have to watch out because they're completely fucking insane.
Like Philly people are out of their minds.
So there was also that of like.
Like like New Yorkers are snooty, so we don't like them for that.
But then Philly people, they're almost like kind of like feral animals,
and you just don't know what they're ever going to do.
And that was kind of the and I think there's still some probably truth to that,
that being the at least the cliche.
Like, man, like a lot of my friends, I will say,
the craziest night of their life took place in Philly.
Like when the Jersey people go out to party, we're like, yeah, things just got
way too out of control in Philly.
That's not that's that's a pretty common thing, I think.
Yeah, like a real like wild card, maybe there wasn't even a definition
of what type of craziness you'd get up to.
I remember actually, and I'm not trying to like slip in an extra plug
when we we filmed at a theater in Philly for my special.
And we were driving to the venue and my buddy Dave,
who was doing camera that night, and he goes, whoa.
And I go, what? And he's in the back of the minivan.
He goes, we just passed a guy on a bike and he was wearing a Jason mask.
And it was like nowhere close to Halloween.
And he's like, he's just driving around on a bike in a Jason mask.
I was like, well, yeah, like we're in Philly, Dave, like we are like.
It's like.
Like we feel like that's not I'm not saying that it's like happens all the time,
but like you should expect to see one completely
inexplicable thing on a trip to Philly like that's right.
So yeah, this is not out of bounds.
No. In his memoir, like David Lynch describes Philadelphia
as like the darkest place he's ever lived.
Like not surprised.
One of the biggest influences on his work.
And then he moved to L.A.
and immediately started making a razorhead.
And that's just what you know, you come out of Philly.
My brother went to LaSalle University
and he moved down there in 1995.
And I remember I'd go to visit him and I was a sophomore in high school.
And it was like I remember sleeping over his house one night.
We went to a 40 store and I'd never seen it.
Philly, they just have stores just for beer.
Like, wow, this one is just 40s.
Beverage distributors.
Yeah. Pennsylvania liquor laws are kind of weird.
It's it's it's insane.
You can get beer at one place or you can get it at a takeout at a pizza place.
You can get a six pack and then liquor and wine.
You have to get at state stores.
It's very complicated.
We were at this 40 store and we paid.
And as we went to leave, this guy walked into the door
and he was wearing sweatpants and no shirt and he was carrying like a weed whacker.
And he said, OK, you guys got any change?
And we're like, yes, sir.
Of course we do. Like, what are you going to say?
Like, sure. Of course.
You watched us get our change and you're you're wielding a lawn
implement like a weapon. So, yeah, yeah, we have a change.
We have change.
Yeah, I know that Philly, I know that Philly fanatic.
But if you walk around Philly, are there like a bunch of those?
Is that like a like a type of animal that's just roving the streets?
Yes. Yes.
It's the hundreds on hundreds.
You know, we should we should talk about the actual park talk.
But I do have one more question.
Jason, Jason is a very I would say he does not into a lot of wild stuff as a kid.
But he does sometimes surprise us with mentions of like East Coast stuff.
And I was going to ask Chris, did you eat the meat Scrapple as a kid?
Scrapple is kind of the that areas Taylor Ham, which was mentioned.
OK, they're both these kind of like hideous mystery meats.
Like definitely, you know, like like pork products made out of like a bunch of like
lips and toenails and rights and stuff like that.
And yes, Scrapple, I think I always associate more with Pennsylvania.
Taylor Ham is similar kind of.
I call it Taylor Ham because I'm from North Jersey.
You will see I promise you, you will see tweets from people when this comes out,
going like, fuck you, it's pork roll because people get really mad.
It's either whatever you call it.
It's like like a very sort of looks like Canadian bacon, like a round pork product.
But it's just so gross.
It's like dirty and you fry it up on a griddle.
And a lot of times you eat it on a sandwich with egg and cheese.
And it's so delicious.
I stopped eating meat a few years ago and I still am like,
I have one thing is going to get me to go back.
It's Taylor Ham. It's it's like every time you eat it,
you probably take 36 hours off the end of your life, but it tastes really good.
Please don't say that. I don't have a lot of time left if that's the case.
I've just eaten my weight five times over in Taylor Pork Roll.
I just it's so surprising because it's such a though I never knew anything about it
as a kid or even even like up until a year or two ago.
And then when Jason said it, it sounded like something a little rascals ate.
So well, on the board, some of the boardwalks, it's like you go to burger places
and you can get a cheeseburger or a cheesesteak hot dog
where you get a pork roll sandwich, just pork roll and cheese.
And you add ketchup or mustard or lettuce and mayo.
And my favorite place to get it burned down,
burned down like a few months ago.
And it was next to an amusement park like in an amusement park,
the arcade of an amusement park that was a been in big hangar
that had been moved from a World's Fair.
Do you want to do a parody song?
They blew up the Scrapple Man in Philly last night.
I like that. Yeah.
The boardwalk also legendary.
I mean, I I'm sure you guys have talked about the Jersey Shore boardwalks, right?
A little bit.
Not yet. Not yet.
He's bringing me back because waiting for the opus
because there's also these there's a lot of boardwalks down there
that I'll have these big spinning wheels that's just like pay a dollar,
spin the wheel, win a prize.
And very often, one of the prizes is a two pound
log of Taylor Ham.
Whoa. I can just imagine you're out.
You're out, you know, you're showing your girl a good night.
You get the cotton candy.
You go on some rides.
You play the game where you try to get the frog to the end of the lily pad.
And the next thing you know, you got to carry around a two pound
log of meat all day because you got over ambitious.
Some of these wheels are so fun.
You could literally win a carton of cigarettes.
You could win. Wow.
Like like any random bullshit, man.
The Jersey Shore is those boardwalks you guys would love.
You would love.
And we got to we got to go, it sounds like we got to do it.
Well, I want to get there and like do like in lieu of a live show,
just get people find this place where you win the ham and have Jason.
The audience members just pay Jason until he wins.
It's just like everyone collectively win Jason a ham. Yeah.
Yeah, that would be great. Jason's came for it.
I didn't play the wheel. That's North.
Again, that's that's the North.
That's Asbury Park and Seaside Heights.
Wildwood a little.
Yeah, I would say wild wild.
Wildwood and Seaside are regarded as the two sleaziest.
Like there's rides and there's games and fights out on the boardwalk.
And then quite pleasant is a little bit more family, but still elements of that.
And those are those are the ones I think of that have a lot of ride driven stuff.
Yeah, the bigger coasters and and there's something.
OK, and everything you just listed, it seems like there is some like
there's varying degrees of trashiness to a lot of these places.
And then when we were going back and forth on what are we going to talk about?
And we you know, the Six Flags Great Adventure came up.
There's also this place, Wild West City.
And we know, you know, you're a fan of Action Park.
Collectively, all of this is just like so many of these places are so
dangerous and accident plagued.
Like the quote incidents section on the Wikipedia of this place.
Goes on and on and on.
I will dive in, but I wanted to ask you real quick on the way
because you brought up this thing, Wild West City, which is I take is a
I mean, it's what the titles it's like a little miniature
Western town where there's little shows and demonstrations
like horse shows and whip shows and the like.
Yeah. And they they do like a shootout at the OK Corral show.
And it's I believe it was built in the 50s and really hasn't been updated.
It's kind of in some ways, it's actually kind of lovely
that it still exists and is hanging on because it's in Netcong, New Jersey.
It's like the middle of nowhere.
And they have a bar that serves the saloon serves real beard appearance.
And then the kids run around with these shows.
And then this was something I had thought was a legend.
And then recently found out it's real because I do a New Jersey podcast
with friends of mine and my one buddy was like, no, this is real.
And he found the news articles that two of the cowboys
at Wild West City had developed a hatred for each other.
And one of them put real bullets in his gun and killed him during one of the shows
and tried to play it off like a Brandon Lee accident.
Oh, my God. Oh, I thought it was blanks.
I don't know how that happened.
And then they found out, no, you just that was your that was your alibi
to kill him in plain sight.
And by plain sight, we mean during a show aimed at children and the whole.
And when I tell you that the whole place is.
Smaller than a city block, I'm not exaggerating like it's tiny, it's tiny.
Wow. Wow.
And you're going to you're going to pull off a murder.
You think you're going to successfully pull off a murder
with with a boy with a bunch of suspects willingly.
Like the whole point is for these suspects to the suspects paid to be here.
You're trying to be here. Yeah, it's really not a not a
not the toughest case to crack, I would imagine.
Yeah. So you put a bullet in your gun and you shot that man.
And they saw these. Everyone saw it.
Yes. There's an audience.
There's a paying audience. Yes.
These children have no reason to lie.
They saw what they saw.
It was it was like one of them was a bandito and the other one was Wyatt Earp.
I don't know which was which.
I don't know who shot first.
But these are and these are teenagers.
The day that a teenage Wyatt Earp shot a teen bandito.
What a day. That's so insane.
There's a lot of strange, a lot of really intense stuff where where I grew up.
Really intense. Yeah. Well, this is kind of that's what I'm getting at is like,
like I just try to dissect the the character of it all.
And how do these parks end up so particularly insane
and full of incidents and accidents?
What is it about the place?
Well, it's a really good question.
And I thought a lot about it.
And I think that
for whatever reason, maybe it's because it is between New York and Philly.
And maybe there's like
some insecurity, too, I'm sure.
But there's like this.
I think there's this real like priority on being tough in New Jersey.
Like you kind of have to be tough.
And that's a very valued thing.
So I kind of feel like it's sort of built.
For these sorts of places, because.
It's like not only is it like you should go on this roller coaster that's super high,
it's almost where we're from, like the more rickety, the better.
And the less safe it is, the the more you got to like demonstrate your balls by going on it.
So there's almost like a death wish where I grew up with.
I think it's the short way to put it.
But and there's like a sick pride in getting hurt.
And.
A really unhealthy obsession with.
You know.
Don't be a pussy to just like put it frankly, hopefully by the voice,
you can hear that I'm mocking that attitude, but especially in the 80s and 90s,
that was really, really omnipresent and not just in theme parks, like
being a music kid, he used to go to punk shows.
There were always fights like there were just always like there was just a lot of
it was there was just a lot of you always had your guard up.
You always felt like things were going to go wrong.
You kind of expected them to go wrong.
And for some reason, we found it very fun and funny when they did.
And it was almost like a point of pride to be at the center of a disaster.
So, yeah, Jersey is just a place that's very.
Kind of obsessed with toughness, I think, to its detriment,
for as much as I love New Jersey and obsess over it.
I hope my son growing up there doesn't feel this constant need to just sort of
prove his toughness, but that was always there.
So it's like the more potential that a thing could be a disaster.
It was sort of like that was like moths to the flame almost, you know,
in many areas of growing up.
The danger, anything was like dangerous, like thrived, at least at a certain time,
because obviously, like there's still stuff that's there that's dangerous,
but obviously, like theme parks now are like the disnification of so much of stuff,
or the corporatization of so many things have happened.
But I assume the others we were talking about, there's still places,
especially in Jersey, where you can feel it still.
You can feel the danger.
Yeah, I think. Yeah.
Jersey knows it's not New York. Jersey knows it's not Philly.
It's like we know that there's a lot of derision towards the state
and it creates this kind of internal pressure cooker.
It's also so densely, it's the most densely populated state.
So everybody's on top of each other all the time.
So it's like you're constantly
it, you constantly always feel like you're kind of being judged or looked at,
or, you know, like you don't want to go on a ride and scream
because you know that somebody's right there is going to make fun of you.
And it just creates this thing of,
like I said, this thing that's very hard to verbally explain, that's just,
oh, that's the thing where I might get my head lopped off.
Well, then I should just go do it because why? Fuck you.
That's why. That's kind of the attitude.
The whole. I.
I found this picture of a sign that's in in today's park.
Six Flags Great Adventure.
I had I vaguely remember seeing this sign,
but it did it. It's surprising to me a little.
And it's the bluntest side.
It reads warning line cutters will be ejected from the park
with no refund.
Anyone who leaves the line for any reason must return at the end of the line.
And usually like that's polite or, you know, matters dictate that.
And people, you know, if they have a good excuse, people usually let people through.
But that's a really stern sign to put it like a family entertainment center.
A lot of exclamation points. Yeah. Yeah.
It's like pointing a finger at you. Yeah.
To be clear, probably this is at the one that's probably the most above board
option in New Jersey is Great Adventure.
And and one of the nicest six flags, too, because it's filled with like
it's got a lot of interesting stuff.
It's filled with a lot of tall trees.
There's a big lake.
There's a questionable safari park.
That's that's one of the main things to talk about, by the way, with great.
Oh, oh, please. Yeah. Yeah.
That's Safari Park.
I just remember we did it a couple of times as a kid and
you drive your own car through it.
And yes, you didn't just used to do that.
You can still do that.
Now, I think they've put up more fences because the slideshow I found from like
the 70s showed like giraffes just crossing the road,
big cats right next to the shoulder of the road, like lions and tigers.
And it's like the great adventure safari.
There were rumors about great adventure.
The big ones being the things everybody heard were the biggest one was
you have to wear a hairnet on free fall if you have long hair because a girl's
hair got tangled up and her scalp got ripped off.
Everyone in New Jersey heard that story.
I think there's versions of that around the country.
I think that's a very popular park urban legend.
I know that their haunted house did burn down and a bunch of kids died
and a bunch of people got really messed up on this ride.
Lightning loops, this roller coaster that went backwards loop.
So yeah, and that said a safety precedent for like
worldwide roller coasters had to upgrade like safety measures
because of that. Yeah, because of lightning loops.
Wow. I didn't know that.
Well, they didn't want to incur the punishment that was leveled at Six Flags,
like whatever board or bureau regulating these things,
rules not in favor of Six Flags, and they were forced to pay one thousand dollars
like the ultimate price.
What was the way? What was the lightning loops thing?
What was the the accidents doing now?
I believe the safety harness.
Let's see. I have it here.
Lightning loops.
Teenage girl was thrown from the train because she was seated
on the wrong side of the shoulder restraint.
And so I think that means she's sitting in front of the restraint.
So not locked in at all.
So, yeah, that's the wrong side, I would say.
I guess traditionally where you sit.
That's that's how I interpret it.
But then there's other little things like, yeah, like Chris was saying,
with this fire park, we were told at the entrance of this fire park,
please retract your car's antenna or unscrew the antenna.
Otherwise, monkeys will rip it off and then they will wail on your car.
We got to talk about this, because I was saying all those legends
about what happened in the park.
You always heard those.
You talk to anybody who grew up around my era.
The the safari was where the true insanity happened.
I went through it so many times.
You're not wrong. Those animals were running free.
And Emu once attacked my car, once started slamming its face
into the window right next to my poor brother.
My poor brother always weird things happen to him.
And Emu started trying to smash the glass.
I saw elephants having sex there.
There was a really there was one of these crazy things where
and me and my friends have talked about it for some reason.
It was always church groups.
You'd see these church vans and they'd always be the ones rolling down
their windows, trying to like feed a giraffe cheese.
It's and then the next thing you know, there's like animals
charging the church van and then the Wranglers got to come out.
But the baboons were legendary.
You just mentioned the thing about the the antennas.
That was very true.
There were a few other things about it, because from what I remember,
the baboons, I think, were the last section of the safari.
And it was known that they were like not under control.
They had these pink butts.
I remember that.
And the two things you knew, the antenna thing we all heard
and the other thing that was so great
was, if you remember in the 90s, they're still around today,
but they're like real classic cars, those cars that have kind of like the,
you know, it'll be like an old man car with like that leather or pleather
top half, if you know what I mean.
Yeah, like antique cars, antique cars were like a go to at parks like this.
And you're like kids rides.
Now they will.
Now they'd be antiques.
But back then, you'd still see like a 1984 Chevy celebrity
or Monte Carlo or something.
And some of those cars from those era, they had these tops.
I'm sure there is a name for them, but they basically be material.
And there would be signs everywhere.
And before you ever showed up, you were told if you have one of these cars
that has like a fabric or material top.
Don't drive it through here.
These baboons will destroy it.
And it almost became part of the fun because you'd be in this line of cars
inching through and you'd be looking around, go to any of these assholes.
Did any of them do it?
And you'd see it happen.
These baboons would seize upon these cars.
And you just see a dozen baboons coming, screaming with joy, ripping it apart.
And I mean, you'd see I had baboons have sex on the hood of my dad's car.
They'd be jacking off.
They'd be having sex.
They'd be throwing feces like.
And I remember so distinctly that at the end of the baboon section,
there was a guy, it was like a fence that I assume must have been electrified.
And there was the opening for the cars to get out.
And there was a guy who would sit there with like a bunch of,
I think, probably like German shepherds, like attack dogs.
And he had like a taser.
And his whole job was that when the baboons try to like
flee through that car entrance, he has to like use these dogs
and this gun to get them out of there and get them off the top of your cars.
And the safari was lawless in the best way.
And I have a lot of really good memories about it.
But, yeah, those, it was just so on.
I tell you, anybody who was a kid when those cars were still on the road right now,
who who went there knows exactly what I'm talking about.
These baboons would rip these things to shreds.
They would rip them to shreds.
And it was the best because that's another thing.
Another thing about that Jersey attitude is like
sometimes bad things will happen to people.
And there's very, very little sympathy if they deserved it.
Like in Jersey, it's kind of like if you want to drive your dumb
fucking car with that fabric top through and a monkey rips it up, I will laugh.
I will not feel like I'm not going to feel bad for you at all.
Because it was the safari is one of the great underrated
chaos pits of New Jersey is the great adventure safari.
Hands down, that place is the best.
I've heard it's better now, but I hear that it's not
not totally. It's yeah, it's not like it still says, like, allow 1.5
to three hours to get through.
And that's it back.
It would back up a lot.
We'd just be sitting there and then you'd see a car a few ahead of you.
And it's like, do they have their windows down?
Some accrete, an animal is coming towards that car.
And you would you. Yeah, you would see people like put the windows up,
put the windows up.
Yeah, just some asshole needs to try to feed a rhino, a Ritz cracker.
And now all of us have to wait here 90 extra minutes for this thing
to stop trying to tip this car over onto its side.
It's just the best.
And when you were a kid, Chris, because we three are notoriously for the podcast.
There's not in, you know, widespread America scared kids.
We were three kids where we the littlest thing would make us nervous.
Like when you were eight or nine, were you cheering at the baboon
jacking off on the car?
I was also a very scared kid.
I was constantly terrified.
I mean, I was raised in a generation where it was just satanic panic and
kidnappings and all this stuff.
So I was scared all the time, but I took a lot of sick joy.
And other people's pain, I guess you could say like similar to the
action park thing where, you know, you'd wait at the bottom.
You know, everybody was waiting by the Tarzan swing to cheer when people
got completely obliterated.
Same thing.
I would say.
Pretty much, you know, the first time you went through the great
adventure safari, you were probably psyched to go look at the animals.
Every other time you went through it, I would say that it was probably
increasing percentage wise, how much you were just there to see dumb
idiots get their comeuppance.
That's true.
That's what the whole theme of it was, was like, you could maybe, you know,
you could see an emu and it might sprint right past your car.
Or if you want to throw a cheeto on the ground next to it, now you might see a,
an angry emu attack the passenger seat while your mother screams.
And like, there's, I gotta say, like, I know it maybe is a little sick, but
like, it's really funny to watch.
It's really funny to watch because it's not, there's a million signs.
That say, don't behave like an idiot.
And they, there's so many signs.
There's just so many things you shouldn't do.
And then you see somebody who's just ignoring all them to do those things.
And yeah, maybe now I'll get to see, now maybe I get to see a swarm of over
stimulated baboons ejaculating all over your windshield.
Like that's, that's awesome.
It's like instant karma.
There's some really something to love there.
Yeah.
They should have like just videotaped 40 years of this and made a clip show out of
it, like animals attack clip show.
Oh, I bet they could have.
There's gotta be a lot of footage smuggled out.
I also know it's in, it's in Jackson, New Jersey, and two of my best friends from
college are from Jackson.
And they told me that there's all these like off road trails in the woods and all
the kids who grew up in that area know that like you can drive your four wheeler
back there at night and just be alongside the fence.
So it's like, you could take a date and be like, you want to go see some fucking
live giraffes right now so kids know how to get back there.
That close during the pandemic, two kids, I think just drove in.
They just found a back way and were just rolling around in there.
Really?
Oh, that's awesome.
Like the only people who got in in that eight month lockdown period or whatever
long it was.
Oh, I love that.
I love there's other stories of like, Chris, I don't know if you ever wrote, we
talked about this on a previous show when we were talking about Batman based rides,
but there there was a kind of short lived roller coaster called Batman and Robin,
the chiller, which was famously technical difficulty prone because it used a
launching system that drew on the like it drawed so much power it was starting to
cause brown outs and it it opened for like a day or so and then they had to
shut it down for months and months and months to to rejigger this.
When Universal Studios Florida opened a coaster with a similar launch, they built
a power substation so they did not blow the grid for the city of Orlando.
In Jacksonville and Six Flags learned that the hard way.
So eventually this ride was shuttered because it was also very rough.
They kept trying to make it smoother and then they they took it apart and for a
long time pieces of it were just sitting in a field rotting and rusting like by
by the park and then they were supposed to sell it to a theme park in South
America and then the deal fell through and then I think it just it was just
scrapped. But like just just a rusting Batman like ten foot tall Batman insignia
in a farm.
I just had another memory come back because I don't love roller coasters.
I've never been a huge roller coaster fan and they have there's a roller
coaster they have called Rolling Thunder, which is like this kind of very
charming wooden roller coaster like not you know they have like the sleek metal
ones with all the loops and stuff.
This is just one of those ones you just go up real high and it's like the clack
clack clack clack clack clack like that thing.
And I would go on that one because it wasn't you know you didn't go upside down
and there's actually a video of me that I think is still on the Internet where I
went on it and my friend in the seat in front of me was filming my friend and I
and it stopped at the top and it froze which is kind of the nightmare for
anybody who doesn't like roller coasters.
And it then proceeded and there's a video of me because I lost my mind.
It started going and I was like no wait it's broken it's broken.
No it's not it.
And I had there's a video of me having an actual nervous breakdown on Rolling
Thunder.
Oh wow.
But that's one of those good ride like one of those old wooden ones where you're
like you get off and you feel like you were just in a boxing match taking body
blows you know because you're getting like tossed around side to side.
I always enjoyed Rolling Thunder.
Well Chris you got the last laugh because that that one closed in I believe 2013.
No that's yeah that was an old classic.
Still on board with it despite the like attack it into yours like no don't you
can't kill it.
That's again like it's the same action park thing right.
Like what am I going to tell you the stories about the rides where I went on and
it was fun and then I got off like.
No I want to tell you about the one where you were physically in pain at the end of
it and also it broke while I was on it like that's that's a fun story.
Drove you.
Yeah.
I have the stories about the fun stuff and then I got off.
Yes.
I'm the host.
What the show is a lot of the time.
Yeah.
It's fun to go on Space Mountain isn't it.
Yeah it is.
Successful journey.
Yep we love it.
Six Flags I will say Six Flags still has you know of the big three of Universal
Disney Six Flags Six Flags does still have some of the spirit we're talking
about because you can there are a lot of people not paying any attention when
you're getting loaded on a ride at Six Flags like you can still there are antics
at Six Flags and like you know teen like a lot of teen employees that are like so
checked out and you could easily see where stuff like slips in the crack so
they're like I guess what I'm saying is you can still find it's like it's like
you know it's like Green Day they used to be an authentic punk band but they'll
still play the echo plex once in a while you know they still have elements where
they're actually trying to do the old the old spirit stuff.
And the equivalent of that is that under skilled underpaid employees.
Yeah.
Will sometimes not strap you into the thing.
Green Day playing a 500 seat place or is similar to like a teen just going yeah
are you ready okay I'm not going to check the restraint and then hit the
button for the ride to go.
Now here's exactly the same.
You guys may know more about than I do but another thing that my my co-hosts on
my New Jersey podcast hit me to that I did not know which is apparently in both
the the boardwalk ride attractions of New Jersey Six Flags all the theme parks in
New Jersey apparently a lot of the people who work there are actually very
young Russian people because there's apparently some system set up where it's
pretty easy for Russian kids to get a work visa at New Jersey theme parks.
Wow.
I've been told that a lot of these workers who might not be paying the most
attention may actually be Russian people on theme park specific visas.
I thought I thought that might be some food for thought that would get your
guys gears turn in.
Sure.
Yeah that feels like we could do a two hour investigative episode about.
I have not heard that.
I don't know if you guys have.
I know a little about that.
I hadn't heard specifically Russian but at Ocean City where my family always went
there's two two parks Playland and Wonderland and yeah very young workers and
you hear a lot of like European or Eastern European accents and and there is
a thing.
Yeah there's a work exchange you know summer work exchange where they they
they like put them up in like you know big old either either rental houses or old
converted hotels and then they work you know make money all summer and then they
go back back home.
Yeah my friend Nick has also I believe been to the exact places you're
describing and he says that there are like shockingly hot young Russian workers
at all of these places male and female.
He's just like they're stunningly beautiful Russians that are the people
like strapping you into the haunted house that looks like it's about to break down
for good like very big dichotomy.
There's a six flags exclusively using like hot Russian models to operate the
in in Bugs Bunny outfit.
You can't even tell they're in.
I don't know.
I have a story about that too if you want it.
Sure.
These people in the in the in the Looney Tunes outfits I realize now as an adult
that those that's probably not the best gig you know being out there on a humid
August day.
Yeah that that's another thing I think adding to some of the the vibe at a lot
of New Jersey and Pennsylvania theme parks these places are only open like nine
months of the year because the fall and winter is come so quick and the summers
are so hot and humid like this Swamp Land it's converted Swamp Land so like
tensions can run high in long waits and so to be in a Daffy Duck outfit and it's
a hundred degrees with a hundred degree humidity like a hundred percent humidity.
It's not ideal and I wish I felt more empathy as a child but I didn't and my
brother and I found it very funny to torment the people in those costumes and
there was one year we were there for the the Pfizer family picnic and my brother
just kept relentlessly messing with the guy dressed as foghorn leg horn.
When we went to leave there's a big fountain that's sort of you know you walk
up the entrance and maybe 30 yards up or so there's a big fountain and as we were
leaving we were walking past back back past the fountain and my brother saw
foghorn leghorn he ran over to mess with him one more time and the guy dressed as
foghorn leghorn took my brother's hat off his head and threw it into the fountain.
I find I hold that memory very near and dear I'm just you know think that I'm
like you're a kid you're like let's mess with that's fuck with that guy.
Then I'm an adult now I'm 40 I'm like that guy was probably like four years
older than us pissed like it's probably his last summer before he goes to
college.
She's like got a girlfriend she's like waiting for him to get off this dumb
shift but he's gonna be even later because he has to go take a shower
because he sweated off a third of his soaking wet.
He's so mad he's here he's already dressed in his foghorn leghorn for his
job.
None of the hot Russians want to hook up with him and his foghorn leghorn and he's
got this pimply face do we mess with him just takes his hat and throws it in
the fountain.
I hope he quit that night.
I hope that I hope that I hope the manager was like we have footage of you
throwing that hat he's like out of here dude.
Hope that was the end of that nonsense for him.
I would just like to say I found some something that reference that at one
point marketing for Six Flags Great Adventure referred to the park as the
greatest day of your life.
So keep that in mind.
My memory was of a radio jingle where they they really you know they were
stayed up all night burning the midnight oil to come up with Six Flags Great
Adventure.
We had fun and that was it.
That was it.
That blade elaborates nonstop.
You want to get it?
Nope.
Nonstop all summer.
I would hear that song on the radio.
Do you remember Splash Water Falls?
I don't remember Splash Water.
Was that a ride in the park?
It was.
So Great Adventure had two log flumes.
One was a pretty good traditional log flume.
You know it's the circle thing.
You walk you sit down it goes throughout a couple different drops and it was
good.
And there was another one called Splash Water Falls which all it was was it
went up it went over it went straight down and it was built in a way where the
weight of the actual log boat would just launch a massive wave and they built a
bridge that you could stand over and just get creamed by this wave.
And when you were talking about the heat and the humidity it brought back this
vivid memory to me that is so disgusting from an adult perspective which was there
were some days July August where you would go to Great Adventure and it was so
hot and muggy that people would start their day by going through the bridge at
Splash Water Falls to get deluged with this like filthy theme park water just to
kind of cool down.
So you'd start your day by going let's get soaking wet with theme park water.
And then work it off all day like well by noon I'll be level.
And then yeah if it gets sweaty again I guess I can go back and just get soaked
with impetigo again.
You know.
Yeah.
Just talking about this how like the realization that as an as an adult like
why did I ever think it was refreshing to get splashed by theme park.
Why was this equivalent to a an actual shower.
It doesn't make any sense to me past the age of 15 or so.
Let alone in the era before aqua socks.
You just be wearing your sneakers and your socks we would do that.
Let's walk around with socks.
Am I ignorant.
I don't know what's up with aqua socks because we've talked about a lot about a
wet sock preferences on log flumes.
Maybe this is the answer.
What's up with aqua socks.
Well aqua socks are like those water shoes that you'll get that have like the
rubber soles and the mesh and people wear them in the ocean so they don't cut
their feet on shells and stuff.
And action park had a really good scam where they sold aqua socks.
And then you couldn't wear them on half the rides.
So you still had to walk around on like hot blazing hot asphalt and then you'd
have to walk back up to get them because they made you take them off.
But yeah those were like I think they're pretty popular item in a water park
gift shop because it's like you can wear these and not have to walk around in
disgusting wet socks.
What you're saying is this is a very old thing and I have just learned about it
in 2021 and I'm talking to you like it's a new gadget.
Well they were they were hugely popular in the Jersey Shore when I was a kid.
And I remember there was one or two summers where my mom's like if you're going
in the ocean put them on.
I don't like my parents are just like you keep stepping on shells.
Just put the aqua socks on.
They are not the most pleasant thing to wear but I see them a lot when people go
to Hawaii and they hike they hike through a mountain to like a waterfall and you
don't want to like if you're going in in the stream or whatever you don't want to
have bare feet you know if it's sharp rocks and stuff.
It's like the Scrapple of footwear you know.
I'm not that familiar with them either and it must be more regional.
I feel like the best way to date them for you would be I remember them distinctly
coming out around the same time that slap bracelets were hot.
I would put them in the same era of time.
Yeah.
And similar designs potentially potentially some garish neon.
OK.
Yes yes you got it.
And slap a Taz t-shirt on top of that and you're just going to have a great day at
Six Flags great adventure and some some hyper colors.
You had some hyper colors in there.
Sure.
When you touch them maybe some cross colors like there's a whole no fear.
I feel like aqua socks crossed over into the fear generation.
This tells you exactly.
This is the important work trying to culturally date aqua socks.
Yeah.
It's honestly more from surreal clues.
I got it more of this one of the more substantial conversations we've had on
this show honestly.
OK.
Very informative.
The other.
Oh go ahead.
Well I was going to say the other log flume which I believe is still running is called
sawmill log flume and splash waterfalls was really wide.
Technically a shoot the shoot attraction and a lot of parks in their marketing in
their commercials would show the big splash down and show the bridge.
I think Doherty Park had the bridge too.
You could stand on and get as wet as if you're on the ride.
But sawmill log flume was a long like regular style log flume that it's I forget
what the area is called now.
I think it's called something adventures.
Adventure alley.
Did I see that phrase somewhere.
Front Frontier Frontier Adventures.
So this is like words.
Yeah.
For our interest like this is like a very fun area because in the middle of the
log flume there is a massive like surrounded almost by water.
There is a massive two story barbecue restaurant and then across from the log flume
there is a runaway train like which I always liked as a kid.
I loved I loved roller coasters runaway trains were a great entry because you're
like OK this will be a little fast and a little rickety but it will it's not going
to be too intense.
And then the runaway train goes around the building for the skyway and their skyway
was a double cable car skyway meaning there were two cars going in each direction
and it actually been transported from the 1964 World's Fair campus and then used in
Six Flags Great Adventure.
Wow.
So it was an old it was old like when do you know when it was transported.
It was all it seems like that's old.
Well yeah I don't know if it was just sitting in storage because he has Six Flags Great
Adventure open in 74 just as Great Adventure and then it was bought by taking over by Six
Flags in 77.
But yeah they replaced the cars at some point with cars from Six Flags Great America.
But yeah there is a historic plaque like you can see if you go to the the Frontier
Adventure I think the Skyway station there's one and there's two stations you can use it
practically it goes like three quarters of a mile and you can get off Frontier Adventures
or the lakefront.
Chris I bet you and your teen friends always made sure to go check out the plaque on your
visits.
I bring a date to you and look at the plaque.
You know probably the things we would talk about most though we're heading down to Great
Adventure.
Let's make sure we see some baboons eviscerating a car if we can cause someone in a plushy
outfit to have a nervous breakdown that would be fun.
But before we get to any of the high jinks guys just make sure we learn a little bit
about history.
Just make sure we're really soaking up some history.
We appreciate the kinetic energy of the Frontier Adventures area with trains and log flumes
and and cable car you know gondolas and cooking meats.
That I'll say to that log flume I think is probably my favorite ride in that whole park.
And there's people who love roller coasters and obviously they got some badass roller
coasters.
But as someone who has always been scared of the old roller coasters that log flume is
a legitimately great ride.
Yeah it was always very solid.
I am I've never been so I don't have the rights to say my favorite ride but I do have a
favorite ride based on title alone and it is a Looney Tunes themed ride and the ride is
called the Michigan Jay Frog Fun Flotilla.
Four kids died four kids died on that.
No no no.
In memoriam of the Fun Flotilla 4.
Say their names.
Yeah the that I believe was part of another really great named thing or promotion there
which is that they at the same time they added 25 new rides 25.
Now a lot of these were kind of like little dopey kid sorts of rides.
Jason I think you know what I'm talking about.
That you know it's just like to get the count up and obviously it increases capacity if
we had a bunch of rides and is impressive to say 25 new rides all at the same time.
But this caused the ad campaign where they declared that this was not just 25 25 new
rides showing up.
This was a war on lines.
That was their promotion for the summer of war on lines.
The war on lines.
Pick a side.
Are you for the war on lines.
Congress had to vote on part of the war on lines.
So it's just so grand so grandiose and like yeah and like violent.
We're in that Jersey spirit again.
It's not just like hey oh there's a fun flotilla now we're declaring a war on lines.
Yeah you could just go with fun flotilla but instead let's tie it into the war on drugs
or war on terror.
People know how we feel.
The most fun things have that have been happening in the last few decades.
Let's remind people of them.
This is a place where you keep in mind the centerpiece ride for many years was called
the great American scream machine.
Yeah.
Machine that's what gets New Jersey teens flocking through.
Let's go on a machine that makes you scream.
And the subject.
I uttered in the same breath as Batman and Robin the chiller and Viper which was it came
in 95 and again commercials nonstop for Viper.
Viper and great American scream machine some of the roughest coasters I've ever ridden
like immediately like out of the box.
I feel like they were pretty rough.
I do know my wife is a coaster enthusiast and she grew up in Westchester County so she's
also been to great adventure a million times and she swears and I've heard a lot of her
friends where that El Toro is one of the great roller coasters that she's been on anywhere
which I think is an all wooden coaster that's a great adventure now and that one has a
really good reputation.
Again scared of coasters.
I like a good spinny ride maybe a log flume but I've heard that El Toro is kind of a
pretty basic coaster but that people really love it.
Yeah I think that that one's been a long time favorite.
I remember really liking it came in 2001.
It's called Nitro and it's just very big but there's no loops but you have a lot of air
time like you you spend a lot of the ride just hovering above your seat and it's very
smooth too.
And I just remember my dad and I riding and just like laughing because you just feel like
you're going to fly out of it even though you are appropriately locked in God willing.
Yeah right.
There's this one currently in the works that seems like it'll it'll really join the pantheon.
I think it's opening soon.
Maybe they've even been previewing it a little bit called the Jersey Devil.
We got a Jersey Devil coaster which is that it's the tallest longest and fastest single
rail roller coaster in the country in the world.
And I read that and like oh sure.
And then I realized I don't know what that means.
Single rail I can't even picture.
You guys look this up like I don't it's a very odd like it looks like there's no like
I don't know gears or track or anything.
It's just a very thin track right.
It's like a very little monorail style.
Yeah it's confusing.
I don't know how it works defies science to me but it looks very cool.
And what a good name.
Yeah I think we're supposed to open last year of course the pandemic delayed it but I
believe June 13th of 2021 is supposed to be opening day.
That is a Sunday I looked.
So that's a weird day to open a ride.
It's the Lord's Day yeah.
Devil it's the devil.
So they're open.
It's kind of a themed thing.
We hate God.
This is the devil.
I say the Lord's Day but this is all about the devil.
So if you hate God and Jesus come ride the devil.
That's right.
Well it's the whole theme.
That's how they've been actively advertising it and I think it's working day.
Good goody.
Or on Jesus.
Come at Jersey Devil.
And then that goody.
What's her face laid in the woods and laid with the devil.
That's we all know.
The commercial ends with come spit in God's face.
We'll shoot you so high in the sky.
You slap God in the face.
And you're waiting for you head back down to hell.
Lease Mus's hair up.
Pretend you're a monkey jerking off straight into heaven.
They have a king to cause well right.
Which that's one that I look at it and I go I legitimately don't understand how
people find that fun that looks horrible to me.
Yeah.
If there's one that's similar.
Yeah there's one similar at knots down over here and I've I'm getting we've all I
think gotten a little braver as we've done this show because we're all kind of
scaredy cats when it comes to coasters.
Jason the least of us but like that one to me still seems like I don't know.
I think I'll have like a mental break going on a thing like that.
And it's just the fact that it's just kind of about shooting up going up coming
back down like for me because I've had over the course of doing this podcast I
got over my fear of launches.
I was dubbed a no launch queen and now I'm sort of shaking that off a little bit.
Maybe not.
But like for me the launch is the thing to get past and then I can have some fun.
But these rides where it is only the launch and then the most terrifying climb
and terrifying drop and the whole thing is over in like 40 seconds.
That's none of what I want in a ride experience.
Yeah it's I think I will do the not Sperry farm version of it at a certain point.
But I do I mean maybe the speed of it maybe it's truly one of those things it'll
be over like you won't even it'll be like surgery like it's so quick you'll be out
knocked out so quick it won't matter.
You'll just bully your blur your visual blur and you'll be like oh listen to how
we explain these things that are supposed to be fun.
Yeah.
Maybe surgery.
You're saying that as a positive.
You know that's a good very good point that that that it is a bizarre like we've
I've now gotten into doing like the haunts and mazes and I was always afraid of
doing that and those but I mean it takes it took like eight mazes for me not to
just be like clenched like that like the pain the stress I was feeling initially
had to go away like I had to get through it like it was a like a trial by fire.
Yeah there there was it actually is a nice story there.
They have an attraction called Houdini's Great Escape and it's it's we we learn
this I think when we talked about on our European vacation episodes it's a mad
house where it's not a haunted house it's not quite a fun house.
So what it is is like it's it's like a con artist trying to bring back Houdini
from the dead and and then Houdini does come back and says you're a fraud and
then turns the room upside down like you're sitting in a room and all of the
like you're sitting in like rows of chairs and then everything else in the
room starts to go upside down that comes right side up and then it does it again
and it starts doing it really fast and they closed it down for a couple of years
and then people were like hey bring that back it's still there we see it like and
it is it is back open again but I remember that being very cool because we
didn't know what it was when we went in they're like oh well it's kind of a
haunted house sort of thing like they didn't spoil it and it was super fun.
Sorry it involved the trickster and a voice says you're a fraud and this is a
bizarre somebody's like stealing Houdini's identity this is a really
bizarre premise for a roller coaster.
Well it's mostly you have to get his social security number and his mom's maiden name
that's like most of how the attraction works you're just stealing his actual.
Zooming by grab it grab the numbers.
It's like a sit-down show it talks about all this actual historical stuff
because Houdini famously debunked a lot of charlatans a lot of people who were
like fake spiritual mediums and stuff.
Because he gave his wife and a secret word and he said secret word die you go to all
the people the you know empaths we're not empaths you know what I'm talking about.
Yeah they can.
The media.
Spiritualist mediums thank you and if they don't know the word then obviously
they're frauds and nobody knew the word.
I just realized there's something and this might be a complete diversion that
you guys should feel free to cut.
I'm talking to people who will either enjoy what I'm saying or find me totally
insane if I may.
Okay go ahead please.
There is.
Let's swing.
Yeah.
So my parents spend a lot of the year now in Orlando.
There's snowbirds.
My mom really really loves Disney World and I have a two year old so they love
bringing him so we go once a year.
And when we go to Hollywood studios my wife has always been shocked because she
will sometimes really have to ask me just come on this ride with me.
She loves rides.
It's often just us.
Come on the ride.
I want to go on the ride.
So I've bit my tongue gone on some rides I don't like with her but she's never had
to beg me to go on the Tower of Terror.
I love the Tower of Terror.
Really.
I love it.
And first of all it's right the thing Disney has that I'm sure you've talked
about to death is like even like even like the people dressed as the bell hops
in the beat like they'll roll their eyes back in their head and you're like oh
they actually like they try to make it.
They dress this up as something it's not like even Space Mountain.
If it was in light you'd be like this is a pretty weak roller coaster.
Right. But it's not.
They dressed it up right.
So I like all the pageantry of it.
But my wife goes it's pretty much just like free fall from great adventures.
Just a free version of that.
They were and I said something to my wife where she actively told me I was
insane and I don't know what you guys will think or if I'm going to just come
off like an idiot I said to her oh that's fake.
And she said what do you mean.
I said I don't think I think the Tower of Terror is fake.
I don't think you're actually dropping.
And she said what are you talking about right now.
And I said well it opens up and it shows you that you're up high but then it
closes and you feel like it.
I said I have always been under the assumption that Disney is using some sort
of hydraulic thing to make me feel like I'm getting flung up and down.
I don't think it's real.
That's why I'm OK going on it.
And she goes it's totally real.
You are going up and down.
That's what you're feeling.
I said I think the Walt Disney Company has us all hoodwinked and that they're
very creatively holding us in place and using some sort of hydraulic system to
make us all think that we're in much more danger than we're in.
And she said if you need to tell yourself to keep going on this ride with you
that's fine. But it's also one of the craziest things you've ever said.
You're half right though.
You are half right.
Well, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah. Because you're you're not really free falling.
You're being pulled down.
You're actually going faster essentially.
Yeah, you're getting in a little you get loaded in a little box and then you are
going far pretty far up and down.
But you're not free falling.
The little box just has like, you know, cables and it's moving you up and down
essentially. See, in my mind, you're staying almost totally still the whole time.
Not quite. That's like Star Tours.
That's totally still.
So it's not I wouldn't go that far.
But I also won't call you crazy.
I won't get on board with crazy.
You're a little bit there, by the way, as a Star Wars nerd.
That new version of Star Tours is a considerable improvement over the old one.
Well, this is the whole.
Well, we're not going to agree with you there.
Oh, is this the whole thing?
I miss the. Well, no, I just I love the the pilot, the Paul Rubin's voiced pilot
so much. I feel the loss of him.
They finally got rid of that weird old robot.
Oh, no. Oh, man.
Now, this is scandalous.
Now, we're going to need to cut this.
Brought him back to be the DJ in Galaxy's Edge.
He would not be the DJ in the bar were he not beloved.
They wouldn't entrust him to spin the coolest tunes in the galaxy.
If he was just a hunk of junk.
And I'm not. I'm just saying everybody has their role to play.
But I was like a complete Star Wars obsessive as a kid.
And when you go to Star Tours and you're so psyched and it's some robot
you've never seen before, you're kind of like, OK, OK.
It's an expansive world. I like that.
But that new one where Darth Vader catches you and kind of flings you back.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, that's where I think perspectives differ, because I went on Star Tours
having never seen any of the movies
and which ended up not coming for like almost a decade later.
So I have a Star Tours centric view of the of the franchise.
So to me, Rex is like more Skywalker is right.
Yes, exactly.
So you are really much more of a Star Tours guy than a Star Wars guy.
Oh, yes. Yeah. Very much so to this day.
I still watch him and get confused.
Who's that and what's this and have I seen this one?
But I know I've seen the ride and I've seen all these different versions
and I've been the spy twice. Pretty cool.
Are you are you just like subscribed to Disney Plus
waiting for that Rex vehicle to finally hit the screen?
Oh, for. Well, God, I mean, what I'd like to do is make the Rex vehicle.
There's any interest in that, but it seems like there
I don't know how they're feeling about comedy these days.
There would have to be comedy.
Actually, no, it's very serious.
You know what? There's the issue.
It's a drama about a robot trying to make it,
trying to suppress his urges to be an artist. Yeah.
That's what he ends up being.
But he's Rex is back.
Rex is back and he's got depression.
I would set the DVR for that.
This upon announced.
I I think we should.
My pitch would be it's like Flight of the Navigator with Rex in the ship.
But then, Scott, you're the like you play like a boy like Martin
Short does in Clifford.
So you are like a little boy that Rex is like kind of
driving around in his like Flight of the Navigator star speeder.
Now, look, I'd like that for me.
I did. It does seem like audiences are, I'll say,
repulsed by adults playing young boys.
So much less myself.
It's now I'll do it.
I will look all star in this if you get off the ground.
Is the commercial potential is dwindling?
I thought you were going to say I I would do it for me,
but I think audiences would be so overjoyed
and over exhilarated that they would all be passing out
and suffering from medical issues at how good this show is going to be
based on what we've come up with here today.
I'd say so.
They're like the rush to tweet.
There's so much Twitter activity with, you know, with Winter Soldier
and every Mandalorian and like people would dive for their phones
and just their fingers would start convulsing and they drop to the floor.
I would like to see a series that's just
six hour long episodes,
and each one is basically you doing my dinner with Rex
in my dinner with Andre in a different theme park eatery.
Oh, geez. We go around.
I show him the other stuff.
I take him out of the Star Wars universe and then and teach him
and like to give him a corndog for the first time.
Just an hour long conversation with Rex.
Oh, it's like a different eatery each time for an hour.
No real drama. No, no real narrative arc.
Just real mundane at ease.
Like so the sodas come in small, medium and large.
Sometimes there's an extra large, not necessarily in the theme park
environment, but a lot of places have refills.
So they got you covered.
It's like, oh, really?
Anthony Bardane's Parts Unknown with Rex.
Yeah, yeah.
Parks unknown parks unknown.
Oh, man.
Well, look, as long as if I can get some help like moving them around,
that'd be the main issue.
It's just physical.
The physical labor involved.
But besides that, I'll fill the bowers.
No problem.
Speaking of Disney, can I mention I like I have not been to this park,
but I like the ripoff attractions that this park has.
Do tell I can't think of them offhand.
Well, Six Flags, it's got enchanted teacups.
Good word soup of theme park words.
Yeah. And it has air jumbo, which is obviously the Dumbo Spinner Ride.
And these were there before, I believe, Six Flags purchased them.
But yeah, there's no mistaking what they are.
And I just love I love bootleg anything.
And did you have you guys seen a picture of this?
I could pull it up real quick here.
Well, yeah, that's in here.
Air jumbo here.
Yeah. Jumbo.
Air jumbo.
So I really like that.
Close legally, lots of lawyers check that.
Now, that's not to say that they are entirely, you know, ripoffs and
generic properties, because with the Warner Brothers connection,
there's obviously the Lunditons, but they've also involved some other
Warner Brothers properties.
Batman, as we've said,
there was a lethal weapon show for a long time, and that got replaced by a show
where I'm going to bring up the sign and show you what is,
I think, one of the most unpleasant phrases I've ever seen.
The great adventure show
Quest for Camelot Nights presented by Tyson Chicken Chunks.
And let me clarify, that's not chicken, that's chick
apostrophe in implying that whatever this product is, is not necessarily chicken.
What a combo of brand and who even knows what this was movie?
This particular night was in by Taz and Chicken.
They really wanted to make sure that one product, which was like
it was going to be pushed because they didn't want just a general Tyson
sponsorship, they were like very high on that product specifically.
Like they need out of our chunks.
Are you saying we shouldn't be proud of our job?
Proud of our chunks and we want everyone a great adventure to see it.
If you're a fan of like of two headed dragons, then you'll also
enjoy the adventurous taste of these chunks.
So odd. The other thing about that, let me share the screen again,
because there was like so Jason, you talked about this lethal weapon
boat show a while back on a stunt show episode we did.
So there was that and there was like, you know, so there's there's boats
where all the stunts happen from.
And then they had to turn it into this medieval animated movie quest
for Camelot. And they just like I'll show you a picture.
They just took a boat and just put a bunch of like fake rocks.
But that's even going too far to use that term that we like.
It's just like rock flats everywhere, still in a boat shape.
Very clearly one of the laziest makeover jobs I've ever seen.
Sad little Stonehenge on top of. Yeah, that's a sad Stonehenge.
Yes, like a spinal tap size stone.
Yes. Yeah, they built it to the to the small proportions, not the big ones.
Eleven inches. I yeah, God, really strange.
So it doesn't I don't know that that was the biggest hit they ever had.
Quest for Camelot. It's hopefully chicken chunks did OK.
Since you're talking about licensed stuff and Mike, you know, they yeah,
they may have, you know, had some generic rip offs of Disney stuff.
But in the summer of 1994, they were going all in on a new attraction
because as the commercial says, first there was Star Tours,
then back to the future, the ride.
Now there's the right stuff.
Mach 1 adventure.
You all remember the 1983 film The Right Stuff, right?
About breaking the sound barrier. Chuck Yeager.
Well, now it's a simulator ride, a simulator theater, in fact.
Uh huh. And that's how they advertised it was that that is how they advertise
the biggest, the biggest cockiest walking in the room swinging like
fuck those rides.
We've got the right stuff, folks.
The mostly dramatic, like not exactly like you don't think of it
as like the ultimate kids.
Well, we remember kids kids when The Right Stuff came out,
they were all on the front lawn playing the right stuff with each other.
They all wanted to experience it.
I want to be Sam Shepard.
No, I'm going to be Sam Shepard.
Yeah, they were all there doing it.
And then finally Six Flags capitalized on that desire.
It was pretty fun.
I mean, it was just a theater.
It's like a D box theater, essentially. Right.
But we did. I did like I liked any anything movies, anything where it was like,
this is a real movie and now it's a ride of it.
I was like, good done.
You know, we're an hour from home.
You know, I know it's not going to be Disney World exactly,
but I'm like, cool, they have a simulator ride now.
Did you see the right Tutsi simulator?
This is fine with me.
This Tutsi's rushed journey to work at the soap opera station every day.
Yeah. Now that I'm living Tutsi in a more interactive environment,
I realize how intensely stalkerish it is.
A man, a man deceiving a woman.
It's just a man deceiving a woman.
Oh, God. Get me off this ride.
How can I follow this person around?
That was a life lesson, right?
It was like Mr.
Toad where you would learn something by the end of it.
What have we missed?
Just to wind down here.
What's the big...
The guy who started the park is my is what I want to bring up.
Oh, we haven't learned about this man.
No, no, no.
And and I believe his name is Warner Leroy.
Scott, did you take a look at any of these photos?
Anybody know?
Not particularly. No.
Show us Warner Leroy.
All right. Here's Warner Leroy.
I found an article where somebody referred to him as a Liberace type,
which obviously we like that.
Oh, cool. Like Elton John glasses.
He's yeah, he obviously like dressed in fun ways.
Jason, you have his interesting parentage.
Yeah. Well, Warner Leroy,
we should say first, he was an entrepreneur,
I believe, was his company called Leroy's of Adventures.
I think I saw that phrase in here somewhere. Yeah.
And it it it had a lot of, you know, food and beverage establishments.
Most noticeably, I thought it owned and operated both the Russian
Tea Room and Tavern on the Green.
Yeah. For a while, which are, you know, New Yorkers.
You know, New York institutions.
But Warner Leroy is the son of film director Mervyn Leroy, who
when he worked for Warner Brothers, directed the classic films Little Caesar.
I Am a Fugitive from a Chain Gang and Gold Diggers of 1933,
which is a big Busby Berkeley showstopper musical.
And then he went to work for MGM, where he pitched them the idea that, hey,
we should wake.
We should make The Wizard of Oz a movie.
Whoa. This guy's dad.
Yeah, this guy's dad. Oh, my God.
And it's it kind of came full circle, too, because a little known fact
is that after the Wright Stuff Simulator ride struck out,
they said, why don't we rebrand it as an I Am a Fugitive from a Chain Gang?
The rush of becoming a fugitive running down the hill.
Oh, my God. It was really it was really fucked up, it turns out.
So they switched it back within weeks.
People really jumped when they put chains around their legs.
Oh, geez. It is really dark and racist and exposed to prison.
Yeah. Complex.
You can't you can't make a ride based on a movie that was pre-haze code.
Are you crazy?
This is well, this is this is some lineage.
Yeah. Leroy. Wow.
Leroy. Yeah.
And I was trying to find there doesn't seem to be a good
or like an easily accessible YouTube interview because I was like
I was ready to be like, here's a new one of our favorite characters on the show.
But I still I'm going to have to do some deeper digging to find
some more Warner Leroy stuff is that I was not aware of him before this.
Hmm.
Hmm. I oh, you know what?
I got I got one more thing.
I forgot that with this with the the the haunts came up.
And there is a thing that happens here that happens at
as much as you guys know, at at Magic Mountain.
We talked about it on the Fright Fest episode.
And they do this tradition here to Chris.
Are you aware of the 30 hour coffin challenge?
Oh, I know about Fright Fest, but I don't know the 30 hour
coffin challenge, though.
Well, so so this is something I mean, Mike, you witnessed some of this in person.
But they do it.
They do it at the New Jersey one as well.
That at least in this case,
six contestants chosen from nearly six thousand applications
are all all face off to spend 30 hours straight in a coffin.
And on the grounds of the six flat.
Just yes. Yeah, you stay.
You stay in the Six Flags Park like you can kind of look up
and wave at people because they can walk around the car,
at least the way they had it set up out here was there was like six
or eight coffins all just on the ground.
And you could tour the coffins
and see the people and they would maybe wave to you.
And that would be the bizarreness.
Now, I'm sure you've covered this on your prior discussions, but it's 30 hours.
Where do you pee? Where do you poop?
You are allowed to go to the bathroom.
I believe that's it.
And I don't know that they I don't think they check.
I don't think they own breaks, too.
I don't think they check to make sure you don't have like the bag of pee
as if you were trying to fake a drug test or anything.
I don't think they check that thoroughly, but I could be wrong.
They dug a hole. It goes out of the coffin.
What do you win if you stay all 30 hours?
Well, the one out here, I don't know if I'm stepping on some of you,
but say, Scott, I believe you win six hundred dollars.
Is it six hundred sixty six? Was it? Yeah, yeah.
Six hundred sixty six dollars. Thank you. Sorry.
It was six hundred sixty six dollars.
I don't know if that's worth it.
I feel bad if you need the money, but I really wish Six Flags
would give them, you know, something a little better.
Yeah, that's not that much.
Not a ton of money or just real like being in pain and like mental distress.
It's not a life changing amount.
I'm not even sure it's like a month changing amount.
No, that's it's it's pretty it's pretty nothing.
And I so but, you know, we talked about it a little on the previous episode,
but I just ended up on a video where there's specific
dictating of the rules of the great adventure one.
And I was so charmed by this.
And I'm just going to let this guy explain the rules.
If anyone wants to stop and discuss any of the finer points, let me know.
But here's here's a quick clip.
The rules of the great adventure coffin challenge.
They will face challenges with live bugs, unsavory food and green goo.
They will be tormented by zombies, snakes, scums,
yacht rock and baby shark.
Just that, by the way, the switch from gross stuff to
the threat is yacht rock.
I think I'll be fine.
Yeah, I think I will happily do the coffin challenge now.
I have had baby shark stuck in my head, though, as the parent of a two year old,
and it's not an enviable position.
I will say, yeah, I'm really hoping I can write it out.
By the time he like I got, you know, a couple more months
before he really knows anything and maybe we just missed the whole thing.
But is it just going to find him?
Am I like it's in my school?
It's inescapable. Yeah, yeah.
I want to know more about the goo goo.
Yeah. Did it just say green goo and what is that?
It was very general about what type of goo it was.
Is it dripped, dripped on you while you're sleeping?
Is it something that you have to consume while you're there?
The only thing you get to consume?
Yeah, it's a good question.
I really they should elaborate more.
Yeah, yeah. But this is just, you know, they'll be 30 hours
for everyone to learn all these announcements.
I just now just pay attention to as this list wraps up
the the the person who is saying all of the rules.
Meals in the coffin, keep their body parts in the coffin at all times.
And should they exit the coffin for any reason
other than the allotted breaks and they will be disqualified.
So we for the listener, we have just like like a ghoul
in a long burgundy coat and a top hat.
And like white face make up is kind of reading from a list
with a microphone very, very long.
It's well, it's that right there.
He's in front of the old beat up hearse.
He has this incredible outfit on the minutes.
Like he's just holding the piece of paper and reading off of it.
And it really it really undercuts the whole thing.
Yeah, we put it on a tombstone like it's engraved.
These are the rules that have existed for thousands of years.
And we must obey them tonight.
And some old dusty tome or something, right?
Yeah, scroll. Yeah.
Yeah. Roll a scroll of some kind or.
Yeah, it would be.
He looks like he's looking at like the schedule
for whenever he was working at the park.
It's also very bright.
It's broad daylight.
Like there are bucolic clouds and sky in the background behind it.
It seems really nice.
Yeah. And also what so what I was saying earlier about six flags, like
you're not going to find a universal or Disney, a shot of inside the park
where you can see the porta potties.
You will not see porta potties on theme park grounds.
Yeah, just a shitty tent.
Yeah. And that's what's that's that.
That is and I I'm not even saying that ironically,
that is still the magic of six flags is that they like no one noticed
that that looks like shit.
That's what we love about it.
It's so insane.
The the the winner of the the winners are announced
ultimately, at least this year, by Butch Patrick from the Munsters.
Is that true? Yeah.
Oh, he read the winner.
Oh, I love it.
Now, have you talked about entering?
Let's be honest.
Oh, that's a good.
Could any of the three of us handle it?
I have I would I first think for sure not me.
Jason, perhaps the best sleeper.
Jason is the most equipped because of his sleeping schedule to do well.
He can sleep for 12 hours at a time.
No problem.
I didn't know that.
I didn't know that there was a weird cage lid.
I wasn't sure how open or closed it was, honestly, the way you talked about it.
But I also didn't know they like bothered you.
I was like, oh, you can.
Can you just lie in there with an iPad like?
No, I know there's a part where zombies walk up and get up.
Wake up now.
Oh, come on, man.
The egg toss.
Oh, no, really?
I can raise.
I don't care if it's for him.
There's the rules from the piece of paper.
But you can win six hundred dollars.
Have you thought? I mean, yeah.
The only thing that's out, that's like that.
That's like the tax.
Yeah, that's a little back.
And, you know, that's a nice lunch at the best of the West.
The famous, you know, Six Flags barbecue restaurants around a biolog.
And now, yeah, maybe.
But Mike, you love haunts.
So are you the person to do it?
Yeah, I love haunts now.
That's true.
But, you know, if I could negotiate sort of the terms of my of a victory
with Six Flags with like I could get some sort of a lifetime
annual pass or something or one of those food passes that they just give you three
like three square meals for 80 dollars a year and I can get that for free.
Like something.
And those passes are real.
Like there's these weird.
It happens at Nats, too, where you can you can just tack on
like an extra hundred dollars under your yearly pass and you can eat
all your meals at the theme park for the whole year if you want.
But if they could add something like that on, I don't know.
I feel like if they could sweeten the pot somehow for me, not again.
Yeah, I don't know. I'll think about it.
I'll tell you on my end, I would consider entering this.
Really? Yeah, because it looks.
And I'll tell you exactly why.
The image of that asshole.
And I feel like you guys are and I'm potty mouth.
But that guy, God bless him and not as a human, but like
that's the foghorn leghorn of the of the Halloween season.
He doesn't seem totally enthusiastic.
He seems unfamiliar with the rules himself.
That that feels to me like it's being run by someone who doesn't care all that much.
Yeah. And those are usually situations that lend themselves to very good stories.
Yeah. Do that at the age of 41.
Yeah, that's I think I think maybe this year will be my year.
I'd be willing to step up in the Jersey rendition if you guys want to do some
follow up with this. We all do it.
We all do. If we all do it.
OK, if we all do it, I mean, I mean, I've either rule on this podcast is if everyone wants
if two people want to do it, I mean, I won't.
What if I get my cohost from my New Jersey is the World podcast?
We all enter or elect a rep in Jersey.
You guys do it out there and we have some sort of friendly standoff between the two
clicks. Oh, East Coast, West Coast.
Right. Right. Nobody's traveling even.
Wow. We're just we just like, you know, like text like each other out.
And we can we we can leave if you get like six hours in, if you like kind of go crazy,
you can leave. You know, that's the challenge aspect of it.
So it's not like we're really stuck there.
Once the green goo hits your face, you can leave.
If you're like if the green goo touches my face and on me like, fuck this, I'm a father
and a husband. Yeah, you can.
Like what am I getting out of this?
Six hundred sixty six dollars in content for two podcasts.
Not worth it. Yeah, I am.
Yeah. If we could ensure if we could ensure, though, one of the cast members of the
original Munster show will award us the victory.
This is the problem getting like Butch Patrick to be by coastal to be able to give you
that money.
I would say that I am 100 percent down to enter either myself or someone from that
podcast on the Jersey rendition if we can come up with a bit.
I can say that we would be happy to do it because that's idiotic and ludicrous.
All right. I will. If I have one of us has to do it, I'll do it.
I will say that I will do it.
I'm willing to do it. I'll let you do it.
I will. I think all three of us.
I think all three of us should do it, but I will do it if my two co-hosts will be
cowards. No, I think I think you got it, brother.
I think we'll just be dragging it down.
I think that goo is your name.
I'm ready. I'm ready to do it.
I'm ready to get in that coffin and shit wherever they instruct me to.
It feels like one of those things where at the end of the day, they're not allowed to
hurt you. Right.
Right. I don't think so.
Some guy dressed as a zombie wants to let me not sleep.
I have a two year old.
I don't sleep anyway.
That's true. Yeah.
Years. Yes. You want to throw green goo on me?
There's feces on my hands pretty much 24 hours a day
all day. Very possibly green, depending on the diet.
I have changed my son in the morning after he ate raisins.
You think your green goo is going to scare me?
I've seen substances more horrific than your green goo.
There's nothing they can do.
Baby shark, I've already been exposed to it.
Yeah. You may sleep better, honestly, in the coffin challenge.
Get away for a bit.
But yes, I'm used to that.
I am in. I'm ready. I'm ready to do it.
I'll do it. Geez, geez.
Well, you heard it. You heard it here first.
This is all we'd look forward to.
Any closing thoughts about this place?
Did anything else you want to get off your chest about
that great adventure and the great adventure spirit?
I would just say that, first of all, if you've never been,
there's a lot to love in both
the fact that there's really good rides and it does have just a little bit
of grittiness compared to a lot of corporate places.
I would say absolutely 100 percent.
If you want the full experience, the Safari Park is extremely underrated.
It is a well-known source of ludicrous joy in New Jersey.
And I would also just say that
I was, you know, pretty major part of that Action Park documentary.
And Action Park deservedly has its insane reputation.
But I think that it has maybe swallowed up
a lot of the insanity that was talked about with Great Adventure.
And Action Park was certainly crazier significantly.
But Great Adventure is a piece of New Jersey lore in its own right.
A lot of stories, a lot of formative memories for a lot of people.
So I do just want to, as a Jersey guy say,
let's not let Action Park sort of suck up all the air in the room
because there's a there's a lot of other places around here that are
insane in their own right.
And this is a big piece of that puzzle.
Also, the Tower of Terror is fake.
I like the Tower of Terror, truth or kind of movement here.
Yeah, we've got started here.
Pretty innocent truth or ism, all things told.
So I think pretty harmless for sure. Yeah.
Yeah. No storms happening over that one.
Well, yeah. Well, thank you for shining a light.
And for sharing the New Jersey theme,
dangerous theme park insanity spotlight with Great Adventure.
Chris Gathered, you survived podcast, The Ride,
easier than a coffin challenge, I would say.
And let's exit to the gift shop.
Is there anything you'd like to plug?
Yeah, you know, I got a new special. It's called Half My Life.
You can download it streaming a lot of places, iTunes, Amazon, Vimeo.
And and I hope people like it. Check it out.
It's a little tour documentary stand up special.
And just because it came up enough times on this, I would say I do have a
another podcast called New Jersey is the World
that explores all different Jersey topics.
And Episode One was actually about New Jersey amusement parks.
So there might be some people who are interested in that.
Absolutely. Cool. Cool. Well, thank you.
Oh, wait a minute now. And Gatorland is some Gatorland presence,
which is sort of in the theme park.
I can't believe I forgot that. Yeah. Right. Right.
Probably the major crux of my special revolves around a joke
about Gatorland and then spoiler.
It ends with me performing at Gatorland for the Alligators.
So you want to talk about like and the whole theme of that joke is, hey,
Disney World's the corporate option.
Gatorland's right down the road and it has rejected all corporate feeling to it.
So I do have a true love for Gatorland and and even just in Florida.
I mean, like the Wiki Watchy Mermaid Park, not a theme park, but just an insane place.
Insane roadside places. I love them to death.
So, yeah, Gatorland majorly featured in a huge way in half my life.
Geez. Cool. All right.
So theme park content, very funny, special New Jersey podcast.
Check it all out. Chris, thanks for being here.
As for us, you can find us on all the socials at podcast the ride.
We got merch in our tea public store and for three bonus
episodes every month, check out podcast the ride, the second gate at patreon dot
com slash podcast the ride.
So good stuff, really fun, fun to talk so much Jersey stuff.
And I guess if everybody out there just make it a make it a quest for Camelot night
worthy of worthy of your chicken.
Yeah. Cut your chicken into chunks tonight in honor of that show.
Yeah. Yeah.
Mm hmm. It'll be a great one.
Great quest and a great adventure.
Thanks for listening. Bye bye. Bye bye.
Forever.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson,
Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Cilio and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts dot com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter
and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.