Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, The Second Gate,
a podcast ostensibly about theme parks, except when it's not.
I'm Scott Gardner, Mike Carlson
and Jason Sheridan are here, hello.
I'm here and I'm in the dark.
My name is Mike Carlson.
Jason Sheridan here as well with me in this dark room.
I may as well be in the movie Bird Box.
I've got a blindfold on, right?
Remember that?
Was that one year ago or three years ago?
Unclear.
Who knows?
It's the most popular movie ever made.
We're all watching it so often.
It's hard to remember when it came out.
That's right.
But we're not here to watch Bird Box,
not here to talk about Bird Box.
We're watching some stuff though.
And we're gonna talk about what we watch.
There's surprises, surprises on you guys.
We'll explain.
There's a lot to get through so we'll dive in.
And first things first, let's introduce Podcast The Ride's
first in-person guest in 16 months, Eva Anderson.
Yay!
It's a hallowed spot back with the ceramics
back in the creaky green chair
which didn't break in the interim.
First person to be in the hallowed chair.
Edwin's growling at me.
Yes, he's unhappy that the people are here.
He hates the podcast and he humps my leg in stress
before people come, he can sense it.
I think it's nice to have that counterbalance
so we don't get too full of ourselves.
A constant presence that despises the podcast.
Yeah, yeah.
And maybe not you but he despises us, certainly.
Well, he doesn't like change.
He's like Jason in that way.
You can relate to that.
Oh yeah, it's a big trigger point.
Talk about it with my therapist for years.
Well, I hope surprise isn't too triggering.
Oh, surprise is delightful.
I love a surprise.
Great, yeah.
I would like to think this will be a delightful surprise,
maybe, to say it's not a horrible surprise.
It's not a marathon.
I'm not making you guys do a marathon viewing.
It's not- Father of the Pride.
It's not more Father of the Pride.
That's how it was set up to us a little.
Well, it's Father of the Pride style
in that we will watch some things
and then live react and talk about it.
But we were told to set aside like three to four hours
in the day, I think.
That's probably what it'll-
I feel like you said five hours.
Four to five, maybe?
I think four to five was the estimate.
We'll see.
I think it'll be less of that
but we could still figure it out.
I'm not gonna run you guys into the ground.
Eva has brought spicy hard waters
that we have chilling in the refrigerator right now.
Hard waters, you call them?
Hard seltzers.
Hard waters.
My other kind of water.
Water is seltzer, right?
Oh man.
I have a theory now that because of pandemic,
they've just been putting out
these really weird alcohol drinks.
Like there's the hard iced coffee that they have at my store
and a hard cold pressed juice.
That's not good for anything.
No, that kind of counteracts the idea, I think.
Hard kombucha, I've been seeing that pop a lot.
Yeah, that's been around for a little bit.
But the message is like, you could drink alcohol
all the time if you gave up.
It's like that movie that won the Oscar, right?
What's it called?
Leaving Los Vegas?
Oh, okay.
We were just drunk all day.
Not all things are meant to be hard.
And also just like, it's also eliminating
the hard step of pouring one thing into another thing
with that blend that actually makes sense as a blend.
I believe that Cut Water Spirits, the canned cocktail company
has introduced hard popsicles or hard otter pops.
Yeah, yeah.
I did a little of that.
I did a little, I put otter pops into alcohol
during the pandemic.
You infused otter pops.
I was infusing things during the pandemic.
That's fun.
It was just sort of like one of those drinks I have
at like a theme park.
Okay.
That's what you're after.
It wasn't crazy.
You kept calling your kitchen Pym Labs or Pym Labs.
Pym.
No, it's not Pym.
I had it, I had it.
I've been reading it since second grade.
I've just been seeing the word Pym.
And I didn't know how to pronounce it.
Kids are dying to go and eat at the restaurant theme
to Michael Douglas.
To Michael Douglas.
Michael Douglas.
Scott, I have a test lab, Scott.
Scott.
I just watched Behind the Canelabra again, it's great.
I would love to, yes.
Well, you know, that's a film with some amazing fashions.
Some amazing, you know, heights of 70s luxury.
And that might be sort of the realm
that we're playing in today.
Oh, just to really clarify,
this was sort of an Eva and I scheme
hatched late one night for no particular,
there's no vilification in surprising Mike and Jason.
Sure.
Just seemed like a fun way to do it,
to just spring this on you in the moment.
I just wanna tease too, and I said it to you,
that there is sort of a thing
I was going to surprise you guys with,
with Eva, what you were talking about months and months ago.
You may not even remember.
I don't know if I remember.
Yeah, there was a little,
there was an idea we had for later.
So there might be another surprise.
This is a forgotten secret surprise.
Yeah, I'll remind you later.
All right, all right.
So basically I've been like texting with Scott about this
and I was like, I wonder if this could be a second gate,
but I don't know if the connection is there
that makes it justifiable.
Like, you know, it's like borderline Billy Toppett.
Yeah.
Like, you know, does this count?
And then I found this quote
that I think ties this all together.
Yeah, like kicked it over the fence,
way, way over the fence.
Wow.
It is so tied in to,
inextricably, is that the correct word,
to what we like and what we talk about?
So this is a, yeah, quote from the book,
this book that we'll be referencing, and here it is.
It's from Marty Croft.
Oh, all right.
There's a link already.
We got the Crofts involved.
Michael Eisner called me and said,
hey, I have a new show for you.
Let Donnie and Marie go to Utah.
You'll stay here.
I want you to do the Brady Bunch Variety Hour.
So I said, yes, that was the first mistake I made.
That's how it all started.
That's Marty Croft on the Brady Bunch Variety Hour.
On the Brady Bunch Variety Hour.
That is what we will be watching and talking about.
Oh, wow.
Have you guys seen it before?
I have not.
No, I haven't seen it.
The bits and pieces.
Of the Brady Bunch Variety Hour,
but I've never watched a whole episode
or like what, 90 minutes, is it 90?
How long is it?
It's about 40 minutes an episode.
Okay, so we're watching the whole?
Not the full series.
I would have said more time if that was gonna be the case.
I have a DVD of episode one and episode four.
Okay, great.
And I would like us to watch the pilot just off air,
and then we'll come back and we'll talk about it.
We'll get some context.
We'll get your guys' reactions,
and then we'll move forward in the best way possible.
Sure, the potential of other odds and ends too,
you were saying, because there's things outside
of the strong moments within episodes
that aren't entirely essential.
Yes.
Though it's all clearly essential.
Right.
Okay.
I spent the last week watching all of it.
So you really know.
I really know what happens on it in every episode.
And I also, we each did some research,
read some books that have some context and some history.
Yeah, so we'll teach you guys,
we'll teach the audience,
I guess some major bullet points before we dive in.
If you've made it this far in the podcast,
I don't think we have to explain the Brady Bunch
from the ground up.
But beloved, relatively grounded sort of family sitcom
that ran from 69 to 74.
I say in terms, you know, there's an alien episode,
but what didn't have an alien episode in the 70s?
Was that the last season?
Yeah, I think so.
Yeah, with the Cousin Oliver season where they had aliens?
Yeah, well, it had, yes,
it's the Flintstone style unravel.
Cousin Oliver in general is sort of a weird latter day
mistake, you might say.
The show ended with this weird episode
that involved a hair tonic
and the youngest brother, Bobby,
dying the hair of Greg, the oldest brother,
bright red before his graduation.
This episode was so infuriating that Robert Reed,
who played the father, sent massive memos
to the producers of the show
explaining why this is not a good plot
and not a good direction for the series to go.
One of which being like,
how in the world would a nine-year-old child
in the 20th century be dealing in hair tonic?
Where is he getting it?
Who is his vendor?
Completely the realm of fiction.
He refused to appear in the final episode of the show.
And then it was just sort of yanked off the air
and this awkward cousin Oliver, it just sort of unraveled.
But in the intervening years,
not nostalgia, because it was just on,
but the popularity of the show only grew and grew.
So it gets to 1977 and Michael Eisner,
ever the pursuer of financial opportunities
of crossover tie-ins,
realizes maybe we need to bring this thing back in some way
and he's maybe gonna lose Sid and Marty Croft
or wants to keep them happy,
wants to keep them employed in the variety realm
that they are dominating at the time.
Besides their kids shows,
they're also doing Donnie and Marie,
which has to explain why they would have even thought
to give the Brady Bunch a singing, dancing variety hour,
because why does it?
I feel like it's some Donnie and Marie tie-in.
Like it's a family and that makes sense.
What year is the variety show?
77.
Yeah, shot in 76 and 77.
I don't, maybe this is not a second gate,
but we were just watching last night,
cause I'm fascinated,
cause both Mary Tyler Moore and Dick Van Dyke
had their own variety shows, sketch shows.
Oh yeah, Mary with David Letterman.
With David Letterman, Michael Keaton.
And then Dick for the Van Dyke and company
and Lucille Ball is on and Andy Kaufman is on that.
Oh wow.
Oh yeah.
And it's weird.
I mean, some of it's okay,
but like it's just, it was interesting.
Everyone was like, Saturday Night Live is out,
but then like there's all this old school variety
still on TV.
They had broke, so the Brady's also in the kind of later
years, they had done a show at the Hollywood Bowl,
like the Brady Bunch Live.
They were performing occasionally at Knott's Berry Farm.
But the really important thing was that most of them
could not sing or dance.
Two of them could very well, Florence Henderson
and Barry Williams were both like at this point
in the intervening years become like Broadway stars.
Like Barry Williams was in Pippin.
like she was already known for that before the Brady Bunch.
Tons and tons of musicals.
But they go to Barry Williams and they say,
it's gonna be the Barry Williams show
featuring the Brady Bunch.
They go to the middle son, Christopher Knight,
and they say, he says, well, I don't wanna dance.
They're like, you're not gonna dance.
No, you won't have to sing and dance.
Like they'll just do comedy sketches.
You'll be the funny one and we won't make you sing and dance.
And they just lie to every single person
to get them on board.
And they basically, and the only person who was like
really excited besides the two of them was Robert Reed,
who's just liked the idea of singing and dancing.
One other interesting thing is Sherwood Schwartz,
the creator of the original Brady Bunch,
found out about this show when he read about it in TV Guide.
Oh, wow.
Really?
What?
That's how much he was not.
Wait, it was coming out and that's how he learned.
Yeah, he was also like by all accounts,
a very bad person who like didn't go to Robert Reed's funeral.
Oh wow, really?
Yeah, so really bad guy.
But he did read about it in TV Guide
and went like a what?
Wow, that's wild.
There was two things, two things theme park related.
Just now I was thinking, of course,
Robert Reed saved the Brady kids
on a roller coaster in real life.
Yes, when they went to Kings Island,
there was a pretty, what looks to him like a rickety rig
on top in front of a roller coaster
where they were gonna shoot a scene.
And he walked up and like,
this thing's gonna look at the clearance there.
It's gonna come clean off.
And then they did fine, we'll do a test.
They did it, it did come clean off.
It decapitated all of the Brady kids.
So while he hated the show a lot of the time
and sent these mean memos,
maybe he might've been correct.
He hated Sherwood Schwartz.
Okay, and that seems to add up.
By all accounts, he and Florence Henderson
were very protective of the kids.
Which leads to, you probably have heard
about this other big hank in trying
to get this thing together.
Is that Eve Plumb, who played Jan,
was just starting to become very popular
as like a movie of the week actress.
And so she wanted that kind of build out
into her contract so she could do some other stuff.
They were like, no.
So she just didn't, she said no.
And that is referenced, of course,
in the Simpsons parody, the Simpsons variety hour
where Lisa is replaced.
So you'll notice a fake Jan.
There's fake Jan in this.
Fake Jan.
When we were talking about all this,
I was recalling how,
when there was this 90s Brady's mania,
some of it just being like,
remembering it in this 20 year itch kind of way.
And now we get that there's an ironic level
and then the movies were made,
which I still am very fond of.
I bought all this hook, line, and sinker.
I loved all this so much.
To the point where when the Simpsons episode came out,
I'm like, oh, I see, of course,
they are referencing Jerry Reichel
having to come in as fake Jan.
I am 11 years old.
And I completely know what they're doing.
I am really close to having to start dating,
having to start growing up.
By the way, you don't have to.
Yes, yeah, that's what I figured out now.
Now I just kind of, I did a weird route.
Yeah, I was just,
I could not have been more socially screwed
by the fact that I understood the Jerry Reichel.
You would have won up to me
because I knew the reference,
I knew the history, I think, in general, vaguely,
but I did not know Jerry Reichel's name.
So you would have dropped the mic on me
at the playground if we were in the same school.
At a trivia contest,
between a 70s trivia contest among 11-year-olds in 1996.
Yeah, I would have been able to be like,
I can name the cast of I Dream a Genie for you,
but I can't name the extra Jan.
Yeah, I couldn't.
Both Aarons.
Yeah, I could name all the sweat hogs, probably.
I really liked Welcome Back Hotter
for a short period of time.
It wasn't on Nick at Night for long,
but I got really into it once.
I think we've also, I've also floated the idea
of reviewing one of Barry Williams' Branson shows
on the second case.
I would absolutely go to Branson.
Yeah.
Are we going to Branson?
I think we can.
That's probably a good idea.
All of the four of us go to Branson.
I think I'm two degrees away from Barry Williams also.
I think we could get him on the show.
Well, I also just,
I think I mentioned this in a previous episode,
but I tricked Barry Williams into signing a DVD
of this show.
Trick.
Oh, wait, that's right.
Wait, wait, wait, what was the story again?
I was working on the, like a Comedy Central special
for Dickie Roberts, former child star,
and it had just a bunch of former child stars in it.
Like, and this was also when Emmanuel Lewis tricked me
into driving him to the Nick at Night convention
by acting like he wanted to rent a car there
and then like just ran inside and got lost.
I was like 23 years old.
He made me call him Manny Moe.
And, but anyway, and Leif Garrett quit last second,
like called me crying.
Like he was like, Eva, I quit.
And then he, an hour later was like, I'm fine.
And we'd already replaced them with another guy.
Like Butch Patrick or something?
Yeah, but I turned the DVD cover inside out
and got him to sign it.
And then he asked me what it was and I showed him
and he kind of like glowered at me.
Oh no.
And then I lost that signed copy.
So this is another copy that I bought.
I bought this so many times.
You know what, this is, I was thinking,
I said to them, like, especially once Scott was like,
Mike, do you have a DVD player set up in your living room?
I was, I was not thinking it was gonna be Brady Bunch.
I thought it was gonna be,
cause you would, were texting us
from California Adventure a few weeks ago.
Oh yeah.
And you were asking us about Oswald the Lucky Rabbit.
Like, is there a big Oswald sensation right now?
And I was like, and then when Scott, you know,
prepped us for this episode, I was like, oh no,
did Eva buy the full Oswald?
Is Eva gonna make us watch two dozen Oswald collections
in this episode in one day?
Yeah, we just like Oswald in my house now.
And my husband bought this Oswald shirt
where he's shooting lightning from his hands.
It's in the font of the shirt
that says Oswald is a lightning font.
Very like 97 with attitude.
Oh yeah.
Yeah, we just bought an unlicensed Oswald shirt,
which is great.
It looks like he's about to run into a small arena
and just really fuck up Vince McMahon.
We did, we like watched one Oswald cartoon
and he's just kind of mean.
Yeah.
Yeah, he's kind of a dick.
Unpleasant.
Does the audience have an answer for us that is,
is the question just, is Oswald a thing?
Does anyone care about Oswald?
Is it working?
Is there recent featuring of him a little
in the parks move the needle at all?
I think when they redid California Adventure,
Disney had in the few years prior to that
gotten the rights back.
Well yeah, that was the Al Michaels deal.
Yeah, they traded a sportscaster
for the rights to Oswald the lucky rabbit.
So weird.
And so they were like, okay, well the time period works out
where like it would make sense for Oswald
to be on Buena Vista street
and the version of Los Angeles we're presenting.
We don't need to go into the like gnarly details of like,
oh, the distributor screwed Walton up Iwerks
out of ownership of this.
Like it's a cute kind of obscure character.
And I think the locals will like it.
Yeah.
You're right.
He's right behind you.
Oh, there's an Oswald here.
Oh yeah, there's a massive Oswald.
Lindsay got that for me like eight years ago.
It's great.
Yeah.
I mean, Oswald's a cool, the guy in the Oswald suit.
Well, that's why we were,
I was sort of like, who is that?
I looked it up and I texted you guys
cause I was like, this guy's really a good character
performer and walk around guy.
He was really doing little dances and
Yeah.
projecting a lot of life onto this guy.
Right.
Well, it would be nice if we could know who was in like,
they had like a little name tag, like today Oswald is Brian.
Oh God, we gotta get Brian, get Brian day.
You can like go on the app and see if Brian's Oswald.
Yeah.
Brian, is Brian working today?
And then it would be like a weird, like a,
you're going to a strip club and it's like,
is Denise here?
And they're like, yeah, you gotta get out of here, man.
You're a little too into,
although I guess it's like Amanda Lund telling us about
the fans at Tokyo Disney.
Oh yeah.
Like there was a, they made a scrapbook of her,
as the princess.
All right, fine.
We should maybe stay away from that territory.
Stay away from it.
It'd be like international creeps.
One other thing about, about fake Jan,
as she's known pop culturally.
So this was just,
cause I read another thing that Eve Plum was sort of,
that's what you were saying.
She was like, maybe she wasn't so angry about it,
like Lisa and the Simpsons.
Yeah.
She just refused on the grounds of what the show is.
I think she's like, I'll do some,
but can I not do all of them?
And they said, no, all or nothing.
You are out.
But then that left them without a Jan.
So they had to scramble and find somebody
who kind of looked like Eve Plum to,
and it came so down to the wire that they only had Jerry
Reginald the day before rehearsal started.
Wow.
So, all right, your Jan, go, go, go now.
And she was a, like a very accomplished
country Western performer.
She had been in a band.
She could sing and dance better than almost anyone,
but yeah, that's very weird that it happened to Eve Plum
because she was like, I got a 40 share in like this TV movie
I did, and I just, I feel like I have a career here.
And they called her like, started calling her like Eve,
I've got a 40 share Plum.
And they just were like, well, you're out.
But then also then Mike Lookinland who played Bobby was
like, can I have, I won't do it unless you pay me twice
as much.
And they're like, okay, I guess we're paying everyone
twice as much.
Like, so they gave him the money.
So only Eve Plum really got punished.
And even though she wasn't being that bad about it,
it does say in the book that like the night this aired,
she sat in front of the television,
her home sobbing hysterically.
Oh man.
Poor Eve.
It's her family that moved on without her.
Yeah, but she was, as we'll see,
like she made the right decision.
Yeah.
Did you see the thing about, I discovered this
in an interview with series writer, Bruce Valanche.
First TV job.
Let's write that in too.
His first TV job.
Yeah, or like first big one, like series job.
He was trying to soften his resume
so he could get more TV writing jobs.
So he like, he was like working for like Lily Tomlin,
writing jokes for Lily Tomlin.
And he was like, I guess I'll do this.
This is right, also right before Star Wars,
No one's listening to this anymore, are they?
They've turned it off.
Oh, there's gonna be like a lot of weird 70s old guys.
My mom is gonna be thrilled by this conversation,
but everyone else has turned it off.
If you're crafting the comment,
not about theme parks and preparing to send it,
just know we will text each other
and make fun of the comments.
So if that's your plan, joke's on you.
Anyway, let's continue.
Yeah, Bruce Valanche worked with like Paul Lind.
He also worked on the Paul Lind Halloween special.
Yes, yes, absolutely he did.
Which is a thing we need to do in episode about too.
The fact that he was just like in the writers
for a year is like very unusual
and a first time experience for him.
Yes.
So there's an interview where he talks
about the fake Jan syndrome.
And I watched this this morning.
I didn't realize that it came down to two women.
Oh yeah.
One of them, Jerry Reichel, who got the part.
The other one, Kathy Hilton,
eventually the mother of Paris Hilton.
My God.
Yeah, almost was Jan.
Connie's daughter, right?
Conrad Hilton?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh yeah, so already mega heiress.
Yeah.
So she didn't need to be Jan on top of it.
And one more tiny thing
and we should probably start the pilot
is that this was shot at KTLA studios
on Sunset Boulevard where the Netflix building is now.
And do you guys, have you ever noticed that Denny's
that was right across the street on the corner
kind of right when you get off the freeway,
there was like a floating Denny's on Sunset Boulevard.
Yes, with a massive parking lot.
Massive parking lot and a full bar.
That was built because KTLA didn't have a commissary
and Norman Lear personally asked Denny's
to build a Denny's there with a bar.
What?
And it closed during quarantine
but that's what that Denny's was there for.
Wow.
I don't think I realized there was a full bar in there
and also there's a Denny's two blocks away.
That was Norman Lear's Denny's.
Wow.
And it will figure into the story later
in a very negative way.
Oh no.
Oh boy.
All right, so should we watch this pilot?
We should probably pop it in
and just let's keep in mind,
I'm so excited to have the new context
that everything that we're gonna see,
everything we're gonna describe to the audience
is brought to you by Michael Eisner.
Like so much of what we love.
Right, right.
And you have to think about like,
was he, did he approve the cuts?
Did he look at costumes?
How involved was he?
Was he proud of it, of his creation as it was forming?
But Eisner plus Crofts plus Filanch
plus all the Brady's plus one fake Brady.
What a combination.
A guest star that is really fantastic in this pilot.
There's so many, I feel like mega guest stars,
like seven of them every time.
Oh yeah, this one is one very specific guest star.
So all right, so we'll shut it down.
We'll pop it in, audience,
we'll be back with you in a moment.
of the Brady Bunch Hour.
Yes.
Sure did.
What do you think?
It's, I guess it's way worse than I thought it would be.
I thought it would be bad, but it's like worse.
Yeah, that's been my,
cause I've been fascinated by this show
and the existence of it,
but anytime I've tried to watch more than 10 minutes,
it's difficult.
It is a slog, it wears you down.
but the concept is confusing and they just,
the thing that really strikes me is,
cause I watch a lot of this era variety specials,
Jack Benny stuff, as I mentioned, I think,
Letterman, the Dick Van Dyke and Mary Tom Olmonds,
they really like,
like lean heavily on doing old 40s style,
boring as hell musical numbers with no gimmick to it.
Just like the costumes are fun.
They are like Sid and Marty Croft-esque,
but it's really just like, baby,
like a Las Vegas review from 1950
on television in the mid 70s,
like just, I don't know, they'd so much of that.
I would think there would be more weird comedy
or attempts at comedy.
Well, like the most modern thing,
this was 76 we were saying while we were watching it,
the most modern things in it are they sing
like a very stiff version of Shake Your Booty
and they do one singular sensation from a chorus line,
which was the original production of chorus line
was 75.
So that's only a year old,
but that is a show about people in the 70s
doing like a kind of traditional Broadway musical,
which is a little old.
Yeah, I don't want to be called by that as contemporary.
I hate one.
They sing Attitude Dancing, which is a modern disco song.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, right, right.
That's what Greg sings in the disco medley at the end
with Shake Your Booty.
It's a very funny phrase, attitude dancing.
That's what I love about some 70s stuff,
where it's like, there's a new kind of sound.
And then what they sing is like already
in the 70s, 25 years out of date.
So I think it's important to jump in right now
and let you guys know that a lot of this stuff
was replaced stuff that was deemed too bad for the air.
Whoa, so post filming the pilot,
there was another pass done
and what we just saw was the second pass.
And that to complete this, get this on the air in time,
that the editors and director worked for like,
three straight days without sleeping.
It's important this, they had to.
The underwater clown thing,
which seems completely unfinished.
That just ended up in the show,
the idea of people staying up all night for three days,
losing their minds.
Also, apparently while shooting this,
the director was screaming at people.
He got fired.
He threw something and hurt somebody.
He was this violent, furious guy.
But this is important.
So from the book,
the script featured a Halloween themed skit,
later removed entitled, The Frady Bunch.
Which was described as our lovable Brady's,
made up in light gray tint and dressed unlike,
not unlike the Adams family,
your average American family of vampires or ghouls.
Among other things that involved Marsha feeding McDonald's
cheeseburgers to a live plant named Waldo
and a dead corpse seated at a harp
as the Brady's sing the Monster Mash with the Osmonds.
They built an entire set for this.
I mean, that sounds so much better.
That sounds awesome.
That's a premise.
There's a game.
You see B stuff we learned.
That's what would love that game.
That's what would love it.
But the final draft of the script eliminated
The Frady Bunch and added a chorus line,
pip in an additional series of disco songs for the finale.
So that's what went in instead of The Frady Bunch.
Wow.
So less comedy, more jazz.
More Broadway.
Yeah.
I'll let you keep talking.
Cause I went wondering if there's more insight into like,
cause like when you watch a Jack Benny special like this,
Jack Benny knew what he could do.
Not every sketch was good.
Not every piece was good, but like it was clear,
like he knew what he could do.
He knew he had a guest star who could sing.
They're going to do the song.
This is like, well, the Brady's can do it all.
They can't do anything.
But they can't do anything other than be in the show
that is fine from the original show I'm talking about.
We're all collectively watching The Frady Bunch Variety Hour
together for an audience, which is weird in and of itself.
Yes.
Well, we were on a real kick in like 10 years ago
or nine years ago, Netflix got a bunch of seemingly
public domain stuff, like all, like the Jack Benny show.
And I think one of the Groucho game shows,
but only like 10 random episodes each.
But the Jack Benny stuff from like the 50s was pretty solid.
Yeah, I mean, there's always going to be like
problematic stuff, but I think we were,
cause I didn't see a lot of Jack Benny as a kid
on Nick at night.
And we were watching him and we're like,
Jack Benny is funny.
Like he's really, really funny.
And some of the episodes are like just as good
as any classic TV.
And then, you know, once in a while, yes,
I will find a Jack Benny special,
like the one I found recently where he gets a new look
and it's in the seventies and he's like 75 years old
or something.
And they're like dressing him like Austin Powers.
It's like not a great special, but you can,
like there's some things that are interesting.
The best one of those is one of my favorite clips
of TV ever.
And it's, I don't know, it's some variety show.
Cause most television seem to be variety shows at the time.
It's Tennessee Ernie Ford, who's saying 16 tons.
Yeah.
And he comes up to the host.
He's like, I hear there's a new kind of sound out there.
So I've, I'm giving it a shot.
And he just sings a slightly faster 16 tons
while there's like go-go dancers around him
and very light rock.
It's like, it's so funny.
That's great.
This was in 1995.
Well, speaking of like in context things,
this is also important behind the scenes stuff.
So obviously the guest star is Tony Randall,
who has a very strange arc where he comes in,
they try to replace the dad with him.
Then he comes back almost seemingly like two hours later
and does, I think my favorite thing in these shows.
I was gonna say by far,
that's the highlight of the show is Tony Randall
is dressed almost like,
like you would play like an old leprechaun in a sketch
with like big kind of puffy, like sideburns.
And like a mutton chop.
Mutton chop, thank you.
That's what I'm looking for.
And then like, yeah, like a greenish suit.
And then screaming a poem at you
that you can't really understand.
Yeah, like a dense.
I just wrote down the line,
like through the wheezing hurdy-gurdy.
You're just being pummeled with lines like that.
While a little person dressed as a bear
is doing like dancing for their life.
Yeah.
Seeing me dance the vogue, said Mr.
Wag like a bear.
In my top hat and my whiskers that,
tra la la trap the fairies.
Where the waves seem chiming, hey cots,
I dance the vogue, a fair.
Stand Venus' children in the gay procs.
Maroon and marine and snare.
The sea be fire my pistol.
Through the distance, blue is my coat.
Like Wellington fire on the mark,
with the crystal, busby creek, feeds float.
While the wheezing hurdy-gurdy of the marine wind blows me
to the tune of Adiruni sturdy, over the sheeps of the sea.
And I really, when I was watching,
there was a clip going around yesterday
of an outtake from X-Men 3 where Kelsey Grammer's Beast
does a speech about Crispin's day
to psych up the team.
Wow.
And I was like, wow, Tony Ranna was like,
before Kelsey, like Kelsey Grammer would love
to do this bit, I bet.
Oh yeah, yeah, it's a precursor to the laughing and rhythm.
Has everyone seen the laughing and rhythm?
Hmm, that sounds familiar.
at a Just For Laughs festival in 94 that Kelsey Grammer did
and it's this weird, it's him with like an upright bass
and a piano guy.
Oh, I have seen this.
Yeah, you know what I'm talking about?
Yes, yes, yes.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Yes, I have seen this.
Laughing in rhythm.
That's what it is.
Yes, yes, I've seen that.
Musical haws, like he's laughing weird.
We'll add that to the clip watching
and I'll show you Crispin's day speech as well,
which is fantastic.
Well, this is important.
So this is from the head writer, Karl Kleinschmidt.
Marty Croft and I went to visit Tony
at the Chateau Marmont on Sunset Boulevard.
Tony had one of those bungalows and he came out
to greet us in his bikini underwear
and he laid down on his chaise lounge
and he talked to us for an hour.
I always thought that was one of the strangest interviews
I've ever had with an actor with a man lying
in his bikini underwear.
He was agreeing to come on the Brady Bunch hour.
So that's like how they got, like how they sold,
like the behind the scenes of this is extremely fraught
and weird and yeah, it's like one guy
like almost breaking someone's hand
for like doing stuff wrong.
Also the pool was kind of a half-assed idea.
There's a giant pool on stage.
That was because Donnie and Mary had ice skating.
So they're like, okay, they have ice skating,
we'll just do a pool.
But no one had ever done a pool
like on a soundstage like that before.
And immediately it was a disaster.
Like it, you couldn't see the water was all milky.
So they had to fill the thing with sparklets
and constantly like filter and add chlorine to it.
And then also like it had to be held
at this specific temperature so that it wouldn't,
like it wouldn't steam because it was cold there.
It was like, it was something where they should have
just said, you know, forget the pool.
But then the pool became the centerpiece of the whole thing.
Cause they had, they had dancers who then had to learn
to be synchronized swimmers.
They weren't already.
Wait, I thought the point was like,
and then we'll have a synchronized swimmers.
They just drafted dancers.
It seems like a chintzy Busby Berkeley sort of thing.
But if you read about how they made those
Busby Berkeley movies, they had hundreds
of synchronized swimmers and dancers.
They had massive camera rigs and it would take weeks
to shoot a musical sequence.
Not in the way they would just crap out
70s variety specials on TV.
The Crofteds also talk about in the book
that there wasn't this, the pool didn't have any stairs
in or out of it.
Oh my God.
So you had to just skull for hours to like,
and they would shoot the swimming from like midnight
to 3 a.
m.
And these women were just like floating like,
or if you held, you could hold onto the side of the pool,
but it was slippery and it was very like,
but people were worried it was gonna explode
and destroy and electrocute everybody.
Cause it was just like on a crappy sound stage.
This is like one of Jigsaw's twisted games
from the Saw films.
But it is used for, yeah, the underwater clown sketch
which is a really pure piece of comedy.
That's a highlight.
Where you don't know what's happening at all.
And Scott, we were in the dark.
We didn't know about the underwater clowns.
I didn't either.
I mean, I didn't know exactly what happened in this pilot.
Just imagine me like, okay, so I've already watched
20 minutes of bizarre, bad Brady Bunch singing and dancing.
And then a screen comes up that says coming up next.
And it's two painted clowns and fireman hats
swimming at you.
Yeah, underwater clowns.
Coming up next.
What a threat for me specifically.
Yeah, so the list of podcasts to ride clowns now
are growing.
So we have Chukko, we have like.
Never remember that other one.
Sugar Smacks.
Sugar Crisps one.
I had it.
I tweeted a joke about them.
Why is Cliffy?
Cliffy.
Cliffy the Clown.
Yeah.
Cliffy, there's a Dorney,
we learned about a Dorney Park one.
Yeah.
That sent us.
Right, and now we have the Brady Clowns.
Whatever they're called.
Oh, and we have Bozo.
The Crofted Clown.
And we have Bozo and his clown babies.
Oh, and the clown babies.
That I added that I don't know.
Bozo's babies?
There was a, yeah, I was trying to figure out
who owns the rights to Bozo.
Okay.
And there's a website for Larry Harmon Productions,
which is a guy who was, he played Bozo,
because there's many different Bozos,
but he played Bozo.
He claimed he invented him.
He did not.
He was in the Clown Hall of Fame
and then was removed from the Clown Hall of Fame
when they found out he was not the original Bozo.
But his wife still owns Bozo and Laurel and Hardy.
So if you want to license Laurel and Hardy or Bozo
or the property Bozo and his clown,
Bozo the Clown and the Clown Babies.
These little shitheads.
Oh no, I hate them.
They're terrible.
But they are podcasts about characters now
in the clown family of clowns.
And underwater fire clowns.
And the Brady, underwater Brady.
Fireman clowns.
Yeah.
This is, just to like.
Roster of clowns.
Just to back up a little bit and get into it,
because I think we have to explain what the premise
of the Brady Bunch Variety Hour is,
because if you weren't clear on this,
it is musical numbers done.
But the hosts of the show are the Bradys.
And I don't mean Robert Reed and Florence Henderson
and the actors.
It is Mike Brady and Carol Brady.
So this family of which the patriarch is an architect
are doing a variety show for you.
And he's very apologetic.
That you discover that they wrote
Bobby's complaining about writing the scripts.
Bobby Brady, who's a 15 year old regular kid
from somewhere just the middle of the country.
I don't know.
But it gets so odd and murky because yeah,
what is, we're in a universe,
this isn't the universe where the Brady Bunch,
the sitcom aired, right?
It's a world where some random family has a show now.
But then they'll say things like,
the boy, the kids are a little taller
than when you last saw them.
When did I see them?
I don't know these people, right?
Because we've never seen the Bradys.
You know what I mean?
Honestly, I missed that.
I thought that the idea was like that the show was
a show that everybody liked, but they were a real family.
The reality was that people-
It was like a documentary.
I guess, yeah.
That the Brady Bunch, the show,
the first five seasons you're saying was-
Was real.
That's capturing the Freedmans.
But the Loud family had just been on PBS
where you're following around Lance Loud and his family.
Oh yeah.
The Brady Bunch was, yeah, the Freedmans,
it was like a-
We do know them.
That's how my brain squared that circle.
But that's not how, they didn't explain that.
That was not an explanation of like,
you remember our show that everyone liked.
They didn't say that.
No.
So then there's wraparounds where like some of it,
most of it is them on stage introducing songs,
but then it'll cut to them in a house,
not the standard Brady house, but a new house.
And there's stories where they aren't playing out to camera
except sometimes at the end, like, boy, what's his problem?
Wait, so you could look at us, the audience the whole time?
Are we in your house or is this reality?
of the sketch to pull a Deadpool
and start talking to the audience.
Or a Wayne from Wayne's World.
The original Deadpool, Florence Henderson.
And you get this sense that like,
I'm feeling like behind the scenes,
they're not talking about this as like being conceptual,
and we're breaking the fourth wall and we're combining,
it's the Brady's, but we're twisting the variety.
Like when people talk, like Bo Burnham has that new special
and people are like, oh yeah,
and it's these specials where people are like,
oh, and they're deconstructing what standup is.
That is not what's happening here.
This is just a straight variety show.
Yes, and the way they try to fix it
once the show gets picked up is that in the second episode,
they re-move into that house.
They move into the house you saw in the pilot.
What?
Wait, because I, yeah, in the little bit I've seen
of this show, I do remember them moving in.
They moved to Malibu.
They're like, we just moved to California
to do our variety show.
So that happens in episode two.
In episode two, which they've already been in that house.
And so then they're like, okay, there's,
and then their mover who moves them in,
who becomes a major character is Rip Taylor.
Who is a brand-new angel.
Fantastic.
He plays Jackie Merrill.
He runs a moving company.
Then later he's a real estate agent.
And then also he just tells everybody he's also a comedian.
Okay, that makes sense.
He's in every ensuing episode of the Brady Bunch Hour.
They brought him in just to smooth things over,
to have somebody who had some variety experience,
but also very importantly to be a love interest for Alice.
Oh my God, thank God.
Because in the two years or three years
since the Brady Bunch had been off the hour,
Ann B.
Davis, oh sorry.
Davis left Hollywood.
She had disappeared from the Hollywood scene,
moved to Denver, Colorado.
And she was working as a volunteer at a vicarage
of the Episcopal diocese
under the leadership of Bishop William C.
Foy.
Oh my gosh, because this is my question.
Because the first episode, there's not a lot of Alice.
And I was like, well, Alice was always the funniest one
on the show, that I wanted any sort of like comedy chops
or timing.
And kind of a Betty White over time where you could tell
she's been at this since the 50s, she's a pro.
Yeah.
So she was, she said quote,
I decided to sell my house in LA
and yield control to the Lord.
And she was just living on this compound,
giving lectures, leading worship,
and performing daily chores.
And so she made a deal with them
that she would do the show if they would let her go back
for like most of the weekend, do her chores on the property.
Her religious chores.
But so two other things about this is that
she wore the same shirt every day to set,
embroidered with Jesus's Lord on it.
Alice, in real life, Alice needed to do a lot of chores
and wore the same thing every day.
Yes.
And the negotiation was like,
she had to fly back to Denver midweek to do her chores.
And so they were like, okay, we'll figure this out.
But Jerry, who played new Jan, says that she,
over the year that she worked at the show,
never had a single conversation with Anne B.
Davis.
What?
Oh my God.
And that a lot of times she just sat by herself.
That's a quote from Jerry.
Wow, weird.
So, yeah.
And so then she gets paired up with Rip Taylor,
who she despises.
And everyone else was just very quiet.
Rip Taylor's quotes about Anne B.
Davis,
like behind the scenes of this thing are so vicious.
Oh man.
Like she hated him.
She wouldn't speak to him.
And it sounds like Rip Taylor was just like,
we'll watch a clip with him later,
but like he was really just trying to make everybody happy,
he was giving everyone little presents.
He was like being real friendly to the kids and like,
and she just like, he's like, she didn't have to,
I told her at some point, why bother?
Like, why bother even pretending?
Like he has this like crazy invective about Anne B.
Davis
just being so mean to him.
Wow.
Probably just because she was extremely homophobic
and he was like an out gay guy.
He was not an out gay guy.
He well.
But he was like super like.
Yeah, but Susan Olsen said his boyfriend
was just like hanging out on set.
Yeah, he was out there.
But the only reason I say that is because when I went
to the silent movie theater with Andrew Thurman
to see a Rip Taylor documentary with Rip in attendance,
they kayfabe that in the movie.
Wow.
They didn't bring it up.
Nope, his relationship with women,
that's what they talked about in the movie
and they did not get into it.
Andrew and I were both just in West Hollywood,
which we have not been in for a long time
and which is where he used to live.
And I know this because I went and picked him up myself
for a Funny or Die shoot and drove him back to Funny or Die.
And I was reminding Andrew Grissom of this and he said,
oh yeah, me too.
Yeah.
You also had a solo car ride with Rip Taylor.
I know that is a fact that you both had a solo car ride
with Rip Taylor and interactions with him.
Two good friends who didn't put together for a while.
I was just in the room with Rip Taylor five feet away
and he almost sat next to me for the documentary
because the director came over and said,
would you mind if Rip sat next to you?
Oh.
And I was like, no, sir, please.
Was he fun to drive around?
Was he.
Oh yeah, yeah.
Well, a lot of fun and told great stories and everything
and just doing completely his thing.
And then for like the four person crew for this video,
he did a big confetti show,
a very gruff cameraman friend of mine.
He like commanded to sit on the floor
and put an orange cone on his chest.
Like you go down there, do that.
And this guy who like never cracked a smile
at any comedy video ever just was like dying
at having to do that.
And then he gave us all white chocolate rip mustaches.
That's great.
And they rolled them all up
and he made us take pictures.
Now you go over there.
Now here, now you, Matt Mazzani has been on the show.
He was just, he wasn't even part of it.
He was just walking through the, down the hallway
and Rip was like, here, take these
and handed him a ton of toilet paper rolls.
All right, now I'm gonna put my tongue out behind you.
Just like directing a madcap photo shoot.
But then there was this weird thing.
I don't think I've told this on the show and RIP,
R-I-P Rip, sorry he's not with us anymore,
but the, I was in, basically like he kept calling
about various things and I like, and he had my number.
Oh, weird.
And there was a thing where funnier
that I gave out a gift basket that year.
And part, and the joke of the gift basket is that
there was an invoice for the like the monetary worth
of what was in the gift basket.
So like, here's all this stuff,
but also send us back $300 or whatever it is.
That's funny.
Yes, funny to us, we got the joke.
He did not get the joke.
He was given this gift basket.
It was sent to his home and he decided
to take his anger out on me.
And the funny thing about this story is that
when this happened, I was at Disney World.
I was at the Animal Kingdom Lodge,
that nice restaurant there.
And I got a call from an unknown number
and I was expecting something from my parents
who the only unknown number I had and like,
I like, oh, I better talk to them.
It could be an emergency or a problem.
Like, hello, with a lot of urgency.
Scott, it's Rippy.
There's invoice, what are you doing to me?
Is it some kind of a joke?
Yeah, it is a joke.
Well, it's not very funny.
And I'm out, I'm in the like the lobby,
like the valet pickup of the Animal Kingdom Lodge
with Rip Taylor yelling at me.
This was an experience in my life.
Another tie into the podcast.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
See guys, it's all, like Eisner's watching over all of it.
Yeah, I, well, I'll use that as a transition.
We got sent a good Eisner thing,
which I think we had seen,
but one of those celebrity auctions,
which Eva, I think we're all checking,
you got me at least into looking at these celebrity auctions.
And now I'm sure we're all looking at it.
But there was this framed wallet-sized Michael Eisner photo
on one of them.
Wallet-sized and framed?
And framed, so it was a place setting.
That's a very small frame.
A framed wallet-sized photo of Disney CEO Michael Eisner
served as table decoration for his birthday event at Club 33.
And the description says,
since Eisner was new at Disney,
he did not know Disney executives were discouraged
from appearing in mouse ears as it was deemed unprofessional.
Oh no.
So it's a very specific bit.
I mean, there's lots of weird stuff
about the Disney corporate culture back in the day.
And I'm sure I still-
How much did that go for?
How much did it go for?
I have to log in to see price.
Oh yeah, well, let's look it up.
They were estimating 100 to $200, which seems low to me.
The last celebrity auction I went to
was a very slipshod, ramshackle one.
My favorite thing in it, which I did not bid on,
was an empty bottle of Valium
that was owned by Truman Capote
that was donated from the estate of Johnny Carson's wife,
who was buried alongside Truman Capote.
They were buried together.
But not Johnny.
No, Capote and Johnny Carson's wife.
But then I looked and the two years before,
there'd been a huge lot of Truman Capote's used medicine
that went for auctions with people.
Somebody bought that and was piecemeal out.
The Valium's the good one.
And then, Mike, remember what you wanted to bid on,
but you didn't?
Chase Meridian's notes from Batman Forever.
What was that?
So there was another Batman Forever thing
that was really good.
I was sending you life.
I went to the auction, I sent you photos.
What was the other one?
Mr.
Freeze's frozen TV dinner.
Oh, from Batman and Robin.
It was the frozen dinner,
the Mr.
Freeze frozen dinners
when he goes into that like extra freezer part of his lair.
Where his wife, where Nora is.
I think they were called Gotham meals or something.
They were branded after Gotham City.
But there was a lot of great-
The sitcom thing in that movie
where he's got all the snowmen who he makes sing.
I missed it, yeah.
I missed it.
That's like pretty much the right material.
Oh my God, I love the movie.
The Eisner photo sent to us by Ed Roberts on Twitter.
Thank you, Ed.
Thank you for sending it.
That's awesome.
So just a couple more things.
Okay, I'll tell you what happened.
So the show's gets picked up a series,
major overhaul, new director,
because that guy was bad,
new, I think, choreographer potentially,
definitely new costume designer, new set designer.
They redo this, they make the set more attractive,
but, and they also change the format
where they add a musical guest,
it's just flat out just singing a song.
So they get their format down,
they have a guest star and like one or two musical stars.
So January 23, 1977, the next episode airs.
And very quickly, the show kind of gets,
the only thing that's weird is that
the show will only be airing once a month
in a shifting time slot.
And they have to explain that in their opening monologue,
which they call an octologue,
because all eight of them get to talk.
So the opening is basically that they move into their house.
Rip Taylor is the moving van guy,
but then he tries to put his furniture in their house
and he flirts with Ann Davis, he flirts with Alice,
and then Lee Majors and Farrah Fawcett show up
and they wanna stay in the house
because he rented the house to them for the night.
So they're just like living in the house with the Brady's.
Married at the time, correct?
Yeah, very confusing, just a confusing setup.
And they're not really doing sketch acting either,
just kind of like mincing around and being quiet and stuff.
And so it's just weird.
The musical guest is Captain Cool and the Kongs.
Of course.
And just some highlights are that
they do a really weird version of the car wash
where they're all dressed up like the characters
from Wizard of Oz and Ann Davis is the Wicked Witch.
I've seen this, I've seen this, yes.
That one's crazy.
I've seen that, yes.
Yes.
And it's just, it's bad.
There's like, they start off with like a really long
Yankee Doodle Dandy, like just in Yankee Doodle.
I may have seen that too, that sounds familiar too.
Can I ask a question?
Do they explain why Alice is no longer with Sam the Butcher,
her longtime boyfriend on the Brady Bunch?
I don't know, that's a good question.
I don't know if it came up or they just were like,
I mean, they had to move.
Right, of course.
You didn't move with them.
That's a good point, okay.
So yeah, she moved and she left Sam behind.
I feel like they got married in one of those movies.
And during the car wash number,
this is an interesting detail,
the headdress worn by one of the dancers was fastened
so tightly that she was in excruciating pain
and discovered her head was bleeding when it was removed.
Oh my God.
So like the amount of like human misery
this show inflicts on people is really crazy.
Did you see the fact, this was just a Wikipedia thing,
maybe it's in the book too,
but that there was a shared studio,
which you know where they were doing this at KTLA
and next door where Chevy Chase was working on something.
Yeah, so this is really interesting that Jerry,
so when I could tell Jerry and Susan,
who you know, fake Jan and Cindy
were really stoned all the time.
And they were in high school
and they just started skipping school
and going and hanging out with Chevy Chase.
Oh, this wasn't even where I was going.
Oh yeah, they were just like,
so like just going over, hanging out in his office,
like sitting on his desk, winging their legs around.
In high school and they're on drugs?
I don't like the sound of this.
But it sounds like also like,
according to the story, like he didn't do anything.
He just sort of liked having these like
cute stone teenagers in the office
and Paul Schaeffer was there too.
So it seems like he was like.
Paul was like mitigating,
he was making sure everything was okay.
Yeah.
He was like a chaperone.
Yeah, they're just like running away from their in school.
They're supposed to be like,
we're gonna work on our ceramics project for school.
And then they just go and they're like, hey Chevy.
And like, so that's going on.
I was gonna say that they,
according to Wikipedia that Chevy and I guess Schaeffer
would go, they'd like call,
they'd cut meetings short for their things
so that they could go like overlook,
like look through a window at this taping
and ogle the Croftettes, the swimmers.
Oh yeah.
Everyone would come by and like look at that.
Cause there was also a window in the pool
that they would shoot through.
And so you could just like watch the women swimming
through the water.
Oh, also.
Could you watch the clowns?
Yeah.
Okay.
Then other thing is that they repeat like a conversation
really early off where like all the men on the show,
except for Bob Reed, just talk about how much like
they would fuck Jerry.
They're like, man, like all the three brothers are like,
oh yeah.
That was on the camera?
No, no, behind the stage.
They're just all talking about how this like teenage girl
is like, oh God, yeah.
The new girl playing their new sister
where they just met like a week ago.
They all, oh my God.
So they're all just like,
are they doing like the fifties version of it
where they're like a wolf, woo, woo.
Like, are they doing like wolf?
No, I think one of them,
I think one of them like bit his fist or something.
That sounds like the fifth.
Yeah, they're just like,
they're just openly talking about how this like,
this teen girl like could get it.
Sure, sure.
Well, can we say something also about like,
because you're watching a lot of,
at least in the pilot, I imagine the other episodes,
it's as we've said, a lot of musical numbers
and a lot of, you know, songs that are usually,
that are usually romantic and from the point of view
of I'm singing to you how I love you and you're beautiful.
And these songs are being sung to you by a husband and wife
and then a bunch of pairs of step brothers and sisters.
So there's so many moments that are like,
then they break off and Greg and Marcia dance together
and Bobby and Cindy dance together,
like slow dancing and dipping.
And they're always like,
there was this one scene between Greg and Marcia
where they're inching closer and closer to each other.
I don't even remember what they're talking about,
but it's like the framing you would have
right before a kiss happens.
Yeah.
And no kiss happens.
It's just like the weirdest, horniest show
between all of these step siblings.
Predicting a worldwide communications network
decades later filled with terabytes and petabytes
of videos labeled not sister, not brother, step siblings.
Did you say the word petabyte?
Petabyte is the one above terabyte.
Wow.
That's awesome.
Yeah.
I never heard that.
And it sounds- What are you referring to though?
A porn website?
Oh, pornography, like pornography.
Like- Did you general the concept of pornography?
That would be funny to just upload this show
and be like, step, step siblings.
Like step siblings dance together.
So this is interesting.
So the next episode is, so we have Tony Randall
and we have Favre, Foz and Lee Majors,
like, okay, those are modern stars.
But then the next one, the star is Milton Berle.
The guest star is Milton Berle.
So once again, it's like an old person
that nobody really cares about.
And the plot of that one is that he takes over the show.
There's a lot of like people take over the show
and he makes it annoying
and he makes dad wear a Carmen Miranda outfit
that embarrasses him.
It's a long sketch in the pilot is this,
the humiliation of wearing a bunny costume
or a bear costume.
And there's a story that I guess Bruce Valanchelike
was like, I wanna see your giant penis, Milton Berle.
Cause I've heard it's really big.
And he's like, and Milton Berle's like,
why would I show it to you?
And he says, I don't care that it's yours.
I care because you had sex with Marilyn Monroe
and I wanna see something that she saw.
And that's, so he like says that to Berle
in front of the whole writer's room and Berle denies him.
Sounds right.
Am I wrong?
That's unnerving.
Am I wrong though that it's in the Tom Shales book,
Milton Berle shows like the cast of Saturday Night Live
is penis, am I wrong?
They're cool, they're hip.
He's gotta impress them.
There's no Valanches.
Valanches time will come later with crystal monologues
and whoopee monologues.
In the 90s he would have shown his penis every day.
Right.
But yeah, Milton Berle was like, no, leave me alone.
Wow.
And the guest, the musical guest for this episode
is Tina Turner.
So it's Milton Berle, Tina Turner
and a puppet named Colette who sings,
it's like a sexy puppet who sings a song with,
with the mill songs.
I think if I've seen Colette.
You maybe have seen it.
On a different show.
Yeah, where she's like, I sing with you
and she's like this weird.
She keeps calling him like some phrase involving pussy.
Yeah, and she was an old school Croft show
from like Croft's puppet from.
Okay, okay.
They had an erotic follies that kind of made them famous
and then got them on Dean Martin.
So they brought that out.
There's a part in that number also where she's French
and alluring and like, please, I want you to sing.
What do you mean sing?
Sing, sing.
Isn't that a prison?
Good joke.
Little sing sing.
Yeah, little sing sing joke.
So, okay, so then we get to episode four,
which for some reason this,
this tape is just the pilot in episode four
and there's no other episodes
have ever been released officially.
Oh, it's all on YouTube.
I watched most of them on,
the only one I can't find is the Red Fox episode.
I can find some clips, but yeah, that one,
but everything else is fully on YouTube
and pretty good quality.
So I encourage anybody who's interested
to just go on YouTube and watch this stuff,
including the ones we just watched.
They cannot, they cannot let that out in public.
That one's locked in a vault.
They cannot let out the comedic,
like an actual comedic.
A funny person.
Yeah, a funny person.
Not that Tony Randall wasn't funny,
but that was bizarre.
His appearance in this is bizarre.
The Tony Randall musical number
and I think the underwater clowns
are the most where you can see like,
oh, this is a Sid and Marty Croft thing.
Yeah, and they're losing their mind and like.
Fucking gross shit.
What Florence Henderson's wearing in that clown thing,
like a big bulbous kind of like,
Commedia dell'arte.
I need anything like that,
a stupid little clown hat and then like a big Y.
It's like Cirque du Soleil too.
You know what I mean?
Where like, yeah, like, yeah,
you're a regular shaped person,
but you wear a thing that makes you five times wider
and little dots on that.
You're kind of a doll.
Well, but you like the Studio 60,
Commedia dell'arte.
Exactly.
That's smart.
That's like something you saw Sandy Duncan do
30 years ago.
Oh, it's shields and Yarnell kind of stuff.
Awful, awful.
There's that one Disney World special they're in,
which I like because it's an old Disney World thing,
but oh, and it's a Pinocchio thing.
Shields and Yarnell plus Pinocchio.
The worst.
Raggedy Ann, raggedy Annies.
Awful.
Adults should never dress like Raggedy Ann,
Raggedy Annie ever.
So upsetting to me.
So I want to show you guys just the middle
of this episode four.
And so maybe we could stop down briefly
and we'll watch it and we'll talk about it.
And this is like, just like extended,
this is what the house sketches evolved into
once Rip Taylor was on the scene
and they had made it more clear that they had moved.
Sure.
All right, we'll be right back.
Okay.
Okay, we're back.
We just watched a one act play.
Yeah, there really had a lot of moves.
There were a lot of moves in it and unexpected moves.
Yeah, lots of surprises.
Like I gotta say that you didn't see where it was going.
Well, because so this sort of,
let's just synopsize it before we have our observations
really that there's a, well,
in a very traditional sitcom way,
Greg is annoyed because he's trying to play guitar
and Marsha's reading a magazine.
You can't, those things can't coexist.
He's getting upset.
And then this pushes him over the edge
to announce his intention to move out of the house.
He doesn't want to live with the Brady's anymore.
So one thing to note for the listeners
not looking at this,
Greg Brady is 32 years old.
He looks very old.
In all of the scenes that we're watching,
he has the, it's the most 70s on 70s on 70s,
butterfly collar.
It's huge.
This is like why people started hating the 70s
and making fun of the 70s is this was like maybe the,
the most like height of insane, too much 70s at once.
But anyway, all that to say he is like,
it is the most open chest.
Yeah.
The shirt goes, it's like,
it's down to one button almost and so hairy.
So why is it even a crisis that he's moving out of the house?
Cause he's old, very old.
He's very old.
Very old.
Yeah.
It's too much chest hair for a mother to be upset.
You know what I'll say that I'll say about this.
Cause we were talking about like,
what do you like the, the first episode was confusing.
Cause it's like, there's still the Brady's
and they live in a house together,
but it's mostly just about the variety show
and them planning it.
I do think probably people putting the show together,
we're just like, well, what are these fuckers good at?
What do people like about them?
Well, they like it when they get into some sort of drama
interpersonal drama.
And they obviously were like, all right, great.
Let's give them a juicy piece of plot
that we're going to put into play here.
So they're like, yeah, Greg's going to move.
Instead of another medley about the general idea of dancing.
Yeah.
Let's get back, let's tell a story.
Exactly.
So I was like, okay, I could see where they're like,
let's just do the thing that people like, you know?
So this is where we're introduced to Rip Taylor.
Mr.
Merrill.
Who is a renter of things in general, items and places,
anything that can be rented.
Yes.
And just in the next episode, it's supposed to be like,
also a comedian.
He just says that he's like, I'm a comedian also.
And then he just sort of ripped that on as a comedian.
He's probably just on the variety show part two.
Oh yeah.
Okay.
Yeah.
Makes sense.
So he comes in with the discovery that,
with the information that there's already been an apartment
set up for Greg.
And then you watch them tour the apartment together.
And this is very like,
well, I think step-by-step did this five times.
Yeah.
Where a sibling,
like a kid wants to move out and be on their own.
And then they do for one night,
but the apartment is weird and bad and run down.
And I'm like, I'm way ahead of this.
I've seen this a zillion times,
but there was certainly a move that I did not see coming.
Mike, do you, you were, because you lit up at the move.
Can you, do you want to?
I got excited because I heard there was a voice,
very famous voice.
I still can't really explain to you what he was doing there.
But all of a sudden you hear a voice that I, I'm like,
Oh, it's Vincent Price is about to make his presence known.
And that was correct.
Yeah.
And he comes in and he's very, he's just, you know,
he's speaking like Vincent Price and doing his normal,
like he's saying things like I can't track any of them.
It's like, it sounds good, but I'm-
Such dense language.
The only one I wrote down is that he's assessing the
apartment on behalf of half of the, the AGEA,
the American Ghost Encounters Association.
You're right.
That was great.
That was the best probably exchange.
And he's talking about how it's beyond that.
It's just a junky, bad apartment with a dirty window.
The apartment is haunted.
And who better to describe all that than Vincent Price.
Which, which Greg realizes, like realizes,
or just even says it about five minutes into the interaction.
Hey, you're Vincent Price.
Yeah.
So he's not a character.
Unlike Rip Taylor is a character and Barry Williams is
Greg Brady, but this is real Vincent Price.
Right.
Does he wait, does he live there also?
Or is he just checking it out?
Cause he knows that a bunch of ghosts have been there.
He's just an investigator.
Yeah.
He's just heard about some ghosts.
He's like that.
He's like, he's a creepy guy in real life, I guess,
who loves ghosts.
Yeah.
But like a four minutes into the sketch,
Greg goes, you're Vincent Price.
Yeah.
Yes.
And is it helpful to clarify?
Casey didn't know.
We recognize him.
But it is, cause you think maybe he's just some weird
neighbor, but no, it's the actor.
Rip Taylor leaves to rent another,
cause he's got to rent another place to a 98 year old man.
And he's shrinking by the second.
So he gets out of there and then you're left with just
Vincent and Greg.
He mentions a lot of different ghost names.
So many ghosts.
So many things.
And so many like turn of phrases that don't land.
Oh yeah.
He keeps naming someone named Binky
and it's just getting no response.
No response.
This is what the Imagineers saw when they're like,
we got to get him to do the voice of a Phantom Man
or Disneyland Paris.
Oh well he's fantastic.
I mean look.
And then get rid of it right away.
And then get rid of it and then bring it back.
He's back now.
Yeah.
He's no, he look, he's Vincent Price is great.
It's just, this was a very, it's a long watch in this scene.
It feels, every scene that we've seen so far,
every element of this show feels like it could be shrunk
by a third easily.
Maybe more than just that's the first pass.
Yeah.
It's a different type of bad variety show sketch.
Cause usually with all the old stuff I've been watching,
like if Bing Crosby is doing a variety show
and he's doing a bad sketch,
it's full of lines that don't mean anything,
but they at least usually move fast.
Like it'll be like, oh, you're Bing Crosby.
He goes, well, that's what the papers say or whatever.
Like, what does that mean?
That's not really a joke.
Like it's not referencing anything.
It's just to try to move, like fill up time.
This is, yeah.
Fill up, filled up with like just so much, so many words.
And what is it all?
It's still that we're struggling to even synopsize this.
And then- The best part.
Then we thought it was over.
I was even said, okay, so is that,
cause there's a long applause.
And then it goes to Marsha in the studio talking to camera.
Boy, things have been crazy at home lately.
Anyway, check this out.
And then we go back to the house.
So why, when does the show happen?
Is, are we missing a bunch of the variety show
or is the, are the scenes in the house
the variety show or not?
I'm so hung up on reality here.
I don't know.
Way more so than the, the could the markedly stone writers
were like the, the Lanch says as much
that he was just high the whole time.
Everyone involved in it, apparently.
Yeah.
And probably the director and musical director
because the next thing is real hazy that, okay.
So the next scene is-
Great calls to give them his phone number
and lies about liking the apartment.
Right.
Yeah.
And everyone's so sad, especially Florence Henderson.
There's a little like quiver in her voice.
Mom, are you sick?
No, just something in my throat.
And then she stares at a very awkward photo
of like a 15 year old, kind of not something you'd save.
Yeah.
A bad photo of her son.
A bad black and white photo of her son.
And it's big.
It's a big photo too.
And she's just holding staring at it.
She doesn't doing it in front of everybody.
That's usually a move you would do alone
where you would stare at a photo,
which I don't think I've ever done that.
She just walked away from in the room with everybody,
picked up a photo and stared at it.
Two steps away.
And then we were in her mind palace
and she sings a song called Traces
by the band called Classics Four.
I did not know.
I did not know that.
Sometimes it's a famous hit of the time.
And sometimes it's Classics Four.
I just, I pulled it up on my phone too.
Just so the listener can get a taste of this.
So here's the song.
This is, somebody saved this on YouTube
with the video title Carol Brady Reveals True Feelings.
So on the flip side, she's staring at a photo of her son.
He's staring at a photo of the whole family.
They're thinking the same thing.
They need to be back together.
It's been three hours apart.
He can easily move back in.
They're gonna see each other at work.
They all make a television show together.
Long hours, presumably.
They'll all see a dance rehearsal.
But no, the idea that he moved out for a few hours
is so sad that all this happens.
This is all done with like a really hazy blue vignette.
And we can describe things as we see him.
He's on us.
Let me skip back slightly.
Traces of love
Long ago
All that didn't work out
Grind
Traces of love
The real history.
And then now there's a spiral staircase behind her with
I'll burn myself
I don't wanna be
I'll burn myself anymore
I'll burn myself
The other stuff we've watched today has an OK voice.
Obviously he's very cheesy and old school and whatever.
That is not the song for him.
It's a real Simon Cowell here.
Yeah, yeah.
So here's something that's really, really weird about this episode is that
Vincent Price was not supposed to be that part.
It was supposed to be Ted Knight.
Wait, but Ghost Inspector was Ted Knight.
I can't tell.
But the last second, Ted Knight canceled and Vincent Price,
I guess, did that part.
They maybe they maybe what's supposed to be a ghost inspector.
I don't know what they they got these guys.
They got Vincent Price and Tony Randall by just leaving a door open.
And they were just what's going on in the air.
It's like, great, great.
Come on.
You got to fill out this start work real quick.
I mean, he's in front of the camera now.
Keep your stiff three piece polyester suit on.
We'll just use it.
Cameo inside.
What?
Yeah, maybe maybe the reason that that was such an odd scene
was because they quickly rewrote it to be ghosts.
Maybe like Ted Knight came in and he was going to be just like an uptight
landlord or something.
I don't know.
But then we wrote it.
The other thing is like this became so the ratings are just like plummeting.
At this point, it did well when it was just one special,
which is maybe what Eisner wanted to begin with.
It did surprisingly OK.
Hey, the Brady's are back.
But I think nobody was ready for this to be on again and again.
Once a month, once a month, and the time changes every time.
Yeah.
So this like you just are kind of turning on the TV a month later.
This happens.
And so because of that, also, the musical guests just kept canceling on them.
So for this episode, the musical guest is Asia Puff and stuff.
Wow.
What?
Just flopping his big head and playing piano and like it's no it's not good.
Did he regularly perform music on the show?
I don't know.
I don't even know that to be.
I don't know the show very well.
This is I don't either.
I'm fascinated by the Crofts and so much of what they've done,
but I find the Croft veneer so scary.
Oh, yeah.
Unpleasant.
Well, I brought some of it to this.
It's not it's not too full of scary puppets, but sometimes it is.
But it is like the sets are horrifying.
They're that first number of the entire series, baby face.
That is the blend of like dark orange and the kind of olive yellow
and dark reddish brown.
It is such a like nausea inducing color palette and then just sparkles everywhere.
And the sets are like falling apart and shaking as people dance on them.
Like they were they were good at putting together a spectacle, but like a truly
it makes things make me sick to my stomach.
All of the Croft things.
And I bet that ride, that pinball ride.
Oh, yeah.
That may be like I would have thrown up on the pinball ride.
Too much Croft ism at once.
Yeah, I am realizing
I have a collection, a DVD collection of Croft stuff
that was lent to me before the pandemic.
So now I've had it for a year and a half, but I still haven't cracked it open.
And it's just random, random collections,
random episodes of different, different series.
And you were never tempted in the most like you needed escapism.
The worst year ever.
It was never going to go that far.
It is it is underneath the best of the Jack Benny show DVDs.
I'm not kidding.
That's correct.
Yeah.
So one other important thing is that this episode ends with Frig
moving back in, obviously, after like an hour.
And then the family does a medley of songs about happiness.
Happiness is a warm gun.
Thank you.
So the next episode is with Charo.
I was going to ask earlier when is Charo show?
Yeah, next one.
It's the plot of this one was just another like this keeps coming back.
Everyone tells Mike he's a bad singer.
So he teams up with Charo and then Carol gets jealous.
And this is the famous thing that happened in this was there's like a sketch
where she's a cowboy and she and Peter Brady ends up kind of underneath
her on the floor with her like having her leg up on him.
And she's wearing like a denim, extremely short pair of shorts with no underwear.
And he like looked up and saw her, her vulva and talks about it in the book
that it was one of the most like jarring, like she's on camera staring.
You can see his face, see her vulva.
And it's crazy.
He's like his eyes just like just his face.
You can watch this.
That frame exists.
Yeah.
Oh, I have it in the book.
They actually single it out.
This book is like pretty crazy.
Like people are very open to just being.
Susan Olsen involved in the book tells all that just comes clean about everything.
And it is all this is pure variety show.
The book.
Yeah.
Um, a lot of there's a lot of Brady books out there.
I that's when I loved the Brady Bunch growing up and how I caught up
so hard on Braves and when I was 10, 11, I read growing up Brady.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Williams.
Oddly horny book.
The book that is like entirely about I then I really had a crush on Florence
and I took her on a date and I kissed her and then I really like we after every
scene with Marsha, then we'd go hide and make out.
And then there's this hideous TV movie based on it where they visualize all this.
And it's too it's the Cali Cuoco far too young
as like like seducing him in the pool with this little Barry Williams kid
watching her descend into a pool and just like staring and licking his lips.
It is the most upsetting.
This is on NBC.
They film this like time TV movie.
Yes.
Yeah.
I don't know why all the people talking about Hollywood,
Pedo, all the queue, all that stuff.
They never point to the TV movie growing up, Brady.
Well, now you're getting right there.
Fuel.
Yeah.
Go find it.
All your answers are there.
I will find you guys this frame, please.
We're done of him looking up and up her butt.
It's really she's Louise.
So but importantly, OK, so the next episode.
So back behind the scenes, things are really going to crap.
And I'll explain how.
But the Charo episode ends with them just singing
a America, the beautiful.
The next episode is Edgar Bergen, Charlie McCarthy and Rich Little.
And Melanie, yes, I've got a brand new pair of English.
Every person's name, you say I've watched 10 YouTube videos about them
in the last week.
The plot of this one is Rich Little develops amnesia
and believes he's one of the Brady children.
Like, just to be clear, you know, the pandemic ended, right?
You don't have to do it.
Antemic.
What?
And then.
OK, hold on.
The next episode is the one I can't find.
It's with Rich Red Fox.
Right.
But the plot of that one is
Marcia announced her engagement to a to a carefree hippie named Winston Beaumont.
Meanwhile, Red Fox lurks around the set.
OK, what would a hippie be named Winston Beaumont?
It's a stuffy name.
I don't know.
So then we're we're in the OK.
So this one's really weird.
Episode eight is Rick Dees and and the kids from What's Happening.
And the plot of that one is that the Brady kids meet the kids
from What's Happening and they're like, you should be on the show.
You should be guests on the show, which is like, OK.
And then everyone's like, no, they can't.
They can't be on the show.
Oh, what?
Which is why I don't I don't know.
It's like racism.
It's just very uncomfortable.
And and Rick Dees sings a disco, no, just gorilla.
Damn it.
Which is the later.
But he's he's debuting his new song Dis Gorilla.
And it's a real thing where I've never heard of this.
It's on this episode.
You can watch it.
I love the Bee Gees documentary where Rick Dees personally is pinned
for the death of disco and for making it not cool to like stuff like the Bee Gees
for a long time.
It's all put on Rick Dees shoulders, rightfully so.
What a bunch of crap.
You don't like disco duck at all.
I don't know.
Stupid, bad.
And I guess it's supposed to be a novelty.
But I also listen to Rick Dees growing up because he was like the he was the DJ
on the cool station.
Yeah.
Where I'm trying to I'm like, OK, at this time, I'm like,
I know too much about the Brady's and Jerry Reichel.
I have to catch up on what music is.
What's cool right now?
Quad City DJ is OK.
Oh, God.
Oh, yeah.
All right.
Now we're at the book around Peter staring up at Charles vulva.
And yeah, he's in awe of his legs in the foreground.
Pass this around.
You guys can be in awe of this too.
Just about Rick Dees, I was going to say, like, so I'm trying to like
I have to suffer through like, well, I guess Rick Dees is my ticket
to what's cool in 1997.
I better listen.
You know, he would just do Karnak just Karnak in 1997
on the radio post Carson retirement.
And there was no twist.
It wasn't like Karnak.
But this just stole it.
On the low, the weird list.
It's same thing.
We're back.
He'll disco like the stink of him ended up on the Bee Gees.
And he stole from Carson.
Wow.
So this is OK.
So this is where we're getting up to the end of this.
This.
So this is how things start to fall apart on set.
So Francis, for the first time ever, turns on everyone.
She's been nice to them their entire life.
She starts screaming at everyone for not learning their choreography
because they're according to the words of the Susan Olsen
quote, shitting in her church, which is musical theater.
Florence, Florence.
OK.
Yeah.
Florence is yelling at everybody.
OK.
And being like, you don't learn the choreography like
and start screaming at everybody.
So Bob, even though he's good friends with her, starts screaming at her
for yelling at them.
This was way before Arrested Development.
It's predated the whole thing.
There's all just like there's all screaming at each other.
He starts like going to this bar.
That's not the Denny's.
It's like a bar on the other across from the studio.
And the crew guys keep finding Bob like just drinking after work.
A horse steps on Susan Olsen's foot and breaks her toe.
So she has a hard time like just doing choreography.
This is outside of shooting.
Mike Lookinland's mom just abandons him on set
and stops coming to tapings because she's getting divorced
and she's worried about getting excommunicated from the Mormon church.
Oh, my God.
Marty Croft calls Susan's mother into a meeting and says like,
she has to lose weight.
She's 15 years old.
She's like 105 pounds.
You have to lose 20 pounds.
You have to look more like Marsha.
And so so Susan has started sneaking to the Denny's to eat salads
instead of eating with everybody else.
So she's going by herself to the Denny's.
Cast across the street.
Denny's got a freeway.
But the real problem behind everything is Maureen,
because this is the point at which she's been open about this.
She is for the entire episode of all the whole year, coked out of her mind.
And so she starts she's locking herself in her dressing room,
doing lines of coke, not coming out to do.
And every scene has all six of them in it or all eight of them.
So they can't do anything without her.
And we're pointing at her.
Like she's skinny, be like her.
Is there an anorexia part of it as well?
Both bulimia and she's also like like she has covered in like they have to put
makeup on her because she's covered in bruises because she's like injecting cocaine.
Oh, my God.
Jesus.
So this is the darkest making of I maybe have ever heard.
Darker than the Vincent Price cameo.
She shows up having not slept for three days one day.
Then she then the next day they're shooting with Rich Little.
She just doesn't show up.
And so she so they and then they call she calls.
She's like, I've got the flu.
So Sid and Marty Croft, this is an interesting thing.
They were actually there was no studio behind it.
They were financing the whole show themselves.
And if they have to shut down production, it's on them.
So they are like, OK, I guess we do have to do insurance
and like shut down the show until she comes back.
So they call insurance like we have to shut down the show.
We're we're missing an actor.
She has the flu.
And the insurance is like, well, you have to send her to a doctor right now
to get a physical to prove that she has the flu.
But we absolutely can't do that.
So they teach fake Jan all of Maureen's numbers.
She stays up all night and learns them.
They're about to shoot.
Maureen just walks back in like, hey, what's everybody doing?
So Marty Croft in front of the entire cast shrieks at her
and yells at her and like makes her start crying.
And then then the Rick Day's episode, they film it.
And that's the one that aired opposite the Oscars telecast.
My God.
Why put anything on?
I just don't.
Wow.
So then we get to the finale, which is like the darkest.
And I don't want to I just tell you what it's about.
But it's like because I encourage you guys to watch it separately.
But it's on.
Are we going to be like too depressed after it's disturbed?
Yeah, it's really weird.
So the musical and guest star of the final episode is Paul Williams.
And I didn't know anything about Paul Williams.
I think I barely even knew he existed before this.
I'm not a huge person.
Like, I don't know, Emmett, whatever.
I just had missed Paul Williams.
Yeah.
So the only plot for him is that he just walked into the house
and said, Carol Brady, he's in love with her.
And as soon as he gets in.
Yeah, he just says like, I'm in love with you.
I'm in love with Carol Brady.
And then like the dad's like, hey, you look here, mister.
Like, there's a lot of that happening back and forth.
Like people going like, look here, like Charo.
If you if you also if you don't know Paul Williams, yeah,
probably most famous for writing Green Book Connection.
If you if you don't know who we're talking about, just Google image.
You'll go, oh, yeah, right.
Yes, this guy like 70s oddball.
Phantom of the Paradise.
Yeah, yeah, like cameo machine, like odd, odd light hair.
Still a rat like wrote a lot of stuff I like seems cool.
Yeah, like big sobriety advocate.
But he on the 70s, like so I discovered him in the same way.
You just see him on things and like what?
Why?
Who are you?
Yeah, he's got such a strange presence.
It's usually missing the context of he's a songwriter or musician.
You just don't know why he's there.
Often not singing, like acting.
Yeah, he's never he's not very well justified in this era.
His newer stuff.
He's in Baby Driver.
He has one scene in Baby Driver.
Yeah.
And then he's on that Last Daff Punk album a lot.
He wrote Evergreen.
He won an Oscar for the Barbra Streisand song.
Yeah.
Evergreen.
The Ishtar songs I just discovered.
And I was wow, is a Ishtar mixed bag for me.
But the songs are pretty awesome.
Bugsy Malone, which I always in the back of my head always thought Harry
Nielsen wrote, Paul Williams wrote and recorded all the songs for Bugsy Malone.
Similar figures, similar, like sort of like the same, like clever
songwriters, like insane heedness in their personal lives.
But also and Randy Newman, maybe kind of like around the same.
But so basically what comes out is that like he's super drunk on set.
And so because I was like, I was just like really sensing a lot of like anger
from him.
And that's why you watch this, like you can sense the anger.
Because also, like at this point, the writers have gotten just so vicious.
So the only joke they make over and over again is that Paul Williams is short
and they make everybody do it in these like really cruel, like
ways.
And it's he's always the butt of every joke.
And he's like, I'm in love with Carol Brady.
And everyone's like, yeah, you're well, I shan't be watching this
triggering a crazy musical.
The lead into the pool, the and every episode, like
Greg shoves Peter in the pool and this one like Peter's already shoved himself
in the pool and then Paul Williams, like so he's like, you can't shove me in the
pool.
I'm already in the pool.
And then Greg's there and Paul Williams comes out and they make some like
more jokes about his height.
And then Paul Williams gets up close and he says under his breath, don't ever
touch my body and shoves Greg into the pool.
And it seems it's the most like raw line I was ever delivered on this show is
just don't ever touch my body, like barely audible.
So I encourage you guys all to watch that in the finale.
How many are there?
Nine episodes.
There's nine episodes.
And it aired over the course of one year, like basically once a month for nine
months.
OK, but they're producing it nonstop because it's all such complicated
production.
Yeah.
And this is crazy.
So they this is this is where I'm like, how is this possible?
The end of the book implies that nine episodes are aired.
The show gets canceled after the wrap party at the old spaghetti factory.
The only person only person who sat is Jan because she has to go back to school.
Everyone else is just like, oh, thank God.
But they implied that they shot like like a full season.
They shot dozens and dozens.
There's tons of episodes in the can somewhere of this show that were never aired.
Wow.
And they just exist somewhere.
Like twenty five episodes.
Whoa.
So this wasn't supposed to be the finale.
It's just like this is how it goes out with this weird Paul Williams episode.
Whoa.
And that's it.
That's the end of it.
And this is well before Eisner has the hits at Disney and stuff.
Yeah.
He's at Paramount or ABC.
He's at ABC before Paramount.
He got ABC out of last place.
That was what he did.
Right.
He's a programming executive.
Part of the success of Happy Days, I think.
I'm trying to think what I associate with Eisner.
Some big, big hits.
Donnie and Marie too was his thing.
He put that together.
OK.
So, yeah.
But yeah, he's he's a young enterprise executive.
So this but this was like a huge, huge disaster on all fronts.
And people, I mean, literally splintered the family unit,
made them all mad at each other.
Right.
And yet they kept like there were so many more.
Yeah, they would come back.
There's the Brady's Get Married, which turned into this pretty awful
brief threes company kind of show called The Brady Brides.
And then there was the.
Marsha's still on drugs through that.
Wow.
Really?
And they're all like, should we ask if she's off them?
Should there be an adjustment?
It's fine.
Just get her in.
She's willing to be here.
So.
Yeah.
There's always one missing in all of them.
Like there's a fake Marsha in the movie.
There's a fake or wait or Marsha.
There's a fake Marsha on the show.
The one hour drama, The Brady's, which has a big
story about Bobby being like almost paralyzed.
Ray and a race car driver.
They set up that he's a race car driver earlier and then in one
and one movie he gets like almost paralyzed.
That's the one I've seen the most.
Yeah.
Is that the one where Robert Reed saves somebody from saves
like a bunch of construction workers from a site
because there's a collapse of some kind?
It's a Christmas movie.
That's OK.
Am I being gaslit?
Is this weird?
Like, I didn't know any of this happened.
I thought it went to the sitcom, the variety show.
And then they did the get like 90s, the funny 90s movies
that acknowledge.
Oh, my God.
Not three, two entire other series, which involved a lot of mini movies.
One in the late 70s and one in the early 90s.
From somebody who's even more of a Brady Fane here, like we do with Lucy.
I think that they set up Bobby as race car driver in Christmas
special where Robert Reed saves people and then they parallel
almost paralyze him later.
Yeah, they made a separate event.
And then with the love of his girlfriend, MTV, VJ Martha Quinn,
right, was able to slowly learn how to walk again.
I remember this like seeing that on TV.
I was vaguely aware of the Brady Bunch already at like three or four.
And then this comes on at five and like groan Bobby Brady
is in a car accident and can't walk like I think I had to get
like talked down to sleep that night.
Like my parents, it was way too upsetting for me.
Five.
Wow.
So much content.
Yeah, so much content.
They that's what I love about that.
I think like, I mean, they encapsulate a lot that I love a lot
where it's just like boatloads of stuff and some of it's good legitimately.
And some of it is the worst junk ever made.
Like a lot of bands, I like sort of follow that format.
I feel like I learned it's like the entry point to Kitsch is the Brady's.
Like how much how far can this go?
It was already like a little wild with the froze and open chest.
And the fashion was crazy.
And Florence Henderson's hair with the weird bob.
And then it like the the variety show is just like all of it on cocaine.
Just like these times, Brady's times Brady's.
Yeah, yeah.
Like literally give them all drugs and like the one girl.
Like you can see the light in her eyes, just sparkling with cocaine
and those shots went out with it, you know, and you know,
she looks a little crazed, I guess crazed with drugs.
Yeah.
She's wild, which he hasn't slept for three days.
She's out of her mind.
We make jokes about, you know, like the Disney announcing the 10 different
Star Wars shows, but that's what this shit is.
It's all just like it's also more spaced out and less planned.
It's like, all right, now they're a variety show and let's throw some shit
at the wall and it's all now they're not slanting, not slanting.
Yeah, just dump whatever you do it.
They're not busy.
They aren't dead yet.
Great.
Milton Burl's bullying them and whatever.
Rick Deez is here.
OK, go for it.
You're good.
Whatever.
Let's just make eight episodes about them fighting.
Here's the idea.
The Brady Bunch has a song and dance show together.
And every time all of them are mad at one person
and want them to not be on the song and dance show.
Oh, well, change it up.
Let's have the cast of What's Happening show up.
And now they're mad at them and they can't be on the song and dance show.
It's so much more snippy than the show.
Yeah, they love each other.
And this whole thing, it's just busting balls and you jerk and Jan saying,
I wish I was dead and Marsha then replying.
Yeah, I wish Jan was dead.
So abrasive.
Is this the most just
exploited property from this era?
Because like there were so many monster shows.
Oh, yeah.
Movies, shows.
And then one with Jason Mars.
There's a couple of get smart.
Brady Bunch was a great series that had legs.
Get smart.
There's a couple of get smarts.
And there's get smart again with Andy Dick in the 90s.
I I sat.
It was a point in the television for me to watch.
I've watched it.
Smart.
I watched their pilot of Get Smart.
Whatever.
I don't know what's called Get Smart again.
I think it was just get smart.
I watched that pilot in the last two months, I think.
I was thinking about it.
I was remembering and thinking I should look it up.
Yeah, it's it's bad.
Her brains are broken.
This Brady industrial complex, this this kind of makes me understand
why like when I was growing up, you'd see comedians or commentators
or every now and then like academics or something like, oh,
and then there's television.
Yuck.
And I was like, oh, maybe that is about the Brady.
OK, maybe that's what this is.
Yeah.
And like cynical variety show crossover.
Hard to defend.
That's for sure.
I mean, it's it's wretched.
It kind of makes the era of like, I guess,
Presti were in like Prestige TV version two or three at this point.
But it kind of makes it like a miracle that like from the advent of television.
So in so few decades, it got to Prestige TV.
But through its infancy, it had to go through the Brady Punch variety hour.
Yeah.
It's funny also that like, you know, the weird
the twists and turns of Eisner's career where now he's one of the people
responsible for Bojack Horseman, which is like a pretty prestige.
It's always on critics lists and well regarded and like a deeper show for anime.
So he's part of that.
But then also greenlit this like right.
70s meets the 1920s,
like razzle dazzle, lots of celebrations of pseudo incest.
He like set up this this den of iniquity
where they're just like he set up like a place on the KTL lot,
a KTLA lot for sort of beloved sitcom actors to lose their minds
and completely unravel, go to their darkest points like the worst trash.
Like what happened to Bojack Horseman is he did that to them.
And he made Bojack Horseman about what he did to them.
Basically.
And he was he was feeding the secret stories.
Yeah, that was only he knows.
I'll tell you about what happened to Marcia.
And then and then Eisner at the end, like towards the end of his heights
at Disney is replaced by Bob Iger, who worked his way up
and became the head of ABC, did a similar turn and saved ABC
by putting on Who Wants to Be a Millionaire eight days a week.
And then just through sheer luck, through like clawing and fighting
on the creative's end, they begrudgingly greenlit two big hits,
Lost and Desperate Housewives.
And everyone at Disney was like, what are these fucking things?
Fine, just do it.
And then like just kind of like within the first seasons of both those shows,
I feel like we're we're we're pretty big.
So then Iger, it's it's but yeah, who wants to be a millionaire?
They were like people similarly were like kind of sick of it pretty quickly.
Yeah.
And then and then it was topped by Survivor.
Survivor immediately eclipsed.
No, yeah.
Reality.
Yeah.
You guys know who invented the game?
Who wants to be a millionaire?
No.
Steven Knight, the director, who also he made Peaky Blinders.
He made the movie Serenity.
Really?
He made a lot.
He he was one of the two people that came up with what was called
Cash Mountain when they pitched it.
Better name.
Yeah.
Who wants to be a millionaire?
Parky.
Yeah.
Cash Mountain.
It was fun.
Yeah.
Wow.
He like owns that game.
So he's the richest person alive.
And then he went and made all these weird Tom Hardy movies.
And then he made Serenity.
Wow.
I didn't know.
Oh, the McConaughey Serenity.
Yeah.
OK.
Oh, geez.
He made that and he made the one people like more.
No, no, no.
Insane Serenity.
The Fishing Noir Serenity.
From the same mind.
Wow.
Yeah.
This guy is kind of a this guy is kind of a nice nerd.
Weird dude.
Oscar nominated for Dirty Pretty Things screenplay.
Wow.
And yeah, weird guy.
I don't know what else to say.
Yeah.
What an odyssey.
I appreciate you guys taking this journey.
I know we appreciate you bringing the journey to us.
Always do.
Like just dictate topics.
You tell us.
That's I think how this works.
Well, how many episodes like I'm looking for an excuse to talk about Rip Taylor.
I'm looking for an excuse to tangent on all of the things I'm
consuming more than popular culture.
As long as I know you consuming to like this isn't like a recent thing.
This shit on this is the real shit.
You'll be you'll be watching some of these, I think later.
But I think I think you got to watch the finale.
It's wild.
Yeah.
Well, how far are we from like, you know, I kept watching a very bunch of
it's good.
Maybe Brady Bunch is good.
Rip Taylor is cute.
He's very the hair is very natural.
Taylor, cute.
Yes.
He definitely immediately walked on screen and added a hundred percent
more life to the Saints.
Yeah, I forgot the one detail that that everybody liked him on set.
But some of the crew didn't like him because he would throw confetti
and it would get in the pool.
Well, God forbid, the pool has got to be kept in tip top shape.
You know, it's just a massive death hazard.
That gets in the filter.
Yeah.
And they can't clean it for weeks.
Rip Taylor just keeps saying in the book that he was scared the pool was going
to explode.
I mean, I don't think he's wrong.
Every everything that could have happened on the show happened.
Every type of problem, injuries and sexual tris and drugs like,
boy, oh, boy.
But, you know, I did not mean to turn it on like that.
Sorry.
I was going to end the show with Kelsey Grammers,
Crispin's Day speech.
Oh, OK.
OK.
Well, we can point our microphones to this.
I guess in the in the interim, Eve Anderson, you survived an in-person
podcast, the ride.
Array.
I'm so happy to be here.
Thank you guys for having me.
This was great.
Because this was mixed with us watching the clips and the clips felt like
it was that four minutes or 40.
I don't know how long we've been going.
I don't know if this is a short episode or the longest episode.
It's long, but it's not the long we've done longer.
OK, OK, sure.
But it's the sort of madness that can only come from in person.
And I'm glad we're back.
Madness befitting, I guess, the most maddening production of a television
series ever.
It was a blast.
Exited the gift shop and plug.
No, I just check in.
I was doing the courtesy.
Mike, is Kelsey Grammer have anything to plug?
Well, I think he just just.
Money plane is one of the one of those movies that you can find on
any streaming service.
Money plane starring WWE wrestler Edge and Kelsey Grammer.
But this, of course, is this deleted scene from X-Men 3.
Bret Ratner's X-Men 3.
Oh, man.
OK.
The greats.
And I don't know why it was.
Nobody says I'm the whatever bitch.
That's the movie.
Yeah, that's the same movie.
OK, OK.
Should we point our microphones?
I'll put it in there.
OK, OK.
All of us.
We few.
We happy few.
We band of brothers.
For he who sheds his blood with me this day shall be my brother.
Be he ne'er so vile, this day shall gentle his condition.
And men in England now are bared.
We'll count their manhoods cheap.
They were not here with us to fight on Christmas Day.
We're in.