Five, four, three, two, one.
A theme park attraction that's almost entirely in the dark that isn't supposed to be scary
Sounds dangerous.
This is Podcast the Ride the Second Gate.
I'm Scott Gardner joined by Jason Sheridan.
Hi.
That was a very smooth intro.
I thought well yeah yeah hey when you have it ready to go and you're basing it on the promotional posters and such for this attraction it lends itself to that.
Mike Carlson, hi.
Hi I'm here yes.
This ride scared the shit out of me I will say that real quick.
I was very scared.
I wasn't supposed to but.
You say that and absolutely that's how I felt.
Oh interesting.
Before going in so I just wanted to when you said that I went oh yeah that hits close close.
I didn't take into account that this could be terrifying.
Well look it's a crime story.
It's a gritty crime drama which is one of the scariest genres.
So yeah it's pretty you know it's it's Sopranos and it's.
Clockers.
You said clockers not blockers right?
I said clockers no not blockers.
No.
The crime there was those parents not minding their god damn business.
Right right that's a different thing.
Scott you also said sounds dangerous very quickly much like the script of this attraction where a narrator says sounds dangerous very fast.
Like the phrase is rushed what do you mean?
Oh like within the first like two minutes of the show they say sounds dangerous.
Sounds dangerous.
I guess they're explaining the concept so it makes sense they say the title of the thing they're doing a quote unquote pilot of.
And they're proud of the pun I guess is it.
I don't know what it is exactly I mean sort of the word sound is in it.
It's got a double meaning I guess.
I guess.
Maybe I don't know it's a phrase they put the word that was what the show is in a weird context.
Look we'll explain all this.
This is a this is a Disney MGM studio attraction.
I think they crossed the border over to being a Disney's Hollywood studio attraction.
And a weird one one that either I can't tell if people don't know at all or if it was there strangely so long that it was the Drew Carey's face haunted people as they walked two different attractions passed by this.
It's a good question.
This is one of those where I don't yeah I have not seen a rich fandom for it.
And we've we've got a couple of these two where like I go I don't know that anybody was like stanning characters from body wars.
But body wars feels a hundred times more popular in the fandom than this does.
Yeah yeah I mean I like this because I liked everything MGM studios.
I didn't realize it stuck around for 13 years.
I can't believe how long this ran.
Yeah it did die a slow death in 2009 around there started going seasonally.
And that that feels just like the kiss of death for attraction if it starts to run seasonally except the Houdini where I did six legs great adventure where the demand was like bring it back and they did.
It's like bringing a show back from the debt like you know if they move the time slot there's probably trouble.
But yeah you know a massive fan campaign has to be launched.
This I think people had their fill of whatever what sounds dangerous.
Yeah I think they they got it.
I go ahead.
I was going to say you know it could look the every TV show has come back now.
There's not a single television show that has not been revived.
So perhaps the sounds dangerous movement will happen.
Yeah the the detective Foster people wanted hear more of his stories.
We see some see two minutes or so and then yeah and then hear the rest.
There's so many I mean there's I have noticed there's so many Disney bounders bounding is foster lately you know that like subtle foster look and if you don't know what we're talking about.
Drew Carey plays a character named Foster.
Yeah yeah he's a he's a detective and he's on the poster and up really big on the marquee of this attraction.
He's doing a real like hot cha cha.
Oh I Yikes.
It's hot out here.
It gets mighty hot being a detective which I would really like to say honestly I would call for this at a live show if somebody wants to if you have a puffy coat don't spend a lot of money on this.
But if you feel like you could easily do a foster cosplay and have some mild resemblance to Drew Carey I would or don't does that doesn't matter.
Just make that face.
Yeah you yeah I mean full cosplay too.
Yeah but bounding is the bounding is less of a bounding is the subtle.
It's a little more it can be a little more subtle though like bounding I feel like you know you anytime I see somebody bounding I go to the costume is immaculate.
Yeah it's like normal clothes version of Prince Eric is immaculate or something.
When I was first back to Disneyland I was like oh people really getting close getting close to the line on some of these Disney bounding things where I was like you you look like a walk around face character like it's like oh really.
Yeah well then then they're not bounding if it's something where you go it looks like you're wearing a costume.
I think it was just just like clothing enough.
I was did you notice that I was bounding as scuttle from the Little Mermaid.
I didn't notice.
Okay well that's what you that's what I want I want it to be very subtle.
I don't want you to notice that I'm.
I was dressed like honest John but I got heat stroke from all the wool.
The three pieces you're always dressed like I'm always dressed like honest John yeah.
And you're always dressed as one of those Disney lakes when you wear that blue shirt.
Well the new thing that we hit you for is the blue shirt.
All blue.
Set the strap for myself.
All bluey.
Has that come out chronologically.
I don't I'm not sure.
Well here let me I'm going to I'm going to date it specifically because I could be wrong because I there's a there's a date sensitive reason to be doing this as I alluded to you guys.
You insisted and you were very insistent on this coming out on a specific you really wanted to do it for.
Why in the world just sounds dangerous with Drew Carey a Disney MGM studios sound demonstration.
Why does this need to happen on this particular day.
And I can reveal now why but still with a little bit of mystery all the kind of mystery that Detective Foster would try to crack.
But I'm not going to leave too many clues but I am going to say this.
So this was done this attraction was really at the height of Drew Carey 1.
0.
This was at the height of the success of the Drew Carey show.
I think he got in whose line is it anyway on the the king of ABC's in the Disney family.
So of course we could get him to crank out this attraction really fast.
He now is sort of out of the Disney family and he's moved over to CBS and for a long time he has been the host of The Price is Right where I think he does a fantastic job.
Long long career doing that at this point.
And that brings me to this point.
So this as you hear this this upcoming Monday June 28th time may vary.
Check your local listings Monday June 28th.
If you tune in to The Price is Right with Drew Carey you may see a member of the podcast The Ride family.
And that is all I'm going to say.
Did I abscond with your dog and get him to either be a contestant or be part of the like did I make him do the mountain game.
What's the mountain game.
Oh yeah the climbers.
Yeah I made it.
I made it.
I went and climbed the mountain.
No I not at liberty to say but somebody who might be familiar to the podcast The Ride audience may may legally may make an appearance on the show.
And again now and again I don't I don't can't say what I know or don't know but you you may want to tune in like really at the top of the show.
So find out when it you know because you want to see the come on down you're going to see the come on down.
I don't know why I can't I can't elaborate any further.
I have a guess but we'll talk about it after.
Yeah yeah no you you might listeners might have a guess.
But you know part of me thinks look it's behind a paywall could just say it maybe.
But you know there's this.
The rules.
What if we get like 50,000 new subscribers in the next few days from recording to release.
Then everyone's going to hear about it.
All the producers on prices right will hear if suddenly if there's just like oddly a big pocket of listeners at CBS.
Yeah.
And this goes all the way up to the top.
I don't know who runs it now.
It's not less moon vets.
No I don't think so.
Yeah whoever took over Sumner Redstone.
His I think it's still his A.
I.
I think he technically like the pen is still in his hand in the ground.
Yeah.
So he's got to sign off on things and this could anger this.
This could all make him so angry that it awakens the ghost of Sumner Redstone.
Yeah.
Bursts out of his grave.
We don't we don't.
I had to double check to make sure.
Yeah he died.
He did.
He did pass away.
Yeah.
I remember that.
Finally happened.
Well I kind of forgot too and then he was in the in memoriam in the the Oscars potentially
after maybe both Oscars and Emmys and I of course shed some tears to myself.
I also like applauded first of all you're not supposed to applaud for the memoriam.
But standing ovation to myself at home then a long cry reflected on Sumner's career.
Yeah.
And then got scared about how his ghost might haunt me if I anger him.
So don't want any of that.
But what I do want is for listeners to tune into.
Wow.
The prices are right.
Monday June 20th and I.
This is exciting.
That is that is all I can say.
But this but that just is if that just using this this Drew Carey relevance as kind of
a Trojan horse to bring up this.
Wow.
So you're hearing this on Wednesday.
Check it out on Monday.
Wow.
Okay.
I'll try to tweet and stuff as well.
Very exciting.
Yeah.
Just go through the roll of the could it be a Monday.
Could it be a ghost boy floating down the stairs.
Yes.
Does he think that like matching up some numbers or a path out of right.
It's still is it Tillman for Tita.
Is it you know any is it.
I mean I'm not saying this is anyone that we know personally.
Right.
I think it's basically on his comeback tour.
Is it blue.
Is it not Jason's shirt but the alien blue.
Now I'm worried the shirt hasn't come up.
When does the shirt might not come up.
Okay.
Well get ready for it.
It should be right.
No but if it's a 28th it's no you're right.
No no no no.
Yeah.
Well I made a big mistake.
Well get ready for it because there's a big reveal of a new recurring.
One of our favorite new jokes coming up this Friday.
Yeah.
Oh my god.
There's so much to check out.
OK.
So check out the reveal of a new thing to make fun of Jason for checkout prices right.
On Monday it's going to be a big long weekend.
Everybody I don't I don't I don't think it's going to stick the shirt thing.
What I think there's so much there.
I think it's going to stick.
The idea that you wear a blue shirt.
A lot of your neuroses.
No I think I don't think it has legs.
This is a big one.
We got to be brewing.
It'll be like the I think one of the primaries.
It's going to shoot past treats potentially.
Yeah.
Oh OK.
And then yeah.
And we really want if you see Jason don't say hello to him or anything just yell you're
my boy blue Adam from now on.
You'll get the whole picture on that soon.
You'll get all these you get all these pictures soon.
A lot of homework for you the listener.
But right now let's focus on the task at hand which is a very strange Disney MGM Studios
attraction.
Yes.
So this is at a this was a theater.
Right kind of right as he entered the heart of Disney MGM Studios.
You're you know right off to the left of the of the Chinese theater if you're facing the
Chinese theater and this like this whole zone when the park opened these were like pretty
big marquee attractions.
They're like here's one that's all about television and we're going to put you the guests in your
favorite TV shows and then here's one where we're going to show you all the secrets of
of sound of Foley and all that stuff one of those classic attractions where we lost the
sound for some reason the famously clumsy post departments that plagued Hollywood they
lost the sound and you the listeners have to fill in the horse clip clops and what have
you.
Right.
And then those early attractions start dying off and I just in general this little alley
this like blue building zone the shiny blue building art deco kind of it's been just a
weird run.
Have we covered anything that's that are in these buildings we haven't talked superstar
television.
No we didn't do that.
There used to be the animation tour.
Right.
But that's not there though.
I'm talking about these two.
Oh you know what I mean like the theater show sound show monster sound show which was what
was in this space before.
We haven't talked and I forget which is which we haven't talked American Idol experience
which birthed the weird thing of like shirts were goofy is supposed to be like Randy Jackson
calling people dog.
Right.
Very odd time in the park.
Very odd.
Where was Millionaire.
Was Millionaire here or was it a.
Millionaire I think had its own space.
Was that in a sound that was in a soundstage potentially like in the soundstage district
right.
Like I feel like this has been like weird sing alongs.
What's there now.
Do they.
Is it the just Star Wars clips.
What replaced this.
It was there was a it was a guard.
I know it was a Guardians of the Galaxy preview at a certain point.
I think they've used it for a lot of previews.
I think it's yeah it's sort of like what happened to the Captain EO theater.
Uh huh.
Seemingly but it's just one of those spaces where they're like we don't know.
I mean there wasn't a lot of infrastructure for this show.
So it wasn't like they had to probably do a ton to this place to get it ready for a
different like.
No it was already like a very temp soundstage feeling.
Yeah.
I don't know that they even replaced to the screen the non high def screen that was still
running past 2009.
They might be able to run this show today right now.
They may just flick a switch on and the thing is fine.
Yeah maybe.
Yeah.
By the end of the day get it up.
They just need a little heads up.
They got to like put a fake microphone somewhere.
Just off some headphones.
Yeah yeah yeah.
Well there you know that's true.
We're discounting the special equipment involved in this.
Yeah that's true.
So what this show was you know the basic premise is that you're watching a new pilot
and the pilot is going to involve the use of binaural audio.
Binaural audio which we love on this show.
We discussed binaural audio.
If you don't know the sprays off hand long ago we did an episode about great moments
with Mr.
Lincoln.
They were obsessed with this technology for a while that is very realistic sound 360 degree
sound and certain effects that can really make you feel like you're there.
Certain effects.
Yeah.
Some of which are repeated somehow between a show about Abraham Lincoln and a show where
Drew Carey is a bumbling undercover cop.
Yes.
And repeated in like little booths kind of in this area.
Yeah when the show is done you can go do some of the very same things in weird little pods.
Yeah a lot of hair cutting.
Always hair cutting.
That's the one that's the most effective I think.
Yeah.
Honestly and of course if you remember our episode I think we gave Mr.
Sheridan a haircut
or no?
Sheridan.
Oh yes.
That's right.
That's what our binaural audio was.
That was our binaural presentation.
Just to get us up to date this building is now as of in the start of 2020 this theater
was renamed the Mickey Shorts Theater.
The seats were given a Mickey Mouse design and it currently shows the Vacation Fun Mickey
Mouse Short.
Okay I thought this was just one short.
Well with Runaway we're L.
A.
opening I think we're trying to tie it in together but I'm
sure yeah.
These theater every one of these theaters in Disney parks worldwide have died such sad
deaths.
Yeah.
It's such uncreative like it's just it's where all the synergy happens and the cheapness
happens and the laziness happens but Jason as you pointed out it's also where the naps
happen.
Oh yeah very dark in here very cold.
Perfect antidote for the Florida weather.
Yeah yeah yeah which that feels like a hot park too.
I mean they're all hot I guess but I don't know our last two is it I felt like it was
pretty scorching there.
Yeah I mean it's not as bad as Animal Kingdom.
No it's not the humidity bowl that is Animal Kingdom.
But it's still yeah pretty that open area it's still pretty open.
I wonder yeah what is the hottest is it is it it's got to be Animal Kingdom I think but.
I think so.
The big selling point now you asked is it just one short it's an original short for
this area.
Oh alright.
Alright now we're talking.
Power talker.
And it's a new it's a new style.
That is good yeah.
That is better.
Alright alright.
So yeah it's just it's just one of those I mean they would I guess it's honestly better
for these type of things to go away because it's it's easier to just plug something in
as opposed to like taking down a ride because you like have to do something with it or just
sits there.
Yeah.
It gets sadder and sadder.
I understand why these things happen.
I understand this is the most like on paper kind of attraction like we have this technology
and we want to do stuff do something with it.
The old thing the Chevy Chase Martin shirt things filling a little old.
Drew Carey is extremely popular right now.
So pop you forget how big the Drew Carey show was how his salary got up to seven hundred
fifty thousand an episode.
Oh my god.
How much did the friend wasn't that's like getting towards like friends.
Friends made a million.
By the end.
Yeah.
Which like I think the cultural impact of Drew Carey show is muddied a little bit because
I the other day I was like so where do you watch it.
Is it on.
Is it on Disney plus because it's like and the answer is it's nowhere.
It's one of those ghost shows really in all the all the platforms that have lined up nowhere
has the Drew Carey show.
That's odd.
Yeah.
And there's been no chatter of bringing it back.
No it's the rare.
That is interesting.
He's too busy and rich and fulfilled and happy.
He seems like a guy.
I feel like the reports are good about Drew Carey.
And he's I know he's a Parks fan.
Is that so.
I believe so.
I think he's a really nice guy.
The reputation is during the writer's strike.
I believe he said he paid for everyone's lunch.
If you showed your writers guild card at Bob's Big Boy.
Your lunch was covered by Drew Carey.
Wow.
Hey that's pretty good.
He was friendly with a friend.
He was a friendly with a guy we know a friend of ours.
If he interacted with anyone that we might know that he might have been very nice in
that setting.
But I don't know.
I don't know.
Don't sue me Sumner.
I don't know what I'm talking about.
I'm crazy today.
But so if he is a nice guy and a Parks fan and this all seems to be true.
How has he been done so dirty by the.
Like he's in two attractions and you'd have to think that both of these attractions are
in the running for one of them obviously is Superstar limo.
He's a robot in it and he's displaying maps to the stars home.
We've covered this and then there's this whole thing that is devoted to him.
I don't know how you guys feel about this attraction to me revisiting it.
I'm like I think both of the things Drew is in are like in the conversation for 10 worst
attractions.
Good question.
Yeah.
As a kid I went on it once and I was just terrified.
I thought something was going to hurt.
I thought something would hurt me during the show.
You weren't joking about that.
Not joking at all.
What made you think that?
Because we were in the dark and I knew like once in a while they'd have like a chair that
would poke you or something.
And like I just remember being stressed out the whole time.
Yeah.
That was not a joke.
So I was watching this rewatching it on YouTube and I had no memory of the actual contents
of the actual show.
You don't say.
Believe it or not.
And I think partly at least because I was scared.
Now you may also say the show is a bit unmemorable.
But maybe I would have thought I would have remembered some element of it.
But yeah I was just but anytime the lights got shut off I was kind of freaked out.
So and then yeah and then I was like I remember I'm trying to think like tough to be a bug
would stress me out because it would touch like it would hit me.
It would like touch me.
I was older at that point.
People don't like bugs.
Little bug pokes were weird.
I think I was a big enough nerd that I knew like well this is where the this is like the
audio annex like this is this is always audio.
Brother this is the audio.
Brother I OK.
I wouldn't say that as a child.
I'm saying that now.
But I had gone to enough attractions here that I'm like oh it's usually a headphone
thing.
It's usually an audio thing.
And I like little here's the little tricks of how they make movies.
I'm an audiophile but their mother it's a studio.
We're not likely to be poked in here.
Not poked or there would be no books brother but there will be audio treats for your ears.
I insisted to like exiting going in the booths like I've got to do that.
I got to do the booth.
You know yeah yeah I think I did them and then left them usually like I think I got
it.
This is longer than 50 seconds.
It's not the memory that like maybe Jason's you're proving this wrong but it's I feel
like did anyone leave Disney World like that once every three or four year trip that like
we would take as a family like and go and then there was the time when I thought my
hair was being cut like was that ever in the top 10 memories as far as experiences.
I have had conversations about the haircut.
Yeah I have had conversations.
But that's you.
Yeah no no.
I'm saying you ask anyone.
I am a person.
I know I'm asking.
That's what I'm asking.
I'm saying you can prove it.
I was just delighted by anything.
I just like all the Hollywood stuff at MGM studios.
Well you because you did you feel like you were part of the movie making apparatus.
Yes I did.
Yeah I would.
I bought it.
I loved it.
I was proud.
Proud member of the crew.
I liked a lot of it too.
I'm just saying this particular thing was scary to me and then also wasn't like something
We got to get back to Disney World so we can get our fake haircut.
Yeah like that's all I'm saying.
No I feel like people are like coming in and out of this thing like it's a bus depot.
Like you're just milling in.
What is it?
Watch it.
Don't laugh or smile or respond.
What was that?
Oh so that wasn't the tower thing?
No that's over there.
Okay let's get to that.
We made a mistake.
That's how I feel like the Florida audience must have regarded this.
It's going to be interesting because people might be furious at us and I don't really
have a sense of it because people don't talk about it.
People aren't often talking about Sounds Dangerous so it'll be interesting to see if like half
the listeners are like go to hell Carlson.
What is this shit?
I loved it.
Again we cannot understand this is a park that has always had a limited number of attractions
so like when everything's 45 to an hour plus wait a place you can walk in and sit down
and it's air conditioned and cold sure and maybe there's a little show and you want to
be entertained but it's air conditioned and cold and you can sit.
I think that's probably a big positive memory for people.
I would put air conditioning in Florida in my top 20 of the nice things about it and
that's all the air conditioning.
You know Carousel of Progress air conditioning is one but I would lump it all in.
I don't think we could do an air conditioning final four for Florida because so much of
it is similar.
It's all equal.
It's existing.
I loved my pop century like all hard surfaces room just blasting AC all day even though
we weren't there so we could walk in and feel like we were stepping into a refrigerator.
That's right.
God bless it.
It was my favorite thing.
It's the most utilitarian hotel room I've ever stayed in.
Yeah extremely.
Like most amount of shelves and hooks.
But all hard surfaces.
It's a lot of hard surfaces.
It's all so much cold particles bouncing off each other.
I love it.
I don't want any soft couches or anything comforting a cloth painting that isn't going
to do that AC bouncing for me.
Hard.
All hard.
I want like a Lego room.
I'm not sure how I feel about all this fake wood fake vinyl flooring they put into the
hotels.
Oh I don't know anything.
I know it's more sanitary.
It's more sad.
A lot of hotel design now.
It's like fake hard wood because it's easier to clean than carpet.
But sometimes I'm like I kind of like carpet.
But well but yeah.
Hotel carpet is disgusting.
Yeah you run out.
It's a real.
I get what you're saying.
I'm a carpet fan all day but hotel carpet if we really analyze it it's gross.
Yeah.
It's got to be gross.
I was parroting my parents opinion for a long time.
Like but don't you like a carpet isn't it kind of you know it's kind of nice and comforting
don't you think.
And I said that to somebody once who was like no disgusting wrong.
There is a reason we've all switched.
Yeah sure.
Because I do like you know I don't know.
We are well kept up carpet maybe.
Sure.
But I realized how I sounded out loud in that I was I was carpet shamed.
You were carpet shamed but you were also carpet parroting as well you think.
Yeah yeah yeah.
It was a stolen opinion.
It was like clearly something I just borrowed from.
Uh huh.
Yeah because it's not you know it's nice.
It's what we grew up with.
Yeah.
Comforts are home.
Uh huh.
It's also really easy to let it go for a while.
Like it can be there years after it should have been changed.
And then when you have to change it it's the biggest pain in the ass in the world.
This isn't an episode about carpets but let me real quick sometimes you get the hotel
carpets or even carpets in general that it's like barely carpet.
If we're doing carpet let's do carpet where it's like cushy and it feels good and especially
if you got your bare feet on it it's like oh that's nice.
But like often times it's just like that flat nothing carpet.
Yeah.
That's like coarse and like what's the point.
Yeah like an uncomfortable rug.
Right and like that might not be there.
It may have been stepped on so many times.
That's possible but that's obviously then you need to replace it and if we're going
to do that then just put the hardwood in at that point.
Yeah.
I grew up in a house that I guess my parents were big carpet people.
This is the carpet parroting that I grew up in a house with bright green carpet everywhere
because my dad wanted it to be like a putting green.
That's very fun.
So I lived in like a mini golf course basically until like two years ago they changed it.
It was very cool.
Really did he like putt inside the house a lot.
Yeah.
Yep.
Wow.
Like an 80s executive.
That's like an imagineered house that you had.
A little bit.
Yeah.
I mean it was a little so it wasn't like pure it wasn't like lime green.
It wasn't a green that made you nauseous.
But yeah definitely was meant to evoke golf course.
Oh wow.
That's interesting.
Wait I want to do a survey real quick.
We'll get back to the attraction real quick.
Did you guys ever have a carpeted bathroom in your childhood homes?
No.
Because that was a design style that we had on and off.
I can't believe that exists anywhere.
We were looking at a place to we were thinking about a place that had that and we were like
well that's a strike one.
And it was like big like that was it was like huge it was like like big long dog hair.
That was hugely popular hugely popular in the suburbs for a while.
It is very strange.
It might be yeah maybe the cold winters like but the minute a tub overflows or a toilet
you're like fucked you immediately like oh great now I have to pee.
Ricochet pee goes everywhere.
Every time you step out of the shower you've got that like well that'll be wet overnight.
Yeah that's madness.
Yeah but our parents loved carpeting and I grew up also loving carpeting.
Yeah yeah.
No it made me angry to see in person several years ago when I did yeah yeah.
Like no scarring.
That's interesting.
That's just it should be ashamed those people who put it in.
Well you're right it's not about carpeting though we're happy to share our carpeting
thoughts if you wish to hear more.
We're talking about we're talking about Sounds Dangerous which is a show that you step into
and then immediately are told welcome to undercover live.
Okay so what is it then?
Undercover live.
The show has two names so I don't even I don't remember what happens before they press play
on the thing but I guess they convey you come in and you put on your headphones as we said
that's an important step.
Put on your headphones and you are told that this is a new pilot setting and then a title
comes up that says undercover live in the cheapest font the most iMovie that like the
stock effect where like a light is blasting through and the light moves from the left
to the right.
It is such iMovie template like shockingly poor font.
This oh wait and in an attraction that already has this is finally my opportunity to really
address something I've talked about before and I truly despise like where cool 90s aesthetics
started disappearing started going away and gave way to the ABC yellow the worst.
We'll post this somewhere this is what I was referencing earlier.
Drew Carey is an undercover cop sounds dangerous and it's in that gross yellow horrible black
on yellow font that ABC did all their advertising with where you know that was boiled down to
like we like TV.
TV's been going a while and there haven't been any world wars since.
Guess TV must be good.
These like snotty kind of like almost like rip off of adult swim title card just the
worst.
This might have come first though.
The I think that I think they were using this scheme the scheme the black on yellow scheme
did not come from this attraction.
Oh no no but the adult swim title cards I think came after.
Oh maybe this yeah when did they.
Adult swim around 2000 I think.
Maybe yeah yeah yeah.
But I started is it is it typewriter font too is it courier like this kind of font.
Yeah it is not.
It's like a bad like asymmetrical like if you look at the edges of it it's all like
bulbous and undulating and like it's not all even but not in a good way not in like
the way it feels handwritten.
It just feels like poorly supervised.
Right I can't I don't know exactly what bothers me.
I think that's it.
They can't decide if it's typewriter or handwritten and just the black on yellow does not work.
Maybe a bumblebee might like it but not me.
I'll tell you that much bumblebees we factor into this attraction.
Awful poster.
These fonts are bad.
Oh and oh my god on the marquee of this where Drew Carey's smiling real big at you.
Look what we got over here.
Comic Sans bright yellow comic sans written over like creases on a building which is what
turquoise.
Yellow on turquoise and it's a font that doesn't appear anywhere else.
Just like this is where I you know I'm an aesthetics person I'm a fonts person some
of the worst ever.
Some of this is not the most sought out because Drew Carey's outfit makes him look like a
like security guard or like a California highway.
He's like the Carl Winslow.
Yeah he does not look like a detective usually is portrayed in media.
Well in an undercover cop would not be wearing this jacket or a band.
This is not Serpico.
Yeah there's a lot aesthetically there's like there's 90s Disney we've talked about
this on the show Disney World like when you see some of the signs still when you're driving
into places that's like that teal and purple and roads.
Just the street signs.
Yeah.
Street signs are great and like so much of Blizzard Beach you go feels just like they
haven't changed a thing since the 90s.
That stuff is great.
But then there's this like other I don't know what you would call it.
I don't know if we named it on the show before.
There's this really unpleasant aesthetic and it's like maybe the most this era is the most
unpleasant aesthetically.
Nothing remain nothing's kept up that looks like this.
Yeah it's all been torn down rightfully so.
It's trying to have an edge but there's no purpose.
There's no vision.
Well sure that's true.
Trying to be current and modern and then they I feel like gave up at a certain point
of that.
Yeah and it's like it's all part of it's still part of Superstar limo I feel like aesthetically
in a way.
I think City Walk was still kind of using this vibe the kind of thing where it's like
there's a bunch of like film burnouts and things are shifting in and out of focus.
Yeah.
As titles that you can't fully see go by and it'll be all lowercase.
Like that was edgy somehow to people.
We didn't put any capital letters in.
We broke a rule.
What's how chill we are.
No need to use a capital letter.
Who's shouting not us.
I anything like that.
I feel like my high school yearbook had like a here's what pop culture was at the time
and it was like that.
There was a thing called Channel One News.
Did you guys get Channel One News.
I vaguely was this supposed to be like a hip news network for teens.
Yeah they aired it in high schools and it was a deal with a bunch of schools to like
we'll give you TVs if you play our news show and also we've made ad deals so there will
be Eminem ads in your classroom.
It was a way to get commercials into classrooms which my high school and middle school did.
It's the most egregious looking back.
I have so many memories of like wait those free book covers they would give us for textbooks.
I was like that was an ad for Chex Mix or like the planners.
It's like hey everyone here's a here's a free planner and you can write what activities
you have today or what homework assignments you have today.
I was like wait there sure was a lot of ads in that for like yes Snickers and new TV shows.
Like it was practically a copy of Entertainment Weekly.
It's an ad for two guys a girl and a pizza place on this planner.
Yeah I voting for we I do remember us all doing the Pepsi challenge and then also voting
for the new color of Eminem which I was very excited when Blue won.
Is that true?
Oh yeah I was.
I voted for Blue.
You were cheering for Blue.
Yeah I was voting for Blue.
I guess yeah you just really love Blue.
I do love Blue.
You're my boy.
I like how this is all a prequel.
Yeah right.
Now to a bit.
It's a prequel.
But made after the original.
But like yeah Blue M&Ms replaced Brown M&Ms I think.
And you were part of that.
I was part of it.
You raised your voice.
We handed out branded branded ballots.
I think they used it to show us how voting worked.
I heard you canvassed door to door for Blue during that election.
I rat fucked Purple.
You and Lee Atwater or Carl Roe who was Lee Atwater still alive at that point?
Parked a garbage truck in front of the ballot drop off so people wouldn't know where it
was.
You push pulled Brown M&M.
Carl Roe got all his practice on this high school M&M campaign.
And the Daley family.
You know you were from Chicago area.
I am from yeah.
I know them.
Did some dirty tricks.
Jason was the Lee Atwater or Carl Roe of the M&M pick the next color campaign.
Dumped a bunch of fuchsia's in a river.
Eight year old me talking with Roy Cohn and a young Roger Stone.
Oh man you got to get back in the game Jason.
There's got to be another candy election coming soon.
Oh yeah.
No mail in ballots.
If you care about it go in in person.
You and Mike Lindell can team up.
I'm still mad they brought Crispy M&Ms back but they couldn't make the bag blue anymore
because pretzel M&Ms were blue and now it's green.
That really throws me.
I love pretzel M&Ms.
Oh I love Crispy M&Ms.
Those are good too.
No I mean they're good.
And come back.
Yeah right now.
All right.
How quickly would Scott be in the hospital if he ate like you and I did.
Too much of a shift.
Too much of a shock to the system.
Yeah it's a good question.
We should switch diets for a week.
Well I do always whenever this comes up when you talk about like I don't know Scott why
don't you eat sugar cereal.
Why don't you eat like you know things encrusted with free pebbles for every meal.
But then also in every episode you're talking about how you're dying.
Like every time you go to a theme park it's always like I couldn't walk anymore and my
stomach was giving out.
We don't take care of ourselves we injure ourselves.
I said I just wasn't in theme park shape again.
I by the way I'd like to officially announce I am back in theme park shape.
Yeah I'm getting there.
Yeah I was just saying that first time.
You were vanquished by sunscreen so like.
Yeah yeah but I'm just saying the first couple times I was like oof.
Not just recently though I feel like if you did a super cut of stomach issues of like
clutching your side and morning pains and the health concerns on this show are amazing.
How many junk food based accounts do you follow on Instagram that track new junk food offerings.
Hmm that could be a zero.
I follow a handful.
Any like ones that track new fast food offerings.
I can't say I do.
Jason can you share those with me because I'm interested.
I mean some of them you've sent me.
But we'll cross check our list.
I just want to make sure yeah.
Look it's more fun what you're doing.
I'm just saying note the connection between the health complaints and the complaints about
what I don't eat.
I see what you're saying.
Yeah I have to remember I've forgotten most of any ailments theme park related ailments.
There's been a couple of food incidents.
Incidences.
Is that a word.
Wouldn't be.
Incidents would be the incidences.
Okay well whatever.
Yeah there's been a few of those but we'll if somebody would be a deer and go back and
cut those together so I can see.
Help the host run a physical on themselves.
I need to see exactly how many how many times.
But I would like to declare I'm back in theme park shape and I continue to beat Zach Reno
at tennis.
My tennis skills are back as well.
Jason wearing blue shirts is the new thing.
Mike constantly saying he plays tennis.
Mike saying tennis in almost every episode is the new thing.
These are these are your post pandemic changes.
I hope you enjoy them.
My Achilles tendon is a bit sore.
But that's not a theme park shape issue.
Not a theme park shape issue a tennis issue.
Got it.
Okay sounds dangerous with Drew Carey.
So they they show you on this poster in these horrible fonts the kind of things you're going
to be dealing with.
This is no regular undercover cop.
He's wearing prescription glasses.
Well that's just a regular thing.
That's not magical.
He's got a hidden microphone and it's in his ear and that's where the binaural audio is
coming from.
He's got a spy camera.
It's in his little it's in the top of his jacket.
He's got a secret decoder ring which I cannot recall an instance of this coming up and sounds
dangerous.
It's not used.
No no no.
I didn't realize that until right now.
Does not come into play.
Don't worry about it.
It's like an appendix.
It's not so it doesn't serve any function.
Yeah.
So that's what the show is.
You meet Sharon Brooks the director of undercover live.
We'd also love to see some Sharon Brooks costumes at future live shows.
Sharon Brooks and she lets you know that they're going to be following Detective Aran.
So it's a pilot but it's live.
It's the rare pilot that is live and for no audience.
Right.
And she's assures us that the camera that I feel like this a real 1999 relic.
The camera is high res.
This is pretty weird.
I feel like a lot of stuff was advertised as high res.
Pre high def.
You know which everything we have now is so much higher res than anything that was ever
called high res.
So we have what this is a show where you watch things shot on a camera that is so much worse
than your phone today.
Yes.
It makes it a rough watch now.
Also a super sensitive microphone they say.
So we're justifying that we're going to get this little audio demonstration and then we
meet Detective Charlie Foster who right away.
So the reality of it is you're watching a live pilot that only you are seeing.
You're watching it in a room in a theme park that is equipped with headphones.
There is a detective that you're going to follow around with a super sensitive microphone
and where is the detective?
He is in a snow globe factory.
Yes.
And you're tossed right into this because they cut to the feet of the camera and it's
only static.
Oh my God.
The high res camera is not showing anything yet.
Oh that's because old goofball Charlie Foster is messing around and futson with the snow
globe.
That's the reality.
It's a it's a detective in a snow globe factory.
You know of course.
I just at this point already just where are we.
What is this.
Yeah.
What is the show.
It's like that.
They canceled the show because you know it's I never saw that that live version of cops
was called live PD.
This is almost unbelievable.
Yeah.
This is like this is like an early version of it I guess where you just all of a sudden
thrust into the action.
You're just right there.
Yeah.
You can watch Detective Foster plant a drop gun on a suspect.
While he's wearing a t shirt that says yes I am an undercover cop.
So blue lives matter grumpy shirt.
Jason cannot wear a blue lives matter shirt.
Oh come on.
Let's.
Oh man.
Prequel.
Yeah really.
OK.
So this is it's a we're undercover at a place where snow globes are being used to smuggle
something that much of the mystery has been cracked.
Snow globe.
Right.
This is an operation.
Somehow crimes are involved with snow globes.
And he's trying to find a guy named Lefty Moreno.
He's trying to find a villain from 1928.
Yeah.
Weird things already.
Dick Tracy's all too many.
There is.
This is like this is a no straight men scenario.
Every detail is weird.
There's never a reality planted in this.
So he gets caught right away.
This undercover cop probably because he's in a in a place he's not supposed to be making
no effort to disguise himself or hide.
So he very quickly is caught and he panics.
What do I do.
He hides his undercover camera in his mouth.
And then we get the point of view of Drew Carey's mouth.
So if you want to see what the back of his teeth might look like, it's still kind of
dark.
You get to see that.
It's like the Walter Mathau Dennis the Menace shot when he shoots Dennis shoots.
You know, does they do what they do?
A mouth POV?
Well, they built a big fake mouth and Dennis like shoot something with a slingshot into
Walter.
Walter Mathau's mouth.
Wow.
It's a famous shot.
Was that Dennis the Menace superior piece or was it like 1992?
Was the movie set in 1990?
Sort of in like every town America whenever.
Yeah.
Now he didn't time travel like the Brady Bunch.
Oh, right.
Yeah.
Wasn't a relic.
So the undercover mission has not gone well already.
He has already taken the high tech gear and gotten it wet in his mouth.
So it starts to short out.
That is two minutes into this attraction, which has been built to you as it's the Drew
Carey thing.
There is his face.
You see his face.
Get ready to see his face.
And then the attraction continues for 10 more minutes.
That is all audio where you do not see Drew Carey's face.
So good for him for getting it.
Like he got off real easy in terms of the shoot of this thing.
Yes, that's true.
I forgot my memory of it.
I don't I was saying I don't remember much of it, but if you had told me, oh, do you
ever see anybody?
I would have said no.
I've never seen any characters.
So like my memory, like I don't it's the whole thing was that way.
But obviously it's good because it quickly went to black.
Yes, that's true.
It pops out to sort of establish where you are.
Yeah, he's driving and you see a little of that.
But it definitely feels like they shot all the footage in one day.
Yeah, one day shoot one day in the audio booth.
Yeah, yeah, extremely.
So then you're off on this little adventure with him and he's snooping around this office
where he's not supposed to be.
And you hear a stapler, which you hear really loud.
I guess he puts it up to his own ear to make sure that it is a stapler.
Yes, to demonstrate this technology, he does really strange things
just so we can get a little bit of a taste of some object.
It didn't occur to me.
It's all right now.
Yeah.
If we're hearing it this well, that means he's sticking his ear up so close to his ear.
I mean, even your silliest detective.
Who would?
Maybe they have justified that he is a little hard of hearing
and he has to.
This is the only way.
But even then, why do you need to confirm?
Maybe if you were checking, are there any staples in the stapler?
But besides that, yeah, don't put your ear close to it.
Unless he's doing like a funny gag or he's using it as a phone.
Yeah.
But he's not doing that either.
I don't believe what he's making.
Inspector Clouseau look like Hercule Poirot.
Huh?
Right.
Because he's so silly that Inspector Clouseau looks very competent.
Yeah.
Detective.
Oh, right.
Yes.
Yes, you're right.
That should have been the poster.
This guy makes.
That brings to mind when you bring up a Clouseau,
I think that is a weakness of this attraction to me, is that
you want your bumbling detective to be this master of physical comedy
and so but to also have this kind of
gravitas.
Yeah, that's the word.
Yes.
Yeah.
It has to seem like a professional self, so that when the bumbling occurs,
you are kind of surprised and the surprise causes Leslie Nielsen.
You want him to be Leslie Nielsen.
You want him to be the Don Adams from Get Smart.
Yeah, that's the thing.
He's not playing it straight enough and he's not playing it bumbling.
And it's kind of like in between.
And then you don't accomplish either.
Yeah.
And which I look, I think Drew Carey is doing what Drew Carey does.
And he's great at what he's great at, which is being pretty much
like being himself and being an affable guy.
And if you watch him on The Price is Right, it's say, oh, I got the price.
Right.
You watch him on the show.
Hey, maybe what are you doing?
He's like he sort of has his one speed.
It's great.
It's a great speed.
But he would not call him a fine actor.
This is not a problem with Mr.
Drew Carey.
This is a problem.
No, it's a miscast, I believe.
And the whole thing is or just miss written wrong.
Yeah.
A different idea going.
There's really like no one like in the Drew Carey show, he had
Ryan Stiles to play off of and he had Mimi, which an actor,
Kathy Kinney and she was she was huge.
Like her and Drew Carey to get like they were the like big part of that show.
Playing surrounded him with you.
This is an all Drew Carey thing that relies on.
Well, it's also like a physical comedy thing where you only hear the physical
comedy.
It's this is a strange breed.
You almost have to give him credit for trying like a truly new type of experience.
Yeah, it's a whole new type of experience that's been established.
Yeah.
All new type.
So you got to get down to Orlando to see what choice do you have?
And this new experience does sound dangerous.
They're not going to know what's going to happen.
It's risky.
As Sharon Brooks herself, the director tells you
like she knew was going to go awry, of course.
And then there's this sort of bad, self-aware joke of the things that are in the
this.
I hate this.
They're trying to be meta here and they're saying what's in the
office and like, and in a jar with a bunch of killer bees.
And this is like because we know that bees are one of the things that they can do
well with the binaural audio.
So they're trying to be jokey and saying like this.
It's a random thing.
Why would there be a bunch of bees in this snow globe office?
But again, listen to me, this is too much.
There's too many silly components.
Too many.
And he goes from one location to another.
Easily could have walked by a beehive that got loose, you know, or something.
That's right.
Yes.
Got his head stuck in there.
He like goes to the wrong address and then that walks and busts, thinks he's busting
some perps and then that turns out to be a bee farm.
Sure, yeah.
Yeah.
Did Lincoln have bees?
Lincoln didn't have bees.
Four score is seven years ago.
Oh, fuck.
There's a bee.
Oh, no.
There's a bunch of bees.
Oh, oh, gee.
Get them off me.
If I can kill the queen, they'll all bow to me.
He wanted he was jealous of the power of a queen.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's one thing I'm not president of.
I want to be president of the bees.
The White House.
But what about the yellow hive?
Yeah, they needed to put bees in there.
I mean, still chance they can.
They can put bees on great moments with Mr.
Lincoln.
Yeah, I want more gimmicks going in there.
All with bees.
Just add that to the sign.
I mean, if I knew that that animatronic was, you know,
nimble enough to swat a bunch of bees away.
Oh, man.
I know it can like slightly gesture and stay a speech, but I want to see
the attack.
Lion attack.
Cougar attack.
I haven't watched the Mario Kart ride yet, but you do have like
a are goggles or glasses on.
Correct.
So maybe you can do an A.
B.
R.
attack during great moments with Mr.
Lincoln.
Oh, no, it's a bee.
Oh, Mario's coming.
Oh, Mario's in there.
Oh, he buzzes.
Yeah, he just.
Oh, so Mario's on the Lincoln ride, too.
Now.
Watch out the bees.
They're after me.
And then Mario shows up and.
Yeah.
No.
OK.
Now I'm going to be the president in 1865.
Yeah.
Look, A.
R.
is the future.
And the more Wario and Mario we can get, I'm in favor of it.
Yeah.
But they didn't have that.
They had a bunch.
You can hear a bunch of bees.
We then we then we got a new guy we're looking for him.
Johnny Marsconi.
There's a bunch of flames that shoot by.
It does sound good.
They can do the wish of the flame very well.
But why?
How does this detective story lend itself to it?
You know, or like a there's an old telephone.
There's an old like a receiver telephone in this office.
They can do that.
But like, I don't know, why did the Imagineers think that their ability
to have an old clangy telephone or flame whooshing was enough
that they had to try several attractions based on this?
And Binaural Audio was already a part of Alien Encounter.
Yes.
Which it makes sense to be a scary thing.
So you feel the intimacy of a scary creature right next to you.
But then why do you step it down to a failed pilot presentation?
Yeah, I don't just everyone.
I want to know who was so excited about this technology.
It does make the most sense in Alien Encounter.
But that was did you have headphones on an alien counter?
No, you know, the speakers were just right behind you.
And that's such a that's such a more seamless way to use the technology.
Yeah, I'm guessing they that the thing here that before that was
pretty low rated.
And they're like, all right, here's what you have to work with.
You can get Drew Carey for a day and you have twenty thousand dollars.
Make a new attraction.
I think, yes, we have a deal with a headphone company.
Right.
Yeah, the headphones can stay.
We pulled the trigger and bought them.
We stopped renting them.
Yeah, because because I I get how you would be excited for this tech
that for binaural audio, binaural audio to be
used in attractions to make it cool, like slightly better,
more dimension, sound dimensioners be scared.
But like for it to be the thing where you put a headphone on headphones on just for it.
It's like that feels like it.
Yes, it belongs in interventions for you to put it on for five minutes
and then take it off and go, OK, well, this could have been like a canary
in the coal mine of like what was coming where movie theaters, theme parks,
everyone is competing with the very good technology you already have at home.
They either have to keep a pace or surpass it.
Yes.
We all of a sudden it was like you can have surround sound at home.
Yeah.
And I remember we had some like Sam's Club version of it
with like two little speakers like that we put behind.
I'm remembering this right now.
Two little speakers we put like on the sides of the couch.
And it was like, wow, we have surround sound now.
And it was like it was cool.
I don't think it was the top of the line equipment.
But yes, that suddenly became something you could get in your house
where it would be like the speakers are different.
Still not really a priority to me that like I need if there's a scene in a movie
and I'm watching it at home and a bunch of wind which is by me.
I need to feel like I'm in the I'm in the windstorm.
Right.
No, I don't.
I if I was like a multimillionaire and I was building home theater, sure.
But all I need is like a decent amount of bass and a soundbar.
And I'm right right now.
I don't need I need something crazy.
Mm hmm.
I don't even look, you know, I have a baby.
So what I need is to keep it quiet.
So I I do not have a soundbar.
You know, headphones probably won't tell you.
No, not that not that bad.
OK, yeah.
That is a fun feature on Roku is where if you get the Roku app
or you get the one with the remote, you can listen to headphones.
Listen to your TV with headphones either through your phone or through a remote.
Yeah.
So that's good.
Do all that and don't instead of the binaural.
Yeah.
Don't fall for these expensive binaural machines that you're always seeing.
You go to your sharper image and you see binaural headphones.
You make you joke.
But like eight years ago, they were trying to cram down our throats.
3D television like, yeah, right.
Get out of here.
That was extinct as it hit the shelves.
I still don't really know what it was like or what it did or might have been good.
Maybe.
But the like shit.
What about the curve television?
The curve is kind of growing on me.
But like you got to make sure the curve was a curve was gone.
Is the curve going?
Well, I don't know.
There's some very wide ones now.
Oh, you're a curve television.
Hard to tell.
Hmm.
Oh, that's another running joke.
But I can see.
New for 2021.
Jason loves curved TVs.
Well, no, you see like in the Jurassic World queue now, they have those really wide TVs
and like desktop monitors you can buy for your computer are like super wide now.
Interesting.
Wow.
I got I thought those I thought that fad was gone, but I'm seeing.
Yeah, that it's not.
Feels to me like if I wish that Disney had suckered
Jeffrey Katzenberg into thinking that things made just for binaural audio
or there's going to be a whole platform that is only what audiences want now.
It's all consuming audio.
It's what millennials want.
They're sick of just staring at TV and the sounds over there.
Where is it?
I can barely hear it.
I want it right here.
And I want to watch little plays that happen that are mostly sound only.
Millennials want two minutes of video and then the video to short out
and then 10 minutes of pure audio happens.
And it's little scenes where somebody's in a swarm of bees or caught in a tornado
or what else works for this?
They're in a, you know, like they fall down in a kitchen
and they hit a knife drawer and all the knives go shing past them.
This is what they're getting attacked by ninja stars.
I think this Katzenberg raises two billion dollars for
binary.
The man.
Look, he's looking for his next venture, I assume.
So so I could be I could go pitch binary.
I think you could probably get him to do binary.
And as long as he never Googles my name and Quibi.
That's right.
Yeah.
He's things that I said.
Right.
I could do some great business with him.
Yeah.
And it's funny because you're now all in on like all the great shows
are now on the Roku channel for free.
Yeah.
They save them.
No, my problem was the medium.
I didn't like watching on my phone.
The shows obviously are all fantastic.
And now that they're on Roku, I'm loving the Roku originals.
I am binging them like crazy.
Well, what else happens in this thing?
There's like, I don't know, he goes.
So he goes and gets a haircut.
We're getting back at haircut,
you know, and the haircut guy says you got to drive somewhere else.
He ends up at the circus, which is a reason then to have
you go to the circus because they're good at making the sound of a knife
whippen by your right ear so that he gets caught in a knife throwing thing.
And then I'm then I die inside.
Don't forget the guy who's in the haircut who owns a barbershop now
had recently gotten out of jail and was known as the slasher.
Oh, yes.
The very grim.
I did forget that.
Why is that important?
Well, because to make a danger supposed to be a little like a gag
that then you're getting a and he goes straight razor, the sharpest one.
You know, he might Sweeney Todd.
Yeah.
I see.
And then the guy in the circus is is he the great was he is Rinaldi.
Rinaldi.
We're going to find Johnny Marsconi and then they got to find Rinaldi
and lefty Moreno.
Yeah.
These are are these all characters in the same family as superstar
limo Swifty LaRue.
Oh, yeah.
They feel in the same.
They do.
Lefty Moreno.
Absolutely.
Yes.
I wonder if anybody could point us to or knows like
did one imagineer come up with all these names or is this just the style of the time
for like made up theme park character?
Hmm.
I don't know.
Yeah.
You got lefty got Swifty.
You got thrifty.
You got hefty.
There's a whole bunch of the whole family of them.
We didn't get to see.
Mm hmm.
So, yeah, is there that's they were trying to do their version of C
with like Subdick Tracy level characters and it just didn't take off
with all light with.
Yeah.
The 20s to 40s shysters.
Right.
Exactly.
And this is a less popular
Ronald Moore will not be turning this into anything.
Sadly, no.
Yeah.
So I am interested.
I want to know, like, yeah, we're who loved the 1920s.
Like gangster names.
Yeah.
Was that imagine Andrew Carey?
Clearly, like that's what sure combines both of these attractions and poor
artwork, logos and fonts.
Right.
It's a good question.
What a time.
I was trying.
This is a little bit of a side note of like
of all the sort of appearances of TV sitcom people from the 90s
and movies to as well, like Martin Short.
Yeah.
Is the most successful appearance?
And I guess I counted, I guess it opened in 2001,
but that still feels like the 90s to me is the Patrick Warburton's.
That's never going away.
I think pretty right.
Beloved Patrick.
Yeah.
But that's sort of in the same genre of like, oh, on a sitcom.
People like him a lot.
Mm hmm.
Yeah.
But that's sort of like of the moment guy.
Right.
But that's going to last for I mean, that's still a couple of years from
science away after Seinfeld's over, but still like he also was never
like an overexposed person, really.
He's just like trustworthy character actor.
I love him when you see him.
So like nobody got sick of him.
And he doesn't feel like a dated person because he's still in stuff.
So that's kind of a per feels like a good like timeless.
Right.
But that's the only one that's that's like that's the only one in these
like this genre, I feel like, well, like is like going to last forever.
He also it's also good that he's not like constantly in the ride.
He's not telling you that.
Yeah, watch out for those skiers.
Yeah, it really dates rides.
When you have like a style of or like whatever, like, yeah,
Ellen commenting or smell that grass big guy
and he flies in, he's on some weird flying contraption.
All right.
Just a few more places to go.
Follow me.
Check it out.
Soren would have gotten torn up, torn down at this point.
If like Patrick Warburton had shown up on a hang glider,
he's in there making hanging Chad jokes.
Yeah.
For like 19 years.
I guess what you call me hanging Chad.
My name is Chad, by the way.
Full context.
He's like dressed like culturally insensitively when he goes to different
we go to different places like how we got to get rid of this attraction.
You got to at least get a new film.
That is yes, that is for the best.
It's not an attraction.
You don't you're not like helping him.
Yeah, that's a good point.
You're not traveling all over California to help him find his wallet or something.
You don't know much about the character, not overexposed.
As much as I would like to know about what is he even?
Is he a pilot?
Yeah, that's a good question.
Does he just own the building?
I think he's a pilot.
Yeah, he's got a pilot gear on.
But also like Soren even kind of tread at the line,
because like you're on a hang glider, but there's a pilot here
and there's a lot of history of aviation stuff here.
So it's yeah.
Are you want to?
Yeah, well, you're learning about planes, but you're on a hang glider.
Yeah, yeah, that's a good point.
And now you're in the Grizzly Peak airfield.
And we've picked it all apart too much.
Yeah, man.
I get soren stinks.
Yeah, concept of flying.
Don't worry about it.
Yeah, I didn't want to.
I didn't want to turn on in a tread.
This thing made me turn on another ride that I like.
Well, OK, so mystery is solved.
And OK, can any of us confidently say
Rinaldi was is Rinaldi also Johnny Marsconi
or is he just in business with him?
Can we explain the mystery coherently?
That's a good question.
The answer is no.
No, I don't know.
Anyway, something happens.
Rinaldi, he was smuggling diamonds in the snow globes.
You're right.
Yes, that's correct.
It was a diamond operation.
Why did we end up at the circus?
I truly don't.
I just watched it and I still don't know.
I didn't retain it any better than I did back then,
even though I was supposed to.
I was like, I'm on the clock.
Right.
This is work.
I'm supposed to study this thing.
I'm a work.
Yeah, you're a work.
And then the clown pops a big thing right behind you.
Gary startles him, pops a big thing.
Startles him and it makes him break the camera.
Breaks the camera and then off camera,
he just beats the shit out of that goddamn clown.
You don't make me look like a fool.
Well, Scott can get behind that.
Love it.
Yeah.
That's why I don't like this attraction more.
I didn't get to see him.
You wanted more of the LA confidential kind of darkness.
You wanted to
And then like, tell me where your clown brothers are.
I want to find each and every one of them.
Do you want to scare me?
You wanted a bad lieutenant kind of clown.
You wanted to hear Drew Carey like get out some pliers
and like you want to hear the clown's teeth being pulled out of its gums.
Now that's binaural audio.
Yeah, the shield.
Disney's the shield.
Let's see you laugh.
Let's see you laugh now after this.
There we go.
Yeah, that's binaural I can get.
Yes.
Finally.
I want Detective Foster to do a nationwide clown hunt.
Taking out all my clown enemies.
Yeah, his partner, Harvey Keitel.
Yes, we bring a
We bring like a
Now there's a there's a crime guy with gravitas.
That fixes the whole thing.
OK, well, we just plus it up right there.
Yeah.
More more blood should have been super violent.
Oh, man.
A good fellow's Lufthansa Heiss attraction.
Now that would have been
Why haven't any of Martin Scorsese's rides been adapted for a theme park?
Taxi Driver Jr.?
Sure.
I think they're all open.
It's all possible.
Yeah.
Well, that sounds dangerous, I guess.
And then you file out and then the the director,
whose name is Sharon Brooks, says,
join us next time on another when it'll be another mission on undercover.
And like, what next time?
Do you mean this was a lie?
This was a limited audience pilot.
It's all that might not get picked up, especially after these mishaps.
If this is what happens just in the first episode,
I don't think you can trust the crew of this show.
No, I wouldn't be able to.
And but then the thing they greenlit instead was Emily's reasons why not.
Which aired one episode.
They did have their gram dirty, too.
She deserves more.
Tough run for ABC.
Well, strange, strange attraction, eh?
Yeah.
How did this run?
This ran from 99 to 2012.
It's straddled the prices, right?
He's been hosting priser rides since 2007.
So you like, you know him primarily for that and then go see this thing
where he's a detective messing around with knife throwers.
Very confused.
Yeah, all this stuff.
It's so funny.
This has happened so many times now on the show where we go,
this was still there when?
Yeah, there's there's high definition footage of what?
Yeah.
I would be like, oh, well, that closed in 2002.
Right.
And you're like, no, no, no.
Decade, another decade.
Big Drew Carey face like when prime real estate in this theme park.
Yeah.
So so long.
That's a good question.
Yeah, I.
But people remember, like when it's when it's a person
whose name is in the title of the sitcom and they're like in other stuff,
they're in theme parks like look at it, look at the calendar
for any big casino and see what comedians are playing.
And you're like, oh, I didn't know they tour like it's like,
I forgot about them.
But it's like, yeah, you know,
they stick around.
They do stick around in the popular consciousness in one way or another.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
So you're you're saying that as a sort of a defense for people
who have more fond memories after I was saying I was trashing it
and saying, no, I think people regular theme park guests,
probably whether they know it or they're like, oh, yeah, Drew Carey, famous guy.
You would have a ride, you know, even if his show had been on
for like six years or whatever.
Yeah.
So that might be why they kept her like the name.
That's my deal with him.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's true.
But man, when Disney goes, stuff goes seasonal, it's like, oh,
you're just looking for that.
You're just waiting for financial quarter to come around
where you can afford to tear this down.
Yeah.
Let alone a financial quarter where you plug in something new.
We just need to develop like a good new ice cream
that will eat up the same amount of people as this attraction.
And we can easily let this go.
Yeah.
If Disney wishables do well at the gift shop,
like a new kind of stuff.
Yes.
Yeah.
It was well.
It's like, oh, well, OK.
Yeah, good.
We got some.
Yeah, we can bring back this thing.
The wishables are the small ones.
Those are they're not the ones that I'm very excited about,
where you can put like Mickey and like a polo shirt and like some blue jeans.
I forget that might be a variety.
Yeah, they're Duffy in up like stuffed animals or something.
Yeah, you can dress them in normal clothes.
Here's the one where the characters don't have bodies.
There's and they have big eyes.
There's the ones where they have really small eyes
and his weird little tails like a slug.
Here's the one where they sleep inside of a sock.
They will find so many weird different.
How many types of main character plushes can we crank out?
Oh, it's a new moat and new emos.
How do you pronounce them?
N-U-I-M-O-S, but M-O is new.
Emos, new emos, new emos.
Have they hit America yet?
Yeah, yeah, this is it.
No, I've seen those advertised in.
Yeah, look at Mickey and Minnie or Donald dressed like a leather day.
What?
He's got a leather daddy hat on there.
Mickey and Minnie are wearing like leather jackets.
And Mickey's got like leather pants.
And then Donald is wearing like kind of a leisure suit
and has like a leather daddy type of it.
It's not.
It's on further inspection.
The material is not probably leather, but it's no way it's similar to it, though.
It's fake leather.
Can you see that or no?
It's a little far for me.
You can text me as many.
Yeah, I mean, leather characters as you want.
I need more details.
I could use a narrative.
Oh, that's like a yeah.
What is that?
He's got leather, though, on his on his collar.
That looks like a pop punk like ensemble.
I don't know.
Like a band.
I mean, Daisy's wearing maybe you could say that's a Cruella type outfit.
Like fashion Cruella.
Yeah, fashion.
Yeah.
Classic Cruella.
But anyway, you can buy clothes for a lot of these characters now,
like sweatshirts and leather pants.
Good to do.
You love these characters or not?
You don't have one new emo in this apartment.
You don't put any leather jackets over Donald's seat.
You haven't put you.
That seat is unclad with leather pants.
It's a good point.
I mean, I'm looking here.
You can buy a little Hawaiian shirt and shorts.
This stuff is really good.
I really should not buy any more collectibles
as I'd like to like to call them to make it sounds sophisticated.
Yeah.
But there's a little Kermit.
There's a little piggy.
I mean, look, maybe it's a lot of little pants.
This is Sunday.
Dressin.
Well, I'm very excited because I got a couple of months ago.
I got these four Ninja Turtle NECA toys, cartoon toys,
and they come with trench coats and little pants.
And you can take the little blue pants.
Oh, because they're under cover.
Yeah, because they're the undercover turtles.
So I already have four sets of little blue pants upstairs,
but they don't fit on the new new modes or whatever.
But they fit on different figures because I wait.
Does it fit on Doc Brown?
Could you make it look like Doc Brown was wearing slacks?
The Doc, the Back to the Future NECA's are a little bit in a different scale.
And they in Doc Brown has longer legs.
You could try.
Can't trade the characters pants easily.
Well, for the for the cartoon line, you depending on how tall the character is,
like they have I have two of the punk frog characters and those,
I think you could probably put the pants on because you can put the jackets
on those guys pretty easily.
But like crying, my crying is very big.
So he could not wear the turtle pants.
So some care, some characters, but not all characters, right?
Trade little pants before you put them in their little beds.
That's right.
Yes.
And they hopefully they're coming out with a little bed playset
in the next year or two where they can sleep.
Just don't start a fire, Michael.
I told my mom about that.
She still stands by that, by the way.
Oh, really?
Hasn't budged?
Yeah.
Thinks that was right.
The right call to make that that was a fire hazard.
Geez.
Have napkins sitting.
Oh, you do have a candle burning in the bathroom.
Don't forget to blow.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Fire.
Tell her she's not here.
Any napkins near it, especially not any little beds.
OK.
Or the turtles little pants to our flammable, probably.
Oh, probably.
Yeah, just made of asbestos.
They call they're called soft goods.
That's how that's a toy terminology for cloth accessories.
Soft goods.
So the soft to buy my turtles, their little soft goods.
So some some of my turtles come with soft goods and some with hard goods.
Well, I don't say hard goods.
They don't say that's just sort of because then it's then it's
just kind of put on the character itself.
But I'm just saying the soft goods might be flammable.
Hmm.
OK.
Yeah.
Well, then knowing that we're in the same house as some soft goods
and some candles that are currently lit, we better get out of here
so we can say you survived podcast the ride so we can say that we survived it
because it's getting as harrowing as Charles Foster's journey.
Wait a minute.
Isn't that the is it?
Oh, no.
You know, Charlie Foster's.
Charles Foster.
Yeah.
Is he related?
Is he related to Citizen Kane?
God, we just put that together.
No, the Foster's litigious, like the goddamn hearse.
Are they going to sue us now for even mentioning the words?
Citizen Kane, Charles.
Yeah, maybe.
Well, not more danger to get.
We better dive out of this episode, but not before one more reminder.
Price is right.
Monday, June 28th.
Check your local listings here in Los Angeles.
It's 10 o'clock.
But maybe get there, maybe make it more of a nine nine fifty eight.
And again, I can't tell you why lest I incur the ghost of Sumner
Redstone.
So Michael Eisner.
So that'll do it.
And that makes sense, because I knew Mike, you said
that we had to wrap up the episode because it's time for Edwin's monthly haircut.
Correct.
I did say that.
Yeah.
Well, bring him up on your lap and let's yeah, he's looking a little shaggy.
Maybe we need to give that guy a little trim.
Yeah.
Cheek, cheek, cheek, cheek, cheek, cheek, cheek, cheek.
Wow.
He's so well behaved.
Oh, geez.
It's not bothering him one bit.
Oh, but you know what might bother him a little more than that?
That swarm of killer bees that's coming in through the window.
No, they have flamethrowers with them, too.
No, for for for for for.
President Lincoln, you buy you rubbing your beard on my face.
I just wanted to show you this
this great new peanut brittle that I just found.
Oh, it really helps relieve the pressures of being the president.
Oh, now you're kissing my neck, President.
President was the president.
Reagan,
Reagan's here, too.
I'm here, too.
No, those kisses were me.
Tear down these bees.
Yum, yum, yum, yum, yum, yum.
Oh, so many presidents.
So many presidents kissing.
Oh, and Edwin's licking them now, too.
Oh, my gosh.
It's a dog pile with one dog and two presidents.
Fine, Norel.
Let's just let's just let you know what?
This is disgusting.
I'm just going to light them all on fire.
Wow.