Five, four, three, two, one.
We don't have to have anything, you know?
We haven't set the bar there.
We don't have to say something clever for this episode on podcast The Ride the Second Gate featuring the Stargate.
Oh, we're in it, now we're in it.
Yeah, now we're in it.
It's the Maren, it's kind of the Maren start.
It's the Maren, yeah.
That's sort of a new thing we're doing now is doing the Maren start, sort of just like, you know, we're just bullshitting.
We're just shooting the shit, as they say.
I think that's a cool move to incorporate in 2021.
Yeah.
Almost a, I think a decade into the Mark Maren discography, podcography, I don't know what the word is.
Podcography?
That's a horrible word, I kid, can't be that.
I don't know.
It's maybe up to us to decide.
Yeah, we'll figure that.
I mean, like, it took years to figure out that our listeners were called Cliffords.
So it'll take years to figure out that what our catalog is called, what our back catalog is called.
So long to perfect it.
Yeah.
To get the right, the perfect name that everyone agrees on.
Everyone agrees on it, they love it.
Today we are talking about a popular topic, I feel.
Much requested.
This is a much requested topic.
I think it's a lot to do with the name.
It's all about the name.
The name is really good and really perfect.
And it looks so good, neon.
It is just awesome to stare at that word.
Yes.
Because this, well, this is, I think, an especially good arcade.
I think, like, if you liked arcades and this, then you walked into this thing, you'd be psyched.
But ultimately it is an arcade.
It is in no way thematically really Starcade.
Right.
But the word does so much of the work.
It's one of the coolest words maybe ever invented, maybe ever created.
It is, and I believe not, maybe not copyrighted by Disney because I found some other Starcades.
And I think CBS had a children's cartoon block called Starcade for a brief while.
There's a 1981 game show.
And the reason I happened upon it, and I happened upon the website that has archived a number of these, is because I wondered, there is a famous WCW and then before that NWA, National Wrestling Alliance, pay-per-view called Starcade, which was sort of before WrestleMania.
Oh, yeah.
WrestleMania, which was like a super card where they would have different companies having, you know, big marquee matches.
And I texted my friend Justin and I said, who made up Starcade?
Kind of knowing the answer.
Dusty?
Oh, Dusty did.
Yeah, okay.
Dusty did.
Dusty Rhodes.
Father-in-law to past podcast, or I guess Brandy Rhodes.
Oh, right.
Oh, maybe I didn't know that.
Okay.
The American Dream.
And Dusty is a, was a legend.
He came up with a lot of gimmicks, came up with a war games cage match.
He also would take a lot of ideas from TV and movies he just watched.
So there's a Reddit post, and I don't know if this is completely accurate.
We could probably get a fact check on it, but somebody's like, how did the name Starcade come up?
Because there's nothing in Starcade that you would think about.
Like, WrestleMania makes sense.
It's crazy.
We're wrestling.
It's a mania.
It's, it's, of course.
What does Starcade mean?
Why would that be the name?
There are stars in it, wrestling stars, but arcade, I couldn't really.
Yeah.
And somebody's like, I believe he just saw the game show that started in 1981.
And he was just like, that's a cool name.
And then Starcade was born.
And now of course that's IP owned by WWE.
So is it spelled with two Rs though?
Yes.
To get away from the copyright.
Wow.
Yeah.
Insert an R and then you're good.
But also superfluous.
Yes.
Makes you think of Ringo Starr, but it has even less to do with Ringo Starr than it has to do with Starcades.
And Disneyland Starcade 77, right?
Yes.
I had an opening day, May 4th, 1977.
Same day as Space Mountain.
Yes.
Very exciting.
Because it's part of the Space Mountain complex.
This is maybe, I think if you are a more of a Disney world centric person or another part, if you're a Carowind centric person, you don't know you've never been to Disneyland.
It is, yeah, it's basically like part of the same building essentially as Space Mountain.
It went in along with the part of the same structure essentially as now it's the Captain EO enclosed theater or whatever, the Magic Guy theater.
But it was the outdoor stage that was built for cool bands like Halix to play.
And then the people mover goes through it.
It's one of those great interconnected, you know, Tomorrowland, everything working in harmony.
It's hard to imagine a Disneyland without the Space Mountain complex.
I just never seen anybody call it that before.
So that's somewhere in the research.
I'm like, cool, complex view that was coming.
The Space Mountain complex.
Yeah, I have a space.
I have a Space Mountain complex.
Right.
I think about it all the time.
We all sort of have saw a Space Mountain complex.
I think it's.
Yeah.
It's not been diagnosed by like a psychiatrist maybe, but it would prove to be our most our biggest hurdle in our lives.
For sure.
Yeah, I feel like if you were a teenager when like all of this was open and like really, really brand new and everything like this is, you know, into the 1980s when, you know, Disneyland before like,
unfortunately, the Eisner group, the Eisner executives who were like, we're leaving money on the table by not charging triple the amount of for admittance to theme parks.
When there was like an outdoor stage and a brand new roller coaster with an arcade next to it, like seems like a cool hangout spot.
Like that's what you want as a teen.
And that's how it comes out of the gate.
But then you add that like, you know, like in the subsequent years that we put in a 3D movie with a relevant pop star and then we put in a simulator ride with a relevant movie.
This all at the end, there's so much neon around.
I think this all makes this is when Tomorrowland was cool.
They have it pretty current.
You could see why this would appeal to teenagers above the, you know, the fairy tale rides several steps.
Yeah.
And another important component of like mall like common spaces, a massive restaurant, the space place restaurant also opens around the same time as the space stage and space now.
What I believe now is Alien Pizza Planet or Alien Pizza Port.
You know, it just favorite.
It rolls off the tongue.
You know, yeah, this also suggested me.
I don't I don't want to get off on a rant here, but this also.
Oh yeah, you're talking about this complex and you're talking about arcade and you're talking about hanging out.
This is a different time of more romanticized time when they wanted teens and young people to come and hang.
Bob Chapek's on a call a couple days ago saying, you know what, there's going to be like a reward loyalty program that will replace the pass holder program because the pass holders were not spending enough to justify the program.
We were losing money.
And I don't like any of this shit.
I don't like the sound of this.
This sounds like, oh, we'll get like an extra day if we go five days a year.
Like it sounds it doesn't sound like this.
Like, hey, come on.
It's a fun hangout for locals anymore.
It's like it's a Starbucks rewards tricks where it's like, I spent eighty dollars and I got a single beverage value.
Yes.
So I don't.
So hearing this, yes, I get I get wistful for a bygone era.
Yeah, I got a little distracted during all that.
Because what, Jason, what you said about space place, I was like, OK, I think that's right.
Where it was.
I don't know anything about this restaurant.
I never thought about it before.
But wasn't that mission to Mars thing open like too late?
Like, wasn't that still open in the 80s, which is where the pizza port restaurant is now?
And I think while you're telling me what you think, but I just found this picture, which is I believe what we're looking at is the end of the Space Mountain Corridor,
where now it's where they give out the fast passes.
And I think at the end of that corridor was once a counter.
Oh, like you walk up to the counter restaurant, which like right near where you waited for.
You know what?
You're probably right.
I have, you know, two thousands are a Disney bias because you used to get up to Space Mountain with giant outdoor escalator.
I'm forgetting about the speed ramps.
Yes.
I love the excuse me.
I know I didn't know you are correct.
You know, I'm saying excuse me to listeners.
I yeah, yeah, I am.
Please learn places.
No, I didn't know I do.
There was a restaurant all the way in the back and with those those whatever you call them, those like steel bars that feel very 70s, 80s airports that kind of like cascade up at an angle.
I mean, we're talking about this little alcove that I love so much.
Maybe one of the best parts of the Space Mountain complex.
Love that area where you waited for EO or Honey, I Shrunk the Audience.
No idea.
There's a restaurant back there.
Yeah, I don't think I did either.
Yeah, I mean, they've definitely, you know, it definitely seemed like a design sensibility for like the Golden Age of malls.
And now it is kind of a little bit like the current age of malls where it's like, well, the pennies are still open, huh?
The pennies are still open.
And that Space Mountain, you know, where you pass by lots of stuff that was something once with the Starcade being one of those things.
Yes, it's not really.
It's certainly a shell of its of its former.
Yes.
And in fact, the most recent Starcade news is a video I found on YouTube as of 2017 where the YouTube account for Disney meetings and events are encouraging you to have your event in the Starcade.
And we'll set up folding tables and pour you cocktails, strong cocktails or weak cocktail, probably depending on, you know, who's buying a cash bar, open bar.
How good is this company to its employees?
Yeah, for sure.
It's that saying you could host a party in the Starcade though now where there's no arcade like what?
That's such a barcade.
Yeah, no, Cade.
Yeah.
I mean, I guess is the name of the room now, but that's.
I mean, my experience with it was like in the mid 2000s, you know, there was a handful of arcade games, a lot of merchandise, and then it got a second life in 2012 when Wreck-It Ralph opened and they filled it with vintage games and a bunch of free fix it Felix games.
And whatever they just put on a truck and moved over from the short limited time magic Flynn's arcade from California Adventure from Electronica.
The Tron Arcade.
Yes.
Yeah.
Switch rules.
Love that.
Yes.
Yeah.
Is that what they did?
So anything that was there in that temporary Tron Arcade just became part of they quickly put games back into the Starcade.
That was my guess.
And then I found like a retro gaming message board where someone's like, hey, it looks like this happened.
So it's a lot of the same stuff.
Yeah.
I mean, I think there were still some games in there.
It seems like 2015 is about when they were winding it down because then they ran limited time stuff for Big Hero 6 and the Tomorrowland movie in there.
I think we got pictures with Baymax in there maybe once.
Probably.
Yeah.
Yeah, I remember that.
That was fun.
But yeah, I get the Flynn's Arcade was the highlight arcade of my Disneyland going days.
Like that was like I had much more atmosphere and like experience like was character.
Yeah.
I think it had the illuminated like the weenie in a way of the Tron game where it's kind of off on its lonesome and calling to you down a big hallway like as it is in the movie before Jeff Bridges gets sucked in.
I thought they did a good job of recreating that like this like the Tron machine is special.
This is epic.
Yeah, one other thing like AP Lounge during they were running something called AP Days a few years ago.
Maybe you guys went to record it.
Like you could get stickers or magnets maybe and there were some phone charges and I think furniture like IKEA kind of furniture.
They were so good to us.
I miss being an AP so hard.
Chepik said that they're not going to have any furniture anymore.
He said it's over with furniture.
No more IKEA furniture in the AP Lounge.
And he's too comfortable.
It makes him sleepy and they don't want to spend money.
Yeah, it'll be the loyalty rewards lounge from now on and it'll be no furniture and it will just be like a punch card.
You'll get a punch card and then like your 20th Disneyland trip will be free.
Like that's it'll be a spot like a sub.
It'll be like a buy 20 subs get one free card.
You have to take a loyalty test to get in.
You have to answer like did you see the three men and a baby reboot?
Yes.
Did you enjoy it?
Was Zac Efron did Zac Efron bring the franchise back to life with style and charm?
Yes, he did.
All right.
You may sit on this couch briefly.
Is this the first place you learned about what a triad or polycule is?
Please respond yes or no.
Do you wish Gordon Bombay to find love?
Do you hope he can get himself out of the dumps and find love with Lauren Graham?
Do you think adding Lauren Graham to the Mighty Ducks averse is in a word epic?
So let me ask what was your guys relationship with arcades growing up?
Are you big arcade guys?
Oh yes.
The arcade this is such a and I'm it's funny because it starts in the 70s.
I obviously this starts starts physically 70s but arcade like mania where arcade seemed like the most cool thing to possibly go to existed up until when I'm interested to talk to like a young person.
No.
Oh, are you kidding?
There's still big business at the Jersey Shore because the kids want to go off and do their own thing from their parents for a little while and they're still making like new cabinets.
Oh yeah.
I know there makes I look I've been to a Dave and Busters in the last few years.
I know what's going on there.
Yeah, there's busters.
But I think last summer was the first summer I didn't text you like hey look there's a giant Batmobile now or like look there's a Ghostbuster where you have a proton pack sort of arcade discovery.
I've seen I've seen that Batmobile.
Is the Batmobile like the Batman Returns scene where Penguin is like having sex and then they're like shooting it from underneath and it's really really sexual?
No, it's the other direction where it's like you pick which Batmobile there's like 20 different Batmobiles.
Oh wait maybe I have series.
Batman movies like yeah.
So you're saying the youth of today are as excited about arcades as we were.
I don't know about as excited because I mean everyone's got you know games on their phones now.
Well that's yeah that's where I'm going where it's like the technology at home now is so crazy good.
That was always a big part of the draw because I loved video games as a kid.
But the arcades were way better than like Nintendo or Super Nintendo.
And now it's kind of lapped it like the technology goes faster I think on your home devices than arcade cabinets.
Yes.
Yeah, that's what I wonder.
I mean I had.
Yeah, we talked a little bit on Mortal Kombat episode like there was like such a an obsessiveness I would have I would like imagine playing the game for I remember going to the bowling alley and being like yeah yeah bowling's fine but the Ninja Turtle arcade cabinet is going to be there.
Yes.
And I hope that the older cooler kids aren't hogging it because they always did.
And then I could sneak in and play as one of the turtles.
And then I'd probably like die because I'd only get like a dollar worth of quarters.
Yeah, for sure.
I mean by yeah by the time we were hitting arcades.
It's like the golden age of our kid they're well-oiled machines licensing is kicked in so it's like Ninja Turtles Simpsons X-Men Ninja Turtles and Simpsons are the two I remember from being the young like Chuck E.
Cheese had that Simpsons one which is so funny in hindsight that it's just the Simpsons have to like punch and kick.
Smash people in the face with the vacuum cleaner.
Yeah, specifically the life is hell rabbits.
They're fighting the life is hell man grading.
Yeah.
Kill my old IP.
Bart is just like wailing on the life is hell rabbits with a skateboard and then like Smithers is bad and you have to beat up like a crusty balloon in the first level.
Yes.
Yeah.
It's just yeah.
Smithers is bad.
Smithers is a bad guy.
I never meditated on that.
There's the villain of the show.
There's I'm sure there's 10.
Times more funny things about it if I think about it.
Yeah.
Those two are loom large and then X-Men as well.
X-Men off the pilot the X-Men pride of the X-Men pilot that did not become a full series unlike the massive 92 different great costume designs.
Yeah, yeah.
The animated series.
We all know.
I think I've said my I have major arcade memories at Disney World and one of them includes that X-Men which I think was at was it at like an ice cream parlor in Grand Floridian maybe that's possible.
I mean mostly arcade the hotels had pretty big arcades.
There's a big arcade by Space Mountain.
Yeah.
Also in Florida.
I beat the X-Men.
I beat the X-Men game with a bunch of kids.
Yeah.
The X-Men.
I beat the X-Men game with a bunch of kids.
Yeah.
I탑t's a lot of people.
I'm not a big fan of X-Men.
I
Yeah.
That's a lot of fun.
You need the full team.
That's like a thrill.
Cheering you watching.
Well there was a four.
It was much like The Simpsons like a four player game.
So for like I feel like it might have been broken.
That was always the best when you find an arcade that was broken.
You could just keep hitting start.
Yes.
And I think that's how we beat it because there was never ever a chance.
I think that my mom would give me enough quarters for it for to make it through the whole game.
No.
I had an experience.
I had a couple of experiences where it was like kid in a candy store.
One every now and then down in Ocean City.
We would go to this one arcade that was off the boardwalk with my dad and brother and he'd give us each a roll of quarters and then we'd go to get ice cream afterwards.
And it's like I can't imagine like a like a pig and shit.
You know it was just the best thing.
If Monday were here he would have taken that roll of quarters and thrown it at some kid.
Yeah.
Well you wrap your fist.
You wrap your fist around.
It's been on a bicycle just like hitting kids with his quarters fist or you put it in a tube sock swing above your head.
Yeah.
You would have done a lot of different things with those quarters.
Bad man.
He's a bad man.
Also I played a Ghostbusters arcade in the contemporary arcade which was I never saw the game again.
It was not at the and we've talked about the little this fabled Little Caesars I talk about.
It's only barely documented online and was the only one of its kind.
That was the proof of concept for like a Little Caesar's Chuck E.
Cheese.
Yes.
Yeah.
And they had a Bucky O'Hare arcade there that I didn't see.
Very rare.
In my experience.
And I would remember like these would be very big deals on a trip to Disney World which is so funny in hindsight.
Yeah.
Right.
I like this.
The contemporary one is talked up.
Yeah.
And it's still there.
OK.
It's maybe had its like super height in 70s 80s.
Yes.
As did the contemporary maybe in general.
Yeah.
Not to say it's not cool now but just that's when like the style was right.
Right.
Very contemporary.
Yes.
Now the contemporary is getting very contemporary by theming itself after a movie from 2001.
The Incredibles.
Does it have a general Incredibles.
Well they're redoing the rooms to add like more incredible stuff.
It's kind of like more concept already or credit is kind of like timeless you know evergreen sort of.
Hmm.
Design.
But it is very funny where it's like classic nature to.
Yeah.
Incredibles.
There's um yeah that's not quite as good as it was but that's not bad.
Yeah.
Something.
It's a way to some direction to take it in.
Yeah.
I know.
Disney World.
I never had time.
I'm like trying to jam it all in.
I like maybe I don't know.
I guess I recall little ones like it like it night maybe you're back from the park so I not run over.
I mean like I.
I talked before when the StarKid came up before about how when I did a school trip to Disneyland and everybody agreed the whole class agreed to spend lots of time at the StarKid and I lost my mind.
Right.
Yeah.
What are you talking about.
These are games that are elsewhere.
Why would you not take advantage.
And I think that I may have broken off from the group in a way I was not supposed to.
I think I'm like I got to get on that people mover.
I'm getting on a ride.
Yeah.
I'm not crazy.
We both did that.
We both went to the.
I was a chorus group.
We were to Hershey Park.
My one friend just wanted to do bumper cars and do the arcade because he was too scared of anything bigger.
And we weren't supposed to go off on our own.
But I'm like I am.
And then like and I did a bunch.
I did roller coasters.
I had a hot dog.
And then when a teacher almost saw me some other kids I knew were walking by and I was like hey just act natural like just pretend I've been with you.
And they're like what.
I like just keep walking.
Don't worry about it.
Kids you knew or not.
Kids I knew.
OK.
Wasn't a stranger.
I wish I had had been precocious enough to address strangers like hey act natural.
You're fake laugh fake laugh.
Yeah.
Give you some tokens after.
Yeah I don't know.
I would never by the way those that stresses me out both those stories.
Well I think clearly both Jason and I too but like it would just you had to do it.
Yeah.
No I know.
I went twice and he fucked me the first year this guy because he's like he didn't want to do any of the big stuff.
And I'm like you son of a bitch.
And like we had all like group.
I think they it's like all right.
Who's everyone going to be around with.
So we have a general idea where everyone is.
And I was like I'm not making that same mistake again.
Oh and then the third time we went on a course trip a third time and my dad was kind so kind because the school the formal dance was that night.
And that like ninth grader 10th grade formal and they refused to let us arrive late even though we were going to be back in time to catch the last 90 minutes of the dance.
So my dad drove up to get us after we had a few hours in the park and drove us back.
I mean it's probably 90 minutes to Hershey Pennsylvania from where I grew up.
But still that was very kind of him because I know that's right.
Doing that drive immediately round trip sucks.
And also I was an idiot.
Why did I get formal sucked dances suck shit.
Don't go.
If you're at a theme park don't leave it.
Stay there teens stay there.
Stay at the theme park.
It will just make you anxious.
School dances.
Wow.
I took your advice well into the past when I did not go to any prom or homecoming.
I went to two proms.
There's nothing that's that's correct.
Yeah.
Also if you have fun.
I would say I know what you're saying but that's stupid to not go and I recognize what was stupid about it.
Yeah I remember one school dance I stayed home eating Chinese food watching a blockbuster rental of memento and I was like this is the best night of my fucking life.
You know I do I I don't I hate to revert back to how I felt when I was 16 17 but that sounds great.
I remember my senior prom that instead of my weird friend and I blew up a fake building like a like he got little fireworks and there was he made a little model building for some movie video that we never ended up finishing.
But like we blew up a little building instead of being a pro.
I don't regret that either.
I mean that's cool.
I think that's beautiful and I think that's really sweet.
I did go to two proms and they were nothing but stress.
I was definitely stressed but I had a good time.
Would it surprise you to learn to learn that one time I went to a dance with a girl and then her like I didn't know her so well and I didn't know her group of friends so well.
But I am one friend who went alone.
We all went back to my house and I forced them to watch TLC wrestling matches on our TV for a couple hours.
That's all right.
Hours.
I don't mean medical blunders.
Maybe at least maybe a couple hours after junior prom we went back to someone's house and I brought I like had a bag of DVDs.
I was like what does everyone want to watch and we're like I guess Jay and Silent Bob strike back and I'm like great.
Of course.
Yeah.
Like I think I like TV.
So it's like all of them were Kevin Smith ones.
So you're probably statistically you're probably going to end up on that.
I mean I had fun at school dance.
I'm just saying like oh I was well you know but the other.
Oh I had an arcade memory a very arcade specific that I have a feeling you guys did not experience.
Anytime I went to an arcade thankfully I didn't have to worry about it for too many years but for a number of years as I walked in the arcade I was like I hope to God there's milk cartons because I had to stand.
I had to stand on milk cartons when I was younger to get to the control.
I was too short to get.
I thought you needed like a school lunch milk carton.
Oh no no no no need a hit.
I know cartons or some had like you know wooden crates or like glorified apple box or whatever.
But yeah that that was I mean I could suffer but like I always played the games better if I was you know the correct.
Proportion to play them.
Yeah that sucks I'm sorry.
I wish though you wanted every arcade to have like a 2% milk that you could sip out of.
I don't think I was necessarily the most clumsy child but I would have been smelling milk left and right if I was trying to manage a milk carton and an arcade game.
As as a kid and I always thought wouldn't it be great to have an arcade cabinet at home.
I remember going we would go this is just a thing I guess you did in the Midwest and other places.
We would just go look at model homes sometimes.
Yeah yeah I did some of that.
Oh yeah.
Those are themed environments sometimes.
Yeah.
That's a good reason to do that.
And I remember we went very it was very close to our house.
I mean you know grandma would come over and we'd just go tour some new houses.
Which is funny.
Yeah that's still my parents thing for sure.
Everyone looked at the house it was nice.
Yeah and I remember one of the display they had in the basement for this one house they had an arcade in it and I was like oh my god.
This is this is must be the richest person who ever lived if they had this.
And now recently they've been putting out smaller scale versions of arcade cabinets you can buy.
So you can buy the Ninja Turtles arcade.
It's not as big as a normal cabinet but for like 300 bucks you can get a smaller version.
But I think I would play it once or twice and it would sit there because it's sort of not convenient to stand always and play.
Yeah.
An arcade.
Yeah it becomes like it's a thing that you think that you want around.
There may be listeners who have arcade cabinets and could tell us it's the greatest thing ever to have it.
I think you've got it there's got to be like a lot of traffic in your house to make it worth it.
To get like the wow right out of it.
There's got to be like a lot of kids coming over or a lot of people your age friends who want to play it.
I remember you guys are going to parties at the birthday boys house when they all live together.
Oh yeah.
Sure.
Yeah.
Because they had a Ninja Turtle.
I mean that's and they were they like that was a real a time.
So that was that like they aced it perfect made it like oh I got to go back there.
That was a real one to a real arcade.
Yeah.
Very air brushy.
Like that specific way that they looked only on that cabinet and no in no other media you know what I mean.
Yes the suit.
Well what's really fun is the I've mentioned many times NECA toys makes all these Ninja Turtle things including arcade toys and they have that art on the boxes and stuff.
Yeah.
Weird suit looking things that like you never saw again.
April looks really funny.
The whole thing and Michelangelo's bandana is yellow.
Yes.
That always is weird.
Why is it yellow.
And then it just became a color that doesn't exist in nature because it would immediately get a sun or fluorescent light down.
Yes.
Oh right.
They all look like shit.
It would fade.
Yeah.
So that makes sense.
If you have a party house which yes that would that's a good call.
One of the you know one or two of them were heroes in that they sacrificed.
They they sacrificed to have a party house because one or two of them did not have a door.
Oh yeah.
One or two of them were sleeping in the downstairs open area and I think had the curtains set up which I know is kind of a common like cost saving divide a one bedroom apartment.
Yeah.
If people don't know what we're talking about birthday boys are a sketch group that Mike Mitchell Mitch from doughboys was part of and there were seven guys and five of them lived in a big house and there would be big parties there.
Yes.
And like you know like ecology like packed the house is packed type party.
Yeah.
And then they and then they moved out of that and then no party house replaced it.
No no parties.
There were two I mean there's we'll do an episode on a party houses that we party that later.
I'm sure there were there was another party house off a sunset called Camp Hollywood.
That was also I don't know if you get invited to Camp Hollywood.
OK.
Well we'll talk about that off air.
But that was a tell me a give drop every name every fellow podcaster now.
I think every one of them was a good guy.
Every person at every one of those parties back then has a podcast today.
I think to you saw a snapshot of a 2011 kind of way all do you see me in funny or die.
I think every single person is a good chance.
Yeah.
And look these were stressed that they weren't as stressful as school dances but reasonably stressful and the awkwardness.
I think the awkwardness levels probably as high if not higher but managed by weed and cigarettes and beer.
So you know you don't have that in high school.
You can't really you got to sneak in.
I don't want to.
Yeah I don't want God to be mad.
No I had the complete Kevin Smith filmography.
I did not have.
I wonder what that stuff is.
They keep talking about and do.
Well Kevin wasn't getting high back then.
So you were just.
No I was following his lead.
It was saying Kevin didn't get high until after Zack and Mary and as the legend goes.
Yeah that's true.
More reasons to not.
OK.
Let's talk about the with of about our kids.
Let's talk about StarCat.
Let's talk about this specific place and what's what sets it apart.
One big thing that unfortunately not in a very long time but when it came out of the gate two stories this is a two story.
Yeah.
And even though there may be one story arcades that had more games and bigger space doesn't matter.
Two story really cool.
Also would you also call that a speed ramp.
I guess you would.
Not an escalator but just but like airport airport style ramp you know that you and if you run up that thing and it's moving on its own.
Yeah.
What.
It's incredible.
It's better than sex.
Running up a ramp that is also moving on its own moving whatever faster.
This whatever sex is like that's better than it.
That's what I yeah I think you're right.
And this upstairs area now one of the actually accessible parts of StarCade because it's the extended outdoor queue for Space Mountain.
I was going for yes long and the windows you could do like it's like slightly dark and slightly tended but not really windows so you could always see into that StarCade second floor and see that nothing was going on up there.
Yeah.
Why not.
So it was exciting that they started using the room even if it is just for more line.
Yeah.
It is much better than cooking out in the sun like cooking out in the outdoor switchbacks and just staring at like why is there a sniper's crosshair painted two stories tall on the ground.
Oh I love that though.
I like that was that was my dream is like is there some way to get married in that spot on that very that X.
There is.
I do like it.
But it would cause.
Yeah yeah.
Yeah.
I carry Nick Cannon got married on that I think is probably people who've gotten married there you've heard you know their names.
Very famous people.
I did however.
So this is this is this like wonderful dream experience which is that and I might have talked about this in the show a long time ago.
I was I got to be part of a film shoot or video shoot I guess in Space Mountain.
And this this experience caused me to be just the crew and the actors of this thing hanging out in Space Mountain from Disneyland closing till like five in the morning.
Yeah this was one of the best things I ever got to do so surreal.
And here's here's the great part about it.
I didn't really have a job on the shoot.
The people were nice enough to just say hey you're a dork you're going to want to just hang out in Space Mountain for a while you want to go.
Yes please yes.
So they pretended that I had a job or was like taking notes for the head or something and I did not whatsoever.
So it was just this insane dream like I'm just going to hang out.
I just like kind of like lounged on the floor.
I took a lot of pictures.
I walked the queue entirely by myself.
And when after I did that like I walked through the queue and then realize and then I was up on Space Mountain patio and I realized like like oh I'm in Disneyland alone right now.
This is like an out of a dream where I'm looking out and there are no other people.
And I like what can I do what can I do within reason I can't exactly you know run around and like kiss robots or something.
Obviously my deep seated dream.
But what can I do.
So I ran I'm like into Marlin by myself and knowing that probably is only going to last a minute.
Like somebody's going to tell me to get out of here and I was down at the well to that one I walked into the Magic Eye Theater which I think had not been running for a little while I just opened a door and was just in there.
Whoa whoa whoa closes door got scared really quickly.
And then I'm looking at the starcade and the starcade doors are open and there was no barricade on the speed ramp and for now like at least a decade it's that the second floor has been closed and I'm like oh my god this is your chance you can go to the second floor of the starcade go go go.
Sprinted up that ramp not speeding not moving on its own so not better than sex for that reason is a regular still right.
The same really the same as sex.
That's exactly as good as sex is and then as as satisfying of a finish as sex can have because then I got up to the top to see an empty room and a fading mural and you know like a box.
And truly that was like oh my god wow a box really like being in that I don't know like you build up a space like that like why would they block it off it's so special and cool up there and how I get to do it and truly it was nothing but like I but still such a great like loopy.
Yeah.
Thankful for you can see into that there's video on YouTube because the people mover you used to be able to see into the second floor starcade and you used to be able to see in Mickey star traders.
And it seems like there were some recollections of starcade online too and you can see in the video that it's a lot of air hockey tables up there.
And there are some arcade cabinets to think pinball was mainly on the second floor.
Yes.
For a while it seemed like a lot of pinball or exclusively pinball pin.
I was not a pinball kid.
I liked pinball for a change of pace every now and then.
Sure sure.
It was more of a pinball man still more of a pinball person in a way maybe because like yeah video game you can play at home not all video games some you know arcade specific but being that it is such a physical tactile experience love that Adams family.
Sure.
One yeah up fester.
There's currently a monster pinball.
Yes.
So good.
I played this.
It's at the Burbank mall not far from here.
Just a rad so many effects and odds and ends and if you're rolling you get so many videos you get so much grandpa Al really fantastic.
I got so I was like I got to look up the company NECA style that does this and I don't remember it anymore but I think they do really good Star Wars pinball machines whatever it's like a very current 2021 my own the pinball game.
Yeah, there, there was a ghost there's a newer Ghostbusters pinball I think I've played that's really fun.
I feel like pinball.
Maybe.
Yeah, I think so.
There's a rolling stone pinball game at the park MGM that I enjoyed playing at the off the record lounge.
Oh yeah, I know what you're talking about.
Yeah, I think I saw it.
Yeah.
Okay.
All right.
I think there's a soprano pinball game that's pretty fun.
And there, we were at Comic Con like the last Comic Con at one of the hotels they had a bunch of gaming like vendors set up and they, I think they were selling shrunken down pinball cabinets that you could put in your home with geo at that point.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
And they looked pretty good.
I don't know.
Yeah, I feel like pinball still has a mystique that maybe video games like don't.
Yeah, video games are just so common.
That's the thing you won't have now like there's that's probably more valuable because yeah, yeah, if I have a PS five now and it's like that's actually more powerful than most Dave and Buster games, like the hardware in there.
Yeah, but like a pinball date and change it.
It's not.
Yeah, time that it was built and like VR like at home VR is already a thing and will only get better.
Yeah, next in the near future.
Yeah.
There was some VR in Starcade.
Did you guys catch this?
That there was a.
This was an Epcot thing we might have talked about this in I think this was at Innoventions that there was an Aladdin magic carpet VR experience that I associate with Disney World and I don't remember it being at the Starcade but people online mentioned that it was at the
Big clunky helmet.
You're flying a carpet around, you know, the Sultan's Disney Quest.
Was it different than the Disney Quest one or was it the same?
Oh, was it?
Yeah, was it a Disney Quest?
Not.
I feel like I'm remembering some other because there was like an Imagineer test lab at Innoventions that might have been like a cousin of this.
Okay.
But was this it?
Yeah, maybe it was.
There was an Aladdin VR Disney Quest and I'm sure I mentioned it on the our Disney Quest episode.
That's the one that I was the most excited to do was ride the carpet going to Cave of Wonders and I did it and I immediately wanted to throw up and felt sick almost the rest of the day.
It ruined the rest of the Disney Quest day.
I felt sick as we boarded the plane that night.
We had to de-board the plane for some mechanical reason which was scary.
Oh, jeez.
And then I remember they gave us a voucher for a sandwich in the airport and I ate a sandwich, you know, seven or eight and then I was like, I feel a little better and I had been sick all day just because of the Aladdin VR.
Geez, threw you the whole day.
Oh my god.
Yeah, it ruined the rest of Disney Quest which again I was so excited to do.
Like when we were that was like my number one going down there.
Lured you in and then like the Cave of Wonders lured you in and then only peril awaited you.
That's right.
Inside.
Yeah, I don't know much about what this was like at that Starcade or what the whole experience was but I did see it in looking for validation like yeah, was that Aladdin thing there?
I saw on Twitter a couple people mentioned it and somebody said that they got to go and said there was a huge influence on them and got them thinking about VR.
And then I look at that person's bio and is one of the founders of the void.
Whoa, really?
Yeah.
So they're there as a kid or a teen going VR thing huh?
And then they went on to nail it so much better.
So I hope they're okay that company.
He didn't.
Well, something's weird.
Yeah, what's going on?
I don't know that Taylor Swift lawsuit's gonna go well.
I haven't seen an update on that.
But yeah, it sounds like at least he didn't get violently ill or anything.
I guess not.
Which is good.
Yeah, could have been there would have been no void I suppose.
Yeah, a lot of we were talking before like there's not a tie.
I was trying to find like is there like a massive database that says all the games they had at the Starcade and there is not.
No, Yesterland has some good pictures from the 90s, some good neon neon stuff.
That's my dad.
Those two like glass cases with like kind of loose squiggly neon side.
So cool.
I don't remember this mid 90 mid to late 90s.
Also a good time for arcade.
They've got the tiny first time crisis.
Of course, time crisis too is the preferable one.
It's got there's an area 51 next to it gauntlet legends.
That was another good one.
Good to play with people.
They have the Aerosmith game where you shot records at like aliens.
I wouldn't be surprised that there's a revolution X.
Is that what you're talking about?
Yeah, I, I, oh man, we got to maybe we should do it.
That was a revolution.
Well, we got to the Simpsons arcade.
Yeah, there are a lot of fake guns.
It's crazy to see.
I mean, there's still plenty of fake gun games in arcades, but it's crazy to think like, oh, this is the middle of Disneyland.
Oh, yeah, there's a with area 51 shooter rifle.
Oh yeah, that's true.
There is still a shooting gallery.
Yeah.
So some of them wouldn't start this now.
They wouldn't.
Well, yes, that's grandfathered in.
Yeah, at least for now.
I mean, who knows?
Maybe the best was different.
They needed them then.
Yeah, they had this dispose of their bottles and cans in some fashion and they only knew one solution for most of their problems.
Shoot it off.
Get a can off the fence.
Yeah.
Somebody on Reddit said their memory of of the starcade was sitting like standing around and watching kids play Mortal Kombat, which is very funny because people are like Mortal Kombat in Disneyland.
That is strange, which I believe the arcade cabinet.
You could turn the blood off.
Yeah.
Right.
But I think you could you would still be, you know, you're beating the shit out of somebody and then you could kill them.
It just wouldn't be bloody.
I guess nobody was like really maybe the starcade was kind of out of sight, out of mind.
Yeah.
Getting those getting those quarters.
Well, I think that that's come up a lot about that.
Like the 80s and 90s about the theme parks.
Like, yeah, corporate used to watch the theme parks a little less obsessively unless they were spending too much money or not earning enough money.
But like you would have odd little things or like stuff that would sneak through.
Yeah, this is like the thing I think I've said before.
I was watching an interview with Bob Newhart and he talked he talked about how it was better in Vegas when the mob ran everything because he's like before corporations came in, the mob was like, OK, these parts of the business could be doing less well, but we like it.
And like as long as we're bringing in money from one area, like we don't need to like have this obsessive need to maximize a profit, which is maybe ties back to what Bob Chapek is talking about, where it's like he's approaching all of it is just purely we need to make sure we're sucking everything in.
We need to make sure that every single person in the park dry for as much money as we can.
And we can't let a bunch of freeloading annual pass holders come in anymore.
I mean, that is a philosophy.
There's I'm not saying you're wrong.
I feel like there is so much shape back hatred on this.
I just don't I'm not I just haven't thought about it enough.
I have no strong feelings either way.
This is this is your like your blood is boiling.
What shape this a couple of days ago, there was a whole thing that came out.
There was an earnings call.
And he said all of this stuff, which really underlined.
And we'll see.
Maybe that maybe the reward program will be fine.
The rewards Disneyland program.
I think when we've taught, it seems like we were in agreement of like, well, I know passes will be back.
My personal theory is they will be back and that will cost three to four hundred dollars more than they used to at any level.
Theory.
Always a good theory.
Really good theory with anything.
Yeah.
Or any item in some cases.
But yeah, I don't know.
Yeah, I got to look into this loyalty thing more.
I think if you read the interview or whatever the recap, I think you'll go, I don't like the sound of this at all, because it's very the mobs all about loyalty.
And if things worked so well under mob rule, then this maybe this would be great.
I mean, I'm not saying I like the mob, but if the mob ran Disneyland, would it be better?
Maybe it might be great movie ride would come back.
Right.
These crime stoppers would go in.
Yeah, that's true.
There'd be a lot more mob related rides and attractions.
Yeah.
Bugsy could get a job.
All right.
Back, baby.
Yeah.
Well, what have we not said about?
Oh, you know what?
I know I don't remember in this 4am haze of getting to run up the ramp and see the mostly empty room.
I don't remember if this big facet of the Starcade was up there or not.
The X-wing, the huge X-wing up on the floor ceiling, which is a very frustrating part of seeing the next to the space on line.
You're looking in this room and like, and there's a X-wing up there and like there's a cool, like 70s looking mural.
I want to see better what that is.
And an X-wing that just no one gets to see except through tinted glass.
Well, some life insurance agents who are celebrating a very, very successful Q4 are going to get to see it.
If someone important is retiring, he can point up and say, what the hell is that thing?
The chancellor of like the Cal State system is retired.
Chancellor?
That is a term used in higher education.
I think that is a title.
That's funny.
That seems right.
Yeah.
But yeah, that was cool as hell that X-wing.
And I have to say this, this I've said this before maybe that, you know, like I'm not saying that the X-wings that have gone into Galaxy's Edge or the Quinjet are not cool, but they're built up so much.
The planes here.
Have you seen the plane?
There's a whole video just that's just shots of the plane.
And I'm still kind of like that there was an X-wing years ago with the Starcade that nobody.
Yeah.
Nobody got to see for a long time, but it was cool as hell in like 87 or 92 hung up there.
It is like, yeah, they took that.
Yeah, because there were there were a lot of like rumors flying around.
And I think they were legitimate that they like in Galaxy's Edge that we're going to have like ships coming like drones landing.
There was some like, you know, blue sky of that.
But in the ships aren't bad at that, like on the top of the buildings.
But they're great.
It's all this way hanging, I would say.
And I would say maybe even like the 80 80 outside of Star Tours in Florida is like even as cooler, cooler.
Well, yeah.
And the fake, yeah, the forest of Endor like outdoor queue.
So a lot of the various Star Tours queues have had X-wings also.
What I am not trying to take away from the X-wings that have recently gone in or the other planes have gone in.
They're very cool.
I just remember hearing a lot of buildup of like a menu around the corner.
There is an X-wing.
Right.
Well, yeah, those have been in the.
Yeah.
That's why that of like and there is really impressive.
Like, of course, Millennium Falcon is jaw dropping.
Yeah.
But I don't know.
No, hey, no, no.
Hey, I love.
No, but I know what you mean.
Like the bottle soda that looks like detonator look like grenades.
Like the that is something we haven't seen before.
Yeah, that's that's something new.
It's something different.
We are cocktails and weird bulbous glasses with weird fizzy ingredients.
That's a that's more of the surprise and delight angle where it's like, oh, yeah, I got this.
But I already know that.
Yeah, no, no.
I I hope there's bathrooms.
It's what needs to be there.
There's good.
I'm glad they put planes in.
Yeah, you have to.
Yeah.
Is it is it Poe's X-wing?
It is Poe's X-wing.
It's the black touches.
Poe's X-wing.
Well, I mean, love Poe, obviously.
The I love all three of them.
That's right.
Three different movies, three different pose.
Yeah, I guess made him woody.
Who would have thought millionaire spending years backstabbing each other would result in that?
Uh oh, those grapes are going to fill up again.
Oh, no.
Come on.
I had a nice time.
I saw them all opening weekend with my family.
We all had a nice time.
What more?
They got my money.
Some case I think I saw Force Awakens twice.
Yeah.
I was before.
That's a better joke.
I was just gonna say something about Poe knows.
No, no, no, no, no.
Anyway, anyway, I had to say it.
I had to get it like the itch scratch in my brain.
I'm sorry.
Poe knows quips.
He knows X-wings.
Hey, it was BB8.
Yeah, this literally.
Well, David Stalers, certainly that's one thing we do know about his character.
He knows BB8.
He does.
Well, he is.
He is.
BB8 is his droid.
That's right.
We have to think.
Everybody likes BB8.
Regardless of how you feel.
The BB8 like kind of has his own like adventures.
He doesn't want to be by Poe a lot.
I feel like I feel like he's always getting away from Poe.
It seems contentious.
Yeah, like they're growing apart.
They're changing.
You know, they're still friends, but you know.
I don't associate them really.
Yeah, it is.
I'm thinking about it now and I had to like double check my brain to make sure.
Yeah, that is his droid.
But it seems in some of it, it seems more like Raze.
But then he's friends with Finn too.
I put them together and you see them together at the end.
Right.
But then but then BB8 is with Finn and Rose in Last Jedi.
Yeah.
And not Poe.
But then BB8's on stage with Mark Hamill at the Oscars.
Making everybody laugh with beeps and poops.
Who's pet is BB8?
Is BB8, I guess, is with him in Nine.
Is he with them when they meet Babu Frick?
The only way I know is to watch all of them again.
Oh, I will.
I'll watch them all tomorrow.
Lindsay, Alice, Tabinon and Lindsay will come down and go like, why are you watching whatever, whether it's Attack of the Clones or whether it's like Rize the Skywalker.
She goes, why are you watching this again?
You just watch it.
I go, yes, I just I try to act like it was on.
She goes, yeah, but it's obviously Disney Plus.
It's not TBS.
You know, I do that with Diners, Drivers and Dives.
What's the House Hitters, House Hitters International where everyone's really insane.
I thought you said House Hinters and I was like that.
No, I can't remember the name.
I do that with the Late Shift.
That's the biggest one that Erin like, come on.
Lindsay hates that.
I don't know.
She's like, why do I don't want to watch the Late Shift again?
That's exactly where, boy, when the girls are away, the boys, Leno and Letterman, come to play.
You would think like we're watching some like some like swimsuit tape or something.
Some like 90s like, yeah, this is what we want to watch.
This is what guys like.
It's really the Late Shift.
Some anonymous actor, Brandon Tartakov.
He's in his manly watching made for TV movies again.
I'm sure they'd come around if they sat and watched the whole thing and to see that it's a movie about male late night hosts who are torn apart by a very mean woman.
That would make our wives enjoy the portrayal of this woman is like so horrible and unredeemable.
That's true.
Jay's manager, Helen Kushnick.
Helen Kushnick, of course we all know her name.
We all know the story.
Played by Kathy Bates, fantastically.
Great performance.
So first, they're across from the commissary.
We should have Betty Thomas.
We should ask to see if we can get Betty Thomas on.
I think we should just do a full break because Betty Thomas directed it.
I'd have to give some time to Brady Bunch movie too.
Oh man, Brady Bunch movie is so great.
She did High Spy, I think.
Owen Wilson, Eddie Murphy.
High Spy as well.
She has a very interesting career.
Second City, Betty Thomas.
They were talking about, you know, they were going to put Galaxy's Edge in the Paris Disney,
probably I believe the Studios Park because it always needs help.
And they because of COVID closures, they stopped construction.
And now Jim Hill seems to be alluding that like, well, the Mandalorian was such a big, you know, hit.
And people are so excited to see Boba Fett back in the mix.
And it's like maybe their Star Wars might be a little more like fluid there.
Like they might not do just a full faithful bit too.
They might have like a little of everything.
Like make it different.
It is bizarre that Disneyland and Disney World are the same thing.
Maybe like breeze through it in Disney World.
It's like, all right, I don't need to see.
I know what this is.
I think, yeah, we've talked about this enough times, I'm sure.
But yeah, like you want to have like, let's say Rey meeting Dexter Jettster somewhere.
Like, yeah, maybe that doesn't make sense in the timeline.
But yeah, come on.
That would be amazing.
Well, because they're doing that with the Marvel stuff, like each little Marvel pocket at all the parks.
Well, yeah, we've talked about that.
They're treating it like kind of like C because there's a Marvel cinematic universe and a Marvel theme park universe.
And all the different Marvel lands around the parks are like different home bases for the heroes.
Which is a better, it makes, you now need kind of a collect them all.
Yeah.
As opposed to the two identical.
Right.
So, yes.
So Dexter Jettster will only be in Anaheim.
And then, you know, you can have Babu Frick in Orlando.
The Pugas are a drinking game if there is one, like, if you were doing it with this episode, you'd be taking a lot of shots.
Because Dexter Jettster, we've got some Aerosmith in there, got some Late Shift in there.
Yeah.
A lot of greatest bits.
A little bit.
Grumblings about the new Disney.
Child, child, childhood eccentricities.
Well, that's the whole freaking show point.
Yeah, yeah.
You can't call that part of the drinking game or you'll drink for two straight hours.
Yeah.
Sometimes twice a week.
Look, folks, you know, it's nice to see people in person again outside of your individual households.
And we're a little excited.
Okay.
You know.
We don't know.
I don't have to apologize for my Aerosmith references.
All right.
I'll talk about Jaded.
I was just listening to it.
A mere hour ago.
You can't not.
If Jaded enters your brain, Jaded has to be said out loud.
The song Jaded is so good and it remains so good.
This is, I think, our dynamic in general.
We collected on Jaded.
Yeah, Jaded was pretty good.
I kind of stay there.
You go to one of the top 10 songs of all time.
It's like up there.
So your history is just Jaded and mine's just like Surrey with the fringe on top or Shabooby.
It's from the Music Man in Oklahoma.
The podcast, the ride, mixtape.
We got zero cents.
Oh, it'll be.
Yeah.
Could you do all of You Got Trouble for us right now?
No, that's so speaks.
Speaks.
I know.
But how much do you do?
I don't know if I could do a lot of that.
That is so dialogue heavy.
Okay.
Do you think maybe for another Patreon tier, you'd be willing to learn the whole thing?
You could perform it.
Seems worth fitting for like a live show.
There's suddenly a musical number.
Oh wow.
What a dynamic.
We've talked internally about a very musical type live show, perhaps.
So maybe that is the spot for it.
Get a bunch of guests to come back and do the full like 10 minute tableau from the end of 42nd Street.
Okay, that's possible too, but you're going to be doing…
We're going to make busy friends of ours stand around in a free musical.
And do some Panama because it's pretty much wordless, except like Ruby Keeler tap dances, you know.
So you don't have any lines, but when you step back and see the full effect, it is going to be quite the spectacle.
There should be an all encore for you where you do You Got Trouble and then Ladies Who Lunch.
Oh yeah.
And then into Shaboopi.
Well, that's the exit song.
Yeah, yeah.
Because they'll be like, all right, was this done yet?
And then Scott does 20 Beach Boys songs.
Solo.
The famous one part harmonies of the Beach Boys.
If you could find…
yeah, that's good.
If you could find one Beach Boy to back you up, even if they're not currently in the band and bring them on stage.
Oh yeah, well there's like 50 of those floating around.
So you could find somebody.
The Beach Boys are dime, dime's a dozen.
Somebody who Mike Love fired in 1995 or something.
He was playing like third percussion or whatever so he could back you up.
No, no, you missed that chime.
All right, Starrcade.
Starrcade.
There's not a lot on the internet folks.
What do you want from us?
People excited to hear this evidently, but then yeah, like people did a bad job of photographing this place.
At its height.
The Yesterland article is very good.
However, those photos are from like the 2000s.
I want to see this thing in 77.
I want to see how it's different from 83.
Hey, listener, if you have photos, please post them in response to our post about this.
I'd really love to see Starrcade at its height because it's boy, it's not really out there.
And the Tokyo one, because this was in Tokyo too, opened in 83 along with the park.
That thing must have looked fantastic.
And yet there is no right photograph other than the outside.
So what are we to do?
So much neon we're missing out on.
I believe the Tokyo one lasted till like 2007.
Like that lasted for a long time too.
So why wouldn't there be a picture of it?
Yeah, I didn't know.
Well, you just got to remember to take pictures of everything.
Yeah, because what doesn't seem special now could be gone someday.
I've gained a lot of perspective in this code area.
And I've I thought of deep thoughts like that one, like remember things before they pass pretty deep.
So you thought of the song Don't Know What You Got Till It's Gone independently.
I'm not familiar with his work.
I came to a completely on my own.
It sounds like you don't want to miss a thing, quite frankly.
And I agree with that sentiment for sure.
And I guess you could just say I'm just a little too cynical.
I don't know what that's.
Instead of Jay did it's like a swerve.
It was a swerve.
Oh man, Jason.
I have forgotten how to do comedy outside of podcasting.
I was like, here he comes.
He's going to top me.
Any favorites for like vintage, like old, old video games?
Did you guys have any favorites on the way out?
Arcade?
Like Frogger?
I was a big donkey.
If I saw Donkey Kong cabinet, I would always play.
Yeah, Popeye, obviously.
Oh yeah.
Popeye was similar to Donkey Kong where you'd go get spinach.
And I remember being so because you say obviously I don't know this.
Really, Jason?
Have you ever played?
I have once or twice.
It was basically very similar to a Donkey Kong structure of a game.
Like it was like you didn't side scroll or anything.
It was just the map and you try to like climb and defeat Bluto.
And there would be like spinach, spinach, like I feel like mid like on the corners of the screen or and then you would get that.
Then you would be like in the same way that maybe I'm completely wrong, but in Pac-Man you would get the big ball.
And then you would be like indestructible essentially for 10 seconds.
So it'd be the same as that.
And I really enjoyed that.
Yeah, the bucky-o-hair thing.
Great.
Centipede with the with the or with the thing that you spin spinning the ball.
Is it just a cool?
Oh, yeah, that's yeah, that was fun.
I guess I liked anything where the controls are are different, whether it's a weird cool gun or a weird cool like you're in a cockpit or I didn't play this growing up.
But what's the game with the beer where you've got the tap and you're you're filling up beer quickly as it's coming down.
That's oh, yeah, root beer.
Yeah, is that called?
Is it root beer oriented to get away from alcohol?
Because there was one where you made burgers to I burger time.
Tapper Tapper.
Root beer Tapper.
I don't think I've ever played root beer Tapper.
Is that the like that cool barcade in sort of like Silver Lake that I think is closed because of COVID has a lot of these things.
What a button mash.
Button mash.
Yeah, I think that's gone.
I hope I don't know if I'm wrong.
I that boy tough industry after all this.
I really hope I bark it would be a lot of fun to go to at this point and to that end talk about plus ups and stuff.
We're starting to get alcohol finally into Disneyland.
Starcade became a barcade.
Oh, yeah.
Drink and then play.
Just get the most basic old game.
Buy them out of hipsters garages.
Yeah, personal collection.
Yeah, the basics.
You don't have to go nuts.
Now I'd be I would spend time in there today.
The teenagers you you dipped.
You got their money in the 70s and 80s.
Guess what?
They're older now and they have more disposable income.
Double dip.
Get it again.
Put the same arcade games in.
But have a few Golden Road brews and those cut water spirits can cocktails and you can pick their pocket a second time.
You know, yeah, hey, I'll willingly have my pocket picked.
Yes, I you know, if they do a full I've been thinking about this more.
We talked about wanting to do an episode where we we fix Tomorrowland, which I think we should do.
Yeah, soon.
But yeah, if it's going to be a whole overhaul, yeah, get rid of the second level queue because again, we like being elevated and drinking and looking at the park.
That's better because you have the view of the right tomorrow.
And yes, so something like that where you have like, you know, a space cocktail and then a couple of beers or whatever like different as far as variety.
And then, yes, literally all you need is like 10 arcade machines.
It don't it doesn't have to be nuts.
Doesn't have to be.
Yeah, it's really more for ambiance than it is for actual like getting kids in or adults into play video games.
Yeah.
And if you have if it's a reservation thing like like it's like, yeah, fine.
That that actually seems to be working pretty well at this point.
Sure.
Like, yeah, yeah, I think so.
Would that be cool?
Yeah, we got to keep this little gap to know it's what people want more little bar in the park.
Yes.
So they're going to because what were we up to now?
We're up to blue Bayou serving and that's it for right now.
Items soon.
And it was so OK.
So they're slowly they have to, you know, phases here.
They can't do it all at once or else people would lose their mind, I guess.
I've been told by a Club 33 member that if you were on the exclusive Club 33 Facebook group, people are as mad as they are about anything on Facebook about
drinking in Disneyland, especially in the Blue Bayou, devaluing our membership.
We pay for that right that we get to drink.
And now they just give it away to the plebeians.
I mean, bully for them.
I'm so sorry.
You're 50 dollars.
That is just unbelievable.
Cry the Bohemian Grove.
Tell to someone who cares.
That is truly.
All the things to be mad about now.
Yeah.
What?
Oh, I'll tell you what it kind of made me mad thinking about Starcade, though.
And this will be my final thought.
And if anyone else has other ones, if you are taking if you are going on a family vacation, I know they're expensive.
But if the kids just want to play on the playground or go to the arcade, do not like Hemin Hall about it.
Like, do not go like I spent all this money and they're going to be in their arcade the whole time.
Like, I hate that.
I hate when I hear people do that because to me it seems like that.
Well, that's the kids equivalent of like sitting on the beach and smoking a cigar or like having a drink like that.
It's the same thing.
It's the same thing to kids like, you know, it's like you're going to have your cigar on your trip.
So let the kids.
But it's like I hate like it.
Do you know what I'm talking about?
This is saying where people like we spent all this money on this trip and you're just going to hang out at the hotel or it's like, well,
that aligns maybe how I felt like why we were here.
Why would we not?
We won the we read the books in order to get the pizzas that got us to the final Disneyland goal.
Why should we should be going on the right?
But I yeah, I mean, I'm sure.
Yeah, I would whenever I am doing vacations of this nature with my son.
Yeah, I will take that about.
You're right.
Because like it is Disney World and you got to do this, you got to do that and you got to do that.
But like it's a vacation too.
So if there's boy, let's take this stretch to, you know, just hang out at this restaurant or to do the little boats as you guys did in Disney World or or play video game.
Yeah.
Anything vacation should be on the table and a strict itinerary.
You got to have give and take.
If it's family vacation, everyone in the family should have their their say.
Yeah.
I think vacationing.
I think I think I'm a better vacationer because I'm a longtime annual pass holder.
I think being an annual pass holder made me an overall better vacationer in general because we've said this many times before.
If you talk to somebody who doesn't go to these places a lot and you go, yeah, I go to this.
I got to pass Disneyland.
Some people will look at you like you're out of your mind.
And it's because they went their parents found it unpleasant because they were probably running and gunning, trying to do everything.
And it was very stressful.
And now they're imagining as an adult, this is going to be a nightmare.
Why would I want to do that if I didn't have kids, especially if I didn't have kids?
So I think that the leisurely because I we've converted people, Jason and I, at least people that are skeptics.
And I said, you know what you got to do?
You come down, you party with Jason and I and you're going to turn it around.
This is very mobish of you come to what you're going to do.
What you can do with us.
First off, you got to agree to a merita.
It's got the code of sight.
No, you can tell anyone about this.
What would your mob name be?
Like what was the root beer game called?
Root beer tapper?
Yeah, that's not good.
Root beer tapper.
Root beer Jason, maybe.
What would Jason's mob name be?
He's the root beer tapper.
Yeah, that's true.
Milk carton.
Probably just like.
Milk carton Mickey.
Yeah, you come down to Disney with milk carton Mickey and I.
We'll show you a good time.
You just want to play arcade games, don't go on the rights?
They got arcade games right here.
We're not going to break your balls about that.
Go to the arcade, I don't care.
Will you make the day your own?
You can just jump right ahead of the line.
What's the deal with it?
You got to know me to know about it.
Milk carton Mickey and his tall friend.
Oh, it's so fun to see the milk carton Mickey's walking around in their denim cuts back in the day.
They can't be happy about this alcohol thing.
Well, that's true.
They're pissed.
My closing thought is that the floor is like orange tiles.
That like orange brick kind of vibe that like all the best malls still have and they disappear more.
We're losing the orange bricks more and more by the year, folks.
And you hate to see it.
They're taking the orange bricks out and we got to keep it.
We got to keep the orange bricks.
I don't know why I went into that tone.
I know.
Organically.
I'd like to not be reminded.
What you were saying is right, but.
You're hearing it more and more.
And they're doing it and we're not loving it.
We don't like it.
And that's why we have to stop it.
That's insane to equate these things.
Preserving our orange bricks is important.
More important than having that statue garden that apparently Biden stopped.
Do you remember that?
I did hear about that.
We're never as mad about monuments coming down and Trump's like fine, how about a thing with 300 monuments?
That's one of the best Biden moves so far.
Like what?
No.
Why?
You think we're not going to get to see the statue of Lawrence Welk next to the American sniper?
What the hell?
You'll take that Lawrence Welk statue though.
I will take that.
If that's on eBay.
I want to see how they can cast bubbles in copper.
My closing thought.
You know what, that eBay real quick, I do want to mention this about the experience.
The tokens.
Because.
Because tokens were always, you know, tokens, you know, in the age of Bitcoin converting money and stuff, the original Bitcoin were tokens at different places.
Like that was a different way to convert your money.
That's, you know, they have things called stable coins now where our digital currency that are that stay, they don't appreciate or depreciate in value.
But tokens were, I believe the stable coins, you could think of them that way.
And Chuck E.
G's would have their own token.
And the Starcade would have its own token as well.
And you can buy them on eBay and they look cool as hell.
That does look very cool.
Cool font.
Good logo.
That's it.
We haven't said that enough.
Because yeah, awesome logo.
And you know, it's a thing to say that that sign, even though the Starcade has gone in and out of like sometimes there's photo ops there, sometimes they just becomes merch and they haphazardly toss two games in.
Maybe they aren't even good, they don't care.
They've stopped really curating an arcade there.
And yet the sign remains.
Yes, I wasn't even sure in 2021 post pandemic if the sign was still there.
I asked my friends, Tyler and Kia, that neon sign still there.
They said, yes, shine and bright and beautiful as ever.
We love to see it.
No, we can't edit all that out.
I'm going to edit that part out of the show.
And that and that is one of the predictions Tomorrowland inadvertently made about the future, the modern world we live in.
Like Tomorrowland is filled with remnants of closed detractions or defunct technology.
We all live in homes filled with like useless crap.
Like phones or old gadgets or old DVD players.
It's like, well, inadvertently, Tomorrowland was right.
We will be surrounded by the remnants of like digital camera, like technology that was the height of technology.
Swimming up to your ears in old broken phones and cameras.
I have a box or two of like, do I need a micro cassette recorder anymore?
Like, why do I have these?
No, you can get rid of them.
It's not impossible.
I know.
Got milk cartons full of.
I don't think I'm wrong.
You meant milk crates too, right?
You meant milk crates, not cartons, right?
Whatever the plastic things that like quarts of milk come in.
Crates, I think.
I guess crates are right.
Wouldn't be the box because the carton is the bottle, which you would just step on and just collapse.
Yeah.
Okay.
Crates, milk crates, milk, crate, Mickey, milk, crate, crate, crate, crate, Mickey.
Yeah.
Milk carton, Mickey's a different guy.
Come over here, buddy.
Bring that milk crate so I can look in the eye.
See milk carton.
Mickey is two feet tall.
He's small.
Well, I think we did it.
I think we survived podcast the second gate.
We did.
Thanks to Mike and to milk crate Mickey for as always for all the laughs.
Stay tuned here to podcast the second gate for three bonus episodes every month.
And we didn't acknowledge it really.
This is the first time in what 14, 15 months that we recorded in our usual place in Mike's apartment.
We just sort of dove in and we weren't even sure we were going to do it here.
Like, I think I thought about that a lot during the time.
Like, what's it going to be like to be back?
And that means that for me, the first sighting of Edwin.
Oh, yeah.
We're back with Edwin.
The core components of Sleeping Edwin are finally back on the show.
So, yeah, we are in.
We are inside right now.
Again, we're going to switch now.
We're very mobile.
We'll be outside.
Make sure you have a read.
Yeah, I don't even know.
Yeah.
Yeah, exactly.
Oh, my God.
Maybe we'll record an episode while we walk around City Walk.
I don't know.
Go to the park.
Maybe we'll go to Galaxy's Edge and record in Galaxy's Edge.
Wait, we've done that before.
We haven't done that.
No, no, this is a new, it is a great, innovative way.
We're going to sit down.
Now, I'm sure a lot of people are going to want that a lot.
All right.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
OK.
The listeners are waiting for you to say the catchphrase,
like everybody looking at Bart saying, I didn't do it.
Because you were against this.
That's what I was going for.
Oh, right.
I'll counterpoint you're wrong.
I don't know.
Now, say it like Milk Crate Mickey would say it.
Counterpoint, you're wrong.
Wow.
And you're going to die.
No, Milk Crate Mickey.
No, don't do it to me.
No.
OK, bye.