Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast contains a limited use sword, lazy toy name creation,
a confusing circus, and an arena show that's 5% action and 95% religious service.
Griffin Newman returns to talk the Masters of the Universe power tour on today's podcast,
The Ride.
Welcome to our universe podcast, The Ride universe.
It's podcast The Ride everybody.
I'm Scott Gardner joined back in the Zoomiverse by Jason Sheridan.
That's right.
Thank you.
Oh yeah, well we're going to get into that.
I mean, why not just get that off, right?
You know, the audience might not know that song yet, but you will and you'll love it.
It'll rise to the top of your personal charts.
Mike Carlson, hello.
Hi, I'm here.
Yes, I was watching our topic today and I was thinking we need actually some sort of
pledge of allegiance to our podcast that we need to develop.
And I don't want to do it right now because we have a lot to get to, but I just want to
put that in the air that we need to figure something out to make sure that all the Cliffords
out there pledge their allegiance to us.
We need to do that.
So anyway, not enough nationalism in comedy podcast, podcast nationalism is that the name
for it?
It's just proud.
I'm just proud.
You know, I guess I'm just proud.
You know, podcast the lism.
Is that is that?
No, that's not good.
Does this imply that they can only listen to our podcast or that they just have to like
always listen to it?
Like that's unfair.
It depends.
I don't know.
It depends how we write the song, honestly.
How we write the pledge.
All right.
Well, it also just that if you can only listen to our podcast, then that cuts out people
like our guests with their own podcasts.
And I would hate to because because look, we're everybody's supposed to get along unless
we start getting more militaristic about this.
Choose a side, I say.
Come on.
OK, but until the anthem is in place, then you are welcome to podcast hop.
You could listen to a blank check.
A great podcast that our guest today comes from.
Well, here, let me say this.
That today's topic is the Masters of the Universe Power Tour, which was the live
touring theatrical spectacle that's that supported He-Man and She-Ra in 1987.
Sort of they're coming out of our shells tour, which is how our guests today
presented it. And our guest is the voice of Orko on the new series Masters of the
Universe Revelation, which premieres on Netflix today.
As you are listening to this, it is accidental PTR legend Griffin Newman.
Hi. Hello. Hello. Accidental PTR legend.
Still my greatest credit.
I always ask to be introduced that way on other podcasts and they refuse.
I do want to say right off the bat, Scott, we've been we've been emailing back and
forth for some months now.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, yeah.
Some delays. Yeah, I've had some correspondence with with Jason and Mike over
the pandemic as well for different subjects or different issues.
What was the thing, Jason, that you were asking me to weigh in on in real time
during a recording? Oh, oh, it was Shrek shaped fun nuggets with swamp pudding.
Right, right. It was the Shrek fucking meal, which is revolting.
And then Mike and I, of course, messaged back and forth about our struggles to
successfully preorder action figures, but also looking into the numbers of how
much it would cost for us to produce a run of toys based on our respective
podcast. Oh, you're in that game as well.
Oh, my God. I mean, Mike's doing the heavy lifting, but I'm constantly sort of
trying to compare notes with him. Yeah, I think it's doable.
I do think it's doable.
And probably next year, I think maybe we could shoot for some motivation.
Yeah, I have a thought, a possible lead that I want to bring up with you after
we're finished recording.
So I'll just I'll leave that dangling thread here.
But but Scott, you and I have messaged back and forth mostly about what matters.
Podcast the ride, the most important thing in the world.
That's a pledge of allegiance.
Yes. And I don't remember if you emailed about something else or I emailed first
because of this, but the chain quickly became me sort of saying, look, I really
feel like I let down podcast the ride listeners in 2020.
And I know it was a hard year.
Oh, I know it was a hard year for all of us.
I know why I was not up to the challenge.
You know, I went through my struggles and what have you.
Well, I don't know. But you're on the show.
You were on the show behind the paywall.
Is that what feels weird?
It was just feels weird.
Because there's that thing where the listeners did their vote on best episode
and best this and best that.
And I got voted best guest.
And I only did one episode.
I only did one appearance, whereas the previous year I did three appearances in one year.
I only did one appearance in 2020 and it was a paywall only.
I know it was a long episode.
I know it broke the record and made Jason break out into flop sweat.
But I remember I needed to urinate so badly.
We we might have to plan on a break in this.
Absolutely. We have to be smarter this time.
But I just felt like I didn't do enough.
And I would see certain episodes and topics come up and go,
maybe I should have thrown my hat in the ring for that.
Maybe I should be suggesting more.
Maybe I should this. Maybe I should that.
I felt bad about it.
So I reached out to you and I said, I want to put three things on the book.
I want to commit to coming back.
Twenty twenty one main feed and second gate with a vengeance.
And the first one, I don't know if we want to spoil stuff,
but there was a ride that had been talked about derisively on the show.
And you guys had said, we'll probably never do an episode on that.
And I emailed you and I said, I would like to do that episode.
Can we put that on the books?
The second thing, which I do want to announce here. Yes.
I said Muppet Haunted Mansion, that's mine.
Very good. OK, people are going to be really happy about that.
I feel like I need to tease that the ride we can keep secret for now.
Wait, it's a ride talked about derisively.
I is it not to me and I don't think I would have did we or did others?
I've been listening to the show on on a big delay
in the pandemic.
I got way behind all my podcasts.
And so I've been that I feel like also to you, Scott,
I've been that annoying fan who like emails you about things
you said nine months ago that you no longer remember.
I made a joke about how are your two sons doing?
And you said, I only have one son.
And I said, what do you mean?
Eight months ago, you made a joke about Rex being your first son.
How could you not immediately recall that?
Yeah, I thought it was a reference to two hours ago.
Yeah, yeah, I thought it was it was phrased such that it was like a
that he's like not a baby anymore, that some so much time has flown.
I was like, OK, that must be what it is.
Yeah, I think, yeah, we have dropped the Rex as my son thread.
Look, I thoroughly I didn't learn the joke.
And this is what I'm talking about.
I've been letting everyone down as a podcast.
The right legend. The emails have been sloppy.
Too few appearances.
No bathroom breaks in the Fallon episode.
These are all problems that I want to rectify.
But in an episode I was listening to, I think that is what caused me
to email you in the first place.
You guys were like, we'll probably never do an episode on that.
You kind of shrugged at this ride and said, like,
we never have to do an episode on that.
Wait a minute. Are we talking about the right thing?
I'm confused, by the way. I'm confused.
Wait, can we just say what it is and then cut it?
Say what it is? Yeah, yeah, we will believe what it is.
Wait, of course we would do an episode.
What do you mean?
Wait, you have a zoom background that's fighting.
It's getting blurred. It's getting blurred out.
It's still a secret.
I'm trying to in the zoom background.
We all that's that's the thing we all think we're talking about.
Yeah, of course we would do an episode on that.
What are you talking about?
When did we say that? Who was derisive on it?
Was it one of us?
I'm telling you, there's an episode where the three of you say
we never have to do an episode.
No, it can't be.
There's got to be confusion there.
I'm going to ask the listeners to go back and find it.
But that's what motivated me to send the email in the first place.
Were you watching a different podcast?
Were you listening to Jim and Len and like Len said that ride sucks?
The bumper car boys.
Yeah, they'd hate that.
Bumper car boys would hate it.
I'm telling you, I just know that's why I sent the email because I was like,
concerned about it.
You're sort of like, maybe we don't maybe we don't ever do an episode on it.
Is it not necessary?
I truly cannot imagine.
Was it a bit were we being was our bit not clear?
It was the pandemic. We were all losing our minds.
The point is.
Yeah, I can't.
But now it's pandemic two and we feel so much better
because we've had practice.
We're all pros at this.
At this point, we know how to handle it.
But yes, but then things shifted around.
I was having health problems.
You had a job, Scott.
And I said, like, the third thing I'd like to do is when the He-Man show is coming out,
do you guys know that there was a He-Man equivalent coming out of our shells tour?
And it feels like it's right in your guys wheelhouse.
And so absolutely.
And I you guys, Mike and Jason, tell me your thoughts on this.
I I had never heard of this.
I didn't know this existed.
You brought a totally new thing, at least to my attention.
I I I may have found out about it like a month before we put this on the books.
I was not this is not something I've lived with for very long.
I feel like some account that we probably both follow, Mike,
one random day started tweeting out a bunch of photos from like the the playbill.
Like the big full color photos of the costumes.
Like I remember they were circulating around Twitter around the time.
Yes. Message Scott, which had sort of activated my mind like, oh, this
this might be a PTR subject.
Yeah. Do you think it was one of our toy accounts, one of our toy Twitter accounts?
I think it was. I think it was a preternia or something.
Perturnia, Toy Bro, I was going to say Pixel Dan.
Did he tweet about it?
Look, I think Pixel Dan might have retweeted it,
but I think if Pixel Dan was the one uploading the photos, I would have remembered.
And I don't say that as any slight to preternia or Toy Bro.
But I think of Pixel Dan as the preeminent sort of like
Motu, obscura scholar.
You know, I agree.
Wasn't it was impossible to that?
Possible. Yeah, it was possible.
Pete Scott, that is not funny.
Yeah, not funny.
All right. It's not.
I know. When it's regular, when it's theme park stuff,
I could do it. This I got to know when I'm not wanted.
Would be very upset to hear you just wantonly making up fake toy YouTuber names.
Mike just muted his zoom window and threw a folding chair like Bobby Knight.
How do I do a podcast with this guy?
I don't get that. I don't get that reference, Jason.
I did. I get the name wrong.
The coach. No, no, I did. I'm saying I'm a toy guy.
I don't know. You're a toy guy. Oh, I see.
Yeah. I call it sports.
I think I saw.
Yeah, something like what you guys are saying, like it was tweeted or like
he man collage of stuff of like different like, oh, remember him?
Like a nostalgia account and like showed a quick flash of like this show.
My my he man.
I was very into he man as I was learning object permanence.
Like I caught the tail end in the late 80s.
I caught the tail end.
My real passion for he man, I believe, was the
reboot that was called The New Adventures of He-Man, which was noticeable
because he wolf wore full pants.
And I had this toy sword, which was great.
But I just can I can I read, Jason, your notes?
You just shared your notes so you could show the picture of the sword you had
and your notes for our 1990 show.
It was awesome.
This was the one where he man wore it.
Yes. And then I saw this plastic sword on the ground.
And I specifically owned I specifically owned this sword.
So I'm looking for it.
I didn't share it. It wasn't a co-op thing.
Could we publish your notes for Patreon subscribers?
No, but they're all they're all like me writing out thoughts I've had.
Like it's it's it's. Yeah.
Really? Yeah.
Very good. The formatting is funny.
The formatting is insane because sometimes they use dashes, sometimes they use
nothing, sometimes they use the Apple Notes bubble.
I have like five gigabytes in Apple Notes of just mostly notes for the show.
Will you allow me to have access to those and pick out the ones I think that are
the best? Absolutely not.
No, these have to be they have to be public record.
We know the people are given the pledge and at this point they owe.
They should be able to peruse the Jason Sheridan Library.
I agree. For the right price, for the right.
Well, now we're talking.
We will we will certainly be digging into this because this is the interesting
context to this show is that like I think this show was sort of supposed to be a
victory lap for them timed out around the same time as the movie, which they
thought was going to be this big brand rejuvenator.
And then this show ended up being like a death rattle.
Like this was the last successful thing to come out of He-Man.
And it was very successful at a time that the rest of the brand was like plummeting.
Like sales were down, the movie bombed.
And then the New Adventures of He-Man was their hail Mary pass.
They were going to do a show called Hero that was going to be like a prequel
show about He-Man's ancestor and like an earlier person who had held the power.
And then there was an alternate pitch at one point where Hero was going to be
He-Man's son.
But the first hero show was going to be set in pre-Eternia, so there were going to
be dinosaurs in it.
And that was their big business like thing was like, this is how we're going to
save He-Man. We're going to put dinosaurs in the toy line.
Now it's new characters, so the kids have to rebuy all the heroes and villains and
they're all riding dinosaurs and the dinosaurs are going to be huge and
expensive. And I think they were trying to sort of get in on like the G.I.
Joe vehicle playset money of just like constant huge dinosaur toys.
But then New Adventures was like the like, fuck, this is plummeting so fast we
need to do like a huge pivot, go steer totally out of the like the barbarian
swords and castles shit and go into space and just fight fucking Star Wars.
But they were fighting Star Wars like 10 years too late.
And that show was a huge flop, except as I know, because I've spent the pandemic
watching too many videos by former Masters of the Universe brand manager at
Mattel, Scott Knightlick and his new channel.
That sword was like the best selling thing Mattel produced that year and the
rest of the line bombed like everyone bought that fucking sword.
So no one watched the cartoon show.
So the one that Jason showed the picture of that sword was like a huge seller
specifically. And then no one watched the show.
No one bought the figures. Every kid I knew had that yet had that sword.
I played with it so much and it was pretty solidly made except the blade,
because eventually the blade just snapped off.
And then I just had a handle with a tiny light bulb sticking out of it.
So it was made great except for the sword part.
I somehow never managed to break that tiny light bulb.
It's a miracle.
Wow. It's like a Hanukkah miracle.
Yeah, it's it's fascinating.
There's that Netflix documentary I watched recently, The Power of Grayskull,
that has a lot of that history in it.
And it is fascinating. Maybe I even talked about it on one of the episodes we've
done recently about just watching a bunch of guys go, I don't know, it's Skull.
And they want to call it whatever you want. Grayskull.
OK, great. Like nobody gave a shit about it.
But then they were all trying to strategically just figure out how to keep
this thing going. And yes, they were.
There were like there were some toy people that were like, we weren't even that
creative. We threw it to somebody else and then they gave us a better idea.
There's a guy who was really like down on all his ideas from that worked on the
toy line initially. I forget his name in the documentary.
There there is that documentary is worth watching on Netflix.
There's also The Toys That Made Us episode about Master of the Universe.
That's a really good kind of more condensed version of it.
But like I am a huge Masters of the Universe fan.
Like it sort of is to me what I would argue may be what Ninja Turtles is to you.
And similarly in lockdown, my collection has gotten out of control.
It just became my large overarching obsession.
But I like actively, actively sought out and fought to play Orko
on this show, perhaps more than any other job in my entire career.
Like I was just like very single mindedly focused on like I love He-Man.
There's a new show. I want to be part of it.
Orko is the character I want to play partially because I feel like Orko is
very divisive and people either like love him and they were like,
that was my favorite fucking character when I was a kid.
I dressed up as Orko. Orko was the funniest.
I rooted for him. Or people like hate Orko.
He's like 50 percent Jar Jar, 50 percent Chewbacca.
Like there's like no middle ground.
And I just felt like there are a lot of easy ways that someone could sort of
sell Orko up the river, you know, that you could kind of like make him into a joke,
whereas he is the comic relief character and he should be like silly and fun.
I didn't want it to be like a like Scrappy Doo thing, you know, like in the in
the Scooby Doo movie where you have to sort of like reframe him as like, oh, well,
we all hate him. And I also got bummed out at the idea
of some famous person just doing it because they were offered it.
Oh, sure. And not knowing it or just doing it as themselves and not like making a new
Orko as in an actorly way.
And he's got a very fucking specific voice, which I'll get into.
Maybe not here, but I was very protective of all this shit.
My mind as a fan, I was like, I really want to be the one to do it.
And I was working like 18 different angles to get cast on this show.
Like I had friends in the writers room.
I found out the Netflix executive had an Instagram account that was just action
figure photography. So I started like following him and liking his
posts until he followed me back.
And then I like slid to DMS and then was like, I'm going to be in L.A.
I'd love to have like a general meeting and then just sort of talked about how big
a fan I was of Motu and then ended by being like, by the way, I just sent it
in tape for Orko, but like just wanted to prove to him my bona fides.
But I was like, I fucking know this shit.
I like far too well.
So I really I really worked really
aggressively for it and have been working on the show for like
a year and a half now, and now it's finally about to come out.
Animations just like so such a long drawn out process.
But needless to say, I
my first record was like right before the pandemic.
It was maybe like end of February.
It won weird at home one minute.
I had one. I actually I got lucky.
I was able to do all of them in studio.
I did most of my work.
I did I did like a real marathon session, most of the episodes in February
in person in a studio.
And then they sort of put everything on pause, started just animating everything
they had because the season is going to come out in two chunks.
What is dropping today when this episode
has come out is the first five episodes and there's another five that are almost
finished that I don't know when they're going to announce when those are coming
out, but within this year, so they focused on the ones that they had totally in the
can and then when I had to go back and record more, it was when things were
a little less scary, at least numbers had dipped in New York.
And like I was terrified about being on a set, but being in a hermetically sealed
recording booth felt as safe as any type of performance could possibly be.
That's pretty ideal.
You barely do like meet anyone on the way in.
Do that kind of thing. Right.
Right. And like everyone's directing over Zoom anyway.
So, yeah, I was able to do all that in studio, which was great because like doing
shit from home doesn't feel professional.
It's very hard to feel like you're doing a job.
And there's no pump up.
There's no like the commute where you think about it and what could go wrong,
but what could go right and how do it like sort of talking yourself up and then
you're in a place and you perform.
Right. You lose that.
And you also gain a thing I'm sure you guys can relate to the added stress of am I
fucking this up on a technical level at every single moment, just like checking to
make sure everything's plugged in correctly because it's like, oh, I have to be
my own engineer is now well as well.
Add distracting.
Yes. Yeah.
Which I had to do for some other voiceover things.
I was very happy that I got to do or go like all those sessions in studio in a
normal way, not rushed with the animators and Kevin Smith, the showrunner and the
voice director and everyone like on and sort of guiding me through stuff.
I think the show is going to be really good.
I'm really proud of it.
And hopefully people are liking it now.
But all this to say,
my love of He-Man stems from I'm a little younger than you guys.
And as Jason said, like generationally,
that's when he man is just petering out. Right.
So most of my He-Man toys came from garage sales.
Right. Like my object permanence phase comes
in when he man is like done, when, you know, like the new adventures is bombing out.
And I was a big nerd kid and like just never stopped collecting action figures
and was obsessed with comic book stores and everything there.
And every other, I feel like 80s kids property still existed in some form into
the 90s. Right. Like there were evolutionary changes.
But like Transformers is still in the ecosystem.
It might be Beast Wars now, but Transformers still exists.
You know, like G.I. Joe is going through
reinventions, but G.I. Joe still exists.
He-Man was just nowhere for like 10 years.
It was just like memory hold.
It was gone.
There was just like no media.
There was no retail presence.
There was no nothing.
And I would read this magazine, Toy Fair magazine that was like the big action
figure magazine, and they would talk about He-Man all the time.
And I'd be like, what's this reference I don't get?
Like I was very much a kid where I was
trying to understand what the nerds 10 years older than me liked.
So I could like be in the club and make the jokes.
And I was so confused by the fact that there was no,
like, cultural presence for He-Man outside of this one magazine that was weirdly
still obsessed with it. They would be in like cartoon.
Toy Fair would have like these like jokey
cartoons, which honestly felt like the precursor to Robot Chicken to me.
It was Toy Fair Theater.
Yes. Most of the writers and creators.
OK, yeah. It was Twisted Migo.
And then they changed it to Twisted Toy Fair at a later point because of copyright
shit, I think. So both of you are.
Both right. Jason and I, both right.
Great. But no, but literally the creators
and original writers of Robot Chicken are largely guys who wrote that.
Yeah. With Seth Green.
Yeah, that makes sense to me.
It's the direct precursor.
And it was this toy magazine that had like a sense of humor.
And they would put Skeletor and He-Man in their comics.
But they would also just like write them up as like, oh, these are the big ones.
You know, it's like Duke and Snake Eyes and Lion-O and He-Man, you know, like
that's their sort of like Mount Rushmore for like 80s kids who grew up with the,
you know, fighting action figures.
So it was when I went to summer camp and there was a kid who was older than me,
who was obsessed with He-Man, who started like telling me about it.
And then I got really into it.
And then there was a relaunch in 2002 where they did a new modern He-Man show
that was on Cartoon Network.
And I was like 13 or 14 at that time and then got super into He-Man.
A children's property from the 80s.
It was a great, very cool time for me to suddenly be all in on this thing
where everyone was like, you're obsessed with a cartoon show from before we were
little that none of us remember that is now rebooted for current day children.
Like, why can't you exist in your own time?
Why are you like simultaneously older and younger than you should be?
Hey, man,
it pretty much guaranteed you became a podcast.
Like how if you survey podcasters, how many could be described in that way?
It's the unconscious training for the media landscape we now live in.
I feel like Thundercats kind of fell into this memory hole too and then got rebooted later.
My exposure to a lot of this stuff, there was a run, there was period in time
kind of related to the comic book boom, kind of related to like action figures
just becoming big business when people would open quote unquote collectible
stores and it was mostly just like junky old toys.
Some still in boxes, some not in boxes.
The handful of comic books.
If you could rent a retail space and you
could get a bunch of this shit, some of it's probably your own collection
you're selling like that was that was where I would find some of this stuff.
Like, especially in South Jersey, this caught on.
And my family is like, we want to go to the beach.
And I was like, I want to go to this dank
basement where someone sells dusty old toys, please.
Absolutely. Yeah.
And like if you're seeing human toys at like a flea market or collectible store or
whatever, they truly looked unlike any other action figures.
Like they they just as they say, their whole thing was like this was Mattel
trying to fight with Star Wars first wave, right?
Like, you know, early 80s going like we passed on Star Wars.
Kenner has just been making hundreds and
hundreds of millions of dollars with these things.
Now Hasbro has rebooted G.I. Joe.
I mean, I began my timeline wrong.
I don't know if that's right before or right after, but it's like they had their
sort of famous boys property that they were able to relaunch and make smaller
and build into vehicles and new cartoon show and all that shit.
Mattel was like, we need to own something.
And this is what as I've gotten older,
I've come to love more and more about him and is sort of what Mike was talking
about, where it's like it's a boardroom of people trying to solve the equation of
how do you make something that every single kid would find cool?
And it's just like these cynical guys like chain smoking, throwing every idea
at the wall, and then at some point someone comes in and goes like,
what if it's just all of them at the same time?
And it's sort of just like this this jambalaya of all of it, of just like sci fi
and fantasy and barbarianism and monsters and robots and like everything
with this mythology that is like so thinly sketched out names that are like
established within like five minutes in the back of a napkin when someone's
taking a shit and then it gets passed around to all these different mediums
and all of them start trying to actually make something out of it.
So like, you know, there's no media to support it when it comes out.
They go in and pitch it and Toys R Us is like, how will this is cool?
But like, how will kids know any of these characters?
And they're like, oh, because of the comic books.
And they were like, what kind of books and like their comic books inside
the packaging and they're like, oh, good idea.
OK, we'll order like 10,000 of them.
And they walk out and the one junior Mattel guy says to the other guy,
like, what kind of books?
Because I don't know, that's your job to fucking figure it out.
Now,
well, I was just saying some shit, but now that's your purview.
We have no budget. Make comic books.
And so they started like hiring these guys who are like science fiction
novelists to write these comic books that came inside the action figures,
which were starting to establish the mythology, which then when the toys get
big, they do a cartoon show, the cartoon show almost immediately negates 50%
of what is in the comic books that come with the toys.
And then they're like DC Comics.
You should do some comic books, too.
And the DC Comics, that maybe comes before the cartoon show.
But DC Comics creates a bunch of new things that negate that.
So you already have like the DC Comics are different from the comics that come
with the toys are different from the cartoon show.
And there are shared elements, but there are areas in which they totally bump up
against each other.
And then the movie comes out.
It's its own fucking thing.
When they reboot, it's its own fucking thing.
Modern comics are their own fucking thing.
There's a modern toy line from the late 2000s into the 2010s that establish its
own mythology that was trying to reconcile everything and weirdly power
tour, I would argue, is one of the first times they kind of cleanly laid everything
out and presented a somewhat definitive story that tracked.
They took all of the mythology and they because this is what happens actually now,
I feel like, because like Turtles is the same way where there's like 15 different
timelines you can go back.
So when you're making a new version of it, you literally just have to pick and choose
and try to make something like cleaner out of a bunch of just like haphazard
decisions people make.
Is there like, I don't know, this got thrown on my desk today.
I have no affection for it because it's new.
Who gives a shit?
And then 20 years later, people with actual affection are like, here's how it
actually happened.
Here's what I think is actually the true can.
Because I have that with Turtles.
I know what I think is real and what's not like I get.
Right.
So this is the cleanest version, you're saying, of Masters in the old days.
Way. Yes.
In that early days, because like what you're saying with Turtles, it's like
everyone every time they relaunched it, someone kind of came in with a new thing.
Right.
Whatever the creative team is, whoever was on top, they sort of like, well, this time
we're going more cartoon, more serious, more like the comics, less like the comics
or whatever. He man, it was like four things right out of the gate that all
clashed with each other that like didn't make sense.
And there's even stuff where like the paintings on the back of the packaging
for the original He-Man toys, half of them look nothing like the characters.
Like they made prototypes, they painted
the prototypes and then they changed the look of the characters.
And then when those characters showed up in the cartoon show, they had a third
different design and in the comics, they had different colors.
Like it was just such a mess.
It was so disorganized, but there's weird magic that comes out of that.
Like it's an interesting counter to like a George Lucas Star Wars universe
that is very specifically crafted and it's the vision of one guy.
And then watching like 200 people try to replicate that and not really talking
to each other, there have been so many lawsuits with guys who claim like, no,
I was the creator of He-Man because there are like 10 different guys who can say
like, well, I'm the creator of He-Man because I built the model.
But like I came up with the name He-Man, but I came up with this part of the
mythology. Well, I have the idea to do a toy line that was like this.
You know, they looked at these like Star Wars action figures and they were like,
these are small and wimpy and they just put clay on top of it and as much muscle
as they possibly could. And the He-Man toys.
And this is like when Arnold is starting
to get big and Schwarzenegger is presenting this like new body type.
And they were like, just go for that.
Just like absurd muscles upon muscles, you know.
What's the timeline with Conan the barbarian?
Like in terms of affecting and influencing this or they sort of separate,
but then interweave at some point. Great question.
A lot of controversy in this era.
There is a rumor that Mattel
had the license for Conan toys.
Started producing them, then found out the movie was going to be rated R,
realized it was not a child friendly property, took the prototypes they had
made and made them He-Man instead, that they were actually supposed to be
Arnold's sculpts. That has been disputed by a lot of people,
that the timeline doesn't work out, that there was one meeting taken,
but that didn't really line up and that this was already in development.
When He-Man was originally created,
the muscle thing was a big thing because they were trying to like big dog the
Star Wars toys. That was the big thing, was that all the Star Wars toys had that
like kind of like straight arms, straight legs, kind of very vanilla posing.
We're all very skinny to fit in vehicles.
And they like all the He-Man toys are in this crouch and their arms are bent,
their knees are bent.
They sort of look bad already.
And they just have like grotesque amount of muscles.
It's rock and wrestling time, too.
It's Hulk Hogan.
It's so like kids are just kids are desiring a jacked guy.
They want a toy of a jacked guy now.
Yeah. And the original idea for He-Man,
there was this character that Mattel had in the 70s named Big Jim,
who was like their competitor to G.I. Joe.
Hold on.
You follow up questions?
Yeah.
Now I just want to know about Big Jim.
Oh, I'm about to tell you.
Oh, please.
Big Jim was like their answer to G.I. Joe, where it was like, oh, this is like a 12
inch, like handsome built brunette man
doll with removable outfits.
And he could be anything.
Like hair is nuts.
Or sometimes he has this like helmet hair.
It's crazy.
This is the thing. Big Jim, they were just like, he's just like a blank slate.
And he can be an astronaut if we want,
or he can be a fucking like the six million dollar man or a secret spy.
Yeah. Or a lifeguard.
So he's the next generation of Action Man.
Yes.
Action Man was a very similar like kind of a thunder, kind of had a thunderbird sort
of outfit, but yeah, you could get a million different.
He could be a scuba diver.
He could be a soldier sort of thing.
And then Action Man survives in the UK and becomes the dominant thing.
Like in the UK, they have no cultural fondness for G.I.
Joe. Action man lingered and has become their dominant boys action figure hero in
history.
Can I just say Big Jim?
I'm looking at a lineup of Big Jim's.
Look down on the bottom right.
Big Jim is a firefighter in a silver suit.
He looks like he's like a 50s sci fi robot.
What firefighters have you ever seen in silver suits?
I mean, let's be honest, Big Jim's a sociopath.
He's right.
It can't be everything.
He's a catch me if you can.
You're telling me he's talented Mr.
Ripley. Yes, he's camping football, baseball,
firefighter, Arctic Explorer, race driver, boxer, cowboy, Safari hunter, commando,
warm up, skin diving, karate and basketball.
And this is like one page like spies not on there.
As you pointed out, he's got his like secret disguise shit.
Why is he when he's a football player?
Why does he have a cape?
Football players don't have capes.
That's one thing I know about sports.
Big Jim's got a lot of shit going on and like moderate success, but didn't really
linger in the 80s. They come back around.
They go like, is that the concept?
Do we do a modern Big Jim thing in a smaller scale where it's like a hero who
can become anything?
And they were sort of thinking a more fantastical version of it.
They made this prototype I love where it was the one figure with like the body
pose we sort of know in the musculature of He-Man, but they were removable parts.
And it was like he can be a spaceman.
And the spaceman armor was just Boba Fett armor painted orange.
It was the helmet and the jetpack, the exact Boba Fett shit.
Painted orange.
He can be a barbarian.
And it was like a Conan style barbarian, but a slightly different look.
And this predates when Mattel would have taken the Conan movie, bitch.
And then the third one is a tank man.
And the tank man is his head is just the turret of a tank.
He like he is a military vehicle.
And they were just like the barbarians, the thing they did, all this focus group
like shit with little kids and they were like little kids are obsessed with the idea
of power. That's the whole thing.
They want to feel powerful. They want to feel in control.
The whole thing is like I have the power
that he man is like this dude who has power.
No one can tell him what to do.
And then they just threw every single thing into the pot to like flesh out his
universe, every type of supporting character, every type of genre,
all of that. And it was, yeah, hugely successful.
Outsold Barbie for like a number of years was Mattel's number one thing was making
billions of dollars. The cartoon show was huge.
It like just flowered.
And then it was so big and they realized that they had a very,
very sort of unusual percentage of female viewers as opposed to most boy action
shows. So they decided we're going to spin this off.
We're going to do She-Ra, He-Man's sister,
make a show and have to explain why his sister has never been mentioned until now
because she was like stolen Maleficent style.
But
She-Ra is very big.
And at a certain point, I think was even out doing it in the ratings,
out doing it in sales, maybe. And then like 1986, 1987, it just plummets.
It just plummets out of nowhere.
It was one of these things where it went from like He-Man is making five hundred
million dollars a year to He-Man's making twenty million dollars a year.
It was like one year where it dropped like that.
And there are all these different theories on what happened.
All the cranky dudes at Mattel blame it on She-Ra.
They say that like there was this show that the boys little sisters like to watch.
And that was fine.
But then once there was a girl show,
then it made He-Man look like a girly property.
And when the girls had their own warriors
to play with, then the boys got territorial and abandoned it,
which I don't know if I really believe that.
There's also a story that they fucked up like circulation,
that the toys were selling so well, the retailers were like, we want more and more.
And they kept on creating more and more characters.
They made so many different characters
in the original line over the span of only like four years or something.
But at a certain point, they weren't still producing the main characters.
And so the stores just got clogged with like a lot of these final year deep cut
characters who end up in the power tour, who they were desperately trying to make
cool, who like never made it onto the cartoon show, were only in the power tour.
And now like your shelves were filled with snout spout and like blast attack.
I love snout spout.
These guys weren't in the...
Because I'm not so up on all this mythology.
Some of this is only tour.
Some of these, I don't want to get reamed by He-Man fans who are more
comprehensive in their knowledge than I am.
I don't remember which are which, but some of these characters
were never on the cartoon show, were only in the tour.
Some of them only appeared in, you know, like mini comics.
Like there was that sort of like scattering of it.
And
the movie was supposed to be the big thing that sort of rejuvenated it.
And then it bombed really hard.
It was tied up in canon sort of like going under in Superman 4.
And the budget was getting cut and it sort of like fell flat.
But this show was like a huge fucking success.
And to the best that I could check it
still holds the record for the most sold out performances at Radio City Music Hall.
That seems so insane.
I was trying to find any like further validation than the people involved
in this show, but it is 18 is the number.
18. I don't know. That's a lot.
Why wouldn't that be the winner of that stat?
That's crazy.
They sold out 18 performances at Radio City Music Hall.
And that is the smallest venue they ever played.
I was going to say, because if you're comparing it to Turtles, this is arenas.
Turtles was a theater tour.
And this is in LA.
It was the LA Sports Arena.
Yes.
I mean, and if you see any videos or it pans to crowd.
Yeah, it's always like, you know, theater in the round.
Radio City was the only theater they played.
Otherwise, it was stadiums.
Geez.
Yeah.
I as I started looking up pictures and videos of this,
I was kind of surprised because this looks expensive, really fucking expensive.
Yeah.
The Mortal Kombat show looks a little chintzy, but this looks like they spent so
much money. I think that's why the costumes were sort of going viral.
However, many months ago it were, I mean,
viral within our very nerdy corner of the Internet.
But like, all of us sort of noticed it in our timelines because you are kind of
taken aback by like these costumes look higher quality than the other types of
these shows that you've seen before.
Like there's something less chintzy about this.
And even just the scale of the show,
like the narrative ambition of the show is wild.
Like this is a thought I had watching it.
It feels like this show is every different type of theme park show
run back to back to back to back.
Like it has like 30 minute stretches where it's like now it's a condensed
musical version of the story.
Now it is a stunt show.
Right now it is this weird fucking attorney in circus thing.
Yeah, which is less less
tracked on you or less like archived seemingly.
I didn't ever see a really good copy of the attorney in circus.
It's also like Starlight Express kind of performers on roller skates.
Skating.
That's where it really hooked me.
Yeah, it's like it's like a dance show, a stunt show, a musical rock opera,
a little rock opera, pseudo futuristic rock opera.
The moment where I felt like I need to bring this to the good boys,
we need to talk about this on podcast.
The ride is songster just feels like such a PTR character.
Oh, boy. Oh, you know, I lit up at Songster.
Let me just I'll pull him up on the screen.
So let's explain Songster, I guess he's well, there's a little
we're looking at kind of his like his hero shot from the program of the tour.
And we'll post these somewhere.
But his little like attribution Songster,
the cosmic troubadour tells the ancient legends through his music.
So he's introduced lately.
I guess we have to say a little about the premise of the show,
because it's not just it's not that the He-Man characters are touring a concert.
And it's not just that this is happening and you're not part of it.
It is a tour. Power tour is correct.
It's almost like if the pope was coming
to your town or just like a bunch of dignitaries from a nation that you knew
a little about but wanted to know more and they're bringing the best that they
kind of a shin you right?
Like a shin you see a five thousand years of eternal civilization.
But that's like a very important distinction, Scott,
because coming out of our shells is the turtles have decided they want to rock
for you, right? Yeah, that's when I taught them about music.
And now they wanted to share it with the world.
Yeah, right. And they're like doing a tour.
You know, it's like we're treating this like it's a concert.
And then I remember seeing like a Rugrats Radio City Music Hall show when I was
young that was like an original stage show with people in terrifying costumes,
you know, and lip sync songs.
But that was just a play.
You know, that was just a Rugrats musical that toured.
This this is the format of the show is, as you said, it feels papal.
It does feel like you are going to be blessed by visitors from Eternia.
Yeah, and it's very because it's very pomp and circumstance in like a way that
things in the 1600s would have been pomp and circumstance where it's all like
banners and fine lemons and then they show you their traditions.
It's like it's their culture.
It's not like here's like a random random smattering of people and bands or something.
It's like this is the best and brightest of an entire culture.
Right. The narrative of this show is
the attorney and the high attorney and want to share their culture with you.
And some things get disrupted. Right.
But this is almost supposed to be a very
regal, austere, educational presentation for the audience.
You know, the first act in a way, if it wasn't characters who you knew about from
toys and TV, you as a child might be bums to see this.
If it was for anything else that you'd never heard of,
royal wedding, like what are all these weird traditions?
It feels like religion.
It feels like you're in church.
Yes.
It's like you're like, what?
What now? A reading from the book of.
Yeah, like they tell you to.
That's what Songster does.
And when you say it's interrupted, I feel like it's not interrupted that much.
It's interrupted a couple of times, but they get to do a lot of their presentation.
A lot of the bulk of it out.
Yeah. Act one is totally uninterrupted.
It's mostly like an in-universe show.
You know, it's like, well, this is what those characters would do.
It almost feels like you're visiting the palace, except, of course,
they are visiting you, which is the other weird wrinkle of this.
Eternia is like a far off planet in a distant universe, right?
That's a big thing.
And in the movie, there's like a portal that forms, you know,
like Skeletor sends He-Man to the New Jersey.
I think it was shot in California,
but I think he's sent to New Jersey and all the good guys are stuck in New Jersey
and they have to find their way back to Eternia.
But it's like that sort of like fish out of water thing.
This is sort of doing like a non-terrifying alien encounter thing
where at the beginning they're like, we have technology.
We're going to bring them to you.
You know?
But only nice stuff, only good things.
Right. But I find it fascinating that like they even kind of cared enough to be like,
No, we have to answer why they're able to come to like,
you know, the IZOD Center.
I was trying to think of what these things would have been called fucking 35 years ago.
But like, you know, well, kids know they come from a different planet.
They can't just show up here.
They're not going to show up here in a spaceship.
You know, you need to create this new
like commander character at the beginning who's like, we have the technology.
Hold on. Transmission coming through.
Let's beam them onto your stage.
I imagine that now this is just not I'm not saying it has to be.
I just appreciate that they justified everything logically,
because I think now if you see Paw Patrol live, it's just so these dogs are doing
a concert for you, they are here in your city and you're going to sit and watch them.
I don't think that logic holds
other jobs they have to go to on Monday.
But they took a break for this weekend to do seven performances.
I feel like if you're a little kid and you go see the show,
it does make it feel more real to you, where you're like,
they are really justifying how these characters could be in the same physical
space as me, you know?
Was this like first?
Oh, I was going to say they even work in like the souvenirs.
Well, that is so fucking canny.
It's very canny.
So craven.
But I love that as a kid.
Like I bought it hook line and sinker.
You know, right.
They do. They're sort of like if you believe in Tinkerbell,
you have to clap moment, except the clap costs fifty dollars.
You got to get a sword like there's like everybody.
Everybody takes a pledge, basically.
And which, by the way, that's that's one part that I I like.
I have to jump around too much, but I really enjoy when I think part of the
it by this point, Skeletor has been introduced.
Skeletor is a presence in it.
And there is the line that he has everybody or ask everyone,
just do you do you promise to protect this country from the wrath of Skeletor?
And the particular this particular performance was filmed in Calgary.
So when he's talking about country, it's Canada.
I find it really funny that like, will you children protect Canada from Skeletor?
Well, I'll see the the online records of this show are the guy.
I think his name is Greg Park.
Gus Park.
Gus Park. Yes, thank you.
He played ninja in this show and he videotaped like 50 different performances.
But not great because it's 87.
Don't forget.
So it's just like camera in the back.
It's the best as you could do.
A little hard to make out.
But like there's a video that's just the first hour of the show.
And then on his account, he has like three parts of the attorney in circus
in the second act, but they're titled weirdly and I miss them.
It's a really hard YouTube to navigate.
Yeah, it's hard to navigate.
And they come from different nights at different venues, I think.
And then he a couple of years ago went to
Power Con, the He-Man convention, and they screened it with some of the other
actors who were in the show and did like a live commentary.
And there's a video of that.
And that's you watch.
You just I think right before we did this.
Yeah. Yes.
So that's a better quality performance.
But it's like they only have it's a better quality performance.
No, it's the opposite.
It's that the video he has up of just the first act is the better quality.
But he doesn't have the second act of that show.
And then he has the second act of a different performance split into three
videos. And then when they screened it at the convention, it was the whole thing
all the way through, but from worse angles with worse sound.
If you go on his YouTube, it's so weird and messy where it's like it's all messes
the universe and then numbers, but then there's a missing number two.
And you don't know if that video is going to be a bad back of the room video
of the show or a brief clip from P.M.
Magazine, an early 80s, I guess, all of 80s news show where they interview some
of the cast and then there's five videos in a row.
He's like, well, all right, I better upload all these Masters of the Universe videos
finally, although I should upload this Oak Ridge Boys music video as well.
I got to get to that because if I don't do it,
got like modern martial arts, like demonstrations on there as well.
I found it the kind of message where he said a couple of years ago that he was
trying to get the clearances to do like an ultimate cut and take the best
performances from whichever sources he had and put together the most viewable
video, but he still hasn't done that. But there are some great.
In addition to the local news interviews,
there's some great local TV like Coming Soon to the Local Spectrum,
He-Man, Masters of the Universe, Power Tour, like great local commercials for this show.
All of this to say, you do kind of need to navigate the power tour,
unlike Coming Out of Their Shells, where like it was
recorded professionally, released on VHS, there was like clear representation of it
if you didn't get to see it live.
You have to sort of construct this event like it's the JFK assassination.
You're looking at it from different angles at different sources.
Not the best video ever, but they're trying their best.
Reading synopses, looking at photos.
Is there any talk of why?
Where is the master recording of the audience, like with the songs?
Do they exist?
Nobody knows.
Because I just I want to put this forward right off the bat.
The songs in this are good, right?
Yeah, yeah, pretty good.
Yeah, pretty good.
Yeah. Are they as good as Turtles?
I don't know, but they're pretty good.
Yeah, I knew this was going to be the issue.
I knew Mike was going to come in arguing for it.
And here's and now I'm not going to I'm going to back off.
But I'm going to say this, but just know that I already backed off of this point.
But by the time when I'm watching it by Songsters first song,
which I did a little snippet of at the beginning, by the end of that number
and looking at the scale of the set, which is this bit, this like giant round
like a cliff piece essentially.
And there's kind of solid gold dancers and like bright purple.
I really like the song.
Songster descended from the ceiling.
There's so much going on and knowing that there's fighting and roller skating.
There was a moment like 15 minutes in where I was like,
I think this is better than coming out of our shells.
And I don't know.
It lost me a little bit.
So I'm not I'm not going to say that now.
But there was a minute where like just pure scale.
I really like the music.
That it was it was neck and neck for me for a minute.
I'll say this to be democratic.
I think at this show's highs, it is better than coming out of our shells.
Coming over shells is a more coherent, cohesive work.
And I say, yeah, rarely, rarely said point, but I threw in the person
who has watched the entirety of the attorney in circus, which is like interminable.
It's so fucking bad.
And in the commentary where they're watching it at the convention, they're like,
so we're just going to talk over the next 20 minutes because this part sucks.
It never worked.
We never once went over well with a crowd.
We never figured it out.
We never fixed it.
It was a fucking nightmare.
The second act of this was like a problem.
I have to go to Mike for your any is this is your blood boiling at the that there?
No, I mean, it's ambitious.
I appreciate the ambition.
And then the songs, too, like I especially I would like that's what I'm looking.
I'm looking to hear like an official recording.
Do they even make one like I would like to hear it because you could really judge.
Yeah, because it does feel like from the
songs are like the songs are a little more interesting than most of the turtle songs.
Well, look, I love Skipping Stones and I thank you guys for turning me on to that one.
I think it's a genuine jam.
I've listened to it a lot.
It's the biggest genre breaker because the right because they get into a run
of like there's a few like mid album cuts that are very just like, all right,
they're doing kind of new kids rehash.
But that's the one like they there's a new
genre applied and I think it really hits a new high.
Brr, brr, brr.
It's also just the vocal performance that is unbelievable.
I'm so fucking on a hip when it comes
to popular music that most of my major
music discoveries of the last couple of years have been because of podcast The
Ride, where I'm like, have you guys heard hot drinks?
Hell, yeah.
Like hot drinks and the McGruff crack cocaine song and Skipping Stones are like
in pretty regular rotation for me and all three I only know because of this podcast.
I'm honored, but also like, oh, my God, we're those and us are your reference
for for new music.
Discover.
Yeah.
You have Phoebe Bridges.
That's all I know.
You haven't gotten into South Side, Johnny and the Asbury Jukes yet.
I have not even heard of them.
That's a podcast, The Ride favorites.
You say that, but I've never listened
to them, even despite all of their references on the show.
They're fun.
When do you guys bring them up?
Maybe I just it slipped past me.
That's OK.
We brought them up once and then Mike said frequently brought up on the show.
And I was like, are they?
I brought about in the last episode was the gathered episode we did.
I don't know.
I feel like I brought them up twice before that.
But maybe that's only once.
Yeah.
I'm trying to see if there was any.
Official soundtrack release, but it doesn't feel like there was and it feels
like such a bizarre missed opportunity.
It was like, obviously, this show existed
to sell merchandise and sold a tremendous amount of merchandise.
You can only imagine how many millions of swords they sold, not specifically.
The sword Jason has not specifically that one.
No, that's pricey.
That's a nicer sword.
But we haven't mentioned most of the show was pre-recorded.
Like, yes.
Oh, yeah.
And man at arms were the only two people with live microphones.
Yes.
Is what I saw.
Songster we started setting up, but is the Cosmic Trooper door and is
not only the narrator of the show, but the lead character of the show.
He's like the one guy who's on stage the entire time.
And he is the new character created only for the tour, which in and of itself
feels audacious to me, but I think it fits into this concept they have where it's
like, well, he man's not going to put on a show for some kids.
That's not what he does.
He's a hero.
Songsters a performer.
He man will make his appearances.
Right. He'll he'll wave to the crowd.
He'll fight off evil.
He'll show up when he needs to.
But you need someone whose power set is music.
Music.
You go to see the pope.
He waves from a box.
He doesn't go.
He doesn't sing a song for people sing.
Right.
He means he means the pope if Skeletor
invaded and the pope had to get out of the box and fight a little bit.
So like if the devil showed up during a papal visit, right, which sounds like, God,
I wish that would happen, boy.
I mean, who wouldn't go see the pope if the pope comes to your town if you thought
the devil was going to actually get be there, especially if Songster was narrating it.
This is the tale of how the devil became the devil.
I'll say there was a this I mentioned previously, but this action figure line
called Masters of the Universe classics that started the models that have ruined
Mike in my life forever.
Right.
Where all these toys get pre sold online, you have to order them on a specific day
because the 2000s he man had failed.
There were still like a big adult collectors market.
Yeah, there's mutagen man
from Super Seven, which is a direct lineage of Masters of the Universe classics
in how that toy line structured.
But it was this toy line where they were
trying to make the definitive version of every character from every version of the
property and all these characters that never been done before and variants and
shit like that. And
I heard that they wanted to make a Songster action figure
and they were going to do it as a San Diego Comic Con exclusive, which like Mike,
you were beating the drum for the coming out of our shells toys for so long.
And Randy and that kept on being dismissive about it for years.
But then all of a sudden he started playing along with me on Twitter and then
made it feel like I may have been the reason he did it.
I just feel like there was this like attitude for a long time that you really
helped push back against that, like coming out of our shells is not real turtles.
That's embarrassing.
Whereas Mochi was was going to do a fucking Songster figure like 10 years ago.
Is there are you on multiple Facebook groups,
Masters of the Universe Facebook groups?
I mean, it's going to be hard now that you're on the show.
But like I'm on multiple Facebook groups that involve the turtles.
And when the turtles, when they made coming out of our shells tour turtles,
peep, there were like half the audience,
maybe 30 percent of the audience that were furious.
This is garbage.
This is dumb, childish shit.
They shouldn't be making this.
I want more serious turtles.
I want the Eastman and Laird red bandana.
I want a new version of that from NECA.
And there was a very large, angry portion
of the audience that felt coming out of shells was not real turtles.
So I wonder if it's similar to this.
Those people are so fucking cool.
Yeah, you know what's really fun, Mike,
is when you're going into those like message boards and groups that you've been
part of for over a decade and now they're arguing about the thing that you're a
part of and you can't say anything must be weird.
The fucking weird and it's like social justice warrior orco.
I can't handle this character.
Jason, not even a joke, not even a joke.
Oh, yeah.
Just absolutely absurd projection shit and like shit that is based in nothing or
shit that is correct, but like it can't be explained because it's a spoiler.
And why don't you just wait and watch the thing and then decide whether you like it
or not, rather than listen to these YouTube channels that are trying to stoke outrage.
Anyway, songster, it felt like for a long time,
Motu, because of its goofy origins and how
disparate all of its different like incarnations were, was more accepting of
all the weird nooks and crannies and things like songster.
They were going to do the songster action figure as a San Diego Comic Con
exclusive, and the idea was to get the guy who played songster on the tour to come
to Comic Con and do a concert and like be in the Mattel booth and make like a splash.
And apparently he asked for too much money.
Oh, geez.
Oh, bummer.
I've had this image up on the screen for a while.
Let me just like we'll post it on Twitter, but like let's just describe some details.
It's like a little bit Ren fair with spangles and open chest and like kiss to like
the color palette, but the actual pattern of the outfit with like shoulder guard
kind of things and yes, and like tight in the pants and big boots.
Absolutely. It's a colorful kiss.
Yeah.
And then the guitar is unbelievable.
It is like it's like a space broom.
It is.
It's got no strings, seemingly no strings.
Yes.
Big turquoise rod and then like kind of angular cut weird pink plastic with stripes
that mean nothing, but then still a dial, still like a little crank it to 11 dial.
I mean, this image and then he himself is sort of it feels like
I mean, there's like a little bit of Siegfried and Roy in there with the cape.
A lot of it's a little bit like if you squint and especially you look at this
black and white one, you know, like Prince is influenced in this a little bit.
Oh, yeah.
And the hair and the earring.
Yeah, there's a in this one.
There's kind of a you could sort of make out the penis shape in the pants.
That's the man as a prince.
Yes, extremely.
He looks like that Robin Chris O'Donnell hot toy that I'm going to buy next year.
Yeah, although a little kind of a little bit of a tiny shape.
No offense to the guy.
If you're going to show it so well, maybe kind of like puff yourself up.
He could have done some stuffing.
I think that's no, I'm not going to.
That's the I just had the grossest thing I was about to say.
No, Mike, you have to say the grossest thing.
Say it.
I was going to say maybe that's just a vein.
That's oh.
So the penis, what he is the grossest thing you could possibly say.
That's pretty gross.
Yeah, that's the grossest thing I've ever said on the podcast.
That a vein, just a vein on a penis would be as big as someone's actual penis.
Well, yeah, because you are not seeing the rest of it.
That seems like it'd be more concerning.
Yes, I don't know.
It goes his actual penis goes up his back.
He's hiding it because it's too
he wraps it around.
I just I like a I think this guy playing
Songster is giving and I there was an injury where Songster got stuck from the
opening where they drop him from such an insane height.
So I think he missed a small number of shows, but it was the one guy doing it
for like 98 percent of the tour.
I have his name and his
wait, I got it.
Doug Howard is the guy's name.
And I sparked to his Wikipedia because a couple of things.
One, he for one tour and one album was in the band Utopia, which was Todd Rundgren's
prog rock band, a big Rundgren guy.
But also, here's one for Jason.
This guy Songsters grandfather wrote the song.
Hello, my baby.
Hello, my honey.
What the writer of that wrote the Michigan J.
Frog song.
Yeah. Yeah.
Which was apparently at some point
purchased outright by Warner Brothers.
It was like a song in the world and then became a war.
So it could be in the WB server verse.
LeBron and Granny could run into who they could.
They could run into that song and the writer, Joseph E.
Howard, as much as they needed to louse his way in again.
Of the many, many
sort of systemic failures of Space Jam, a new legacy, some of which we're talking
about right before this record audience, we did a full pre air podcast about Space
Jam, a new legacy, we did at least a second gate on the legacy.
Sorry, we didn't record it the day before.
I have to record a fucking two hour episode about Space Jam.
Wait, you'll be covered.
Yeah, you got to get warmed up a little.
You got to get the muscles flexing.
I was just going to say, because it's so hard to formulate an opinion on that movie,
I was just going to say you just made me realize
how does that movie not use Mr.
J. Frog once?
How do they not call it cyberspace jam?
It's right there.
Jason. Yes, right there.
Yes, I was saving that for blank check.
But yes, I had the exact same thought.
Yeah, yeah.
This is the bug main texted me.
Space Jam 2 is not in space.
No, never.
The title is not applicable.
I mean, I guess their justification is that they hijack Marvin the Martian spaceship
and they go into toon space briefly.
It is planets.
The game is distinctly not in space.
It's in cyberspace.
Yeah, yeah.
I was going to say, on to things that are great and perfect in media.
I think Songster is a virtuoso performance.
And I think it is just fascinating that this is like if Botanicus was the main
character of the E.T. ride and he just showed up a couple of times.
But everyone loved it like it worked.
Yeah, yeah.
I have a video clip and this is I'll ask for patience from you guys and from the
audience because the quality is not great, as we've said.
But I think just to give you a taste of the song, not only that, but also this
might be good for setting the stage in general because you will not just hear
Songster, but also He-Man and She-Ra's introduction.
And as Jason mentioned, this is a classic theme park trope pre-recorded.
So we are looking at actors who are mouthing along to a track.
And boy, there is something this He-Man, this voice.
I mean, I guess it's what he sounds like in the cartoon, right?
But just so just verbose and clear and not that emotive.
I don't know about that Skeletor.
Like it's all very there's this weird like winky quality to it.
A little removed.
This is the first section of the show,
which is like a meet and greet where they're like telling you the customs of
Eternia and just introducing the characters to you one by one.
Yeah, yeah.
And so you've like met a lot of the folks and then who beamed in and then and then
you get to He-Man and She-Ra and they introduce
Songster and say what his purpose is.
So forgive the quality.
I might interject with a thing or two.
We'd like you to know a bit more about the magical history of our planet.
And so we roll along our kingdom's finest storyteller.
His name is Songster.
And so his name Songster will create our
Eternian legends before your very eyes.
That's right, She-Ra.
So sit back.
And enjoy Songster and the legend.
Really, that's right.
She-Ra is so much like when the equivalent of when Osmode are the tiny green space
alien that only Homer can see shows up.
Damn straight, Troy, my man.
All right. Now then Songster goes down.
Sometimes
from the ceiling.
And
choose to fit.
Where are you?
Dab towards the teller.
Let me review a spell that will keep you on the edge of your seat.
Let me take you now.
A bunch of solid gold dancers come out.
He landed perfectly in the center.
All the dancers had to guide in his little stage, which is very precarious.
I mean, love the song.
I love that in this performance, he's shouting out Fairfax, Virginia.
Hello, Fairfax.
He's just got like such a fucking like smooth voice, you know?
It's a real. Yeah. Yeah.
Very, very strong.
Very powerful, very smooth.
I also just to continue my ET Ride analogy.
That's the other thing I'm realizing about the structure of this show is like.
Here are the attorney and customs, right?
Here are all the characters.
It's building to like a boiling point.
He man and she were a holy fucking shit.
They're here and they're like, wait a second.
You are excited for us. No, no, no.
Now let's introduce the real star of the show.
It's Songster.
It's like if the opening of the ET Ride was like, guys, just wait until you fucking
meet Botanicus, I'm telling you, this guy is the shit.
And then you just spend the rest of the ride like Botanicus apartment.
You know,
like Songster just becomes then the the protagonist of the show.
Yeah, because from this point on, he does like five songs in a row and they all
correspond to a different tale of attorney and legend.
Before he finishes this one, let me say,
because I don't want to get to it in the clip, but he starts singing about other
we've got stories to tell and he gets kind of, you know, into the meat of what's
going to happen tonight and then adds, and by the way, Songster's my name.
He takes you back to.
But like and why would you like he man,
the guy with the clearest voice in the universe said his name is Songster.
And then he said it again.
Some people might have missed it.
Yeah, if it's a new guy.
You want to make sure you say I'm Chevy
Jason, you're not coming in and going out of that.
That's why you became a star.
And that's when you say your known name on television.
Things change.
That's what I when I was talking to Songster, I gave him the advice, you know,
you got to say your name twice.
Somebody has to say it once and then people will tell you it's overkill.
They're wrong. I said Songster when people go to the zoo.
The first thing they go to see are the lions.
But also just in isolation.
And by the way, Songster's my name is such an incredible sentence.
There's something about anyone saying, and by the way, blank is my name is such
a weird way to introduce yourself because it's making it clear you're not introducing
yourself up front, right? You front loaded some other shit.
And by the way, blank is my name.
But then for your name to be Songster is incredible.
But yeah, narrative reigns completely
thrown over to Songster.
He man and she have vacated the stage, not just the star of the show, but two stars
of two different shows, the cross section of this audience has both been told.
It's not about them.
Don't worry about them. Songsters, the fucking guy.
And then Songster takes you through this,
like a bridged reconciliation of the origins of like the he man mythology.
Going back to like the legend of Grayskull, the formation of the tower,
the power of the sorceress, the formation of the castle.
You see dancers turn into Castle Grayskull
and and yes, setting up like this thing that was all retconned.
Like that's this insane thing where it's like he man doesn't have a sibling.
Right. Like it's Prince Adam is the Clark Kent,
the mild matter teen who gets this power,
this ancestral power in the form of the sword that he can conjure, turn into he man.
But he is the prince of the kingdom.
His dad is an attorney and his mom is a human astronaut from Earth who landed on
their planet, something this show takes the time to work in.
Like, I'm just impressed with how thorough they are in their backstory,
which admittedly, it lost me a little.
This is where it lost points to Ninja Turtles.
But yeah, the mythology sense and then also the songs end up.
I mean, that first song is that's Guns of Blazing.
I love that song a lot.
And then you end up in a little bit more of like space version of medieval bard.
Like that's like structurally, that's what the songs are like.
A little bit is like telling you it's like the guy in Robin Hood, the rooster
telling you like they work less as like fun concert pop songs.
So I have to give it back to the turtles in that area.
It becomes like a decent theme park musical.
Like there's this 30 minute stretch where it's just straight up.
Here's the story.
And you're having story songs sung by the characters.
Right. Like songs are singing as well.
But you have why am I immediately forgetting the tune of it?
But that weird staccato, semi-spoken Prince Adam song about the fact that he can't
lift the sword.
Mm hmm.
Yeah.
What's the.
Where he doesn't have the power.
He doesn't have the will.
Oh, right. Right.
But the rhythm of that song is so odd.
I just think it's interesting where I was watching this and going like, huh,
this is interesting that like as opposed to these concert shows or writing a new
narrative, they're kind of making like a big budget musical out of the origins
of these characters and the universe that were never very clearly laid out in the
cartoon.
And instead, they just do that a bridge and then they're like, and now some other
things.
It's yeah, they really threw every again, as you were saying, they threw everything
at it because it was like it feels like it's somebody probably was just like,
yeah, let's just make let's just tell kids about what happened.
They should know that.
And then someone was like, no, we have to make it present.
Something has to be happening now.
Right. And then they were like, yeah, let's just do all of it.
Because I guess it's like you're here and watching this and you didn't know
anything about like what this kids show that your kid likes.
You'll know what's going on by the end of this.
You know, it's sort of helpful.
They're giving the parents like a crash course.
But isn't I guess it's like, are we seeing like historical documents of what happened
or reenactments or projections?
But you're right. They're like, we want present action.
We want the kids to feel like the shit's happening here.
So then like you have this 30 minute section, 20 minute section, whatever it is
of like the telling of the story where the characters are singing their own songs.
And you're seeing how he got the power and Hordak like rude the day said he would
some back come back to claim his prize, which ended up being she rather twin sister.
And that's why she's at her own show and all that shit.
And then when that ends, like Skeletor shows up on the screen and is like fake news,
not how I remember it happening.
And their solution is we have to fight for who gets to tell this story.
And the fight is what do they call it?
The power race, the power race.
Right. It's not a fight.
It's a power race, which is a roller skating tournament.
Yeah. And he like he kind of just seems to want to be included in the ski.
He's just like Skeletor seems lonely and wants to be in a skate thing.
Yes.
He just wants to have friends.
There's a line in there like once.
So, yeah, I get where you're.
You're all the way through the first act with no presence of Skeletor.
And then if I then you hear him, then it's just his voice.
Right. Right.
There's like a half a second appearance where they say like and then Hordak found
his like protege and Skeletor's on stage for half a second, then disappears,
is not part of the story as they set it up and then only comes in afterwards to say
I dispute the telling of those facts.
It's propaganda.
Review all sides before you judge.
But then there's I think my favorite line in the whole thing is right after
Skeletor first appears and then he says, where are you, bone face?
How did you get here?
Show yourself.
Where are you?
Boneface is what a dad would call like, hey, why don't you go play with your
boneface figure?
Skeletor is already like one letter off of what dad would have like that skeleton.
Like, OK, well, we could change the name.
And now it sounds like it's like a little bit.
Dad couldn't have thought of Skeletor, an average dad.
But that boneface, he has perfect peak dad.
Skeletor specifically says I will destroy
everyone in that arena, which shows you that they are committed to being in arenas.
It's not an open ended venue in this.
This production hall, it's like, yeah,
this is an arena show for sure and really specific.
And then I think there's some he man stuff about like somebody says, how is he
going to destroy everybody? I don't know.
But when Skeletor sets out to do something, he finds a way.
I don't know. That really doesn't put the urgency there.
It's you.
You should if anyone knows how to deal with Skeletor, it would be you.
Yeah, you don't. What do you mean?
I don't know.
What's anybody's guess what he's up to?
They build up the power race like it's like someone challenging you to a duel
in medieval times like, oh, fuck, this is the way things get settled.
It's definitive.
And then but yet you're allowed to have like eight participants on each team
and only one of them needs to win for your side to win.
This is life and death.
So let's real quick.
This side of the audience cheer for the door and this side of the audience cheer.
It's like medieval times also.
They bring them out one by one and tell the audience to like, let them know how
you feel about them. But it is funny that like this show hits
the major characters, right, which like on the good side or he man
man at arms, Tila or co.
And then his parents to a lesser degree.
And on the bad side, it is Skeletor, Beastman, Evil Lynn.
And then everyone else in the cast is the newest line of action figures.
Like these are not the primary supporting characters on the cartoon show.
These aren't the toys the kids own.
They're the toys they want them to buy.
So it's like odd if you're a he man fan to see like a real blast put in like such
a position of prominence, you know?
Well, tell me who.
Because I pulled out just my favorite ones from the program and I don't know
mythology super well, so you know, it is just a good excuse to see him.
Yeah. So here's Grizzlore.
OK, so Grizzlore comes from the Horde.
They were originally supposed to be a new group of villains for He-Man.
And then the She-Ra team took them.
So then She-Ra kind of had better villains than He-Man for a while.
Oh, OK. And the toys sold really well.
When did he learn to do like the Thriller hands?
I'm like, ha ha ha.
The other thing, I mean, the famous thing about He-Man was they they had like four
sculpts, by and large, that they just reused for everything and would like
kit bash different parts and be like, now the robot has lizard arms and his name is
Robo Lizard, like it was just the same pieces finding ways to paint different
colors or whatever. But Grizzlore, the action figure, looks like this,
where it's a muscle body and then they just put fur on top of it.
Oh, boy, that is aged well.
That that's preserved well.
It's not flaking off in anyone's cardboard boxes and starting to stink.
Absolutely not. Yeah.
And then just regular boots, just like kind of like, you know,
hot topic sort of boots.
And then this guy, really like this guy, Clamp Champ.
He's good.
Does anyone know the movie Laser Blast,
the mystery science theater movie Laser Blast, where a guy gets a big clunky thing?
That's a laser gun attached to his arm.
It's like the Tomorrow War, except much bigger, entire arm.
And that's kind of a clamp.
I guess, yeah, this is his he's got a big, big old clamp on one arm.
No, Clamp Champ is like a fan favorite
because he was the only black character in the original show.
So like a lot of fans had affinity for him because for a lot of people it was
like their only representation.
He is funny in the sense that
so many of the He-Man characters are like otherworldly or inhuman.
And whatever their power is, is part of their physical being.
Like there's a guy named Mechaneck whose power is that he is like neck and
telescope, like a thousand feet up in the sky, like he's like a human periscope or
whatever, but it's like he's got a fucking robot neck.
Whereas Clamp Champ just holds a thing that can clamp people.
Oh, it's not even I thought this was clamped to him.
That was absolutely not.
It's like a thing he holds in his hand.
And then from either side of this, like two pincers come out
and he can sort of trap people.
Clamp Champ is just a dude who has a weapon.
Owns a good thing.
OK, he owns a good thing.
I really like that you're saying this guy's new.
He's one of my all time favorites.
He's got a freaking like robot elephant head, like a big pipe trunk.
So this is a question amongst fans is like, is that a helmet or is he a robot
elephant? Like, is that his true form or is that a mask?
But he is made it don't know, probably.
No, no, no.
He is canonically an attorney and firefighter.
Like it's the point is that he uses his
snout to put out fires and the toy squirted water.
Wow. Oh, that's fine.
That would have been my favorite toy.
That's why it says, yeah, a frontline attorney and warrior.
That's not a rule.
I was always really like as a kid, really into the toys that looked like very
detailed or had very odd features in addition to him and like the toxic
Avengers like action figures were so great.
Like I kept those in such good shape
because they just had such odd features to them.
Well, that was a lot of the He-Man designers then went over to Playmates and did
the Ninja Turtles line and the Toxic Crusaders line, some other lines.
And that was them trying to like one up He-Man and be like, what if like the poses
are even more extreme and the detail is like bananas?
And if you look under their foot,
there are like five different objects sculpted there.
Yeah, like Muck Man. Right.
Turtles. Yeah. He was like a Muck Monster.
Had a lot of garbage stuck to him.
You remember?
Here's we got Man at Arms and Tila.
Man at Arms is just a great mustache dude.
The musculature on these suits is also just kind of insane.
Like they really have gone for,
you know, in the way that people always throw out that statistic of like,
oh, if Barbie, like if someone had Barbie's proportions in real life,
they wouldn't be able to stand up. Right.
They like took the musculature from the action figures and made it just as
grotesque as it would look scaled up to a real human.
So it just requires like a bunch of padding.
It's just the most like fake sumo suit.
Soft muscles.
Because like nobody looks
so as as mighty.
Yeah, it's hard to find a bunch of people
who are built like He-Man and She-Ra, which brings me to this point.
Do we know the thing about where who those people were in the tour and where they
came from? Yeah.
So great story.
We all landed on this.
I think so. I mean, somebody else feel free.
But Jack and Leslie Wadsworth
are and by the way, Jack and Leslie Wadsworth are their names and they
are married in real life and they met
while portraying Conan and Red Sonja at Universal Studios Hollywood.
They were in the Conan live show,
date, met there at both as muscle people and then were married by the time they
were touring the country as He-Man and She-Ra.
Brother and sister who kids were often confused with their relationship
played by a married couple, a happily married couple who are still married to
this day. Did any of you read or hear about their wedding?
No. Yes.
Oh, that's the best.
Yeah. Yeah.
Jason, you want to go ahead?
I don't think I see that part of the article in front of me.
I'll say show us your notes.
No, I just click on public.
Oh, wait. No, I do have it.
Universal offered to pick up the wedding tab if they would exchange vows on the set.
The wedding album shows bride and bridegroom in the set's dungeon with
barbarians looking on. And that's terrific.
They got married in the Red Sonja Conan
Universal stunt show.
Universal was so charmed by the fact that they were together in real life and that
they met through the show that they came to them and said, we will cover your
entire wedding if we're allowed to make this into like a press event.
And and Bob Mackie built her dress for her wedding.
Wow.
That's insane.
And she's like, it was crazy.
I was like not a girl who grew up dreaming of like my big extravagant wedding.
And then I had the most extravagant wedding of anyone I know.
I only had to pay for like the material cost of Bob Mackie's dress.
He just all he asked me to pay for was the the materials themselves and that
everything else was comped by Universal.
But all my wedding photos look like they're in hell.
They're in this like nightmarish set.
Can we take a picture by the globe?
No, the set, the photographer will only cover the set.
That's just a reporter.
That's like catnip for like a human interest story for Universal, for the He-Man people.
There's a long LA Times article about this tour.
It's a very funny artifact because I feel
like it's pop culture reporting that isn't done nowadays because it's kind of
like confrontation. It's kind of like, well, this is silly bullshit.
That's a sinking ship, right?
And it's kind of it's a little mean.
And I kind of but like reporters don't write about companies like this nowadays
because they would immediately get a call as soon as it hit the press.
Oh, like, what the fuck did you say?
We gave you free tickets, motherfucker.
Like,
but it is very funny where they're like, yeah, the show's really big and it's
touring a lot of places, but these toys are making a lot less money.
So who knows how long they'll be around for?
Well, it is fascinating to me that the toys were cratering so fast and that this
show was maybe the most successful element of this property ever, that, like,
simultaneously, the two things are happening where this is the only part of
the property that is succeeding.
Yeah, very strange.
It's funny, the Conan reference, because I feel like the the Conan stuff,
the rights get really weird where it's like, oh, the Robert E.
Howard, Robert E.
Howard created Conan, the Red Sonja with a Y was in a Conan story,
but Red Sonja with a J was created by Roy Thomas and Barry Windsor Smith at Marvel
Comics, so they're sold off separately.
Red Sonja Comics are published by one company.
The others are published by Marvel at this point.
And it's very bizarre.
It's like Micronauts or He-Man where it's like the legalities of it is just totally
insane. Well, He-Man is also now because
Filmation got hired to do the cartoon show and then Filmation was bought by like
company after company after company and then was bought by Classic Media,
which is one of these companies that was like gobbling up every independent vintage
cartoon or property that was out there, and then that got bought by Katzenberg and
then Universal bought Dreamworks.
So like Universal owns part of the He-Man rights and then Mattel owns the other part.
And some characters are in one silo and some are in the other.
And some of like the imagery or the music can only be used by one party or this or
that like this feels like the last moment, maybe where everything's kind of like in
one place and everyone's working together happily.
Yeah, right.
Because, yeah, I mean, there's all this.
I think I talked on the Turtles is like that all of a sudden when Nickelode or
Viacom, but Turtles, it was trying to get all the rights from the various places
because of how confusing it was.
So the characters created in the Archie comics, they'd have to go to the guy who
was writing and the guy drawing and get the rights for like, say,
Raphael's girlfriend Ninjara.
And then the writer would say, no, I'm not selling you the rights to
Raphael's girlfriend Ninjara, the sexy female Ninja Fox.
And he still owns it to this day, I believe.
Like Oracle was created by Filmation.
Oracle was not in the toy line or any of the comics first.
But Mattel seems to have a lot of leeway and control over Oracle,
whereas there are certainly characters that were Filmation only that like can't
be touched unless there's an additional license taken out.
But also, I know like the the show,
the show that I'm on, Revelation, is primarily produced by Mattel with Netflix.
But then the She-Ra cartoon, which was also for Netflix, was produced by Dreamworks
animation and not Mattel.
It's very confusing. Everything is very confusing.
And part of it is that I think more of She-Ra was developed by Filmation
and Concert Together, whereas He-Man and the toys were already on the shelf before
they brought them on to do the cartoon.
But like, yeah, it's the question I've been having to answer for the last year
and a half, which is like, oh, the show I'm on is not connected to the Netflix She-Ra.
And the Wright's answer is so boring and convoluted, it's not worth answering.
So the easier answer is this shows a continuation of the original 80s cartoon,
which is in the same continuity with the 80s She-Ra cartoon.
So technically it's connected to that She-Ra as opposed to the new She-Ra,
which is a new reboot.
There is a theme park connection in the midst of this.
2018 She-Ra was briefly in Universal Studios Islands of Adventure in the Lost
Continent taking pictures a few years ago, like when that come out.
2018, I think.
Yeah. So around there, there was a walk around She-Ra.
Universal seems to have a lot more free reign with what they can do with She-Ra
without Mattel's permission versus He-Man, where it's like
Universal owns these cartoons.
They don't own the characters.
It's also complicated and it's why everything needs to merge so that all
properties can be in one convenient server verse.
Just, you know, something as clean as and understandable as Warner 3000,
where algae rhythm reigns supreme and can dictate what properties everyone makes.
God, it just make life so much better.
Wouldn't be very easy.
I was thinking and I didn't find anything about this because I wonder if like by
the time Turtles rolls around, if it's like they've learned.
I wonder if this was brought up in the meetings because Turtles is so much more
synergy. The tape was being sold at Pizza Hut.
It was an immediate quick show.
Obviously, the tapes, VHS tapes, not the audio cassettes were also being sold
multiple. I have the making of VHS.
I have the actual first performance of it.
And I wonder if Masters of the Universe, they were thinking like they're going to
do the Jay Leno stand up comedy idea of like, you know, don't ever put it on video
because people won't come out to see it.
Like it was that they're thinking because it's crazy for a property for toys that's
all about selling people things and merchandise and souvenirs from that live
show. I wonder if that was their thought process with it.
Like we want people to come see this music.
We don't want them to be able to.
They'll never come if they have an audio cassette of it.
You have to imagine that was the thought.
And I guess also that by the time the tour was done and I guess they would have
released the video now that it wasn't cutting into the tour, the thing was pretty
much dead. You know, like, yeah, I guess it's all of it at once.
The demand to even have the remnant of the record of this.
Right. Like the other thing is Turtles.
I do think Turtles learned a lot of lessons from He-Man, which like blew up so
quickly and then burned out relatively fast.
Another one is like Turtles has been so
consistent with reinventing itself, and even if every reinvention doesn't work,
they sort of understand like if your thing's been around for five years.
I heard some watch some fucking YouTube video or some toy executive was explaining
this. But like when when kids realize like I'm five years old and this thing's
been around for five years and the older kids are into it, I don't own this anymore.
Like this is some old cartoon that's predated me.
You need like a new version every like six years so that new kids can come in on
the ground floor. Right.
Yes, that makes sense.
I mean, in my kid brain, it was like, oh, man, Turtles was gone for a while.
But Turtles, they did next mutation with Venus de Bilo, like right after the first
original cartoon.
Like the original cartoon is like eight seasons, nine seasons.
I mean, it was like a healthy run.
But the next mutation actually.
Yeah, Jesus.
Yeah. But next mutation is only like a year or two later.
And then there was that reboot in 2003,
which it's like that's the longest they were ever dark, it felt like.
And that was five years.
Right. Well, and like, say, Power Rangers never stopped.
I mean, that's a totally different.
It's like they'll make a season in Japan.
Right. Fly the costumes to not America.
I think it's New Zealand.
And then they will make a totally different story, a totally different set
of rules of like, all right, we have these costumes and we have footage where the
Zords are trains and then they become fighting robots.
How do we do this?
It's because of the weird way in which that show is made.
But I do think it sort of provided that model that everyone else has copied now
where you just need like even these Netflix cartoon shows.
I noticed that like season two will have an entirely different title than the first
season, you know, they never position something as like it's season two of this
show, it's this show, colon, new subtitle.
You know?
Yeah, it's interesting.
I don't know.
I'm trying to think about what's the most modern version.
I guess it's hard because you need to have
some property that's been around for like 20 years.
But like because I know like modern
cartoons and stuff, you know, they're still trying to screw people over.
And it's like they like to end something
at season three before they can renegotiate contracts,
unless it's very, very popular and then they will bring it back and then milk it
forever. It's like a weird.
No, I feel like there's also this thing with like I think it happens a lot with
superhero cartoons where like, oh, they'll do a Spider-Man cartoon and like everyone
will flock to it and be like, this is the best one.
They finally gotten it right.
And then they cancel it after three
seasons and immediately announce a new show, which is on the year nine months later.
And they're like, why did you cancel that?
Everyone loved that it was working and they were like, time for a new Spider-Man.
Like, it's just like, what can you say every three years?
New Spider-Man. Like these things just they don't let them linger.
And I think the same thing happened
with Ninja Turtles where there was like the Nickelodeon reboot that was going over
very well, then they canceled it somewhat abruptly and then did Rise of the Teenage
Mutant Ninja Turtles, which was very well liked, but didn't connect.
And then that just ended like kind of in failure.
Like they just canceled it for low ratings.
And everyone was kind of left saying, like, why wouldn't you have kept the earlier
show on the air? It wasn't losing steam.
But it feels like now these companies don't want to let things get to the point of He-Man.
Like you have to reboot it before the audience starts dipping.
Well, yeah, with Turtle and with I'm sure with all this stuff and maybe I'm not sure,
but I think this is what I think this is what I know is that it's like they're like,
you know what? The ratings aren't going to be if we just do a new version,
the ratings are going to be pretty similar.
Yeah. So as long as they're pretty similar,
we don't have to renegotiate contracts for all the people that are making this
who are going to want more money because they're doing a good job.
So we tell them to fuck off.
We get a bunch of new people for less money.
And by and large, the ratings are going to probably hover around the same place.
And if they're not cancel it and try another one.
I think merch is a big part of it, too, where it's like we have sold 18 versions
of Donatello in this design style and we've done the entire supporting cast now.
Like the kids have them all.
We need to reboot it and redesign everybody.
So there's a reason to rebuy all the characters.
Yes. Three seasons is like a very there's
an economic reason why companies are stopping things there.
Right. And if you get to five, it's like a blockbuster.
And they're like, we let you stay longer than we should have.
Now, please gracefully leave.
You're lucky. You're lucky that we let you do this.
Well, and it seemed like He-Man had some of the like behind the scenes, like the
writers, like the big name, like that.
I remembered this about He-Man.
And I double checked it and I never know how to pronounce this name because I always
just read it, J. Michael Strazinski.
I think that's right.
Yeah, he was the main writer on it or at least one of the best writers on it.
Yes. And then was Paul Dini on it, too?
Correct. Yeah.
And so Strazinski left eventually.
And he was writing on like a million cartoons and stuff eventually creates
Babylon 5 does a very well received like five years on the Amazing Spider-Man
comics somewhere down the line, writes the script for the Changeling.
Is that what it's called? The Clint Eastwood Angelina Tully movie?
Yes.
So there are people certainly like, you know, came out of the He-Man world.
People went on to other careers.
Well, and I think that's, you know, why there is affinity for the cartoon show,
because there are a lot of things that are easily mockable in it.
And it was produced very on a very thrifty sort of way.
And there were famously all these regulations about what they couldn't
couldn't do with the show at the time,
because it was like when the government was fighting against the idea of cartoon
shows just being commercials for toys, which they absolutely were.
And also like whether
cartoons were perverse influence on children.
So like He-Man's an action show where the characters can never really fight.
He-Man has a sword that he never once uses in a single episode.
He's never allowed to swing it at anybody.
He's never allowed to stab anybody.
I think he can only use it for deflection, like he can only use it to block
and then he uses it for his transformation.
But like the fighting on He-Man is almost always one guy gets behind another guy
and gets him in a bear hug
until the other guy pleads uncle.
This is another problem.
I think the turtles, I mean, I think government regulations,
but the turtles solve the problem with robots because like, how are you going to
have Leonardo use his sword unless these are not humans or living beings?
Right. They have some robots like Horde Troopers and Skeletor has robots.
But I think they were always so invested in trying to sell the new characters,
you know, that like they didn't have as sticky a sort of like army as the foot soldiers.
But what was I going to say? Oh, yeah, these people come to it,
these comic writers and these animation writers cutting their teeth who like
really have grand ambition, the type of genre storytelling they'd like to do.
And they start imbuing it with a weird
amount of thought and consideration.
You know, so it's like this shoe, the show produced on a shoestring to sell toys
with a mythology that doesn't make any sense.
A guy like J.
Michael Strazinski come in there and go like, but can we like actually turn this
into something? Right.
Yeah, that's what I always like.
Anytime I'm complaining about any any modern day movie, I haven't seen Space Jam
2, maybe I'm going to love it. I would love to love it.
I would love to be the contrarian.
It's a very pure good movie made for the right reasons.
And you get to see some of your friends,
you know, you get to see your friends at least.
Jabberjaw, but ultimately in the background, McGilligarilla.
I am excited to see McGilligarilla.
But anytime like any of this stuff that we would see as kids.
And I know you're like even just professionals going in and seeing
character designs, you go, I could make something cool out of this.
These characters are really awesome.
But especially as like kids, it's like it doesn't even matter that some of this
stuff sucks like you watch old turtle cartoon.
I don't give a shit. Like it's bad.
The show is bad.
I own all these toys because visually this was making me think this show is
fantastic and it was not.
But that's what anytime I'm complaining about, like any modern version of a thing
I liked as a kid, I'm like there's like eight year olds watching this.
And this is maybe the greatest thing they've ever seen.
Sure. Like they're not worried about a certain character not being treated the
way I think they should be treated.
They don't give a shit about that.
But I do think it's funny and interesting how like humans view like all of this
stuff that's made cynically.
And I guess this is what our whole show is about.
Stuff that's a product and made cynically.
But like we all feel it's real magical.
And some of it you can look back on it and it's not it's not magical at all other
than just your child brain memory of it and wanting to see it.
I think part of being a healthy appreciator of these things is learning to accept like
the goofiness of it when it exists, the crumminess of it, the craveness of it.
Like all these things are part of it.
And sometimes the parts come together and create some greater whole, you know,
that does transcend like its intentions or has some meaning for you or whatever it is.
Like this is I mean this genuinely.
This is not just me trying to sell a show.
But like I work so hard to try to get cast as work going to show.
Right. I do these audition tapes in my closet where I'm playing every single
character to show them like how invested I am because I didn't have anyone to read
with me and then I get the part and I realize I haven't read the scripts.
And I have no idea if this thing is good or not.
Right.
And I'm a fan.
And there's that worry where you're just like, am I going to read this and think
this is dog shit and now I'm orco on the dog shit show and I have to just kind of
stay quiet for a while.
And the thing that I genuinely love about the scripts that was such a relief for me
was sort of I've been told that the idea was like this is the show for people who
grew up with the cartoon. The idea is like the way it felt when you were watching it
as a little kid and everything felt important to you.
Can you make a show at that level where the stakes are real, the budget is higher,
the scripts have more time to be polished.
You're able to actually show fight scenes,
but you're able to sort of like put the emotional depth into the things that you
projected as a child, but maybe weren't fully formed.
And that was what they were saying.
And my fear was, is this going to be like overly self-serious?
The thing that I think all four of us dislike, where it's like trying to make
fans of a thing feel less guilty for liking a thing.
Right.
Yes, it's real stakes.
Insecure.
You can feel how insecure some things it's like, no, this is this is deathly serious.
The chest puffiness of it.
And like the thing I love about this show is that I think it is so in touch with
everything that is incredibly goofy about the original cartoon,
not just in terms of where it puts the humor in, but like which elements it
embraces, it's not like shunting anything that was too silly, you know,
in a way that I think a lot of these modern things go like, well,
you have to drop that character. That character wouldn't work.
You can't do this.
You know, that lines a problem.
They sort of like without spoiling anything.
And I guess some people might have watched it by this point, but they like they found
a thing in the original show that is fucked up if you think about it,
that like would be like a cracked article, right, where you're like, huh,
there's this like weird plot line on this kid's show.
If you actually think about it, that's kind of fucked up that the characters did
this and they just kind of invested in that being a real thing and like wrote
this 10 episode season that is about like the emotional and larger fallout
of that situation, but, you know, are trying to do the show that you imagine
when you were a kid, but something I think kids would also enjoy watching
and something that is also like completely unembarrassed about how silly this thing
is and where it came from is trying to keep those two things in conversation
at the same time, which is which is what I find very exciting about it.
And once again, if I thought it was dogshit, I would just say nothing.
This is my genuine opinion.
You don't have to promote anything.
Right. People might disagree with me.
And it gets into this thing we're talking about here, where fans get very
territorial, like that's not my version.
That's not what I liked about it.
I only like this era and these characters and whatever.
You're never going to make a thing that everyone likes.
And also we live in an era now where everything gets rebooted every five years,
as we're saying. So it's like there are already people who are upset about what
they think this show is going to be.
I think some of them will watch it, be pleasantly surprised.
Some of them watch it and they'll hate it.
But guess what? Like Netflix has another He-Man show coming out this year.
For kids.
And they're trying to make a live action movie and they'll do a thousand more
things like none of this stuff is sacred anymore.
I do think at a certain point, being
an adult nerd is learning to accept that, like, for so long, we had this very
clenched territorial position of like,
they're only going to get to make one Batman movie.
And if they fuck it up, then Batman will never get to be a movie again.
You know, that pressure.
And it's like, fuck, Burton did it.
It worked. It worked.
But now it's Schumacher.
And then that bombed.
Fuck, we're never going to get Batman.
Schumacher ruined Batman forever.
And now it's like he ruined Batman and Robin.
Well, and then it was perfect.
He made a perfect movie with Batman
forever, and then he made Batman and Robin, which I still like.
At this point, you're just like, like, I used to be so anti-Snyder just on a level
of just like, this is not my vibe.
Yes, I agree.
And I switched. I completely switched.
Because I'm just like, you know what?
Let this guy make his thing.
It's not for me.
I appreciate what he's doing in the same way.
I read fucking comic books.
And if I don't like one Batman arc, I'm like, well, OK.
And then a new writer will come on and negate all of it and do their own thing.
Whatever. Who cares?
Yes, I am 100 percent.
I was feeling the same way.
I was like, oh, this is just going to be all of the DC.
It's all going to feel like this.
Oh, man. Come on.
Like, I don't want it to be so bleak or whatever.
And I'm like, there's going to be another one next year who gives a shit.
And then I watched them again now in that context.
And I'm like, there's a lot to enjoy with this nonsense, with this bleak nonsense.
And I think if you're going to be a healthy fan of anything, you have to learn
to love your songsters, you know, like the songsters aren't the things you hide.
You have to accept that's part of the weird history of the thing.
It's what I like about Masters of the Inverse is that it was such an accident
that these things get like pieced together in reverse, you know, that like
you cannot claim the sanctity of the thing.
Well, I think you got to do like two things.
You got to play it straight.
You know, you got to like, you know,
be a little respectful to what's come before and like play in the world.
But then also you have to have fun with it.
And like part of my engaging with stuff and having fun with stuff,
it's like teasing the goofiness.
Like, I feel like on this show, like people sometimes a bit like, oh, well,
they hate that. I was like, I don't hate that.
I love that. I would rather be on this
attraction than running errands my day to day life.
But it's a little goofy.
Like there's some corny shit in it.
But yeah, I think the fun sometimes,
you know, I think I think especially the Marvel stuff, they're starting to branch
out a lot more in the movies and TV shows and add more characters.
And
but but I think some of the shortcomings like like rough, it's like, all right,
you've set up too many rules like you're not playing it straight.
You're not honoring your your you set up too many restrictions for yourself.
And you don't seem like you're having fun.
You seem like you're checking out boxes.
Yeah. And like you have to have.
If not embrace the goofy elements, you have to at least sort of accept them
as being like part of the whole of this thing, right?
At the very least, the evolution of this thing, the different eras of these things,
whatever these odd elements are, be they a theme park ride or, you know,
a cartoon show or a toy line or whatever it is, rather than starting a change.org
petition to ask that it be officially taken out of continuity because it's like
sometimes the best shit comes out of people course correcting after something
that's unpopular, the answer isn't that no longer counts.
It's unofficial. Never acknowledge it ever again.
It's like what what can we learn from what didn't work here?
And when you step back, you can like
appreciate Adam West and Michael Keaton equally for doing different things.
And like, you know, that's that's part of the beauty of the stupid shit we care about a lot.
Yes, it's just
seeing anyone who's like like religious and dogmatic is really isn't, as I said,
on those Facebook groups I'm on, it's you'd be surprised how many people get very upset.
I'm not surprised. I mean, I mean, you wouldn't be surprised.
Are you in the man? Are you I don't maybe I'm outing you.
I shouldn't even say which I do.
You tell me off air which I look around.
I look around some things. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
I look around. I mean, I and I have forever.
You know, I just feel like
I don't want to harp on this, but it's weird because there was no new he man stuff for a while.
Right. And in that time, fandom has curdled.
And I feel like these message boards and these websites and these groups and whatever
that I used to lurk, I was never a big poster, but I would read these things
and I would be like abreast of what fans thought were responding to things.
There'd be disagreements about things.
People dislike stuff.
They'd get up in arms about toys and whatever.
It's like it's not like it was entirely civil and serene, but there there is this weird
aggro defensive paranoia about this new show, about whatever the kids show is going to be,
where there's this it's an extension of the Kathy Kennedy shit where people want to buy
into this idea that like whatever is being rebooted is being rebooted by like OCP
and Dick Jones is behind the boardroom and he's like, I want people to die.
I don't care. And 209 has to succeed.
It doesn't matter.
You know, like like there's a conspiratorial attack and resentment of fans.
There's like, yeah, there's like whoever's posting is like he really thinks like
Kathleen Kennedy is like, I want to punish Ben from Missouri.
I want him.
I want him to feel pain.
I hate Ben.
I hate that Ben likes Luke.
And so I'm going to cuck Luke.
So Ben feels bad.
Like they truly were not exaggerate.
You see people post these videos and they're creating like narratives about like
this is the fight going on within Lucasfilm.
Oh, I know exactly who you're talking about.
I know exactly the videos.
These people are claiming Kathleen Kennedy did not want Luke Skywalker to be
in the Mandalorian spoiler for a season two finale that came out fucking nine
months ago and that everywhere that Jon Favreau smuggled him onto set.
And Kathy Kennedy didn't know about it and was outraged and wanted to smuggle
him into the previs department.
Well, what the fuck are you talking about?
He was digitally rendered.
What are you talking about?
The guy you're talking about makes videos every week about this.
Yes. And like that Jon Jon.
He calls him Jon Favreau, first of all, which always funny to me.
And he's like, it's just like it's like he's like physically battling Kathleen
Kennedy, like it's Kathleen Kennedy and Brie Larson.
And now there's a different channel that once a week has been doing anti
mo to revelation stuff. Oh, and no.
All right. Look, Griffin, you get you got a pick.
You either get the super fans who love this stuff or you get the weird
moralistic teens who are doing like tipper gore shit.
And it's like, I don't know.
I think he man revelation is like, oh, that's kind of weird.
It's look, it's a it's a it's a tough choice.
And ultimately, I try not I try to focus on the people who seem to be enjoying
things in a healthy way.
It is just
frustrating to see people doing that sort of like
rumor mongering and projecting of what they think is going on behind the scenes
and knowing for a fact, it's false.
Like with Kathy Kennedy, I know it's false
because I am a reasonable human being who understands how the world works.
And someone does not take over Lucasfilm and go, my job is to destroy this.
I want this to fail so that boys feel bad.
But I don't want to keep having money.
My mission is pain now.
I mean, I saw a website that claimed that Disney literally has decided not to care
about money and to instead let all these properties fail to advance the woke
agenda. And it's like, if that's what they said at the last meeting, we were all at
the last media meeting. We were all there.
If you just typed out the sentence, Disney doesn't even care about money anymore,
you should take a really long look in the mirror.
The woke.
Oh, by the way, I want everyone to be reminded that the woke agenda means on a
piece of paper, it says Loki is bisexual.
Yes, that's what reflected in the series.
It's no, not yet.
That's like people are projecting into the fact like Tila has a different haircut
and that Orko has eyes that they think look more feminine on this version of the show.
And then your ass is grass.
My ass is grass.
And they're producing like 40 minute videos of their conjecture of what they think
is being like planned out in a boardroom to punish people who grew up with this
stuff. And it's just wild.
So the character who is on this live tour in skating around in a dress, they are
worried about some femininity entering.
Yeah.
And this is like a character that half of them found annoying in the first place.
And I say this as someone who loved him dearly and did not find him annoying.
Orko, the winner of the attorney in race, right?
The best roller skater.
I mean, you got to feel good about that.
You must have been on pins and needles.
I feel incredible.
I mean, he's got he's got some hits in the show.
He also has his number where he's trying to make magic work saying hocus shocus.
And it keeps on failing until he does
successfully conjure up a dancer.
His magic is conjuring one dancer added to all the dancers that are already on stage.
And then in the attorney in circus, he comes out in a different outfit,
like a different robe and is like the co ringleader.
The attorney in circus stuff like sucks, by the way.
We didn't talk about it, but it's just they parade out.
I never found it.
What is it?
Dumb animals like it's all these like the actors who were playing the actual heroes
and villains you like in the first act of the show are now in like two part four
people, eight legged like this is an attorney in giraffe.
That's like very to rook the avatar like Cirque du Soleil.
I feel like a little more like to rook.
It also feels a little like the weird circus number in the Star Wars Holiday
Special. Oh, yeah.
Where it's just like kind of a long parade of like, here's a new species on
attorney, our elephants have four trunks or whatever.
It's a songster and orco like spinning around singing the same song, showing off
these crappy costumes.
And then the show finally kind of rebounds in the last 15 minutes and Skeletor comes
out and they actually like do the fight.
Then there's like the big fucking fight that everyone's been waiting for.
Nobody is that on YouTube.
I never found the fight.
It's also I only saw a lot of skating.
Yeah, the fights hard to find.
Once again, it's label.
It's a video that I think is labeled VTS 0 1 3.
Oh, yeah.
Well, I guess I don't feel bad about not finding it then.
Yeah.
And it's really, really low quality and it's statics out pretty early.
But yeah, the first half of the show is definitely better.
The second half is way too much attorney in circus.
What the hell is this?
I'm looking at this synopsis.
He man, I just saw the sentence he man fights all three Skeletor's.
He beats the fake ones and eventually finds the real one.
Yeah, we have multiple Skeletor's around.
It's like a magical decoy thing.
Yeah.
Can I have it on your show?
Fake Skeletor? Yeah, they're fake Skeletor's.
No spoilers.
There aren't their decoy versions of other characters.
Oh, can I ask who's by on the show?
Well, I want to be mad.
I want to get mad about that.
All of them.
If you ask Clownfish TV on YouTube, everyone is by.
OK, all right.
Shove down our throats.
Got it.
Seriously, maybe this is a question off the air.
Internally, are you trying to push for a new tour, a new live show that you could
be a part of? I would love nothing more.
I'd love nothing more because I've been trying to nudge my way into Turtles for
years and I would be the most annoying person if I had even like a one line on an
episode. I'd be like, I would try to get everyone's email and be like, no, we should do.
I've really like the amount of energy I've
had to spend keeping my cool about this mic, like when I'm in the professional
settings and the job,
I mean, because it like I I become very
quickly overcome within the terror of what if I fuck this up?
Right.
So like a lot of that like nerdy, like can I ram myself into this and pitch a
thousand ideas shit goes out the window because I'm just like, oh, what if I suck
at this? I just need to be laser focused, at least doing the things they're asking
me to do. Right.
But I also would voice or go in anything like I would do anything.
You would do like a 90s city tour of arenas playing or go on stage.
Absolutely.
In the suit with your face not visible.
Yeah, you wouldn't be seen.
It would just be your voice. Right.
Like the the other the sort of kids modern
reboot show for Netflix that's coming out later.
I looked into like playing or go on that and they're like, no, it's a different
show. It's a different continuity.
But I was like, but what if I just played or go on everything?
What if I just sure they claim to this?
So you saw your soft your soft
like touching the boundary, touching the boundaries lightly.
I mean, that conclusively didn't work, but I have tested.
I have tested. Yes.
So maybe live tour is not something you could get done right now.
I push for it, certainly.
I mean, I think it depends on what the response is to this.
You know, it's five episodes coming out
today that this episode comes out and five episodes coming out another point this
year. And I think it works as a self-contained thing.
Like, I think if this is the only thing we ever get to make, I think this is a
pretty good like it's sort of in my mind's eye, the kind of thing I'd
imagine a He-Man movie being.
It feels like a very epic story that is tied to the history of this property
told on a grand scale, incorporating as many characters and vehicles and things
as you remember as possible.
But I think everyone would like to do more if if the interest is there.
Like it has not been designed to pointedly be a one off is not one division.
If people want more, I think everyone wants to do it.
And I certainly would like to just absolutely
run or go into the ground.
Hey, great. Wow.
Looks like, hey, Mayor of Eastdown has a new partner.
This season, why it's Detective Orko.
And he's by so by
one more question is is on your show is does Orko have visible duct tape
holding his hat onto his head?
No, it is.
It is a funny thing.
Pulled up a photo, by the way, that's what you like.
It is so like this.
This is what they put in the program.
It's such a wild costume, especially because I would argue the rest of the
costumes are pretty high level executions, especially for this type of show.
And the Orko one is really kind of haphazard.
Orko is also tough because like Orko's tiny, like Orko sort of like great
gazoo size, just floating around characters' heads.
So when you need a human person to play it, the scale gets all thrown off.
So like the commentary I was watching from the convention, they were saying
the woman who played Orko was for ten, like they found the shortest performer
they possibly could.
But even so, it makes Orko look weirdly
gigantic because like Orko doesn't have any legs.
So the robe has to extend past the actor's feet, which makes the torso look huge.
You know, and then the hands are bigger because they put bigger gloves to be in
scale with the torso and then the hat has to get so big.
And then where's the head in this?
The head up.
This is what I was about to say.
Oh, the actor's head, I think, is in.
Above the eyes, maybe.
Maybe I feel like the arms we're seeing, like the shoulders are in the scarf.
If that makes any sense.
I think so. Yeah, it is confusing where they're coming from.
Right. And their face is either above the eyes or in the hat itself.
It does not look like a very easy costume to operate.
But this is the other thing, Orko,
from a design perspective, the idea is he's a trollen, right?
Which is like this magical troll type species in the Motu lore.
But his face is hidden all the time.
They can't show their faces.
So Orko, it's like supposed to be that that's the shadow created from under his
hat and the scarf around the lower part of his face.
And so the eyes are the only things that you're able to see in the shadow.
Whenever you three dimensionalize Orko, it gets very spatially odd because it
looks like his head is just a black featureless orb with two eyes on it.
It's not like a black tree trunk.
Right. Right.
The idea is that you can't see his face.
It's cloaked in mystery.
Right. Yeah.
Well, it makes you respect.
I'm going to be wearing it.
Yeah.
You'll have a perfect understanding about this works when you're hitting the road,
when you're given shout outs to Calgary,
happy to do it when I'm begging them to let me do this.
Yeah, it might just be an Orko tour.
If they don't want to do the whole thing, it might just be like Orko comes alive.
Yeah.
Sure. Yeah.
River dance with Orko.
Yeah.
Or just one man show.
Just every every talent you have and every talent you think Orko would have.
And you have to develop that from scratch.
It's like Mark Twain tonight.
I just do my sort of like.
Yeah.
The poster is Orko with like his tie undone, holding a cigarette and a drink,
like a lamp and looking down.
Yeah.
We're going to do some songs, do some stories.
Just telling tales from his childhood.
Yeah. Fun stuff.
Weird stuff. You know, Garth Brooks, like Garth Brooks' Facebook.
Long-combed Facebook presence.
Start the conversation.
What a time.
Let's see.
Well, did we do it?
Did we survive podcast ride Legends of Eternia edition?
I think so.
I mean, feel free to shout out anything else from the I just have like spare quotes
throughout the rest of it, like, oh, no, where's Rock on?
I don't know what they're connected to.
I mean, there's so many.
There's great little or as we call him, Rocky.
I think I just thought that's the thing I love.
No, thank you for reminding me of this.
Rock on is also a late character.
He comes from the Stone Warriors and they're a race of sort of semi cybernetic
characters, robotic characters who have the ability to camouflage as rocks
so that people don't attack them and they can sneak up by just laying stagnant
on a battlefield and it's Rock on and Stone Dar and Granita.
They only put Rock on in this.
But his whole thing is that he's like a transformer, right?
It was Mattel trying to get in on the Transformers market.
And so they they announced him in the show and I was like, how are they going to
fucking pull this off as a costume because it has to look like Rock on in like
humanoid form and the rock form and in the cartoon they do all sorts of like they
take all sorts of license with design to make that transition happen.
And with the toy, it's like engineering that a human body can't do.
And with this, they're just like Rock on Rock on.
Where's Rock on? Has anyone seen Rock on?
Then a video screen shows a meteor.
Then there's a crash sound and then Rock on stands up and they're like, oh, there he
is. So they just never show him as a rock on stage and explain why that was him.
And now he's just going to be standing up the rest of the time.
Oh, that's why.
Oh, no. Where's Rock Rock on?
Yes. That takes care of that problem.
I love this lazy Bing Crosby take on He-Man.
I could listen to this guy's voice all day.
I really wish I'd seen this.
If I'd seen the show, I think I would have thought about it my whole life.
It is so grand.
And
I guess that's I. Hey, we use Griffin Newman.
You survived podcast the ride once again for time.
I believe time number five.
I think this is the I think you're in the five timers.
Yes, there's there's.
Wow. This is huge.
Yes, it's the 3D movie trilogy of 2019.
Yeah.
And the and the second gate, Jimmy Fallon, record breaking Jimmy Fallon episode.
Yes. Yeah.
And unless you count smaller, unless you count your performance as the.
Oh, sure. Whichever kid.
No, I think it's host. I think I think or not hosting.
It's hosting.
Yeah. Yeah. Full guest appearances.
And some people will decree that this does not count as a proper five because
second gate is its own continuity, to which I'll say that's why we have
redacted, controversial ride and Muppet Haunted Mansion on the books for 2021.
Yeah. Which I think would get you up to.
I was trying to crunch the numbers.
I think Eva Anderson has the title for most appearances.
If you count on this second gate counts as his own thing.
She's almost entirely second gate.
But I think it's one that fucking YouTuber.
I know he goes on about it every week.
Listen, you don't know anything about
Kathy Kennedy and you don't know anything about the second gate.
Lay off.
He hates the second gate.
The second gate is what's happening behind the doors of this behind the gates
of the second gate. The second gate is too woke, quite frankly.
It is just bizarre that fan culture has gone from like, oh, like fan fiction is
this robust thing where people want to write their own stories with the characters
to now people want to write their own fan fiction about what's happening
at a corporate level. Yeah.
He popped a correct pod into the machine, grumbling as he reached for his mug.
The term like forced their dinner plans for the diversity, forced diversity.
And you're like, did you ever see the movie Predator?
Like the movie is diverse.
Like it's in like, you know, you know, you can cast you cast people.
Humans cast people that are.
Yeah, I mean, also, I try to repeat this whenever I can in any fucking medium,
because I don't feel like this gets circulated enough.
They recently went viral again.
A clip of Carl Sagan on Johnny Carson complaining about the fact that everyone's
white in Star Wars, right?
And he's like on a scientific level, that doesn't make sense.
Like on a scientific level, it doesn't make sense that the people in power
look like humans, even though they're not.
And they're all white and they're all like this.
Like they would have crazy alien colors
or at the very least would resemble other races on our planet.
Sure. And people were like Carl Sagan saying
the shit that everyone was afraid to say.
What doesn't get acknowledged a lot is that he says that that was a big fucking
interview because it was the time when everyone watched it.
People in the media started talking about the lack of diversity in Star Wars.
And Lando was specifically written and created to address that.
Like the exact thing that people get up in arms saying that Disney is doing,
which is like shoving diversity down their throats and creating characters just
to fill a quota Lando, who you all fucking love, was George Lucas taking
the criticism to heart and going like, yeah, I should hire a very charismatic
actor and put him in this franchise and set him up as an old friend of these
preexisting characters so that he's earned his place in this universe.
Isn't it interesting that you liked it
when you were a kid and when you watch it now, you go, what's the agenda here?
Why are they forcing this on you?
If you watch Alien or Predator, the original Alien, like I don't.
All these things. Yeah.
All of them. And they always go like, well,
I like Ripley because she's actually a good character.
Not these characters today where they're
just a woman for the sake of making me angry.
Right. Like what's the what do you think the difference is?
Yeah. And science fiction, like the history of modern science fiction is
authors slipping in future looking ideas, ideas of like progressive societies,
of diversity, of different ways of thinking.
And like people either, you know, they absorb it and inadvertently get the lesson
or like maybe it goes over their heads and they just see it on a surface level.
But it's in there like it's in all of this stuff.
Yeah. On that note, I would like to plug
Masters of the Universe Revelation, the wokest he man to date.
So much is going to get shoved down your throat.
Open your throats, everyone, because so much so many agendas.
Nothing but agendas.
I'm a big fan of episode five, which is just Clamp Champ explaining
critical race theory for 30 minutes.
Well, I'm glad someone is.
Yeah, someone has to.
No, I think it's a good show.
And I think most of the people who are up in arms about it will actually
like it if they watch it and don't listen to YouTube.
I think I think the people were paying it.
I think they like probably the megaphones loom larger
currently because it hasn't come out.
And when it comes out, it'll be mostly people who like and enjoy it and enjoy.
I'm not losing sleep over this, but it is just one of those
frustrating things to watch where you're like, oh, the the loudest megaphones
are the people who are creating hour long videos based on conjecture
versus the people who will like this show, who cannot weigh in
because they haven't seen it yet and aren't writing things about what they think
is going to happen like a lunatic.
Well, we get all that pre conjecture about what blue shirt
Jason's going to wear next.
And I just like let him pick the shirt and then you'll see.
I got a couple of new ones.
That's part of the process.
I also I just want to plug, as I always do, blank check.
My podcast with David Sims, past guests of this show as well.
What's Kensington?
Chessington, Chessington, Chessington, Chessington, Chessington.
The most frightening
80s sci fi rides you've ever seen.
That was really something.
He really brought us something we were completely unaware of.
But to acknowledge the
a now non joking online podcast controversy.
There is a there is a section of shared blank check
PTR listeners who have continued to be outraged
at the fact that the three of you have not appeared on blank check yet.
Oh, sure. I want to stay here.
It's getting acknowledged. Oh, my God.
Not a conspiracy.
There are there are culprits, most of which are based around disorganization.
The fact that until the pandemic, we never let Zoom records happen.
Yeah, we book things far in advance.
There's a lot of weird strategizing that goes into how we plan out our main series.
A regret was that
Scott, you obviously would have been a great guest for Back to the Future Part Two.
Nicole Byer had called that very early.
Oh, you don't say no to Nicole Byer.
You never. Right. Right.
But but if I can just also say just to kind of peel back the curtain a little bit,
I want to as a commitment. OK. Whoa, whoa.
Our schedule, we booked very far in advance.
We always do.
It's because we go chronologically through filmography as David has a baby now.
We need to plan things out. Oh, yeah. That's David.
The rest of this year is full.
I'm committing to all three good boys appearing on blank check main feed 2022.
Oh, my God. Wow. Exciting.
That's something to look forward to, at least for us.
I don't know about the audience, but I'm excited.
I want to say because this is the other factor that was at play.
And this is not a good excuse.
As a friend, I feel like this is not a good excuse.
I'm not talking as a podcast creator, but talk as a friend.
I don't think this is a good excuse.
In my mind, I had this idea
that it would be cute to save you guys for Pirates of the Caribbean.
Wow. Oh, interesting.
That was my thing, where I was just sort of like maximum impact.
Would it be best? And I never told this to you guys.
I was like, would it be best if we saved it and we had all three of you on one
or we did the trilogy and each of you did one?
Because Gore Verbinski felt like he was a guy we were going to do at some point.
Then we put him on our march, badness bracket this year and chaos broke out.
And I don't know if Gore Verbinski is happening any time in the foreseeable future.
Oh, interesting.
So a lot of weird shit got stirred up in the Gore Verbinski thing.
And at least for the time being, we're putting that on the sidelines.
So that's why I'm saying.
Look, also, I've never seen any of these films, so I probably wouldn't be a good guess.
Wow, really? No, not one other like theme park movie are we going to cover.
It's not like you guys can only come on to talk about theme park.
I thought that would be a nice kind of poetic crossover.
And that was the one obvious thing to do.
And there are three of those movies and what have you.
So I kept that in my mind.
That's now off the table.
We booked the rest of the year.
Twenty twenty two. We're going to figure something out.
Wow. Wow. I don't know if it's separate episodes.
I don't know if it's three of you on one episode.
We don't know exactly what we're doing for 2022 yet.
But I just want to state that cleanly.
Well, if you think Carol Reed, the long dead, Carol Reed,
the third man, has a big Ferris wheel scene, a vitally,
a vitally important Ferris wheel scene.
I like that you jumped to the third man as the next most obvious theme park movie.
Well, that's my favorite movie.
So I was being selfish. Oh, sure. Sure. Sure.
Well, you already look, you already did Joe Dirt.
So I'm I'm up Shick Creek now.
That would have been Scott's choice.
Yeah, obviously.
If there's an Adam Carolla movie about wokeness, I'll do that one.
The ringer, right?
It was a ringer.
Is that what it's called?
Is it? Didn't you do one?
Yeah, but there's also a stand up one.
There's one called Road Comic or University.
There's newer, like more.
I feel like he made a movie.
Maybe his first movie wasn't so like focused on.
Carolla is a great blank check director.
I think if you ever do Bill Maher, obviously,
we'd love to throw our heads in the ring.
Dennis Prager, you know, all the filmmakers.
Dennis Prager is one of my favorite filmmakers.
Oh, God, don't click.
Oh, no, don't let anyone clip that.
Each decision.
Fuck, you beat me to do that.
I will say I because last year, not last two years ago,
for March Madness, our bracket, we do where we let people vote on which director
we're going to cover. We had this idea to a theme bracket where one side was all
best director Oscar winners and one side was all
worst director Razzie winners.
And David and I had a very long drawn out,
like over weeks or months fight about whether or not to include
Dinesh D'Souza in the bracket.
And I wanted to include him.
I don't know if that was the right choice.
But at the time, I was arguing to include him.
He did, in fact, win a Razzie for directing
Hillary's America.
I don't remember if it was that or if it was
26. What is it?
2016 is Hillary's America.
And then the other one is called like America.
Imagine a world without her.
Well, we when the three of us and Paul Shear
and I forget who else was there, Ben Rogers, maybe Gabriels.
Like when we saw Mission Impossible fall out in the downtown
L.A. with the seats that rattle and move, we were like making fun of in the lobby.
There was a poster for Dinesh D'Souza.
And then as we were going to our theater, there was like a big
like step and repeat background and like a photo.
And we're like, are we walking by a Dinesh D'Souza premiere?
There's no one here.
I went to see two of them in theaters.
I bought tickets for other movies, so I didn't have to support him.
But I was very fascinated by him in a pre Trump era
where it felt like the damage he could cause was somewhat minimal.
But just to clarify, I combined three separate titles.
There's 2016 Obama's America.
Then there's America.
Imagine the world without her and Hillary's America,
the secret history of the Democratic Party.
Which is a movie in which he presents his grand thesis
that actually the Democrats are Nazis.
Oh, my God.
That was discussed at the meeting where we talked about
Disney not being interested in money.
You know, yes, yes, absolutely.
All right.
So those are my thoughts.
We'll all get to that one.
There's three of them than three good boys.
Exactly.
The ultimate good boy.
Dinesh on the book will do the the America trilogy.
His his remaining two films, I feel like once Trump got elected,
his juice was gone.
Like I know he got a lot of retweets on Twitter,
but those three movies made stupid amounts of money in theaters.
And then the other two, Death of a Nation and Trump Cart,
I feel like made no imp.
Once he wasn't standing in opposition.
Yeah, it's it's well, it's been a nice diffuser of a lot of
of a lot of bullshit stuff that's like pretty bad.
On kind of a moral level and mainly on a graphic design level.
Yes, we see so much less horrendous graphic design and documentaries.
Now, I mean, the poster for Death of a Nation is a composite
where the right half of the face is Abraham Lincoln
and the left half is Donald Trump.
And I will tell you, that is a very jarring transition.
Yeah. In hair, in skull shape, in complexion.
Yes.
OK, so we're set for that.
We're set for other.
I still am like I am so curious about the to me.
It's not a controversial, redacted ride, but unless you guys feel different.
But I was less interesting if it's not a fight.
I it's it's on the I think I can say this on Mike.
It's on the books. Yeah.
I'm going to be coming to Los Angeles in a couple of months for for,
in fact, Power Con, the He-Man Convention.
Oh, I wasn't sure if you wanted to bring it up.
You're going to be at Power Con where, by the way,
the Anaheim Convention Center, where the power tour played when it was in town.
You'll be in the room where Songster himself said his name.
So I'm going to be in Anaheim for that.
And I'm the four of us are going to go to the parks together,
which I've never gone to go to the parks with you guys.
Oh, my. And then we're going to record an in-person episode
theoretically about this redacted, controversial ride.
But all I'm saying is in the time between now and when that happens,
when I see you guys next in person and it's lovely,
I'm going to fucking go back and find the clip where you guys talk racy
about this ride, because I swear it.
I hear it. I swear it happened because I know my email was in response to that.
Was it what maybe was a joke?
It just felt like it wasn't super critical,
but it was kind of like a little off the shoulder dismissive.
Like, I don't care.
We're never going to do an episode about that.
Well, the biggest, most questionable thing to me is that we would ever say,
let's not do an episode.
That's why I emailed because it was so wild that it was like not even.
That's a second gate.
It was like, can we just say we'll never do an episode about that ride?
That's could that be just the most deadpan joke delivery possible?
Like the most Bob Newhart style deadpan?
I don't know. I'm just I'm just saying stay tuned for that episode for Dacted
Ride. I think that we're treating this ride like it's Kevin Spacey,
like it's like the subject we can't name.
It's going to be so confusing when it comes out and when it's just like a ride,
like what people like, I believe there's really no way to know.
I don't think what was said exactly,
except I think the only way might be to release Jason's notes.
It's the only way we're going to start this out specifically,
release the notes. No tear. I agree.
Jason's full archive of notes needs to be released if we could actually know.
Let's publish it in a book. Jason, to end this episode,
can you just scroll to a different part of your notes and share screen with us?
Yeah. A different page of notes that we haven't seen.
You don't have to share with the whole podcast,
but can we see it and read out loud and you get to pick which page it is of
what the masters, the notes, your notes for this. Yeah. Yeah.
Any note, any part you want. Any note for this episode.
Or else we're going to have to make a really,
we're going to have to make a crazy documentary about you. Jason's America.
2022 Jason's notes. All right. Let me, here's the bottom.
So this is, this is,
sometimes I will, when watching along, make just like impressions when watching.
Them introducing Songster was pretty stiff. Agreed. Yes.
Next. His name is Songster.
And somebody could have used a songster. Yeah. Mortal Kombat.
Live. Absolutely. Oh my God.
There wasn't a lot going on with Mortal Kombat. Live. Of course.
The song is Troubadour for sure. Yeah. Well, I will say Jason. Yes.
Some of these are direct quotes,
but seeing them in this format just as like kind of bullet pointed notes on a
spreadsheet where you don't put them in quotes,
it makes it feel like you, Jason, yourself are typing in,
welcome to my universe masters of the universe. Oh yeah.
Well I use quotes if I'm like you like actually writing down,
but if I'm watching live, I'm trying to keep up with the live video.
So, uh, yeah.
Lots of presentations and singing and roller skating.
There's a sword fight and still 15 minutes left in this show.
So I think that was cause I watched most of the act one one and I was surprised
like, wait, wouldn't you,
this is either the end of half of the show or the end of all of the show.
Wouldn't you end on a big sword fight? And then no,
there was like another 15 minutes of just hanging out.
Well it's like, wouldn't you end this episode by saying you survive podcasts,
the ride and then like a couple more things.
Or do you do another half hour after that?
Possibly.
This is what we did.
But I don't mind it because now there's plans. There's plans for 2021,
there's plans for 2022 and you can keep abreast of all of it on our socials at
podcast. The ride is merchant RT public store and for three bonus episodes every
month, check out podcast, the ride, the second gate at patreon.com slash podcast,
the ride where Griffin will not be. It's main feed. You're saying,
look, maybe one of the two, maybe Muppets haunted man is second gate.
I want to show love to the second gators.
I don't want to feel like I'm neglecting them.
You know, when we do three hours on the good, the bad and the low key, you know,
we're going to probably hide behind the second gate.
On the Simpsons, the good, the bad and the low key.
Yeah, that's right. Yeah. Everyone's demanding it.
I just noticed on Disney plus the force awakens from her naps.
Where did that come from? I've never seen that.
I think that came out on star Wars day. Okay. That came out recently.
I want to say May of this year.
It's the same fucking thing as the good, the bad, the low key.
Um, yeah, yeah. One of those. Okay. Yeah. Well, we'll get to that.
We'll get to so much Griffin. Thanks so much for being here.
Thanks to you all for checking it out. And by the way, podcast,
the ride is our name.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson,
Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo,
and Alex Ramsey. For more original podcasts,
please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com and subscribe to our shows on
Apple podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and
Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.