Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast contains abusive wood, a sad man's clock room, a father and
son reunion, and the real life fairy tale of competing on the magical game show, The Price
is Right.
Aaron Garner returns to tell us the tale and talk Pinocchio's daring journey on today's
podcast, The Ride.
Hi, diddle-dee-dee, a podcaster's life for we.
This is Podcast The Ride.
I'm Scott Garner joined by Mike Carlson.
Hi.
Joined by Mike Carlson.
When I thought about what joke we might make, it was exactly that joke.
Hey, all right.
Great minds think averagely.
I said, yeah, Scott doesn't have anything.
I got something in the chamber, something real original.
You know, it felt nice and jaunty to say it.
Gave me the boost I needed.
Jason Sheridan.
How are you?
And if you'll take a look at my notes, I also have hi-deedle-deedee, a podcaster's life.
I written down.
This is across the board the same?
Yeah, completing the Patrick.
I wasn't smart enough to land on we.
I said me.
Oh, that I think was the key change.
I think that's the little bit of magic.
If we were on match game, we would have all matched.
That's right.
If Gene Rayburn were asking us to fill that in.
You know, it's funny you mention that because we are joined by a game show luminary today.
Long running game show luminary.
Besides that, well, there's a list of superlatives that I wanted to say that are new since the
time our guest was here, which was way back in the City Walk saga.
Which was I think it was that like nine years ago now.
That's how it feels.
That's right.
But since she was here last, she's the designer, not just of our main logo, but of the second
gate logo and our best piece of T public merch, Potana Kush, our beloved Potana Kush.
She and I also since last time she was here, we collaborated on a human being.
That's an ongoing project.
It's going well.
And but most importantly, she's a recent winner on the price is right.
Erin Gardner, come on down.
Happy to be here.
Oddly enough, I also had hi diddley dee podcasters life for we so we've got the full match.
You guys match the couples match the couples match.
Written on your hand.
Thank you for bringing it in.
Thanks for being here.
Good to have you.
Thank you for having me.
We were going to do this back in what was it?
February of 2020.
Yeah.
And then I got bronchitis and then COVID happened.
So we were going to do this episode a very long time ago and I thought it was going to
be second gate bronchitis to.
Yeah.
Remember I was super, super sick in February when I was pregnant.
I don't remember that because so many things that one's completely left my head.
And also it was that I think there was a date set and then we found out fries was closing
on the day like that all happened.
So so many things conspired to make this episode not happen, which was potentially going to
be the announcement of our son of you expecting.
It was almost going to happen.
Of your little wooden boy.
We're still waiting for him to become a real boy, but he hasn't found the courage yet.
Yeah, he's got to prove himself.
Yeah.
Pure of heart and truthful.
Well, he's a little dick right now.
So I'm just kidding.
He's John and Gideon smoking American spirits in the back.
He's on Pleasure Island right now while you guys are here.
Because he's not with you.
No, I mean, I don't know where he is, honestly.
No, he's offending for himself.
Yeah, he's learning.
He's getting his virtue.
His first word is tobacco.
That's why it's like almost difficult to talk about this topic today.
It feels like a preview of what years of parenting are going to be like.
Yeah.
Extremely harrowing cigars.
A lot of cigars.
Tons and tons of cigars.
Snatching cigars out of a child's mouth constantly.
That's what Jason's childhood was like.
You know, if it's what the 1930s were like, then thank God we live today.
This is such a grim, the film really.
Way back when we were going to do that, I think we watched the movie in preparation.
If you have a faint memory of that.
We did.
And it's horrifying.
I loved Pinocchio when I was a kid.
It was one of my favorites.
It was like Cinderella, Pinocchio.
Those were probably one and two.
And it is horrible to watch now.
I don't know if you've watched the film recently.
I have not watched it.
I was actually in preparation.
I read what the original story was, which I will read a piece of it at a certain point
today because it's very funny to me.
But I was watching some clips of it.
I loved it as a kid.
But yeah, it's the nightmare inducing.
Yes, it's it's it cracks me up that it's like family like film because to me it's horror.
This is a horror film.
I might as well be watching Saw.
Yes.
I mean, there's definitely like it starts with like kind of a Cronenberg style, like
come to like something that shouldn't be turning into a human turns into a human.
Hundred percent.
There's so much body horror.
So much body horror and Pinocchio.
Between the nose and the and the donkey stuff.
Yes, the donkey stuff is very disturbing.
I get like hot thinking about it.
Like when I watch things that make me like just psychologically uncomfortable, I start
to shake and get like hot like hot flesh.
Not hot.
You don't get it's not a it's not a turn on.
OK, no, let's be clear.
I get like like somebody get me a cold towel because I feel like I'm going to faint.
Yeah.
Pinocchio's hero's journey is not dissimilar from like one of the Indiana Joneses where
he's just constantly getting his ass kicked.
But he doesn't get to do any ass kick.
Like Pinocchio doesn't kick anyone's ass.
No, he just constantly gets manipulated and fooled and tricked.
He's a child.
He's a freshly born child.
He's like an impossibility like like like doesn't shouldn't exist.
He's a child like.
Yes.
You mean saying he's godless like a monster.
Yeah.
Does he get does he have the soul?
Does he prove he has a soul or does the blue fairy when she grants him boyhood give him
a soul?
That's it.
Does his daring journey is what gets him the soul?
Yeah, I guess.
Yeah, but even but it is a journey in which he has no agency.
He's just shoved from bad room to bad room.
Yeah.
It's worse than the last.
Then the last bad room is the sea.
And yes, the room is a whale.
The room is inside a whale.
Why is and Geppetto is that disgusting that like he is an old man and he like he never
found love like you know his backstory.
And that's really presumptuous.
I don't know.
Maybe you might.
Maybe he had a barren wife.
Well, now that we're not.
I thought we were to start with.
She was made of what was all splinters inside.
We're going to have to start with Pinocchio here and then we'll get back to Price is Right
because I was looking through the original story Pinocchio.
This is just the Wikipedia.
I did not get the book.
I'm a very terrible reader.
I'm an idiot.
I'm terrified of this because every it's always like the Little Mermaid is so nice.
Well, you know, the origin, the original.
Well, she was nine and got gutted by a hook and like they're always so horrible.
But after America sings, all rides are now a mercy.
All rides are a blessing.
Oh, yeah.
This is a this is a great attraction.
I will say this, even though some of the stuff is depressing, I laugh out loud at least two
times per paragraph of the original Pinocchio.
Right.
Settle in.
So so so bear with me here.
There's a lot of this and you cut me off of this doesn't become interesting anymore.
A carpenter named Master Antonio, but whom everyone calls Master Cherry has found a block
of wood which he plans to carve into a leg for his table.
Sorry, Antonio and Cherry.
Who are these?
I don't know.
These are new.
These characters, I believe, were cut out of the original Disney movie.
When he begins, however, the log shouts out, frightened by the talking log.
Master Cherry gives it to his neighbor, Geppetto, an extremely poor man who plans to make a
living as a puppeteer in hopes of earning a crust of bread and a glass of wine.
Isn't that what we're all looking for, though?
Accurate expectations, I think.
Yes.
He's a DIY content maker, just like us.
Exactly.
Press some bread, please.
I am but a poor streamer, good eye.
But a poor podcaster, may I trouble you for a food box subscription sponsorship?
Jason holding the old Dickens cup.
Like the poo.
The tin cup.
Robin Hood.
Almost for the porn.
He's got the glasses on.
Pinocchio already has a mischievous attitude.
No sooner than Geppetto is finished carving Pinocchio's feet does the puppet proceed to
kick him.
Once the puppet has been finished and Geppetto teaches him to walk, Pinocchio runs out the
door and away into the town.
He is caught by Kara Beener, I think, who assumes Pinocchio has been mistreated and
imprisons Geppetto.
Well, that's awfully different.
Don't recall an imprisoning scene, no.
Okay, so left alone Pinocchio heads back to Geppetto's house to get something to eat
once he arrives at home.
A talking cricket who has lived in the house for over a century warns him of the perils
of disobedience and hedonism.
Him being very elderly is a strange detail.
Yes.
In retaliation, Pinocchio throws a hammer at the cricket more accurately than intended
to and accidentally kills it.
No!
Now, I don't know the page count of this, but within your synopsis it seems like this
happens within two minutes.
Immediately.
I think this is page seven.
This is first act.
A 120-year-old cricket is felled as soon as he meets this screeching block of wood.
Where is the cricket?
The cricket didn't consult.
Does Geppetto know about the cricket?
Are they friends?
I feel like the cricket would be like, I don't know about that block of wood, man.
I feel like avoid this guy.
It's not very well-created, like a sitcom or there's a common place where they all know
each other and there's a connection.
These are all disparate characters and species that have no central hub.
No right being in a story together, that's for sure.
No, they're all different tales.
It's like a big car crash is why they're all meeting.
It is like the movie Crash.
But it was puppets and the movie Crash.
They modernized and changed all the names based on original Carlos Colodi.
Is that the name?
Crash?
No, no, no, no.
They made the writer of Pinocchio.
I don't believe that's Brendan Fraser's character's name.
Does Brendan play the author of Pinocchio in the movie Crash?
Wow, I guess that's crazy.
I didn't realize that.
He's 120 years old.
He has an unpleasant Pelebird monologue about different woods have different shades.
And you're like, oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, you can't.
You cannot do this.
This beat broke back mountain.
Jesus.
One more and I'll be done.
I swear.
Pinocchio gets hungry and tries to fry an egg.
But what comes out of it is a little bird that flies out the window, forcing Pinocchio
to leave the house to ask for food.
Then he knocks on an old man's door to ask for food.
The man thinking that Pinocchio is one of the hooligans who ring the bell for fun.
And instead of giving him a good piece of bread, all he gets is a bucket of cold water
on his head.
Wet Pinocchio comes home and lies down on a stove.
But the next day he wakes up, he falls to the ground with burned feet.
Luckily, Gepetto is released from prison and makes Pinocchio a new pair of feet.
In gratitude, he promises to attend school.
Gepetto sells his only coat to buy him a school book.
The end.
That's four paragraphs into like 25 paragraphs on Wikipedia recapping original Pinocchio.
I love it.
The rest of it's not going to be nice.
If that's some of his little journey.
But then these people did not live happily ever after.
If that's just a slice of their life, it's just horrors every day.
Burning your feet, Pinocchio is going to need new feet daily.
Honestly, he's lucky if he laid down on a stove and the only thing he burned was his feet.
Oh, yes. If he was all the way reclined, yes, that's half of his body.
Hasclap. Hasclapful.
Hasclapful.
Is exactly what I meant to say.
Nice lesson.
So bizarre.
How could Walt Disney have known about this and thought, now this is the tale?
All of those things they made nicer.
All of those awful, I mean, not awful, but just scary.
Now some of them are awful, but scary children's stories.
He probably liked them as kids.
I read for this one that an animator had gotten a hold of a newer translation of Pinocchio and pitched it to Walt.
And Walt was like, you know, into it, delighted by it.
Or what have you.
There's a more pleasant version.
Oh, I'm sure it was way more pleasant.
I'm sure.
And I have to say, I agree.
When I watched the movie as a kid, I found it very unnerving, but I made sure to ride this when I went back to Disneyland and stuff was reopening.
And riding around, I was like, I like this ride.
I feel like I didn't have this ride as a kid because it was Disneyland exclusive in America.
So I was like, oh, this is this has a lot in common with Mr. Toad.
It's like the level of weird and scary.
This is about what I could handle as a kid.
I feel like these kinds of rides.
Yeah. Well, let me let me tee up, Aaron, because you're here to talk about Pinocchio, because if there's somebody more enthusiastic about this ride, I haven't met them.
We've been to Disneyland so many times and you just like you're magnetized to it.
You sprint up to it.
It is such a joy.
My favorite ride at Disneyland.
Wow.
Ride at Disneyland.
Yeah, you will.
I might be the only person in the world who can say that.
I can't imagine this being anyone else's favorite ride.
Maybe somebody somebody related to Carlos Colodi, maybe somebody, a great, great grandson or something.
Yeah.
How can how how to begin to explain why this ride is of all the rides of all the wonderful attractions?
I feel like I'm going to backtrack immediately, though, because this doesn't sound like a reason to like.
But I think that it is neglected shitty.
You know, that's a reason to like, it has no right being at Disneyland.
It just confounds me.
And that's why I love it so much.
Would you say it's like you mean like lo fi when you say shitty, like in the sense that like it's those flats like as opposed to a lot of shitty.
It's OK.
So if you look at all of the other fantasy land rides, it doesn't get any attention.
Like it just I feel like it needs a couple of 60 watt light bulbs and that would help it out.
And they're not going to give it to them.
It's just it's dark.
There's no need to be a reinvest in Pinocchio.
That was a big takeaway last time we went that Chippetto is calling to him after Monstro and he doesn't have a light on him anymore.
It's just like worst.
This attraction is crumbling and I love it.
It's been crumbling for decades and every time I go, it just tickles me.
It's a good point because it is definitely the least popular of the four Disneyland Dark Rides.
100% and now with Snow White getting a redo, which I think makes it so much better.
Even this thing is way distant last place at this point.
Yeah, if you did a poll, yeah, that would have to show up around five percent or something.
I was going to say zero.
Like I can't imagine anybody who runs to this ride the way I do.
But I also like it because like I think people are going to tear me apart for this.
But I feel you stay away.
I read it. People I feel like Mr.
Toad gets too much credit for being the fucked up ride.
You know what I mean?
Because Mr.
Toad, everyone's like, oh, you go to hell at the end.
That one's like crazy.
And like, can you believe that this is a Disneyland?
Go on Pinocchio's daring journey because it is ten times scarier, way darker.
They swear in it.
They do a cuss.
Yes.
It's just it's it's terrifying.
They live.
OK, there's in the end of Mr.
Toad's wild ride, you go to hell.
But Pinocchio lives in hell.
Yes.
Every moment of his life is a living hell.
But yeah, I just feel like every time I get off Pinocchio's daring journey, I step off the ride vehicle and go, oh, my God.
Like, it's it's still the same.
It's still it's still as crazy as it is.
Yeah, I found one or two tweaks.
Well, one I was very surprised by.
There's one thing in this ride where I was like, you had to close for 16 months and you didn't pull that, which is the bird cages in the bird cages.
There is a very peculiar Asian caricature.
And it's like that could just be an empty bird cage.
Like, how did you not swap that out during the closure?
There's a lot of things that are problematic in the ride.
Yeah, from a cultural sensitivity point.
Probably the last mention of tobacco on Disney property, Disneyland property.
Yes.
And that has its problems, too, with the cigar store Indians.
Oh, sure.
Wait, are there are those in the ride?
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Yes.
There's so much going on.
There's a lot.
Hard to remember.
Yeah. Like half of this.
I was watching the video because I haven't been on it in a little while because I neglected it last time.
We were the last two times were Disneyland.
I was like, well, we went on the other three.
But we I think we always do it.
But I think it really scratches that itch of, well, we're going to we will get on this.
There will not be much of a line.
We will.
It's like a tick a ride tally.
It could be Labor Day and everything in the park could have a three hour wait and nobody will want to go on Pinocchio's journey.
So that's another reason that I love it.
Yes. Another reason for it to be a favor because you will guaranteed get on it no matter what.
Yeah. And the Pinocchio like the Pinocchio presence in this area even because they changed Pinocchio Village House to do they permanently change it to Red Rose Tavern?
Let me look that up because it lasted a lot longer.
I think that's supposed to be a temporary thing.
Yeah, I believe it was.
So yeah, I think they were like, no one likes Pinocchio anymore.
Get him out of here.
Pinocchio Merchants selling.
Yeah, yeah, I did kind of like that restaurant.
I mean, I like let me say I like the vibe of the love the exterior of the of the carts and the restaurant ties in.
Yeah.
It's very nicely like it all it all feels it's a pretty core component of that fantasy land redo from 83, which I think is so great.
It's very to me.
I don't know how to I don't know why that I feel that it is 80s wood.
Everything is made of 80s wood.
It's just like a comforting reddish brown to the whole thing.
There's something. Yeah, it's it's darker.
Yeah.
Kind of like more knots.
Yeah, you're right.
There's a lot of 80s wood at knots as well.
Oh, no, I meant knots in the wood.
Oh, I thought you meant.
Oh, not very much.
Plenty of beautiful knotted wood as well.
You're OK. OK.
You're talking about the knots.
Yeah.
Yeah, sure.
Detailed knots.
Yeah.
Appreciate those knots.
It's an interesting thing about this ride is it only dates to 1983, although it does seem like it's been there forever.
Yeah, people think it's an original fantasy land, like after they yanked out the pirate ship and skull rock and move some stuff around and expanded some of the existing dark rides and gave them facades that look nice and not like little pop up tents.
It was all kind of it was it felt like a temporary land for a long time.
Yeah. And I think they had a story explanation for that, that it was like a traveling circus that came to town and set up by the castle.
But like it was also like, well, what was running out of money?
And we just had to get some stuff there.
That's why that was their idea that a travel, a bunch of like hooligans in a cart.
What's the idea to put up the thing that he was trying to make a place to get away from?
Oh, yes. Yeah, he doesn't like shady carnivals.
Yeah.
So let me make a shady carnival.
Yeah, which is an interesting like conflict in Pinocchio, too, because they go to like a shady carnival island and then like Walt is clearly roasting it.
But it's like and then you built 20 years later, you built your own shady carnival island in the sea of Orange County, Orange Grove.
Sure. Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, it replaced something called Mickey Mouse Theater, which was just a room where they played Mickey cartoons.
Was it Mickey Mouse Club Theater?
It was Mickey Mouse Club Theater.
Yeah.
Gotcha. So it was.
Oh, for the TV show?
Yeah, Mickey Mouse Club Theater. Yeah.
An outpour, I guess, if you were, if you considered yourself a member, as a way to, if you like showed up there a lot, maybe you'd get some face time with Jimmy.
I don't know if Cubby was hanging out there a lot, but it was, yeah, it was just like on a loop.
I don't know. No bands played.
Yeah.
I think that.
One block away from the Main Street cinema where you could also see old Mickey cartoons.
You can watch Mickey cartoons in Fantasyland.
This thing literally had a sign.
I saw a photo where it's like, you know, dazzling cartoons, air conditioned inside.
Like that subtle thing that makes us like, you know, not so great attractions.
They were just advertising.
But so three decades of that and then we got to do something less chintzy.
So they they do this.
Let me here's something I like about the premise.
When you just look at the sign saying what the ride is, you were told that here's the synopsis.
Board a woodcarver's cart to travel through the adventures of Pinocchio.
A woodcarver's cart.
That's what you're on.
Is that implying that Geppetto made the carts?
Or if it's his, then maybe he made it.
And it is wood with nice knots.
So maybe.
Or is it like, are you on a cart that he would use to transport lumber around?
But it is made out of wood, too.
It looks hand carved.
Although they're pretty ornate.
Those are really nice vehicles.
It doesn't seem utilitarian.
I wouldn't say that's.
But Geppetto is so Geppetto didn't have time to get around to making 25 of these.
This guy can barely get out of bed in the morning.
Let's be honest.
He filled his house with cuckoo clocks.
I can't wait to get to that part.
The clock.
The grand finale.
Just to confirm, it is still Red Rose Tavern, the restaurant.
Yeah, that's what it is.
It's open and you can still get the grace.
But they got rid of Pinocchio.
It was Pinocchio Village House, which is AUS.
And they were like, get out of here.
Can I say one of the driest facts that has ever gone in and out of my brain?
There was, I had subscribed to this thing, Disney News.
Once quarterly, get a bunch of advertisements for Disney parks to make your parents take you.
I mean, I got the annual report too, but it was like getting four more annual reports.
My brain was very warped by all this.
But there was some trivia article where they said that at the village house, when you're leaving, there's an exit sign.
But the exit sign, they messed up the dimensions of it and it is not directly over the door.
It's way over to the right.
So they made this right.
They justified it by drawing Figaro the cat with a rope, pulling the exit sign to where it should be.
Wow, that's cute.
That's nice and cute.
And then I heard that in the same article, they say that in Paris, they did another village house restaurant.
And this time the exit sign is in the right place and Figaro is given a thumbs up and leaning up against it as if to say, I got it.
It's the one thing we got right in France.
The only thing you corrected.
It's such an odd little like for no one.
I liked this so much and I really wanted to remember reading that and think, well, I'll never go to Disneyland Paris.
There's no way that I will see that.
And I don't know if you remember that I wanted to say, oh, so we got to go into the, can we go to the village house so I could see this thing?
There's this thing where Figaro is dragging the sign over, but then here they fixed it.
And here is a handkerchief.
Breathe into this as they cook the fetid Disney theme park French food.
This is our honeymoon.
That's OK, right?
This is how we're ending our honeymoon.
And we tried to do that and I tried to go into the village house, but it was closed.
Fair may.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
We saw so much fair may.
Everything was closed.
The word of the day.
Closed, closed, closed, closed.
Oh, that's closed too?
OK, that's closed.
Yeah, yeah.
There was nothing.
That was a foreclosed park.
Depressing.
Really?
I'm so, one of you guys have to go one day and see if we're.
Don't go in winter.
Just don't.
That's what it feels like.
You may have gone at the worst possible time.
Like it's like all of a sudden the park, I feel like started getting a little bit more money and they started making stuff a little fresher.
That's what it feels like.
But it feels like you went in like the worst, like was bad weather, right?
As well or no?
Yes.
Yeah, just freezing.
Like, yeah, bad weather.
Everything was closed.
It was like the complete like lowest point of the decade for the for the park.
So yeah, so much is closed and then employees are like mad.
They're mad that you're there.
That implies that they had any employees.
Yeah, that's true.
It was like a six flag when Gionno had six flags and that we could barely find an employee on the justice list.
Yeah, that park wide and that we like checked ourselves in.
You scan your own tickets.
Really?
They didn't have any employees at the gate.
You caught them during their traditional four hour break.
Yes.
It was 8 to noon.
We are on break.
Yeah, the French siesta.
Ride their self service like kiosks for those four hours like at a CVS self check out.
You have to hit how many people are in the car and then you hit OK and then you get in the vehicle yourself.
Disneyland Paris extra bucks.
Yeah.
Now, what's your thought?
Village house.
A village house.
That was a.
Yeah.
How long have you had?
Did you have that fact in your head?
Thirty years?
Scott.
Something like that.
Yeah, I probably read around seven.
This has been my dream has been to go to France and see what the Eiffel Tower, the great art.
No, no, no.
The Figaro squaring the circle.
Right.
Getting his job is a job.
Of exit sign installation.
That's your sister.
Right.
This time.
That's Figaro's back story.
That's probably in the Wikipedia to you had up.
Yeah.
Do we see the literal Sistine Chapel on that trip?
Yes.
OK.
I remember that less than not see not achieving.
You had to ask if we saw that.
But you do remember that.
What you didn't see.
Oh, man.
That's great.
On the plane.
In the airport on the plane.
I'm going to see the sign.
Making a list of things to do crossing things off.
Yeah.
I don't need to ever sign.
Here's that sign.
I'm going to say I'm a circle sign again.
I can feel my brain working.
I can feel like an extended family member's name and face or like a beloved family member's
name and face.
I can feel that.
I can feel like an extended family member's name and face or like a beloved childhood
friend leaving my brain to have these Figaro facts.
Make room.
Figaro nuzzling in backwards like a cat getting comfy.
Great at Betsy out.
Bye bye.
What don't we need?
What don't we need in here?
Sure to make your acquaintance, Jason.
Figaro then pulls on a rope to get more family members out.
Lamp with your being the giant billboard that's lamp with the coachman.
Yes.
That character's name being the coachman.
You're in something your parents worked really hard to make really nice for you when you
were eight years old.
Out.
And then the phrase wet Pinocchio is now living.
Pinocchio does feel like an intrusive thought.
I will be lying in bed before I am trying to count breaths to fall asleep.
And then I just keep going wet Pinocchio.
It'll be like in a clown's wet Pinocchio.
Erin, if you ever been when we've been taking care of our son and we put him in the bathtub,
has the fact ever occurred?
Has the phrase ever occurred to you?
Oh, we drop him in the tub and he warp.
Yep.
Every time.
Please don't warp.
Oh, what a funny little wooden puppet.
I mean, that would be I would just pretend my son was Pinocchio.
If you're a newer listener, we're referring just consult the Christmas episodes for this
Geppetto nonsense that we talk about.
I also never hit my son for fear of splinters.
Very good.
Only that reason.
Morally, whatever, you know, got to keep him in line.
But, oh, ouch.
What's his name?
Avery Schreiber.
Yeah.
Classic Pinocchio performance.
Another name that's in all of our heads.
Yeah.
And is pushed out like.
Your beloved tree house.
Yeah.
Gone.
Avery Schreiber in.
Did I have one?
I don't remember.
Was my dad around?
Not sure.
Probably not.
Avery Schreiber.
I wake up every morning thinking of his face.
I should call Avery Schreiber.
Tell him I love him.
Make sure he knows.
Let me just quick reunite Jason with his son.
All right.
Here he is.
Little puppet boy.
What?
What's happening?
Is this the surprise?
This is the surprise, yeah.
Jason, this is Jason's son, little puppet boy.
You're going to notice that I had to cut the strings on him because he was too tangled up.
So I apologize.
There are no strings on him.
You're going to have to restring him.
What's happening?
What is this?
We're looking at a little marionette of Pinocchio.
Well, it's a not specific puppet.
It's got a long nose.
He's a liar.
Pinocchio's in, I feel like that's public domain.
He's all over Italy.
Yeah, he's just kind of a puppet.
And yeah, we bought this for a show at UCB years ago and then ended up using it in like a dozen other shows.
But it's been in my drawer upstairs and I realized I saw it last night just by happenstance.
I went, oh, yeah, little puppet boy.
We pass it back and forth.
Jason hasn't been with his son, little puppet boy.
He's been falling over the years.
He's not in the best shape.
So we'll put the photo, but I want Jason just to be able to work the puppet during the show.
If he feels like inspired or anything.
You can't, though, because I'm not then you can really work.
You could kind of work the.
Yeah, there you go.
That's a little bit of a dance.
Yeah.
The posture isn't great.
Stromboli would whip him.
So we'll post a photo of father and son here as well.
I just wanted to do that on.
Can you sing as much of that song as you remember?
Or could you sing?
Cat Stevens, father and son.
Either way, your choice or a medley.
Old man, take a look at my.
That's the way.
And three.
The other the other prop we bought that then used like two dozen times was a Teddy, a child's extra large Teddy bear costume that fit me pretty well.
And I feel like I can get in it.
I Mark Rennie has borrowed it like many past guests have used it or gotten in it.
Mike can get in it.
That stretches.
Yeah, you see, I'm sorry.
You have a little bear costume that you're passing around from guest to guest.
You don't have to wear the bear costume.
All right.
I'll put on the bear costume.
That may be downstairs.
That might be downstairs by the car in the storage.
We'll wait.
Leave a recording.
We'll talk about something.
Next time you're on the show, I will bring the bear costume out.
Great.
If we do get to wear an old bear costume from a garage in about four and a half years.
If it's really we're still doing it.
We got more on a mansion to get through.
Yeah.
Grizzly Peak.
If we do Grizzly Peak or something, we really should have done it for that.
Or when we did what we did though.
Ride, right?
Marry.
Grizzly, Grizzly.
We're not.
We're not ready to Country Bear Jamber Week is going to be too packed.
Yeah.
Grizzly Peak Week.
We'll have more time.
Exactly.
Show and tell that area where you get to chill out is just lovely.
And we don't talk about it enough.
And the little paths.
And the little paths in Grizzly Peak.
Forget about it.
It's so good.
My best friend, Kia's favorite part of the park.
Yeah.
She listens.
Hi, Kia.
That's the tree.
Count the rings of the tree.
Yeah.
Kia would only have one, I guess.
I guess, yeah.
That's how it works.
From fresh wood.
So fresh you can hear it scream.
The wood, it screams.
You want to dive into the ride a little bit?
Yeah.
I feel like I need, because I'm so excited to talk about the ride.
I feel like it's not coming off.
Yeah.
The joy.
I am so joyous when I go see it.
And when I say it's dilapidated and not cared for, those are all positives in my book.
It's like you call things that need a little more love duds.
Yes.
Like our dear departed cat.
It was a dud, but a dud needs the most love.
Or a lemon.
A dud or a lemon.
That is my highest praise.
The things that I love the most in life.
I feel like I'm opening the door for a slam for you right now, Scott.
Oh.
What a dud.
I love them.
Oh, geez.
Hey, okay.
Well, I shanked the first word and I rose again.
Is that a mystery date?
Scott's a mystery date?
Yes.
You got the dud.
But no, it's the highest compliment that I love things that need it the most.
Yeah.
And if somebody doesn't go to this, because Peter Pan is going to be full day and day.
There is plenty of love to go around for every other Fantasyland attraction.
Everybody loves the other ones.
Nobody loves Pinocchio and I'm going to love it.
That's a good point.
Yeah, because Snow White just got a big refresh.
Peter Pan, it may as well be in another park.
The lines get so long.
And then Toad is like the cult favorite.
Exactly.
So then you're left with Pinocchio.
Yeah, Toad is like, here come the warm jets.
Brian Eno, like that's the hip of the four.
It's big star.
I'm still confused by the notion that...
It's a big star.
I agree with the cool.
I remain confused by the notion that Mr. Toad is obscure or off the beaten.
I think it is one of those famous things on Earth.
I think the thing that maybe makes people think it's obscure is that it's not a beloved like Diamond Classic film.
Oh, the Diamond Classics.
Yes.
And the clamshells.
I haven't thought about that phrase in a long time.
Yes.
Yeah, because who even...
It's hard to even remember.
Like you almost think that the thing is called...
Yeah, but then the movie isn't...
That's the part of Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad.
Right.
It's from that weird murky era and you don't know which one had Casey at the bat.
It's so confusing.
I declared a while that I was going to read The Wind and the Willows.
Do you remember that?
I never made good on that because we were watching a Mr. Toad cartoon and I was really tickled by...
Is it the one, the thing where he is...
It's the claymation thing where he's driving and yells, poop?
Poop, poop, poop, poop.
Yeah, there's something really juvenile and I was like, I'm going to read those books.
He's funny.
I haven't read a book in 12 years.
You're going to start with a book in 12 years.
I'm going to read this one because it has poop in it.
Mr. Toad is funny.
We watched some old Toad stuff a couple years ago and we were like, Mr. Toad is funny.
Driving like a maniac and then the ride is funny.
That's really how it sets itself apart.
I guess, originally Snow White was scary and Peter Pan is magical to some people.
Mr. Toad is kind of the funny madcap one.
What is Pinocchio?
Depressing?
Sad?
Moralistic.
Very moralist.
Heavy-handed morals.
Heavy, heavy-handed morals.
Heavy-handed morals but makes the immoral stuff look awesome.
There is some element of Pleasure Island that you go, this is cool as shit.
It's scary but also it's stylized in a way that you'd go, yeah, I see why you'd go over there.
I think it's so grimy though.
Maybe it's because I know what's coming.
It is, but I could see why you would be like, this is such a...
I know what a real rundown, scary...
I'm trying to think of something.
Yeah, it's Pleasure Island.
Although rundown isn't the word.
It's not rundown.
Yes, I think it is imagineered.
There's massive heads and mechanisms.
No, that's fair.
It's a terrifying...
If the Imagineers were evil, that's what Pleasure Island is.
It's an immaculate Batman villain's lair which is enticing to go to.
Depending on your Batman media, if you're in the Joker and he's got a cool carnival fun house or something that is his lair,
you do want to go there even though you know you're going to get killed.
I think if a drawbridge didn't come up, if you didn't know you couldn't leave Pleasure Island...
Well, you can leave.
Oh, yes.
But as a slave donkey.
In a crate.
To the salt mines.
You can get a park hopper between Pleasure Island and the salt mines and you can go back kind of freely.
I mean, clearly Imagineers were like, yeah, this should be fun.
Let's name our nightlife district, our brand new nightlife district after this 40-year-old hellscape.
That is a really funny thing.
Was that a way to curb drinking, like public drunkenness?
Now, remember, have fun but don't go too nuts here at Pleasure Island.
I've had signs up everywhere saying don't make a jackass out of yourself.
If they do, I mean, I was about to say if they do a Pinocchio.
Everyone's doing a Pinocchio.
Every studio has two different Pinocchios in production.
Always, always somewhere in the world there's a Pinocchio being made.
Every older actor is obsessed with doing Pinocchio.
Robert Downey Jr. has been trying to do it for 20 years.
He's like roped everybody in.
Always let him do any 19th century story that is his heart's desire.
It's always going to work out.
Tom Hanks is in the Zemeckis Pinocchio that's coming out soon.
But they should add.
Is Pinocchio like an unknown child or do they do some horrible that it's like in a dog?
Oh, we can mocap Martin Short.
Yeah, Martin Short is Pinocchio.
No.
Mocap.
We must have.
Have we brought up the Drew Carey made for TV Pinocchio?
We have not.
We brought up the Drew Carey TV movie.
Drew Carey, Aaron's pal.
My good friend.
Your good friend.
Good, good friend.
Yeah.
Have you seen it?
Like did we watch any of it in the?
I feel like I must have seen it at some point.
Not recently.
And it didn't come up when you were at the show.
No, I did not talk to him about Pinocchio.
And he did not say, hey, you know, if you like this, you might like my movie.
He doesn't plug his made for TV movie to the guests.
There was an article going around a few weeks ago on Collider or some film website about like everyone is memory hold this made for TV Drew Carey Pinocchio.
It's nowhere to be found.
And Cinderella just came back with a little bit of fanfare because it's got Whitney and Brandy.
Very talented cast and not so with with Jepetto specifically with Julie Louis Dreyfus, the Blue Fairy.
Oh, boy.
It's really strange.
He has like a this like show stopping number that is like, do you guys know the song?
It's about like if when I when you took my love away from me, it's about all the things you could take from Jepetto before you take his son.
I do not know this.
And he's singing to like a mean banker played by Brent Spiner.
Well, he does have a house full of garbage, so it could be a long song.
I will say expendable.
You saying mean banker played by Brent Spiner makes me ashamed to not have because that's right.
It's really cute.
I know that's sorry, but if I had a bank account, you could take the whole amount.
That's the one that's in my head.
If I had does not have a bank account.
It's beyond that.
It's negative.
He just never had one.
I don't know.
I go in the bank.
I get confused.
Our simple.
So sad.
I know.
I don't know amounts and ledgers.
I just instinctively knew you would be able to pull facts about this movie.
I don't think we've ever talked about this, but I was like, someone in this room will know this movie.
I feel like it's one of the ones where I just watch so much TV.
I knew the commercials by heart and it just it felt like I had seen the movie and then never, never got around to it.
Never done the whole thing.
There's just been so much Drew Carey.
Yeah.
So much care in there that YouTube is now algorithm algorithm me.
That was tough to get through.
Yeah.
Whose line Montauk like clips like 10 times that Ryan Stiles owned Drew in the hoedown.
Are now clips that are like that's every time.
That's what he always what he always did.
We'll get better.
We will.
You know, there's altiz.
There's a little bit.
There's maybe a little game coming at the end of the episode.
We'll get back to Drew.
Drew will have his time to shine.
But we got to talk about the Gepetto.
We know the Pinocchio that we know and dear God, not about Joseph Gordon, let it Jiminy Cricket.
Oh, yeah, I forgot about that.
It's going to be we're going to have we're going to be seeing him on street corners and billboards everywhere for a long time.
We'll deal with that later.
Yeah.
There goes my first crush's name.
And here comes a new friend.
Here comes Figaro.
Pull it in.
OK, the right.
This is like when I think about sitting down in boarding a woodcarver's cart with you and the anticipation and that you're just like bouncing bouncing.
Yes.
I just like physically bounce in my seat like a little king.
Baby in a high chair.
Yes.
But and which which the tonally fits so great with the first scene.
No, I wouldn't call it a scene.
The first half scene, you get half of a room.
Hi, diddley dee slam.
And then it's just horrible from there.
It is so quick to gloom as all like even faster than it's kind of the same format as Snow White.
But at least there's like that cottage is sort of big.
You got to get to the other side.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And seven dancing carry eight now that they've added snow white.
But here it's just Pinocchio and then like the Dutch girl and the Russian girl, the puppets who he barely meets.
And then you're just two and a half seconds.
And then it's interrupted by just haha.
A big slam sound.
There's just a divide where did you think this is a fun ride?
No, it is not a fun ride.
It's so fat.
And now it just like it's so fast.
It's so fat and now it just like it's still surprises me how fast every time I love it.
Yeah, darkness.
Heidi, you know, the day that's also my theory for a long time has been like that.
Walt probably loved that song and he's like that was his real what he really thought of actors.
He's like these foolish little puppet like they're a necessary evil.
These these foolish, ignorant little puppets.
100 percent.
I was thinking that with the three of you actually, because this is something I have not had the pleasure.
But like when I hear this the line, hi, Dilly, dumb and actor's life is fun.
And then I think about you guys driving to Santa Monica for commercial auditions.
I did do commercial auditions for about a year and a half.
It's awful.
Not fun, you're saying.
Then actor's life in that case.
Not fun.
Yeah, I walked.
Well, I went to the funniest one I ever did was I did drive.
I drove like maybe three hours round trip to walk into a piece of plexiglass and then leave.
And that was the entire audition.
I didn't even have to say a line or anything.
So there's yeah.
Yes, there's a lot of unglamorous parts of it.
Now, if you're lucky enough to get on set and you get a breakfast quesadilla in the morning.
Now, that is fantastic.
See, I was never lucky enough to get on set.
I was not very good.
But again, my theory is that like because what you wanted to be you wanted to be doing the kinds of ads that air during your favorite show, The Price is Right.
I wanted to be doing a consumer cellular ad.
Oh, my mom just signed up for that.
Did she really?
Yeah.
Rated number one for customer experience.
You want to be a nice lady telling older folks.
What I'm excellent for is is game show auditions because I'm a big jackass if you want to tie it back into the right at hand.
Like I'm good at being like big.
They want they want big.
They want braying.
I can pray among the best of them.
Now, let's see you break.
No, I know what you mean.
I think just like weaving in the Price is Right story through it.
That is what I recall is that like, yeah, there's certain like you guys can attest like some things that commercials want now are just like the driest, most subtle, just kind of like look at the camera.
John Krasinski take.
Yeah, yeah, it's a lot of like, yeah, like a little bit of like, oh, like you make the eyes and you go get a little this guy with but say it with your face.
Throw it away is said a lot like don't even think about the line.
Basically, they're telling you, hey, we know we told you to do improvise a full half hour for us for 10 years.
Stop doing that shit.
Just say this and leave, please.
And it's like, all right, man, whatever you want, hit you with a big board.
Yeah, see what happens to your face.
And then you go.
But that's what like when because just the way the Price is Right thing worked out.
You did a zoom audition that I heard happening in the other room and small dry.
Not part of it at all.
I heard you doing it and I was like, she got it.
She got it for sure.
She's going to be on the show.
I just knew it just propelled.
They want loud idiots and I can do that.
Glad you got your shot.
Yeah, your idiotic shot.
I anyways.
So yeah, in the in the pleasant scene, you hear about the life of an actor.
And then here's something I noticed in the so immediately from that you are backstage at Stromboli's puppet theater,
which is just like this will be face looks like a fun show with a nice smiling guy.
And there's a bunch of Stromboli posters in the beginning of the rat, like four or five.
If you look at them and they sort of like cascade down in terms of his friendliness,
like he does look like kind of a warm guy initially.
But by the last one you see, which I think is black light, those eyebrows have gotten much thicker and much more pointed down.
He's just so much more frightening and frothing at the mouth.
It's funny. I've never noticed that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Maybe I don't know if that was on purpose or they just didn't like copy the paintings correctly.
But I don't know the idea that Stromboli like that you'd want if you live in the town,
which is apparently called Pinocchio Village, using the canon of the ride, you might think that that's a fun.
This will be a fun afternoon.
Let's go see this like glaring laughing man in this tiny decrepit theater.
He's worth the patronizing, given money to.
Well, and as you discover later on in the town, there might be not a lot else to do around there because the the signs,
the directional signs in the town point Pinocchio Village and then another one that says to the sea.
That's your option for local sites.
I mean, no wonder Pleasure Island is so desirable.
Yeah, yeah, it's something. Something's happening.
Jimmy Cricket, not a great helpful guy, though, if he's telling Pinocchio like, um, I guess follow the one that says to the sea.
Yeah, wait. Yeah, it's kind of on his guidance. He ends up there.
Yeah, really weird to safety.
He does eventually in a long winded way.
Yeah, you get the phrase, the huge star rally phrase.
This will be your home.
Right away.
This is scene two.
This is like setting the seeds of the ride.
1.5.
Yeah, and then you yourself are in a cage.
Right. Right.
That's creepy.
Then you're choosing between Pinocchio Village or Pleasure Island.
Jimmy Cricket says over here, not Pleasure Island.
He's popping up throughout the ride telling you don't go this way.
Don't go that way.
But pretty quickly, you're at Pleasure Island, which again, like I mean, as we're saying, this sort of mixed messages in a way because like it is.
Yeah, it's a it's a fun themed environment.
Yeah.
Some of the problem, I guess, is that people are drinking a lot, but usually we have been drinking a lot when we've gone on this attraction.
Like, what are you mad?
What did I it seems like I'm doing what you're going on rides, eating junk food and sweets.
I mean, we get in brawls all the time when we're at Disneyland.
Like it's just constant roughhousing.
You're always in those Tic Tocs where you're fighting a family reunion.
Yeah, no, we look like that Andy Cap, who got in like big fights.
Well, yeah, any cap.
Look at Jason when you ask that question.
100% of the cap's wife was like hitting it with a frying pan.
Right. Did they get in like like pig pen style cloud fights though with like commotion like commotion clouds, motion fights?
I think so.
Yeah, I have come across lately.
The sizes were all very odd, but there are opening Islands of Adventure like first couple years shirts that just say that kind of very cheap Islands of Adventure logo at the bottom and then have Andy Cap thinking about a beer and his wife just looking mad at it.
Rolling pin.
Yeah.
How much are these shirts going for?
Like 50 bucks.
So in a good shape, I would encourage you to buy.
I got to find one at least like in the realm of my size.
So I think there were kids was one of them a kid's one.
Maybe it was bizarre.
With any cap wanting a beer.
I loved Andy Cap as a kid.
Yeah, I did too.
I loved his hot fries and his cheese fries.
And I like the comic strips.
I mean, they were the like the Lockhorns were the bummer couple that hated each other.
But Andy Cap and his wife at least gotten some antics.
Yeah, they had like high highs and low lows.
The kind of relationship you really want.
Wait, does Andy Cap is he just the like spokesman for the hot fries or does King Features Syndicate own hot fries?
No, I think it's a licensing thing.
What's hot fries?
What are you talking about?
I don't know.
I've never had them actually.
I actually don't.
I know that Andy Cap is posted like plastered all over their little fried like potato sticks.
Like kind of like Cheetos or Takis.
Figaro's pulling a new fact.
I'll remember.
First kiss gone.
Like it just auto complete Andy Caps taste the oven baked crunch like flavor punch in every crunch.
Yep, there he is.
But it is even called Andy Caps.
Like it's his name first.
Yeah.
So I got to figure out if King Features Syndicate owns hot fries.
I don't think so.
Oh, no, I'm getting con con Connagra brand.
Connagra brand.
I think they are a big.
So they are licensing from King Features Syndicate.
They own Healthy Choice and Bird's Eye and Banquet.
So it's some like sinister food concern.
OK.
Andy Cap had his own food empire.
That would imply that he's industrious and that's the opposite of Andy Cap.
He's a lazy drunk who sleeps on the couch.
Yeah, it's a laugh.
I can't imagine him being a potato.
One of these one of these companies stole his recipe.
He stumbled upon made some fries once then it got taken out.
Before alcohol showed up.
He was a real go getter before.
Zere, you take this.
Here's your payment.
Bunch of beers.
It's nice that he's making some passive income.
Yeah.
Andy Cap notable for being the only person ever fired from working on Pleasure Island.
You're too.
You're too much of a loud.
Get out of here.
Shady even for us.
OK.
So also one more thing.
Are you like Mike?
Are you at this point like angling for a job at King Features Syndicate?
Yes.
At some point like the full use of the full phrase.
I'm like, what is the end game of saying King Features?
Yeah, it's a good question.
I was actually as you guys were talking, I zoned out just now and I was imagining like,
could we license a King Features Syndicate character?
Could we have like Andy Caps podcast, The Ride?
Could we call it that for a while?
Andy Cap proudly presents.
Yeah.
Or any of his hot fries.
You'll love his podcast.
Yeah.
The Phantom presents the Billy Zane Phantom presents podcast, The Ride or, you know, I don't know.
Is this going to cost us money to have to engage in this partnership?
I assume it might.
I don't think I'm going to chip in just to have King Features Syndicates involved.
But maybe I email.
I don't know quite the boost it's going to get us.
Maybe I email King Features Syndicate and I say like, do you have a list, a sheet of how much it costs for each character to endorse your podcast?
It's like those bands.
You see like a list of the bands like and how much they cost to like play a state fair that came out a couple of years ago.
I don't want to burst your bubble, but the founder of King Features is listed as William Randolph Hearst.
So I think they're going to take you for a ride.
This might be difficult.
It might be difficult, but maybe there's like a don't bring up Sergeant Kane.
That's the only thing that can blow the meeting.
Do not say that's my signature, though, and my emails.
I've got this. I come to you today with the citizen Kane of ideas.
They press a button and the chair falls back.
Thanks for the water, at least.
Hey, enough of this nonsense.
We have donkey Ferris wheels to talk about.
Everything is donkeys in Pleasure Island.
Yeah.
In our rewatch, like the carousel is all donkeys that you ride donkey gingerbread donkeys.
There's a lot of like pre-luting to to what occurs in the in the gate when you come in as a big donkey head.
You like donkeys, kids.
Hey, it's the international symbol for fun.
Seeing a lot of donkeys in one place who had to be there.
You know you're having a good time.
A working farm animal.
I and then a lot of cigars.
That's continues to be a strange thing about this attraction.
The preponderance of cigars and tobacco row.
I liked watching the Paris version where tobacco row was a thing.
That was fun to see tobacco street tobacco street.
Right.
A little more clear.
You got the I had to remember the name.
OK, the Fox.
Honest John is the Fox.
Yes, who sat on you.
Who sat on me.
Or was it Gideon?
I think maybe Gideon sat on me.
Oh, Gideon.
Gideon sat on you.
Yeah.
I think I remember the name.
Gideon sat on you.
Yeah.
That was one of the first things maybe that ever happened to me at Disneyland.
And yet I still liked it enough to talk about it every week somewhere.
They're doing like a strength testing machine that is so caustic.
It is like.
What, the mallet?
Yeah.
It is like it's just like crazy loud.
It feels very haunted mansion and it's like almost like a little mini jump scare.
Am I crazy?
That thing is like dialed up so loud.
That noise is so like unpleasant, you mean?
Yeah.
Just kind of adds to the.
I mean, they, you know, they do very well.
They, they're very good at recreating like a hectic shady carnival for sure.
That's true.
Yes.
It feels chaotic.
Yeah.
But I guess there is, there is a joy to this sequence.
Again, if you didn't know what was coming.
Oh, but do you think, Erin, do you feel like it's all a little grimy?
Yeah, I don't know.
If I was there in real life, my like shady senses would go off.
I'd be like, no.
Yeah.
Keep the kid away.
But yeah.
And then you got the rough house.
Yes, the rough house.
Which in the movie, the rough house is like just kids like break glass.
I think I'm trying to remember in that sequence.
I think they are just throwing glass at each other.
I just, I'm so confused by like the morality here.
Like Walt smoke and drank.
Was it just saying kids don't do this until you're 18?
Like, is this what the whole point of it was?
Or like 15?
What?
It's just funny to me that you're like, yeah, don't do this thing that I'm, you're going to do later.
And I do all the time.
Yes.
Yeah.
And some of it involves rides and stuff.
Right.
I don't really, if it is a morality play, what's the moral?
You step out to a carousel.
Like that's what the exit points you to.
Oh yeah.
And it's not about like drinking in moderation.
Like Pinocchio only have two beers before you drive home or something.
Like it's not that.
And he's not doing like, he's not doing opiates in Pleasure Island.
Is he?
I've never gotten that sense.
Cigar and beer.
Cigar and like a bottle.
There's some fortune telling, but I don't know that there's any drugs implied.
Unless the cigars are laced with something.
It could be.
Yeah.
We know Pinocchio likes to get wet, but I don't know if he likes to get wet in the PCP sense.
No, Pinocchio doesn't like to get wet.
There was an act that a guy threw water at him.
Pinocchio is not you.
Right.
Okay.
So Pinocchio is more like Ethan Hawking training day where he gets wet by like a chip.
Wet Jason.
Yeah.
Wet Jason is a new character.
So it's all strange.
It's all strange.
And then you end up in the, going through the eight ball where you, this is the first that
you see is little buddy Lampwick and Lampwick turns around and reveals his donkey face and
the body horror, or this chapter of the body horror begins.
Yeah.
Oh boy.
And it's, this is a hologram trick.
Oh, in the mirror.
You're right.
In the mirror.
This is one of the first uses of Disney using holograms.
Similar to the Queen that we're going in the Snow White ride.
Yeah.
Similar to the same like trick in the.
Oh right.
Yeah.
But here's where we, here's where the curse comes in.
Yes.
Yeah.
Or yeah.
Do you want to do the honors?
Yeah.
Go ahead and make a jackass of yourselves.
Like so crazy.
And just like, here's where you start feeling like you're being scolded by this attraction.
Yes.
Which I love.
It's like calm down.
What are they doing at this point?
We don't really, especially with the story of the ride stripped out, what exactly has
Lampwick done to make himself a jackass?
He played pool.
Played pool?
Which is as far as I know is legal.
And maybe had a beer.
There's beer in that part, right?
Yeah.
I think they have beer in that and they play pool.
They have beers, yeah.
Which is as bad in the music man as well.
That is, yeah, they get a pool table.
That's a real bad thing.
That is a big thing.
I assume that kept you away from pool for years, Jason.
The music man.
Well, you know.
This is one of the discrepancies I noticed is that in a 2020 video they say go ahead
and make a jackass of yourself.
But then I caught a 2021 recording of this ride and he says that kid always makes a jackass
out of himself.
So I don't know if it's, there's a couple lines in there or they changed it.
We were watching a ride through earlier that was something about like bad kids.
So you enjoys being bad.
There we go.
Yeah.
So maybe it's a.
There's a few of them.
There's a few different lines.
That one is pretty fun.
I like that one.
Yeah.
You were asking for the salt mines.
Which sounds like Bugsy recorded a few of these.
Yeah.
Mind your P's and Q's.
He works at Bugsy has worked on Pleasure Island.
I assume that would make a lot of sense.
Somewhere.
And then we're now this is where it's a like a litany of darkness.
I just like when I, when I talked about like just my temperature rising with thinking about
this, like just think about, and it's so upsetting in the movie also just like you still have
your brain.
Yeah.
But now my form is a donkey and they're just waiting for me to not be able to vocalize
that I'm a person anymore.
Do you remember that in the movie where it's like, what's your name?
And like, oh, I'm getting upset thinking about it.
We're like, the kid says like Daniel or something and he goes, this one can still talk and throws
him back until he can't talk anymore.
Right.
So that implies like your brain is still human brain, but you're just in the body of a donkey
and all you can do is scream as like a donkey's voice.
And you're in your mind saying I'm a person, like let me go home.
But you're to, we're watching this while you're pregnant.
Also we're like bringing a kid into the, and like watching the grimace to like this thing
about boys, bad things happening to little boys.
Just thinking about, yeah, just, it is truly like, and that's where it like, it is funny
that they get any mileage out of the magic of Pinocchio.
Tom Manx, America's greatest, the real life Geppetto would be finally Geppetto for real.
And I like, and when you wish upon a star is the anthem.
And then it's for a film that has things that grotesque in it.
It's upsetting.
Yeah.
I can't think of much more upsetting than that.
Have you had bad, have you had dreams about that occurring?
I will tonight.
Now we will.
Cause now it's, now Figaro's keeping that in your head.
Yep.
Well that's pretty in multiple copies.
I liked Pinocchio as a kid, but all this, I think I blacked out a lot of this stuff when
I was like, I liked that stuff you're talking about.
Like, oh, Jiminy Cricket's fun, isn't he?
Well, it just didn't bother me as a kid.
Like it was like, man, they turned into donkeys and like not thinking about, you know, what
it actually means.
It's terrible.
I think I didn't even, so I was like, I didn't even think like, oh, I better not smoke cigars
or drink beer.
I just thought, oh, you're going to turn into a donkey soon.
Like this will be what happens to you.
So I just didn't want to deal with that part, that reality that I would soon be a donkey
boy.
As long as you don't get tricked by grifters, as long as you avoid like, you know, railway
men.
Don't take improv classes.
Well, yeah, see that's what happened.
The lesson went away as I learned so much theme park stuff and then I had to relearn
it.
COVID was a reset.
The theaters went away and then like, like two people in coats are going to be like,
isn't it time for you to get back in classes?
Sharpen your skills.
Be a performer on a stage.
Everyone clapping for you.
We take Venmo now.
Local theater needs your help or whatever.
Oh, there's nothing.
Yes, we need your help.
We're all a family.
You may as well just be boarding the raft to Pledge of Island at that point.
We all fell for it.
Page slams down.
This will be your home now.
Practice your third beats.
Oh, the best part of every show.
Do your group games, your nonverbal.
Yes, sound and movement openings.
Everyone ends up acting like an ape.
There you go. Act like a jackass.
Why don't you see if it inspires any seeds?
We're joking about, you know, we're all going like, yeah, a lot of dark stuff in this.
But I don't know if you guys remember this, but in the middle of the pandemic last summer,
less than reputable theme park webs like did clearly get worked by some readers who sincerely
wrote in emails complaining about like they need to read.
If they're redoing Snow White and Splash Mountain, they need to redo this.
And sincerely were complaining about there is child slavery in this ride.
And the emails all had the same ring of like they're using the same phrase of like the
Pinocchio ride.
It's not the happiest place to be on earth.
The Pinocchio ride is not the happiest place in Disneyland.
And I was to be on Earth.
It's really clunky.
Wait, so somebody had sent like a fake email to emails like Astro Turf emails, a false
flag in the middle of that, like save the children epidemic where it's like Wayfair
is selling kids like a QAnon madness.
And this website posted it.
It's like readers are saying they should change this ride.
And they printed all of these.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's yeah.
Well, I know the one you're talking about that'll say like fans demand.
And then it's like it's one guy.
It's this it's the account that posts about Jack Sparrow three times a day and has for
the last three years.
It truly is like what is this like a game meant to drive me insane?
I can't unfollow it.
I can't do it.
We text each other every time they did it again.
What's happening?
What does it mean?
How can grown adults care about Jack Sparrow to this extent?
Five out of six people that I ran up to at this diner want Jack Sparrow back in the
movies like headlines like that.
You're like, that's newsworthy thing.
Anyway, so look out for the new Q drop on the new Q's daring journey.
Bizarre.
I well, you know, it is it is odd and strange.
But but Aaron, you were saying that like there OK, there have been the redos of these
rides and they made Snow White not scary.
Oh, if they redo this ride, I won't like it anymore.
Touch one.
They change one salt mine.
I know I complained about the 60 watt light bulbs that they need.
If you put in one 60 watt light bulb to brighten this place up, I won't like it
anymore.
I need it to be decaying and sad and a dud and a lemon.
Yeah, yeah.
If they did things, though, to make it sadder, what if they put more donkey boys in
the cage like they're poorly lit and already falling apart, even though they're
brand new from a construction standpoint, I'm all in.
OK, yeah, because like whatever they like, stop the car in front of one of them.
And it's really upsetting because you hear there like a minute monologue from them
about what they're going through, what they're leaving behind.
So as long as it's under the upsetting or like low rent range, it's good.
I'm all for it.
Yes.
OK, I was going to graduate third grade.
Now it's all mine for me.
I was just coming here to stop my friend.
Your car won't move until I see you shed a tear for me.
We have the technology to do that.
We're scanning your eyes.
You're scanning your eyes for tears.
Show that you care.
And then Aaron's like, yes.
All right.
I love you seeing the new interactive crate.
It's amazing.
It's almost a breast after Pleasure Island when like Jiminy Cricket slowly gets
lower down and then later goes like, oh, my gosh, Monstro like.
Before it's too late.
Yeah, when a whale gets launched at you.
Oh, which is so confusing.
I love that, too.
There's so much time devoted to Pleasure Island and the donkey stuff and, you know,
to the salt mine and, you know, every whip cracks, whip cracks.
All the kids have been sold their crated and then you just round the corners.
Monstro.
Oh, yeah.
Huh?
Yeah, wait, whatever.
What are you talking about?
Why do you know his name?
Oh, yeah, you know, this specific whale in the sea.
Yeah, that is one of the classic Disney dark ride, like the Ursula thing where
somebody pops in and you go, wait, what?
And Ursula is dying in the background.
We're past it.
Look, love loves in the air.
It's the old ending to Snow White where you're like, ah, the dwarves, they're
like, they're on the mountains.
We're the rise over.
And we're like, what?
I love it.
Just like weird, like out of left field things, which I feel like they are
getting rid of slowly.
But I maybe to me, maybe it's part of the fantasy land experience that at least
in the majority of them, there's like something really, you know, at least in
the recent past, something strange and dark has occurred and then, and then
doors swing open and you're outside again.
Bye.
Thanks for coming.
Oh, dream is what your art makes.
Bye.
Part of the charm.
Yeah.
They, I, you guys, none of you have been on Snow White though, right?
Not yet.
No, we didn't get to do it.
Yeah.
Really solved this problem for snow.
Like there's really like, you have a night, like everything feels very satisfying.
All the moves make sense in the story.
So maybe that's bad.
Maybe that's bad.
I don't know.
You don't want it for, well, what happens in the movie to the, I don't think
they get saved in the movie.
I think they do go to the salt mines.
They do.
Yeah.
All those kids are going to die.
Donkeys.
Hopefully sooner rather than later.
Like, honestly, you pray for death.
Yeah.
Pinocchio gets out and sends no help.
Which also begs the question, why does no one help Geppetto?
Is he just that reviled that or was he going around to people and going like,
can you help me find my lost puppet?
It's like, no, man, I already, you're already gone thin fucking ice.
Well, yeah.
A puppet theater is the biggest attraction in town, but a puppeteer is spit on.
How dare you?
They should foreclose your creepy store.
Your 40 clocks wakes up every night.
I don't know.
I make them, they're set to 4 a.m.
I don't know what else to do.
Has anyone ever bought, are his clocks for sale?
I would think.
You would hope.
I mean, what is he doing then?
In the, not in the, not like in the ride.
You can't like buy the ones at the end.
No.
In the world of the.
Although there used to be used to be at the.
Yeah, there used to be a Geppetto like wood shop gift shop at the end of this,
where you'd buy like in the same way on Galaxy's Edge, you can buy like little
wooden Boba Fett's, you can buy like little wooden like trinkets that the Geppetto
would make and apparently that didn't sell very well.
No, it's like this where you could buy your family crest or like an actual sword
or suit of armor, like really fun to walk through.
What do you clear every year?
Like, how much do you make?
I bought an $800 cuckoo clock custom made shipped from Italy.
I have to carry this on splash mountain with me.
So yeah, it is like that litany of whip cracks and salt mines and now a whale.
And what is the whale doing?
He's jumping up and jumping up.
There's some light flashes.
Yeah, he's trying to eat you, I guess.
Right.
And we know that he does eat them in the movie, but I guess we just skip over that
part.
Right.
Yeah, because Geppetto is already OK.
Yeah.
Geppetto is just looking for Pinocchio, but they find each other in the whale in
the movie, isn't that right?
Yes.
Yeah.
Which why it'd be fun to like end up in the whale.
It would.
It would be.
Yeah.
That'd be.
I mean, you do it in even though you don't really do it, you do it in the
storybook boats.
Yes.
Yeah.
You go through it at least.
You're not in it's like guts.
But guys, remember opening morning of Galaxy's Edge when we got to see the guy
brushing monstrous teeth?
Oh, wow.
Boy, did we cheer.
And that's not ironic at all.
Oh, my God.
We were so excited.
Just never would have occurred to me that the whole group of people walking by as
we saw it, we were all everyone, I think, had the same reaction.
Like seeing a giant whale.
Nobody knew that as a Disneyland fact.
Nobody had.
And the hero had not pulled in there yet.
Right.
Let's do it.
What a delightful one.
Yeah.
That can replace any pubescent memory I have.
Wedding day out.
Wedding day.
Yeah.
Sorry.
That memory is done.
Whale toothbrush in.
So, unlit Geppetto.
Then the blue fairy shows up.
Then you are back in the comfort.
You kind of weave back through Pinocchio Village.
Things get kind of peaceful.
It's redundant.
Yeah.
Because you've seen it a little bit before you go to Pleasure Islands.
Yes, true.
Yeah.
Well, the whole ride does kind of end with like a bunch of ballast a little bit.
Like sort of the robots and the excitement are a bit done.
I mean, you get blue fairy, the Pepper's ghost effect.
It's neat.
Yeah.
Not even really sure where she is hiding.
I don't know where that is.
Right.
Stage.
Yeah, that is a good question.
Because I was rewatching it.
I was like, oh, yeah, that's pretty cool.
Yeah.
I also like to just imagine that it's just Geppetto is like fantasizing and it's not real.
And he died in the whale.
Yes, I'll say yes.
It's just, yeah, it's a nice, like peaceful death dream he's having.
And none of it.
That was just he like brought.
He did make the puppet, but it didn't come to life.
And he kind of carried it around and imagined like, what if that fox told him to go somewhere?
It was just like a bunch of madness until he fell into the pier while he was talking to himself.
Isn't that a better?
Swallowed up by what?
I like that.
It's a better story.
Yeah.
But so he, well, this is the scene where he's supposed to become a real boy.
And yet does this, did this occur to anybody that he does not?
If you watch the video.
Right, right, right, right.
It's the same like logic of like the Little Mermaid cartoon.
She's still a mermaid.
Maybe it was a prequel or something, but it's just like, you know, we just watch a whole movie where you got unmermated.
Yeah, forever.
Yeah.
Yeah, I don't know.
That's yeah, that's a good point.
I don't know.
Are they trying to say that this is just an infinite loop?
Is this like that we're going to do this forever or like we don't want to resolve it?
Because then you would never need to go on the ride again.
I mean, they don't do that with other rides.
So it is an odd choice not to put in a very pivotal moment in Pinocchio's life.
An unpleasant moment because we were talking about smooth Pinocchio early.
He is a little even as a kid, I was like, oh, that's what he looks like as a boy.
That's how I felt about the beast too, when he turns into a beast.
Yeah, that's disappointing.
Because you've grown to like this character just as they are in so many other stories.
Or it's like you had it inside you.
You were right.
You were good all along.
You know, right.
And true beauty is your inner beauty.
It's not your exterior.
Then the lesson for a lot of the stuff is like, yeah, but he's also like this.
Luckily, luckily, he's a beautiful man.
Now he's not the beast.
He's sort of like there's like a little bit of Fabio going on.
That's what I, yeah, that's why I said, be like a beautiful man.
Like, yeah, yes.
The way that Fabio is beautiful, like a horse.
Exactly. Yes.
Luxurious man.
Exactly.
So, yeah, he's just like it's a different it gives him a different vibe, which maybe
you spend another movie with him, you would feel that way.
But now we've, you know, we'll see.
Was there never a weird sequel where you hang out with like?
As soon as I said that, I was like, is there a?
This blonde Adonis?
Because there's the sequel.
The first sequel is the like, isn't it doesn't like take place in between like
Christmas and Thanksgiving or something?
I've never seen it.
There's like a prequel Beauty and the Beast where it takes.
Enchanted Wish.
Yes. Tim Curry is a CGI organ that mismatches the rest of the film.
Yes. Right.
Like just utterly different movie.
Yeah. Like was drafted straight out of reboot.
Right. And that's a prequel.
Yeah. Yeah.
Now they had to keep finding ways to like, we got a remake of Fire.
We got a really good guy.
Yeah, because they knew it was a problem.
Nobody wants to see this Fabio looking beast.
But in this case, don't you want to like have the resolution of this?
Don't you at least want to say now he's a real?
Now he's a real boy.
The pride underplays the lying element of the story.
It focuses on the journey and adventure and sometimes it's a big nose,
but they really don't cover the lion.
They don't talk about it at all.
Right. So it actually takes out, I guess that one's the most like concrete thing
you should tell like a kid, like even though, yeah, like you should tell them,
like, oh, don't lie.
Always tell the truth, even though, you know, sometimes you don't always have to,
but that depends situation by situation, you know, but that's a nuance.
They learn that.
Yeah. But okay, generally, don't lie.
Just keep that to yourself.
Not everyone needs to know everything, you know.
But at least that would give like a clear thing to a kid that they want to understand
because most kids aren't like, I'm dying to have a cigar at five.
Like they're not looking for that.
So if you were really trying to teach some kid something,
at least that's the closest thing to a lesson.
Okay, I get it.
Pinocchio is being tortured brutally because he lied.
Okay, got it.
I can draw a straight line there if they see if they're on this ride.
You can still have heavy handed morals.
Just make it applicable to your real life.
Yeah, something.
Yeah. Why are you yelling at me about cigars?
I don't know.
Look, especially now, like my childhood past, I did not,
me, I've had a try to cigar or two in my adulthood, but that's okay.
You did it.
Walt, I didn't do it when I was a kid, I swear.
So why are you mad at me?
Right.
And all if you didn't know anything about Pinocchio, you'd be like, oh, look at this
young actor and now he's being punished.
I guess I shouldn't go into the acting profession.
Was this all, was Pinocchio just a big way to get kids to stop coming up to Walt and saying,
how can I be in one of your movies, sir?
Well, I'll tell you what, go see this new film I have.
He did himself a personal favor.
Unless you've got the charm of a young Suzanne Plachette, don't even think about it.
Yeah.
Knock it off, kid.
You all look like the children from this picture, this, which I am showing the Walkman's
first album cover of just children smoking cigarettes.
Oh, they're all in like, like sooty halves.
Yeah.
Showing us.
I see. Yep. That'll be you. That's actors.
All right. Well, that was my child.
Yeah. I have a cabbie hat.
I was just smoking.
How was being a newsie?
Well paid.
It was terrible on the joints. A lot of work.
Children should not develop that level of arthritis.
Hours of tossing the one motion over arthritis.
And on Sunday, the thicker paper don't even get me started.
So then, so Pinocchio is maybe he'll become a real boy after we're gone.
The blue fairy shows up.
The blue fairy is there.
That causes Jiminy Cricket to say, does he say this is a cause for celebration?
Yeah. Something like that?
It's something about like, let's celebrate.
And then you go into an empty room full of clocks.
There's not a single person.
There's not.
Well, now.
Like, are we supposed to assume like, let's go celebrate.
We're out of here.
We're all left in the car while they go celebrate elsewhere.
Eight and ten.
Why not get to hang with the cricket?
It's like a party with him after all this.
Where your primary entertainment is a puppet theater.
To go in a room and see so many accurate clocks ticking in one place is a party.
That's a celebration.
That was the equivalent of going to a movie back then.
Yeah.
Going into a room with different kind of clocks and looking at them.
Look at all these synchronized clocks.
That was like seeing the Avengers.
If you saw like seven clocks on the wall.
And that's how this ride ends.
That is your like, ta-da, grand finale is a quiet room of ticking clocks.
Rooms of well-maintained clocks.
The time is accurate.
They're loud, but enough, but not too loud.
They're charming.
Well crafted.
Good knots.
Rise of the Resistance ends with you're on a star destroyer and it's blowing up
and you have to get in an escape pod and fly back to the surface of a planet.
Yeah.
Pinocchio.
The equivalent of looking at seven accurate clocks.
Exactly.
Same thing.
Lieutenant Beck could have a cuckoo clock at that console.
Oh yeah, for sure.
He'd love to.
Yeah, and then you're out and you see a sign that says,
when you wish upon a star, all your dreams come true.
All your dreams of seeing accurate clocks.
Sit in a clock room, look at a bunch of plates on a mantle.
What's going on with that?
You see that at knots.
When you go to Knott's Berry Farm, I'm like, here's what a mantle was like.
And it would have five silver plates.
And I feel like I remember my grandma having her five plates.
Make sure you have the plates.
What is that?
You would have a piece of furniture that would display plates standing up.
And I do recall, I think my grandmother had it too.
I don't know, you would show your plates, I guess, to people.
Yeah, you're not going to...
They're probably dusty as shit.
You're not going to eat off of them.
They would be like plates.
Sometimes you put it under a different plate.
What do you call that?
Oh yeah, like for an elegant meal where you have the show plate.
Where the mayor comes over or something to the house.
And then waiters come around and take away the show plate.
This gets no time.
Back into the cupboard or back into the display cabinet or the mantle.
Yes, that's still a trap, a part of the show at fine dining, fine restaurants.
But I think people were like, we don't have to do this in our homes every night.
This is exhausting.
I make my toddler his dinner with a show plate.
Yeah, once Kmart came along, once you're like, I bought my plates at the same place I bought my underwear.
It's like, oh yeah, show plates are on their way out.
It's like sometimes I feel like the kid's just in it for the little pieces of chicken nuggets
and doesn't even care about presentation.
Put so much effort into the show plate and the white glove.
I've seen no appreciation for luxury.
And the mayor's baby's coming over and he's not even going to impress him.
He doesn't even know.
And that's Pinocchio's daring journey.
What a strange.
I always bounce off the car at the end and go, ah.
Yeah, I mean, it's good.
We did it.
It's almost odd to step through it in this way and go and then salt mines and then plates
that you are always on this ride like, yay.
Like you're a dog sticking your head out the window.
Look, that and that, it's so exuberant.
One of these days I feel like they're going to change it.
And when they do, I'll be really disappointed.
Little pockets of weirdness slowly getting cleaned up at Disney.
Even 10 years ago, there was so much little oddity.
I mean, that Carnation Gardens stuck around for so long where it's just like, this is just
an outdoor gazebo kind of thing.
And sometimes people swing dance here.
And it's like, isn't this the most expensive real estate in the country?
Yes.
People swing dance at Fantasy Fair now, though.
They do.
So there's still some strange swing dancing happening.
That sums up a lot of stuff that we're all obsessed with about any of this.
It's like the primest of real estate that a corporation spends billions of dollars
to maintain every year.
And some of the things there are the most outlandish blockbuster things you've ever seen.
Unreal uses of technology and storytelling.
And then also, here's this cuckoo clock room.
Some of it is just confusing trash, and I love it.
But that's part of it.
Yeah.
And I don't know.
I think what we get caught on so much is how has this been allowed to stay here?
But it's great that it's allowed to stay.
If they were able to micromanage everything, it would be something so much kind of sleepier.
I think I said, was it on the Fortune Teller one?
Where I was like, I think if Disney or any other, say this was a new idea to build a giant
multimillion dollar theme park entertainment place, so much weird stuff would be gone.
There would be no like, now we must allocate a spot for people to square dance or to dance
like for once every month or something like that stuff would be gone.
Where will the ska bands go?
So yeah, I think they're like some of it's hold over, but then now it's just sort of
grandfathered in to try.
I'm sure the Imagineers have like some fondness for some of the odd stuff like this.
I mean, with Pinocchio, yeah, I don't know.
It's still who knows if it could be replaced by what would be the most popular thing.
I guess they're probably make a bigger Frozen ride, but that's what I think this is going
to end up being some like it's some maybe this will be the one that gets changed out for.
This is Tangled or something.
For sure it will be.
Yeah, it's like, I mean, who knows if that's in 30 years, but there's no way they would.
The other three are more untouchable, especially with Snow White.
I would have said Snow White was not untouchable until they did this new redo on it, and we'll
see how the lines are, but them doing that much work to it and Snow White's the first
movie and that feels a little more precious.
This is the second one, right?
The second one.
Yeah, second appears at the time was not a big hit.
I don't believe.
I suppose.
Why?
Why was it?
It's 1940.
America has entered the war.
The world is at war.
Come see a sad, upsetting film.
Come be upset with Mr.
War might be depressing, but if you think about turning into a donkey might make you appreciate
the war.
Yeah, sure.
So yeah, I will say, I mean, depending on how it's funny because I think depending on how
ambitious they're going to get with their new like Disney, whatever they're calling it,
the Anaheim Initiative thing where they're going to build the one that built like tons of stuff.
Such a boring phrase.
I already don't remember.
Yeah, I don't remember what it is either.
I don't remember that one.
The initiative, the Disneyland Initiative.
Disneyland proposal.
I feel like if that stuff goes like they go like, yeah, do whatever you want.
And they're like, let's put a bunch of money into that.
Pinocchio has a bigger chance of being say like it will stick around depending on the
ambition of the rest of it.
Because then they're like, well, we don't need we have the room now to do other stuff.
Why would we?
Right.
Well, and Fantasyland is always packed.
Like it's always you go to Fantasyland at noon.
Sure.
It's always packed.
So it's not like hurting for like, oh, we need something to draw people.
It'll always be very popular.
But I'm just saying like if they're not going to do a big ambitious plan,
they're definitely going to like find places.
Start finding the holes.
Yeah.
And they're going to go, well, one of these is not like the other.
One of these dark rides, not like the other.
Yeah.
One of them has the notion of salt mines.
There's a cuckoo clock at the end.
Yeah.
Has anybody been on this thing in 10 years?
My little dud.
No.
Yeah.
But you love it.
You want it to be how it is.
And let me ask you this.
If it were to go away and there was some opportunity to salvage one item,
and have it in your home, have it in our home,
and pass it on to our next generation, what would we want to have to remember our little dud by?
I only get to pick one.
I'd probably, I mean, it's massive, but I'd probably take the crate that says to the salt mine.
Oh, man.
And that's how you keep them in line.
Yes.
All right.
You want to go to the penalty box?
I was going to suggest a different thing to keep Scott in line.
This clown.
You know, he's fine.
Let me clarify.
I am not scared of all clowns.
I love it.
There are some clowns.
Every other episode.
I love it.
New clowns around every corner.
It's like 1950s men who are dressed as clowns.
I think that's it.
Yes.
That being a cartoon, I think I'm rarely scared
of cartoon clowns, but when it's like, yeah, it's like, you know, like a guy with kind of
drink bloat and like who hasn't shaved properly and he kind of like rushed some clown makeup on
and then like a little hat with his like stringy unwashed hair coming out underneath.
So now I have to rewatch Mad Men to see if there's an episode where like John Ham or Rich Summer
dress up as like begrudgingly dress up as a clown for their kid's birthday.
So something I could have done.
Scott, do you so you like Bozo's clown babies?
Oh, wait.
Oh, God.
I stepped right in.
No, I don't like all cartoons.
Bozo's clown babies.
Do you see if you've seen those clown babies?
I haven't.
I have poor vision.
So I kind of can't see.
Okay, let's keep it that way.
Imagine the cutest little clown babies you can.
Well, now I just have the Muppet Babies theme song stuck in my head.
Seems very that era.
While we're while we're asking running things by you guys,
Erin, I want to ask you something I asked Scott on the last episode as a kid.
Did you watch the film Rock-A-Doodle about Shana Clare the Bird?
No, no, Rock-A-Doodle was not part of my my my kid.
Okay.
But we have a friend who was very into it and showed it to us and I was like, oh, this just doesn't.
Did we check out of Rock-A-Doodle?
Yeah.
Hmm, interesting.
Yeah, I didn't listen to your last episode.
Jason's.
Oh, well, hey, spoiler alert, Rock-A-Doodle is back and back again.
Well, it comes up is like the when Disney was going to do a story of the legend of
Shanta Clare, but like this was a Don Bluth.
I was talking about the Don Bluth film in the the 80s and that that I feel similar to when
you describe something as a like that has a Pinocchio level of sinister energy in it.
But I also wanted to run you by you guys and Mike, you do a newer theme park innovation.
This was sent to us by a Twitter user Fry Cook on Venus and the person who uploaded the
video originally on Twitter is named Asher Adams.
This is a new offering at Universal Orlando and it's a big walk around boss.
Maybe.
I know all about this.
I'm a big fan of this walk around boss, baby.
I was at Universal not but a few days ago and I did not.
Is this in Hollywood or no?
Just this is this is in Orlando.
This video is walking.
Stern is a guest.
I think I love it, though.
It's a little bit of the vibe of that walk around toad.
Universal Japan.
Yes.
It's like little guy with a huge head.
Yep.
He's kind of cool.
I agree.
Yeah.
I've never seen boss, baby.
I think I love it, though.
If you just like judge it off of this.
If he's just a guy who kind of makes finger guns at you from a from a great distance.
Right.
All for it.
Yeah.
No reason to be upset about that.
We got to hopefully they bring him to Hollywood so we can I guess we can go out to Florida and meet
him when you were talking about unpleasant old cartoons that you've that other kids didn't like.
Aaron, I know you were fond of this bizarre movie Pinocchio and the Emperor of the Night.
Yes.
That's what I thought maybe you were talking about Pinocchio and the Emperor of the Night.
I loved loved loved Pinocchio as a kid and I had a we went to the video store every week to go rent
movies and I loved it because all I had to do was give the phone number like my parents phone number
and I can rent videos so my mom would let me go like be an adult like you could go into the video
store and I rented Pinocchio and the Emperor of the Night probably monthly.
Which is like this other Pinocchio just to clarify it's not Disney.
Is Christopher Lloyd in it?
Christopher Lloyd is in it.
Emperor of the Night.
No I didn't write down his character.
As a boy.
He's always the Emperor of the Night.
Okay.
I think he is the villain of the movie but it also features if you don't know this this odd non-Disney
film yes Ricky Lee Jones singing this weird creepy song that I found was written by the person who
wrote all the Steve Winwood hits.
Really?
Yes back in the high life and Valerie and eventually my heart will go on.
No wonder I liked it.
Also wrote this this creepy what was that song do you know it?
No I don't we rewatched it when we watched Disney's Pinocchio as well.
Yeah.
Wow Tom Bosley Don Knotts.
Don Knotts as G Willikers Ed Asner as Scalawag the Raccoon
Jonathan Harris from Lost in Space as Lieutenant Grumblebee what's any of this who are any of them?
But this movie is packed.
It's another bizarre like the original Pinocchio another like just insane characters that don't
fit together why are we in space there's lieutenants why's Pinocchio meeting lieutenants
and emperors Pinocchio looks a little bit like Rainbow Brite or something.
That's probably why I liked it I really liked Rainbow Brite.
Very similar to Rainbow Brite.
That whole aesthetic.
It was really like drawn over like really like it felt like rotoscoped a little bit with some
of the characters and like creepy too much detail.
A filmation movie which was founded in the valley it was founded in Reseda.
Yeah and was really close to where I grew up.
My beloved Reseda.
Yeah.
Um yeah that's a that's a bizarre one.
Which episode do we do there's a character named Willikers we just came upon right in the recent
past am I wrong?
Not the name of Knott's new.
No that's Whittles.
That's Whittles.
That's Whittles but Willikers is a character we came upon months ago and I cannot remember
and somebody who's listening now is yelling the name of it out at me.
You know what I'm talking about though that sounds familiar.
Yeah a cartoon character.
Willikers from maybe a different like a different old ride or something.
Oh this is gonna get no.
Not sure.
Well we'll come back to it.
Okay um let me move let me move on to this uh because we have to talk about this a little bit
uh and it'll it'll bring us into our final thing um Aaron you wished upon a star and your dream
came true uh you you got to be on the prices right.
Oh yeah.
Yes this was and which was a a lifelong dream like you attempted to do this many years ago.
I got tickets um I've loved the prices right for ever and ever and for my 18th birthday
that's what I did I skipped school and I got tickets to go to a taping of the prices right
but that was back when they just gave tickets to anyone who wrote in and I didn't know that
you had to get there at like four in the morning if you wanted a chance to even walk in the
building so I waltzed in there way too late and everyone was like yeah like.
He worked on.
I don't know what you're thinking getting here at 10 o'clock like um and that kind of turned me
off from it so I never I never tried again.
You didn't pursue it again and then in this bizarre COVID lockdown era they changed their
system of doing things and they had to vet people and test people and it still was like not you know
it was not guaranteed that you would be on even after passing the audition you still get there
and they have to talk to you and make sure you're not a crazy person.
Make sure you are a crazy person.
Sorry I'm sorry yeah don't be afraid of myself as jackass as possible.
Yeah they bring in 12 and nine get to play.
Yeah yeah which is pretty good.
Good odds yeah.
Really good odds.
Those numbers are great I don't know how much longer they'll be doing it this way
but you sort of took advantage of the new way that they've been doing it which led to this
great moment of the show begins it is like they say the price is right and then Aaron
Garner come on down like immediately after um and you're and this is still so let me let me say this
also that this this happens it just aired and thank you to our audience for checking it out
and being super supportive of it and for cutting a clip of it the user uh apathy monger yeah on
reddit which like like it was gave you a handy thing to send to people yeah thank you um um
whoever you are because I I was I actually sent that clip to a few people because I was like I
just I'll just film it off the tv I guess like with my camera I know how to rip it or anything
so yeah geez so wonderful so appreciate it and it was so like so fun watching people like live
react and watch and watch the thing but like so you this just aired but you did it in February
when things were still so covety and so miserable and you got to have this moment of it where you
there was like a there was like a little hook to put your mask on correct yeah at the at the
podiums show show oh that was at the podium but you like like you got to like you were still
masked but then like took it off to run out is that correct oh yeah yeah you held your masks to
your face in the wings and if you heard your name they had a garbage can and you throw your mask in
the garbage can right before you exit the door yeah you got to do that and then run out and have
this moment you're on tv and on your favorite show just like so magical in this like dreaded
not great time um just was and we're heading to something here but is there anything else you
want to say about that experience or anything the listener people wouldn't know about the show or
whatever oh no I don't think so I just yeah you played thank you which game you played I played
one right price right which is I was both relieved and disappointed because I am such a fan I'm a
super fan of the show right and I feel like I could play anything and I think that's why they put me
like in the first four to become on to come on down because I feel like I know every game and
I can play any game and I'm pretty good at them I'd watch you for months preparing for this because
it also got pushed because things got even super locked down so you were thinking about this for
so many months and playing along you're watching every episode and going I'll see how I would have
done this and she overbid and she you were so primed yeah just like very serious about it um so
yeah I get I play one right price which is just the easiest most boring game it's the quickest like
it's the quickest game yeah so I was a little disappointed but also relieved because I was
nervous as hell like it's so much harder when you're in there and you know I flubbed it when
when it was I got the opportunity to bid last in the second game and I I made a rookie mistake and
anyway it took the entire show for it to come back around to me to be the last person to bid
which is the position you want to be in so I had to wait the entire show so I didn't I was the first
person called to come on down last person to play a game you got to it was fun watching the audience
like live feel how you felt where you're like you like keep getting snaked by the just adding the one
dollar it's not that's how you play the game yeah it wasn't mad at anyone who did that to me it's
just strategy it's how you play the game well I was mad they were standing in my way of a
trip or maybe some nice plates I did it at the end though it's how you play the game yes yeah you
that it did end up being your your ticket up you play so for for people who did not watch this um
you uh you play the game and you are the prizes our prizes were uh so I won a giant tv uh to
get up on stage which is great and then it ties in so nicely to the topic of the day a billiards
table was one of the prizes yes and um a fire table a fire pit wow a fire table I wish it was
called it is what it's called really yes I was calling it a fire pit but I've gotten many
email or not many I've had some email exchanges now with the company to confirm shipping and it's
called a fire table that's awesome there is a little like marble table around it I'm so excited
we feel like like it's going to transform our backyard into like a uh like a Tucson Marriott
you say that because I'm currently watching bachelorette and it feels like something
there yeah there wow no they're in like New Mexico or something right now but
yeah it feels the base currently it's not like a Benny Hawn table you could I think you can cook
with it really is it uh propane powered I think it's gas oh it's gas okay yeah um well look
everybody's invited all the listeners are invited over we'll get out our address you can come check
out the fire we're not going to be turned into donkeys anytime soon though because I forfeited
the pool table I don't have room for it don't have room for the yeah yeah you can forfeit
prizes you don't want so yeah couldn't do it yeah couldn't keep the pool table kind of broke
old Scott's heart but you know what we talked about it yeah yeah like well I don't know do we
need a bathroom what if we stood it up long ways and only pulled it out when uh you know the mayor's
baby is over but I guess it is the right move uh for our son this would clearly be the path to
to bring out yeah yeah yeah uh yeah donkeys turns into donkeys as soon as we set it up um okay but
all of this to say uh that now I think this is a perfect opportunity to tie everything together
and to have an actual now price is right winner attempt to play our equally iconic segment that I
had to remember what we officially we were calling it souvenir smackdown yes all right
that we don't have a cue or anything it's not as exciting you don't get to run uh you can stay in
your seat um but so not only souvenir smackdown but this I have prepared a specific Pinocchio themed
version nice of super smacked I did not know about this yes yeah yeah everything is related
or well it's related to things that have been in the air uh in the episode uh in general so uh let
me let me find my notes here um everybody will play you know I think like while Erin
has proven herself on price is right uh we're also it's like weird uh crap off of ebay which
I think gives Mike an advantage and some of it is rather old tiny so Jason is in the game as well
so everyone's got some sort of a hook so we'll have our strength yes yeah yeah superpowers um
okay and uh and as with uh price is right as with bitters row uh it's whoever is closest to the
actual ebay price without going over um do we do they shake it up every time do they change the
order Erin should Erin I'll start with you uh well no whoever wins um if we're doing it yeah
price is right way whoever like if we're going uh clockwise I guess yes whoever wins uh the first
person to bid will be the next person clockwise okay here well look we're gonna start with you
and then you just tell me how it works next time okay next round well like if I win then um well
technically I'd be out uh-huh we'll just make it so that I'm not not the last person okay okay I
win got it all right uh I'll try I'll still consult with you okay let's do round one okay
figure it out uh okay so I will I will try to show this really quickly off my laptop and then I will
uh describe it a little bit more so uh round one is an original copy of a hand-drawn political cartoon
from 1986 this is so it's like it's it's original art drawn on paper this was in a newspaper but
this is the actual uh copy and what the political cartoon it's not Ronald Reagan close this is then
Massachusetts governor Michael Dukakis oh and he is dressed as Pinocchio and uh well before this was
cleverly said about uh Trump throughout his presidency he is portrayed uh as with the long
nose he has told many lies and in this case his long nose has enough room to write the whole phrase
Massachusetts payroll under Dukakis so body just oh and you're not coming back from that son
he tried to run for president yeah really why'd you even give it a shot um okay so this is original
artwork it's said to be in very good condition um and uh it's it's very cutting and satirical
um let's uh let's take a guess uh what this is uh the asking price on eBay Erin four dollars
four dollars Jason I'm gonna say five hundred and one dollars Mike uh 150 dollars
Erin you win round one the actual eBay price 39.99
so by taking the low round what was that what made you think that maybe this would be a
valued item for people oh I've just gone to a lot of comic book conventions and looked at original
art and yeah it's much higher even if I'm even if it's like little Lulu or something that's
probably a bad example because a little Lulu kind of beloved yeah more iconic than this one than
Pinocchio fused with governor Dukakis but you never know I don't know I feel like political car I feel
like there are big fans of like Doonesbury and political so you never know um okay now actually
now I said eBay but we're actually going to switch to Etsy for this next round uh for which I will
show you uh this uh child's Jiminy Cricket costume okay is a a uh cosplay Jiminy Cricket
for a little boy I will demand that we never have this item I'm glad this isn't my present
right and we could end up with it I do not want to it looks well made yeah I think it is very well
made now I don't have the facts in front of me but this is a custom job on Etsy so they'll make
it to your child's size I believe some uh I think I saw some uh taffeta was involved it looks it's
it's it's prettier than a giant hat huge hat so and you know and you're getting buttons and gloves
the the the hole where this is from Etsy user Petit Leon so for a custom Petit Leon child's
Jiminy Cricket costume um where do we where do we start well I should like the advantage since I won
the last one I should start because the advantage is going last okay okay so maybe same order yeah
all right let's do that all right okay I'm gonna say uh 190 um Jason hmm I'm gonna go with 60
dollars okay Mike 99 dollars uh Aaron you win um now I was gonna I've prepared four and the idea
was the two was going to take it so I believe you have already won I'm already 21 uh which I'm really
good at game shows you're very good at game shows if you have a game show get Aaron on it you have a
tip of a game show that is happening uh and you know I want more fire tables also so let's keep
this how much is it actually because it looked nice uh 400 okay yeah for wow handmade to your
child's size yeah that's the ringer there's photos also of this guy's uh costumes in the
wild they're pretty good people wear them to the parks and everything they're pretty well done so
you're already the winner let me quickly rip through uh the last two um I mean my my favorite
you know actually I'll just I'll just do this one just for fun I like this more than maybe the
final one um and here's the old here's where the old timey comes in because what I'm going to show
you is a signed photo of the actor who played Geppetto to the voice of Geppetto who is of course
we all know Christian Rub the actor Christian Rub we knew it yeah uh-huh um which is also how far
sounds like an urban dictionary Christian it's how how far I thought I was allowed to go with a girl
yeah yeah over the clothes 13 or so okay great a Christian Rub uh Christian Rub apparently also the
basis for the uh the visual of uh Geppetto uh so let me show you this it is a photo of course of
Christian Rub in a dark room on the phone he is cloaked in shadow talking to somebody and he has
signed this photo with a lot of text here's what Christian Rub had to say
signed and inscribed in white please betty with an extra e take five gallons of arrowhead spring
water one can colonial stout three pounds of white corn sugar and don't forget to let me test it
July 15th 1932 Christian Rub what's happening here what is this a recipe for moonshine yeah
is that in prohibition era wow no no that's before not the 30s right huh right it's the
that's uh truly insane okay so he has he has a photo of himself on the phone and has written
out a moonshine recipe from 1920 to 1933 so okay still oh my god yeah okay so so he's is he like
trading celebrity status like if i the famous actor Christian Rub say hello to you can i get
some back alley liquor in exchange for that um let's hope that he got it let's hope betty came
through uh the condition says light oxidation what yeah what are they let's we'll we'll we'll
change up the order uh uh Aaron for this uh photo of Christian Rub oh so i'm not going first um
wait i've gone first every time i can go first i go first um is um hmm it's what is it's we're
yeah we're asking like what it's starting at what the what the auction price is starting at yeah yeah
what this person thinks it's worth thousands and thousands of dollars all the Christian Rub heads
up of course um but uh uh 250 dollars okay um do maybe we do we put uh Jason in advantage here
Aaron let's go to you okay um eight bucks great and Jason uh i'm gonna say nine bucks yeah see
that's the smart thing to do yeah yeah so jason's michael's yours again 250 uh it is 375
you win this round yeah see now autographs by their nature bring like i i don't know i don't know if
personalization uh lowers the cost or ups the cost but like yeah autographs are always yeah those i
feel like are more than you think don't know what oxidation does to it um don't know what people not
knowing is something that happens to food not photographs i think a lot of old media
is starting to deteriorate and that physical photographs might fall into that category
depending on how they were processed deteriorate like our memories so the important things in our
heads we have to keep them like the name the name of the actor who played Geppetto Christian Rub
the fact that the figaro signs don't line up in america and france um and all of the wonderful
moments in this ride remember remember the salt mines always remember the salt mines uh Aaron
Garner you survived podcast the right thanks so much for being here thanks for playing thanks
for playing yeah thanks for winning um you guys should really chip in on another fire table for us
to celebrate if it's a Benny Hanna style fire table i would love to do it you're welcome over
we'll get we'll get somebody over or all attempts i'll put on a show uh just flinging shrimp hot
shrimp in your face i just want somebody to fling hot shrimp in my face um Aaron let's exit through
the gift shop is there are there any recent game show appearances that you would like to plug i'm
so glad you asked yes i'd love to plug my stellar appearance on episode 9345 of the price is right
original air date june 28 2021 tape date february 10 2021 uh people people are gonna have to wait
for the price is right uh first half 2021 box set to come out right yeah yeah i'm pretty sure i'll
be heavily featured as everyone's favorite contestant in fact yeah tweet at the price is right let them
know that you want me to be a recurring contestant yeah they haven't done it before but if you enjoyed
seeing me win a pool table in a fire pit yeah just think of how great it would be to see me win a car
yeah i mean i would just purely for entertainment value yeah not for game and hey for fun if you uh
rate and review podcast the ride but give it um five plinko chips like give it five stars yeah
give give it five plinko chips oh specify yeah uh absolutely oh and later let me tie one more
thing together and say that you know please uh go to our tea public store buy merchandise which
in large part is designed by erin thank you for for all the great stuff and i did like the comments
that we got on reddit which is that uh you are you are a coward because you didn't wear a
patanakush shirt on the prices right those are both true statements i am a coward and i did not
wear a patanakush t-shirt so yeah i think they i think they would have let a weed smoking shirt
pass in that one it doesn't have logos so yeah oh yeah that's right you just can't wear logos
right they might have like if they had a problem they could have just digitally
blurred it frame by frame i mean if you were wearing a traditional patanakush shirt it would
have been far too many sizes too big so you would have eaten it as you came on down right
now that's right i've ripped over my own feet it's like an elephant in the chipmunk shirt
yeah shirt dress um that's right if you're gonna buy it buy it many sizes too big that's that's
what we asked for uh thanks thanks for being here um as for us um what's the stuff uh let me scroll
past the christian rub info we said tea public patreon find us on the socials at podcast the ride
and for three bonus episodes every month check out podcast the ride the second gate at patreon.com
slash podcast the ride um and just as one note to go out on um i just want to tie it into the
film i really do believe that when you subscribe to a podcast paywall content your dreams come
true
we are absolutely as good of singers as that guy beautiful better i think better every every
shriver what a funny little podcast we make forever dog this has been a forever dog production
executive produced by mike carlson jason sharridan scott gairdner brett bohme joe
cilio and alex ramsey for more original podcasts please visit forever dog podcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on apple podcasts spotify or wherever you get your podcasts keep
up with the latest forever dog news by following us on twitter and instagram
at forever dog team and liking our page on facebook