Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast may contain backwoods psychos raised by wolves, untrustworthy
hot dog magnets, and laser violence against Dickensian insects.
Mookie Blakelock takes us on a cozy but disturbing journey through the weird wild theme parks of
New Hampshire on Podcast The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, a podcast hosted by guys who love theme parks, but today we'll
determine if we also love weird facilities where bears play basketball.
I'm Scott Gardner and I'm joined by, let's go Jason Sheridan this time.
Sure.
Yeah.
I'm of two minds about like animal shows.
You know, I feel like I've mostly seen bird shows.
I don't know if I've seen a lot of bear shows.
I personally have never seen a bear show.
We're going to talk about a bear show.
Mike Carlson.
Yeah, I'm of two minds.
I both like and love a bear show.
So yeah, we will discuss it obviously more as we go along, but.
I see you covered the two sides of my head and as far as this show is concerned.
Yeah.
Listen, everybody today.
Here's a phrase I didn't think I would say on the podcast.
Probably today we're talking about the theme parks of New Hampshire.
I don't think this was ever on the board.
I don't think this was like going to come up from us, but a guest has brought this to
us and I'm very excited about it because I love when we can explore an area we know nothing
about.
We've got a lot of odd stuff that we figured out due to our guest.
He is the host of the podcast.
You are worthy with Lil Mookie B. He's one of the funniest guys around.
Mookie Blakelock is here.
Hi, Mookie.
Hi, guys.
Hello.
Thanks for having me.
Of course.
So happy to have you.
Thank you.
And yes, sorry.
This is look, it's all I could come up with.
I love it.
I built it up.
Yeah, I got excited about it now.
It sucks.
It's stupid.
We can change it.
We could just kill this and do it later.
We're just thinking new.
It's dumb.
It's stupid.
Do you want to do the Cars ride?
We'll talk about the Cars ride.
I guess nobody likes me.
I guess I'm just a dumb idiot.
No, don't say that.
No, I guess I'm just a fucking loser.
No, come back.
I don't like it.
This is spinning out faster than any episode ever.
We've never had a spin out.
This is like a spin out on like Lightning McQueen's track on the Cars Land ride.
Clearly we should be talking about it and I know that, but that's not what we're talking
about.
Look, we're here.
I'm excited about it.
Yeah, it's going to be great.
Jason, I think you were psyched about what we've found.
You were saying you've got a ton of tabs.
You're overflowing with tabs.
Yeah, I think it was starting to slow down my computer earlier and then I lost them all
because I had to restart, but I got most of them back.
I have a book.
I was wondering how to start.
You have a book for this?
Well, I was wondering how to start researching this episode, which I think we should go the
other way.
I think we should declare like a 50 state, you know, we should do the Soufian and go
like every state's theme parks.
But as I was one starting to research this, I was like, what park should I start with?
And then I happened by a little free library that had the Amusement Park Guide, a book
published in 1990.
Whoa, whoa.
It gave me the two of the parks I'm sure we're going to talk about today.
New Hampshire has two entries at this.
It is a state by state guide and New Hampshire's two parks listed.
And were two of them the ones that I had brought to you?
Canobie Lake Park.
Storyland.
Which I believe is part of Santa's Village.
Yes.
Oh, no, maybe not.
Maybe not Storyland.
They are separate.
Storyland I believe is the one.
One of them is run by the people who run Kennywood in Pennsylvania.
They also run Storyland.
Feels like the vibe.
There's some Kennywood vibes in these I would say.
But all the parks I read about were very charming, a lot of natural beauty, a lot in wooded areas.
And you don't get that every place you build a theme park, you know?
No, true.
Not at all.
What's your...
Ibuki, like what...
Well, I guess I have a couple of New Hampshire questions.
I don't think I know like the vibe of it in general.
I don't know what are the like, what are the stereotypes or like what you might regard
as what is like particularly New Hampshire-y?
What can you tell us on that on that front?
Well, it's interesting because I feel like I kind of have a little bit of an outsider
perspective of New Hampshire as well.
I grew up in Massachusetts.
Oh, gosh.
Okay.
And so we would...
So my family, I'm an only child, so it's just me and my mom and my dad.
And we would go up to New Hampshire every year for a week to the same campground every
year, McBurke Campground in Lisbon, New Hampshire, and we would go to one of these places every
year.
But it's the only place we literally ever went on vacation.
We literally never went on vacation to another place.
We didn't go...
We didn't like...
When I was four years old, we got on a plane and went to Florida and went to Disney World,
which I have no recollection of.
But other than that, my family is very like, we like things the way we like them.
And so we went to the same place.
And so I haven't even explored New Hampshire that much.
But New Hampshire and Vermont, I feel like, are kind of like the same vibe.
I mean, they're right next to each other, but it's like, it's woodsy, it's like, cabiny,
there's lakes.
It's like a lot of...
It's very New England-y.
It's like, there's lots of like, lots of things are made of wood and there's like a lot of
brick walkways and cobblestone and stuff like that.
You know what I mean?
Like it's very New England.
There's lighthouses and like...
Actually, I don't think New Hampshire is on the coast.
I think Vermont is.
I could be wrong about that.
This is how little I fucking know about anything.
I can't even tell you like where towns in Massachusetts are because like I was so...
I never went far from my town or whatever, but like geographically.
But yeah, New Hampshire is like woodsy, New England, like brick and stone and wood and
like, you know.
Is it cozy?
It's cozy.
It's like fireplaces and little shops and like dads with their shirts tucked into their
shorts with sandals walking around, you know, getting ice cream on like a farm that has
cows on it or whatever.
That's my best description of like the New Hampshire vibe.
And then it's like, if you keep going up New England, north to like Maine, Maine is like
even more of that, but it's like even almost a little more like back woodsy and like everybody
has a fucking tractor and you know, like you catch lobsters off of the dock.
What's the word I'm looking for?
The dock?
The pier?
Yeah, the pier.
What's the harbor?
The harbor.
And like everyone has a boat and like, you know, that's like Maine is like where, you
know, that's where people are like, you know.
Oh, up here in Maine, you know, that's the...
Yes, yes.
No, I was walking down the beach or whatever.
And so that's the like, that's like New England, New England.
That's like the almost like Maine is almost like no man's land.
And then it's like you go down south New England and it's like Massachusetts and Connecticut
and Rhode Island, which is just a totally different vibe, but still kind of like, you
know, seaside town or whatever.
But like as you go up, like Rhode Island, Cape Cod, New England is like seaside, like
lighthouses.
And then you keep going up to like New Hampshire, Vermont, and it starts getting like a little
quieter and a little greener.
Is there an accent?
Is there a New Hampshire like, is it a dialed back Maine?
It's the New England accent.
It's like a Boston accent.
It's a Boston accent.
Oh, OK.
A little.
Oh, sure, sure, sure.
OK.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Did you like the one place that you went on vacation or did you get tired of the one place
you went on vacation?
I don't know.
Somewhere in between.
Well, it's like so we went to so it was like one week a year we went to this place, McBruik
Campground in Lisbon, New Hampshire.
It's some place that like an old friend of like my dad's like took him to once and he
fell in love with it.
And it's like this very, very quiet campground in the middle of kind of nowhere, New Hampshire.
It was like it's like a couple hours like up into like from the New Hampshire from the
Massachusetts New Hampshire border.
And we stayed at the same campsite every year like my dad would book it a year in advance
because he wanted the same site.
And you know, it was like us going and it was very quiet and it's like it's very woodsy
and there's like there's a brook that runs through it, the Mink Brook.
So that's why it's called Mink Brook Campground.
There's a brook that runs through it.
We had a campsite that was on the brook.
And like if you go to the front of the campground, it was like they had a pool and then they
had a little shop with like the office and like you could, you know, a little shop you
could buy like candy and like baseball cards and shit.
And then they had a little they're cool part about it is they had this big Airstream trailer
that they turned into an arcade.
And so there were like video games inside of it, like arcade games, which was just like
I would spend all my time there because it was just me and my parents.
I was an only child and my parents were there to get away from the hustle and bustle of
our lives and like read books.
So they would be reading books.
We have like the pop up trailer and shit where you tow it behind my dad's Jeep and then like,
you know, like the sides come up and expand and, you know, you like crank up the thing
and you pull the awning out and it had two beds and like a little shower in it and stuff.
And then my dad had like, you know, a gas stove and we like we he like really did it
up. It was kind of like early glamping.
But, you know, my parents like would put out like their shit, their like foldable Shays
lounges and read a book.
And I would be like, throw a frisbee with me, walk to the store with me.
And they would be like, go do that by yourself.
And so I would ride my bike around like by myself.
I would go down to the store and they would give me money and I would and they would be
like, don't buy candy with it.
And I would buy candy with it and I would go find a place to hide and eat it.
And it was just like and then every now and then my dad would be like, all right, let's
throw a frisbee back and forth or like we will go down to the pool together as a family
or whatever. Or if there were other kids at other campsites, he would be like, go make
friends with that kid, even though I had like crippling anxiety, social anxiety and like
did not want to go talk to kids that I didn't know.
That's a vacation nightmare.
Like never do I want to.
I've never done anything good.
Come from me trying to make friends on a trip.
I don't understand. Like you walk into scenes where like you guys don't know each other
before. How did this happen?
I can't make friends on trips.
The only time that ever worked for me was on a cruise ship and there was like kids,
ours by age group.
And we were kind of forced into it.
It's like we don't want you just wandering a cruise ship all day.
And then looking back, I'm like, well, I was 12.
Why not? Why couldn't I?
What? You let me wander half the time anyway.
Why did I have to do little skits and like activities and stuff?
You did skits with 12.
I was strangers.
Oh, oh, yeah.
And like crafts, there was crafts and like pool hour and stuff.
And it was like here, staff occupy the children so your parents can drink at the pool before
dinner time, you know, so your parents can do the on ship casino.
Yeah.
Wow. I'm killing.
That's it. Yeah, it was fun.
I mean, it was fun, but I never like when we went to Disney or even if we went to like
the mountains or stuff like it, never again did I really have that experience.
Mm hmm.
Yeah, no, I didn't make friends with anyone on vacation.
Yeah, never happened.
So what what what a like I guess maybe as an adult and you know, we've all got our
little boomer parents, but just like just like go go go up to that kid and make
friends with them, literally just like go walk up to that campsite right now and say,
Hi, my name is Michael Blakelock and can I please play with your daughter or whatever?
And I'm like, are you fucking kidding me?
That is a nightmare.
I don't want to talk to that kid.
I'm too I'm I'm literally scared of that person.
Like I don't want to talk to people I don't know.
Yeah, and it's kids.
So they might say, get out of here, idiot.
Like it might be like it won't happen if you feel like I want to try to like talk
to this girl or tell you these people at a bar.
It might probably won't happen as an adult, but like get the hell out of my face.
Could happen with a child.
Yeah.
Or like I go up to it's just like, Hi, can I play?
Or and then it's like, oh, so you're just our responsibility now.
I'm just walking.
Exactly.
Can I play cards with you guys or whatever?
Just like my parents don't want to do it.
So like I'm now I'm your problem.
And all of these parks, the New England kind of parks, it seems.
If you look on their websites, like places to stay,
they're sending you to either a campground or they're sending you to
like a motel, essentially.
And because it's very rusty, I usually like if you look up six legs,
places to stay in the area, it'll have a link to like, all right,
there's a courtyard Marriott, there's a Hilton Garden in less
the case, seemingly in New England.
It's a lot of still little motor lodges.
Yeah, it's it's all especially like in that area of New Hampshire.
It's like it's very like you start getting into like
like the wilderness where it's like there's you're going to have to like,
if you're at this campground,
you're going to have to drive 25 minutes to get to something
to do, right, right, which is the thing, which, you know,
speaking of what we're speaking of, but like that would be the thing.
So like we would go up there for a week every summer and then one day
of the week, we would like take a day trip out to like one of these places.
Oh, that's the the trip is to the one place, but this is the right.
I guess we should do something.
So you go to one of these.
It is just like we cannot be here every single day.
So we would go into like or it would be like a couple of days.
So it would be like, you know, one day we would go into like Littleton,
New Hampshire, which was like a couple of towns over.
And they had like a little town square with like a bookstore.
And we would go to the bookstore and like they would they would be like,
we will buy you a book and you can read a book from this place.
Or or we would go to Sanders Village or we would go to Clark String Bears.
Canopy Lake Park was not a vacation thing for me.
That was just another New Hampshire.
Like that's the big New Hampshire, like like independent,
like little amusement park that I had been to many times.
But that's separate from these vacations that I took with my.
But if we took a day trip, we would either go.
And it was and it was we went there for years.
And we would go to every year it was last year.
We went to Clark's Trading Post.
And this year we'll go to Santa's Village and next year we will go to Clark's.
And then the next year we will go to Santa's Village.
And then next year we'll go to Clark's.
And then it got to a point where like, you know,
when I was like maybe 12 or 13 or 14 for like a couple of years,
they were like, you can bring a friend so you have someone.
They were like, this kid is going fucking stir crazy.
You can bring one of your friends.
And then when I was like 15, they were like, you can stay home alone
while we go out. And I was that can rules.
Yeah, that's great.
But yeah, those were those were my those were my experiences
with those smaller places where it was just like we would go to those two places
every year.
Mm hmm. So then do you like did you like them or was it like, well, it's a place
there's there's distractions, there's signs I can point at and that will fill time.
I mean, I think it was like Stockholm syndrome where it's like, well,
I have to like it because I don't have a choice.
You know what I mean? It's not like I hate going here.
I'm like, I think that my dad tells me every year that I like this.
And so I believe it because like I'm I'm your hostage.
I'm like your lifelong hostage.
That's yeah, there's a there is a point.
There's points for I think it happens a lot when you're a kid
and either like you finally realize you can have like an opinion
or you can have a choice about something.
Like when I was a kid and I was playing soccer a few years in a row
and I didn't realize I hated soccer until my mom said, you know,
you don't have to play it because like she got my she got the sense
that I was not maybe that into soccer because I'd run away from the ball
and only cared about getting a hot dog after the game.
And then she presented that to me.
And I remember going, oh, I don't want to play soccer anymore.
But it up to that point, I felt, oh, I'll be playing soccer for my whole life.
There'll be never a time when I won't be playing soccer.
Yeah, that's just who I am.
It's just yeah, I was told that this is what I'm doing.
And there's no part of me that goes like, well, mother and father
are certainly not wrong.
They're always right. In fact,
they know they happen to know everything and I actually know nothing.
Yeah, I stuck around in Boy Scouts and baseball
for probably a year or two, too long, because I was like, oh, well,
I don't want to upset anyone by not doing this.
And then once I started doing school plays, I was like, well, I found this
and I like this more.
So I think I'm just going to gravitate towards this.
Sure.
We're Mookie, when you were going on the trip, were you like, at least
do you think like, OK, that candy store is good and the arcade is good?
Because that's obviously that would have appealed to me.
And I would be like, oh, yeah, it's the, you know,
old time confectionary with a bunch of taffy or something.
I'm just imagining what it is.
Yeah, I mean, no, I mean, literally, it was like a little
it was like a tiny, like, like the size of like my bedroom,
like, like just like corner store.
It was it was literally like it was like the front desk to the campground.
So it's like when you when you pull in and you're checking in,
you go in this little shop and then there's the lady
who owns the place behind the desk and you go, hi, we're in site number.
We're the Blake locks and we're in site number 36 or whatever.
And then they go, great, welcome.
And then, you know, it happens to just be a little general store
where it's like they got a little freezer with like ice cream sandwiches
in it and stuff and like, you know, you can get like candy bars
and candy and like fruit pies and shit like that.
But it's like it's like the office slash front desk slash
little general store where like you can go.
It's like where you would go and like outside, you could buy like fire,
like bundles of firewood or like, you know, they had like
it was almost like a little market where it's like you get marshmallows
and Hershey bars and graham crackers to like go make s'mores at your campsite.
Gotcha. I'll be honest.
I said it before. It sounds cozy.
The whole thing sounds very cozy. It's cozy. It's cozy.
But I can see how you might bristle
just doing these things over and over again, especially because Santa's Village
and like story land fall into the category of this is an amusement park
catering to 12 and under maybe 13 and under.
So as you're hitting adolescence,
it this stuff hits less and less.
My family, I feel like my family got so into theme parks
that we tapered off from like storybook lander
Dutch wonderland kind of parks kind of quickly. Right.
And I mean, like I understand I understand this more now is like an adult,
like approaching 40, but like,
you know, like I got what was appealing to my parents.
It was just like it's a quiet,
relaxing place that has a babbling brook running through it.
And I get to escape the hustle and the bustle of Ashland, Massachusetts.
And
and like go and like I get to like read books and be in nature and stuff like that.
And it's like, yeah, I might like that now.
Right. But just like as a kid, you're like.
I mean, it's fun to just be like, we're getting in the car
and we're going someplace different and like it is fun and like we're
we're like sleeping in a tent or whatever.
And it's cool. But it's also just like, I mean, as a kid, for most of it,
it's just like I have like child energy and I'm just like,
oh, I have nobody to fucking play with or do anything.
And it's like, I want to do way more than they want to do.
And it was always just them just being like,
oh, can we please just sit here and read a read the new Janet Ivanovich?
Look, it's you don't understand.
Mookie, it's two for the show.
We read one for the money last summer.
Two for the dough. Excuse me.
We get deadly for the score.
Five. Stephanie Plum is back.
And I'm the last person in my office to read about her adventures.
Those books are so funny that they just like there's like 23 of them or whatever.
And like the like the the names just start being like
like it's 12.
Yeah. What do you do after there's no puns?
13 dream any numbers north of 19?
Yeah. They had three good ones.
They had one for the money, two for the dough, three to get deadly.
One score, one for the money, of course, made into a movie starring Catherine
Heigl. That's right.
It's glued into my mind
as the only movie I've ever seen sold tickets,
tickets sold on Groupon for a movie.
Oh, my God. Yeah.
It was a it was box office.
My my parents were like, that was one of the worst movies
we've ever seen, and we love those Stephanie Plumb books.
It's like, yeah, it's such a God sucker because they like the book.
Oh, my God. Group rates like how they did, like what they did with, like,
Passion of the Christ.
Get your group together.
Oh, no, no group pond.
Like, get us. Oh, no, I know.
Ticket. Yeah. Yeah, boy.
That's crazy.
Um, you know what? I went to I have a New Hampshire memory, too,
which is similar to this is the high end of this is the the the like,
this is the like annoying, fancy version of the boring place.
Do you know what the what the Balsams is?
Does that sound familiar?
Do you know about Dixville Notch, New Hampshire?
The Dixville Notch is the town where only like seven people live there
and they get up early and vote first thing so that they can be the first place
where the election results come in in the New Hampshire.
Well, and they you mean in the primary because the New Hampshire primary
is the big one. You just mean the election that that's like as a collective group.
They're like, we're getting up early so we can have this claim to fame.
Is the New Hampshire primary the first primary?
Yes. Yes. It's before the Iowa caucus.
Then that must be the thing.
Like they cast their president vote first of all, as it's the first state
and the first time they all know each other.
So they wake up and it's the it's the most like odd, mundane little.
But there's like a there's a really nice resort near there
where you get to learn about this tradition and how it's been going for.
And I was watching videos about the place and it flashed me right back to like,
yes, it's pretty. It's so pretty.
There was nothing I wanted less as a kid than pretty.
Pretty, so pretty was absolutely boring.
And now in retrospect, I feel like my parents probably took me
to some like jaw dropping places where I was like, no, but it's not.
I would like absolutely rather be playing Mario Kart than any
any one of these places.
Yes. Yeah.
Leave me at home with a bunch of sunny delights or something.
You just the beauty of Mumu Farms is better than anything that's in New Hampshire.
That's right.
Yeah, they all have like Egyptian levels, like the deserts, the
all the winds you see there.
That's one of the wonders of the world. Hey, I relate to that.
I think also that was a hotel that I really specifically
this is how fancy and traditional the hotel was, is that they
I remember getting that.
This is very important to me because it was the season premiere of The Simpsons
when we got there.
You can't miss the sea. These will never be able to be seen again.
No one's tracking the Simpsons.
If I don't see it now, I'll never see it.
Mom, dad drop. I don't fancy dinner or whatever your plan.
I do not want to do it.
I want to watch The Simpsons no matter what.
And then and then I am told, no, no, no, this is a traditional resort.
There are not televisions in the room.
I'm sorry. What are you talking?
The whole summer is ruined.
Wait, but that's OK. There is a television room.
We did at some point recognize that these ghost
children wanted to see TV and they opened a TV.
And I'm like, wait a minute, I as a 13 year old have to convince the room
to put on this show or else I will miss the show.
And thankfully, there was enough group think that we wanted to watch it.
And then it was Mike, the one we were just talking about.
Was it the wait?
The one we agreed was the yes, Edison.
And then like so after all that, then it's the episode
that lets you know that the show is no longer good.
Absolutely awful memory.
All of this, all this.
I have to get to the TV room and I think I had to wear a coat.
You have to wear a coat to sit in a room and watch a fancy restaurant.
Yes. Yes. A coat for a child.
I had to wear a little coat for the TV room. Yes.
My parents loved this.
We came back from this trip.
I remember like my sister and I still talk about it, that my mom,
like a threat in the car as we were leaving the place said from now on,
when we get home, Wednesdays will be fancy Wednesdays.
We will all dress up and we will eat dinner as a family and we will look nice.
And I was like, for Noah, for us only.
I have to wear his coat while we eat like fish sticks.
What are you talking about?
I love when like suburban parents like get outside of their bubble
and see something and then they go, OK, we are doing this now.
This is we are now making a change.
And this is this is the rule of this is the law of the land from now on.
Do you understand?
And then it lasts for like, you know, a couple of weeks or so.
But it's stupid.
There will be like a short like making we're going to make our own pasta now.
We I'm not buying it out of the bags anymore.
We'll do it together and you will cut the shapes and I will put them
into the grinder.
And then it's so bad. The first time you try.
We had like a law like chore allowance.
We're like, we're doing this now.
You're not just going to get money when you beg for something.
Here's what you do.
That's we'll reward you.
Twenty five cents per you make your bed, you clean you.
OK, that's how we're doing it.
Three weeks later out the window.
It's just the begging system for whatever you want.
It is back in play.
It's gone. It's over.
And white all or nothing, just like
there's no like patience or like examination of like,
you know, there's stuff in our family that maybe isn't working
or I don't like the attitude of my kids or something.
And then you see one other idiot be like, my family does it this way.
And you're like, we're doing it this way.
And you don't have a say in it. And we're doing it.
And if we don't do it, you're in you're in trouble.
And then they're the ones that give up on it.
And then like a month later, when you're back to the way that,
you know, business as usual in your family, you're just like,
do you want me to go?
My family's was like, I said, I'm they think
they thought I said I was bored too much.
I was always like, I'm bored.
And so my we we we took a bunch of piece, little slips of paper
and wrote like things to do, like do a puzzle, like read a book, like take a walk.
And if I ever said I'm bored, we would put them in a drawer
and I would open the drawer and pick one out and be like, OK, do a puzzle.
And now like we do, you know, that's like the shit we would do if I was bored.
And it was just like so like walking over to that fucking drawer.
My mom being like, let's go over to the drawer and pick something to do
if you're bored and then pick out something where it's like, you know, it's like
build a castle of blocks and it's like, oh, this fucking sucks.
And then and of course, after a while, it was just like, I'm bored.
And they were like, well, I don't know what to tell you.
Yeah, I'm bored is not like
I think kids just say that as like a response.
You know, it's it's like a little verbal tick.
And it's like, yeah, well, you're probably not really bored.
You probably just need like
the equivalent of jangling keys in front of your face.
But you're seven.
You're that I can't jangle keys.
And you didn't fucking give me a brother or a sister to play with.
So like me, a child has to fill 24 hours of the fucking day.
Yeah, that's true.
I know I got to figure it out.
That's a lot.
You really advanced my mental arguments for should I have another child?
This is this is typically pushed me a long way.
It's your life, it's your family, it's your whatever.
But just let you know.
Do you really want your kid to turn out like me, Scott?
Well, Scott, I have one brother and do you want him to turn out like me?
So these are your options.
I'm looking down two different river paths.
I don't know which that's right.
I just crashed down the middle.
As we're saying all this, so I'm realizing like, oh, yeah, that,
you know, my family did little bits of this, but it's like,
it's kind of chill looking back in some ways,
because I'm realizing like, well, my mom was the youngest of five
and my dad's the youngest of four.
So I think maybe at some point they're like, all right, well, let's
let's keep a quieter house.
Like, that's not let's we don't have to do this insanity
like our parents did.
These are numbers of siblings that are impossible.
Like they are. You could maybe get your head around.
All right. Maybe I could have a kid and not go bankrupt.
But five like, do are we going to know anyone
our age with five children, unless it's an accident?
Well, and also if I when I'm asked what did my grandparents do,
it's always like, well, he did a little of this and a little of that.
Like, it's never like, oh, is that this job for 30 years or that sort of thing
for our parents? I mean, my dad worked for a long time.
But like, yeah, my grand, I feel like my grandparents
were retired by the time I knew them.
But but they jumped around to other jobs a lot.
Mm hmm. Mm hmm.
Yeah. We should get to these parks or where we have the least
theme park content.
But it's all applicable. We got we're in the vibe now.
So we're in the vibe. We're in the new.
Yeah, I was told this is a loose structure.
Oh, yes. No, no, no. That is correct.
I'm just making sure we do it.
That's what I was told. That's what I was told.
There's no there's no itinerary.
There's no every five minutes.
This happens.
Let's just start.
Let's start tossing them out. Can't it be like park?
This seems like the biggest of the one.
This is like the most like major. Yeah.
Theme park of all this.
So this was not this was a separate trip.
This was not in the regular rotation.
Yes, this was not in the and I'm not even remembering where it is.
I think it's a little closer like to like Nashua, New Hampshire,
which is like a little closer to the like Massachusetts, New Hampshire border.
But can it be like Park was like the like?
I don't know how to describe it,
but just like, you know, the independent, like small local like theme park,
but like with legitimate like roller coasters and stuff.
Yeah. Family owned seemingly, which is sort of rare.
Yeah, it was the place where you went, like on a school trip
or on a camp trip or like, you know, your friend is like,
we're going to Canopy Lake Park if you want to come with us.
And that was like, you know, it was like an hour and a half away
or something like that. You know what I mean?
And that that was the like that was like a full like
theme park with like rides and roller coasters and,
you know, like, I do.
Yeah. 30 miles outside of Boston.
So pretty close.
There's that area originated as a trolley park.
And this was like where I was, you know, to or something.
Yes, that's right.
And so where trolleys would terminate, Kenny, what I mentioned in Pittsburgh,
also a trolley park, Dorney Park and Wildwater Kingdom and Allentown, Pennsylvania.
Also a trolley park.
When I was looking at the Wikipedia and I saw the phrase trolley park,
I'm like, there's no way Jason will not say this for that phrase is like Jason Bates.
It's like a little crate was put up
in front of a sign that said trolley park. That's right.
And there used to be quite a few trolley parks in America.
But as the automobile
rose in prominence, a lot of the trolley lines closed
and a lot of the barks went away or they evolved into amusement parks.
But there are still 13 left that started as a truck.
God, yes. Thank God.
How are the trolleys doing? Do those work?
Oh, no, they're long dead.
They all burn up.
But but later you can still hear the sound that a trolley makes.
The ghost of the rail.
What do they have a horn?
If anyone knows what trolleys do, it's Jason.
If they go clang, clang, clang, as we learned in Meet Me in St.
Louis. Oh, that's right. That's right. That's right.
This seems like you're Jason.
We're saying this is like a Kenny Wood field of this little you.
You'd probably dig this place, I'd imagine.
Yeah, I mean, it's it it it's right up my alley.
It reminds me a lot of Kenobles Park in Pennsylvania, another older park.
It's got a few roller coasters.
It's got a dark ride.
They do a Halloween event.
And it also is the was the inspiration for a Stephen King novel called Joyland,
one of the newer Stephen King novels.
That's unsettling, though.
Yeah, that's scary. Yeah.
Um, what was the like?
Did I I don't know what like what you was the one who went here?
Like like, did you have fun when you when you went here, Mookie?
Yeah, I mean, this is my my my my my fondest memory is that
it was the first time I went on an upside down roller coaster.
So they had the cork.
The corkscrew is like their big fun upside down roller coaster.
So it's not like a full loop roller coaster.
It's like a you go up and you do a little twist.
You know what I mean? Kind of thing.
Mm hmm. And I remember going with my dad
and like him being like, you're going to love it.
And me being like a scared little boy and being like, no, it's scary.
And he's like, let's just get in line. Let's do it.
He convinced me to do it.
And it was like one of those were like, we did it.
And I was like, that was the most fun thing I've ever done.
And we got back in line and we went on it like three more times.
It was like my first upside down roller coaster experience.
It was it was a fond memory.
Oh, there's that there's the corkscrew.
And then they have like the really old I think it's like the oldest
or like one of the oldest.
They have the the Yankee Cannonball, which is like their old wooden
roller coaster, like the like the standard wooden roller coaster.
Which was lame, rickety and fun.
And then like the only other thing I can remember there was like they have one
of those like, what's the fucking it's like the Gravitron,
like it just spins really fast and then they drop the floor out from under you.
Like they have one of those.
Oh, it's I mean, that's why I always call it a Gravitron.
Yeah, like a tilt to whorlers or not a tilt to world, but just like, you know,
you get sucked up against the side of the thing.
But those were like the big rides there.
Oh, and they had a big they had this really cool one where it's like,
you know, one that just spins and it's like you're you're like sitting in a thing
that's hanging from hanging from like wires and you just basically
just get like flung around or whatever.
You know, it's a bunch of little things that you sit on.
They were like shaped like roosters and you sit in them and they're
you're hanging from a wire and it spins and you're just like going around the thing.
Maybe that's more like tilt to whorl or whatever.
Now, it's not.
Well, it's all to whorl is like, yeah, that like half kind of
I don't know how you describe it.
Like it's like sort of circular back and then there's a little seat
and then it spins as the whole thing spins as well.
It's literally just like you're just getting swung around by a wire,
but you're sitting in a thing anyways.
A little chair.
It's like a little chair, like a little swing kind of thing.
Almost was like a little like I'm trying to find.
They were these big roosters and they could fit two people.
So it's like you're almost sitting in like a little like
I don't fucking know.
A little spinner ride car.
Yeah, like you're just sitting in a thing.
You're like sitting in a little.
Is it like that? Hold on. I'll show you a photo here.
Is it like this one here?
Is it like this thing right here?
Yes. Yeah.
But there were less.
There were less things and the things were bigger.
The things could fit like two people in them and got probably like 10 of them
in the whole thing.
And then you would just it would just get swung around.
Not sure. Sure.
We were a different kind of theme park podcast.
This would only be all we know the names of the things.
And we say all of the names and we say the manufacturers.
And there are no jokes.
Oh, that's you want that podcast.
It exists and the audio is way worse than ours.
So you might want to stay with us.
Hey, Yankee.
Yankee Cannibal was made by the Philadelphia Toboggan Company,
who has made quite a few rides in the last 100 years.
Jason's got your cover.
You're saying he's got all of that.
Let me I think the question you asked me was, do what?
What are my memories of that?
And my memories are.
I I wish I had more of them.
I think my whole childhood was just like fear and anxiety.
And so I don't retain a lot of memories.
But I remember going with a friend of mine,
my friend Bear Klaus, his name was Robert Klaus, but we called him Bear.
And we would go and we would like it would be like this whole like fantasy.
Like we like for some reason, I always we like me
and my friends always had these fantasies of like,
we're characters on a TV show and like.
So like we're like when we get in the park, we're like these characters.
And so we're like we're like these two guys who like are on some adventure
and we're in a movie and like, you know, the roosters are like we're
we have a big pet rooster and we fly on it or whatever.
And like, I don't know.
That's like that's why you were having like one.
You had a persona.
It wasn't just like we're going to the park.
It's like we are we're turning this experience into like this is a fantasy
of like we are these two cool guys.
And this is an adventure that we're on.
And each of the rides is like part of our adventure or whatever.
So that's like it was like Muppet Babies.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like you would have just like kind of a fantastical fantasy journey.
I guess not. They were in the nursery.
So they weren't even in a cool place like theme park.
But they're in a you're in a cool place imagining it's a cooler place
or that you're cooler people.
I guess that would be it. Yes.
That I that I would I would die if I had to just be myself.
So is that why you take on personas and play characters?
Is that like? Yeah, I know.
You know, I think the coolest thing about acting and performing
is that you get to be whoever you want to be.
You know what I mean?
You know, you could be someone who knows England.
Or you could say something cut out there.
You became some.
Wait, the Mookie's cutting out.
There's these other people showing up and say, who else got the zoom link?
Well, so far, so the Queen of England and a bum on the street,
a bum on the street, I think both from the same part of the state.
Assistant football coach Jerry Sandusky.
OK, anybody.
Wait a minute.
Maybe you shouldn't be anybody blackout.
You can be anyone in your wildest fantasies.
Do you?
I don't know. Maybe I'm getting ahead of myself here.
But do you remember the characters at the park?
Oh, God, this is like going to be too embarrassing.
I think it was like we were whatever it was.
It was like we were supposed to be two guys who are very cool.
And like we're starring in our own TV show and it's about.
The two of us being like.
Like like two adventurers or something where it's like,
like I feel like there was like a fantasy element to it, where it was like
there were people chasing us and we had to like get away from them and fight them.
So it's like, you know, we're on the rooster thing going around
and the people in the rooster thing behind us are chasing us with their own rooster.
Or like, you know, like the like the corkscrew roller coaster is like us,
like on some like train track, like getting away from the people
that are chasing us or something like that.
Again, that's like to the best of my memory.
That's it was something like that, where it was like because we would play
these characters like not at the theme park, too.
It would be like when we were just hanging out with the wilds, like
the theme park was like the the theme park was like, you know, and it's like
like the special episode of Family Matters where they shoot it at Disney World
or whatever. It's like that, where it's like the the special on location
episode of the fantasy TV show that we are in at Canopy Lake Park, where
normally when we're playing at one of our houses, we're just two guys
that have that have that shoot guns and play with swords or whatever.
But when but when we're at Canopy Lake Park, it's like now we have flying roosters
and like tilt the world tracks that like pull us into other dimensions or whatever.
We had we had we had we had wonderful imaginations.
I admire that you found someone who would commit to this with you,
because I feel like I would have flights of fancy like this.
As a child, and I would never in a million years utter them out.
I would be like this.
I cannot vocalize this where I will be put in a straight jacket.
Like they will wheel me away.
I probably had something where I like for some reason,
because I felt embarrassed about every fucking breath that I took as a child,
where I was just like, I don't know, maybe there was no filter on this one.
Or like this friend in particular was just like, I do that stupid,
dorky shit to idiot. Yeah, that's awesome.
I love that you had like a like a long narrative.
It was like a like a long serialized pro TV show or something.
Yeah, yeah.
That's like only child stuff to me, where it's just like,
I'm alone with my imagination 24 seven.
So if any if if anybody wants to like do this with me, like, please, you're welcome.
Sure. Yeah. Thanks a lot of psyche, a major service.
I know I'm just like, I've got all these I've got all these.
It's kind of how I feel now.
It's like I have all these incredible creative thoughts in my head
and I just need to get them out.
Yeah, of course.
And if we were a different kind of podcast, right?
We would spend the next half an hour or so exploring those kind of things,
but we don't have time.
No time.
We have to say facts.
We have to say when things opened, we know there's there's characters in the
you don't have to just invent your own characters in the part.
You can meet some characters.
They're not tied to Disney or Warner Brothers or any of those things.
They had to make up their own things.
So so, you know, they have a set of characters.
I feel like Jason, maybe you have more about the about you as a less Jason.
I have pictures, but I didn't really find names.
There's a video where some of them have
there's like a video where they go through character boot camp.
Did you find that?
I saw that.
Yeah, like like it was just a little promotional video.
They do YouTube content.
They're content makers, too.
Yeah, they also probably have to.
I bet that place has changed a lot since the last time I was there.
I mean, the last time I was there
was probably like at least 20 years ago.
Oh, gotcha. Yeah.
So they have a YouTube channel.
That's one thing that happened.
Wouldn't have been possible then.
Like I didn't do any research.
Kind of a poorly labeled YouTube channel too.
I mean, this guy came across this guy a lot with a button nose.
Well, that's he's patches.
We know he has patches.
OK. Mike and I both we always says it on his stomach.
Yeah, yeah.
It was just funny how much we both wanted patches.
And he's a teddy bear.
Nobody said to I got was for a teddy bear.
Yeah, that's that.
That's the Leonardo DiCaprio once upon a time in Hollywood meme
when he's pointing at the way he went to patches.
But you use that feeling when you see patches.
That's the meat. We'll tweet that.
You're giving us content. Thank you.
You got it, guys.
Hey, look at that motherfucker.
This guy's great. Hey, I like him.
Is that I think his name might be Dapper the dog.
Yeah, I think that's right. Dapper the dog.
Sometimes you could find them because if you look on their Instagram,
they hashtag it with the name Dapper dog.
There's Molly Mouse.
Am I wrong about that?
I think I'm right. I think that's right.
Yeah, I recall none of these like mascots.
So I don't know if they like were a more recent addition to it
or I just wasn't paying attention.
It might be new.
I was trying to get little kids stuff, too.
Or something. Yeah. Yeah, that's kid stuff.
That's stupid.
Maybe they want to hang out with Simon the slug.
Maybe they didn't fit in the narrative.
You would have been constructed.
And then you just sort of ignored them because they weren't there.
You're like, that's not part of the world.
Anthropomorphic animals. Yeah, no, no, no.
Yeah, I'm like, look, we're on.
We have a structure here.
We're in Act two and you're not going to fuck this up.
We can't change the reality of the story now.
By bringing more of a two hander.
Yeah, we don't have time to visit Castaway Island.
We can't weave that into the narrative.
I love this guy. It's a cool parrot.
Yeah, they have a very like compact, but pretty,
pretty thorough water park that has a I think I saw it called a title title river.
It's like a combination wave pool, lazy river,
which I have never encountered that before.
So it's sending waves along while you're going.
Yeah. A little bit.
That's cool. A title river. Yeah.
We're into that.
Another neat thing is that
there were a bunch of it was all family that wanted to bring their hunting knives
into the park and the park didn't want them to have hunting knives.
So the security said they couldn't.
And then they got in a fight with the security and kicked the security
guard in the head.
And then I think they the whole family went to jail.
I want to hunt. We were hunting patches.
And rip his head open bag.
Terrace fluff out.
I have two quick things here from Instagram I'd like to bring up.
This is from a couple of years ago.
This is a performance by a band called Aero Myth.
The tribute band to Aero Smith, Aero Myth.
And you can see this man kind of looks like Steven Tyler.
If he does, and this kind of looks like guitarist to Brad Bradley Whitford,
not the actor.
Oh, there's you know, that did you know that my dad, you didn't know this.
I don't know what you're about to say.
My dad, when my dad was like 19 years old in in Massachusetts,
was in a band with Brad Whitford from.
Oh, wow.
My dad was the bass player in a band.
They were called Sounds of the Poets.
Oh, wow. That is huge.
There's a lot of Aerosmith discourse on this podcast, and that's.
We see Aerosmith comes up all the damn time.
I but this is this is a useful piece of Aerosmith info.
I love it. Well, so you can help form the sound in a way.
Yeah, yeah. Sort of in the early.
My dad says it. I don't know if this is true, but that he left my dad's band
to join Aerosmith. Wow.
That's crazy.
He's like, I'm playing with these other guys who are more talented
than you, Andy Blakelock.
Oh, man. Did he?
Did he ever stay in contact with him?
He I like coincidentally, this is the only thing that I went to.
There was a kid who was in my kindergarten class who was his nephew.
And I remember my dad asked his mom one time, who is his sister,
like, hey, ask your brother, Brad, if he remembers Andy Blakelock.
And the conclusion was like, he said he did.
OK, something that was the only
that was the only and then years later, my dad worked for a company
called California Closets that would organize that would like
design like organization for people's closets.
And I OK, I got very excited
because I worked for the container store and we had alpha shelving
and I planned closets for people.
And California closets was always the thing we'd say, well, that's too expensive.
They come to your house. You don't need to do that.
You come in store. Yeah.
Wow. That's interesting.
Yeah, I'm mad.
I'm mad at you now.
Don't talk about my dad like that.
But he worked for California Closets and he they were expensive closets.
And he would be going to like all these crazy, expensive houses.
And he did Joe Perry's closets. Wow. Really?
Yeah. Wow. Wow.
That's a lot of bookends.
Joe Perry and was like he was like, I went there for a consultation
and I was talking to like his assistant and it was like eight in the morning.
And like at a certain point, like Joe Perry in like a satin robe,
like stumbled out with like a cup of coffee and was like, are you doing my closets?
And then I was like, did you ask him,
did you tell him that used to be in a band with Brad Whitford?
And he was like, no, I was at work.
Very professional.
Yeah, it's closet time. I'm at work. Yeah.
Man, that's great.
And I have yet to have that so crazy.
California Closets, we would hear that all the time as our like
they were our enemy when I worked at the container store.
That that makes total sense because it's like truly it was just my dad would just
be like, you won't believe the fucking houses I'm going to to design closets.
It was like all for rich people. Yes.
So yeah, we were we were it was still very expensive to put in the alpha
shelving that I was designing for people, I think.
But it was not nearly as bad as the California closet price.
This is truly a sign of the way musicians like former working man
musicians like Joe Perry can lose their way and lose sight of what the
what the common man wants.
What's wrong with the closet you have, you fucking.
You made your first album in a closet.
You didn't need a reorganization. Good point.
Well, I lost the last touch.
Well, but Aero Myth keeps the spirit alive.
Here I am. Sorry. Sorry for the tangent.
No, I love the tan. That's crucial info.
Multiple great pieces there.
Oh, yeah. Really? Commenter on this is Abby Elliott.
Is that that Abby Elliott?
It's the impersonator from Target.
I don't think it is.
No, this is the.
We don't have to. We don't have to. I just was.
Let's look at all of our photos and describe them.
The real Abby Elliott was commenting on Aero Myth's Instagram.
That would have been a very small world. Yeah.
A little too small.
You're a myth. Too perfect.
So real quick, let me just I'm going to show you a picture of a recently
redesigned color scheme for the Tilt-A-Whirl at this park.
And you tell me what this looks like.
OK, real quick. Here we go.
Oh, boy. Oh, OK.
So it's a booth.
It's a little like shell.
And it's got stars that are reminiscent of the American flag.
But then also a big blue line.
OK, right.
Oh, man. Oh, no.
I'm not crazy, right?
No, no. I saw it right away.
OK, good. Is that what they're intending?
I don't know. Maybe.
But it's the line. It's just like the cushion that's cushioning you
from banging around in the Tilt-A-Whirl.
That was the color before.
But it's also a full blue.
I'm not seeing any red anywhere.
There's no red. And I don't know if that's an accident.
I think this is a blue lives matter.
Tilt-A-Whirl is what I'm saying.
And I've never seen that before.
So that's where you could at least at this at September 21st, 2020.
That's what the Kenobi Park had going.
Did they redesign it like early last summer?
Like when did we get the scheme?
I went through the comments to see if anyone like noticed it.
And I don't think they did.
Yeah, there's so much.
Somebody went, hey, did you change the colors on this one?
So somebody just maybe innocently and innocently enough was like, what?
What happened? This is different.
There is. I don't like them better.
I don't know what it is I like about this, but I like the new colors that you did.
I ride this Tilt-A-Whirl and yell and yell.
Yeah, this is. Yeah.
Get pumped up and see what else I can do with that energy.
Fox and Friends should broadcast from this Tilt-A-Whirl every morning.
Steve Doocy should ride the Tilt-A-Whirl.
That group now is always.
You have to save to melt the camera.
Why don't you just do what the officer says?
Aren't they to blame in a way to.
Just lock the.
Lock the camera.
If you do what the officer says, then nothing bad will happen to you.
I think they just don't know about it.
That's why there's been no broadcast from here.
I would like to if this podcast caused them to, like,
you know, put a purple cushion in there instead.
Yeah, I think that's yeah.
I think that's just a stock head cushion on a Tilt-A-Whirl.
Yeah, I don't know.
Jason's given them a little too much credit.
I don't well know because like
in the car in the original colony states, the red, white and blue is
especially in New England.
I feel like right.
Mookie, do you think that like they just slap red, white and blue
colonial shit on everything?
Where's the red, Jason?
Where's the red?
There's some red behind there on some other ride.
You mean like, does New England have just like a red, white
and blue aesthetic like naturally?
I just in terms of the design, like I feel like parts of.
Sure. Like, yeah, it's like every it's like every.
I feel like when you think of New England, maybe this isn't reality,
but it's like everything looks like it's like a Fourth of July parade
or something, you know what I mean?
Where there's like, yeah, little one of those little like half circle
like red, white and blue, like ruffle flags or whatever
that are like hanging off of shit.
I think maybe it's not that, but that's what you're led to believe.
Yeah, that feels right to me as somebody who's not been to the States
and just knows it from media, I guess.
Yeah, you know, like it chapter two. Right.
Yes. Yeah. So that feels right.
So, yeah, anyway, if you're a listener, go ahead.
No, no, no, you go.
I was just going to say, just if you're do it, do a report
if you're around there and just see what's going on.
Maybe the red and blue is maybe the red is on the side and we're not seeing it.
We're being we're being stupid.
Somebody's got to check this out for somebody.
Got one car.
Maybe all the different cars are different designs.
That one was that's that card.
That cart was donated by the Hampshire police to put the department
and one is like a snake and says, don't tread on me.
Yeah, yeah.
So where we go on, we go on.
One's just a Sean Hannity's face painted on the back of it.
Everyone's different.
They're all different cars.
The tilt. I don't think we said they do have a ride.
They have a shoot the shoot ride, which is shoot the shoot is all they got.
The longer log flumes that fit like eight or 10 in a row,
like the Jurassic Park ride.
OK, that attraction at Kenobi is called
a canopy, excuse me.
It's called the Boston Tea Party.
Yes, I vaguely remember that ride.
Yeah. Again, just profiting off any like colony shit like New England.
Revolutionary war.
I lost track of the number of times I went to battlefields or like old farms
or like this is how they ran a big crowd when they had to cut the crops, you know.
Yeah, I like New England is so like
you know, there's a lot of history or whatever.
So I think it's like there's a, you know, they were like,
you're right, it was like they were like among the first like 13 colonies.
So it's just like this is our shit, man.
This is like our identity.
Like we were the the pilgrims and, you know, the pilgrims
were on Plymouth Rock and the fucking.
Whatever the Boston Tea Party, like Paul Revere's Boston,
where it's just like this is our shit, our old tri-corner hat
shit. This is us.
We love it. The greatest hit.
They're like doing the greatest hits and like, yeah, that's if you come there,
that's what you want.
And it's like you want founding fathers.
You want some historical things.
And then you want the bad boys of Boston Aerosmith.
You want everything in the area that's famous.
Oh, check out the cranberry,
the ocean spray cranberry processing and visitor center.
Oh, they have an ocean spray sponsorship.
No, I well, no, I've just been to like the ocean spray factory
in Plymouth, Massachusetts or the ocean spray.
Like you can see a tour and see how bugs.
Yeah. Learn how bugs work.
Wow. You've been in a bog.
You'd be waist deep and berries.
No, we just saw like big pictures and recreations like, you know, I haven't.
I'd love to go in a bog and just, you know, get in there and mess around.
But I've seen Plymouth Rock.
I see that around in there, man.
Just fuck around. Find out P in the bog.
Yeah, I really want to be in a bunch of rune, a batch of cranberries.
I Mike, with the the Aerosmith thing, they seem to have a lot of tribute bands.
Yeah, there's I think it's weird that they I'm surprised.
I don't think I knew there was there were tributes of this or how you would do it.
But there is a Bruno Mars tribute, which is kind of funny.
And you can watch that on a YouTube link where the person sat through
the entire 25 minute show and yet still labeled it tribute to Bruno Moss.
Spelled not not Moss like I may guess, but like tree moss.
Right. Right. Oh, man.
I liked it. Nice, nice fella. Nice performer.
Bruno Moss.
And then you think maybe it was a spelling error or something,
but then they made another video.
They seem to go again, post another video and say Moss again.
Is that the name of the like a real myth is the name of the.
Oh, it could be Bruno Moss. Is that the no?
I think. Yeah. Yeah.
Aaron asked that question.
And I think it the video is called Tribute to Bruno Moss.
So unless it itself is a tribute to another Bruno Mars impersonator
named Bruno Moss and then were two steps impersonator removed.
Could be a labeling issue.
It could be. Yes, you're correct.
They're tribute. The likelier answer.
The most likely answer I'd say is that the person that posted it
is a common moron.
You fool.
You're run of the mill American moronic idiot.
You posted an error on the Internet and you should be shamed for this.
What else do we have about Canada?
Because there's other places to hit and there is a ride coming up
that I am thrilled to talk about. But are we missing anything on Canobie?
Let me let me do a real quick one.
And then the ride's big.
If I found this to Jason, you'll be excited about this.
And at least in 2014, there was something you get a coupon.
It's a dollar hot dog day.
And you could. Yeah, it was like there's two coupons.
There's a coupon for like saving money on the actual admission.
And then on the bottom there, you would present the coupon
and get your dollar hot dog.
And you would. I mean, is there a better deal?
From the from the food supply people at Sodexo.
The giant food company.
Wait, is Sodexo bad? Why is Sodexo bad?
I don't think anyone said it was bad.
I mean, it's just kind of like a big monopolistic like food supply company.
Like, I don't think you have a lot of choices if you need a certain quantity
of food, like if you're running a restaurant or like a college
dining hall or something.
So, Jason, you knew what Sodexo was before this,
because I actually was not familiar with that name.
So Sodexo Marriott was the people who supplied
like the dining halls I worked in in college.
Oh, interesting.
So you were like you were familiar. You worked with Sodexo.
I think they paid me.
I think that's who like.
Wow, you're a Sodexo former employee.
Sodexo's blood money. You're rich.
Are they paying you now?
Yeah, they paid you now.
Wow. Sodexo.
Oh, no wonder we had to spend the fucking time talking about Sodexo.
Oh, man, he always has to slip it in now.
What if Mike's in on it?
He brought up that Instagram.
So that Sodexo would get said.
Yeah. You guys want to go out to dinner tonight?
I was maybe thinking we could go someplace where they're supplied
by the Sodexo brand of food supply.
Yeah. So hot dog links specifically.
They just because it's a little more snap to them.
Mm hmm.
Jason and I have both gotten a fat check from Sodexo.
That is right.
Well, do you know one episode every four years?
And that's all we have to do.
So we're good.
We're good for a while.
They won't come shaking us down again.
Do we want to move along?
Do we want to talk about Santa's Village a little bit?
Because boy, oh, boy, I wonder if Mike and Jason,
do we all find the same thing, the ride?
Oh, I think so. Yeah.
But yeah, I know which ride you're talking about.
It probably wasn't there. I think it's a newer thing.
What do you recall about the Santa's Village of your childhood?
I mean, Jefferson, New Hampshire.
Yeah. So Santa's Village is probably the one that I like,
have the least memories of, because it was like a boring ass.
Like you walk around and it looks like Christmas.
And there's like I truly I truly could not tell you one thing
that I did there other than like you walk around and there's maybe
like a little train ride or something.
But like I do. I barely remember Santa's Village truly.
And I'm sorry. I think it's OK.
I know. But you see you brought in a prompt for us is what you did.
Good. And you caused us to have to look up because there's Santa's
Villages around and you sort of know what to expect.
There will be an opportunity. Are they all affiliated?
That's what I've always wondered, because I remember.
So else I remember somebody else.
It's just it's just like a it's just a common concept
because I remember hearing other people go,
we have a Santa's Village near us.
And I was like, you have Santa's Village.
I have Santa's Village, but I didn't I I've never known if they were there.
They're all just separate intellectual properties.
Santa Claus and fairy tale storybook stuff are in the public domain.
So someone starting an abusive park, it's an easy place to start.
Right. And you're probably yeah, you're probably getting like even like,
if you say somebody moves from some other place,
then they like think it's all sort of the same thing, too.
So you're getting probably like, oh, I love Santa's Village as a child.
Let's go to this Santa's Village.
So smart, smart move.
And you're like, this shit isn't anything like mine.
Mm hmm. The different Santa. No brand unity here. Right.
But I say thank God that this isn't like the other ones, because there's like
there's some real odd stuff.
There's odd IP all over the place.
I just want to share the screen really quick so that I could show you
that the area called Pugi's splash pad.
There's a fancy penguin with a top hat and a little
a little tie in one picture, but the knot in the other two.
They're inconsistent just with Pugi's style.
But what a name, though. Love Pugi. Yeah, we like.
Love Pugi the penguin. Yes.
It's it's like it's a character making fun of you, Mookie.
It's like they're like it's a parody of you.
Pugi. So Pugi splash pad is there.
But the main thing to talk about is a I'm just so like
because there's limited IP with Christmas.
Like, what do you do really?
Besides, like, here's the the bake shop where Mrs.
Claus makes her cookies or something.
But this place really figured out something with a ride called
the Great Humbug Adventure.
Yeah, all did you guys? Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Love this. Love it. Yes.
I wonder if do I try to explain the ride
or just allow the man himself to do it?
I think maybe this is the move because I don't know if you guys saw
the same video that I did.
There's ride throughs, but then there's one.
There's this one that's like very artistically cut.
Let me pull this guy up.
I mean, this this explains it so succinctly.
And this is true insanity. Here we go.
I am Ebenezer Scrooge, and this is my home.
And these humbugs are making me miserable.
So it's always stuff right there.
These are bugs are making me like, I don't know why the emphasis is there.
Maybe somebody was arguing that the humbugs aren't making it miserable.
And you have to correct them.
But so this is a rough Ebenezer Scrooge famously says, Bah, humbug.
And I guess this is a ride that imagines that humbug.
That's not just something he's saying.
Ebenezer Scrooge is a grouch because is how this is infested with humbugs.
Oh, my God. It's a reimagining of it's a reimagining of the story.
Yes, which I really like. Yeah. Yeah.
And you know why he doesn't like Christmas.
This is like this is like if you did the or if you did like the solo
like origin story of of Ebenezer Scrooge.
And it's like, why does he say, you know what I mean?
Where it's like, you know how in solo when it's like
that fucking stupid thing where it's where he's like Chewbacca, that's too long.
I'm going to have to call you something shorter like Chewie.
This is like humbugs everywhere.
And you're like, oh, that's why he says humbug now.
And that's that would be everything in your life.
There was a one moment that caused it for sure.
When Paul McCartney walked by that guitar shop and looked in the window and nodded.
And the legend was born.
I don't really remember where this video goes.
If there's nothing interesting, I'm just going to let it play kind of
silently while we talk, because
look, there's one now.
Oh, wait a minute here.
If I go back frame by frame, you can read the sign, which explains further the
I mean, first it says Santa says no food or drinks on this ride.
And himself lays down the rules here.
But then the great humbug adventure.
Tickle the humbugs with your special laser and make them finally giggle.
Why finally?
All right. A lot of questions here.
Finally, I don't know why.
I guess this has been a decade long.
And finally, that's very hard to see.
Mm hmm. I think so.
And it's parenthetical, like fine.
Make them finally giggle.
Really weird.
And then just the phrase tickle your humbugs, tickle the humbugs with your special
laser tickle the kind of with your special laser.
Yeah, just everyone's sitting there for a moment.
Just think about it.
Say it out loud.
So special to go there and with your special narrate in that
tickle. It's a good ASMR.
I said this before. Turn off the podcast while you're listening now and turn to
the nearest person, find them and just run in and say that sentence to them
and then run out.
Tickle the humbugs with your special laser.
Exactly. And see what they say.
We melodic the more you say it.
Tickle the humbugs with your special laser with your special laser.
It seems like a procedure to like that's like a lot of euphemisms for like
getting rid of genital warts or something.
You don't want to tell your child that's what the operation dad is going to have.
Honey, your father is going to have his humbugs removed.
And the doctor's going to tickle them with his special laser.
The doctor is also a master tickler.
Um, this is yeah, this this was made by the Sally Dark Rides Company who made
Mookie there was once a ride based on the moody blues song Nights in White
Satin at a heart, a short lived hard rock park in by Myrtle Beach.
And this Sally Dark Rides Company has made a number of dark rides
all over the country, all over the world.
They did the Justice League rides at Six Flags.
And then they also made the humbug.
I think they've made a lot of weirdo rides.
There's some Looney Tunes ride they did.
I looked up there is a ride.
Have you ever heard of this, Jason?
In Pennsylvania, they did a ride with animatronics that is Mr.
Rogers' neighborhood where you ride the trolley to bring trolleys back there.
I had no idea there was a Mr. Rogers ride.
I've heard a little about that.
Yeah, they changed it into Daniel Tiger.
Is that right? Am I thinking of the same ride?
Oh, did I? I don't know. I thought maybe it just disappeared.
Yeah, there was a Mr.
Rogers ride and they changed it to the just Daniel Tiger specific. OK.
Anyway, this place makes some like bonkers rides.
We might want to do an episode where we just pick off their website,
whether or not they are still around or not.
Like if it is a like weird, wonky,
kind of scary, kooky animatronic filled ride,
I think we might just want to like throw darts at Sally rides and then do it.
That's the point.
But they definitely are because I went to their digital booth
at the IAPA convention last year, which was all digital.
Digital. You went to a digital booth.
That's right. Yeah.
I looked at their prospectuses and such because they sell a lot of rides
that are like pre-made, right, right.
That you could just insert into your park.
Mm hmm. I think I think I got like a cold sweat being like that.
We have a guest here and that and that like a virtual prospectus
for a ride company was talked about.
Yeah, that's all right. We're cool, dude.
I swear we're like pretty cool.
We're not even that nerdy about it.
Let's go back to normal stuff like the narratives we would tell ourselves
as children to distract ourselves from our mundane suburban upbringings.
Anyway, I don't know.
Here's a really this is a like like a scary wax figure come to life.
He's pointing a gun.
This whole video is like I don't know who made this or why,
but like it's kind of like it's not just like the ride going through it.
It's full of really intense angles and cinematic close ups.
It's sort of a fever dream.
And then the the hump like the humbugs are sort of eerie.
In other world, they have like flower ears.
They're like they're soos like.
Yeah. And they're yeah, they're like kind of cute, but they're little gross.
Not Scrooge's house also.
That's just a whole other premise.
So is arriving at where Ebenezer Scrooge lives.
So good, honestly. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I'm fun. Pretty obsessed.
Dying to go here and tickle some.
Why is it tickle though?
Oh, wow. Look at the bugs. They're so cute.
The humbugs. Yeah.
There's like five humbugs.
One of the great trips.
They have a cute humbugs tickled them.
But they're like aliens. Oh, Jesus Christ.
Yeah, there's a lot going on.
I know you wouldn't even like maybe flag these as bugs necessarily.
Like they're a little more.
Well, they have like bumblebee torsos, but this is very like Salem Witch Museum.
OK. Wait, is that a place?
Is that is that a New Hampshire Salem or is that Salem, Massachusetts?
So that's where the witch trials took place.
And they have the they have the witch museum there and you go in.
But they have these like very old, like very creepy animatronics.
Oh, where they like tell the story of like
whatever, like the crucible or whatever.
Right. It's like very it's like very unnerving.
That's that is even on a radar.
We got to do that. Yeah.
If there's weird red robots, that's a pretty cool one.
It's like very old.
And I think they haven't changed it in like years and years.
But it's like you go and you sit in this like little room and there's like little
they like light up little animatronic like things and they tell you the story
of the Salem witch trials and stuff like that.
Oh, man. Yeah, so great.
Hasn't been touched in years.
That is the here's not by our favorite song here.
Also, those humbugs had like little like side mouths like they were like,
like they were slack jawed or something like that.
It's it's.
Yeah, they're all snarky comics.
Yeah, yeah.
They're like they're yeah, they're all little Bill Maher's
YouTube thumbnail face.
Yeah, they are.
They see culture is out of country.
It's run amok.
And we know I know running amok.
I'm a humbug.
So all right, that's what I wanted to say about Santa's village primarily.
Should we move on to the the oddest thing on your list?
Really? Like I think when I gave it the cursory Google, what are I'm sorry?
What? Like I had to double check.
We were talking about the right thing.
Clark's trading post.
Clark's trading post. Yes.
What do you want to describe it as a person who went?
Yeah, well, so I mean, it's like there's there's two major things about this
place that I have memories of, two major attractions.
But it's a it's like a sort of larger like compound trading post
where it's like it's like, you know, like cool general store vibes.
But they have like old trucks that you can look at and like old
an old looking like, you know, like an old 50s gas station facade.
But there's two major attractions there, which is.
Which is Clark's trained bears.
So they would put on a show with bears.
I think they still do, which is sad.
But that was like for many years.
And when it was over 49, it's decades and decades of bear shows
where they do bear live bear shows, where it's like bears are balancing on balls
and like, you know, shooting a basketball into a hoop
and jumping through little hoops and stuff.
So there was that.
And then there's the tram ride with the.
Oh, fuck, what's he called?
Like the old man. There's there's a.
I know about this.
I was delighted.
You would ride through.
It's almost like kind of like the haunted hayride.
But you were in this old like,
you know, like like like hollowed out or like, you know, the sides taken off bus
and you ride through this thing and an old man, an old like steampunk
man, like chases you through
through the woods.
His name is Wolfman Wolfman.
Wolfman, you get him to.
Did you read about this?
The way that you get him to leave you alone.
Did you read this, Scott? I did.
But you I feel like you should say it.
I love everybody on everybody on the bus.
Men, women and children included.
You all yell, Scram, you old goat.
This rules love.
You old goat.
And that's how the Wolfman would leave you alone.
But it was like a guy who had like big, like a big red beard
and big crazy hair, like an eye patch and like a club.
And he had like a steampunk ATV and he would chase after you and be like,
oh, and they're like, it's the Wolfman.
And you had to drive away from the Wolfman and we would all go,
Scram, you old goat.
And then the Wolfman would be scared because you yelled, Scram, you old goat.
And that was the tram ride of.
As a child was genuinely afraid of the Wolfman.
He looks scary to me.
Yeah, of course. Yeah.
That's like advertise that.
They advertise like the guy and that catchphrase right on the front of the website.
That's like the first thing you see when you go to the website.
And he's like written about in the newspaper a lot.
Like if there's change over with the Wolfman when the oldest Wolfman retired.
And he's like, I don't know.
I don't know.
I think it's like the same thing with the Wolfman when the oldest Wolfman retired
and then he's picking his successor.
This seems like major local flavor.
I don't know for how far emanating from Lincoln, New Hampshire,
but at least there's some places in New Hampshire where Wolfman and Scram,
you old goat loom really large.
Yeah, I mean, in retrospect, it must be like those just it must be like a local
actor or something being like, I got the Wolfman.
Well, I found I found the story of it.
I think essentially, but there was a so, yeah, as you said, this was, you know,
the main thing was was bear shows and they'd make the bears play bear
skit ball and and also do like this seemed to like involve bears
in a wedding proposal once, like a bear pulled out a wedding ring,
all kinds of weird humiliating bear things.
And that was like the main attraction.
But then like the only people who knew how to do the bear show
had to go out of town so they couldn't do the bear show.
And it's like, well, we do have the train still or the little or whatever.
You were saying the car with one side missing.
But is that enough?
And then there was like a maintenance guy who just who looked like Wolfman,
who just just was very scraggly.
And he was just kind of thinking and was like, I'm going to take a risk.
But if this risk pays off, it might change everything around here.
And he went and found some weird firsts.
And when the train started going around, he went up and started screaming at it.
And made up the whole wolf.
I'm a man raised by wolves.
He just did it without checking with the owners or anything.
And then it became like, well, if we don't have the bears,
we always have Wolfman like it was a crucial second attraction.
It really like it just like, I think, amplified the place and fleshed it out.
And it was all this one guy.
Wow. And Allegia was born.
And a guy who, I mean, big risk like I'm shocked that nobody was like,
what the fuck are you doing?
Yeah, I want a little tram ride and you're running up going like,
I'm the wolf man. Get out of my woods.
I do like I feel like most people, they'd be like, you can't do that, dude.
Yeah, it's like Disneyland.
You can't just say I'm like, I'm trying this.
I'm going to start screaming, scared, spitting on the tram tour.
Like you can't do that at the container store.
I like put like I glued some of the shelving to my legs.
I was like, I'm shelf boy.
Yeah. Get out of here.
I'm trying to scare you.
Scram, you old shelf.
One enterprising manager was like, I think we got something with shelf boy.
Shelf boy. That took balls, Carlson.
I took a risk.
Container store could be more than a store.
It could be a brand.
I have a little video of the wolf man because it gives you a flavor of the.
Yeah.
This this is this is truly
you guys post pictures of this afterwards on Twitter so people can see them.
Yeah. Yeah. Well, assuming we remember.
Yes. That's right.
I'll send you. I'll get it.
I'll get a few and send them to.
Oh, if you got old pig.
Yes, please. Oh, no.
You know, I wonder if I do.
I should ask my parents if they have because my mom just went through
a bunch of old photos.
I was like, if you have any, please send me some.
I'm going to ask her.
I'm going to text her as soon as we're done.
Oh, right now.
And then she might listen to it and be like, you didn't like the vacations.
I thought you had fun at the arcade.
Oh, my God.
Wow. You've got some of that negative wolf man spirit.
Here's here's the wolf man.
You know, I don't like, oh, dad, you're flat,
my land and my bopping yellow belly, long nose geysers.
What are you doing on my turf?
No, I do. Do you?
I'll take it and I'll take your hands and I'll stick it right down those jaws.
And then so he's a guy in like furs and an eye patch.
We hadn't said that he's missing a lot of teeth.
He's super scraggly.
And then he says, I'm going to throw your down our jaws right there.
And fucking great.
Like this is my car.
Like great Boston accent, just like this, my car over here.
My car has jaws.
Is there a car?
My car's got a car.
This is my car.
You're kidding. You're going in the jaws.
That's it. You're going in the jaws on my car.
So he kind of like he seems to hit a button and then like some big
like bear trap looking thing is going on and off in front of his car.
And it is like little picket fence pieces that are jaw like is
his weird little bad Maxi car has a mouth in it
and he's going to feed your kid into the jaws.
Man, that would have scared the shit out of me.
This guy will.
It's scary, man.
And he like fucking and he's got and his car is like, it's like one of those
like old like it's like a it's like a lawnmower engine or something.
So it's like the whole time.
Like when he's chasing you, it's like loud and he's like screaming at you
and waving his club.
The lo fi.
Yeah, it makes it worse.
The lo fi nature of it.
Well, and it's also not like, you know, you you can kind of smell
in a universal setting that like, well, there's an actor air to the Norman Bates.
And it doesn't it's not a real knife.
But when this like rusted out car pulls up with it like this,
what if this is just a guy who lives in the hills?
It's in the hills.
Like conceivably, he just lives there and he is mad.
Yeah, he's just like he's very believable.
Yeah, you would not be able to tell.
I mean, if I was a kid, I would just be like, what is this accent?
This must be a hill person accent.
He he keeps going and says this is my favorite thing in the clip here.
And if you ever come when they double cross me,
you become vomit stew, especially kids,
boiled kids with cabbage and rottel.
That's my favorite.
The.
I mean, that that little thing is like what Charles Manson would say,
like when he went on Charlie Rose and then like a gibbity gibbity gibbity.
Like that, that is true serial killer stuff.
Yeah, this guy, I, I, I admire the commitment
and I admire the history of the character.
But yeah, I, oh, scary.
Varmint stew.
He's going to with kids, boiled kids with.
Yeah, it's become varmint stew.
It's like it's varmint stew, but it's the special extra ingredient is kids.
His child's flesh. Yeah.
Yeah, no kids. He poils them.
I want to have like a like a listing for playing him on the website.
Like, could I apply to be the wolf man or would I just like they would look at me
and they go, you don't look like the wolf man.
What are you doing?
There's a lot of people vying for that spot, man.
Yeah, that's yeah, that's you're right.
There's probably like they hold like open call nationwide auditions.
That's like that's like that's like like landing, like like hosting the tonight show.
It's it only happens to very few people in the world.
Lauren Michaels has a lot of drama every time there's a change.
Yeah, there's so much the guy says he's going to give it up and then doesn't.
Yeah. And Lauren has a lot to do with it, too.
Guys, mom says I'll look sweet.
All right. A lead. Nice.
Within the episode, we didn't even have to wait for it.
That was a question I had is if like, is there some would a couple
if a couple of different things happened in your life, Mookie,
is there a chance that you're that you are the wolf man?
You know, you know, look,
it's tough. Los Angeles is tough.
You know, am I going to be here forever pursuing this dream of mine?
I don't know. Maybe I retire as an older gentleman in another,
I don't know, 10, 15, 20 years back to New England.
And go, well, I have this skill, this we talked about it earlier,
this skill where I could become anybody.
You know, we do know we know that you have this.
We know that you can inhabit different personas.
And you know, it is entirely new people showed up.
Yes. The answer is I wouldn't rule it out.
Yeah. It's straight.
You do the work now.
You're not gray now, but maybe someday.
And you start growing the hair. Is he not gray?
Oh, you know, wait a minute. What am I talking about?
Yeah, you don't have to be. Wolfman's not old. He's a ginger.
You're right. You're right. But you so if you do.
But if you start putting in the hair work now, if you don't cut it,
start growing. Yeah.
Yeah. If I don't shave for the next 15 years, then.
And then all of your credits and work up to this point
just become like, hmm, I guess. All right.
Well, I guess he seems like he knows that he's acted before.
But does that is that a good thing or a bad thing?
Is he going to intellectualize Wolfman? He was the last Wolfman.
Yeah. And if you're if you're like in the next like 15 years, somebody goes,
oh, you're growing it out for a role.
And you go, yes, a long term role.
The role of a lifetime, the role of a lifetime that I'll get in 15 years.
That's really my future.
I would be curious if any of the Wolfman ever were like,
I was in a local commercial or something or like not local,
even like a regional commercial that was like it was just like I went.
I go to commercial auditions to like.
Yeah, I probably my days off like the guy who played Bozo.
When I was a kid, I played Bozo like I found his website and I found his reel.
And I'm like, he's trying to get like a commercial job now. Whoa.
Bozo is trying to do the same jobs I am.
We're going out for the same roles.
He doesn't. He does.
But just like so they'll pop up and things, but just not with a lot of range.
So it's just like, if you don't buy recliner from us,
for then I'll turn your kids into vomit stew.
You kids at home, you tell mom and dad.
Yeah, you don't buy recliner.
You're going to end up in a stew pot.
He's like threatening flow, threatening flow in the progressive people
with stew, child stew.
Yeah, I'm like, like his wolf man, like his wolf man.
I mean, it like, you know, like has wolf man ever been
like, you know, seen or portrayed in any kind of like pop culture?
Anything?
Had us a reference.
Yeah. Has anyone like done any depiction of their childhood
where there would have to be a wolf man equivalent?
Or even just a mention of it or just like, you know, like, you know, whatever.
In a Stephen King thing where it's like
we went down to Clark's Trading Post where the wolf man was hanging out.
I mean, that's Stephen King would write it a lot better than I just did. But
this is like the one that I would have guessed Stephen King would have been
influenced by. Right.
No, it's the charming little carnival atmosphere of canopy.
Well, if if there was like a
like imagine a horror situation at this place with not only wolf man
and the jaw car, but also a bunch of bears who are probably mad
that they've had to bounce around on balls and play bear skip ball for so long.
I mean, this this place at night is I don't know if you're stuck there
or like in an apocalypse or something.
This is an awful place to be.
Oof. Yeah. There's a lot of darkness here for sure.
Yeah. Yeah. Well, it's you know, it's like local level, you know,
attraction where it's just like, yep, this is the best we can do in this area
that just is mostly like dirt and trees.
Do we have trees?
We could build a train that takes you through the trees, and that's not nothing.
I have a more like wholesome local attraction story, too.
Yes. Yes. If you want something a little lighter,
if you want something a little more scarifying.
Let's go out on some lightness. Yes. Sure.
So this is at Storyland, which is another park we mentioned earlier.
I say it's run by the company that runs Kennywood Park.
And I found a video online.
And from 1983 to 1998, they had a dark ride called Voyage to the Moon.
And it really seems like a
sort of homemade sort of dark ride
that has a certain type of magic to it.
And you can find this video on YouTube.
Someone made like a a video essay about it.
Voyage to the Moon, complete ultimate tribute.
This is in the style of Mookie.
There's a guy named Martin's Vids who makes
video essays about how certain rides were made.
And someone made it for this little Voyage to the Moon ride.
And every I'm encouraging everyone to go and watch this video
because it takes some twists and turns.
The guy gets some stuff from the park as like gifts.
And but a brief description of some of the ride.
So it's sort of like that old, old silent movie,
the Voyage to the Moon, where you're like
or a trip to the moon, where where a bullet is shot at the moon.
In this case, your car overshoots the moon and enters into a black hole.
And it's it says, after emerging on the other side of the black hole,
guests would then encounter a wizard who would appear out of the darkness.
The wizard in the black hole.
In the black hole, there's there's a lot more.
The wizard would then explain to guests that he was able to make dreams come true
and suggested that they come along with him to see what was possible.
Oh, boy. Are you still with me?
OK, then the golden bullet would enter another scene
occupied by strange creatures called Worrywartles.
When you're in the golden bullet, you're not like you're in the wizard
and fire a gun.
No, no. Worrywart, but you do meet Worrywartles.
Guests would then encounter another strange creature named Chugga Chugga Puff Puff.
So I don't know.
I think that sounds awesome.
Delighted by all this.
I was delighted by all this, and especially once you see there is footage
in this essay, this video essay of the ride.
And then unfortunately, it does end with the note that the ride closed
the walls underneath the dome were removed and Professor
Bigelstepp's loopy lab opened for the 1999 season.
Professor Bigelstepp's loopy lab, of course, evicting
the voyage to the moon ride.
Was the character Chugga Chugga Puff Puff?
Is that what you said? Chugga Chugga Puff Puff.
Puff Puff. OK, so it's a weed like character.
It's a weed based.
Yeah, man. Kind of.
They are drinking and chugging like.
Yeah, it's a real partier.
So, yeah, I like the sound of all these characters for sure,
including that professor that replaced the whole thing.
Yeah. But what I really want to see is the Wolfman just going wild
with that jaw car and laying waste to the whole thing.
And all the.
Well, that's what he tries to do every time.
And then, you know,
he's brave kids stop it every time.
Yeah, he's afraid.
He's really. Trust me, he is trying.
He is trying to destroy that place.
Yes, then get out of there and destroy every he wants to destroy story land.
I know. Or canopy.
This guy would lay waste to all of New Hampshire if he got out.
If he ever got out, please, people, this if this message can reach far and wide.
You need to scream, scram, you old goat.
There's only one thing that stops him.
And if this podcast, if something happens in this podcast is the only clue.
If there's a Jurassic Park level disaster at Clark's Trading Post,
where the Wolfman gets out somehow.
But what if the Wolfman is a misunderstood protector?
What if if the Wolfman goes away?
What if New Hampshire is just overrun by worry wardles and humbugs?
You know, maybe.
And absolutely. Keeping it in stasis.
Yeah, it's the only thing keeping it in stasis.
You know. Yeah, well, we won't know.
We won't know until it happens.
I hope to God that that does not happen.
Yeah, let's all pray real quick.
Yeah, let's all pray.
The people of New Hampshire. Yeah.
Yeah. For the sake of New Hampshire, there's a there's a worry wardles
and humbugs are not escaped.
And we don't have to turn to Wolfman and form an unholy alliance. Amen.
Yeah. Amen. Well, Wolfman.
Santa.
Oh, that was the other the Santa's village.
The other thing I had
just right at the end, Mick Foley,
a wrestling icon, AKA, Cat, Jack, AKA, Dude Love, AKA Mankind,
said of Santa's Village, every good thing in my life somehow leads me back
to Jefferson, New Hampshire and the trip to Santa's Village.
My parents took me on when I was only three years old.
Wow. He's a Mick Foley is a big he is such a Santa.
He's like a Santa head.
He has a Christmas room and he like dresses as Santa.
He's very he looks he looks like Santa.
He's like jolly. He's very seemingly nice guy.
What a sweetheart.
And yeah, he loves Santa's Village.
And I think I've said this on the show.
He's a big theme park guy because when he jumped off the top rope
to the outside to try to land on the rock on an announce table and missed
and cracked his rib right on the side of a table in Anaheim, he thought,
oh, man, am I going to be able to make it to Disney tomorrow?
It's the first thought he had during the match.
Geez. Yeah.
Well, so well, that's beautiful.
Everything good in his life came from and I think a lot of good came
from talking about all these places, a lot of great IP,
a lot of great breakthroughs about your life and family stuff.
Yeah, I hope it was helpful to you, Mookie.
You survived podcast, the ride.
We all went through some stuff and we survived podcast, the ride.
Mookie, thank you so much for being here.
Thanks for having me, guys.
Of course, for sure.
That is so much there is like that is an odd amount of bizarre IP
in one neck of the wood.
I did not think that's where we're heading.
I love the wolf man. I love all the humbugs.
Thanks for bringing it to us.
But now before all us old goats scram,
let's exit through the gift shop.
Mookie, is there anything you'd like to plug?
Sure. You can check out my podcast.
You are worthy with Lamouki B.
And.
Follow me on social media, on TikTok, Twitter and Instagram at Lamouki B.
L.A. L.A. OK, I.E.B.
And other than that, no irons and no fires, man.
But you have an iron in the fire of of inspiring people
and of making people of of getting people in touch
with their best selves and getting people away from chasing clout.
And if you I don't know if anyone's ever
plugged a TikTok account really on the show.
And if you do one thing, I think follow the TikTok.
And if you want to be inspired on a regular basis, then follow them.
Yes. With the disclaimer of it's it is parody.
What? Oh, man.
Yeah, I thought it was real.
I had a lot of breakthroughs.
I don't want anybody.
I don't want any any cool people coming there thinking that I'm.
Some kind of fucking.
Have you not there?
Didn't I heard taking those people down?
You know what I mean? Take it down a peg.
Did you not have one that like blew up significantly within TikTok?
Like there was some statement about dating.
Yeah, I got a and it was.
It got about like like something like 13000
likes and a bunch of comments and of a bunch of people who thought
that I was being a like, sincere like.
I mean, basically for for anybody who doesn't know this,
it's basically like a parody of like the type of guy who goes on TikTok
and is performatively, you know, like feminist to in order to get laid.
Sure, sure.
And so it was a video sort of like that,
but it was a bunch of people thinking that I was being sincere.
And I gained 12000 new followers in a week
of all people who think that that is the kind of person that I actually am.
And so, you know, I mean, I guess that's a success.
Yeah, audience, you've always been trying to cultivate.
Yeah, sure.
And then and then they look at and then they look at some of the other ones
and they're like, is this what I was?
Is this what I followed?
And like, yeah, it is.
I'm just being made for the numbers, man.
I just want to get my numbers up.
You're all just little stats to me.
You played right into my trap, fell right into my car jaws.
All you fucking verified.
I don't even look at the names.
Just put them on the pile.
Yeah. All right.
Well, yeah, check out Mookie on TikTok and the podcast.
It's so funny.
And as for us, you can find us on all the socials at podcast.
The ride is merch available in our T public store.
And for three bonus episodes every month, check out podcast,
the ride, the second gate at Patreon dot com slash podcast, the ride.
Yeah. And I think there's only one.
I think you have to end it with a little scrammy old goat.
Yeah. You'll go all you old goats listening to this
scram right now, scram right now before you become vermin stew.
I'm a stews.
And they're right.
So Jason had some vermin.
Jason said varmint stew back when he was a little boy.
Yeah, I'm sure.
Probably.
Pennsylvania thing.
Yeah. Oh, you didn't know you never had it.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson,
Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts dot com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify
or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter
and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.