Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, The Second Gate,
where we hope that it's just the three of us here
and that no one is secretly listening in from a closet.
I'm Scott Gardner, joined by Jason Sheridan.
Hi.
I have some thoughts on the closet.
I mean, it's probably the biggest thing to have thoughts about.
That is the iconic, that's the one perfect shot of the film,
of the story in reality.
It's the one perfect shot of his life, I think.
I had a lot of misconceptions about the closet.
I thought it was, I've always pictured a lot dirtier,
and I didn't realize he already was doing the show at that point.
You also never, oh yeah, yeah, that is important.
The timeline is, it is an odd juncture in the timeline.
It's an odd moment, yeah.
Yeah, well there's a lot to go, but it's also all fictionalized,
so who knows?
We will unpack everything about the closet.
This might have to turn into a saga with an entire sector
devoted to the closet.
Mike Carlson, what do you think?
I'm here, yeah.
The person at the closet is probably, you know,
when we were all negotiating our deals for the podcast initially,
it was very tumultuous, and there were, you know,
there were a lot of other people that wanted this gig,
this Podcast The Ride gig.
Yeah.
So it could be anyone.
It could be Mitch, it could be Anthony Gio,
all the people that were in contention for hosting.
That's weird.
I mean, I don't know if we should be talking about this,
but like you wonder why Nick Mundy has the contentious relationship
with the show that he does, and let's just say offers were made,
and offers were rescinded, and deals were pulled, and...
Yeah, that's show business.
Podcast CEOs, you can't trust them.
They go back on their word.
Yeah, let's be honest.
Nick Mundy's manager was too aggressive, you know?
She just like kept calling everybody involved like chicken shit
and tiny balls and...
Yeah, too much.
Yeah, and he's nice.
So, and I guess, see, that's why he needed somebody to be the bulldog.
He got it, but the bulldog bit too hard,
and thus he's not able to, you know, be here.
I mean, would it be the same podcast? I don't know.
Or would it just largely be about Boston?
Boston.
Yeah.
There would be a lot of Boston.
Instead of the bad boys of Boston,
it would just be Boston on the show if Mundy was around.
As a weekly presence.
Yeah.
Instead of constant references to tennis,
it would be constant references to, what do you play? Rugby.
Rugby, yeah.
So much rugby talk.
Yeah, and it wouldn't be Mike Love, it would be Peter Chris.
You know, it would be a totally different show.
Different rock monster.
Yeah.
I forget if he's a monster. I assume.
I don't know if Peter Chris is.
Gene Simmons we know is a monster, of course.
Yeah, Gene and Paul, but yeah, I don't know.
I don't know actually much about Peter Chris.
That's the kind of thing the audience would know.
Yeah.
Mundy or every year.
But yeah, look, there's drama in the formation of shows.
And when we took over podcast The Ride from the previous three hosts.
Exactly, yeah.
It was, was it, it wasn't, we wanted it to be a smoother transition,
but it wasn't, it was a little rocky.
We should promise right now that when we hand it over to those other three guys
in five years, there's not going to be any of this nonsense.
It's going to be so smooth.
Because after last time, we don't want it to be over.
We don't want it.
I just want to say those three guys, they're good family guys.
Good guys, family guys.
Great guys and they've, nobody's worked harder than they have following us
on the podcast that follows ours.
Yeah, we're not going to turn around and do exactly what was done to us.
Yeah.
Like less than 25 years later.
Precisely, exactly the same thing with no lessons learned.
No, that's not us.
Uncontributely close, yeah.
This bit is really funny if you know what we're talking about.
Yeah.
I just want to say it.
And if you don't, yeah, today it's happening, the long threatened episode,
all about the HBO film The Late Shift.
This year celebrating its 25th anniversary, Happy 25 Late Shift.
Now, this is no fictional thing.
Sometimes truth is stranger than fiction.
This is a film that is based on the battle for The Tonight Show in the early 90s
when Johnny Carson retired and NBC had a difficult time deciding
whether to hand it over to Jay Leno or to David Letterman.
Yeah.
And this was all portrayed in this HBO film.
There was a book written about it by Bill Carter,
the same writer Bill Carter wrote a film of it which was made for HBO several years later.
Yeah.
And it's, yes, it's come up on the show a lot, I think.
A lot of times.
I think a lot.
So it's like, yeah, long threatened to do this.
You might say, again, there's people who will be like, this is some theme park stuff.
But I don't want to spoil it if you haven't seen the movie,
but Bob Iger is a character in the movie.
Yes.
So this is theme park related in addition to just being podcast a ride related.
An actor plays Bob Iger.
Yes.
Has that ever happened in another thing?
I don't think so.
Will it ever happen again?
I hope so.
Yeah.
But it might not.
And someone else plays a man often identified as Bob Iger's best friend, at the time best friend.
Who is it?
Is it the time best friend?
Michael Owitz.
They were best friends?
Yes.
And that's why, yeah, when he brought him in as the president of Disney for like a very short tumultuous, like, I,
Owitz is in the Disney war book, like one of the most sympathetic characters in there.
And then after he left Disney, he had some remarks where it's like, oh, you, you know, you kind of.
The least sympathetic people.
Yeah.
So there's relevant stuff.
The other thing is we did put it to the audience.
We got stats on this.
We got numbers on it.
I looked it up.
I tweeted late shift episode in or out.
And with 565 votes, 87.3% said in.
That's good.
So thank you to the ins that are listening to the outs.
I don't know what to tell you.
Maybe you're not even hearing this.
And if you are listening, expecting theme park content, you might want to recalibrate your expectations.
The only thing and I was trying to like justify, is there anything remotely theme parky about it?
I don't know.
There is.
I don't think there.
Well, like I would say there is.
But you go.
OK.
What I was going to say, it's more like this might be a rationale.
I don't know.
It is.
It does like activate the same part of my brain that enjoys that there's this weird ride with Drew Carey and Regis Philbin that they would like.
Like, why would you do that?
Why would you put these real people in a ride or that, you know, there's a whatever is a Harry and the Hendersons thing there way later than there should be your water world is there like it's just the fact that this exists, that there is a sometimes dramatic film with dramatic scenes with a plastic looking Jay Leno and a bizarre dyed hair.
David Letterman.
It maybe feels a little like like a Bill and Ted show or something.
Yes, that's what I was going to say.
I was going to say Bill and Ted and I was going to say like you like this is like a Universal Studios walk around Jay Leno.
This is like if you saw him, we would go.
That's funny that there's like a guy playing Jay Leno.
Look how crazy he looks as a grunt in a grunt type mode.
And that's probably how you would portray it is sort of broadly right spray spray painted hair.
I know that's not how they did it, but unfortunately it doesn't like.
It doesn't.
It doesn't hold up.
I think Carson's rich little doing cars.
I got to give John Michael Higgins credit because I think of the three hosts.
He is the one doing the best in terms of a reasonable impression, but like a performance as an actor interpreting a real life person.
Yeah, he's doing his absolute.
No, no, you're right.
He's doing his absolute best.
It's still an impossible mountain to climb.
Really hard and he also had not been in nearly as many.
Yeah, I don't think he was the actor then that he is now or was even several years later.
He's mostly a stage actor, so that's a pretty tall like you haven't been in so many things on camera and you go into that like a thing that is where there is a target on your back.
Yeah, no, this is and and I think it is funny that I feel like in other things.
I'm sure this has happened that there have been films or TV shows or TV movies where a recent personality is portrayed as a character.
I'm sure that there have been actors who have said, well, see, I didn't want to just do an impression.
I didn't want to do like the rich little of it.
I know this has happened.
And then in this you have literal rich little who, if you don't know of the famous impressionist, mainly of the seventies and like variety show era.
Still in Vegas, still alive.
Yeah, still doing shows.
Oh, is he doing about that kind of wow.
Yeah, makes sense.
But like and he was he's good at what he's good at.
But it's sort of like, you know, cheeseball impressions of people's personas.
So to then have him act, he really has like almost the dramatic center of the movie where he has to like give this advice one on one to Letterman.
So interesting because each OK, each three hosts are sort of there's a each have a different take on the character.
Yeah, Rich Little is doing his Vegas actors Branson act.
The what's the guy's name?
Plus, Leno I've written down a Daniel Roebuck.
Daniel Roebuck is doing a cartoon version of Lennon doing a face character.
He walk around universal and also like a like a snow white is what you're saying.
Yeah, basically. Yeah. He's a face character.
I mean, this movie is like a theme park interpretation of movies or the behind the scenes of Hollywood very much feels a piece, like you're saying of universal.
And John Michael Higgins is, I think, doing the same thing like the Chris Pine is doing in the JJ Abrams Star Trek movies.
He's not trying to imitate the actor who is the actual actor.
He's trying to channel the vibe of the guy.
He has a little bit of the voice down, but he is not completely trying to just do a cartoon character.
Yeah, and I think it works in those movies.
I think it works in this. Yes, to an extent. Yeah, yeah, yeah, to an extent.
I mean, again, it's there's there's very few people that like talk show hosts are the people like celebrities that we see the most.
They are on TV the most.
So they're the freshest in your mind. Yeah.
Like like I just read I just made my parents watch Behind the Candelabra, one of our favorite movies.
Eventually that we will, I guess, do on this Patreon.
Yeah.
And it's like Liberace has been dead for many years.
So you've kind of forgotten how Liberace is.
But you go, oh, that seems like Michael Douglas doing a really great performance.
But you also kind of just ease in and you forget.
Or perhaps for other people our age, we don't know what Liberace was like at all.
That's true. I know that your pop culture is rooted in such a sense that you know Liberace very well.
Liberace is the sun in which my pop culture universe, they all rotate around.
One season 70s variety shows that we can't do any more of these.
It almost ruined 100 people's lives.
It's like a sun and it's like Al Lewis from the Munsters face, Liberace, Paul and Lidsville.
Lidsville.
Bobby Darin.
Bobby Darin. Yeah.
Yes, exactly. So.
But yeah, yeah, we know we were sort of taking the movie's word for it in a way.
What Liberace was like. And then we don't know Scott Thorson.
Right. Yeah.
Scott.
We don't know how Liberace said Scott. That was behind closed doors, behind the candelabra.
Here we are asked to see them.
We see them in the show. We see a lot of that with Higgins Letterman.
We see him like him like dangling a dog off of his leg.
Going to Paul, Paul and sandwich. I think he does that stuff pretty well.
He does.
He does the straighter impression stuff well. But then he like, he certainly carries the dramatic scenes a little bit.
Yeah, he's great. I just don't know if Daniel D. Lewis could have fully immersed himself in this role in the way this movie is shot as well.
The way this movie is shot, especially in H like in high def, like it looks, you can see the makeup.
I can see his teeth is like Letterman teeth, like the fake teeth.
Yeah, the hair is too bright. It's like it is not what Letterman's hair is.
Don't get me started on the Leno. Like you can see it's like it's like when they up res Star Trek Next Generation and people are like, you really can see warf's makeup now.
I think that's a little unfair to the to the movie and private. I've got a lot of things don't survive the transfer super well.
And yeah, I'm sure the HD is not kind to it.
I was now you one thing you forget is that though the makeup is very strange in this movie.
I looked it up and it was done by a like a completely reputable group like a family.
The Westmore's Monte Westmore is the main one. You know, the Westmore's is just that name.
I feel like it just sounds like is I feel like I've just seen it on like kits or doors.
Yeah, yeah. Reminds me of my dad would point out the name mole Richardson on lights.
And I think he knew the real person mole Richards like a family like that sounds like a fifties kind of.
And this guy Monte Westmore was the makeup artist for seven seasons of Ozzie and Harriet.
Wow, legendary. And then I don't know if it was him or somebody else in the family.
But so one of the people doing the makeup on this movie was the Joan Crawford's personal makeup artist on whatever happened to baby Jane.
Well, that is very funny because the makeup in that movie is insane, is insane and very heightened.
Yeah. And so, yeah, when you add all that up, that is man, that's like a perfect line.
That is like a perfect line from one to the other.
But isn't that why it's good? Like it is part of it.
I have to admit I never saw a feud, the FX feud.
Oh, I love it.
And I like now I'm watching like I need to see that.
I've meant to see it for a while. But isn't like is it a similar vibe in a way?
Like isn't there some like sort of like kitschy campiness to it?
I yeah, I think I think Jessica Lange and Susan Sarandon are doing much more grounded performances.
And then they have to, you know, for behind the scenes stuff.
And then when they're playing, the actors playing parts, then they can go crazy and you can kind of see like the animosity between them all.
You compare that to the animosity between them off stage.
Stanley Tucci as one of the Warners is just having the time of his life.
He's just at like at 11.
I feel like.
Boy.
Yeah.
That sounds like a blast.
Well, yeah, maybe that I know, you know, I do.
I think if the makeup were more subtle, would we like it?
No, no, it's part of the image, because when we tweeted, we're going to do something.
People responded with a very like sometimes you'd see it's very like broad cover or a promotional photo that does not really reflect what the movie is like because the hosts all meet pretty rarely.
There's photos where it's the three, it's Carson, Leno, Letterman, and they're all kind of like putting up the fisticuffs or like fake choking the other.
And like that image is just so silly.
And I think you imagine a dumber movie than this, which is a good movie.
They are surrounded by heavy hitters.
Bob Alaban, a Bigley Jr.
And of course, Kathy Bates is so great in this as Helen Kushnick.
You know, she was having a lot of fun.
These big stretches of like insane hyper verbal swearing jags.
Like she must have really just eaten it up.
It seemed like she was having the time of her life like that seemed like it was such a fun part to do.
Yeah, yeah.
Emmy nominated.
As was Treat Williams as Michael Lobitz.
I'm not sure when to talk about there if we want to like delve into the movie itself a little bit.
But you know, actually, before we do any of that, I have to like I got to get something.
I don't want to wait too long in the episode for this reveal because I think a lot of in asking ourselves, why are we obsessed with this movie?
I think a lot of it is the Leno of it all.
I think like like, of course, you're not going to see like a lot of movies where Letterman is being.
This may never happen again.
But Leno especially seems weird, like Letterman at this point is regarded in this like Kennedy Center Peabody sort of way.
And maybe Jay Leno has received some of those little things.
I'm not sure.
But like he still is kind of like working man's, you know, every day.
You don't regard him as like this untouchable prestige guy, which Letterman sort of became and is with the Netflix show.
Do you guys know that Jay Leno is doing a new show right now?
Yes, I do. I missed this entirely.
It's a new old very old show.
Yes. One of the oldest shows.
You bet your life.
The Groucho Marx show.
I found out about this because I think because I've been watching some Leno Letterman stuff in preparation for this YouTube algorithm to me that Leno was on the local news.
For the full half hour, like Fox 11, he went to the affiliate and just sat there.
They introduced him and he does a joke or two at the top and then like, oh, we're going to do some stories and then we'll talk to you.
OK, sure.
And then they talk about like, well, vaccines may soon be available for age five.
And you just like sometimes it'll cut wide to the studio and Leno's just sitting there just waiting.
And then they give him more to do later.
But they still do the top stories while Leno just sits.
The guy is like it comes up in this movie.
Visiting affiliates is his thing.
He loves to go shake the hands in the small towns.
It's Trump and the rallies.
And with this show, with doing a new game show, he gets to go meet the affiliates again.
He gets to do his favorite part of the job.
Because it's in syndication, right?
It is a syndicated show.
It is not NBC.
It's not even in the family like Jay Leno's garage is.
It's kind of weird to see him in syndication or on Fox.
But now it's just you can look around on YouTube.
There's so many 80 view videos of Jay Leno talking to an affiliate.
Wow.
And then plus, you know who's with him on the show?
No.
Kevin Eubanks.
Kevin Eubanks is back, you guys.
And he's not playing an instrument.
He's just there.
He's just sitting in a chair next to him.
So Kevin Eubanks has graduated.
I didn't know that.
He's bandleader.
Yes.
He is no longer.
He's made the full transition to comedian.
He's not asked to play guitar anymore.
He's been promoted to the Andy Richter, Ed McMahon spot.
Yeah.
But Kevin left and left the last couple seasons.
He left.
It was Ricky Miner.
I know that.
We went to see them.
They did All American.
You went to see Ricky Miner?
Well, we saw Jay and Ricky when the last couple years of The Tonight Show.
You went to a taping?
I went to a taping.
And they played All American Reject's Dirty Little Secret in between commercials.
And I was like, oh, that's an interesting choice.
Like a percussionist singing it or with like...
I think it was just maybe an instrumental version of it.
Which I kind of like that song.
Here's a question for you.
And now I'm remembering this because I get like blanket casting notices or like even
audience stuff from like LA casting.
And I have seen many things called Jay Leno, You Bet Your Life.
Ah.
So I did know about that.
But I've also seen things for something that just says, it's just the title is Jay Leno
at his best.
Exclamation point.
Uh huh.
I don't...
Is that the same thing?
Well, what does the body of the email tell you?
We need an enthusiastic audience who likes Jay Leno and his humor.
We need people who will make a very, very enthusiastic impression.
You must be fully vaccinated by September 9th.
There will be no COVID testing.
Call time Thursday.
Okay.
It says it's in Pacoima.
So let's see if the other casting notices...
Do you feel like people who are really enthusiastic about Jay Leno in Pacoima are maybe that vaccination
part is...
That's where it becomes a no deal for them?
It's possible.
Okay.
I think this is for some reason they're late.
It's the same thing.
Because this is You Bet Your Life and it says Leno fans tomorrow and it's the exact same
copy.
Okay.
So for some reason...
So for some reason they were naming it different.
They were just doing different names.
We're recording in my garage right now.
That was...
A car just went by.
In Burbank.
And that car could be heading to the Big Dog garage.
You never know.
It's entirely possible Jay was driving it.
That was one of my eye points of the first year of COVID was driving by the Gus's Fried
Chicken in Burbank and seeing a sports car parked outside, a man coming out with two
giant bags dressed in old denim.
And I slowed down.
I was just like, no, no way.
And sure enough, it was Jay.
Wouldn't it be buying a bunch of chicken?
That's wonderful.
Of course.
It's all...
I'm sidetracking, Scott.
Sorry.
But I do want to emphasize to this, to the audience, if you don't live in here in Burbank,
anytime you think it's Jay, it's Jay.
Yeah.
It happens a lot.
If you see a car, if you see a flash of denim...
It's always Jay.
And we've been making this joke since we started recording in my yard.
It's come up a couple of times.
And then several days ago, I am out on a bike ride.
I am but five blocks away from my house.
And who should I see when I round a corner?
But there's a classic car.
There is a flash of denim.
And sure enough, and we like...
Okay.
So I waited around for a minute.
I'm like, well, this is...
Oh my God.
I'm doing the late shift episode in a couple of days.
I wonder if I can get a moment somehow or what can I do?
But he was sort of already wrapping up an autograph and then getting in an old timey
car.
But I was able, because I had a little bike seat with me and my little buddy, my son with
me, and I got a photo of Jay making weird brief eye contact with my son.
Wow.
I feel like the dad of the century.
He didn't even know.
He didn't...
You know, my son, God bless him, he sees everyone as the same, whether it be some scumbag loser
or the king of television, Jay Leno.
Driving the car Alec Baldwin drives in that shadow remake from the 90s.
Driving Lamont Cranston's shiny big car.
Or a like D cobwebbed Munster's vehicle.
Half a Dracula.
Dracula.
And he fired it.
It took a big crank to do it.
Oh, wow.
And then it kind of exploded big.
And I was worried it would upset my son, but it did not.
He loved it, I bet.
I think he knew he was in the presence of greatness.
And then, so like, oh my God, this is great.
Right before we do this.
Wow.
And then, right before we started recording, like a half hour ago, I got a text from a
friend who was at a market up the street and was like, I saw Jay at the market.
Jay's at the market right now.
He was within several blocks of this house.
Yeah.
Really, several times recently.
People will think when I said that right before these stories that I was like, we coordinated.
But I did not know that there's two.
I'm truly, you will see Jay Leno all the time if you live here.
I saw him like two months ago.
I was just pulling out of the apartment and I saw an old timey car and I squinted and
I went, oh, guy in denim.
There he is.
Yeah.
It made me nervous.
I like, my heart started beating so fast.
Yeah.
I was like, you're not prepared for that.
And I think that it is him in his signature uniform.
It's like seeing Superman in the Superman suit.
Superman running into Peketo Moss for a bag of burritos.
And as Scott said many months ago at this point, Jay is a larger than life character.
He looks like a street shark.
That's what you said.
That's right.
I forgot that.
So it's like you're seeing a Ninja Turtle or a Biker Mice from Mars, one of the Biker
Mice from Mars in person.
He's sort of top heavy and he's belted off, which I think that helps it too.
That you never see.
It's always tucked in with a belt denim, which just sort of like forces the upper girth.
I would not call him a like chubby.
And I feel like he is like a, he is like, like older bodybuilder fits like all.
Top shoulder.
Yeah.
It's the fashion.
There's a man of a certain age are fascinated with Jay.
We are the age.
A friend of the show, Evan Susser, not long ago said to me, Hey, do you ever watch the
YouTube clip where David Letterman says, don't blame Conan?
Well, that's an, that's an algorithm classic.
Also, they're always trying to, if you watch anything related to any of this, you'll get
recommended that.
But it's just this whole sphere, I think is just so fascinating to a certain, a man of
a certain age of a certain interest.
Well, yeah.
Well, and I think if you're remotely in comedy for sure.
And then it's, it's like part of the fascination with this movie and the story that it's based
on it.
It's like only amplified by the fact that it all happened again.
But worse.
Like the network wanted to avoid it.
This is the Jay himself wanted to avoid it.
And it was so much worse the second time over.
It was so much worse because of the internet.
And I don't think I realized how much like it's happening again.
Like I didn't realize even though like we were just so close to it.
Like I had a universal studios, Hollywood annual pass Conan's taping on the universal
back lot.
Like I was so close to it so many times.
You know?
Yeah.
It's yeah.
It's that's what is that?
Ten years ago already at this point.
And some, some people more age, the first examples of, you know, getting out there,
political activism.
Obama elected and that's saved.
Coke, Coke, Coke, Coke.
Yeah.
Well, that's kind of how I view it is that like that felt like this sort of, you know,
the people are speaking and the people are demanding that justice be brought to this
situation.
And it really felt like, you know, like, boy, everybody's showing up in full force and you
can't deny the masses.
And there is going to be, once they see this, there is going to be some change here.
And then the people, the three people in the room said, nah, actually, they're not going
to do that.
And that gets you pretty used to how everything, how more important things are going to go
for the next decade.
That's right.
It's a lesson.
Yeah.
It very much felt like the low stakes version of like, oh, being a mouthy high schooler
speaking out against the Iraq war, the war happens.
Being a college sophomore, George W. Bush gets reelected.
We did nothing.
We didn't stop that.
Okay.
Yeah.
All right.
Conan's Conan's gone now too.
And I, you know, say what you will about you.
I always associate less bloodshed.
Yeah.
The significant amount of money spent flushed down the drain.
I do remember as a kid, my mom referencing like, you know, at breakfast, you know, well,
when did you go to bed last night?
Mom, she's like, oh, I watched Len was monologue and then turned in.
Like that was a measurement of time.
And my dad always was more of a night out.
So I think would stay up like in the living room watching TV.
And I'm wondering if he was a letterman guy.
I should text him and ask, like, were you, were you also watching letterman or were you
also watching Leno and just knew you were going to stay up longer or like, were you
a letterman guy?
I think I had the most Leno we family still do.
I was pretty deep into making like YouTube videos.
This may have happened when I was that funny or die.
I might have been like, I might have had a job and my mom is still like, you should
send some of your stuff to Jay Leno.
I think you'd get a kick out of it.
You might put it on the show.
Well, you would already been on Jay Leno.
Well, yes, as we've been, yes, I was a trick or treater in a sketch with a Nixon mask on
in 94.
So I would have brought up to him and had I had a second to talk, but I snapped the
photo instead.
But yeah, I don't know.
Yeah, so I mean, he's just going to like press play on videos.
I don't know what she's thinking is going to, but God bless her.
That is her way of encouraging her.
Yeah, get out there.
Yeah, comedy.
But I, my mom was Leno.
My dad was letterman.
Okay.
We have split household.
We'd always watch headlines.
My mom loved headlines.
He's doing headlines on the new show.
He's doing headlines on the game show.
You bet your life.
Really?
Yeah.
Wow.
It's like everything's back.
He just found this way to, I'm just going to go again.
Don't change horses in mid-stream.
Here's my question.
What took so long?
Yeah.
I'm being serious.
How, how has he been off TV?
Like main, I know that we all watch the garage, but how has he been off TV, TV for so long?
And, and yeah.
And then why am I any, why am I surprised at all that he just managed to go back to
the same thing in sort of a lower rent fashion?
Is he going to, is he going to do a green card challenge?
Is he going to drive from the Jay Leno?
The, the, what is it called?
The Jay Leno show?
Uh huh.
The green car challenge Jason is of course on the Jay Leno show when he moved to that
slot before Conan, he would race a green car around a track sometimes.
Uh, can you explain for me, is it a car painted green or like?
No, no, it was like electric.
Environmental.
That was the idea.
Like a sound.
Promoting.
Yeah.
Green car challenge.
Okay.
I got it.
So they, cause they had a lot of time to eat up on that show and how do we, well, let's
just have him like race against Kevin James or whatever.
Like it takes a while.
It'll take a while to get in the car and they do the laps because that was the problem with,
if you read the other book, which of course I have the war for late night, the Jay Leno
show when he, when they moved him to 10 o'clock, that was their solve for the previous pro
and like, uh, they were just bleeding comedy the entire time.
Like they, like from the get go, they did not have enough segments loaded up.
The whole thing was an exercise in killing time and they wanted to end with a comedy
piece.
So that, you know, it's not like other talk shows where it just kind of trickles out.
Maybe you do just watch the monologue.
They're trying to get people to the local news.
So they want to save something really good at the end, like him racing against Kevin
James in a, in a leaf, in a Nissan leaf.
And weren't there rules though, in the same way that Carson put down rules for Letterman,
Letterman was not allowed to do a full traditional monologue.
Letterman was not allowed to have the same type of like maybe musical guests as well.
Wasn't there also a look rules like for the Jay Leno show versus Conan tonight show.
Wait, who dictated that NBC said if you're going Johnny did, I believe.
Well, the others.
Yeah.
You're saying, uh, for Letterman.
Oh, for, for, I don't know if NBC may be like, Oh, this dude will be, it's a different show.
It's a variety show.
It's not a late night talk show.
Oh, Jay, you're saying they gave Jay, they gave, they were trying to do some different
stuff to try to make it, to pretend it wasn't just the same tonight show before Conan.
Tonight show.
Because again, the, the, the very uncomfortable situation that Conan has put in that he is
like asked to do an hour long show after a show that has done the same format at a time
where no one is used to watching.
Like, like the human brain is not calibrated to watching talk shows at that hour.
That is the hour where there are medical dramas and police dramas.
Yes.
And now the first, for the first time ever, ever in TV history, there's going to be a
nightly talk show and it's with a guy who's like been doing this for you.
That's who you want to reinvent the wheel is somebody who's been at it for decades.
Right.
And then of course, regular TV shows get a better lead in, which leads into the news,
which leads in like so many late, so much of like late night talk shows is just keeping
old people's TVs on while they fall asleep.
Well, that's why Jay is doing affiliate tours again, cause his audience would be the ones
watching the local affiliates.
They do watch.
Yeah, I'm here saying that all these videos only have 80 views, but that doesn't, I think
anyone's tracking that.
Like nobody's watching the local news clips on YouTube.
They're watching it as it airs and that is his audience.
Yeah.
They, JR's, JR, Jay's PR people like would send him here into this garage and he'd be
like, yeah, okay, let's go show up.
Like he's just, he does it.
That's why I'm always trying to hedge my, have we said too much bad stuff about him?
Because I kind of feel like he might do it.
I kind of think he would get it.
When I heard he was at the market down the street, I was like, should I just go up there
and either ask him what he thought about the movie?
And I think he would answer me.
I don't think he'd blow me off or like if I really felt comfortable, like you want to
pop over?
Do you want to come in?
My friends are coming.
Do you want to do the Omnibus episode?
I don't want to be.
Do you want to do the Main Street fire truck?
That's a good idea.
It's a great idea.
I don't think.
Main Street Omnibus with Jay Leno.
As much as we go for, okay, here's, here, let me even, and I, this is not, I'm not trying
to kiss Jay's ass now so cause we can get him on, but the, the fact of the matter is
this, Jay was like the hottest, hippest, edgiest comedian until he did the tonight show.
And I think the combination of Jay sort of turning a little bit more family friendly
and then this movie and then the denim has turned him into a character that we just are
endlessly fascinated and turned him into a full cartoon character.
And that ends up being sort of what we all end up joking about a lot is a guy who just
makes Monica Lewinsky jokes, wears all denim, like, like, you know, like, yeah, like a street
like whatever the street shark uniform is.
Achieved the highest heights of show business, fought tooth and nail to do so as portrayed
in the film, did it again and is like, like toppled more enemies.
And yet does he now enjoy the spoils of his efforts?
No, he's just did flappers.
He did flappers every weekend.
Oh yeah, lately.
Like, yeah, the pandemic's still going on.
He's an old man.
He does, he just shows up.
He does a show.
He does, he has never done a special about, he has never done like a night show.
He has never done like a Netflix special, a live standup special because he wants, he
knows the value of his jokes in a standup comedy.
So he doesn't want to just give it away.
He won't just give it away.
That's been his philosophy.
You compare it to Carson who stepped away in this monumental television event.
Like everyone is watching that and cares about it.
It's recreated in this movie.
And he's only appears on television three more times in his life.
He's like utterly unaccessible, refuses everything.
Leno says yes to everything.
He's never gone away.
It is fascinating.
He is like his, his kind of like passive aggressive stuff is fascinating because he's like, he's
trying to project sort of every man guy with a denim and stuff.
And you know, he doesn't touch his tonight show money.
He's a fascinating character.
There's two Norm MacDonald stories that spring to mind here.
Of course, the clip from Conan where Norm goes, you know, Jay Leno, he goes, you know,
everybody has a voice or whatever.
He goes, meanwhile, he's a shrewdest guy.
He goes, every 20 years, a redheaded Rube gets out of a car and he out foxes them again.
Jay Leno out foxed you again.
Out foxes.
Hell yeah.
You can have it after me.
Which I do usually think about him positively, but the obsession with like, I'm a nice guy.
I don't know.
I'm just nice guy.
I'm caught.
I find a little.
It's fascinating.
Letterman during the Conan thing when Letterman was, by the way, this is going to go four
hours.
I have too much to talk about this.
Yeah.
Letterman during the Conan thing where he's like, you know, you know, you know, somebody
would stop over and help a person who like had the flat tire.
But of course, Jay would bring a camera crew with, which is something he would say very
often, which is really funny.
The other I'm trying to think the other.
Oh, the other norm thing.
Speaking of Carson, just as a side note, because I just heard this norm claims that in the
mid nineties, he was called to Johnny Carson's office and all and Johnny had printed out
his like Larry King sketch that he had done or just printed out Larry King's like USA Today
column, which is King's Things, where Larry would say like, for my money, the best juice
is orange juice, which he would still tweet about that even like a couple of years ago.
Some really nothing thought.
Yeah, which I think one of the like if you one of the jokes from the sketch, I think
is like, for my money, the best movie of this year is Mickey Blue Eyes.
Yeah, yeah, no, because I think even Norm was like, we didn't have to parody it very
much at all because it was like that.
Apparently, Johnny had like had just a bunch of Larry King's thing.
He handed that like a copy to Norman said, let's just read them.
And Norm sat in Johnny Carson's office, which he still kept up until when he died and had
a secretary for no reason.
And he just sat there awkwardly with Johnny and traded off reading the script.
Like Larry King thoughts, which is a weird like little backdoor shit talk like a lot
of people would do to like little like quiet text thread about so and so very fascinating.
Wow.
I never heard that.
That's fascinating.
I'll say that since Johnny came up again, one thing this movie, I think, does kind of
pressure like predicts the the thing about Rich Little doing his own thing is that he
does kind of like it's his impression of Carson, but he's also acting a little.
He captures the what I think in 2020s America, we think of as Johnny Carson, which is the
hits that are on Tubi for free.
Oh, yeah.
Best of segments.
That's what if anyone thinks about Johnny Carson, anyone younger than 30 thinks about
Johnny Carson.
They've likely seen the time life infomercials.
Yeah.
The Tomahawk goes in between the guy's legs.
Probably a Joan Embree.
There's something with animals, maybe a Karnak line or two.
Yeah.
Like some of the least less offensive Rickles clip because there's some you watch and go,
Oh God, he's sometimes you go, Oh, it's like that's on the line.
And that's sometimes you go, Oh, wait a minute.
I know that one's not in the greatest hits anymore.
OK.
Yeah.
I know.
Carson's a whole different story because like there were plenty of bad Carson monologues
where if you watch on YouTube, you're like his whole monologue ain't shit.
He looks like he looks like just an old man who's like not funny at all.
Undercut his own joke and not like purpose was just like gave up on it halfway through.
Yes.
Everyone sort of remembers the John, the Dana Carvey or the rich little version like this
kindly old man.
Meanwhile, read the books, you know, read about when Johnny was Johnny was a complicated
character.
And then there's a documentary narrated by Kevin Spacey.
Yeah, of course, took over as primary impressionist for which he did so prominently on the Tony's.
Of course, you know, the what the 2016 Tony's he comes out and does Johnny Carson, you know,
another person way awards, you know, adds up.
Yeah.
He did.
Bill Clinton.
I believe.
OK.
All right.
And then there's a piece.
Yeah.
The master class he takes to I forget if we said this in our space, he was that he like
teaches.
He is, you know, actors who want to learn about acting.
He has him come in and like, you know, see Carson would have he had this thing where
he would kind of lean back.
He'd do the joke and he'd lean.
It was it was always a pivot.
See, it's the pivot.
And he like puts his arms around somebody's shoulders.
Let me show you.
Yeah.
Watch that if it's available, I guess, but it's probably not available.
That's probably not easily.
Although maybe like Eva had clipped it.
Yeah.
No, Eva message.
Eva to get it.
Yeah, she's got it.
OK, let's let's get into the because we could talk about the people forever.
Yeah.
And I don't know that we have to like, you know, scene by scene it.
But if it helps to group it, like generally when things happen, I don't even know how
to to tackle it.
I mean, so if you don't know the the the tail, I guess the main stuff is, you know,
is NBC knows that Carson is going to retire at some point and they better line up
the next guy.
Leno has become the permanent guest host of The Tonight Show, which side note, I was
listening to him on Bullseye with Jesse Thorne.
He had Leno on.
I didn't realize where he tells the story that how he got to be the permanent guest
host of The Tonight Show was like other people started demanding like a lot of money.
Like Letterman was another one of the people doing that.
He'd come in and like I think for a long time, I think Carson was off every Monday.
So other people would do it or Gary Shanley or great John Rivers, I think, was in the
Oh, sure.
Yeah.
Before her show.
So but they'd start kind of like asking for decent amounts of money, you know, like
Carson himself might may or like anyone should be making on TV.
Leno says his own number.
He's like, I cost five hundred twenty dollars an episode.
Wow.
So they're looking at it and like, well, this person wants, you know, five thousand.
This guy wants five hundred twenty.
Well, let's go with Jay.
He like he he himself he like undercut the competition.
He's the working man's comedian.
He's he didn't even spend that money.
He said that old thing about not spending tonight your money.
He says I didn't spend that five hundred twenty dollars I made.
He is so fascinating.
I mean, this is getting a little bit to the thing in the movie.
But one of the main reasons is that Letterman wanted to own the show.
And Jay didn't care.
Jay was just like, I'm getting in whatever it takes.
Yeah. Pay me as little as possible.
Obviously, eventually he got paid well.
Yeah. Yeah.
So he's guest hosting the show.
David Letterman's following Carson for many years.
It makes so much sense that he would move up and do it.
But he's very prickly.
He's weird to executives.
You know, there's never a good relationship there.
Jay, however, aims to please the nicest guy in the world.
And he's able to do that because he's the good cop and the bad cop is his manager.
Helen Kushnick.
And I think Helen Kushnick is why this got made into a movie.
Yeah, she's the fascinating character.
Because whoever who knew about that, I don't know that there's any like footage really still like that you can go find of her.
Right. And how bizarre it is and what a weird revelation of the movie that Leno like,
how you doing that he had this like really severe manager like Tom Hague.
Like a godfather as consignly air like an enforcer that really.
Yeah. Yes.
That enforcer.
That's like a wrestling term or like a heater.
Yes. Yeah.
A heater. They also call it a wrestling.
Yeah.
He's got a heater.
It's like you got like a like a tough guy behind you that like takes care of beating somebody up.
Yeah. Yeah.
For sure.
She was Jay Leno's ward low.
The guys.
Scary guys.
Yes.
Not to jump around too much, but as things are unraveling and all of these secrets are unfurled,
I think one of the best lines in the movie and potentially a line from reality that so that summarizes the whole thing with her that she tells Leno,
you just want me to keep serving you the stakes.
You never want to know how I'm slaughtering the cow.
Amazing.
What are we like?
And that's why we have him and we're at night.
If he did not ride in on this wave of brutality.
Yeah.
And it's also that's also psychologically part of why for the last couple of years he was always like, I don't have an agent.
I don't have a manager.
He kept saying that.
And I feel like it was like him like trying to be like, Helen's not here anymore.
Yeah.
Helen's gone.
He did have a manager.
It's funny because in the movie, one of the plot points is that like Letterman,
Letterman's people are like his producer, like he didn't have an agent.
He was very skeptical and seemingly maybe disgusted by them.
And, you know, but then ultimate then caves to get his way and gets the biggest agent you can.
That's sort of what how it goes down is that she really she's got kind of a better she really guns for it to get Leno the spot.
Suddenly, this article appears in the New York Post.
NBC wants Carson out.
She swears up and down to Jay.
I had nothing to do with this.
He calls Carson on the phone like right then and there in front of her who you hear.
You hear subtle detail.
It's conveyed in the movie that Carson made didn't care for Leno terribly much.
So he answers the phone.
Hello.
Yeah, it's Jay.
Hi.
He goes way down.
As soon as he realizes.
Yeah.
So they sort of push Carson out the door or the heat is on.
He suddenly makes this surprise announcement out of nowhere at this affiliates event that he will be stepping down in a year.
And NBC sort of caught without an answer and without any particular plan except that.
But I might correct that by this point, they had secretly locked in Leno without telling Carson who would have liked to have had a say in all this.
Right.
Without telling Letterman who would have left as soon as he found out.
Yes.
Secret deals.
Yeah, because the story was always that like Johnny wanted Dave to take over.
Right.
Or at least liked him.
That's Johnny for sure.
Like Dave and then would have appeared twice on Dave's show later after he retired.
So that obviously seems like an endorsement.
What I put it past Johnny to be like that show should die with me.
Like, no, I don't know it, Johnny.
And I've never I don't know if he's on the record.
It's like they should just put infomercials on after this.
Like, assault the earth where my tonight show used to be.
I don't know.
Just film the moon.
Yeah.
I know he liked Dave as much as Johnny liked any of those people.
Right.
Yeah.
OK.
So that's about what I thought.
As much as he was capable of liking any human being.
Yeah.
Because he was still like very nervous, I think, about like, well, he can't do you know, he was really insecure and again, wouldn't let Dave do like a monologue.
Like very in the same way, though, that people speculate Dave was insecure and put Tom Snyder on after him because Tom Snyder was no competition for entertainment.
It's a very boring shit.
Yeah.
So yeah, that wasn't a dynamo song and dance man in out in the street.
Well, people's cars like he got in that slot now.
Yeah.
You've got Mr. Entertainment, of course, that time.
Dave does not own that show, though, right?
Or does he?
I don't know.
Does Dave own Colbert still?
I don't think so.
I don't think so either.
But that's interesting.
Worldwide Pants because Dave's company.
Yeah.
So Dave got a big deal with CBS and Worldwide Pants is his company.
But then he also owned the show after.
So Dave made a ton of money, more money than he would have made an NBC if he stayed.
Right.
And the other big thing I remember from the writer's strike days is Letterman was one of the first shows back with written material because Worldwide Pants negotiated with the WGA.
They signed a new contract with the WGA.
So they were able to make new stuff.
Meanwhile, like, you know, while Conan and Colbert are like ziplining from the top of the audience to the desk because they can't have writers and they can only write so much.
And they're stuck with them because their shows are owned by NBC and NBC hasn't sorted out any of this stuff.
I believe so.
Yeah.
There's a little detail I'd like to point out in this like right before Carson makes his announcement.
And this is one of my favorite things in the movie for some reason.
It cuts to this like boring Carnegie Hall event where the that year's fall lineup is trotted out.
Yeah.
And then there's this part where Warren Littlefields is played by Bob Balaban who's the NBC executive.
Very mild mannered.
That's the that's the beauty of Bob Balaban in general.
What a wonderfully like that compelling flatness of Bob Balaban.
No one does it better, I feel like.
One of the best at doing that.
Man, the greatest deadpan ever.
Even like throughout the movie whenever like like you'd really do that you'd fire me.
Yes, we feel that upset about this.
That's how strongly we feel.
And that's still as high as he ever gets.
Never.
This is one part where he goes like Christ.
But it's sort of like he plays.
I feel like Bob Balaban in real life could lose his shit.
He's really great at playing characters who have a cap and he knows that's what's funny about them.
That they're just like timid by nature.
I think too, especially if that's your type, you you probably deal with a lot of frustration where people think you are like that all the time in real life.
And I imagine that is very annoying to everybody's trying to fuck over all the time.
Charging for this meal.
And what do you think?
Look, he's going to do.
Hey, man, you left the menus right here.
I can see the check.
Like, come on.
Bob Balaban punched me.
He threw me to the ground.
I like the idea that the world is so familiar with Bob Balaban's work that they're constantly fucking with him.
Well, you think Mr. Gosford Park is going to give us shit?
Can't walk down the street.
And then, of course, I'm sure you were getting there, but Bob Balaban, of course, plays a Warren Littlefield analog on Seinfeld years later, which is crazy because it's like kind of like.
That's before.
You're right.
You're right. Yes.
That's crazy.
He's already in the in the self reflexive Seinfeld season where they make a TV show.
He's playing a character clearly based on Warren Littlefield.
And then he plays the real Warren Littlefield in the movie.
So it's not it's not completely Michael Keaton playing the same character from the Elmore Leonard universe, but it's close.
It's close.
It's kind of neat.
It is a little consistent tying stuff together.
Yeah.
Wait, what is the Keaton one?
What's like he's in Jackie Brown and then he's in a different movie, too.
Oh, that's the same character.
I believe so.
Let me make sure.
Why is it out of sight?
I think it's out of sight, right?
Oh, yeah.
Those you made around the same.
That's really funny.
I've read a bunch of Elmore.
Yeah.
Characters show up in a lot of a lot of the same characters crossover in some of those books.
This is some Marvel stuff.
Yeah.
They were they were they were way ahead of it.
It is Elmore Leonard and Kurt Vonnegut.
They got should have gotten on that crossover journey.
Ray.
Ray Nicolette is the character Keaton is in out of sight and in Jackie Brown.
Right.
OK.
Yeah.
You've also got Seinfeld royalty with the other executive.
John Agolia is the real guy's name and he's played by Rennie Santoni.
What a name.
Rennie Santoni is the actor who was also Poppy on Seinfeld.
Yes.
He's on the couch.
Wonderful performance.
Completely different.
I didn't put it together until this viewing that he's that guy.
Oh really.
Yeah.
Because that's a different.
And he's really funny.
What I was starting to get at though was this that mild mannered one little field like all
right.
And how about a hand for NBC's fall lineup?
And then he cuts to this great like rainbow.
Here's all the days of the week Saturday through Friday in peacock colors and then this weird
lineup of who is on their shows.
I had that.
I have a question.
Yeah.
I had a question.
What's your what's your observation?
The one closest to Bob Avalon.
Is that a false Seinfeld?
Is that a fake side?
I think so.
Yeah.
That was Aaron's observation.
I didn't catch that till this this time.
I didn't know if this was like nonsense.
They're all like it's just like a very diverse group and some of them are in pseudo costumes
and some of them aren't.
In my head, one of them was wearing a construction hat like it was the village people.
I'm just not correct about that.
But I thought they were all like representing their jobs on their sitcoms.
But yeah, I think you've got to like from this distance where you're looking at my screen,
that's clearly a fake Seinfeld.
Well when they there's a cut to the side to like Balabi on a profile and the one as they're
walking away as the guy turns, I'm like, is that fake Seinfeld?
I think that's they cast an act a lookalike Seinfeld like I think it's a fake.
I think it's a fake Seinfeld.
I think that's a fake Seinfeld.
It's a fake Seinfeld.
I did the fake Seinfeld.
And then you've got I think you got like a fake blossom here too because you got like
a hat.
It is so funny in the movie when they all get put like off they walk off stage.
This line up all I do.
It's so funny.
I think it's supposed to be a Will Smith and a Carlton.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
And then the rest of them I'm not sure.
Maybe it's a fake wings.
Maybe it's a fake LA law.
Is there a fake empty nest in there?
Oh, could.
Oh, maybe the guy next to fake Carlton is fake empty nest.
Because empty nest is on the list is on the banner.
One of the banners.
It could be.
What else is on a different world?
I don't think there's is there a fake quantum leap is on here is this is there a false back?
Could be.
And then a lot of shows that I think are made up unless these are I just don't know these
like Secret Service final appeal.
What happened?
Love the line up.
Anyways, you know, I also don't need to like synopsize the film.
I mean, just like if we want to just call out parts that we enjoy that give us joy because
there's there is so much so many scenes that have been burned into my brain for so many
years.
Well, I should mention because I haven't yet I didn't want to forget I had never watched
start to finish until Monday until the other day.
And I say, folks, if you think we're like into the campy nest, we are into the campaign
that's certain elements of that.
I thought this was a really solid movie.
Yes, I thought this was great for it.
Yeah, I thought it was like very solid.
The there's the bone of fetus, the people who bone of fetus.
I never get that word right.
The people worked on it.
Bill Carter co wrote it.
The other guy who co wrote it, George Armitage, I was saying before we start directed Gross
Point Blank, which was like one of the big I think of that as like the pre the era of
John Cusack movies like right before High Fidelity, like this in High Fidelity back
to back.
That's cool.
Very much a line up.
Yeah.
And Betty Thomas, the director, directed the Brady Bunch movie.
Love the Brady Bunch movie.
Yeah, both of both movies.
Yeah.
The Brady Bunch movie.
Sorry.
The the Dr. Doolittle and Alvin and the Chipmunks, the Squeakwell.
That's right.
She directed the third.
Which is notable of her filmography as it's the only one of them that I am in.
What?
Yes, I am in a crowd scene.
That is one of my few forays into background acting.
I'm in the football scene when Alvin scores the big touchdown.
I'm in the bleachers.
And I found the clip.
The clip is online.
Whoa.
Can you identify yourself?
I could because I was like, well, there was two older people in front of me that just
like talked for eight hours.
Like I was sitting on those bleachers getting sunburned for like eight hours and they just
talked about everything and anything under the sun.
And sure enough, I clocked them and then clocked myself immediately behind it.
Wow.
Well, this has to be posted.
That's news to me.
Yes.
Sheridan and the Squeakwell.
Boy, oh boy.
I don't even think I'm.
Did I know that?
I, I, I don't know.
I, I, I might have been like right before we met.
It was like 2009.
You've been hiding that from me because I did say I do say I never forgot a single thing
about you and I would remember that you were in the squeak wall.
I remember that.
That was like a few months before I think I auditioned to be a Universal Studios tour
guide with three to four hundred of my closest friends going down city walk because there
was a recession going on and people were trying to get any job.
And my buddy, meanwhile, I'm rehashing all of these old shitty jobs and a buddy I went
to that Universal Studios audition with was nominated for an Emmy a few days ago.
So, you know, we're all moving at our own speed.
You have a Patreon.
That is true.
No, I do.
I'm happy to rehash it.
I'm happy to monetize it now because Lord knows Central Casting was not, you know, paying
non-union background.
Consider this now you're making the money you were owed for the squeak wall for the
talking about it on a page.
Yeah.
When you're a 20 year high school reunion comes up in a very few short few months, really
almost like as if it was the plot of gross point.
Yeah.
I mean, obviously I'm hitting mine quicker soon, but yeah, you'll be able to say squeak
wall and Patreon.
Did you go to the 10 year?
I didn't know I did not go to 10.
Kind of want to go to 20.
I kind of want to go to 22.
But I also was like, it feels like it should be like, it doesn't feel like 20 years.
I mean, Jesus Christ.
Yeah, I did.
It's all right.
I went to the my 10 somehow despite being very antisocial and it's so it was a huge
mistake.
I don't know what got me thinking that would be a good idea to do.
Don't do it.
I say don't do it.
Really?
I don't know.
I mean, there's there are like 25 people, maybe 20 people that I had like a good time
talking to for four years that I never talked to after that that I go, Oh, hey, I don't
think we would.
We didn't have those.
I I keep in touch with the.
Yeah.
We are the only people I like from my high school.
I married him.
OK, so I'm spoken for.
Yeah, we had an interesting I was like we had like a floater group that kind of grew.
I was lucky to have people that would like do dumb stuff and movies and stuff in high
school.
But I talked to a lot of them are still so well, good for you.
Not me.
I went and got so I was I got so bored and just started like drinking a bunch.
And then I took a dessert.
Nobody was taking the dessert.
So I took just like a like too much cake and grabbed it and just kind of shoved my face
into it in a Homer fashion.
Somebody took a photo and this girl I never particularly got along with in high school
just said, you and that's all I remember.
I got a flashback.
Yeah. You like recreated like one of those weird high school memories.
It's no stature change.
What's going on when we talk about Bonifitas, if that's the way to say it.
I like that.
I like saying that. So I hope that's what it is.
Daniel Roebuck, as we said, some of these other people like a lot of other folks in
the film have done great things.
Truly Betty Thomas. What an underrated director.
Yeah, not in a pretty much movie.
This and parts right after what a run in a fascinating.
She was second city.
She has like a real fascinating career.
She's in stuff, too.
She's acted a lot.
Yeah. Yeah.
But yeah, not a lot anymore.
I don't know why.
Shoot Troop Everlane as well.
Right. People. Yeah.
So, yeah, which people love.
But Daniel Roebuck maybe has not gone on to do so like maybe is primarily known as
Fake J in this.
There hasn't been like the other thing, but he never stopped working.
There's a ton of other stuff that he's done and been in.
Here's a photo, by the way, of him getting the J prosthetics put on him like
Flabber from the Bible man villain.
We got to get to know not Bible.
No, no, no.
Big bad Beatle Borg.
Oh, flabber is big bad.
Beatle Borg.
And Fibbler is Fabbler is not Fibbler.
Scott Fabbler.
I went over at home to say it out loud.
Fabbler, Fabbler, Fabbler, Fabbler, Fabbler, Fabbler, Fabbler, Fabbler, Fabbler, Fabbler,
because there is no Fabbler and flabber is not Fibbler.
It was from Bible man and the others from Big Bad Beatle Borgs.
Two promised Patreons that we got to get to.
People, please stop coming to our homes and rattling the door.
We know everyone's demanding these.
This this press, these press, like four and a half hours every day, the eventual runtime
of this somehow.
And then they still end up looking as crazy as this.
Daniel Roebuck was also in this other great movie I found on YouTube a couple of years
ago that is a movie about Mork and Mindy, but the making of Mork and Mindy.
And in that, I'll show you a photo.
He plays another real life comedy icon, Gary Marshall.
Wow.
Here is fake Leno as fake Gary Marshall.
If you I don't think it's on YouTube anymore, which is too bad because it has a great part
where there is a fake Robin Williams.
They like it must be this must be for happy day because it started as Mork started on
Happy Days.
You're X. Yeah.
So they're holding auditions for this alien part.
Nobody's doing.
Everybody's just coming in and doing I am an alien and none of it's interesting.
And then fake Robin Williams comes in and oh, oh, daddy, I'll be on all that shit.
And like and it's this and it's the best which happens in this movie a lot to in
the late shift is like, you know, you're in good territory when your movie is full of
people laughing when it requires lots of cut to the people.
Ah, ha ha ha.
All the best things have it.
Studio 60 and such.
Strip has it.
Late shift has it.
This work of mini movie has it.
So cuts to Daniel Roebuck is Gary Marshall just doubled over.
Oh, my God.
I can't hear. He's watching the discovery.
He's making the discovery of Robin Williams.
And and then Robin Williams leaves still in a funny way, almost trips on the way out
the door and is still doing bits.
And a woman turns to Gary Marshall and says, God, what was that?
And he says, I don't know, but I want it on my show.
And then it smashes to more filming obscene.
So if you want to see that kind of thing, yeah.
And more can there are Robin Williams in that movie played by I'm going to fuck up
the name Chris D.
D. Amitopoulos, always the voice of Mickey Mouse, the cool, good, new Mickey Mouse.
You get to see him as a weird fake Robin Williams.
That is it is a very tough assignment playing somebody who a lot of people think is
actually funny.
Can you do the routines?
That's like one of the weirdest artists.
It's almost it.
And it's impossible even like when there's like even in a movie where you're supposed
to be like a rock star like Dennis, Larry can't fool me into thinking he's like a
rock star and like Mark Walbert, a rock star.
It doesn't work.
And to say like a similar very similar thing with like a comedian brand as Aldous Snow
forgetting Sir Marshall and get him to the green Tom Cruise is Stacey Jax.
Yeah, there's something about it that he doesn't count that rocks that does rock.
And he's swinging around on the poles singing White Snake.
Yeah, yeah, that makes total sense to your brain.
Well, he's not I'm sorry.
He's not White Snake.
He does Steal Horse.
I really want to.
Yeah, we're on a dead or alive.
It's just yeah, it's very hard to do that.
I'm sure there's an example of somebody who did it really well.
I guess Michael Douglas played the barachi really well.
Yeah, there's a certain version, but it's hard.
It's very hard assignment.
Yeah, all this is getting to that.
I let me see if this translates in the episode.
But Daniel Robux, he never stopped working still like tons of credits every year, keeps
at it.
And I saw his reel, his reel has really quick flashes of him in different stills of
things. And it has like a subliminal flash to the late shift.
He's not denying the shift, but I think he maybe realizes it's sort of a dead end.
The nobody's going to want a Jay Leno type in anything.
He wants to prove that he's other things.
He's a Brooklyn cop or he's a dad as portrayed in this film.
And this is like a comedy cut to in this reel.
The scene starts.
I'll just start the scene and then a little title reveals the name of the film that he's
in and the name of the movie is How My Dad Killed Dracula.
Oh, wow.
Thirty years ago, when I was a little boy, I grew up in this house and I used to trick
or treat in this neighborhood just like you boys did tonight.
There was one Halloween in Iowa.
I'll never forget.
Yeah, what happened?
When I had my bag full of candy.
Yeah.
And all I wanted to do was get home and have a mallet cup.
Then what, Dad?
I got to the house, expected to see Grammy and Grandpa, but they weren't here.
Because.
I guess it was here.
Dracula?
Yeah, Jason.
Dracula was here.
I met him face to face.
What a scene.
Wow.
One of the scariest things you could have said to me as a kid.
Yeah, Jason.
Dracula was here.
I met him face to face.
Yeah.
And the thing about what was the cup?
What the candy he wanted to eat?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no cup.
Right.
That's also too close.
So because I loved Malik, I was going to say, is that one of yours?
I was always one of mine.
Yeah.
Is that one of your guys?
And now I prefer a Sifir's Valor milk, a little, little less thick.
The thing from Kansas City, somewhere in the Midwest, very specific.
That again, Sifir's Valor milk.
Just got, you know, still has the million year old logo on it.
You used to be able to get it at like, I don't know, did all the rocket fizzes go under or
just some of the Valley?
Sifir's Valor milk.
I'm not a stockholder, so I don't know.
Sifir's Valor milk is also one of my favorite prequels characters.
Oh, OK.
So it's like a little it looks like a peanut butter cup.
It's like a little more flavorful.
The cup is thicker, but it's like the filling is thinner.
Valor milk.
Mine, I'm looking at the website.
My name is Russell Sifir's.
We are a small family owned and operated candy company now into our fifth generation.
That's right.
What? That's right.
Can you tell me more about Sifir's?
Yeah, they made it to the fifth.
Good for them.
Yeah.
You know, you're worried there's going to be an end to the lineage, but not with the Sifirs.
Hmm.
The Sifirs. Wow. OK.
Yes, Jason.
Dracula was here and he ate all of the Sifirs Valor milk.
Son of a bitch.
Dad, let's kill him again.
Can you see this? This is the man, I think.
What a guy.
Hello.
I'm Russell Sifir.
Looks like he's doing a talk show.
He's at his place.
The Daniel Roebuck will play.
Better watch out.
Jail taken.
Can I say?
Yeah, I do the Sifir show now.
Can I?
Are you? Do you have more about Roebuck?
I want to know.
We've reached the peak of his career.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And how my dad killed Dracula.
I want to say something about how also another thing, how he plays Jay.
Oh, yeah.
If you were just kind of walking in and out of the room and watching the movie,
I think you could possibly mistake him for David Schwimmer playing the most
depressed character he's ever played.
He seems to. Robert Kardashian.
Robert Kardashian.
Juice.
No, dude.
Oh, it is like this.
Yeah, kind of a mumbly.
He's like a mopey Jay.
Oh, no.
Yeah, that's shell shocked in over his head.
Yeah.
And I can't imagine Jay was like that.
Exactly.
I get why they're playing it like that,
because they kind of want to seem like Jay is in the dark with Helen.
So he kind of has to play low status.
Yeah. But he's so mopey.
He's I would call him emo Leno.
He's emo for sure.
Yeah.
Geez.
Well, he seems, yeah, just so depressed.
And I don't know, maybe maybe he was.
I don't know.
Helen thinks it's a good idea.
So yeah, I guess it's kind of like like old school.
Oh, gee.
Yeah.
Well, Helen says we should go into the haunted house.
So I guess we better.
Yeah, it's interesting because I mean, I always watching it again.
I was like, yeah, he's so depressed.
Yeah, especially like where's the scene?
Like, I mean, I think one of the one of the highlights of the movie is where things
come to a head just to jump around a little.
Helen Kushner gets him the job, but then it becomes the producer of the Tonight
Show over steps or bounds goes way too far.
It's very rude to all these people.
Burns British almost loses him the show.
And there is like an intervention essentially that occurs where the two
executives and her and Leno meet.
She storms out of the room, thus leaving sad Leno, who's having to deal with the
you know, stakes of the situation and like that he is just so like lots of weird,
like eye rolls and kind of like, oh, geez, you're kidding.
I and then like I think that's one of my favorite things in the whole thing is him
saying where he was at before Helen.
Right. That which is what like, you know, like, you know, before I got to the Tonight
Show, that was why I was doing it.
They have a strip clubs.
You know, I was there. There was no TV show for me.
You know, you know what an agent once told me that I had a state that was scared of
a small child. I'm the host of the Tonight Show.
He's going to do a lot of work.
Well, that's that's really where I think Roebuck does a good job in other.
But this is so hard to like emotional and possibly like meltdown Jay Leno.
Like, I still don't buy that.
Like what you're saying, like, I don't buy it does this in reality.
That is there is sad Leno.
I don't I don't think even in this scenario, he ever got one.
Oh, no. Yeah, I can't.
I don't see it. I could totally be wrong.
But yeah, he's I mean, he's playing it how you might play.
Like if you just heard that story, you go, oh, I can interpret what this would be like.
This person obviously is low status.
They're really conflicted because they're friends with Dave and they don't really
want to do this, but they want this job so bad.
Yeah. But from what we know and have seen with Leno,
yeah, give me a show if you want.
I'll take it if you don't want it.
I'll be over here.
Meanwhile, he obviously deeply wants to dead, but he's playing it.
He's the thing with Jay, I think, is he cannot not play it cool.
He's constantly playing everything cool.
He's not upset about this.
Oh, Conan, don't blame Conan.
Meanwhile, he's like, I guess they're going to give the show back to me.
I guess, you know, we'll find out.
This is probably a syndrome of just any biopath, like a walk the line syndrome
that they, you know, did a very funny job parroting in the walk hard.
If you if you were to read like the Robert McKee screenwriting book,
it's like, OK, the moment that Jay breaks out and takes control
and then like Jay's like, you know, Jay, that there's a scene in the movie
where Jay's triumphant and he hides, as we said, in the closet.
And he calls Warren Littlefield and tells him he heard everything in the meeting.
And Jay has a really good line that I have written down here.
Like this feels like that that arc.
They need that arc and the emotional arc.
And that's what you got to have that in the movie.
So that feels like take them all the way to the ground.
It's Jay's or him to the top.
It's Jay's journey to like see that Helen has been doing.
It's like Jesse on Breaking Bad now finally sees Walt has been bad for him.
And they have to have this.
Meanwhile, in my impression of Jay, it's just like Jay, you got to get rid of it.
OK. Yeah. OK.
She did what? Yeah.
You know, too bad.
But the line, of course, is
I may look stupid.
I may look stupid, but I'm Italian.
I know how to find information.
That's right, because he doesn't tip that he was like physically listening.
Yeah, he doesn't tell them he was in the closet.
Exactly what was said.
Yeah, that is is very sinister to hear like a transcript.
Oh, yeah. Like, how did you get that?
Because then Bob Balaban immediately makes a call and was like, we have a leak.
Yeah. We have this enormous proportions. Right.
I mean, yeah, let's talk about that.
This is I think I think the movie is made so that you can see
Helen Krishnik in action.
I think it's made because of this closet story.
This was a phenomenon.
I was a child at the time, but I believe in the industry.
This is what everyone was talking about after the book came out.
It's referenced in Larry Sanders.
Larry Sanders, I think, feeds into this movie getting made.
Do it's HBO. People like behind the scenes at a talk show.
This is a big story.
Looks like Larry Sanders shot similar.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, for sure.
So things are up in the air.
There is the possibility that even though Jay has been doing
the Tonight Show for a year, I'm not sure something in that range.
They aren't necessarily happy.
They aren't happy because of Helen, but he fires Helen.
So does this put me in the clear?
Well, not necessarily, because they maybe don't want to lose David Letterman.
And they maybe think Letterman could do a better job or they don't want him to
go off to another network, which is sort of what happened with Conan
and why they kept him in place.
So it's still possible that the rug gets pulled out from under Leno.
And then they give it to and there's this big meeting with all of the biggest
executives in Boca Raton, Florida.
But one person who works on the Tonight Show, Rick Ludwin,
and I say that name because he's apparently a very cool executive
who passed away. People speak highly of was part of Seinfeld.
And I'm such a nerd of all this stuff.
I got to meet him when I worked at Conan.
There was some scenario where like a bunch of all the people
went to go see the Pete Holmes show was being taped and he was there for some reason.
Wow. And I'm sure, oh, this is Rick.
I'm like, I, I know.
I've watched the late shift.
I know exactly who Jay followed you.
You prompted the closet situation, Rick Ludwin.
So anyways, he hears like, oh, this guy's going to be, oh, he's listening in
from L.A. to this Boca Raton meeting.
Oh, I get it.
And people say sarcastically, oh, guess what?
They're talking about.
He knows that he's going to if he goes and listens in on this meeting
or can get some info, this is where maybe the fate is being decided.
It's down in Boca Raton.
So he follows.
He finds wherever this office is.
It follows Rick Ludwin to this conference room and hides in a closet to get information.
This is one of those eye of the beholder kind of stories.
It's sort of Trumpian in a way where there's things that Trump did that people like
that you or I might say, well, he's like sniveling.
And that's like a pathetic story.
And other people say, oh, it's the ultimate show of strength.
Whatever that I'd say, that's everything with Trump.
It's like you could view it under those two lenses.
It's sort of similar where I think other comedians and other people
doing TV shows were like, oh, my God, he went to be like
snuck into a closet to hear what was going on with it.
That's pretty weird and pathetic.
I think he viewed it as like, oh, it's kind of cool.
And I was sneaking around and it was a spy movie.
And I can sort of see that, too, in a way.
Yeah, they also present the closet as more like a copy root.
Like I thought it would be a disgusting chemical broom filled like
like the closet, the gates of hell is the worst.
Well, like I feel like in in sitcoms or movies or shows set in an office,
someone ends up in a closet at some point and inevitably the like the door opens up
and everything like falls out.
Or so I thought it was going to be one of those kinds of like scenarios.
Maybe he had to like sneak in through a vent and then he gets covered in soot.
He's coughing up a storm.
And then he has to like pretend that he's like, what was that?
Somebody hears it and he has to make a gurgle like a water cooler.
So they don't know that it was a guy coughing.
Glug, glug. OK, just a water cooler.
And then he like shifts a little too much and a whole open can of paint
falls on his head.
Yeah, I was kind of picturing something more like that, as opposed to like,
well, there's a tiny desk in there and the photocopier's there and the time clock.
And I guess it is.
Closet is maybe a misnomer.
It is like a it's like a side utility support room.
Yeah. I just said it's closet.
What's it? Everyone just says closet.
You're not wrong. Yeah.
It's it's but it's like it's a it's a fancy.
It's like a closet.
There would be on Air Force One. Yeah.
This is no just doesn't a closet in your house is NBC.
It is a fancy closet. Yeah.
I think people somebody might have even worked in the closet.
I think there was even like a computer station there. Right.
But like an assist, like a page might have worked in the in this so-called.
Right. Yeah.
It's the closet is interesting because I also think there's a split.
There's a split, at least publicly in the comedy community.
There are those who are like Jay should have left.
He should have said I quit when Conan was gone.
I you're like Chris Rock.
I just get hit with a bug.
You're Chris Roxxon, like you're Jerry Seinfeld.
They're like there's like five of these jobs.
You hang on to it.
You get as you do whatever you can do to keep your job.
And then there's, of course, like people more like, you know,
I don't know, I can't even think of people are like Jay's pathetic for this.
Jay's all of his underhanded tactics.
Come on. This is ridiculous. Sure. Sure.
So and there's no closet scenario in the 2010 incident.
I don't believe I don't think so.
Come out yet.
It's yeah, there's no there's nothing as juicy as that.
There's just like Jay, which when Letterman making fun of him is like,
he's like when they tell you you're leaving, you don't just hang out in the lobby
and like, OK, I'll be over here if you need me.
Yeah, yeah.
That's the closest to it of like instead of Jay just saying like,
well, I quit if you're going to fire me and put Conan in.
And like when Conan was making his decision
and like, do I write this letter and blow up the entire thing?
I don't think there unless we just haven't heard it yet.
There were there weren't like suddenly like little sticky sounds
coming from under the table.
And he's like grappling in with Mission Impossible gear.
Jay and the human fly suit
that on the side of the building.
Oh, it's nothing.
It's that human fly.
It may have been a thing 20 years ago.
Simpson's joke that I didn't even don't worry about it or Jay.
It's a guy. It's it's one of those Hollywood Boulevard Spider-Man.
He's climbing up the he's climbing up the building.
Probably the fanny pack one.
Oh, it's you know, the tourists aren't allowed at this part of Universal.
Get out of here.
Jay driving Chitty Chitty Bang Bang by the building flying car.
That was one of my favorite Jay Leno's garage
where you revealed that he had the real chichi bang bang and that it does fly.
Of course. Yeah, yeah.
Fine. You know, I think that Colin,
what do you think of that Colin Powell?
Yeah, yeah, that was a great episode.
Colin Powell and Jay Leno flew in Chitty Chitty Bang Bang on CNBC.
Yeah, the best episode.
Chitty's a good car, family car, family car.
It doesn't get along with her.
We the love bug, but they human separate the parts of the garage.
So what?
I yeah, I mean, it's great to see this dramatized.
It's great to see it with, you know, it reminds me a lot of Tommy
of So's The Room, where he had he hatches the plan to record everything,
which he does. He sets up a he records like an answering machine.
He has this whole recording scheme that ends up not mattering
because he just confronts his fiance with information he got separately,
not on the tape.
But there's there's like great stuff with was so just looking like really satisfied.
Like, yeah, that's right.
You old dog, you're going to record.
And you sort of have the same thing with Leno.
Just like making like, yeah, that's right.
This is why they gave you this show, because you're smart.
See, Letterman wouldn't think to go sneaking around like old Jay.
To use like another wrestling reference or something that wrestlers do a lot is like
they point at their head like when they go like, I just did something good.
Like it's it's like a signal to the audience.
Like that like, oh, they did.
I got the brains. Exactly.
It's a perfect like it's a good thing for a heel to do.
And like there's like the guys behind them and they go, I just I.
And they're like, no, turn around.
Like that's really it.
But it is like those moments like cartoon moments,
cartoon character style moments where you're like, I can I.
You're really telegraphing what Jay thinks in this moment.
Well, that would have been that's the only thing that could have improved
the scene in the film is if he turned to camera for the first time in the movie
and pointed at his noggin and then maybe said,
hey, how's this for a headline?
Talk show host has best plan ever.
If he had invented headlines in this movie, it could have been better.
I don't know. We shouldn't get to plus maybe plus it up already.
But if he invented headlines, if he like gets, I don't know.
Yeah. All the different segments, Jay walking.
Well, that's what you want to see is the like the guy just said, Andy Kaufman.
But like man on the moon, you get to see it's mostly mostly in the 70s.
Most adult Jim Carrey, Andy Kaufman.
But you see a little of him like, oh, he put on a little show for his stuffed
animals. He was always entertaining.
And I think you that is something I would like to see is young
Leno, like what was the first headline with a misprint he saw
was the first that he like bumped into somebody on the street,
asked them a question and how you organically think of Jay walking.
Maybe you saw someone Jay walking.
You're under arrest for Jay walking.
Yeah, they were playing.
That's my name.
I mean, I floated during the pandemic that Scott Garner should be in charge
of the late shift TV show.
Oh, that's right. Oh, yeah.
That was the whole plan that it's that it's like a multi season. Right.
But that's it certainly could delve into all of it. Yeah.
With that. And then flash forward, like it started better call Saul flash forward
to like the Conan situation, but it's mostly in the past for now.
Yeah. But then, yeah.
And black and white as with Saul, like black and white, what he's doing now.
Right. Kind of after the main.
I guess it could flash forward to you bet your life now. Yeah.
Actually, well, it'd be a fake out where, you know, you're seeing Saul Goodman
sad working at the mall in his bad little condo.
And you have that with Leno, where he's like, look at himself in the mirror.
Like, what have I done?
What have I been? Right.
Then like kind of splashes water on his face.
All right. Ready?
He puts up opens the closet that's entirely denim clothes.
The Tuesday, please.
And then he wants to go down and has another great day of meeting classic car
guys and hosting art shows.
He walks out of the garage, which just has a stack of money.
He goes, not touching you today.
And then he gets in the car and leaves.
I don't need it.
Oh, part of the plan. Thanks. But no, thanks.
That's another Breaking Bad illusion.
When? Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. When Skylar takes Walter to see the giant stack of cash. Exactly.
Do you think that ever happened with Mavis that like, I want you to see something?
I think this this is your tonight show.
I think how much is enough?
Can I touch it already?
I like to think it's more like the dark night when Joker is like sliding down
the money, that giant money pile, I guess he's setting it on fire, though, too,
which I guess maybe Jay's doing.
Yeah. Some people just want to watch the world.
It's not about the money.
It's about reading headlines.
Yeah. Either of those work perfectly, though.
Yeah. He does have a warehouse in Burbank full of dollar bills
and he does something with it.
And I don't know. It's either.
Yeah. Slide down it or just show Mavis every few weeks.
He might burn. Maybe he'll burn it eventually to make a point.
I'm going to burn the money.
I use it to power my model T.
Do you want to hear I got these cars?
Oh, that was real good.
Wow. Perfect. Rhymes and everything.
Yeah. No.
Would have been good without the rhyme, but it was perfect.
Wow. You know, since I just said it, I just
I just I just said the name.
And if we say it several times, maybe she'll appear.
Mavis Mavis Mavis, the queen lady, Macbeth herself,
the player behind the scenes.
She didn't show up.
But we have but now now she's been addressed and we have to talk about it.
Mavis, Jay Leno's wife.
When we were warming up, Jay's testing the microphones.
Jason, you did your warm up was on screen.
Mavis screen Mavis.
And that is an important detail.
I'm glad you caught it that this is Jay Leno's wife.
One of the biggest like mystery areas of the entire tale.
It is pretty crazy to see that an actress was hired to play Mavis Leno.
Not mentioned by name.
Yeah, not mentioned by name.
Was it was she on IMDB?
I don't know. I don't think I didn't see the actress listed.
Not sure. Mavis, very fascinating.
The most prominent Mavis has ever been is in the is it CBS?
Do you know what I'm talking about?
When they did kind of a make good like like let's tell the J side of the story
and turn him into not a villain.
And some CBS news piece where Jay again is like, I'm not mad at anybody, whatever.
And Mavis is furious.
Maybe it is like Jay doesn't deserve this.
It's the most you've ever heard from Mavis, because like you would talk about Mavis
for so long, you never saw her and you think she was like a made up character.
Like that's in my younger brain.
I was like, well, Mavis must be fake.
Not on this interview.
Mavis is on fire in this interview.
She's trying to defend her man.
She doesn't feel it's fair what Jay has been painted as.
He's just doing what NBC wanted.
Is Mavis a little like Helen?
Is that the secret? That's interesting.
He gets the fire from the women in his life.
That's interesting.
Stand up for him in a way that he doesn't stand up for himself.
Perhaps it is. I'm not sure.
This is the only one.
Yeah, one interview was with Mavis.
So I don't know.
I would have loved to watch 10 Mavis interviews, but I don't think they exist.
She as a kid,
an adolescent, when I when I was coherent enough to know Mavis Leno,
I also kind of think of her in the same vein as like Stedman, Oprah's partner.
Oh, yeah, you hear about them.
You know, Stedman, I think you saw more.
Yeah, for sure.
I like I had a very clear I knew what Stedman looked like for many years.
Mavis, I had no idea.
Yeah, not a lot of info.
I'm going to say something else from the Bulls Eye with Jesse Thorne,
where he had Jalen one and he mentions the story that's apparently from the late
shift book, not reflected in the film.
Kudos to him for bringing this up to Leno personally.
He says, oh, you know, I read in the late shift book that not only you don't
it's not just the you don't touch the tonight show money, you also you don't
relax, you're working when you're not doing the tonight show, you're out doing
stand up and that you've never taken a vacation with your wife.
Yeah, they never
did his wife, who they have been married for four years.
Yeah, there's no divorce in the picture as far as anyone knows.
It's all pretty secretive.
But yeah, he would like like he's got a hiatus from the tonight show.
You'd say like, oh, yeah, go to Hawaii.
I'm going to go do stand up in Peoria.
He just like would he just couldn't.
And he happily he doesn't say to Jesse like, how dare you bring that up?
He's like, yeah, well, you know, you know, I said that Seinfeld.
One time we agreed that if we ever went to a beach,
maybe the worst thing that could happen, we might get to like it.
Which Seinfeld similarly like just like the odd, crazy character.
And I like who all both of them kind of make you go like,
maybe you don't want to be one of the most successful standups ever.
Yeah, you are guaranteed to be weird and miserable.
That there's there are comedians in cars getting coffee with Jay is
is very fascinating, too, because Jay says he won't wear sunglasses
because he doesn't trust the world if he's wearing sunglasses.
I'm paraphrasing it, but that is what he says.
And even Jerry is, you know, the big weirdo is just like, OK, what?
Well, because it also comes with that he's never had coffee.
Yeah, right. He doesn't take vacations.
He's never had coffee and he doesn't wear sunglasses
because they skew your vision of the world.
Again, I'm not comparing them because I do think one is evil
and the other is just interesting, but it is Trumpian in its weird.
Those just things that are off the table for Trump.
The weird beliefs and the you only have so much energy in your body.
And your heart only beats so many beats.
It's a finite number of beat.
This is Trump philosophy.
It only beats a finite number of beats.
So you don't want to waste it exercising.
That is a belief of Donald Trump.
Run through them too fast. Right.
These certain little ticks certainly have me interested.
I mean, I don't I forgot.
You've told me the sunglasses thing before.
I mean, Jay is endlessly fascinating as a person.
Yeah, just endlessly.
Why is just why he's turned into such like a character and looms
so large in our brains.
It makes you go like, well, what do you like, man?
But we know the answer to that.
He likes a reasonably priced, like fast, casual.
He likes getting a double cheeseburger.
He likes cars. He likes.
Here's what he likes. Cars.
He likes double cheeseburgers.
He likes making intern jokes.
And that's he made it during the warm up when he did not have to make.
But when we saw him, you know, toward the end of the tonight show,
he in the warm up made like two Monica Lewinsky jokes.
Unbelievable. In 2000.
What was it?
In Sabbath? No, it was later than that.
It was 20.
Did I saw him stand up in 2014?
He definitely did a Monica Lewinsky.
Yeah, for sure. He loves her and he loves that.
Yeah. Yeah.
So like that stuff he loves.
But yeah, it is.
He's fascinating.
I wonder if he's still never gone on a vacation with Mavis.
Even post-retirement.
After all that, did he not think to maybe take a trip?
It makes sense, though, the read that it's comedy.
Like it's fact that we you will see him in Burbank because he's that's all he does.
He drives around here.
But not her.
But yeah, I've never seen her in the car.
They don't live in Burbank.
Don't they live in? They live close by here.
Do they? The Beverly Hills, actually.
I was surprised to find out. Yeah.
I thought they lived more in Glendale.
I am fascinated. I feel betrayed by the.
Yeah, I'm betrayed by that.
I mean, is the garage.
It's up in the hills, though, because I've seen him on Mulholland as well.
Like eight years ago, my friend was visiting and we made a joke.
We were driving on Mulholland.
Well, of course, you take your people,
it's beautiful view of the city.
And we saw an old timey car coming.
And we said, ha ha ha, this could be Jay Leno.
And it was it was Jay.
So he must have because Beverly Hills, I'm assuming he lives probably closer up the hill.
Because what is that, cold water?
Yeah, probably. He probably lives off the canyons cut through it.
Oh, Beverly Glend cuts through.
I thought he looked more here.
But the big dog garage is in Burbank.
Jay's in Beverly Hills.
Let's cut to the chase. He fucks the cars, right?
Look, look, tell us all this time.
So he and Jerry, they both have like 500 cars, right?
Each. Mm hmm.
All right. I didn't even want to bring Jerry into it.
But yes, absolutely.
Now I can't elevator in New York.
He has like there's like a fake brownstone.
And you're right. Right.
Three story elevator car garage.
Then he's like this guy when I was playing Grand Theft Auto online
that invited me, Susser, Tim Chang and Anthony Geo
into his car garage in the game to show off a three story car.
Like he had bought all these cars in game or like it's a similar thing.
But in real life, Jerry has some like elaborate, crazy car thing.
That's what I've heard. I don't think there's any pictures of it.
I I think I saw like a diagram.
I think a show talked about it with like a lifestyle.
So it's kind of show.
I'll tell you this.
I took the boat tour at Lake Arrowhead once when I was up there
and they were talking about it was clearly the place
to buy vacations home in the 90s because they're like that house
used to be Michael Eisner's.
That house used to be Eric LaSalle's.
That used Sammy Hagar is kind of people.
I think Sammy Hagar was the one that people in town were so annoyed by him
because he bought two massive lakefront homes and then connected
like made a Frankenstein house and I like painted with flames.
And I they weren't happy about it.
The one that stuck out in my mind was they're like that house used to be Jay
Leno's and I think the number was the garage can hold 27 cars.
Whoa. 27 cars up there.
This is like winding roads.
A vacation, though.
That oh, I suppose.
I don't know if it's a home, though.
I don't know if I see maybe.
Yeah, I know. That's not a vacay.
If you live there, you know, you're right.
Not a vacation. Yeah, that's true.
Well, I mean, I feel like there's a lot of work getting 27 fucking cars up to
like the the mountain towns outside of L.A.
Like it's kind of a pain in the ass up there.
Like you go on a vacation to escape up there and it's like there's one grocer.
There's like treacherous driving.
He sends Mavis to Hawaii and he puts a wig on the hood of the car.
Is what Scott's getting at.
I think so. Yeah, it's this long path where there's not a lot of people
and it's just secluded and you can just be alone with your thoughts
or with your cars.
I'm going to here's what I'm going to do.
I'm going to bring up this photo I showed you earlier,
and I'm going to slide my baby son out of it so that he's not part of this filth.
Look how many pipes are on this thing.
I mean, take your pick.
You got one for every day of the week.
That's just this single car.
You're getting into my weird obsession territory, and that is one or two channels
down from the bigger Big Dog Garage shadow.
Yeah, I look, I I shouldn't throw stone.
You know, I have a very it's especially after the last couple of years.
I have a very impressive wall of toys.
Some would say that's excessive.
So somebody might say the same thing about me is he having sex with his Doc Brown toy
when he sends Lindsey to Hawaii.
I mean, nobody here was saying that about you.
No, I'm just saying I've heard people whispering in Burbank,
and it's not true, first of all, but I'm just saying so at all.
I think you're in the volunteering of it just makes it seem more real.
Does he kiss a master splinter on the mouth?
Both his movie version of Mathers
Masters Splinter and his 1987 or 1989 animated series version.
Master Splinter saw him at the grocery store with the gold member
McFarland toys again.
Does he see how many
Ninja Turtles can line up on certain body parts?
How many can he family can the answers?
Their arms around.
Wait, are you picturing like the human sushi kind of table?
But it's Mike lying in Ninja Turtles across itself.
Well, I was picturing them specifically located in one spot.
Oh, that's better.
That's that nicer.
That's a more wholesome one.
Yeah. Yeah.
I yeah.
And has Mike gotten to be a pro to where he can lay them all on himself?
Or does he need somebody to help?
And that's not a sexual thing.
That's just a like that's you're just the helper.
Look, what you're saying is not true, but I have heard people say it.
So I don't want to be mad.
I don't want to say Jay's doing anything on toll untoward with the cars.
Look, people go.
I'm not I'm not trying to shame you for this.
People go crazy when they're doing these shows.
Nobody nobody doing a prominent show, whether it be the Tonight Show
or this theme park podcast that we do.
If you're if you're in a in a high pressure, high octane
performance situation, people start to lose their minds a little.
And it's, you know, better, I'd say better than losing it to drugs and alcohol.
Then I'd say better to lose it to
draping yourself in action figures.
Yeah. Well, sending your girlfriend on false trips.
Yeah. Look, it's it's not true.
I just want to say it's not true.
But is it true for Jay?
You be the judge.
You listener, you be the judge.
But it's not true for me.
It's just want to let let that sit there for a while.
It's just been some whispers about some.
Yeah.
I've been in Burbank comics.
I've been in some picadillo.
Yeah, I've been to the big Bob's Big Boy and I've heard all the rumors.
Yeah. In the booth.
I've been sitting in the booth and I can hear.
So the sewing circle down there.
It's like a party line, the gossip down the gossip at the Bob's
Big Boy in Burbank, please.
Yeah, it's fast.
I would love to know the number of cars both of them own.
Who owns more Jerry or Jay?
Oh, it's got to be Jay.
It's got to be Jay.
Hi, are you sure? Jay Leno.
I'm not sure.
Jerry is so rich from that show.
I guess that everything he's Jerry takes vacations.
That's true. Jerry is.
I guess he involved Jay involved him in this beach scenario.
But I do think that he's relaxed since the show a little more. Right.
I think Leno just like, OK, they took my show away the next weekend.
I'm in Atlantic City. That's true.
Yes, that's true for sure.
That Jerry Jerry's like a Hamptons guy.
Jerry's hanging out with all Ted Sarandos and all the heavy hitters.
Yeah. In the hand, I call that a vacation.
Sure. Yeah. So that's that's more vacation to me.
Speaking of vacations there, I think there's a weird.
Did you guys catch this?
There's a pretty solid, subtle.
I think it's meant to be a callback joke in the movie where like Jay
gets off a plane and Lake Tahoe, he's playing a show in Lake Tahoe.
And he takes a call there.
And later in the movie, when someone's like arguing with Letterman,
they go like, oh, what do you want to be doing with your life, David?
You want to be playing Lake Tahoe or something like they make fun of the thing
that Jay was doing.
This is also. Yeah.
This is also kind of a fake thing, too, I feel like,
because Jay was very popular and very successful.
Like they really try to make it seem like he was like really slumming it before.
But that's not my he was constantly doing Letterman guest appearances.
And constantly selling out shows.
He was very well known playing the biggest venue.
Yeah, he was very well known before that.
Obviously, he wanted to tonight.
Yeah. And he was in the hit film Collision Course.
Of course. Of course.
We know that he was a star of the screen as well as the stage.
But they really try to like sad sack it up, like, man,
they pulled this guy out of the gutter.
But like, well, I think in the long run, I think his sob story
of the clubs, I think.
I think that is all true.
Yeah, sure. He tells weird stories about like he's doing a, you know,
like he's doing stand up for at a library and there's no microphone.
For three people. And that's all.
I just don't think like right.
Yeah, I think you've been successful for a few years.
A pretty success, especially when he was doing guest
because he was guest hosting for a little while there, too.
When there's any disdain in the movie for Leno, it's fun.
I like in the when Dave is making his ultimate decision of do I
take the Tonight Show now that it's maybe back on the table
or do I start my my own new thing?
And he says, I don't want to, you know, I don't I just I don't want to lose the
I can't lose this thing again.
You know, I don't want to lose it first to Jay Leno.
Says it was such to say it's a great performance from Higgett,
just like chewing on the
which to get back into stuff in the movie or in reality.
Again, the ping pong match that that happens, they never offer it to Letterman.
They make a secret deal with Leno.
Letterman gets angry and starts to look elsewhere.
He's offered shows by everywhere.
He ends up getting an offer from CBS.
He wants to take it.
But he has one last conversation with the big boss of NBC.
And suddenly he's offered the Tonight Show.
They do just say, actually, do you want to do it?
And Leno's been on the air for a while.
His closet fears were justified.
They did end up deciding we are going to take it away from Leno and give it to them.
That is kind of a mind blow that they were just like, yeah, sure.
Yeah, you know what? All right.
Let us not screw it.
We're doing that.
And it is what happened again later, like in the with Leno and Conan,
that it was just like, yeah, screw it.
Like, like in both scenarios, NBC has been so flippant.
We've had this plan. We built this set and everything.
But like, yeah, you know, I never mind.
Well, yeah. And then they offer it to him on a timetable, though, which is great.
Crazy, too. Like I think if you were like it, maybe when I first saw this movie,
I went into it thinking like and the big climax is that Jay gets the show.
But Jay gets the show early.
Yeah. In the timeline, there's still so much weirdness.
Act. Yeah. Yeah.
And it's all just like, and you know the ending, right?
Because the shows are on.
We know that Letterman went to CBS.
There's no Tarantino and Glorious Basterds version
for Letterman gets the Tonight Show.
Although in your version, I think there should be and like takes a flamethrower to.
Yes. Well, he takes on all his enemies.
You see executives.
What he likes to do is.
Yes. You know,
I didn't say good night, Jay.
I did not realize that like Letterman beat Leno for.
It seemed like until two years or nearly until they in the movie, they pin it to like,
well, the Hugh Grant thing really skyrocketed.
Jay, they didn't even.
Yes. Yeah.
They didn't even mention the OJ thing was likely just happening when this.
Oh, that's true. That's the long term.
Yeah. So Jay was such a baboon for.
Yeah. Yeah.
This is one of those things that does not make any sense to me now
that it was all not going so good and Letterman's been in every night.
And then Hugh Grant comes on and Leno says, what the hell are you thinking?
And it's all different from there.
What are you talking about?
That seems so and we're maybe Jason, you're onto something where
that's sort of this like folksy version of it.
That doesn't make any sense.
How could that one end like as I described that now,
what sounds interesting enough about that to turn the entire fortunes of a TV show around?
Yeah, that obsessed with Hugh Grant and prostitute.
That was everyone was.
I do remember watching that live.
I have a really distinct memory of watching that live.
Yeah. Well, it was a monoculture.
I mean, everything was a lot smaller and popular.
If there's any. Yeah.
I mean, I think the way it's treated now is that that was some sort of magic thing
that unlocked the reality is, is that that slot is for people,
for older people that like a gentler touch and find maybe that fully exposed people
that Jay is a gentler touch than what is my mom would always be like that.
David Letterman is so sarcastic.
Yeah, she did. And that's my family stick.
That's absolutely I think the reason Jay ended up on top is because Jay shaved off
because Jay was a little edgier if you watch his old like Letterman appearances.
Jay sort of shaved those edges off of his own performance.
And I think it's slowly.
I think that's the perfect moment when like more eyes were on him.
I don't know if I don't know how the ratings broke down.
I'm sure it's more complicated than just that one.
And then it was perfect from there.
But it is it is maybe the moment when more moms were like this.
Jay, I like him. He's being a little cheeky with Hugh.
But like that that story, I do think captured moms' imaginations everywhere
because they all loved Hugh Grant. My mom loved Hugh Grant.
Uh huh. Moms across the nation loved this man Hugh Grant.
And then he was with a prostitute, like couldn't wrap their head.
A Hollywood an actor in Hollywood with a prostitute.
Like it just blew suburban moms minds.
Yeah. And it all converged in a perfect moment with a nicer talk show host
being a little cheeky with him. Letterman would have been really like severe about it.
But this was a cute little way to say it.
Yeah. And I think that have fun together.
I'm sure the numbers break down differently, but I bet that's all.
It's a big stew.
And it all adds up to that moment.
That's when you can point to, at least where it's like the Tonight Show needs to be
about like settling differences, everybody being nice.
If there's somebody you disagree with, maybe ruffle their hair playfully.
Zach, that's what the Tonight Show is simpler times before the president
has enough of the United States as a fair with porn pornography actor.
So when that's just the tip of the iceberg, the awful.
Yeah, it was outrageous what the British man did with the British man
from four weddings and a funeral.
Did your moms like Hugh Grant?
Do you remember that?
I do have a distinct. My mom really liked Hugh Grant.
I my parents stopped following popular culture.
OK, like we did.
They only went to the movies if we wanted to see them.
I'd like to know left at the listener out there.
Did your mom like Hugh Grant?
My mom, I don't I don't know if she ever spoke on that subject,
but I do remember a lot of like, oh, you know who I just love is that Mel Gibson.
OK, what a nice upstanding Christian.
That is a role model.
That is a good man.
Interesting. He's a little handsome, too. Sure.
That doesn't hurt. That is the.
My mom like Tom Cruise a lot.
And then I think the couch stuff, I think she wasn't so into it after that.
Did your mom have an actor, though?
She even an older interesting question.
Oh, I'm trying to make crushes.
Mom crushes. You know what?
It's funny. I didn't put together.
I saw his name in the credits and I but I didn't put together.
That was him in the movie because they look so young.
My mom was vacationing like on a tiny island in New England.
And she's like, they were treat Williams was here filming a movie.
And I think it's called the senator of the Congress.
It's on like it's one of those movies now that you can find on
Canopy and Hoopla, Netflix and like Pluto.
And it's it's on all streaming services.
But she was very excited to see Treat Williams.
OK, Reed Williams, I think was he on Everwood?
Was he the father on that? Oh, I don't know.
Show Everwood.
My mom did have a run her and my brother, I feel like.
It felt like I went off to college and I came back and it's like,
oh, we watch all this.
The WB show we watch on the scene.
Oh, I was like, oh, OK.
Everyone in the house is really into Gilmer girls now.
I go I go out of town for three months.
Everything changes.
A lot has changed.
Let's talk about Treat Williams is as Michael Overt's a little bit,
because the main thing I realized when I was watching this, this is this like
just very like it's just such a slick, well spoken agent portrayal.
The most in control person, the most the nicest dressed, sharp haircut.
And I realized like I've now had two occasions on which to
pick between several people who is going to be my agent.
And I just realized I think both times I have picked somebody based on
who most resembles Treat Williams as Michael Overt's.
If you if I were to show you pictures of both of the people
who have been my agent, like you go, yeah, totally.
Scott's got a type that is like Jason's mom.
Yeah, I got a treat on the brain.
Yeah, the only one who likes treats.
In the family.
I yeah, I I think the stories about real life,
Michael Overt's are a little less hinged.
I would I would say the portrayal is going to be very hinged.
Like, yeah, yeah, so calm.
Yeah, so collected.
It makes me personally angry that a star of your stature has been treated.
This is what I want people to be saying about me.
It makes me personally angry that a star of Scott's stature
has been treated this poorly by.
I assume that's what they're all saying in places.
But yes, then the real life, Michael Overt's goes to Disney,
essentially replaces Katzenberg.
Yes. Correct.
But sort of shits the bed or isn't allowed to really do much of anything.
They really made no impact.
Do anything.
I think it's after I think it coincides with Eisner's heart problems.
But Eisner still like is not sharing a lot of responsibility.
Yeah. Yeah. Didn't learn anything.
Yeah. Well, I'll address this in the Eisner film.
I think every I think everyone was still a little sad
and didn't know what to do with Frank Wells going.
And then like every there's a lot of feelings of betrayal by like Katzenberg.
Kind of Brianna Maynard.
Like his golden parachute out of there, which was litigated for years.
The money that he was by simple contracts, probably owed those millions of dollars.
At Katzenberg or Overt's.
Katzenberg. Well, both of them, I think.
Yeah. Right.
About Overt's that he got such a massive severance
and then stockholders tried to stop it.
Like, why is our money going to that?
But then it held up that he did keep it.
Yeah. And I think the same thing happened with like,
I think Katzenberg had negotiated like, you know,
I am entitled to X percentage if these movies are successful.
And those movies were so successful.
The gold. The second Golden Age of Disney.
Animation is right. Right.
And they tried to stiffen on it when he let like when he was getting out of there.
Yeah. Yeah.
Deal's a deal. Yeah.
He's entitled to that and he's entitled to his cut of the Roku sale.
That's right. And Roku bought 50 stages of freight,
50 states of freight, whatever it is.
Yeah. And the check.
I bought the golden arm. Yeah.
Give him his $21.
But so, yeah, Overt's weird run at Disney doesn't work out so well.
Then he starts some other like agency type thing.
And then it falls apart and he flames out in this horrible way
where he says all these insane things, including the phrase that
that really jumps out where he gave this weird interview.
And he said that his downfall was brought about by the gay mafia.
This horrible phrase that has stuck to him ever since.
That's such an insane thing.
That's like even in the 90s where you watch like 90s comedies and you're like,
oh, man, how that joke wouldn't fly nowadays.
But like, just I'm surprised there wasn't like a Zucker Brothers
ripoff movie called the gay mafia. Oh, yeah.
She's they're all in the suits, but they're pink.
Oh, my God. I can I can I just the whole movie's been written now in my head.
I can see all of it.
What a nightmare.
You know, Dom DeLuis is in there. Oh, yeah.
He's ammin it up. Sure.
I love all the like the setting up the thing.
We can't stop people from talking to us.
We reverse the process.
And he's not even thinking about what he's saying.
He's just like washing his hands or whatever and being fastidious.
Like Gus and Breaking Bad.
It's like, I know I'm like re evaluating the way that a TV show can be sold.
And then you get this great parade of people from all the networks.
CBS, who ends up
getting work, they ended up getting Letterman.
But then you get Eiger, you get your little Eiger portrayal.
What do we think of this Eiger portrayal?
It doesn't seem right, does it?
Well, he wasn't as known then. Yeah.
Really? They're they're basing it on a photograph.
Yeah, it's like the guy is like to like you like kind of a like surfery guy.
Like, not like a bro, but like he's like really like a hair flowy, handsome.
Eiger is much more like kind of buttoned down handsome guy.
But he was a mover and shaker at ABC, like that.
Sure. Yeah. Not owned by Disney at that point,
because if you notice, they mentioned Eisner coming into pitch Disney.
Eiger is there on the have of ABC.
Still two entities.
I think Cap City was the name of the owners of ABC.
And so like, yeah, Eiger is because Eiger was so like well regarded at ABC.
And I'd like climb the ranks that like when they got bought by Disney,
that like he, you know, got in pretty, pretty quick.
Yeah. I mean, so this guy's embodying like the kind of like slick Eisner guy,
but maybe is not accurate to like what Eisner's essence is.
Yeah. Yeah. There's no Eisner. There's not a false Eisner.
There's no Eisner in this work.
And you got to dock a lot of points, not just some a lot of points.
Yeah. I bet I have to give this movie a D because there's no Eisner trail in it.
Yeah, that's a real bummer.
But you got a little Eiger, you get a little fake Eiger.
You get a you get Mr. Ernst from Hey Dude, somebody.
He's like a syndication guy, but Letterman does not want to be on.
He hates syndication. Letterman hates and then Jay, of course, now is syndicated.
That's right. He's happy to do it.
Again, the difference between the two men.
You also have a portrayal of
Brandon Tartikoff, an Eisner figure that we've talked about.
Right. So showed up as himself in things.
And again, I would question the accuracy, unfortunately, because I am so
we're all so versed in Brandon Tartikoff.
Yeah, of course, because he did so many as we have yet to do.
Yeah. Talk more about his intro. Right.
Is his sort of Eisner like intros and stuff video like his
he performed a little bit is what we hosted Saturday Night Live.
Well, yes. Yeah.
And then he would. Yeah. He'd show up in very special episodes.
Right. And he was on Alf. He made a solid Alf appearance. Yes.
So that one's not.
So, you know, I do.
You got look, you got the executives or I'm sorry,
you got the host, Leno and Letterman close and you did your prosthetics
and your wigs. Let's get closer with these executives.
We all know them. Yeah.
We they're icons to us. We know Tartikoff.
We know Iger. Yeah.
I'm sure it pulled people right out of the movie when they saw these.
They were like, that's not Bob Iger.
No, so many people.
That's not his. That's not right.
They turned it right off.
Facial structure whatsoever.
But that's all fun.
Then you've got somebody you have somebody playing himself.
I want to give this a shout out.
Another person I love who I always love a good cameo.
Oh, yeah. It's so weird.
He doesn't get anything to do. Little Richard.
It's just a connective tissue piece that is nothing.
Helen has been fired. Yeah.
And then Jay gives a speech to the crew to say, I'm sorry about that.
All Helen thing.
And in the middle, it's just like a little slice of life
meant to show that the tonight show is back and better than ever.
Jay, all those problems are in the past.
And now he's having a good old time with Little Richard.
And it's so weird.
But all Jay's doing is like, OK, that was a little richer.
OK, we'll see you tomorrow.
And Little Richard is just going, whoo, yeah, whoo.
And I just like to imagine that that's what a full seven minute segment was.
Just them kind of like teetering around and slapping their knees and yelling,
whoo, there were no stories.
He just came out and started doing that for maybe for two seconds.
The funnier. Yeah, that's a funnier way to do it.
Yeah, that's funny to.
Well, it's funny to contrast the scene of Jay with a guest with earlier
in the movie with David Letterman and Sandra Bernhardt. Oh, yeah.
Like, don't be a what's your fucking brought?
Tell it to your therapist.
Cards as I hate myself. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Do you think and I wonder, is there a deleted scene
where Jay talks to Little Richard because it feels like there should be
where you think I should do a little Richard? What do you think?
Yeah. Oh, yes.
A little bit like whatever.
Like, I don't know, because it feels like such a I mean,
you got to do what you got to walk up a little bit.
There you go. Yeah, that's better.
Yeah. Thanks so much.
And then they're like, that's the impetus for him getting rid of Helen or something.
It feels like Larry Sanders in this moment, too, where this would always
look, Larry, it would be the show.
And then they cut like to that close up, like in the Sandra Bernhardt scene
where there would be a little scene.
But you get Little Richard on, you're not going to do any talking with it.
It feels like there may be something cut here. I could be wrong.
Love to dying for that.
I would watch every. Yeah.
From this. Is there like an old DVD with outtakes?
I don't believe so. Yeah.
I don't think that was I don't think HBO was keeping an eye on that kind of thing.
There's not a hunger for that.
It hasn't entered the criterion yet.
I mean, it will post. It's in our personal.
I mean, if we're discussing it in the criterion closet.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Where's a late shift in here?
Like just like frantically throwing the DVDs, Blu-rays on the floor.
I got I got the real 10 months and you know, late shift, obviously.
And we don't have that in here.
Oh, yeah, you do. I have it. I brought it.
I brought it on the shelf. I got it somewhere else.
You're going to put a bunch of
classic films in a closet and not include the ultimate film
hinging on a closet.
And you have both. That's a very good point.
Sorry. There's a gap between Lestrade and the Nels.
Do you think.
Long live.
I mean, you have a long goodbye.
Late. I'm just not seeing it.
Did who is in here was a bill hater in here earlier and he took it.
Is there anything you didn't have anymore?
Yeah, people. Yeah, people just they do the videos and then they just pocket
the DVD onto these guys.
Yeah, yeah, that must be the only reason.
Right. If you on the room and you pick out DVDs, you have to leave with them.
Right. I think so.
You really you do.
I mean, they are criterion so they can just replace them.
Yeah, I feel like I'm a way.
I always thought that they got to keep it.
You know, you don't know what we're talking about.
There's videos, those little videos.
I think they're paid in the stack of DVD.
There's videos that we don't know on YouTube for the Criterion Collection,
which is like, you know, like they make an whatever
prestige version of a Blu Ray release or DVD release of an old movie
that they think is like a classier movie or something or as a merit.
And then they send a celebrity into this closet with all their prestige things
and they pick out things they like.
But I think they get to keep it.
It's so you think it's like it's a cash grab.
It's like a money booth.
It's like when the kids at KB Toys would get to put whatever they want
in their cart because they had a shopping spree.
It's like a gifting. Yeah.
But it's a much more it's like they pick five.
They don't throw everything into the basket.
Amoeba Records has a like what's in my bag sort of thing, too,
with musicians and actors and stuff.
I'm not sure they keep that.
They keep those. That might be it.
They may have to pay. But they might.
Yeah, they might just buy them because they want them. Right.
They just start shopping.
I don't know.
Do we know anyone who's been on the Criterion Closet series?
Yeah, I don't know if we do.
If I get a meeting with Bill Hader, that's the first thing I'll ask.
Meeting with him to be his assistant.
I hope not. I hope I have it.
I mean, nice job. You can get it.
Wala Sean has been in the closet, right?
We don't know him.
And that's true. We don't.
Which I know you beat yourself up every day.
Yeah, I self-flagellate every day.
I take I take shredder and I poke myself with shredder every day
that I'm not good friends with Wala Sean.
But that's not a sex thing.
That is a non-sexual self-flagellation for not being friends
with Da Vinci code. You're doing it for your sin.
Exactly. Six years ago, Andre Gregory and Wala Sean in the Criterion Closet.
Go right to YouTube.
That is the mildest thing anyone's ever slapped their knee about.
Wow. Andre.
Nobody's ever raised their voice about Andre Gregory before.
The closest has come is when when we saw a play that was directed
by Andre Gregory, starring and written by Wala Sean and Ryan Perez
went up to Andre Gregory.
This one's becoming it.
Have I sold it more than twice?
I was listening to an episode where you told it and I know you've told it before.
That's such a fun. I love the story so much.
You're obsessed with Ryan Perez.
I'm so excited about it.
With that, have I even told another Ryan Perez story
other than in the Andre Gregory context?
I don't know. But I know you've told that one.
I love it. It was his birthday.
It was Andre Gregory's birthday.
OK. Oh, the cake. You weren't sure.
You keep telling this.
I've never seen this movie and I don't know who Andre Gregory is.
I know about the movie.
But you tell this as if like, guys, Andre Gregory.
It's so fun.
I'm sure it's good. He seems like so nice.
Yeah. He was telling people at the party, you have to come up to the lake.
We've told this story.
We have to talk about it. It's so fun.
Anyway, what?
Just because it's two hours into the late shift episode of our theme park podcast.
I shouldn't might not have time for our already told Andre Gregory material.
What do we do?
Oh, OK, here's what I got.
The music in the movie. Oh, yeah.
I have a couple of selects.
Yes, good. Yes.
The music is like if you ever see Larry Sanders, it's such a night.
The theme to Larry Sanders is such a very like early 90s sort of synthesized.
What would you call the genre of music?
Yeah, like like I was going to say the phrase uptown funk.
That's not correct. That's a song.
No, you could call any song heard in that show or this movie uptown.
That's true. Yeah.
Uptown.
You know, Larry Sanders.
Yeah.
I don't think I'm going to be able to be with all like that.
See, though, because this is when the hip cats come out.
Yeah, it's all like Casio groove.
But like very like it sounds cheesy and I don't I like it, but it sounds kind of cheesy.
This movie is filled with those type of grooves,
but then also like stuff that's a little sexy.
There's like sort of like, yeah, kind of like a little like film.
It's like there are cues that would play after like the
like the film Fatale.
Yeah, but it plays when fake Jay Leno is driving a classic car.
Yeah. So here's two.
I have two of them and hopefully you can hear this.
I just really appreciate this.
It's just awfully nice of you.
Yeah.
Thanks. Good luck, Dave.
This is for rich little as Johnny Carson talking to you.
Your red shoe diaries.
It is.
It sounds like Axel Foley got his badge and gun taken away,
but met with his confidential informant anyway.
Like, it sounds like a cop movie.
Yeah, but it is sexy.
Like we just watched Beverly Hills Cop actually a couple of months ago,
but it's just a little sexy.
It's a little sexier.
It's it's like treading the line.
This one is a little bit more what I was just talking about.
It's like I got a groove to it and it's a little longer of a clip.
OK.
This is like the climax of the movie, too, when they're walking from NBC to CBS.
But this sounds like a little like Letterman.
Yeah, but also a little like tonight at the Megadome.
Leigh Hawn's big.
And welcome to Epcot Center.
Sin horns.
Yeah, tonight, Bobcat Gold weight.
Like, yeah, so like that there's it's full.
The movie is full of stuff like that.
Sexy stuff like that first one or like detective stuff like that.
Whatever you want to call it.
When you're dealing with Johnny Carson,
an intimate conversation with Johnny Carson and David Letterman.
But yeah, the music in the whole thing, I wish that soundtrack was available.
Well, I have the main theme burrowed into my brain.
Yeah.
I don't know why it again.
Like, what is that?
Do we again?
We might be muddying the waters.
Are we making fun of it or not?
I think it is just this like, yeah, it's this pleasant movie.
You'd never call this like an edgy movie or hard to watch movie.
It's just like you're in all these like peach rooms
looking at guys in brown suits who get kind of mad at each other, but not that much.
Even Helen doesn't.
She pushes everything off the desk at some point, but like
nobody's really at risk of getting hurt.
It's such a TV movie.
Yes. And every way the best way.
Yeah. Production wise, it's not something that looks like a major like.
I appreciate that about the movie that they didn't like
try to make it like this stakes are high for this because it's at the end of the day.
It's a bunch of millionaires making decisions about other millionaires.
You gives a shit.
So I'm glad they didn't like try to like frost Nixon it or something
and like make it so feeling so important.
Yeah, yeah.
There was some that was a compliment that my wife, Aaron, paid it
because I made her watch it all from the back.
Who she is from time to time walked into a room
where I am watching a scene of the late shift and says, you're watching this again.
Yeah. And I say kind of what Jason said, which is like, no,
sometimes I just go in and watch scenes that I like.
Like, I like when Helen gets fired or I like when Helen
has a fight with Ken Craig and the country.
Yes. So I just go and I like pick the things that I like.
And she kind of never understood and was disdainful of the movie.
She watched the movie and enjoyed it.
Some of the things that she said were, I think you could take all of the scenes
and shuffle them up in a bag and then spit them back out.
And then we would work the same. That's right.
Because it is confusing.
We're like, Leno has the show and then he keeps having the show.
And like, which why is why are they having this meeting now?
And I and she also said, yeah, then it's just a nice, pleasant, like low stakes.
And I said, look, I got to disagree with you there.
I mean, when Letterman realizes that Bob Wright is offering in the show,
but it's only for seven to 12 million with CBS has already said
12 is the base and he's going to have to wait for 18 months, potentially.
You don't call that stakes.
And it's looking down from below him.
And there's a bunch of pencils on the ceiling and the angles are all crooked.
You're telling me that's not a high stakes diocene.
Pencils on the ceiling was a go to,
I feel like in movies and TV to go like,
huh, this guy might be a genius, but he's a little nutty.
He's got something on his mind.
You know, yeah, yeah.
Throw in the pencils in the drop tile ceiling.
This is a real bad grab back with Scott said,
I think we talked about this on the show before, is that this is another thing
where like Lindsay is like, you want to watch the late shift again?
Where I don't know. There's like, we like this.
I don't. Yeah, there is a weird.
It is. I mean, I hate to like, again, in the show, like paint, like,
oh, the women are upset at the men again.
But it is not correct.
They're not. They're not wrong.
They're not wrong. And it's not like, boy, you.
I found your sports illustrated swimsuit edition again, either for some weird reason.
We have a couple of these.
This very Scott and I, especially with this similar.
Well, that would never happen with you.
No, my God.
Have I seen the sports illustrated swimsuit edition through the glass
of a 7-Eleven before and said, oh, OK, and then walked by?
Yes. But I would never, never purchase it.
That cover the porn magazines that don't show you the.
Yeah, you put it behind one.
Yeah, you choose to like, only take these slips without looking at the.
I went. I went 7-Eleven to 7-Eleven to put them behind
just to make sure it's just for the decency printed out some decency covers.
This is free of charge.
Do you mind? It'll just take a minute.
Yeah. So no, for whatever reason,
in the same way that I will put on
like just a random attack of the clones scene.
And he goes, what are you doing?
I go, well, I just didn't know what to do.
I was kind of my phone.
So I just put it like attack of the clones. Yeah. Yeah.
I don't know.
The scene with C3PO gets his head taken off
and it's put on the belt.
The Senate meeting with Renny Santoni,
the name of the guy who plays Poppy. Yeah, no.
But coincidentally, he's also a senator in attack of the clone.
And what's the name of Swift Swift Swift for Swiffer Mellow?
What's the first Valomilk?
Sifir's Valomilk.
I'm sure first of all, I'm from the Imperial Senate.
Someone call for fan art for that.
Sifir's Valomilk in the Senate next to the ET one.
Next to Zrek.
But she was there any did she watch it with you?
Yeah, we watched it many years ago.
She watched it and I think she was fine with it.
I just don't think she knew why I was fascinated with it.
Yeah. Yeah. Well, this is I kept asking her and like, do you know, like,
like, does what does what's happening in the scene mean?
Because I'm a I'm a freak who knows who all the executives being mentioned.
I know Dick Carousel is right.
If you're like and I've read the book, so I have the Cliff Notes to her,
like the you know, the like the here's the encyclopedia related to the movie.
And she said, no, I don't know what's happening, but it's all nice
shots to look at.
And I like when these music cues come in.
Yeah, like looking at these weird prosthetics.
It is a pleasure. She found it to be a pleasant watch.
Yeah, I think for, again, men and maybe women of a certain age
who were like watching, because I have such memories,
especially during the summer when we could stay up a little later.
I just have memories of what just mainlining these shows.
The Leno and Letterman. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, yeah.
I did that with Conan. Sure. Yeah.
But like, especially when I was little, little, little, little,
because then I didn't really watch Conan until I was a little older
and I got it more.
And I mean, older like, yeah, 13 or something.
But like, yeah, I remember when when it's you, Grant, 94.
Is that right? A little later than I.
Is it like 95? Yeah.
Like, I guess 9, 10, 11.
And during the summer, we would watch Nick at night.
We would watch old TV because they have the block party.
So we would watch.
I know all about the block party.
Two episodes of Dick Van Dyke, two episodes of whatever.
Dobie Gillis, I don't know.
And then watch go back and forth between Leto and Letterman.
I see. So I guess what they're what they have, what they're doing.
Yeah. So I think that's probably why certain people have.
Yeah. And I think it's weird for a kid
to gravitate to these talk show hosts.
So if you are that type of kid, which I was,
which I feel like my comedic evolution was like,
I got some of the simple stuff out of the way early.
Like I watched Leno, which was just like, here's a parody.
He does a song and it's not the words of the song that, you know,
and he has a guy come out who's dressed as the president and it's not the president.
And then you can advance.
Like, OK, so this is just this is like comedy preschool.
Yeah. And you can advance to smarter Conan and the better SNL and that kind of stuff.
Yeah, for sure.
I think with like Letterman, see, like my first memories are like Rupert G.
And I go, oh, when when someone is weird to a stranger, that's funny.
When somebody says jerky things to a stranger and acts like a maniac.
That I like that a lot.
That is that that's good.
That's some of my earliest like, oh, comedy that got it.
I even remember the summer of like Manny the hippie.
Do you recall this character? No.
There was a guy. It was a summer of Letterman.
There was a guy named Manny who was just like a guy who like this man.
And they would check in with Manny the hippie like all the time during this summer.
I don't think it was even that funny.
But at the time, I was like, wow, that's a goofy character.
I like him. That's funny.
Was it just a weirdo or was it just a weirdo?
Oh, just a weirdo. I think you could have fooled me.
But I think it was just some guy they found out a remote
and they just check in with him. Yeah. During the summer.
I don't know what happened to him.
Well, they were like these shows were like your conduits.
There weren't a zillion things.
These felt like the conduits to to edgy comedy.
So they were important and the guys represented different philosophies.
And then the idea that they were like in this war together,
these very different guys, but that they were friends.
That's the Shakespearean.
You know, I wish there were more things where they they talked.
This kind of only that one scene at the Emmys because they don't
only create some fake scene.
And again, they don't frost Nixon with his drunken phone call.
It didn't happen for dramatic effect.
And that's sort of what you know, you wish there was more,
but they don't falsify. Yeah.
And it's so funny to think about now, there's just a million late night shows
and they're all fighting for like the smallest pieces of the pie.
When back then they were like late night, made us seventy million dollars this year
and figure that out, whatever that is with inflation.
But it's like that was yeah, it was huge when the culture was,
you know, much more narrow.
And with Letterman, you have the creation of that slot.
There wasn't that now we know, OK, so who will take over the CBS lot?
But that just didn't exist.
And they they made it exist for him and moved heaven and earth.
They bought early on, they bought Leno a motorcycle instead of riding on over.
That's a good part.
I like when they the one of the CBS executives walks into a lobby
and then taps a guy on the on the shoulder.
He thinks is Ed Begley Jr.
And says he's been playing the executive Rod Perth.
And he says, oh, Rod.
And then the guy turns around and it's not at Begley Jr.
And he says, oh, I'm so sorry.
And then at Begley Jr. walks out, oh, OK.
And then they go into the meeting.
Does that moment register with anybody?
I remember I remember that that like I don't.
I don't know what to what end the what is happening
is that he walks in and taps the real Rod Perth.
Guys, the real Rod Perth, the CBS executive is in the movie.
Like I look like a poser now as far as being a fan of this movie.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, I guess, you know, you're an expert at certain things,
but I guess you're not a big Rod Perth head.
No, that was a part that registered.
Like it was pretty much that with Aaron and she's like, why did that?
She laughed at it.
Like, why is there a mistaken identity for no reason?
And then when I told her what it was, she's like, I don't like it anymore.
I just thought it was a weird thing that happened.
Yeah, it does.
If you don't know, it does.
It's a weird thing.
I'll tell you, this hasn't been mentioned yet.
The conference call at the end when they're in Boca.
Yeah. The vacation polos all the executives are wearing are out of this world.
You can just tell it's like, well, these are their vacation polos.
They wouldn't wear these on casual Friday.
You know, if they did casual Friday, this is out.
These are outrageous.
Some great outfits.
It all reminds me of the door.
Yeah. Yeah.
Flashes. Those through the money at these fancy executive vacation clothes.
It all reminded me of Jurassic Park and like Nedry at the little
at the food stand at the beginning.
And yeah, it's just all like it's all the same type of guy.
There's like when one of the guys is Bob Wright and then his boss,
Jack Welch, comes in and they're the same man, essentially.
Oh, well, I just wanted to check is kindly Jack.
The head of G, the nicest man you ever did see.
Oh, I would have to cast my vote for loyalty.
It is. I mean, it's funny.
I mean, that's kind of like it's hard to tell it was intentional,
but that is a funny cutting joke that it's like, yeah, these networks are all run
by the same sort of shitty dope, like it's the same idiots
in these dumpy polos like these.
It's amazing. Scumbags.
Yeah, yeah, they do all get character.
It's amazing that you don't like hate these people,
especially when we know that Letterman hated them in reality
and lettermanated the NBC people in the second run when it all happened again
in 2010, you know, like, well, that's the side you want to be on.
Like Letterman's probably right to hate all of these stupid executives.
But the movie, by virtue of casting these kind of nice people,
it's weird that we don't hate Warren Littlefield and John Agolia.
Yeah, that speaks to the same thing of like not dramatizing it,
because, yeah, these are just like guys and they're just like,
they just want to make as much money.
They don't care. Yeah.
Which is like bad.
And even like it's so much.
I do almost appreciate the mundane this of that job, because that's
they're literally just like crunching numbers, which they play up a little bit.
But that's in the IMDb trivia section.
It's like they just like Jay wanted less money because he didn't want on the show.
That's probably that's probably why they went with him.
This is the GE era.
Yeah. So like, yeah, like it's like what they're doing is evil.
But they're just like fucking guys trying to try to go home.
So to act like, yeah, it's this it's legacy and it's all this important.
Yeah, it's fine.
I mean, it's would I like to see the fun version where it's like that,
where they're like true, like super like Dr.
Doom, like Warren Littlefield is Dr. Doom.
Yes, I would like to see that.
But that's fun. That's for fun funsies.
Yeah, yeah.
I we've been going for it.
You want to just like quick shout out anything else?
Yeah. Baseball, the famous thing, the famous Letterman.
So when there's a scene where Letterman is angry and he's throwing
the softballs at a giant target.
Yeah. And then back here, he's in Connecticut.
And this is him deciding if he's going to take the not great tonight show deal.
But it would but it would be the show.
I would have the show or if he's going to go do CBS.
So he's yes, his like mentor, Peter Laselli catches him throwing
baseballs and an archery target, a giant archery target.
He says, well, welcome to my weekend in hell.
And I remember very distinctly when this movie came out,
watching Letterman around this time, because he was driven nuts by the movie.
He hates the movie.
He fucked over John Michael Higgins a couple of times as far as being a guest.
But I'm on and then bumped him.
I'm coming to the studio around.
The I'm not sure I know that the one was the
there was a show with Julia Roberts and that he kept having Julia Roberts
do more segments, which you know that that's going to be in the cards.
Yeah, of course.
But also, come on once Julia Roberts is done right.
Who he like had an on screen romance with essentially.
There's like a highly real them kissing on the mouth,
which I guess they never knew each other off.
She said they never like got to like just casually like went to dinner or anything.
They just had some bizarre like tension on air.
Only in that spot.
But yeah, so he so I remember Letterman bringing one time.
It was like he would bring up the movie a lot around this time, too.
So that extra that made it very fascinating because I don't know that Leno
had any preoccupation with it on air, at least.
No, not really. I know a little about what he thought.
Well, I'll tell you. Yeah, but he didn't.
Yeah, Letterman minded for material, including recreating the archery target.
Oh, he did. Yes, there was a I remember very distinctly.
He one episode he brought out the big archery thing because I don't.
He's like that. I didn't never.
I don't. Why didn't they have me throw baseballs at a target?
As Aaron pointed out, who that's not something anyone does.
Baseballs at an archery target.
I should see if I made up activity.
I should see if I can find the clip because unless I've really like made this up.
But I remember distinctly finally him bringing out the archery target
and throwing softballs at it on air, which I thought was so funny.
I have a quote from David Letterman about the film.
I've seen a clip reel and it's just bizarre.
The guy who's playing me and I'm sure he's a fine actor,
but his interpretation seems to be that I'm well a circus chimp.
He looks like he's insane, like he's a budding psychopath.
And afterward, I thought, well, maybe this is how I strike people as being.
Another review in Entertainment Weekly that didn't like John Michael Higgins
said this letterman is impersonated by John Michael Higgins
in a one man orgy of squints, scowls and growls.
It's a day who seems to have lice in his eyebrows and doesn't know how to scratch.
You know what? That's a really, you know, you know what?
I agree with the review and I still like the performance.
I was going to say what he's also kind of playing Letterman
as if Letterman is performing his whole life.
Do you know what I mean?
He's kind of doing an impression of Dave on the air.
Yes. Performing his whole life, not a caricature necessarily.
But it's like the Dave persona then is like everything in his life.
You know what I mean? Like there's no he doesn't have like an a different
not a quiet, muted version of him, which there, especially back then,
from hearing like how like angry he was and stuff.
Yeah. I'm sure there was a really different version of him.
Sure. Sure.
I as for the other side of it,
Daniel Roebuck and Jay Leno, again, the very different characters.
Letterman was very awful to John Michael Higgins, said these bad things,
bumped him on the show.
Daniel Roebuck and Leno were fast friends.
I love it. I love it.
It makes all the sense in the world.
And here's here's how it played out that they when filming the movie,
NBC and HBO were mad at each other on this corporate level, like we have to allow it.
But there will be no communication between our actual host and anyone
involved, anyone involved on the real Tonight Show and this movie.
These are this is church and state. They shall not mix.
And so like, yeah, hard wall there.
But as soon as the shoot was over, Daniel Roebuck said,
I should try to get a hold of Jay Leno.
And he called the tonight show.
They were giving him the run around. I'm sorry. Who are you?
I'm Daniel Roebuck. I play him in the film.
Leno overhears it just picks up the phone.
Hey, so how to go?
Just immediately is on again, not morally or anything
similar to Trump, where Trump is always available.
Like, oh, yeah, yeah.
The thing about him that you could call, you could always any report,
get him on the phone for any reason at any time.
I think we can get him on the show.
We just have to bury this one.
This is this one's staying by and all our tonight show oriented
episodes have to stay behind the second gate for career advancing purposes.
This is the rule that tonight show episode is Jay advancing purposes.
Yeah, also, this is this is also the fascinating thing about Jay,
because as much as we're like making jokes about Jay, Jay is still like
it's probably easier to be friends with Jay than Dave.
Yeah. In a lot of ways.
And then I was listening to Jimmy Kimmel talk and Jimmy Kimmel did a very funny
thing during the whole Conan thing where he went on Jay's show.
Have you seen this? Where Jay was like, had you seen this?
Have you heard about this? Is that what you meant to say?
He asked like, what was the segment called?
Like 10 questions or something?
And 10, 10. Thank you. 10 to 10.
And Jimmy was on via satellite, even though they were in the same city, I think.
And the studio, he he like basically, Jimmy took over the questions
and just kept making jokes about Jay stole the show back from Conan.
And it's really funny.
Really mean, really mean and edgy, like and Jay is so weird during any.
OK, like he's like doesn't give it back at all.
Never, yeah, never comedic failure and just rolls right through every question.
Yeah, it's coming.
Jimmy turns every question into like a slam.
But then I heard Jimmy last week.
Oh, yeah, when my son was in the hospital, Jay called
and like just to see how he's doing or whatever.
And he's like, and Jimmy's like, I don't know, maybe I'm the asshole.
I don't know.
But that was that the the thing preceding that was him doing an entire show
dressed as Leno the next morning.
The first thing you got to call Leno on the phone.
Kimmeling, come on.
Just it always feels so Trumpy to me.
Just like he's always there.
He's already like work at every angle.
But like, yeah, I mean, maybe because, yeah, they were they became friends.
They're still friends.
Sure. To this day, Daniel Roebuck had a daughter who was born
the day after the shoot finished. Wow.
And Leno was always very sweet to the daughter and like got in on her.
Yeah, it should be.
And then here's here's what ends up.
So so Daniel Roebuck, I believe, you know, why ruin this here?
I'm sorry. Let me just go into the quote and you'll pick up
what I'm going to say about Roebuck.
Here's what he said about I do think history played out correctly.
Do you think the right person got it?
Were you on Leno's side?
And he says, when you look at the history, Letterman had a very successful career.
But Jay Leno was the Tonight Show.
I feel strongly that there is a godly plan for everybody.
And it was in the plan that Jay be the host of the Tonight Show.
All the behind the scenes machinations aside, that's just where he was going to end up.
Daniel Roebuck, I think, is a religious person in general, has been in some religious films,
and he believes that it was a god's plan. God's will.
And when you look at it through all these extraordinary circumstances,
were some of the greatest comedic talent of all time.
One of the funniest people who have ever lived, have all been felled by Jay Leno
in his pursuit of hosting the Tonight Show.
I think now we know, is it just because he was shrewd?
Is it was it because of Helen?
Was it because he costs less money?
I think Daniel's on to something.
It's because God is on Jay Leno's side.
God put him there.
There's someone even more powerful than Bob Wright.
Executive producer Ivan Reitman,
the grandpa of our new favorite character podcast.
That's right. The Grampy.
Podcast from Ghostbusters Afterlife.
Ivan Reitman, of course, directed the first two Ghostbusters movies, right?
And is the father of Jason Reitman, who's directing Ghostbusters Afterlife.
The new Who Thought of Podcasts.
Who Thought of the Character Podcast.
Podcast. We're all going to meet podcast.
We're going to meet podcast.
We're going to do a full podcast on podcast.
That's coming. Is that movie coming out next week or in three months?
It keeps changing.
Maybe November. I feel like it's November.
I think, look, you're right, God.
God wants Jay in that spot.
I hope Jay still hosts another version of the Tonight Show, too.
He might take over from Fallon.
Whenever Fallon's cut, couldn't you see that happening again in a Trumpy way?
And not to will it.
Let me knock on lots of things that aren't wood that Trump doesn't come back.
But doesn't it feel like...
Well, yeah, I don't even want to think about the Trump version of that.
But yeah, an 82 year old Jay Leno taking over the Tonight Show.
Yeah, it's possible.
I don't think any is like, you know, if...
And he just does it the same.
It doesn't reinvent anything.
Just as popular.
Kevin's back. Headlines are back.
The ratings increase.
They play a little bit of You Bet Your Life.
That's the only thing they've gathered along the way.
You're right.
Hot out there, right?
Hot out there.
That's what happens when the globe warms seven degrees.
Short amount of time. Hot out there.
Hotter than an intern's office in the White House.
It might be my fault. All the exhaust.
Yeah, you've got to do what I've got to do.
Yeah, he is responsible for a significant portion of it.
He and Seinfeld. Yeah.
Oh, yeah. Speaking of intern, if anybody knows Monica Lewinsky,
she loves Dudley Do-Right, Ripsaw Falls.
Get her on this. We want her on the podcast.
She's so great. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Love Toast.
What a dream episode.
Well, I mean, that to me is a lot of it.
We've been doing it.
We've been doing this for a long time.
And yet I can't not ask the question.
Well, we've talked about the miniseries.
Yeah. Or just is it late?
I mean, I guess Late Shift 2 just is an extended anthology series.
We love this film. We've talked about this film forever.
Yeah. How do you top it?
How do you do a better version, a better tale of let's just to hone in on
Leno V.
Conan, because like and there's more stories that that can be told.
We will do the flashback.
We will see Leno making all of these neurological leaps as a child.
But in doing that story, how do we get to do something better?
Even if you can imagine a better film than the words prestige television,
we're going all out.
We've got the color scheme is brown and gray and blue,
like all the TV shows that look like that.
Yeah. Conan Domnol Gleason.
Jay Roebuck is back. Of course.
We all agree Roebuck is back.
I think in all of our versions, I'm sure.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Now, Wisen and Harden from having killed Dracula.
And yeah, well, and I'm sure God told him to kill Dracula.
That's got to be an element of that.
God hates Dracula. God hates Dracula.
I mean, how like, you know, that is a perfect kind of like
like the guy return into the old role.
I mean, really, like of them, I think you would have to get
they have to be all of them.
This is this is Star Wars.
You have to get the full group.
Rich Littles back to he's alive.
Yeah. Yeah. Force ghost.
Well, that's exactly what I was thinking.
And I don't know if it's if this is if the people are appearing to Leno
or if they're like haunting Conan when the decisions are getting difficult.
But I think even the people who have passed away like Johnny
and like, of course, Helen Kushnick, I mean, Helen Kushnick,
like being the bad like the devil on
Jay's shoulder when all of that is like like like just go back to the show.
Who gives a shit about Conan?
He had his shot.
Well, it's like if the three months is if he didn't get in three months,
she was never going to get it.
That that fucking little dick licker.
I'm like, what would Helen say?
It's the scene in Last Jedi when Yoda shows up.
That's the Helen scene.
Yes. When Jay sort of at a bottom, like he's like, I don't know.
People don't like me or whatever.
And then like Master Helen.
And then she shows up. She's a force ghost.
And that's on these fucking page turners. OK.
Those old Carson monologues were exactly the same.
Just kept talking about Burbank.
But the ancient Johnny DVDs.
Fine. My goodwill.
Yeah. Yeah.
I want I think we got to get some more more.
Like I already said, I love Donald.
These are Zucker.
I think he got to go.
Giamatti. Exactly what I was going to say.
Yes. Perfect.
Because with Jeff Zucker,
who was the executive in charge of that fiasco,
you have a much deeper, darker villain.
But these guys, Littlefield and Agolia, then like did turn around primetime
and had that all star run right for NBC.
And then they've just done other stuff like that.
Zucker, of course, went on to not be punished for this fiasco in any way.
And then he gave us Donald Trump and the constant CNN coverage of Donald Trump
that superseded anything else they were doing.
Yeah. So he's truly like, is there like a darker figure
on the planet Trump himself?
But like Bernie Mark Burnett?
Oh, yeah. He's got all the tapes.
Well, as I started to say, is there a darker?
I mean, there's darker television producer executive.
Yeah, there probably are. But he's he's pretty bad.
So you got to go. Yeah.
Giamatti's got a.
And like I
I don't know. You know, Gleason's Gleason's good.
I the only thing that I might say is that you have the height issue
with Conan.
And there's not a lot of very tall, lean actors.
But luckily, one of the best actors is maybe the best actor is a very tall actor.
And that is Daniel Day-Lewis,
who I mentioned earlier, and they showed it long ago.
It's towards the beginning of the. Yeah.
It's good. It's good.
But you see, the thing is they work.
I think they cast Daniel Roebuck and Michael Higgins because they were unknowns.
Mm hmm. So but this is a franchise.
Now, I guess you're right. You're right. You're right.
It's like SNL and the politicians.
You got to come in with the biggest stars.
The show's so big, you need you need De Niro playing Robert Mueller.
And I just think that, you know, Daniel Day-Lewis,
who ends up inventing these bizarre American accents,
I think him playing Conan as like, be cool, my babies.
Oh, so like a Daniel Plainview.
I think he might land.
Or, you know, sometimes he's a little more like
flaking like he sees he's like nice in the
in the Phantom Thread.
So if you go to some bizarre American.
But I think Conan ends up in here in the.
Let's see what life is like in the year 3000.
The FedEx Pope.
I can't start my day with conflict, Jeff.
I hate cynicism.
It's my least favorite quality in the world.
If you work hard, good things will happen.
Do something with that, you freak.
Oh, yes.
He'll be. All right.
And they got to have the behind the scenes, too,
because he'll stay in character as Conan.
Oh, yeah.
Which will be fun as fun as well.
Mm hmm. Constant string dances, constant people,
and this constant muttering is a murderer.
That's right. Murderer.
Yeah, look, I'm sold.
If you can get him, he says he says he's retired.
Yeah, I know that's the roadblock that he said that he's made his last film
and that he only makes one movie every five years.
But you think he's not coming back for the chance to play Conan O'Brien.
It's good point. I mean, HBO Max
for too many, for many strung out episodes.
I think there would be as much content as the late shift movie,
but just like really watered down to get to that full season.
It's unclear how much some of these streaming services pay.
Either they pay the pile of Joker money or they pay the Jay Leno five hundred
and twenty five dollars. Yeah, it depends.
Daniel Day Lewis is in like a shack in the woods in the middle of nowhere.
He's cobbling shoes and like a messenger boy gets knuck knucks on the door.
He's like, I told you I'm retired.
And he's like, no, wait, you're going to want to hear this.
He's like, why? I don't want to hear anything.
Daniel Robic wants to play Jay Leno again.
He drops the shoe.
They got Robuck.
They've got Robuck again.
And then he like kind of sort of like weeps at his feet when he meets Daniel Robuck.
Yeah, he's there.
You just want to eat the steaks.
You don't care. The cattle are slaughtered.
I think you got to also go to I know Letterman didn't grow the beard till later,
but I think everybody I think Lennox got a beard.
I think you do the Luke Skywalker just beards on everyone.
Yeah, just to honor that, like the greats have come back
and they're older and wiser.
Yeah, that's true. Everybody's got a beard.
Johnny's got a beard in the afterlife.
Yeah. For whatever reason.
I had another idea, too, which is that Kimmel recreates all those things
that Kimmel did, the Ten and Ten and everything.
But Kimmel's lost a lot of weight.
And I think Kimmel plays himself with prosthetics to become
10 years ago, larger Kimmel.
See, that makes it fun.
You can't just have the person play themselves or else you fall into a Jay
Leno Wolf Blitzer kind of trap.
But yes, if they're wearing prosthetics of themselves 10 years ago.
Now, that's special.
Larry King wearing a wig in the Doge movie to be old, like to be
the age Larry King.
And then Letterman agreeing to be a man on the moon,
but refusing to look like old Letterman.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He'll do it, but he wouldn't look like his old self.
Yeah. So you can't have him.
So you got to have Higgins in a beard.
I think when everybody's appearing as force ghosts and everything
and like guiding, you know, Leno's decision or whatever it is.
Carson just shows up and just does like Carter jokes.
He offers no relevant advice.
So gas shortage.
Put solar panels on the White House.
Ackroyd is Tom Snyder,
which a character he played on Saturday Night Live. Sure.
Yeah, so you get everyone knows that obviously.
But he's he's down for for biopics.
Yeah.
She's smart as Joan Rivers.
She's playing like a Joan Rivers type.
Oh, sure. OK. Yeah.
Who's still a felon is around.
Yeah, felon part of it, because when everything was moved,
it was changing time slots.
It just became like they said, like, now, are you OK with starting at one
in the morning? Yeah, I'm fine.
Whatever. It's all good.
Yeah. Yeah, I'm good.
Yeah. I was thinking with that energy, what about the
cousin Greg from Succession?
Oh, man, that'd be awesome.
Hey, let's not forget.
Often forgotten about, I think, tangentially, Manch.
I never read the Bill Carter.
Carson Daly, the other Carson.
Yes. Yeah, for sure.
And he's in there.
If you're doing a lot of episodes than just one like odd,
miserable, solitary Carson Daly episode is watching him like
I like go about his day filming his show.
And while all the other people are getting manic calls from all these executives,
he just looks at the phone and it never rings.
Earl sent an email like, hey, just did our thousandth show.
I've been on the air for 25 years.
I've lasted longer than everyone else.
Sad, but no one knows.
Zucker, you up?
Ladies and gentlemen, lit.
The big one is Lauren has to be on.
Yeah, and Lauren has not been portrayed.
Lauren played himself a man on the moon and I think otherwise
has only been portrayed in cinema by Armin Weitzman.
Let's bring him back.
That's an easy cast for us, I think.
I think we could get Armin.
I think so.
Mm hmm. He's Michael Keaton.
He's always Lauren.
So that's easy. Yeah, because Lauren Lauren did not produce a Tonight Show.
He did. That was he produced Late Night with Conan and not.
But now then that was so there was a rumors of he was upset with that.
Maybe. Yeah, yeah.
Yeah. But he is a producer now on Fallon.
Yes. So it's Armin just going like like, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
And that's all they get to.
Mm hmm. You just see it as sputters.
Yeah, it's one scene. It's less than one scene.
It's going to be there's a lot of characters and it's going to be like
Toy Story 4. There's a lot more characters now.
You know, it's going to be hard to give everyone their due, but
it's worth an undertaking.
And I had one big idea about it, too, is that because you sort of got to like
take choose a side and you'd be tempted to choose
Conan side because we all love Conan.
But like, I like the idea that the movie would just make the decision
that it's about Leno recapturing what is rightfully his.
Leno is the hero.
Uh huh. Daniel A.
Lewis is great at portraying villain or if it's Dom Mocleese, either one like great for,
you know. So you just like you just make Conan the biggest villain.
This jerk came and tried to steal my land.
And it's sort of a Clint Eastwoodie.
Yeah, yeah, it's like a yeah, recapturing.
So like there'll be like a pivotal scene, much like in this one where,
let's say, Jay is in the green car with like Richard Karn.
And he's like, yeah, they say maybe they'll give me tonight show back.
And Richard Karn is like, the tonight show is yours.
They should have never taken it from you.
And Jay's like, yeah, you're right.
And he puts the green car in gear and they speed around.
They don't do the race. They stay.
They break out. Yes, they bring a lot of security gate.
Yeah, that song shut up and drive plays.
Jay hits Jay hits the drive through of the wiener schnitzel across the street real
quick. Just like that.
They get like 10 chili dogs still going strong.
Yeah, yeah. Still there. Yeah.
Good for them. Richard Karn is with him the whole time.
Sounds good. Just along for the ride.
And they drive right to whoever's office or something.
And like you're about to press big buttons.
One says, Jay and one says Conan.
That's how the decision is made.
It's a big like super villain.
Yes. And the car.
Yeah. Jay crashes the car through the roof or through the wall.
It's on the 10th story or something.
But he just like so he like hits a ramp expertly and goes right through
Zucker's window, dangles him out the window in a Shug night fashion.
Who's buying bottled water?
He's free in the tap.
Uh, I'm slaughtering the cow this time.
I thought of the cow. You hear me?
I'm an Italian guy.
I've shaken people out of window before.
I turned you into Brazil.
I think, yeah, then it like he then he does that heartfelt final Conan tonight
show and then and then just on this like he just like
Leno Burson jumps out of the car and beats Conan to death with a bat
and then looks down and says, I might look stupid, but I'm Italian.
It's the Tarantino ending.
Then Letterman with cigar,
them having become friends during the Super Bowl commercial with Oprah.
Right. And Oprah's in there, too.
They all show up.
Like Oprah as a lighter,
Letterman lights a cigar and then tosses it, burns the Conan tonight show
studio and and they drive off in the distance and don't look back.
And Max Weinberg becomes Jay's band leader.
Play by him. Play by Malia.
Oh, yeah. Demands top credit.
So this all this entire thing is called Max Weinberg presents the late.
She's got that one day nine sixty two scale.
All right. I get scale.
Yeah. Well, let's get Betty Thomas on the on the line.
Yeah. Yeah.
This is the job of a lifetime.
She's up to it.
I this is this is epic.
This is grand, just as this episode was.
And like we knew it would be you survived podcast, the ride, the late shift edition.
You know, some episodes are for the audience and some are for the host.
Yeah. An episode all about hosts and what hosts want.
And these three hosts wanted to do this.
Do you think that we're much stranger now than when you started listening to the
what have your have your opinions of us changed as if this is like a warts and all?
You of us as the film?
It's a question.
I've done this 10 years ago, maybe.
But there's just such a glut of comedy podcast about anything and everything under the sun.
But not the late.
I know I didn't look it up.
There may be podcasts about the late shift, but I would venture to say this film
has never been covered.
Is this the most comprehensive late shift?
Tone. Yeah, tone, whatever you call it.
Yeah, that's out there.
Besides the late shift, the book. Right.
But that doesn't count.
That's since this is this is a post film.
Yeah. Analytical work.
And we didn't even get it.
Like I could talk about all the YouTube videos for all this stuff that I watch every other month.
Yeah. No, I still I go back to the 2010
late night wars so frequently.
Yeah. Don't.
And that's so fascinating.
As David Letterman told Conan O'Brien that he refers to that time as the golden age of television.
And Conan said, oh, you mean the time when I was struggling.
That's for you.
That was a golden age.
Some solace. And at least you were happy.
He's right. It was great.
I watched every night of it.
And I ate up Conan's goodbye speech.
Conan's goodbye speech had a positive impact on me and what I was trying to do at the time
that may have had an effect on me ending up in the building with him.
It was so important to me every bit of that, that it's all that it's everyone's doing
the funniest shit you've ever seen, all culminating in a wonderful heartfelt thing,
which I've devalued by saying that actually there's an alternate history where he gets
beaten up by one of the baseball bats.
Yeah, but in one reality, it still is meaningful.
Yeah, if you haven't, I don't know if I'm sure.
I can't imagine if you weren't into it then you'd be into it now.
But there's so much video of it.
It's so well done. I mean, look up Don't Blame Conan.
It's a masterful monologue.
I think Susser and I were talking about how we could do that for like as an audition for something.
This is a Letterman monologue.
Yeah. So basically, he goes, Letterman's like,
basically like, you know, I said I wasn't going to say anything more about this.
He goes, but I can't help myself.
He goes, last night, Jay did an interview and he told everybody that
you shouldn't blame Conan for what's happening.
He's you know, a lot of people think Conan is trying to push himself out of a job.
It's not the case.
Conan wouldn't do that to himself, folks.
So don't blame Conan.
And he goes, hey, Paul, are you going to blame Conan?
You know, him Conan, you're not going to blame Conan, were you?
And then he goes and he's like, yeah, and Jay, you know, Jay said Conan was a family guy.
So that's the end of that thought.
Yeah. Well, you know, Conan, it's yeah, it's a masterful monologue.
This is about a film about people who do monologues.
It's what they do. And I think there's a number of things in this.
I think you could do any of the Treat Williams monologues for it.
If you have a if you have a drama class or an audition coming up, you could do it.
The one thing I didn't mention, I think, but maybe my favorite thing in the movie is
that Helen is trying to break the photograph.
She finally snaps. She's turned on Jay.
She's trying to break a photograph.
The two of them. Oh, you want to break this?
You're trying to break this?
You're going to break this?
There. It's broken.
I mean, that I want to hire a crew and put myself in Jay prosthetics
and recreate this.
At the very least, somebody do a deep fake.
Put my face. Yeah.
Oh, wow. Fan camp.
I'll know that we have a great, devoted fan who maybe at that level of devotion,
I'd be worried was going to kill me. Yeah.
They know what a deep fake you first I would I would think it was nice.
And this is all been great.
Let me say this really fast.
And you're talking nice things about Susser.
That motherfucker comes anywhere close to trying to take my slot on this show.
If he thinks he can march in here, he's always marching into these shows.
If he thinks he's going to push me out of the chair, out of the sort of comfortable
folding chair that I'm doing this podcast from.
Look, I don't think no, no, it's fine.
Everything's fine. Don't worry about it.
He's not going to do that.
He's not gunning for it.
He's not. He's not listening outside the door right here.
I'll be serving up Susser steak.
I'll tell you. That's what happens.
If he comes if he comes gunning for the for the Gartner spot.
You may need to get an agent, though.
A handsome agent. That's me.
I already. Hey, you have a handsome agent.
I've only had an armada of of it's a tree with treats,
of treats with my armada of treats.
So there doesn't stand. Yeah, he's screwed.
He tried that fossil Susser.
Are you Italian? You're not Italian, right?
I'm not. OK.
That does hurt me in this. Yeah.
OK, so that's that.
And I guess when I thank you for listening
and when we find another TV movie that we want to do,
I hope that you'll come support that, too.
What does he wait then? What does he say?
I build. I bid you all the fun.