Forever.
Dog.
Warning, partner.
This here episode may whisk you back to a rough and tumble time when there was nary
a podcast in sight.
You may encounter Western rides that were never built, a big thunder movie that was never made,
and a plan involving Main Street that should probably never be attempted.
SNL's Dennis McNicholas joins us for a rootin' and possibly tootin' tribute to Frontierland.
And podcast this here ride.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, a theme park podcast hosted by three men who would gladly pay a
premium to drink bottled water dredge from the rivers of America.
I'm Scott Gardner joined by Mike Carlson.
Hello.
I am here.
Yes.
If they could, I wish that sad that Disney store is going away because I do feel like
that was the spot for niche like products like this for theme park fans, but they had
done such mass marketed, you know, Marvel stuff, Star Wars stuff.
They weren't really doing like dirty pirate water, dirty splash mountain water.
I know they wouldn't call it dirty, but you know what I'm saying.
Yeah.
That would have been the street terminology.
But yeah, you can't say that on the shelves.
Not for the normies.
Of course.
Even just like vials and they could like, like holy water type thing, like where you
just kind of bless yourself with the water of Pirates of the Caribbean for somebody in
the Midwest who doesn't get to the parks a lot.
Yeah.
It's just, it's a little, it's a little splash maybe to wake you up in the day.
It's like a cologne and it gives you the confidence that you'd been on one of these rides.
Cologne as a whole, that's another, I don't want to get us off on a tangent, but that's
a whole nother market.
They haven't even been smelling like these places.
Jason Sheridan, are you on board with this line of products?
I would have loved to have a bottle of Rivers of America water, which comes with a certificate
of authenticity and also Legionnaires disease.
Like, you get like three, you got it, you know, you got to get it Sunday.
Of course, discovered in Philadelphia, discovered at a big Legion conference at an old hotel
in Philadelphia.
Is that what it is?
The Legionnaires equal, it was a Legion, what is a Legion conference?
It was a Legion, it's an American Legion.
Really?
Like, yeah.
I didn't know that.
And they found it in the air conditioning system.
Wow.
And then they gifted the world a famous disease.
Yeah.
Man, hometown pride, I guess, for you for that.
Hometown pride for the Legionnaires disease.
Cream cheese, squirtle, and a great disease.
What neck of the woods year wise is that?
Because is Legionnaires disease a product of the era that the land today is tributing?
Um, eight seventies, I think.
So there was certainly like activity going on in the land.
Mm hmm.
You know, a lot of change, a lot of change going on.
1870s, not 1970s?
No, 1970s.
Oh, Legionnaires disease isn't an old timey thing?
It hasn't been named that.
Well, now I'm going to I'm going to have to look into this.
I have no idea.
I'll check back in in about an hour.
Yeah, go down this rabbit hole.
Go do some separate research while we pull the wagons up to today's topic, which is frontier
land.
It's an episode all about frontier land and about frontier lands past, the frontier land
that never was, how it stands today, and the future, a future which is in a way in question.
Like, will there be a frontier land again?
Will new rides be built in the frontier lands we have?
This is all the stuff we're going to discuss.
Full deep dive and we're doing it with a fantastic guest.
So happy to have him.
He is an Emmy winning longtime writer for Saturday Night Live.
He is the current producer of Weekend Update and the writer director of the podcast Batman
the Audio Adventures, which is about to come out very soon on HBO Max.
Dennis McNicholas is here.
Hello.
Hi, thanks for having me, you guys.
Of course.
No, I wanted to do this for a while.
Oh, fantastic.
So happy you could.
Because full disclosure, I mean, you know, doing this podcast and kind of having ears
out for who is a theme park fan in the world of comedy.
It's having spoken to you to a big extent for a number of years now.
I can't, I'm not, I feel like you're one of the top theme park nerds in the comedy world,
I have to say.
I can't, it's hard for me to think of somebody with a vaster wealth of knowledge.
Well, you wouldn't probably want to meet that person, I'm suspecting because any more.
Well, actually, it's you guys that I admire because the one time I went to the park with
you guys, you know, I have been along with showbiz people before who got VIP treatment.
But like you guys were like operating on street level, like you were talking to cast members
and it was like, it really was like, it was Hucky Baron and Allie type stuff.
You guys were executing and I was all about it.
We went on the very first day of the Rise of the Resistance.
Rise of the Resistance, yeah, yeah, you were in this for that.
Yes, indeed.
And I'm really glad I was because you guys took care of us.
Yeah, I think it took seven or eight of us refreshing apps to get a ride on it.
But we ended up doing it because we had a man on the inside.
Like we would have gotten it, but not till like 9 p.m.
And we got there at 5 a.m. because we didn't know how it was going to work.
So yeah, it did take us to do it within any reasonable amount of time.
We did have our man on the inside.
There was some machinations.
Yeah, there was some standing around waiting, a lot of whispering, I feel like as well.
Like, are we going to get to do it?
Or maybe if we go over here, like there's a lot.
I'm not I didn't have a carton of cigarettes to exchange for it, but it felt like I did.
It felt like that was the deal I was making.
Like I slipped a prisoner a bunch of cigarettes and we got to ride Rise of the Resistance
earlier than we would have normally.
So I guess we're big in the Disneyland underground is what you've taught us.
Yeah, I love that, too, because that makes I sometimes I am worried we're like
because we're talking about the park and we get to go a lot.
We feel like we're elitists.
But that just that says we're not.
I don't think so at all.
I think you guys are operating.
You it was it was populist parks, but I'm kidding.
I think. Well, thank you.
I really that makes me feel good.
That makes me feel authentic, I guess.
Wow. Yeah, credibility.
Much appreciated. But like but as I was saying, Dennis, let's not, you know, undersell
your wealth of Disney knowledge, which I feel like if you have a I mean,
there's a thousand things you could have talked about on the show with us.
But it feels like your major in general is well, like, well, I mean,
there's frontier line and everything.
But it also like you grew up in Florida.
You were in Disney World in the 70s a lot like like early.
The first 10 years of Disney World, I feel like is a passion area for you.
Yeah, I love it.
And I was there as a child, as a young child.
I I probably made it.
My first visit was probably in seventy five.
I was three and I probably probably went once or twice more before 1980.
And so dim memories and they did away with so much of that stuff.
You know, it's sort of it's Scott.
You and I have talked about how they they had real ambitions of being a cosmopolitan
adult retreat, you know, the vacation kingdom of the world.
Oh, yes. Your boats and your water skis.
Well, it's water skiing and yeah, the white dinner jacket,
carved prime rib at your table and all that stuff.
And they, you know, they figured out where what people were coming for.
And then the Eisner thing.
And you guys know more about this than I do, I'm sure.
But all of that lost sort of 70s leisure.
I absolutely love about the Florida property.
You look at those pictures is unbelievable.
It's so the brochures.
It's so many of the pictures from those brochures of that era are not families.
It's young fit couples that look like they've either just made love
or about to go pack up to go back to the room to make love.
No, no question.
You know, I was I was just at the Disneyland Hotel and I love that.
If you if you sneak back by the convention center and where steakhouse
the steakhouse is, they've got a big photo collage of the history
of the hotel and everything.
And yes, from the 60s, we my girlfriend and I focused on a one shot
that was two women and a man playing cards
and smoking cigarettes in a hotel room at the Disneyland Hotel.
And I mean, it looked nothing so much like an adventurous marriage.
It is like that, like in the old days, we've talked about this,
like, you know, it was date night at Disneyland,
which was like the high end adult crowd.
Like, I feel like they get these like once every so often they get it,
because even I think Pleasure Island, you would say, is the 90s version of that,
of like we need to get adults, we need to make this place cool.
It's obviously 90s cool and not like smoking a cigarette in the 1950s.
Cool, which is the ultimate cool.
But it is interesting.
And they haven't had it.
Disney Springs is the closest they've had for a while, where it's just like,
let's make a uniform shopping center for people.
But that's far less cool than any of the other things we were just talking about.
Well, that's what, you know, adults with disposable income like now,
they like gastropubs and Uniqlo.
That's true.
You're right. Change.
That's a good point.
So I guess they're on point.
They're catering to, yeah, the current.
But like, yeah, the days are gone of the giant
jello molds with grapes in them and with like like with like ranch dressing
for the jello molds.
That's kind of thing that just that way people ate in the 70s,
like high end 70s dining.
And it seemed like Disney World was front and center.
Another thing to bring up, Dennis, was while you're here,
you know, to give you a platform to do so, because we've talked about episodes
that you could do. And I like that you you proposed something that felt like
like on the more obscure and even for even for us.
And I want to give you the platform to say anything you want about it,
which is the Columbia Harbor House, the restaurant.
The Disney World, which is not to preclude a full episode that could come.
I absolutely will talk about the Columbia Harbor House.
And I can kind of bank it into the Frontierland conversation.
Oh, yeah, they're very close. Yeah.
Well, Columbia Harbor House is, for those who don't know, is a very large,
elaborately themed
chicken and seafood restaurant in Liberty Square,
just off of
the Haunted Mansion exit queue and all that stuff, right?
Right on the border of Liberty Square and Fantasyland.
And it's got so much real estate.
It's a counter service restaurant, but it's got like nine dining rooms.
And it is loaded with
nautical antiques of the sort that, you know, that in sometime in the 70s,
they just pulled a truck up to some place in Maine and just put every anchor
and ship's wheel that they could find in the place.
And it looks old.
Yeah. And they just piled it all in there.
And from what I can tell, it remains popular.
But to me, and this came up kind of recently when
when they opened the Skipper Canteen
for the table service restaurant in Adventureland.
Yes. And I, you know, I thought, oh, well, this is really interesting.
They're branching their rides out into restaurants.
And I immediately thought of Columbia Harbor House
because it's adjacent to the Haunted Mansion and it's ridiculously large
and could be easily outfitted as a table service restaurant
if they wanted to make a Haunted Mansion themed restaurant.
And, you know, they wouldn't have to change it much.
It's all old and 19th century and nautical.
And they've got the space for it and everything.
And this to bank it into the Frontierland discussion.
I was talking with a cast member around that time and saying,
you know, that it was a great idea to sort of expand rides into the restaurant
space and the more, you know, completely immersive
and an interactive type environments.
And they said, yes, there was a rumor
that there was going to be a Haunted Mansion restaurant amongst the cast members.
But it wasn't going to be Columbia Harbor House.
It was going to be on the back island behind Tom Sawyer's Island.
And you were going to take a water launch from the keelboats,
the defunct keelboat landing, which used to be able to take
little watercraft called the Mike Fink keelboats.
Oh, we know all about that.
Second day, we learned about Mike.
Very fire prone keelboats.
Exactly. So the keelboat, the keelboat
dock remains completely functional from what it looks like.
And the rumor was you take a little launch from there to the back of
the four wilderness island or the Fort Langhorn Island.
And there would be a restaurant out there
and you'd have an interactive experience and so on and so forth.
I think that's probably never going to happen.
That doesn't sound like the sort of thing that they would, you know.
You know, volunteer for the trouble of. But right.
But the reason that fascinates me is that island is huge
and there's nothing on it except at the very front of it.
They've got the, you know, the replica fort and
I can't even picture the space here, Tiger.
There's a secret island in Disney World. Well, yes.
OK, so Tom Sawyer Island is really two islands.
There's the front island that has all the caves and the,
you know, the the windmills and so on and so forth.
Then you go at the back of it, you take a bridge out to a second island.
And at least in Florida, there's a fort, there's like a log
like for it, like Frontier Fort out there.
And there there used to be a companion, the same thing in in California.
And it's still out there, I think.
But you can't get out there anymore.
And I think the structure is condemned.
But but yeah, if you look at a map, there's this vast second island
behind Tom Sawyer Island in Florida.
And there's nothing on there.
It's just woods, woods, woods.
And, you know, over on on the left side of it, I guess they have some
showpieces for the
for the riverboat and stuff like like the burning cabin and stuff like that.
Oh, sure, sure.
There's a perpetually burning cabin that they used to point out, but
which which also brings up like all of the fun of
of Frontierland or all these things that are just do not fly anymore.
It's just exploding whiskey stills and, you know,
stagecoaches getting getting attacked by vengeful locals and things.
I mean, it's just it's it's it's hard to entertain around the subject.
It's yeah, it's a more it's like by its nature and subject matter,
a very like rough and tumble world for sure.
I mean, just to start to get into it a little bit,
because I was looking up like what was Frontierland like in 1955?
And I was struck by the like sort of like I mean,
it was the Wild West in a lot of ways.
It feels like it was like kind of undeveloped.
Like a lot of it was just field initially at Disneyland in 55.
Like some greenery a little, but like that wasn't the I feel like a lot of
original Disneyland was just here's a vaguely themed field or a non themed
field, and we just gave it a name, which is, I think, literally
what they did with the Matterhorn space before it was the Matterhorn.
And just like Holiday Hill, that's something right. Sure. Close enough.
But it feels to me like Frontierland initially was like was just kind of dirt.
And then it wasn't like a there eventually was the mind train through Nature's
Wonderland, which is a more organized ride.
But initially, what you had is just like mules and horses running around
who like I mean, of course, look, there's there's there's pony rides
a place we know this stuff, but it seems like very strongly notoriously
in early Frontierland.
It was just mules like peeing and shitting like constantly all day.
And they would just like get mad.
They would kind of buck guests off of them.
They would like just stop in the trail.
And their only solution to that was like a guy having to come out and yell.
And like so truly it was like a extremely like just like
all. Yeah, lawless is a great word.
Yeah, just in a land that kind of didn't work.
But if you're after a Wild West experience, then that's what it gave you.
I think in. Yeah.
Well, I think when we first started talking about this, I was like, yeah,
it is interesting to think about that.
Like Westerns at the time were like one of the biggest things in popular culture.
Like my dad was born in the early 50s and he's like, he still loves Frontierland
because it's like it's his equivalent of me walking into Marvel Superhero Island
and Islands of Adventure because it's just like, oh, well,
giant Adam Qbert art will just just imprint it on me at like 10 to 12.
And that just hits different, you know.
Right. It's it's just what hit me at the most impressionable age.
And, you know, the Davy Crockett stuff and all the cowboy shows and movies and all.
Like they were the Marvel movies of their time.
Extremely and like the most like extremely relevant right then.
Davy Crockett was brand new and a giant phenomenon on television.
And the song was a hit song, which kind of strikes me funny that that all in general,
that like Disney had chart topping hits with like Davy Crockett
and Who's Afraid of the Big Bad Wolf.
These were these were big pop songs at the time.
It's hard to imagine something so like novelty being like a song,
like a nonsense song that the minions sing,
like if a minion speak song topped the charts, it would be a little strange.
Yeah, but like for sure, the Sherman Brothers are the equivalent of like Dua Lipa or
or whoever chains, whoever's popular chain smokers.
Yeah, they were probably genuinely chain smokers.
Not just in name like these fake chain smokers.
100 percent they were chain smoking. Yeah, for sure.
But that's a question, Dennis, is like, were you like like,
were you were you fond of of of Westerns or of any of this like Disney material
that kind of fueled the original frontier land?
You know, it's interesting because I my father was is a little older than that.
And likewise, huge Westerns fan as a kid.
He actually rode horses and stuff, so he was a little closer to it.
But like when he was before he was before he could ride real horses,
he would sit on a fence rail and pretend he was, you know, riding a horse.
And it was just like all he wanted was boots and six shooters, cap guns
and all that stuff.
And I'm not an expert on it, but from what I gather, like that was,
you know, like Mike TV and Willy Wonka
wearing the wearing the cowboy hat and all that watching his hop along
Cassidy or whatever it was.
I think it was that way until Star Wars,
which displaced cowboys and and because, for example, I was I was born in 72
and Star Wars is out in 77.
And so I was five years old and the cowboys never really took root.
I can remember some being very young and having some of that stuff pushed on me.
But basically, from the time Luke Skywalker on, there was just no Western
presence whatsoever.
But you had it hanging on and all that stuff.
And everyone I knew knew knew that song, the Davy Crockett theme song, for example.
I'm sure I never saw an episode of Davy Crockett as a kid.
But, you know, that was still around there enough.
And like and you still read
Tom Sawyer in, you know, that that was pushed on you at the school library
and stuff like that.
So like the stuff remained.
It didn't seem odd as a kid that we had this stuff.
And at least in Florida, you know, they opened Big Thunder in 79 or 80.
And then you still had
Country Bear, which is still there.
You had all the Tom Sawyer stuff.
And then the shooting gallery.
And, you know, it it felt it felt like it had a its thing going on.
You know, it whereas nowadays, like, I don't know.
The reason I wanted to talk about this today is that
it's all about the real estate in these parks for me
and what they can do with the space that they have.
And this is just a big chunk of real estate that they've got all over the world.
And they're just they have no properties that
no no outside properties that they grafted on.
And then the country bears and stuff that they have,
they're not interested seemingly in promoting.
So, you know, they've got an opportunity and, you know, I've got ideas.
Sure, sure.
Are you aware?
We'll cut this if you can't talk about it, but like
you have made attempts at trying to like revive,
like do something in the frontier land.
Yes. So.
A very long time ago now, I think probably 2007, it was around the time
it was before the pirate sequels had come out,
but it was after the Black Pearl had come out.
I went in and I because subsequently
I became a fan of like Spaghetti Westerns,
you know, as an older film watcher.
And, you know, for my money, like Good, the Bad, the Ugly is a comedy.
It's really funny.
And it's got a comedy set pieces just all throughout its length.
And I saw a cowboy
flavored Jack Sparrow adventure
set at Big Thunder Mountain.
And I happened to go into the Disney executive
that was meant to hear this pitch because he had a gigantic Italian
Once Upon a Time in the West, Sergio Leone poster there.
And Once Upon a Time in the West was actually
what I was basing it on to a large extent.
And so it was the perfect meeting to have.
It just worked out perfectly.
And I got to write the movie.
They bought the pitch and I get to write the movie.
And that was the end of the happy story, because subsequently
there was interest and things look good. But
the Lone Ranger and Jerry Bruckheimer came along.
The Lone Ranger, which, like as far as
Disney attempting to do anything Western today, didn't work then.
And now it is like the most canceled movie
on multiple levels continues to be cursed.
Who knows what?
While we're recording this, two other things about it now are problematic.
I'm sure in the background have been tweeting unsavory things.
The only more cursed things are that Phantom of the Opera set
where people just kept getting heard at Universal Studios back lot.
And that Crow movie like those are the most
the other the Crow. Yeah.
I couldn't remember if it's the first one or the sequel.
But yeah, the Spider-Man musical. That one. Yeah. Well, yeah.
You know, from a certain angle, we were blessed with that.
But yeah, no, some people would describe it as curse.
Some people might still have hospital bills, might describe it as Spider-Man
themselves. Yeah.
Jason feels the injuries were worth it, actually, is what he's saying.
To get that song, to get that Letterman performance.
It's a reasonable sacrifices.
But so OK, so that came along and killed them.
But this is this is kind of wild that you're glad you're willing to talk about it.
I know that non-disclosure agreement end of it, but that you know,
you wrote some idea of what Big Thunder Mountain the movie is.
I did. I wrote the I did two drafts of a screenplay.
And believe it or not, this was before Iron Man.
And I wrote it for Robert Downey Jr. when he he.
Let me put it this way.
I pitched Robert Downey Jr. to the studio and they said, how about Vince Vaughn?
So that's where that's where everyone's career was at that time.
So but I had in mind, you know,
Robert Downey with a big push broom mustache and sort of being a
sarcastic, cantankerous, you know, rascally,
Jack Sparrow in a cowboy outfit, basically.
And we had some we had some cursed gold in there as well.
It was sort of a different deal.
But the magic gets loose and the dinosaur skeleton comes to life
from the from the ride and everything.
And yeah, yeah.
Oh, that's Skelet. Yeah. Oh, wow.
So that's like embedded in the mountain and then it starts running around.
Peels loose and and like it was like sort of an adobe dinosaur.
It still sort of had the rock and the and the petroglyphs
and all the Native American adornment and stuff.
And I think it could have really been a
it would have looked unlike any other dinosaurs on in the movies.
But but it had all that fun.
My pitch was they still make Westerns,
but they have completely stopped making this sort of Saturday
matinee Westerns, the family adventure.
You know, Indiana Jones, but but with Cowboys.
And I said, let's get back to that.
If they if the kids want to dress up as pirates now,
which was something I think all of us didn't have as a kid, people playing pirate.
That wasn't.
Oh, that's true. Yeah.
If they can manufacture that out of nowhere, then why not sort of,
you know, find something new in the Western mythos to dredge it?
I think it's I think it's possible.
And I think all the thrills are there from any of these kinds of movies.
And anyway, I had my shot and maybe it'll come back around someday.
But, you know, I had all the fun characters in there.
There was a young inventor and, you know,
there was an evil industrialist and all the fun stuff. It was good.
Can I ask if the goat was the goat of the dynamite?
What was 100 percent? We had the goat in there. It was great.
I'll tell you, since it'll probably never see the light of day.
The gag was the hero is tied up in the mines
and he goes his hands are tied behind his back with rope
and he goes over to the goat wanders in and he goes over to the goat
and tries to get the goat to chew his bonds off.
But when he turns around, the goats got the dynamite in his mouth.
And then he's like, no, no, no, no, no.
And the goat backs away and knocks over a lantern and lights the fuse.
And so then we've we've got.
Tia, that's fine. Yeah, that's great. Great.
Yes. The mischievous nature, the way that there is an air to that goat,
like it knows what it's doing or like you question is that, yes,
it's somehow aware. So you're kind of playing with it.
That's pretty great. Yeah.
So, you know, and then it just there's there was
in the Florida version, at least a big thunder.
You know, there's the town scene with the flash flood.
It's all more articulated, I feel like, in a narrative sense in Florida,
because and again, I'm not an expert on this, but I think they didn't
they grafted on to
mine train and through Nature's Wonderland in California.
Like a lot of the real estate. Yeah. Is is from that ride.
Yeah. The little town.
Yeah. They take it.
And this was part of the old ride. Right.
Is that I think that's yeah, I believe so.
Maybe might have even predated there being a ride that might be like
50s, even pre mine.
I see like Griffith Park mini train type thing.
Yeah, yeah.
It just those little flats.
And I think people were fond of it.
It made sense within within Big Thunder.
I guess, you know, one more thing to ask about the movie,
but because now some of this, I guess the creation of this would have been after.
I think at the time there was no Barnabas T.
Bullion, the the character who resembles Tony Baxter,
who is like the supposed owner of the did you in some other way define
who is who is doing the mining operation?
Like was that up to you?
Like you could have maybe defined it
pre off Barnabas. I well, that's interesting.
There was no other than the original Imagineers notes, which made
which made reference to
there being cursed gold in the mountain
and that the mountain thundered when you stole the gold.
That was all I knew, really.
And other than that, I went around the ride and wrote down names
and stuff that are used in the theming and stuff.
It just spun stories out of that.
So I actually don't even know about the I know that there have
subsequently been comics and and other things that have elaborated on Big Thunder.
But I got to be honest, I don't know what they are.
So, you know, if this is part of that, S.E.A. stuff or.
That's exactly it is. Yes.
Yeah. I you know, I should know and I don't all that stuff.
But I noticed you guys did a whole show on it,
which I'm looking forward to listening to.
We sure did. We broke it down.
We know too much now.
We know Barnabas and his friend Jason Chandler and
various I think like there's like parrots and monkeys that are members of sea.
It's not entirely human.
We know too much now.
Yeah, it's the most it's one of the most impenetrable podcasts we've done.
That does. Have you guys had the opportunity to go to the skipper canteen in Florida?
Because that, you know, that that seems like ground zero for that mythos.
I don't know much about it, but it that whole thing looks like it's
was constructed to tell that story. So, you know.
Yeah, it has like one.
It has a room specifically for sea.
And it is not I was really building up in my mind about how awesome I think it's cool.
But I was building it up as some like amazing thing with like secret rooms,
like a secret room.
And then there's like a glass case with Fez's in them.
And that's kind of the biggest, coolest part of it.
We're like, oh, I know that's Dr.
Albert Falls is fed.
And you're like, very nice.
So it's cool.
But yeah, it's not Magellan's.
I think in Tokyo, Disney Sea is the much more elaborate, cool version of like their hangout.
So I think that's the place where you might the promise might be realized.
Interesting. Yeah, I get.
Yeah. Like so you're starting to see you're aware of sea.
And it is this mythology that's meant to tie together, not just, you know,
like there's frontier land rides in there, but a lot of adventure land, obviously.
And, you know, even I think in the eventual show of it,
it seems like the Matterhorn will be connected to it.
So it's a way to tie together anything that's sort of like older adventure based
or whatever. But were you like in your head, was your attempt at a big thunder movie
like because you've talked about it, like maybe like wanting to light up
all of frontier land in terms of relevance by by starting there.
Was it possible to you that then it like there's like that you're building
some kind of frontier land expanded universe that ties in even the restaurants
or the Golden Horseshoe or somehow the bears are part of it, too,
if the if the bears could possibly be part of the same mythology
as Robert Downey Jr., the cocksure cowboy.
Absolutely. I had, you know, an idea that
for making the big thunder thing into a trilogy
that actually was going to culminate in
a subject that you guys might know about.
It was going to be a play on the Winchester Mansion.
Yes. Yeah. The the the elaborately built,
the insanely built mansion that was made to house the ghosts of
those who were killed by the Winchester rifles.
And it was going to be sort of
I was going to go through the weird west and sort of that was going to be it,
because that's that's sort of my bag.
But it was going to be the folk tales,
ghost stories and basically all the the folklore of the west,
the campfire stories, tall tales, which they've already got.
You know, in Florida, they got the tall tale cafe,
pick a spill tall tale cafe,
which I had the opportunity to have a closer look at recently.
And they've got a lot of theming in that they've got, you know, little
the ideas that all of Pecos Bill's
tall tale friends gifted him
mementos to decorate the cafe.
So you've got a giant axe from Paul Banyan that's like
signed to my friend Pecos Bill on the handle and stuff like that.
But but it had like Zorro and then even things like Annie Oakley.
And it really ran the gamut of all the sort of
colorful characters of the West.
And, you know, you definitely could put something together for that.
The problem is just the idea of taming the frontier
is pretty gnarly and in all respects.
Yeah, there's there's just not it's like neither taming the land
nor subjugating the the locals, you know, are things we
we care to celebrate anymore.
So it's problematic.
That's why I thought you go to stories and folklore and
and we all know ghost stories and campfires.
Oh, sure.
So if it's it's more the Wild West of the imagination and this exaggerated
like the the tales they told, not the real people who were probably
not probably who were there.
There was bad, bad things, but things you don't want to celebrate work.
Yeah, it wasn't like Deadwood meets Big Thunder Mountain.
Yeah, the pitch, the blood Meridian, the no country for old men.
Disneyland, Disneyland's no country for old men.
The Golden Corral is full of prostitutes.
There's just no way around it.
It has to be the case.
It's funny, you say the Winchester Mystery House, because that's
it seems like you were ahead of that, too, because then isn't it?
Correct me if I'm wrong, everyone.
Mystic Manor is based sort of on the Winchester Mystery House.
Well, they believe that the Disney Dish podcast has been discussing it recently
because like Walt and I think it's Kenny Anderson, one of the early
imagineers went to the Winchester Mystery House and just kept taking tours all day
once just as they were coming up with how to do a haunted house.
So like and first off, how do people behave in this environment,
in like a walking tour?
And then also, how do they react to like ghost stories and hauntings
and that sort of thing?
So it's been alive in the company for many, many years.
It's been I guess it's probably influenced every haunted house
they've made, haunted mansion and Mystic Manor and everything like that.
Yeah, I think I think it was very early,
you know, roadside attraction, kind of like
ghost story roadside attraction.
Sure, sure, sure.
Well, it seems like that's where because like some of it in talking about
Frontierland, it like,
yeah, where it stands currently is like it's it's all sort of the lead up
to Big Thunder Mountain.
That's in all of them, at least in the first four part
in the American ones in Tokyo and Paris.
And then it's like and we're not like
it's all been light in new attractions for sure since about 1980 or even before.
I mean, Frontierland's always been sort of an attraction light area.
It's more about but vibe.
But like, yeah, they've basically they've kind of like stopped doing them.
Like Shanghai does not have one.
And then Hong Kong Disneyland opened without one.
And now there's kind of kind of an equivalent, which is the whole area
is called Grizzly Gulch, I believe.
OK, which is where this it's and I don't have the name ready to go.
But there what is their grizzly ride that's sort of like Big Thunder?
Oh, right. Right.
It's called the big grizzly runaway mine cars.
So pretty pretty good at spelling out what it does.
And then Paris has the Frontierland,
which is the Thunder Mesa town that ties together the story of Phantom Manor
and all. And they also have the Legends of the Wild West show
has been going since the mid 90s there.
So it's interesting to see how the Wild West is presented at the Disney parks.
Internationally, yeah, it's kind of like catered to like the place
where they're building the park.
And what is the awareness of even any of that?
Like in Tokyo, there's the thing that they don't really know the word frontier.
That doesn't mean anything to them.
So it became Western land.
It's completely changed there.
But I guess I guess what I'm getting at is like it's like for there to be anything
else in this area for Disney that they have to go more fantastical.
It's got to be here's a weird like mine car situation
where bears are causing havoc to your right.
Or is is Mystic Manor in their version of Frontierland or is that its own?
I don't think I know what land it's in.
No, it is not. OK, OK.
I don't think it is.
Which is funny, because in Tokyo, you can buy merchandise
that is just like you stepped in the 1950s as far as Frontierland is concerned.
You can buy like what Tomahawks and things.
Yes, honestly, like I think you could buy like maybe a headdress.
Like that could be totally wrong.
But you could buy like little figurines just as if they were from the 1950s.
Like it's totally like they just haven't.
The memo hasn't gotten there yet.
That like you should probably not do this.
Well, even into the 90s, I bought like like fake flintlock pistols
or like six shooters like in Frontierland.
And they're like, it's crazy now to think about like carrying those back
in a duffel bag on a plane.
But I think I think even then my parents were like, put that in the checklist.
Don't carry it on the plane.
But while we were talking about that, you know,
I had been thinking about researching for this episode.
I was like, what was my reference for Westerns growing up?
Like because I had a spaghetti Western phase two in college
watching all the Sergio Leone movies.
And I was like, what was it before that?
And besides syndicated television, I'm like, it is Frontierland.
The simulation, I went back and reread.
I talked about a while ago, like the idea of simulation and simulacrum,
which simulation is, you know, a recreation of a real life thing.
Simulacrum, I've seen it described as a copy without an original.
And sometimes that's like you're so far removed from the original.
And that's kind of what a lot of the Frontierland stuff is.
But I was like, oh, yeah, I knew the Davy Crockett song in the late 1980s
because of Frontierland and like repeats on the early Disney Channel.
Yeah, that's that makes sense.
That's probably my first like big thing with it, too, where I was not.
I was a Star Wars kid and Star Trek kid superhero kid.
So that was probably my oh, this is like I like this because I walked through it.
A facsimile of this place that was in movies that other generations liked.
Well, and like theme parks, it feels like a like it's such a like,
you know, like a constant theme park presence is I feel like at least in America,
almost every theme park probably has some something that is vaguely Western themed.
It's like one of the like one of the primary themes, maybe in a way,
one of the easiest themes to do, because if you don't have a lot of money,
it can just be like, here's a shitty looking house.
Yes. A bunch of playing.
So would you do it right if you do it to the Disney level?
It's not just shitty is what it is.
Everything's on payment.
So, you know, at the very least, you save on paint.
Oh, yes. Yeah, sure.
That's what's. Yeah.
For not having you from a great theme park.
Oh, yeah. No, no, I hadn't thought about this until you put it this way, Scott.
But really, the approach is not different than what they did with
Tomorrowland to sort of remake it from a showcase of new technologies
to this imaginary spaceport that, you know, I don't know if you guys remember
before they changed over to the, you know,
but when it was the Wedway people mover and not the Tomorrowland Transit Authority.
But basically, they overlaid an entire theme of Tomorrowland
being a spaceport for visiting aliens.
And none of that was present when I was a kid.
None of that fantasy element.
It was supposed to be, I mean, pre Epcot.
It was supposed to be the world of the future.
It was supposed to be this is what we will what what we are headed towards, you know.
And so but then they put the overlay of making, oh, it's the future,
but it's it's silly made up future.
This is the same thing.
I mean, it's the past.
But, you know, go into things like all that folklore,
like, you know, gremlins and whatever all they have.
You could mine the history of Americana for a million kinds of native folklore.
I mean, even getting into things like Bigfoot and stuff like that
would be suitable for frontier land.
There's there's a ton of things they could do it.
You know, the wild places are still wild.
So everyone's got their local folklore.
That's just to me seems like the answer.
Sure. Jersey Devil and, you know, Jersey Devil.
Yep. All that.
The best man.
The zoology stuff. Yes. Yes. Absolutely.
It's like it had you have to lean into fun theatrical nonsense.
You can't go to the realism of what the future is going to be like
because it's always wrong.
It's it's obsolete within five to 10 years.
And it's the same way with like a land like frontier land, where it's like it's
it's based on what humans used to be like.
Well, they used to be very bad.
You know how they're bad now?
They were very bad back then.
So it's like we can't do that.
It was pretty bad.
Yeah, exactly.
You would even you know, he'd be a G like prison in two seconds today.
The best thing, you know, what was even worse?
Medicine.
So you've got bad people.
You've got no medicine.
Everything smells like shit.
The food tastes like shit.
You know, yes.
The safest thing is whiskey.
Yeah, the whole world stinks.
The whole world smells so bad.
But it's like everyone's probably doing their best to try to make the balance
right between being culturally appropriate, making sure everything is represented
correctly and also just like, yeah, and then there's a goat.
There's a fun goat.
Like, you know, it's all there.
I think everyone, from what I understand at Disney and every
of these other companies are like doing their best to try to hit that perfect balance.
Well, yeah, you know, there used to be a gold
polished brass plaque outside of Pirates of the Caribbean in Florida.
And it said it was, you know, it was there to entice you to go in,
as if that was necessary.
But it said, see a band of fun, loving pirates
sack and burn a Caribbean seaport.
And that always made me laugh.
Those fun loving guys just out to sack and burn a Caribbean seaport.
It's not there anymore.
But it's insane, really, to think about it that way,
because there's no here like now Jack Sparrow is on the ride.
But the ride doesn't have a hero in it.
There's no one like it's a celebration of bad behavior.
Yeah, exactly.
Like Rise of the Resistance, like you're the hero and Finn is there and Ray is there.
But like it's good and bad. Yeah.
And then like you get out of the ship. Right.
But the pirates are just like, hey, let's go party with these maniac killers.
Let's just go have an ale with them. Yeah.
Yeah. We're kind of telling you the whole lesson.
You you caught it right.
That the lesson is don't do this because you'll have all those riches
and you'll be alone. I think. Is that the message?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Let's have a party with these maniacs.
Yeah. Be careful.
You might turn into a skeleton, which sorry.
OK, we're realizing now that is awesome.
Yeah, we messed up.
We were going to turn into a bad ass skeleton.
Yeah, they're a skeleton on top of like a pile of money, which is awesome.
It's like they're not even they didn't even die alone.
They died with just a bunch of cool stuff around them with like they're like friends.
I guess maybe they're not necessarily in the cave next to each other,
but it doesn't look that bad.
My body is not going to be holding like a cool chalice.
I'm just going to be like dead in a field or something.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yes. To be preserved as the pirates are.
It's so cool.
It's funny they didn't think about that because I think one of the reoccurring
themes in these parks is the people behind it over thinking about stuff.
Because when they opened Walt Disney World,
the one thing that I kept coming across
that plays into the unbuilt Western River Expedition attraction,
the one thing that kept coming up that they'd run into
was people would approach gas members and go, where's pirates?
Where's this pirates ride we've heard so very much about?
And they're like, oh, that's that's the other one that's on the other coast.
And then and then they real quick turned around and cloned
pirates for Walt Disney World because it's like, yeah, sometimes it is as simple
as people want to go on the thing they've heard so much about, you know.
Sure. Sure. And I think I heard even more to that story,
which is even more over thinking, which is they they reckoned that.
Eastern audiences would want us that they would find cowboys exotic,
whereas they'd find pirates a part of their local culture.
So like the East Coast, you're you're you already know all about pirates.
You've seen a bunch of pirates growing up places like, I don't know, Savannah,
things like that. I mean, they were like there were pirates
as part of that local culture.
But yeah, they thought nobody on the East Coast is going to want to see pirates.
They're going to want to see cowboys.
Due to proximity to the Caribbean, I don't you grew up in Florida, Dennis.
I can't imagine there were a lot of pirates in your
negative, although a little of that sort of thing.
You'd see like in St. Augustine and stuff.
So, I mean, it's not it's not completely insane.
The local the chachkis that you could buy
as a Florida tourist in that day, there would be probably some pirate coins
and that sort of stuff that as much as you would find cowboy hats and,
you know, bowie knives or whatever out west, you know.
But but but it's still a crazy idea
to think that they were serving a need by
regionalizing the entertainment like that.
I'm going to care. It's just pirate this pirate that wherever you are in Florida
and Georgia and North Carolina.
I that is so funny because I hadn't heard that about that about pirates.
But I've heard other imagineers say stuff like that.
And I always think of it. Oh, yes, they are 100 percent correct.
There's no way they could possibly be wrong about it.
And the one that pops to mind was like in France,
people in France like comedy and ghosts,
but they did not understand when ghosts were funny.
They did not understand when it could be like haunted and comedy.
And I went, oh, yes, of course, that must be correct.
And I was like, wait a minute, maybe that's not correct.
Maybe there's just a weird overthink imagineer
like brain where it's like we must anticipate.
And it's like if it's good, the audience would like it.
That's really at the end of the day.
But they want to make sure.
The two haunted mansions in America, the the the New Orleans
Square one at Disneyland, you know, is a big southern plantation house
because like this will be wild for California.
They don't have this kind of house here.
And then in Florida, it's like, oh, they got all these column houses.
Make it look like this one in Baltimore.
You know, they look like the Northeast. Right.
Yeah, it's strange.
I know. Well, let's let's talk a little about Western River Expedition,
because we've talked about it a little on the show,
and it's probably a full episode to be done about it.
But yeah, if you don't know that mythology, that there was going to be this
there was this whole expansion pad that was meant to be a whole original land
Thunder Mesa that was like an outgrowth of frontier land.
But it was going to be this multi ride campus that resembled Big Thunder Mountain.
And it probably would have had a big thunderous ride, but then also
an equivalent of Pirates of the Caribbean with Mark Davis at the helm.
Great imagineer known for his like especially being especially good at like
comedy tableaus.
And there was going to be this like just wild,
animatronic, rich attraction that I feel like that's it's got to be in the top five of
oh, if it could have been like an unbuilt attractions, it seems like.
And from art that exists and just rumors about what it could have.
And if it truly was pirates level, I mean, it could have changed
the the fabric of the park were it to exist.
Huge. Yeah, it's like it seems like a bit giant.
It would have been like, I mean, I know I've heard there's like
I'm sure there would have been stuff that has to change about it
as far as like theming and characters and stuff.
But like it definitely feels like it would be in the top five or 10 things.
I feel like that's the vibe from it would have been like that's
that would still be there today.
That's one of the mega things, even like Pirates of Haunted Mansion,
that like it's untouchable, maybe.
Yeah, I think because of the nature of that,
that's one of the like half dozen things that sunk the project
where it's like it would have been such an expensive undertaking.
It would have had like they were talking about doing a backwards segment,
you know, and all these animatronics.
And, you know, I think tastes were already changing.
The Western was kind of already on its way out.
And there was concern, you know, starting about the portrayal of Native Americans
and like, oh, are we going to be able to have that in this area?
So like there was a lot of things working against it.
And then when they're like, we got to get something else.
We needed another attraction in here.
And people keep asking for the pirates.
So just make a shorter pirates. Right. Right.
I so what we ended up with was like a minimal lot like
like Tony Baxter took the reins and said,
I think there's a version we could do that is the mine train roller coaster.
And it's only that.
And it's pretty wild to look at the concept art where like, well, there's that.
But it's bigger.
And there's a boat ride going in and out.
And it would have taken up the space that at Disney World is currently
not only Big Thunder, but also Splash Mountain.
Like all of that is one huge campus with this super ambitious ride.
Yeah. And the the the kind of comes back around later on
in in terms of big picture, like they want when they wanted to do
the Indiana Jones ride at Disneyland, that was going to be a massive thing.
And the Jungle Cruise was going to go through that.
So they've definitely like aimed for the stars before.
And then inevitably, the grandeur gets scaled back when you're like,
well, we have a time frame and we also have a budget.
So let's start chopping away at this. You know, right. Right.
Dennis, do you have like a favorite in terms of like in your theme park
Wanderings, is there like a most intrigued thing that never opened?
Is it this or or is it something in the in the Westcott world or like is it?
Do you have like an unbuilt that comes to mind?
I have spent probably more time thinking about Western River
expedition than anything else. Fascinated by it.
Like you say, it would have they were trying to outdo themselves on pirates.
So I think it just would have been outstanding. I mean,
it just such an interesting for starters, just the idea of a river
ride through the Wild West is kind of weird to begin with.
And it seems like they were stuck on the pirates model
and didn't completely switch it over.
So just that being the beginning of it.
And from what I gather, the Thunder Mountain portion of it
was on the roof of the show building.
And it just, as you say, it would have been this this vast thing.
But, you know, sort of adjacent to this,
I heard and maybe you guys can fill in some details.
This fascinated me if I was going to pick something other than
Western River Expedition.
I heard rumors that the Disneyland Railroad was going to stop
in Frontierland or at the Frontierland station
and enact a version of the first act of or the sorry,
the cold open of the Indiana Jones and the Last Crusade,
where River Phoenix is
doing the shoot them up on the wherever that is, Monument Valley and stuff.
I had heard that they were going to have a show scene
that reenacted that Indiana Jones segment
while you were riding the train.
Do you have you guys ever heard anything about that?
I always heard of it as like an amphitheater kind of show.
And yes, the train they may have tried to they're like, oh,
we can't run the train and we can't use it in the show simultaneously.
Yeah, I have.
We're trying to do the math of like, could there be a version
where the train goes through a like Waterworld type show?
And that's part of it, which is insane to think about.
God knows if they pulled it off.
But like, how do you how do you possibly?
It's a fascinating idea.
And I love the idea of linking these attractions and stuff.
You mentioned that the jungle cruise going through
the Temple of the Forbidden Eye or whatever, however they used to have it.
It's a fascinating idea.
I love that the Paris
Haunted Mansion is is the guy who owns Big Thunder Mine or whatever.
Isn't that the backstory there?
Is it the isn't the the house, the supposed to be the home of the mine owner?
Yes, I think that's right.
I'm I didn't know any of this.
I just figured all this out in researching for this.
But yeah, it's not there's no Barnabas no Barnabas bullion there.
So this might have been the first to find who owns Big Thunder Mountain.
Henry Ravenswood and then his his daughter
a factory like his daughter is the bride in Phantom Manor,
who's they're engaged to be married after his daughter, Melanie,
fell in love with a penniless miner.
Mr. Ravenwood's vengeful spirit killed the would be groom.
Wait, it's the death.
So it's the evil Big Thunder owner is the Phantom or the Phantom.
Is the Phantom that is the fine? Yeah.
Wow. The sort of Vincent Price voice, depending on when you've been on it.
Phantom. Wow.
Just because he like didn't like the because she OK, because it was a penniless
miner. So imagine if you're the owner of the mine and then it's some minor bumpkin
who's going to marry my rich daughter.
He's upset because of the socioeconomic disparity.
I there's only one solution.
I have to I got to kill this guy.
And then he's like eternally punished for having which is that's not a good
if you're like if your daughter is getting ready for the wedding, don't
kill the husband.
I can't imagine many scenarios where that's a good idea.
No, no, don't do that.
But that's interesting.
I don't actually don't know how it fits into sea.
I really wonder if that's a big problem.
And they like to retcon that more for sea.
So it fits neatly into the the Barnabas Canon or maybe not.
Maybe they don't care.
They're going to have to.
They're going to have to cast Ravenswood.
They'll deal. But this is all Ronald D.
Moore's problem, I guess.
Now, it's probably keeping him up at night.
How do I come out of a universe where there is Ravenswood and Boolean?
It can't be done.
Yes, what writer could ever.
But isn't that isn't that cool?
Oh, and wait, here's some other stuff in that version.
They do acknowledge the stealing of the land
from from Native America.
So in this world, there is this factors.
So he's like punished by being a phantom in Phantom Manor.
And then meanwhile, all the shit's hitting the fan at Big Thunder
because they stole that land from the Shoshone people
and therefore angering the Thunderbird.
There is a Big Thunderbird spirit over there,
and that's why there's earthquakes and things exploding and everything.
Like so they do.
This is an example of like they're tying all the rides together
and they're acknowledging you did bad stuff.
You're going to get punished by an angry bird spirit.
I mean, that's I don't know that you maybe pick up on all of that.
If you just go on it once.
I would say you pick up on zero.
No, it's only reading a Wikipedia later.
But right, right. You can't.
That is up to you to do.
Yeah, it's there, which is nice.
But even like in that frontier land, which is, you know, I've
I've definitely tucked my share of shit about Disneyland, Paris,
and I will say their frontier land, which could be the last new frontier land,
potentially.
And so that was like the kids who grew up on old frontier land get their shot.
And I think they did it so beautifully and tying everything together.
It's like it's so ornate and the coolest place in the park to be.
And also, like the restaurants are part of it, too.
If you read the full mythology, like, well, the saloon is where they would blow off steam
and then the fancy steakhouse is owned by this guy's brother.
Like they managed to connect like the restaurants and the stores.
It all actually makes sense in a proto
galaxy's edge kind of way, which I was like excited to hear all that.
And Dennis, I know you're like probably your ideal of a theme park experience.
It has all of this math worked out and where there's characters walking around
and there's a backstory and it is you almost in are in like a weird
alternate reality that does make logical and thematic sense.
So they did kind of do it there.
That's yes, I love that.
And, you know, you'd be I was surprised to find out
that that technique is seemingly applied everywhere.
I some years ago, I was staying at the boardwalk in Florida,
the Disney boardwalk, and they advertised there was a sign in the lobby
that said, take a guided tour of the hotel.
And, you know, 9 a.m. or something like that.
And so I show up down in the lobby at 9 a.m.
And I'm the only guy there at all for the for the tour.
And I got a very knowledgeable
cast member who was excited to have someone to tell
everything he knew about.
But but what I was struck by was he pointed out in the construction
of the hotel, it was made to simulate
it having been built over decades.
There being additions
onto the building and so on and so forth, even down to the
where like certain hallways don't align properly
because they reckon that they would have had,
you know, structural problems adding a new wing onto the building.
So they they sort of engineered fake problems they had to solve.
And so from what I could tell,
just something as as seemingly non narrative
as the boardwalk in seems to have its whole history of the of the structure
planned out and why not?
I mean, I was saying if I was in charge of
Galaxy's Edge or sort of looking at a way to to show run
Galaxy's Edge, like I would find like blaster marks
on the walls and ceilings and stuff and make stories of like who shot the gun
that, you know, and so that you just and who cares
if any of this gets written down or or passed on?
But, you know, you point out insignificant details
and you give stories to them.
And then I think, you know, everyone's having a great time.
We went and saw last time I was in the Florida Park.
We went and saw you guys probably heard about the miniature door.
I'd got outside Gaston's Tavern.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I don't might be stomping us.
Interesting. Well, OK.
I'll break this story here.
Oh, my God, I had just heard about it on Snopes or something.
And I happen to be there.
And it's very much like what you describe with the Figaro sign
in one of your other episodes.
Pulling the rope.
Oh, yes. Yeah.
Pulling it's in the wrong spot in Fantasyland and Disneyland.
But then they put it in the right spot in Disneyland Paris.
And he's given an OK sign like I did it right this time.
Which is fantastic.
I had never most of the most mundane information in my brain.
I loved it. I loved it.
But likewise, it evidently in in the area
backed by Gaston's Tavern in Fantasyland,
they built a a building too close to a manhole cover.
So the edge of the building was
was sitting on top of the manhole lid.
So it wouldn't have been able to raise the manhole lid.
So what they did is they cut a little piece of the wall out
so that you'd be able to lift the lid.
But rather than just make a little hole or something like that,
they made a tiny door.
And it's seemingly this purposeless,
bizarre little 12, 14 inch high door over there.
But as you say, they they made a mistake
and they came up with a whimsical, clever way to sort of fix the mistake.
So what's the door for, do we think?
Well, the door is is just so you can remove a piece of the wall
so that you can lift the lid of the manhole cover.
OK. Yeah.
But there's no mythology of like this is where somebody lives.
That it was not that I know of.
Well, that's what I was thinking. Is it LeFou's door?
It's like talking.
It could be LeFou.
It could be that it could be that leprechaun
we were talking about, the little man of Disneyland.
Oh, yeah. Summer place. Yeah. Yeah.
One that was I didn't know that one for the longest time.
Yeah, I think Mike and Jason both did.
And I was stumped on little man of Disneyland.
But together, all of us are finding every certainly every obscure door.
We're going to know the story of every door there is.
By the time this is all done.
Dennis, we should also give you credit for alerting us to the tangled
the restroom area, which we did on the second gate.
You would have this fancy that that dissection.
Well, exactly. And why not?
You know, they why not build a restroom complex with features?
You know, yeah, it's it's deeds.
I mean, if you if you're like us and go this much like the details,
it's like the thing that keeps you going back.
I feel like if it weren't for that, if it weren't for a theme toilet, why go back?
Yeah, I guess that's what I'm saying.
In terms of details and we can
cut this if I'm thinking of the wrong person.
Dennis, I Scott told us something once
or did you come up with the idea for something?
A day plan called exile on Main Street?
Yes. Yes. OK.
So this is because I have been thinking, I think Scott told us this years ago.
And I think about it, it just bubbles into my mind every few months.
Because I think I could do it.
I well, we I would love to do with you guys.
I think we should do it and and and document the experience.
And I think it would it be
it'd be maybe a little easier out here than it would be in Florida.
But I think so.
For the those who don't know, my the my idea would be to have a day
at Disneyland called exile on Main Street.
And the rules would be that you would be forbidden from
going beyond the confines of mainstream.
You have to spend the whole day in the park from park open to park
close on Main Street.
And you'd have to try to entertain yourself through the duration.
And I think with the cinema running and if they're making
candy apples and stuff, you know, I think you get around
and, you know, dapper dance and some carriage rides.
Omnibus omnibus.
I do every type of transportation.
Yeah, every type of transportation.
And I think according to the rules, I set out, you are allowed one ride on
a ground 360 ride on the railroad.
But no stopping.
You don't get off and get off and you can't ride the railroad all day
is what I think I figured.
But but yeah, we should try that sometimes.
The I know the Florida park, for example, they blow glass in the the the
they have a working furnace where they're, you know, shaping glass and burning.
And things like that.
They've got that in Disneyland.
Do they have that here too?
Yeah, yeah. There's a little silhouette.
A little show they have.
We all get so we all get so it's so eating.
Eating is easy.
You can go to the
at some point you eat at Carnation Cafe.
At some point you eat at the plaza, right?
And then you got Holly Jolly for I think that counts.
Holly Jolly Bakery is that's the boundary.
Probably that would be the boundary.
I think I was in check and you could do.
Yeah, so this is decent food.
And you could have a decent days where the Starbucks, you know, market house.
Sorry, market Starbucks.
And Starbucks and I Starbucks.
There's two. We've said too many.
Honestly, I don't know if we'll have time for all of it.
It's got to be frankly, it might have to do three days. Yeah.
Exactly. Well, I actually I think I came up with the idea
because I was killing time once while my girlfriend had to
do a business call or something.
And I didn't want to get too far away or so.
I don't know what my reason was, but I ended up spending about two hours
with nothing to do on Main Street.
And you guys probably know this, but some of at least one in the alley there
on whatever they call that center street or whatever.
One of the buildings has a whole little audio program of
of of of of the occupants of the upstairs rooms and everything.
And that's the stuff that you know, going back to Frontierland,
the this the log cabin fort
that is still standing out in the Florida version
has animatronics in it and everything.
There's a there's a guy sleeping in the in the guard
in the guardhouse and guys hammering
horseshoes and things like that.
But like it's they've got all that those those background
atmosphere, sound effect loops going and everything.
That's just great.
Yeah, that would be I mean, that is a day that I've wanted to do
is really just like and this I am truly not joking at all.
Want to focus on the loops in the park.
I want to go like listen to the loops for like 20 minutes and pinpoint
where all of them are.
This is that no, I'm not joking.
I swear.
Loops. Well, loopy for loops.
Correct. The the market house.
I think they kept it when they switched to Starbucks,
but there's a phone in there.
Yeah. Pick up that's a party phone. Yes.
Yeah. I listened to the entire program on this occasion
where I was killing time and it is it's very funny.
And they they sketch out like a whole Springfield of
of of town residents that have got, you know,
that are you can't remember what any of the jokes were,
but they they had running jokes in the thing and it was a well produced.
I don't know who wrote it or, you know,
what whether the thing is they mentioned coffee a lot.
So I almost think Starbucks maybe
punched it out.
Paid for a little coffee play.
Exactly. But that sort of thing.
Yeah. The squawky old phones was the best.
Wow. Yeah.
And then you made maybe also do Lincoln like a couple times.
Like, make sure you see you get a full sense of what he looks like
on all sides from the back.
Just every vantage point.
Front row Lincoln, back row Lincoln in the pit, in the GAP.
Learn if he plays to the entire crowd or like, does he not really have
like the sense of the space that a performer should have?
That's true. Yeah.
Get to Lincoln, get in the pit, you know.
Look up his nostrils.
And then we take, OK, we go and we do we see Lincoln,
but then we take like X to see we take Molly and then we go back
to see Lincoln again and see what the experience is like that way.
And so lots of drugs are part of the exile on mainstream.
That's a different. Yeah.
Yeah, that that makes. Yeah.
Go ahead. Go ahead.
No, no, I was just going to say that might make it seem eternally long, too.
You never know.
Yeah. It's either either would help you pass the time or it would make it.
When do we leave until I'm in 45 minutes?
And you spend you spend like a couple hours like passed out on a toilet.
Just like shaking in a fetal position.
Freaking out.
Well, you have described something
it certainly sounds like something we would do.
This is we have punished ourselves with with less with less to do.
So it's actually I think we totally good.
Well, right, because didn't you guys devote an entire show
to every retail outlet and Universal City Walk?
Didn't we? Well, a lot of episodes.
It was just 19.
That's 19. Just a clean 19.
That's when I that's when I met Scott and I was tremendously impressed with that.
I yeah.
Well, we were working together and I would do it almost every day of that run
was like, listen, I got to go.
I got to get up to city walk again.
We're doing yogurt land or 16.
Yeah.
Got to go try some menchies.
That's the job.
But that worked out very well because Dennis, when we were working together,
I feel like there was there were so many days where you would like,
you know, mid afternoon say like, I want to head to the park.
What do you think?
It's a park day.
That's right. It was like this guy's speed.
This is great.
And I let's let's let's get a little more frontier land in before we wrap it up.
I guess like in terms of like
like like what have we missed?
You know, so one of the thesis, I think, of talking about frontier land for a while
is like, is there relevancy to it?
Like, are we have we seen all the frontier lands get built that we're going to see?
And is there ever going to be a new attraction in a frontier land?
Could you not see a world where for dear land as it is now
and has been for a couple of decades does not change per se
other than like eliminating things?
That's that's the dark potential future.
Yeah, I've heard I mean, I've heard just from people,
friends who have inquired about things to pitch or whatever.
I do think Disney is still trying to figure out Big Thunder something.
Like, at least that's what they were told.
So maybe they're like, I don't know, but they're probably trying to figure out Big Thunder
something. I think that they'll probably still make attempts
to make the places in Disney relevant
through like Disney plus or a movie or something.
But barring that, yeah, I could see them just being like,
you know, we could get rid of that whole land.
But I think that, yes, if anything else doesn't happen, I mean,
I don't know. I think everything things aren't as untouchable as people think they are.
That's what that's the sense I get. I could be totally wrong.
But, you know, 10, 10, 20 years from now,
I wouldn't bet money that it's there.
Well, a few years ago, they there was a temporary attraction
called the Heroes of Frontierland, which was like a game, an interactive game
where you would go and interact with characters and go to locations and stuff.
And it is not dissimilar to kind of what the not ghost town.
There's elements of that in not ghost town.
But I think after the fact, I heard, oh, this was play testing for Star Wars
stuff for like, you know, which they kind of scaled back the interaction
at Galaxy's Edge, but it could also whatever lessons they learned
from that Frontierland testing, they could be applying at the,
you know, the hotel.
Yeah. Big, big thunder is the thing, I think, keeping Frontierland alive.
Yeah, because it's just beloved.
Insanely popular.
It's not even like the historical nature of it's just like, oh,
it's a big roller coaster that everyone likes.
Like, yeah, that every age can go on any coaster willingness.
Yeah, it really is perfect.
If Galaxy's Edge like extends back, I mean, Galaxy's Edge already
swallowed some of Frontierland, it swallowed a part of Jason's
favorite part of Frontierland, which is goats.
There used to be the goats that you would see in Frontierland.
And Jason, I many, many times over the last decade, he would go,
let's go back and see the goats.
And if there was a wait, I mean, you could always walk in and see the goats.
So you needed somewhere quiet, you know, somewhere to be around nature.
They did keep the bar, the pond, the mossy pond
with the big old tunnel from previous attractions that survived.
The mechanical fish.
There's usually a mechanical fish right there.
Yeah, that's right.
Little guy. Oh, boy.
There's some these are some deep corners that the I.
But yeah, I don't know.
Like, yeah, things have already gotten swallowed.
Like, I think no land has lost more
like territory than Frontierland, if you think about it,
because some of it becomes New Orleans Square, some of it becomes
bear country, which becomes greater country.
And then like the big expansion pad.
I feel like it was always a weird thing about like clearly the air.
The biggest area they had to work with was that big Thunder Ranch zone.
And like that's always like this could be the big
the biggest expansion Disneyland ever does.
And of course, that ended up being Galaxy's Edge.
And I think the reason nothing happened sooner
is that it was kind of something back there would have had to be
Frontierland and Western themed.
And there's only so many things that that can be.
And they never had a hit movie that that prompted something to go back there.
There was the we've heard that rumor of like an Oz stunt show
or something based on the James Franco.
Ozland, Ozland.
That was going to be like riots, too.
Yeah, yes.
You say way you can segue from like rural
Frontierland or rural Kansas to the, you know, the Emerald City.
You had the show in a little.
It sounds, by the way, other than the Franco movie connection, it sounds awesome
because you go in a little tent.
There would be a little like medicine show type thing.
The tent would like spin around while you were in there.
Then the thing would open and you were in Oz.
And it was full Ozland with like for I think it was a Tony Baxter interview
where he didn't even want to reveal the ride technology that it was
because it might still be used eventually for something
or maybe it has been at this point.
But it sounds like there was a crazy ticket
Oz ride with a very, very themed land back there.
Yeah. Since you mentioned Tony, by the way, there is video online
of him giving a presentation from D23 a while ago,
going through the concept art for Western River Expedition and saying like,
so then this would have happened and this would have happened.
Like this is a sample like song that they use when discussing it and like
and kind of associating it with Pirates of the Caribbean.
It's like, well, this is sort of the equivalent of the big,
you know, chase scene that would be this scene instead, you know. Right.
Oh, and you know what? Also, real quick, Tony also talked about
the other thing that might have been in frontier land, which is Geyser Mountain.
Geyser. Do you know about Geyser Mountain, Dennis?
I don't. I've heard rumors about a fire mountain over the years.
But I never heard Geyser Mountain.
Fire Mountain I've heard to fight.
I think that's what would have gone somewhere else.
But Geyser Mountain was basically like you were a group of tourists
on a tour going below the surface to take a look at like miners,
what they're doing down there.
So you'd go down.
I think they were actually going to build it.
So it was kind of underground partly.
So basically it's the Tower of Terror,
but it's like half of the tower is more underground and the other half's above.
And it's this big like mining rig.
So you go down and you'd see animatronics of miners and miners.
And all of a sudden they would like, you know, alarms would go off
and there's a geyser and then water would shoot up all around you
as you shot out of the ground up.
And then you could see like all of Disneyland.
And this is before they built Tower at California Adventure.
But that was very much, I think, possible that it would go
like around that area of Galaxy's Edge and the barbecue restaurant and everything.
Yeah, yeah. It it looked like there is like more concept art of that than I knew.
I was finding it recently.
And we're like that is like Tower of Terror in Florida,
where the car is moving from room to room and then you end up in the launch.
Oh, it was like you're like forward and stuff, too.
It wasn't just amazing. So cool.
And like the other thing that sounds great about this is that this was like
it was more recent than I realized they wanted to do this in like late
90s, early 2000s, which in like with that,
you have maybe the people who end up like you're in the same
like late 90s Disney prowess as Disney Sea.
Like so if that kind of had the vibe of Journey to the Center of the Earth
or one of the many other great attractions at Disney, see if it was done to that degree.
But then 9-Eleven happens.
DCA is struggling.
Let's just clone Tower and do less of it.
And when that's what it ends up being and then there's it be redundant
to have two similar things and one is more expensive.
But this was like this might even top Western River Expedition.
This sounds so good.
Yeah, from what I've seen, yeah, that sounds amazing.
It sounds really amazing.
And it's Western River partly felled by the economic downturn, too.
Yes. Coming at like we the seven economic downturn happens in the 70s.
It's like we just spent all this money to build a whole resort.
We cannot build another massive ride after we built all these other rides.
Yeah, it sucks.
I mean, media consolidation is really bad and these companies shouldn't do it.
But maybe the telecom should just buy Disney so we can do.
Get as many rides every year, regardless of the economy.
Maybe that's the solution.
It's us rides.
Well, we'll do.
But I guess, you know, all this to say like these these were these were our shots.
Now, there's just less frontier land.
There's there's not really,
you know, there's no bigger expansion you could do that one.
That Geyser Mountain also almost went to Paris, but didn't quite happen there
because Paris is always struggling and they got tower ultimately.
But like, I don't know, I like have we seen the last of Frontierland?
And how do you like I is there is there a possibility of a bright future for Frontierland?
Well, you know, here's my thought.
I have a co-worker with small kids and he said his son and daughter
who are maybe in the five year, four year range, they love their favorite thing
in Disney World was Tom Sawyer Island.
And I was thinking about this on the way over.
There is sort of a defunct spur of of imagineering
that they used to have, which was something a kid knew,
but like a insane gonzo version of it, you know, so like Swiss family treehouse,
like kids know what a treehouse is, but this is the most insane treehouse
you've ever seen in your life.
Or the old river country was supposed to be a swimming hole
like you might have in your community.
But this is the most insane swimming hole that's all tricked out and got all this stuff.
And so I was thinking there were these things like that.
Kids love to run around outside and explore the woods and stuff.
And it seems like they may not need to spend that much money to hit a target,
which is the kids running around unstructured play, just environments that
Disney used to excel at doing that sort of thing.
And they seem to have dropped off.
No doubt because of liability issues and other things like it.
But I mean, kids, you know, like the youngest kids, they still what
you give them an environment to play in and they're going to be down with it.
So my my two pitches for for them, if they were looking to revitalize
what they had on, you know, on a budget would be to invest in gamifying
those playground areas, whether something along the lines of
the Star Wars datapad game that they have where you interact with the environment
or the way you I think some of that
Harry Potter wizarding world where you're able to the magic wand can make things.
Little effects happen all over the windows and the doors.
Those, you know, endless delight if you're a kid and you use your cell phone
to make a gopher pop out of a hole or something like that.
But, you know, those those kind of cheap, tiny effects
like they have at the shooting gallery,
you know, that you can affect on your own.
I just feel like, you know, make it an interactive playground, gamify everything.
But then, you know, they have a pirate treasure hunt in Florida
that is self-guided, that operates little animatronic effects
that you activate with your magic band.
And it doesn't seem like that was a hit.
It doesn't seem like you always see people doing it.
But I guess they determined that was not the future of theme parks. But
it seems like it should be because kids play video games.
And if you gamify the experience
and give them collective digital collectibles,
you know, send them around Tom Sawyer Island on a scavenger hunt, for example.
Yeah. Oh, sure. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, there's not there's not like one experience that like encapsulates like
there's no collect them all kind of thing to do there.
It is interesting that like you say, you know,
everyone has a phone where they can play like high end games on them now, essentially.
But the shooting gallery, like an infrared shooting gallery
where you shoot a tin can that's like on a pole and rattles.
There's still people over there like they haven't gotten rid of it.
It's still there. It's still popular.
There's still a list on the Disneyland, a Disney World website, as hard as it is
to navigate that website of like,
here's where all the playgrounds are.
And they keep cannibalizing, you know, taking the the land
for other attractions and all like they did with the Honey I Shrunk the Kids
movie set play area.
But it's like, yeah, kill kids still need to run around and burn off energy.
So they take a nap.
You know, like that has not changed.
You know, right.
Nothing has replaced naps and hopefully never will.
And I saw an aerial photo of
of mine trade through nature's wonderland that had some of Tom Sawyer on it
visible in the photo.
And a lot of it was a gigantic like rock pile
that there were just all these children scampering on a gigantic
like pile of rocks, it looked like.
And it was it had to been two dozen kids on this vast
sort of like sort of boxcar sized pile of rocks that,
you know, and if they, you know, made that sort of thing a little safe,
kids will have fun with that all day long.
Scott, I feel like I called you once when I
for the first time, I visited that ranger park ranger out
that what I call the Tom Sawyer Island of DCA.
Oh, yes. Oh, you mean the yeah.
Yeah, the Redwood Trail, the challenge route. Yeah.
Yeah. Mm hmm.
It's tremendously, thoughtfully constructed.
It's just got the most boring theme that I could ever imagine.
I mean, it's just it's it's.
Some people will take umbra.
My friends, Tyler Keough will defend the the slice of the tree,
the slice of the Sequoia to to their death.
They that's where that's their favorite thing in the park.
But yes, some people are.
Yeah, some people might not disagree.
A lot of Park Ranger Brown and things like that, you know.
But but as far as a playground, I mean, the kids were going nuts
and it's multi level and it's very removed from the park.
It it's got an immersive feel.
And I don't know, like, you know, like I said,
there's got to be a million liability issues, but
but not forgetting that Disney used to do stuff like that,
provide sort of superior versions of sort of common childhood
pleasures, you know.
They got better, crazier playgrounds.
Yeah, yeah, absolutely.
That is the stuff I can't wait when my son's old enough.
Like I'm already ready.
He's going to go nuts for all those things we're talking about.
Yeah, so that's irrelevant.
Yeah, go ahead, Mike.
I was just going to say the other thing, and it's kind of stealing
what Nats is doing, but what I do like Nats as a ghost town,
it's, you know, it's frontier land.
But when Nats and what's fun about Nats is that it's just populated
with like Nats original characters now, like the mayor and,
you know, the way that they have a new character, Whittles,
who's the old prospector.
He's not a face like a human character, but he's like a cartoon character.
But it's like they just keep throwing like character and backstory
at their ghost town.
The maze they had a couple of years ago, and they're having it again this year
at the not scary farm is an origin story for the actual town,
like with a witch that looks like the witch from Wizard of Oz.
I feel like you could really make frontier like that.
To me, it's like the fastest way to make it feel really like fun
and vibrant and alive is like adding more characters, adding more people performing.
I don't think they're ever going to do this, but like steal from Nats
and just like have like a blustery mayor
yelling at people as you walk by in frontier land or something.
Like, it's great. It's real fun.
They think they used to go. Go ahead, Dennis.
No, I was going to say they still I know on Main Street, they still have
actors and actresses that pretend to be sort of colorful locals.
And I feel like they yes,
I feel like they might have that on Hollywood Boulevard at.
Yes, Hollywood Studios as well.
Like, you know, I, you know, period people, 1930s people.
So why they wouldn't have that in in Frontierland is beyond.
Yeah, I feel like they used to have shoot them ups on the roof.
When I was. Yes.
But you said above Country Bear in Florida, like there was there was some kind of stunt show.
They would have just impromptu
like they're robbing the bank and someone would chase the bad guys across the roof.
And there'd be some slapstick.
But why that stuff isn't going on constantly?
I mean, there are enough trained improv actors. Sure.
Not to do it. We'll do it. We'll do it.
If that's what you're getting at, we're ready to do that.
Have a shoot. I'm sure I think a lot of the parks in Southern California
are equity actors and they're not exactly cheap,
but it's cheaper than building an e-ticket ride.
You know, that's right. Yeah.
Look, three years Jason, I run a tarot team for three years.
So I think we're ready to do this.
Oh, man. Old Westinghouse, are you kidding me?
Oh, entirely no current references, no modern references.
No, absolutely not.
No, no reference.
Judge Roy Bean and Judge Roy Bean.
Diamond Lill.
A lot of, you know, you can reference like, oh, Susanna, you just, you know,
you can talk about songs, you can do song parodies.
It's just got to be of Susanna.
Steven Foster.
All the old hair pomades.
Yeah, just hair pomade brand names alone will eat up at 10 minutes.
And if we want to say like, if our brain wants to say like Iron Man or something,
we'll just replace it with Zorro.
We just say Zorro.
Zorro. Yeah, it was snake oil.
Yeah, buy the snake oil.
Go ahead into the Emporium. Get your commemorative snake oil.
Just find out who the president was back then.
If you're ever tempted to say Biden, just like was it
or we, Andrew Johnson at this point, I'm not sure what year.
Well, I don't know what 1850 is, but find it out.
And those clowns, those old so and so's in Washington.
And the crowds just losing it. Just going crazy.
Yeah. Well, I think we've made a real good case that we should be these performers.
Yeah. So well, as many things that we saw on the show, the solution is, of course, us.
Us, yeah. That's always the way.
No one has taken us up on the offer, which about every other episode
we say like, you know, we'll write that ride or we will be the characters
in the park and no one has taken us up on it yet.
Always unbelievable.
Yes. Well, it's that and it's to make Dennis's big thunder.
Do it now. Look, Danny Junior needs another act.
Do a little didn't work.
This is his way to be an old timey, an old timey guy in the right way.
So all of deploy all of us and we'll we'll make it all work.
I think a quick I think a quick rewrite and do little could be on Big Thunder
Mount. It's true.
And then what was his other Mordecai?
What was her? What was the no, that was that.
That was Johnny Depp. That's right.
I forgot about that.
Well, you know, teaming those two up, do little and Mordecai seems like.
Yeah, why not? That was the sleep.
Well, if you think of it all as just prequel, like, of course, they didn't do well.
It was only like it wasn't the sum of the parts.
But once you put them together, that's that's the new dynamic duo.
Yeah. People have a crossover. Yes.
Yeah. OK. Well, great ideas left and right.
Dennis, Dennis McNicholas.
Sorry about the stubble.
Dennis McNicholas, you survived podcasts the ride.
Thanks so much for for doing this.
So so I could have you. It's fantastic.
Oh, for sure. And oh, yes, go ahead.
When in Orlando, visit the Columbia Harbor House.
Yes, we absolutely will.
And seafood recently reopened.
It is up and running.
So it's closed for a while.
They they were serving the their menu at the Tomorrowland Terrace
in the interim, but I'm glad to hear.
Yes. Oh, gotcha. OK.
Let's exit through the gift shop because you definitely have have something to plug.
Tell us a little bit about about Batman, the audio adventures,
which I believe is this is coming out.
I think as this episode comes out, this is a thing you could check out tomorrow
on HBO Max September 18th, which I learned via your press release is Batman Day.
I feel that I never properly honored Batman Day before.
Well, you know, it is a quiet, you know,
contemplative evening with family is is most traditional
spend it with the ones I love.
But no, that is correct.
On September 18th, all 10 episodes of Batman,
the audio adventures will be available on HBO Max.
And it is something like an old timey radio play,
something like Saturday morning cartoons.
It's fun. It is not.
It is not a spoof of Batman, but it is not a serious Batman.
It is it is a Batman that acknowledges the absurdity
and the ridiculousness of the entire premise.
And I've got an amazing cast.
Jeffrey Wright is Batman.
Rosario Dawson is Catwoman.
I've got John Leguizamo is Riddler.
And just about all your favorite SNL
alums are in there.
We've got Jason Sudeikis, Fred Armisen, Seth Meyers,
Bobby Moynihan. The list goes on and on.
So Paul Scheer, our friend Paul Scheer.
He does a wonderful job place.
The Joker's right hand man.
And oh, and the Joker is played by Brent Spiner from Star Trek.
Oh, I don't know if you do that one, Mike.
I did not know that.
And of course, he played a very Joker like character on the UPN show Deadly Game.
It is, which is the which is the show with Christopher Lloyd
playing the character Sebastian Jackal.
Terrific. So I'm very amazed.
He's great on this.
And everyone just really brought it and had a super fun time.
And there are 10 episodes,
total run times about six and a half hours.
So you get a big fat chunk of Gotham City.
And hopefully we'll be back sometime next year with the second season.
So jump on board.
She's fantastic. Yeah.
And I know like a thing along the worst for you and a dream come true to get to do
this is an officially sanctioned Batman to do Batman in a way that you're guiding.
And I'm sure it's awesome.
They'll be excited to check it out.
I would be honored to have you listen.
Geezer. Well, and the other hope is that it paves the way for more Batman
offshoots, because I know I don't want to just call Mike out on it.
But I, you know, I do know that Mike has had a dream for a long time
of his specific Batman spin off, which is Batman Forever
to doing more in the Batman Forever universe specifically,
which I'm fully on board with.
So if there if we're like opening up avenues to like, you know,
many different little side streets of Batman.
Yes. Hopefully that could be one.
I have it already sketched out a bit.
Yes, it's a long time dream.
I don't know that we get you can't maybe do it as a movie anymore,
but another medium, another piece of media. Yes.
Prestige Maxi series.
Yes, sure. Yeah, yeah.
That's the way. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah. Get people for a limited time and
and like way more Chase Meridian, of course.
To nail Nicole Kidman down.
But you'll go.
She's got a very important role in the in the new one in Batman Forever to my Batman Forever to.
Yeah, for sure. We'll look out for that eventually.
But the course on that will be paved by Batman.
The audio adventures.
Check that out on HBO Max soon and other platforms after that.
As for us, you can find us on all the socials at podcast, the ride
merch is available in our public store.
And for three bonus episodes every month, check out podcast, the ride,
the second gate at Patreon dot com slash podcast, the ride
and evidently probably also exile on Main Street.
Oh, yeah. Let us know what you think.
Let us know what we should do.
Let us know some ways to to spend the day because I guess we'll need them
or we will or we'll like that day will fill up quicker than we think.
Yeah, yeah. I mean, yeah, send it if you want.
But honestly, I don't need it. I don't think I know.
I'll be begging for it after my day run entirely by the Disney Genie.
You see Genie on Main Street where you just choose like,
well, what would you like to do today?
I stay on Main Street.
Hey, did you mean to select another land?
No, no.
Please proceed to anything else.
Why are you?
Genie, why are you still here?
Turn your phone.
You have to turn your phone off at that point.
It's what we want. We're going to do it.
Genie be damned. All right.
Thanks so much for listening, Dennis.
Thanks for being here so long. Bye bye.
Bye bye.
Twitter and Instagram at Forever Dog Team and liking our page on Facebook.