Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast contains aggressive trash talk among competitive males, a talking
potato that's not afraid to go there, and host Mike Carlson being played by his identical
sounding brother, Jim Carlson.
PTR accidental legend Griffin Newman returns to break place with us and talk Toy Story Midway
Today's podcast, The Ride.
Welcome to podcast The Ride where we're glad that Sarge reminds us he's not our mother
because otherwise we would not feel permission to break those plates.
I'm Scott Gardner.
Mike Carlson, I assume, is in agreement.
I am in agreement, yes.
Saying that I am not your mother is so reassuring to me.
And if all the characters on any ride at Disneyland could just remind me of that before I enter
whatever world they have, it would really put me at ease.
You want everyone to say, I'm proud of you, but I'm not your mother.
Well, yeah, that's true.
I mean, if they could put all the things, all these comforting thoughts into one sentence,
one run on sentence, it would be really helpful for me.
What your dreams are meant to do.
Like, you'll get the right combo when you're sleeping sometime.
Mr. Potato Head's like, hey, you, I'm not your mother.
Oh, by the way, I'm proud of you.
Hey, hey, by the way, you'll book another commercial.
Don't worry, you'll work again.
That was the last recording Don Rickles ever did.
Yeah, Mike Carlson.
He didn't record more riffs for that, luckily.
Yeah.
OK, Jason Sheridan, hi.
Hi.
I'm mostly hoping that Potato Head calls me over, like gives me the Carson knot,
like calls me up, calls me over to the Carnival Barker platform.
To bark alongside him.
Or to just talk, like to just talk.
Like, yeah, even walking around all day, what are you been up to?
You know, like you've been doing a real good job covering the parks.
Like, I'm proud of you and I want you to come.
That's what you want someone to say.
You've been doing a good job covering the park.
Covering the parks.
I cover the parks.
I mean, I mean, covering your footprint, like not sorry, not covering them as a
media personality.
Walking around, I was trying to mix the metaphors.
We're both. Yeah.
And yeah, he calls me over because when Johnny would call people over,
they would just sort of like chit chat.
Yeah, they would evolve into guests at that.
You wanted to get casual.
Yeah, you wanted to get casual.
With Mr. Potato Head.
As it has gotten casual, let's not belabor it anymore.
Ladies and gentlemen, accidental PTR legend Griffin Newman.
Thank you very much.
So now I qualify it with the accidental.
I hope that kind of like that adds to the absolutely the luster in its own way.
I correct people if they say PTR legend, I go accidental PTR.
You are an accidental.
I'm already overflowing with takes.
And I you know, there's part of me that I I emailed you.
I said I'd like to do this ride. Yeah.
And then when I brought it up again months later, I said,
because you guys said you hate this ride and all three of you went like, what?
And I went like, I swear to God, there's an episode I heard where you said
and I perhaps overstated it, but where
Toy Story Mania was invoked, Midway Mania was invoked.
And then one of you said, what if we just never cover that ride?
And then the other two went like, yeah, that's fine with me.
We can just not do that one.
It sounds familiar.
And I think maybe I said what I want to say that it's me who said that,
but I don't remember why I would have.
And maybe it was an extremely dry joke or something.
Too dry.
I overstated it when I said, like, you guys said you'd never do.
It was just kind of this energy of just like, do we have to do everything?
Maybe that's when we just never do.
Like it was sort of this.
I really like this ride.
So I tried to rack my brain.
I know we can let's say officially we all love it.
Defending it.
And then the two of you, Mike and Scott, sort of going like,
we could just skip that.
And then that's why I felt the need to email and be like, balance the scales.
I would like to talk about this.
We were convincing enough that we didn't like it.
And whatever this was, please, somebody find this.
I cannot.
I'm sorry we bleeped it before, but we had to keep the mystery alive.
Now the mystery is solved.
So now I just want to triangulate a little bit for the Cliffords out there
who are trying to crack this and find the time code.
OK, I believe I emailed you about this maybe October, November, December of 2020.
The craziest months of that year.
Absolutely.
Maybe the most mentally unhinged in my book.
I was losing my mind.
Yeah.
Now, I had gotten months behind on the show,
and that's when I sort of jumped on.
So I was like catching up to everything.
So it's not after that. We know.
This is the thing. It's like that helps.
I stopped listening to most things during the pandemic
because I didn't want to acknowledge the pandemic. Right.
And I feel like that when I was like, I'm like six months behind on PTR.
I got to get back into it.
So it was around the the the beginning of, I want to say, the remote records.
OK. Post-Papa Scotts, like that.
But that territory, like the early quarantine episode.
I love you tossing all these things off as if they're albums or or B sides or something.
Sure. I love this music to my ears.
Well, it's also it's very hard.
And it has I've caught up more, but I'm still not completely up to date.
I'm less months behind, but I've been like working to get up there.
You like so you were on it.
Yeah, yes.
You'll catch up to that one. Right.
I skipped that one. That's easier than it's like, oh, that's one less one to listen to.
Yeah, that's true. But I was I was there, too.
This dog was there.
Let's acknowledge the dog.
You might hear a dog throughout.
I think somebody walked by that.
I don't think you'll keep hearing the dog.
If you keep hearing the dog, maybe you don't hear the dog.
OK.
But it is interesting in a very depressing way to be like three months off of timeline
and hear how wildly things change in terms of our perception of the world in that period of time.
You know, that we were all so upset in October, November, and then a good thing happened.
The cool death, something more good things happen.
But that's the thing. Like, sometimes you'll listen to an episode and it'll be like one.
I have listened to an episode and it'll be like, and we're just in this forever.
And then I'm listening to it in March and I'm like, baby, we're in vaccine territory.
This thing's done. Put it in the rear view.
These guys freaking out.
Right. And then like three months later, I listened to an episode where you're like,
and now everything's good.
We're all vaccinated. Put it in the rear view.
And I was like, these fools don't know it's coming for them.
Another odd thing I've observed is that so many kind of.
PTR universe figures, if not regular subjects, but the types of people who get discussed,
the types of entertainment, entertainers and public figures who are often referenced by you three guys
died in 2020, like a disproportionate amount because listening to the way I stand,
share, all right, listen to episodes and I would be like, you went out so great.
I don't want to go out like him.
We don't want to go out like him.
But there were so many episodes I'd listened to where I was like, this is kind of a morbid run
to do on Regis this shortly after he died.
And then I'd be like, oh, they recorded this like six weeks before he died.
Ditto a lot of Bob Evans coming up right before he croaks.
Oh, we did. He was 20, 20.
There were a lot of 20, 20 people who you got back into and started either for one episode
or for a run of episodes, like doing riff runs on.
Now he's part of the Lexica.
What are you boy? What are you?
You found a layer to make us depressed about 2020.
Is it Frieden Roy?
We did so much. That's right.
Roy, Regis, Bob, Groden, Robbie Evans, Groden, Groden and her.
I'll remember some other ones.
This is though. And I said this on an episode.
A friend of the show, Andrew Grissom, we had made a comment or I had said something
when we were at Knott's Berry Farm a couple of months ago.
I go, it does seem like we're cursing people.
And he goes, well, you are also just all fascinated with people over the age
of 80. It's a big factor.
It's a big factor.
And I think another part of it is that all of those people feel like people where it's like,
I guess they'll just never die.
Sure. In your head, you're like they should have died like 10 years ago.
Right. And now they've crossed some threshold and do not seem to have been diminished
in any sort of way.
I guess maybe they just live forever.
Like you start to get cocky.
We'll do this to where like I did a like run about like Ed Asner.
And David was flipping out being like, don't talk about Ed Asner not dying
when this episode won't come out for two months.
And I was like, we're going to be fine. We're going to be fine.
And like, thankfully, it was that Asner death was like two months after that.
You barely.
But he's in that zone where I was like, Ed Asner, I guess he never dies.
I guess it's just always safe to bank up and Ed Asner run.
It also makes sense that like all like every
podcast or comedy writer or whatever is obsessed with Norm McDonald,
who is the most old man ish, bizarrely old man ish for his generation.
Like, of course. And then he we lose him, maybe just by virtue of him.
But being old, I had no idea how old he was.
That was some of the shock of the death.
It's like, how do I know the age?
He was older than the generation and he kept his disease a secret for a decade.
So it kind of like was blindsiding.
But let's say we're recording this on a Wednesday.
A Monday, the four of us went to Disneyland together.
Norm McDonald came up several times Tuesday morning.
He's dead. So weird.
Well, so will you count this as part of that?
God, I don't know. That wasn't on Mike, but it was odd.
And it's not like I never talk about Norm otherwise. Yeah.
You know, it was more jarring when I would hear Regis reference on Mike.
And it was so shortly before he died.
You know why? Why Regis?
But it was it was odd because we brought up to him a number of times
in different contexts within that radically.
There weren't even about necessarily about him.
He just played into it. Yes. Yeah. Weird.
Here's the word. Quisling, I believe.
That was one of the reasons he came up.
Yes. Used by David Letterman in reference to letterman calling him
Don O'Mire or he's calling Norm.
I'm calling. Yeah, yeah.
You're not being angry or Don O'Mire for firing him. Yeah.
Yeah. But there's a problem with the word. Quisling.
Do we figure that out?
It's apparently the name of like a Nazi officer or something.
But it's used as a derogatory of like you
quizzling you, you man who goes along with the Nazis or something.
Oh, it's bad. Yeah. Yeah. Right.
It's an insulting term. Yeah. OK.
It's not like you, Hitler, my favorite Hitler.
It's not a specific way to praise this guy.
He's my best friend. You got to love me.
He's a real gobles.
You know, it's a quizzling, like derogatory.
I don't I think you're allowed to use.
I don't know. But like Colonel Clink, I feel is still used as like
that that's a very old reference, but it's like an idiot.
Like a dumb idiot.
I mean, that is a fictional Nazi.
We're going to kill Werner Klemperer now, are we?
Have you? I assume he's already passed the quizzling definition here.
Wait, have you said is anyone other than me
reference Colonel Clink around you in the last decade?
I'm using Colonel Clink.
No, I'm saying it is the thing that I use as like
I feel like that one's evergreen like Lucy and Ethel, you know.
Guys, I just I just watched autofocus like three days ago.
So it's really there's all these.
Oh, my God. That's a reference.
You know, I'm going to Bob Crane.
And to Bob Crane, Scott, after you watched it.
Now you're speaking my language.
That's what you don't want to hear is like you tell somebody
something that's going on with you and they're like,
it sounds like a real autofocus situation.
Things might not work out so great for you.
I have a little more information here.
Quizzling, by definition, is a trader who collaborates
with an enemy force occupying their country. Hmm.
So I think Letterman's saying,
why would you sympathize with Don Ohmier?
Who's a bad guy who fired you?
Right. You're a quiz.
You're being a quizling. Mm hmm.
Vidkun Quizzling was a Norwegian military officer and politician.
It's a collaboration with the Nazis. Wow.
Oh, like a Benedict Arnold government of Norway during the occupation.
So Quizzling is a I just want to point out real quick.
We're in the garage here and the door just sort of closed by itself.
But I certainly felt like it was a ghost of some of the some of the people
we're talking about.
Is it Glemper? Is it Quizzling himself?
Is it all of them? Is it as a clink?
Is it norm? So we love you norm.
Is it Montecore, Siegfried and Roy's tiger?
It could be another one.
Talked about Montecore so much.
Montecore died.
Montecore and Roy died. Right. Both. Yeah.
Oh, yeah. It wasn't.
But Siegfried died. Right. They both died.
They both died. Yeah. They both died.
They're both dead. Yeah.
They're both. Yeah.
After we did all this stuff,
so we can't we can't make one pop culture reference to anything you like.
Or else we're we're screwed.
And that's going to be tough for you, Mike,
because somebody you love is in this attraction.
That's true.
Gentlemen, it's just not even I even mention who is in this attraction.
You're talking about Tim Allen.
Yeah.
You know, it was very weird and not to like I'm sure there's a million norm
anecdotes, but learning
one of the people giving a remembrance of Norm McDonald was Bob Dole.
Realizing Bob Dole is still alive.
Ninety eight years old. Yeah.
But Jason, you know what you just did?
No, but I was about to say I don't want to see the next five days.
You did it.
This episode is recorded before the passing of Bob Dole.
You absolutely that's the exact kind of person you don't want to invoke now
with the streak you boys have been on.
Bob Dole represents an America that I think has passed and we say
thank you for your service.
And any anytime it's somewhere you go, I can't believe they're still alive.
Invoking the means inevitably they will die within the week
of the episode being recorded passing through your brain.
We'll cause it.
Well, in advance, I think Bob Dole, you put a lot of evil on the show.
I'm sorry.
And we're all stressed out as we caused all of this.
Here's a death factor that's kind of nice or cool.
Go ahead.
I don't know if that's the right way to frame this.
I'm sure you guys know this, but
Toy Story four, Don Rickles, entire performance is essentially cobbled together
for Midway Mania takes its I didn't know it was in Mania.
I knew it was existing.
That's crazy.
Main base of it.
Stuff they didn't use or even stuff they did use and we wouldn't reckon.
Combination of both.
He doesn't say a lot in the movie.
It's a lot of little sense fragments like, hey, what's that?
What you really going there?
You know, like a lot of like little things like it's woody.
He doesn't have like a lot of sentences.
There are 65 main characters in Toy Story four and most of them have five lines
that easily could have been cobbled together from any number of different sessions.
We were talking about this the other day.
I like Toy Story four infinitely more than you do.
I like it more than three.
I think that complaint of yours is the most valid complaint against Toy Story four.
It is the one I co-signed the most.
Specifically that I felt like it was designed to open up the universe, right?
That's what you're talking about?
Not that complaint.
Okay.
You don't like that one.
Complaint of just they've gotten to a point where the universe now has 60 main characters.
Oh, sure.
Toy Story is unsustainable by the fourth movie.
Like it just it's.
And we go and we meet more and we're bringing back one who's not here.
Yes.
Yeah, we end up with so many.
Yeah, right.
To flash to my other my the other thing I said with Toy Story four, which I do like,
I don't dislike Toy Story four.
It felt like they were redoing three.
But then if spoiler alert, if you haven't seen it, Woody like leaves.
They go off to have an adventure with Bo Peep.
And I felt like they were correcting a mistake where three left the toys in a different kids
playroom, which gives them all the same restraints of like, now we got to get out this giant window.
How are we going to do that?
Right now, Woody's out in the universe.
Like he's out in the world.
You don't have to get stuck with the same like now we're in a daycare.
Now we're in a school.
Like we don't have to do necessarily that.
That's a big four thing for me.
One of the reasons I prefer it is that I think that is the more correct ending to this series.
If God willing, it actually ends here.
Obviously, they will always find ways to do things with the Toy Story characters.
Right.
But if like this is the last canonical theatrical film, I think that's the better resolution to it.
And like I know I think Toy Story three holds a lot of value for people.
Just to make it clear, main reason I'm doing this episode, Toy Story is my favorite thing in the
world, like period point blank.
It is like my number one fandom of any stripe.
Yeah.
And there's Toy Story rides out there.
There's a lot of Toy Story rides, but this is probably the most
like notable, like maybe the best use of everybody.
It's definitely like the most high profile.
I mean, I have a lot of thoughts on this.
And I think it occupies an interesting space because we were even trying to,
I don't know if it was before or after the ride queue, talking about where this ride
lands in sort of the timeline of the Disney Pixar acquisition and them trying to immediately get as
much out of these characters as possible.
Right.
I think there's a lot of interesting stuff there, but I do think like a thing I like about
Meway Mania is I get to see all my favorite characters again.
I get to spend all this time with them.
When there have been a lot of like the other Toy Story attractions, which are largely gray,
I mean, there's kind of the cheapo more carnival bush ones that are just nicely are decorated.
Right.
But then there's Buzz Lightyear's Astro Blasters, which I think is great, but it's like a particular
subsect of Toy Story universe.
Slinky Dog's kind of only Slinky Dog and the Penguin.
Right.
This is kind of the most here is everybody.
You meet all of them.
They all do something.
Right.
And everyone has their personality come through in a way that like some characters don't get
their moments in Toy Story 4.
And it's like you're willing to give them Rickles because he is no longer on this mortal coil.
Sure.
They had to work with the scraps they had.
But that's just like, I wish Rex had anything to do in that movie.
You know?
Yeah.
There's so many of them.
I think that movie really does wrong by Jesse, who's my single favorite Toy Story character,
I would say.
Very endearing.
I mean, like I love Forky now, but Forky has only one movie to compare to like Jesse's.
The Jesse arc in 2 is just perfect.
Yeah.
But yes, it's like, you know, PTR friend of the show, Jeff Garland, Buttercup has like
a successful joke in that movie, right?
Like he has like a runner that pays off.
Two, three lines that are funny.
Yeah.
But they build and it's three beats and the third one really lands.
And it's like a little frustrating that like they couldn't do at least that for all the
characters.
Yes.
It is one of the things that now going on Midway Mania again, and I want to say this
is the first time I've gone on it since 4 came out.
It's just nice to see characters get spotlighted in that way, you know?
Yeah.
It's a thing I enjoy about that ride where like as much as it's like,
it's a screen ride, it's a shooting ride, like really?
And that felt a little more novel at the time.
And I was going back onto the ride this time going like, am I going to be weary about this
now because of like everything else that's become like this?
Yeah.
There's something nice about just being like, here's like four minutes with Sarge.
You know?
Like it's just here's some Sarge time and you're going into these different silos of
theming of Toy Story.
It's a thing I love about Toy Story is you have these characters that would not exist
in the same universe under any other premise.
And you sort of get to go to like all of their, here's Sarge World, there's Woody Old West World.
Because it's just a kid owning toys, Toy Story means you get to have sci-fi and
westerns and dinosaurs and military and everyone plays their role pretty straight.
And it's nice that every little zone you go to is like themed.
You spend some time with the characters.
I believe Pixar actually did the animation themselves.
I think that was a big deal.
It's all the real voice actors.
Yeah.
I think this ride has a lot of production value in that way.
That having been said, frontloader right off the top.
I just don't want to forget this because I almost said it walking off the ride.
And then I went, no, I should hold on to this.
Save it.
Yeah.
That ride opens, I believe in 2008.
Correct.
Yeah.
Disney acquires Pixar in 2006.
We were talking about this that Cars was the last movie of the Disney deal.
Closed out what they owed them post Toy Story.
The original Eisner Katzenberg deal was five film sequels don't count.
Post Toy Story, it's a bug's life.
They got screwed on Toy Story too because it was supposed to go direct to video.
And when they pushed it to theaters, Katzenberg went, no, no, no, no, no.
Eisner went, no, no, no, no, no.
Doesn't count.
You owe us four more.
And that started a lot of the contentiousness between Disney and Pixar for years that made
people think they would split up when the deal was done.
So then it was Monsters Inc., Finding Nemo, Incredibles Cars.
And that should have been the end of the loop.
Right.
And they were like free market.
I forget if the deal happens right before or right after Cars.
I want to say right before because when people were like, I was reading Jim Hill all the time.
This is when I got into Jim Hill because I was like, I want to understand the Pixar acquisition.
Oh, you had a Jim Hill era.
Yes.
I mean, not that.
When is everybody?
It's like when that's a good question.
I ask you, when did you get into Jim Hill?
Like, what was what was your hair?
My thing for me was it was the Pixar acquisition, which was like the first thing Eiger did,
and the Muppet acquisition, which was the last thing Eisner did.
And I was so protective of both of those worlds that I was just like,
I don't know how I landed there, but it was like,
this is the only guy who seems to be really going into the weeds on
everything this means for these companies.
Like honesty and like warts and all.
And then I just got into reading all of everything, reading his Superstar limo pieces.
But that's how I got turned on to him.
When was everyone else's Jim?
Jim Awakening.
Oh, I think only a few years ago.
I think probably around the start of the DCA redo.
But what I was going to say off of your point,
I think the Pixar acquisition happens because Eisner is out.
Because Steve Jobs and Eisner were like oil and vinegar.
Like two big personalities who did not see eye to eye.
The story is that everyone thinks there's no way Disney will be able to get Pixar back
because Eisner has like really sullied the water.
Right?
And Pixar starts independently producing their next three movies.
WALL-E, Up, and Ratatouille were all produced independently, self-financed.
And they were like, and whoever acquires us gets these three movies.
Which is why they're the three weirdest Pixar movies.
It's why they're the three where it's like, how did this get made?
That aren't necessarily like, and there'll be obvious part two and part three of these.
It was just like, let's just like, it's true blank check shit where it's just like,
someone's going to buy the next three Pixar movies.
We do whatever we want.
Very idiosyncratic.
I think maybe the most, I would say the most interesting time.
Although Pixar, I mean, I was like 10 when Toy Story came out.
And so like, I think that was the last one where I was like fully, I was like all in.
Sure.
You know?
But it's, yes, that run is really interesting.
And that's like 2007 Ratatouille, 2008 WALL-E, 2009 Up.
And then 2010 is Toy Story 3.
Because the first thing that happens is like, Eisner slams the door behind him.
Right?
Everyone's like, this is a rapper ball.
Eiger takes over.
His story is that he like goes to the parks and he goes to one of the parades and he realizes
that the only characters in the parade from the last 10 years are Pixar characters.
That Disney has created no characters in the last 10 years that have had any staying power.
And that it's just Pixar.
And he just goes like, my first order of business is whatever it takes.
And he goes to Steve Jobs and he's like, you have all the leverage, you name your price.
We need you guys.
It's yours.
We buy you outright.
It's not.
Right.
Like we keep doing it.
We do another deal with you that could last.
And Jobs said the fact that Eiger came to him with that much humility is like the thing
where he was just like, I liked that.
But he wasn't playing hardball with me after Katzenberg and Eisner were always trying to
be a step ahead.
That he was like, we're fucked.
We need Pixar.
You name your price.
Oh, weird.
Steve Jobs liked people being subservient to him?
Yes.
Who could have seen that coming?
He liked Eiger self-cucking.
But so they pay all this money.
I think Cars comes out right after that.
People were like, they spent too much.
The Cars merchandise the first year alone, like pretty much makes back everything.
Right.
But the first thing Eiger says when he takes over is like Toy Story 3 has got to happen now.
It's been at this point, seven years.
You fast track that by that point, we're already getting into way more.
There are lots of we're past Harry Potter.
We're into this.
Like, you don't just do two movies.
Right.
And three could never happen because Pixar was like, we'll do it if it counts.
And Eisner was like, doesn't count.
And they were like, then fuck you.
It doesn't happen.
Weird.
The direct-to-video when Eisner was playing hardball with them, he started this animation
company, Circle 7, that was named that because they were housed in an old ABC 7 building.
For some local affiliate or whatever.
Because he was going to do Cinderella 3, Twist in Time to Toy Story, basically.
Right.
He was going to make a sequel, like the cheap sequel.
Yes.
ABC 7 is our affiliate.
Los Angeles is the affiliate.
I wasn't sure because ABC 7 is also New York.
That's in Chicago, too.
Yeah.
Last seven.
Lucky number seven.
But yes, that's where I think Circle 7 animation was.
And they announced when they were just like, fine, Pixar, you want to leave us?
That's fine.
Finding Nemo 2, Monsters Inc. 2, Toy Story 3.
They announced all of that.
Imagine that world, all these gross bad, like losing half the actors every time.
Yes.
The Toy Story 3 premise was that the Buzz gets recalled.
He's defective and they make everyone send all the Buzz's back to Japan and all the toys
have to travel to Japan to rescue him from the factory.
But he's like lost his mind.
He's gone like psychotic.
Who knows?
Maybe.
It's not like outwardly.
It's not as bad as there's no fraction in the title that helps.
We're not in Lion King one and a half.
We would have gotten there.
Yeah.
But so Eiger immediately makes good but is like, you got to give me Toy Story 3.
Come on, guys.
Let's stop dicking around.
And then Jason, I think you were telling me that you had found in your research
that Midway Mania was originally developed as a Mickey concept.
Well, see, I found that through Jim Hill.
They were talking about it.
Jim.
Because of the straight line from, let me see if I can get this right.
Pirates of the Caribbean, the battle for Buccaneers gold.
Which is what?
Which is an attraction.
Yeah, Pirates of the Caribbean, battle for Buccaneer gold.
It was a game at Disney Quest that replaced the Hercules game.
And this was like you were on a pirate ship and you were firing a cannon at other pirate ships.
Before this moment, before I heard that, it did not thought of me that the Toy Story Midway Mania
gun thing you use is a cannon, basically.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, sure.
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
That makes sense.
And he was the one who said that I think it was very, very early on because I was digging for a
while and I could not find any articles about that.
But I think early in the development, imagineers may have been like, maybe this is a Mickey Midway
thing.
Right.
That makes sense that Mickey's still on the Ferris wheel.
In the end, you don't really have a Mickey ride yet.
Right.
But even that placement within the pier would make a lot of sense.
It just seems conjecture on my part, but it's like,
Eiger comes in, they close the deal, it's 2006, Toy Story 3 is greenlit, and it's like immediately,
how do we do as much of Toy Story as we can?
That movie is four years away.
What's the quickest we can get something in the parks?
What's an idea we have that is somewhat modular?
That's up for grabs that any IP maybe can be on.
And another thing going on is we have to do something with California Adventure.
Right.
This is the canary in the coal mine of, oh, we're acting from a position of power with
California Adventure.
It's not just stop gaps.
It's not just like, get a Monster Thing thing and get a Chibi Tower in.
This was a big deal when they were redoing this park.
We're starting with this.
What is essentially a technological marvel?
That's the thing.
This ride was such a big, you've never been on a ride like this, but I feel like they
kept on flaunting this is going to be a very different thing.
Yeah.
They also, I found this other history of it though from the Kevin Rafferty book where
the idea was, they had, and this might have been when they're starting the process of
how do we start changing DCA and especially change the Paradise Pier area, which is sort
of the shinsiest, most off the shelf zone.
So how do we do something that's more elevated?
And they were like, there were, there still are like midway games, but I think they're
walking past those and saying, wouldn't it be great if there was a way that you could
play these infinitely in a way that you could cycle more people through than having to go
up to a stand, have a transaction and then play the game.
So they start, they start figure trying to figure out what is a ride around this.
I think even without IP necessarily attached, but what I found interesting about all this
is that they may be, they didn't, they weren't even at screen ride yet.
According to this book that they were trying to figure out a way that you could have just
like a bunch of balls and rings loaded onto a ride vehicle, like enough that were just
ever refilled and that you wouldn't run out of in the allotted time.
I cannot believe that idea lasted for longer than five seconds without someone getting
the practicality of who picks up the balls?
Where do they go?
Yeah.
Like bowling has a system that's been in place for a long time.
We have to invent the bowling pickup system, but more, more complicated with small marvel.
You're in a ride car and you're moving around to different areas and people keep throwing
an infinite amount of things.
How do they not just like take them, grab them, hurt each other with them?
How do you not have teenagers throwing them at each other?
Right.
It would have to come out of like a long tube.
It would have to have like a skeeball mechanism in the actual ride and it would all have to
funnel its way down and then reload into each vehicle, but not ever have it be possible
for you to grab the ball.
Right.
I mean, just a nightmare.
What you just described is a nightmare.
Seems hard, but I know it's not impossible.
Maybe if they had to stay with that line of thinking, they might have rigged something
up eventually, but once they realized screens of the thing.
The other thing from that book, Kevin Rafferty, by the way, the Imagineer,
responsible for this and Cars and A Thousand Things Tower of Terror, like one of the greats
ever, when he described the Mickey situation, he said that it was maybe it was going to be
a Mickey thing and he said that they ran into this weird thing where they've always had
trouble at the Imagineer and cracking Mickey rides because what is Mickey and his world?
He's almost doing a different job every time you see him in a Homer Simpson sort of fashion,
although even Homer is defined as his main job before he has side adventures, but like
what really is the base of Mickey?
And it all makes more sense in this new style.
Weird fact that like, you know, as Disney keeps on getting scared of losing Mickey to public
domain, right, and they keep on fighting and spending millions and millions of dollars in
court to like get public domain to lobby the government basically.
Yeah, years stretched further and further and further back.
The other thing they've done is started siloing.
I'm sure you guys know this, but like different versions of Mickey they legally treat as
different characters.
So if they ever lose Steamboat Willie, they're like, well, that's Steamboat Willie.
That's not Mickey.
Steamboat Willie Mickey is that one character and then like Taylor Mickey is one character
and this Mickey is one character.
Like they split it into very separate licenses with separate copyright.
So they're like each Mickey is actually they're not all the same.
This is the whole the Mickey should end up in the public domain situation is interesting
because like for all of the evil things that Disney does and the evil things Disney does
involving lawyers, this one I'm a little like, what the fuck is that rule?
Why does why do they need like they are they could not be more active 100 years later
for this character.
Why do they have to just surrender it?
It's weird.
I like anyone else going to do with Mickey.
Can you imagine Warner Brothers being like, finally, we get to do our Mickey project?
I just think the graffiti art when Mickey goes into the public domain is just going
to be unbearable.
You mean officially?
The show was basically.
You can do it.
People like to joke about like Disney so litigious showing down everyone's fun.
It's like, do you know how much bad Mickey shit we're being saved from by Disney's lawyers being
diligent?
I think it'll be funny though when like every studio has a Mickey movie that first year.
It's like the Snow White rival projects were just like four untitled Mickey projects.
We are different creative teams.
We're going to develop a movie podcast.
The Ride presents Mickey and we're going to make it.
Jason stars as Mickey.
I love this already.
Jason, do the voice Plum roll.
Hey, everybody.
See great.
He's Mickey.
It's like, right?
Yes.
Yeah, he's wearing the little shorts.
If that's what you're asking.
You can also have Mickey who's just like, hey, I'm Mickey.
He could be like strapping and sexy.
Michael, Michael Mouse.
Yeah.
And just like a kind of hot current version of like sort of a like hipster bartender version
of the suspenders.
Little shorts.
Shorts need to be little.
Why bother to get the character if you're not going to be shorts?
It's been a long time.
People have been asking, you know, when will Mickey get hot?
And now we can finally know.
Now we can now.
Two thousand twenty eight.
Exactly.
But like when we were walking through Toontown, I was saying like this whole area is very odd now
because it is so frozen in amber of like the 90s sort of take off on the 60s Disney cartoon
aesthetic, which is not the best era of the shorts by any stretch.
And then they're doing the short films.
Not the shorts.
Oh, the shorts were great in that time.
Yes.
It's never been a bad era for the shorts.
The only thing that could go wrong is if they went long.
That would suck.
There's got to be poor shorts, Mickey.
Don't.
There's got to be.
Jort Mickey?
Mickey wearing jorts?
Oh, Mickey.
John Cena Mickey?
John Cena style shorts.
Yeah, I could see it.
It's like the 90s, like more day glow, more rounded version of the 60s Mickey cartoon aesthetic
that now has no connection to anything.
And when there was like maybe like three cartoons were made in that era.
And when there was like 20 years of just like, well, I don't know, Mickey's inactive.
Mickey's definitive vibe is Toontown.
Like there's nothing that's more Mickey than this place.
Because what else are they really doing with him?
But the shorts they do now are good and are popular.
They've been using more, right?
Runaway Railways.
Already, there's been enough time for a generation to view it as, well, that's Mickey.
They might not even know the previous Mickey.
So I was saying this to you where you're like saying that your son watches those shorts.
You watch them with him.
And it's like at some age when he is cognizant enough to like feel attached to those new Mickey
cartoons and that aesthetic, that vibe, and what that personality is.
And then understand what's going on when he goes to the park.
He's going to be like, what is this place?
Why is there this weird other?
Yeah, this is nothing.
Why haven't they painted this since 1994?
Right.
Like it's just so odd.
Who is Roger Rabbit?
It is interesting to me that like on one hand, oh, makes sense to swap in Toy Story
instead of Mickey because Toy Story, like all the characters have such defined personalities.
And as you're saying, like milieus, they're worlds to play in.
They're obvious ways to go, right?
There's like no shortage of options there.
But then you also go like there's no logical link between Toy Story and the Carnival.
Like they get to the Carnival in Toy Story 4.
Oh, yes.
After yes.
A movie made after the ride.
Right.
But at that point in time, when you're just looking at Toy Story 1 and 2,
the sweatiness of the premise, which I don't care about the premise, but when they were like,
the idea is that Andy buys a play set that's a make your own midway and he sets it up in the
bedroom and then he leaves and then the toys decide to run the games themselves.
And it's like, right.
Yeah, I don't care.
Just let me play the games.
I don't care.
It's fine.
Andy lead.
Yeah, I found it so specific.
All this is listed somewhere.
But Andy's called to dinner.
Don't get on that ride and start trying to break plates unless you know that Andy is
and he should be here and he should be giant, much bigger than you.
But he had to go eat his giant dinner.
See, but that's what that starts me out on the ride on a stressful note because I'm
afraid someone's going to call me late for dinner.
My biggest fear is disappointing these characters.
And you've been hoping that the ride vehicle will just take you into the dining room.
Yes, I'm hoping one of the delays, it's not target practice.
It's just like, oh, good.
You're finally here.
Water, iced tea, soda.
Jason wants the ride car to move into a room where suddenly he is still toy size and there's
just giant food.
You know, and he's like a little pewter who's able to climb inside a turkey and eat it.
You know, they painted this pot pie with the 3D glasses on so the black light would look
correct when you were wearing your 3D glasses yourself.
That is a good thing about that ride, though.
I feel like more than a lot of other 3D rides.
I don't think that ride looks muted, neither in screen nor in like actual physical.
It still looks pretty good.
I mean, I think at this point they probably could make it a little brighter.
But other than that, it's not as egregious as a lot of rides.
And it also like it's fun.
And this is why I'm curious if this opinion is out there and maybe this is the opinion
that you feared that we had or something.
But like, are there because for sure we've said it, everybody said it like a screen rides
and you're all your eyes at screen rides.
I almost don't think of this as a screen ride or I don't apply like the same.
It doesn't have the sort of the bummer aspects of things I would call screen rides.
No, it's I want this is the main thing I want to talk about.
I don't quite understand how this ride avoids those trappings.
Well, I think the games I think everything works together
in such a great way.
All the games are very clear and simple.
I think satisfying.
They're all very different.
The, you know, blacklight sets are nice accompaniments.
The 3D is not the movement of the cars.
The movement of the cars is very nice.
It's fun.
Yeah, there's enough like real ride stuff between the games.
You're like, oh, I like what the ride vehicle does and how it looks.
I mean, because you guys haven't done the episode yet, but I wrote it with you guys.
And we like we do Toy Story Mania.
And then I think we go over to the web web slingers.
Yeah.
Now I've done that.
You've done your Griffin and I hadn't done it when that ride starts.
I was just like, fuck, this ride is going to make Toy Story Mania look like diarrhea.
And then I'm going to have to pick up the pieces and do an episode on a ride
that's become completely outmoded.
Right.
Stuck in the past.
That was my fear.
And then it took about three minutes of Norm McDonald's opening the door again.
It took about three minutes into web slingers to be like, no,
midway mania is like definitively better than this.
And this is more advanced.
But I think there are a lot of things such as that.
Web singers really feels like a screen ride.
Putting aside, I think problems with the game itself and the functionality of that
and the clarity of that and how that premise is overly confusing and spends too much time
trying to describe it and explain it to you.
I also think when you move from one screen to another in web slingers,
you're just seeing the space between two screens.
They're trying too hard to sell you on the you are immersed in a world,
a door is opening and this is just what's outside this door.
And you're very aware of the fact that you're looking at screens.
And then when the car moves, it just sort of moves laterally to another screen,
another steel door opens, and then you're seeing another thing.
As I'm writing, just like you from left to right.
Yes, I think Toy Story mania is better gameplay aside, just as a ride,
because it accepts the artifice of what it's doing, where it's like cura flats.
There are screens, they're big blocks.
There's this premise that if you really want to know,
we can explain to you that Andy was called to dinner, but also who gives a shit like,
who cares? The characters are talking to you directly.
They're just like, let's have some fun.
I find that I got a lot more stressed out playing web slingers, not only because it was hard to do,
but also because the intensity of the ride of just being like, we got to stop this.
Yeah, it's kind of yelling at you.
It's sort of shades of what there's like an arcade game.
It's called like jungle go go.
What am I talking about?
There's a game that is so stressful where so many giant spiders are jumping out.
It's kind of like that.
I mean, well, it is spiders.
I guess what I'm saying, we did a VR.
No, it's a thing.
You're in a little vehicle and we know our thing in Westwood that was like that,
where we were being attacked relentlessly by alien spiders.
Yes.
Ever.
Yeah, I think maybe I don't like anything like that.
We're like, there's there is a swarm.
Is that there's like that whole subgenre of arcade game that I feel like often would be
in movie theaters of like the alien game Terminator Salvation House of the Dead,
where it's like you have a gun and it's relentless and things just won't stop coming at you.
Yeah, I mean, I was was it like last two episodes ago where I was saying that does
seem to be the trend in these three D riots because we did it in knots.
There's knots 3D thing for very tales, which is like it's relentless.
Right.
There's so much happening or shooting a little.
I like you're shooting Crafty Coyote's sons holding pies, if I'm correct, which is great.
The concept is great.
And we're shooting at his little son.
Shoot my son.
And then the Spider-Man, it's like it's a lot of like relentless and a lot of stuff happening.
And it's like I think I said it about Spider-Man, wouldn't it be just like it would be more
satisfying if you shot a web at nothing happening and like it shot out of a barrel and you moved
your hand left and the barrel whipped there and you would feel like, wow, I did like the Spider-Man
thing versus like throwing my arms at the sex of the sky.
I think that is possible to do in Web Slayers, but I'm so confused.
I know.
It's confusing.
It's hard to see.
That's a great thing about Toy Story Midway Mania.
The color of your cannon.
It's so clean.
The color on the screen, like you can see what you're doing.
They play tested it with like eight to 80, you know, to make sure like all ages can figure this out.
And considering that every game, the objective changes a little bit and what your shooting
changes a little bit.
The adaptation time is zero.
Like you're just like, oh, it's plates now.
My plates are blue.
I'm throwing Matt thing.
It's rings.
My rings are getting them over the thing.
You're in it immediately.
A character slides in one sentence of instruction, not like a whole entire pre-show of it.
You're right.
You're totally right about like simple clarity.
You get it.
I'm comfortable, you know, and you're just like, oh, great.
I want to play this versus like, fuck, what do I got to do now?
Yeah.
And you and you note and whatever like the other rides, which are again, like impressive
technically, and I don't dislike the other 3D rides, but it feels like they got it down
from like pulling the weird cannon string.
Yeah.
It down to the millisecond where your brain just believes it's shooting it.
Right.
Like it, there's no question in my mind that it's coming out of the cannon for real.
Yeah.
Like my brain accepts the reality of it.
And there's just these little like the other rides, like it's off a little bit.
Your brain starts to get confused because it's not putting it together.
The web is not actually coming out of your hand or you're shooting like when you're
shooting on the.
Here's just a basic thing.
The webs are way too thin and it's really hard to tell which colors.
That's also.
Yes.
Colors are too similar.
That's the single biggest issue with that thing is like I did the best of the four of us and
you guys were like, what did you do?
Right.
And I was like, I have no idea.
I don't know.
I was like, I kept checking and going like, did I hit some secret thing?
But I don't think I did.
And every round I was doing well and I was just like, I feel like I'm failing.
I was literally just flailing around.
There's no satisfaction from doing it, which you should.
I think a similar thing also would not just swing us into this to smugglers run.
I think maybe you have to.
Yeah, that's another video gamey.
Yes.
Super like highest tech of the moment.
Which I think I enjoyed because I had incredibly low expectations because this was my first time
going on it after two years of everyone dunking on it and saying it was a disaster.
I thought it was like, OK, I thought it was like fun.
You know?
Yeah, sure.
I was in the gunner role, which I was just shades of like it is a thin like you're not sure what
you're looking for.
Looking at it.
The gunner is frustrating as hell.
Yeah.
You said no, you were like because we didn't we didn't fill up the car so you had you could
swing from position to position.
Yeah.
You said I will not be the gunner.
I wanted to be engineer because they will if you only have four, they'll just give you
gunner and then two pilots.
And I was like, I want to be engineer over a gunner.
Gunner is like, it's not fun at all for me.
But in the movies, very fun.
The gunner pods in the Millennium Falcon sequence in the movies, very fun, kind of
abandoned.
Why is it so fun in the movie?
Yeah, it's more like locking automatic doors on a car in this.
It's sort of failing.
I open and close aim.
That's the most fun thing to do in the world, but they deny you of doing that.
I just I remember like I knew from everyone I've heard talk about this that there's like
an absolute like there are short straw positions and everybody says engineer is, but I disagree.
It's gunner.
I've heard and then when you said no, gunner is the one you don't want to do.
I was surprised because I was thinking like gun Luke and he's got the thing in the head.
Yeah, of course.
Coolish in the world.
Of course.
I hear you can tell what you're doing like the Toy Story games and you can see the results.
Engineer at the very like at like gunner, you have to like kind of like you have to
tilt to the left or right like your back like you're hitting a button.
It's like an awkward spot and watch the screen and try to do it and it's like engineer.
You can kind of chill out and just go click click and you can pretend you're like a little kid like
in Scotty and engineering or or LeVar Burton or whatever.
This gets to a key thing, which is that Toy Story Midway Mania is in no way going for immersion,
right?
Toy Story Midway Mania is only aiming to give you a fun time.
I agree with that, but I also think immersion comes from the fact that everything works in perfect.
That's the irony is then you start to get more pulled in completely immersed.
I think when you're in Millennium Falcon, you're more aware of the fact that it's like this is
them trying to trick my brain into making you think I'm doing the thing and this has any cause
and effect and whatever that seamless right versus Midway Mania where it's just like,
hey, come on, shoot some things.
And you're like, oh my God, I'm in and going for photo reel, which is tougher as opposed to
cartoony.
And I think it's why you're not so critical of graphics from 2008.
Yeah.
That it's going in the same way that you're not so critical of Toy Story from 1995.
Okay.
So here's the surprise.
Besides the humans who you expect to be more photo real.
Right.
Here's the thing I'm surprised by, especially because they have done such a complete
Pixarfication of California Venture after this.
Does Cars Land open before or after Midway Mania?
After.
Okay.
Shortly after, right?
They were considering this a radiator Springs kind of that I think comes up.
I saw it mentioned in the Rafferty.
They were like, we got to add something else to Cars Land.
Could we add some sort of thing to radiator Springs?
And I think like before they hit on like that Midway observation, like,
Oh, this was almost a Cars.
It was potentially like, oh, could we put a thing in cars?
And of course that, you know, there was the Route 66 stuff that was already kind of percolate.
So like, I think this had a lot of lives.
Yeah.
I was just going to say a big part of the announcement is I remember it is like,
Disney's mended the fence, you know, like Pixar's back in the fold.
Toy Story 3 is happening.
Like they got control of these franchises.
Again, these beloved characters are going to be used to the best of their ability.
None, no simple reskinning, you know?
And like this ride is going to be a technological breakthrough.
And then the big thing I remember them advertising is like,
because it's all based around these screens and the games,
the basic ride can remain the same, but every couple of years we can update it and add new games.
It's very easy to refresh this, which I thought was a cool idea.
And they were announcing that especially because it was like,
this ride is going to open two years before Toy Story 3 comes out.
But when Toy Story 3 comes out, we're going to update it with new characters you haven't met yet.
And the only thing they do is, what is it?
They replaced, was there a Bo Peep one, I think, at opening that got replaced with the Buttercup
ham and eggs one?
No, with Trixie and Rex.
Oh, it's Trixie and Rex.
Yes.
But also Buttercup gets put into the...
Right.
Oh, it was a ham thing and then they put...
So they add Buttercup to ham and then the Rex and Trixie wasn't in it at all.
It was originally the Bo Peep sheep.
It was literally, yeah, Bo Peep, they do Bo Peep dirty.
She's missing in Toy Story 3, then she gets cut out of this ride
and then they do a make good with her in Toy Story 4.
But that's what's so bizarre is it's just like...
So this ride has now been open for 13 years.
By the time Toy Story 4 comes out, it's been open for over a decade.
It feels very bizarre that they didn't go like,
new Bo Peep, new Dookaboo, Forky in some capacity.
Ducky and Bunny, who literally are part of a carnival game.
Who are in a game, right?
Why is it just like...
It feels very odd that they didn't do at least one refresh.
Especially being that they have kept that consistent with Star Tours.
You would think they would have given up or gone,
are we really getting our money's worth for that?
Are we really worried people aren't going to see the new Star Wars?
But I think it's really neat that they've kept doing it.
It heartened me to see the amount of Forky merch in the parks.
When you get off this ride, half of the gift shop is Forky stuff now.
Forky's sticking.
I called it.
Forky's here to stay.
You're in love from the trailer, it seems.
I love the guy.
But it's weird that he's not reflected anyway.
It's weird that Bo Peep, who I feel like they very much now elevated to,
to the expense of Jessie, now being the main Toy Story female.
At least in merchandising and branding stuff now.
She's very active and everything.
So how is there not a game?
Absolutely.
There's so much stuff you could do.
It feels a little bit odd to me that they have kept the ride frozen
after doing one very quick update within the first two years of its opening.
It's also extra weird because they did a whole refresh of the pier.
Exactly.
It would have been a perfect time for them to do it.
And now one new game added.
We added Forky into the Woody game or whatever.
You know, added to the ride, added to the gift shop.
And it's kind of a miracle that there was an update to this ride at all.
Because any time they say it's modular and we'll be able to update it, it never happened.
This was the one time it actually happened.
And it happened so quickly that you wanted to believe, like, well, they'll keep it going.
And especially when another movie happens.
And by the way, in between Toy Story 3 and Toy Story 4, they do two TV specials.
They do three short films that play before, theatrical films.
They are doing new stuff with the characters.
Yeah, like Barbie and Kanantix.
I mean, I guess there's a licensing issue.
There's a lot of stuff they haven't done.
To the Toy Story 4 fault, there are 60 main characters in this franchise now.
And there are things like Halloween theming that you could do, you know,
like just seasonal special things.
You know what I bought on that?
And I built with if they did Rex dirty in Toy Story 4,
just watch Party Sorus Rex, which is so fantastic.
That might be my favorite of the shorts.
It's a great film.
I'm a big fan of that one.
All the shorts are great.
Like, yes, it's.
Yeah, all this is the quality is pretty high on those things.
I think Toy Story of Terror is really good.
I just watched it for the first time.
Yeah, and it's like there should be some monsters after dark style Halloween late night.
A wheel.
The midway is broken down.
That was the first for Griffin and first for me as well.
I braved.
I dared to see monsters.
You were you were very scared.
Can we say this now?
Yeah, yeah.
There was a lot of everyone trying to reassure you it was going to be OK.
I was I think I was here because of Mike.
I feel like you built it up.
We're like, no, it's scarier.
It's a lot scarier.
I think the song makes it scarier.
I think I said if I was a young kid, I would I would find it scarier for sure.
Because it's darker in there.
And you were also saying, right, like a lot of what you think would hit you hard as a kid
is like walking into the ride and suddenly everything's red and like,
yeah, alarms are going on.
Yeah, not the.
Oh, it's a little post apocalyptic or something.
Yeah.
And that's what I talk about that ride is I say it's like if you went on
pirates after the town burned down.
Right.
Like it's scarier to me.
Yeah, it's great.
It's great.
It's my favorite thing.
I loved it.
I also I swear to God, like there was some time on this podcast where you were building up the
monster after dark song and I thought I'm going to be afraid of this song.
This is going to be the darkest death metal I've ever heard.
And then the song itself.
I really liked the song.
I am very on board with the song.
So good.
I want to buy the song on a seven inch vinyl.
You can get it's an Apple music.
Yeah, but I want to.
I want to.
You want an album.
Yeah.
You want to hear that when you hit that needle pops in the cracks.
I'm monsters after dark.
Because you gave that exact example.
I got an Instagram ad recently from like Disney records of a seven inch for one side is the
skeleton dance and the other side is the three little pigs.
And I opened the link and it was five dollars and I was falling asleep, but I opened up the
thing and I was like, I will buy that tomorrow.
And I woke up in the morning.
It says this page does not exist.
And I was so mad that like it wasn't for sale anymore.
Like they were like it was the last copy or the last handful of copies.
Now, have you since then found any proof that this item does exist that you didn't dream?
I'm reasonably sure that this actually happened
because I wanted to.
I remember looking up seven inch frames.
Can I just also because I don't want to just assume that we know the song three little pigs.
What is the sound of the song?
The skeleton dance?
Is anyone willing to like, is it like a new?
Well, no, it just had a cool in.
I was more going to buy it and buy one of those record frame and like hang it on a wall
because it had the guys like doing the dance.
It's a thing from the 20s.
It's like a really early black and white.
Yeah.
It's awesome.
And it's in one of the windows right now for Halloween.
You got very excited.
I went skeleton dance.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
Yeah, it does exist.
Okay.
You can get it for like 35 bucks on eBay.
It was for record store.
I'm sorry.
This does sound cool, but Disney doing record store day stuff.
I mean, that's very funny.
That's very much.
They go so hard on that now.
Yeah.
Well, I found a 10 inch rare.
Some day my prints will come.
Holy shit.
Wow.
It's the monkey's uncle outtakes.
It's the monkey uncle demo.
It's in and they pressed it on an orange vinyl.
We did Musker and Clemens on Blank Check at the beginning of this year.
And I sort of just I kept on stewing back on the like.
It is kind of astonishing how successfully in the last 10 years,
Disney has been able to sell Disney as simultaneously being kind of alt.
You know, yeah, that like find a way, right?
Hot Topic is just kind of a different Disney store now
and that they can do all these like vinyl releases that are like manufactured by Disney.
Yeah, like Nightmare Before Christmas maybe just reads is like this cool retro movie.
Have you ever heard of it?
It's kind of this art film.
I think that was their entryway that they had this movie that like Disney was embarrassed by
and that kind of underperformed and then people reclaimed
and then Disney figured out how to monetize and then they were like,
could we do this with everything?
Yeah, we simultaneously sell like aerial dolls to little girls, but also sell like
notebooks that look like VHS clamshells and go like,
I'm just like, I don't know what to tell you.
I'm like a 90s kid.
That is the canniest move.
I and I saw a Toy Story one.
I came so close to buying that.
I was so close to buying.
We like them too.
These things aren't bad.
They do.
They do them right.
Clever.
I mean, my sister is like my sister works in food and like Ratatouille is like a big movie for us
and a couple years ago I got her for her birthday like four very cool things that they had made
where it was like, you know, a recipe book, a fill in your own recipe book that looks
like a perfect replica of the Gusteau book and then it was like a jar that looks like
the jar they have in the restaurant and all this stuff and I was like,
this is just so smart to make the products that are either like replicating a form factor
or a thing you have emotional attachment to or here's a practical version of the thing
in the movie that you can now hold.
Like every time I see the like, oh, it's like a mug that's chip as a cup.
I'm just like, yeah, best product ever.
Like so smart, so obvious.
I have that.
Yeah.
We have Cogsworth in the apartment.
That's another one.
Yes.
Like all of those when it's just like you can own the real thing
and it does sort of what it's supposed to do.
The lapel pin of the up grape soda bottle cap.
Yes.
And I'm just like, oh, God, why are you?
Why?
Well, we can't have this too emotional.
The fucking Monsters University hats are like the perfect example of just like those hats
are bigger than that movie is and I think it just is because it's like, well, it's a movie
where the hat has importance.
So if you're going to walk into a Disney store and look at like a wall of 800 hats,
you can get the one that has a logo on it or you can get the one that immediately makes
you like part of the thing.
Yeah.
They should like any if it's important in the movie, it should exist.
As a physical item, you know, it'll work out well.
Okay, here's something maybe a little shift we can take here just to make sure that we do it.
I feel like we should talk about these games and we should talk about them from
the gameplay perspective and so we can step through it and we'll reveal how we did because
this was a good like, oh, this is a channel with this.
There's four of us.
We weren't quite in the same car, but on the same vehicle, there was like a little face
off that happened.
I feel like it was like a chance to put our skills to the test and display anything that
we knew about how to do this ride and how to do these games.
Mike and I were together.
Jason and Griffin were together.
Correct.
And the ride had barely been going before Mike and I are murmuring to each other and
backseat driving what you guys are doing.
As we look back, we can see where you guys are and we like turn to each other without even
we just knew exactly what the other was thinking, which is like they're doing the practice
rounds.
They're doing the practice that they're going to blow their energy.
Big mistake.
I say they're wearing down their wrists already.
It's something we learned a long time ago.
Don't do the practice rounds.
Rookie mistake.
In fact, I think it's filling up on bread.
Why do it?
I mean, you guys did do better than us.
That is that is how it ended up playing out.
And I did better than us and Griffin smoked my ass.
But then Griffin and I both did very well on web slingers.
Because my web slingers trick is you just punch.
I adopt that as well.
Ben, I'm shooting the webs on the back of his hands, not the other side.
I just started doing like air drums.
I just started at a certain point.
Just anything.
That's what I've heard.
Just wave indiscriminately.
Yeah.
But even at the beginning, I was I was being diligent and doing the thwip hands and even
that's what you want to do.
No, I thought I was doing really well on the ride because I hadn't been on it in so long
that I forgot what the levels of success are.
And I was smoking Jason.
I was like, am I fucking have I gotten great at this?
And then we check in afterwards.
I was like, oh, no, you guys smoked both of us.
We didn't come anywhere close to anything.
Nobody super.
Nobody went out of the water.
I did extra good for my normal score for sure.
But I wasn't in any of that.
I never do better than like the top score that there's people that are so good at the game.
There's no reason to build it up too much.
We might as well just and we can maybe say figure out how we got there.
Sure.
The in ascending score orders.
Yeah.
Uh, or I guess which way should I do?
Mike was Mike was number one.
I was number one.
I was number two.
Griffin was number three.
Jason was last.
Unfortunately, I'm sorry.
Mike, I believe your score put you at you were the only one who graduated from
Beaver to cat.
You were a cat.
I got a cat.
Is it Beaver?
I usually looks cooler.
I don't disagree with that.
It was a fun friend.
I usually get the Beaver.
But no, I got a cat.
I vastly the vast majority of my trips have been the Beaver.
This is also the only context in which the four of us would casually be bragging about
getting the Beaver.
I got yeah, I'm always getting Beaver.
Right.
Like this is the kind of thing that would sound really gross if anyone.
Go on the ride, you do a jerk off motion and at the end you get the Beaver.
Okay, you do a constant flick.
Yeah, your wrist turns a lot.
And then like, oh, yeah, that thing you do when your co workers, you know, they're at
it again.
Geez Louise.
Look, I'm not quitting until I get the Beaver.
Okay, but heading down to Anaheim this weekend, maybe I'll end up getting some people.
Look, the only time I've ever said that word on this podcast was when I was referring to
the famous Jerry Mathers character.
Okay, now that's a wholesome way to use that word.
Colonel Clink.
Although you know who actually has the Jerry Mathers reference from this podcast is Scott,
I believe.
Yeah, because I'm the house that I was born into.
The first house I lived as a baby was sold from Jerry Mathers to my parents.
Who played the Beaver on an old show.
Is the Beaver.
Which does explain this to me.
I was getting a little insulted.
Maybe there's a new listener who doesn't know.
But the house was getting sold then like a decade later.
There had been multiple people in the house by that point.
And we went to my dad was like, you should see the first house that you lived in.
And there was a little like makeshift plaque that called it the Beaver house.
Despite it being as he moved into in what?
1979.
And like a perfectly plain house.
I will say I did just do the check during Mathers 73.
I think.
Not at risk.
Of the blank.
The PTR curse.
My mom regularly tells me what the guy Tony Dow who played Beaver's brother Wally.
What he's up to because she follows him on Facebook.
Wow.
So this is what I this is my life still.
Because I think Eddie Haskell passed away recently.
I forget if the actor's name is.
Eddie Haskell did pass away.
I am also blanking on the actor's name.
We did lose Eddie Haskell.
I don't know that we talked about Eddie Haskell recently, though.
My dad, Eddie Haskell, I feel like is still one of my father's favorite references.
And in a Colonel Klink kind of way of just referring to someone with Eddie Haskell behavior.
You're bringing friends around.
You're like, this guy's a real lady.
Haskell.
Some Eddie Haskell.
Yeah, selling.
Yeah.
Who's that reference today?
Does young Sheldon have a ne'er do well, a slightly ne'er do well friend?
Well, but the thing with Eddie Haskell was that he was a ne'er do well who was so good
at sucking up to every last.
That's right.
It was the balance of the two where it's like I'm not the insincerity of it.
You know?
Yeah.
I don't know.
No one's been able to touch Haskell's lane.
You really think about it.
He retired unopposed.
Retires Jersey.
Do you have it's I feel so stupid that I have never thought about
not wasting your energy on the practice round and get every time I do that ride,
you know, and I do it less frequently than you guys, but I certainly never go to Disneyland
without going on it or world.
I never go to the parks without going on that ride because I want to see my best friends.
Of course.
Every single time, by the time I get to the final round where it's just hit as many times
as you can, I'm like spent.
Yeah.
I'm in pain.
It's exhausting.
Really awful.
And to into the like good up until that point, and then I'm just like losing it.
Yeah.
You know, Jason, your reference, we're talking about any crossover between this attraction
and sexual.
There is something about the way that that finishes where like it like finishes with
a big torrent and then an explosion and everybody leans back in their chairs like, oh, well,
you're like you're like throw.
That's like the Jerry Seinfeld bit.
Like you're thrown clear afterward.
Like your body literally has to move away from everyone sort of has their own style.
But essentially, your strategy is you're going to develop a rhythm that you maintain for
most of the ride.
And then you get to that final one.
You start speeding up and the intensity increases faster and faster and faster.
Right.
More.
You see.
Yes.
Right.
And you're likely to get the best score if you're an active listener.
Yes.
Right.
Listen to what they're telling you to do.
And then you just you have that moment where you can literally just release your hands,
finally release your grip and just go.
But then also you start to actually feel like what position you might have been in that was odd.
And you go, oh, my leg or my arm.
I shouldn't have done that.
And was it like, did you like take some risks, but maybe you did worse in taking the risk
and you should have just aimed for a solid performance.
Yeah, you should have just stuck with what works.
And what we know, what we like.
From my experience, predominantly there's that feeling that immediately where you look
at the screen in front of you and go, what am I looking at?
You know, there's the immediate.
Yeah, it's it's bullseye.
You sort of lose.
What did I do?
Yeah, you lose contact.
It's something.
Right.
What?
You like wake up again.
Yeah, yeah.
Horse.
Yeah.
I got the beaver.
Or is this an army man yelling at me?
Says he's proud.
Okay.
But he's not my mom.
That's another thing.
When you made your Sarge reference at the beginning of the episode, I got confused for a second.
I realized for the first time as a Pixar fanatic that there are two Pixar Sarges.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Yes.
Near identical personalities.
Right.
Obviously, same color scheme.
Both have decent presences in the parks.
Mm hmm.
Similar voices.
I mean, Paul Dooley is Carsarge.
Arlie Army is Toy Story.
Great character actors.
Yeah.
I just like that they just went back to that well and they were like, I know, another militant guy.
If we're talking general strategy on this attraction, I guess it is similar to maybe
do a lot of these kinds of rides and to web slingers.
Do you want to just flail around and do as much as possible?
Like, I don't know, there's no real...
Or is it better to aim for smaller targets, secrets?
I think it just depends on your skill level.
Yes.
I'm a smaller target secret guy and I feel like I always tell myself, like,
look up the secrets before you go on and I always forget to.
But I definitely, I try to like...
My accuracy is always very low.
I try to shoot as much as I can, but I'm saving those shots for the harder targets,
for better or worse by and large.
If I feel like it's been a little while and I haven't gotten anything, I'm like,
maybe let me go down to the easier ones, knock out a couple of quick points,
and then go back up to the little guys.
I think you can really rack up points with quantity on the lower ones.
But I think where I get competitive is like, I want to get those high...
Of course.
Even maybe even more competitive than with the person next to me.
I'm like, I want to get that airplane that's really far away or I want to get the one that's moving.
You know what?
Here's...
You want it for yourself.
Here's another thing this ride has on web slingers.
Web slingers, it's just all of those goddamn spider bots who essentially look the same
with almost no variation, and then you end each room with like a major spider bot.
The targets are so different in this and there is that fun kind of like...
They react differently.
You know, there's the added bonus to like, if you get a harder target,
you get a little fun animation, maybe a little alien launches, you know?
And there's also an ASMR aspect to it too.
There's a very satisfying...
Like the plate breaking is very satisfying noise.
The balloon popping is very satisfying.
Like when I hear it and when I've done it, I feel good.
Like there's some extra level of it.
And the variation is really valuable.
The fact that you're changing sort of materials, projectiles every time.
And that it does still feel kind of tangible to you.
Everything flies a little differently.
Yeah.
You do have to...
It's a little adjust, like this thing doesn't launch in the same way.
Right.
This is blunter.
It's interesting, Jason, I never had noticed that it was a cannon before now.
But it is such an odd like weapon because it's not like astro blasters or Men in Black,
where you just have like a gun, right?
Or Spider-Man where you're just flailing your arms around.
Right.
It's like this odd pull string mechanism that it seems bizarre,
but there's something about it being this one central thing
that doesn't represent any of the activities better or worse than any others,
if that makes any sense.
It's funny we're talking about this ride perhaps and the whole relationship.
It's all about Disney maintaining their relationship with Steve Jobs and everything.
Yeah.
There's like an Apple level of simplicity into the single button and now to the no buttons
that we had, like how much you're able to do on all these devices with very little...
But the aerodynamics of a ring are different from a projectile that you're shooting
or throwing a dart or whatever.
You're still using the same physical motion, but as you said, the arc of it,
as you're launching it, you have that adaptation process every time of like,
I got to adjust.
But how do they possibly land on this single thing that is meant to represent
throwing a dart or launching an egg or a rubber dart?
Is there a real game that has a pull string thing?
Does that have a basis in something?
No, but it's what you said, right?
That it was taken from this Pirates of the Caribbean thing.
Yeah, I think that's where the early version started.
That's like a fuse a little bit on it.
Right, that must be...
And Jim and Lem pointed out, it is amazing that this thing looks like string,
like a pull string and people are yanking on them all day long
and they always seem to be in pretty good shape.
I think that took a lot of engineering.
That's a great call, because this is the kind of ride where you imagine,
if I go on this in two years, it's going to be gnarly.
It's going to be like...
Well, it's like Astro Blasters, where sometimes you get a really bad gun
and Astro Blasters is hanging down and it doesn't even fit in the holder anymore.
Yeah, but they always work.
I've never had...
I think the first game when we were just playing, we were like,
is this a little off today?
But it's always consistent, by and large.
You're not dealing with like, oh, this one's frayed.
There's not even just on a tactical level in terms of what you're engaging with.
Any degradation I really sense there.
It always really works and there's never...
Sometimes a round will end and you'll go, oh, that was it,
especially compared to who you're sitting with,
but you never bomb out.
You get enough satisfaction, you're getting those sounds that you want, Mike.
It's like even in one that's a little lesser, it's not like, well, I didn't hit anything.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah.
It's like impossible.
Right, right.
It does pass that sort of like 8 to 80 test and it also just is fun.
It's like aesthetically pleasing.
There's such a variety.
The music is so upbeat.
You have your nice toy friends saying like, great job.
They always say great job.
That's right.
It's very encouraging.
It's not like too quippy.
It doesn't feel like they're overloading jokes.
They're letting you focus on the task at hand.
Yes, and they're not throwing too much at you,
which is what all these other rides generally do.
Because if there's an element, and I've said like,
obviously Transformers is a screen ride that throws a lot at you,
but you don't have to shoot.
If you were to shoot on Transformers as well, it'd be insane.
But this is simple.
It stays in one spot and it's just clean and easy.
And Astro Blasters and what's Men in Black called Alien Attack?
Yeah, they have the benefit of it being like a classical dark track ride.
So whether or not you're doing well in the game,
you're still getting the experience of going through a cool themed area.
Right.
Like the Toy Story thing felt like, oh, this is the beginning of something new.
And then no one else has really done it successfully since then.
Right.
Because there's something about I think again, where you come back to that,
it's a construct thing where like you don't think about that really,
that you're just landing at TV after TV.
Right.
But oddly, if the ride is trying to do something more immersive than that,
then you just think, well, I'm just going from TV to TV.
It becomes so much more aware of it.
Yeah.
And in like Spider-Man 2, I think I was saying this on the Marvel episode.
It's like they don't put any villains in it.
Which is which is weird.
But then, OK, so it's relentless spider bots.
If it was just maybe like spider training and this one level is like we're shooting
what I was saying before, like taking the barrel and whipping it.
And it's like a much simpler static task.
Well, I bet it might be more satisfying.
What is that also getting at, Mike, too?
It's lowering the stakes.
It's not putting the pressure on you.
It's not making it feel like a swarm game.
It's not like Peter Parker, like sing like, I fucked up.
You have to fix this for me.
Right.
It's just kind of like, hey, I'll teach you how to be Spider-Man.
Yeah.
Even if there is a scoring system there, it's like that's the kind of let me relax.
Tell me I'm going to do a good job.
Right.
Not going to do if we're not going to get attacked by the Hobgoblin.
And we're not going to do any of that.
Might be weird, right?
Shit with the Sony Disney deal.
Like, who fucking knows who they can and can't use?
Yes, very possible.
But we're not going to do that.
Yes.
A simpler Spider-Man training simulation with points.
Right.
If he was like Mr. Stark made me this training facility.
This is like Spider-Man's danger room.
Right.
Yes, sure.
And it's like you have robots coming at you, but they're not just a thousand of the same
little thing.
It's different types of tests.
Yes.
By the way, if it was danger room ride and it was we got to wear the visor, Jason and I would.
We would be like, as orgasmic as at the end of Toy Story with the Omanians.
It just really kind of feels like the web slingers concept should be applied to the danger room.
Sure.
Yes.
But yeah, no, I've said before I want Cyclops's visor on this ride.
But that's again, maybe not going to because of rights.
I don't know.
Although Iron Man's you can get as repulsed you buy as repulser.
So I guess you can use Iron Man on this.
Yeah, we were looking at the all the well, I mean, this isn't a web slingers episode.
I'm sorry.
I was like, I'm not like racing to do one.
So if we want to do a mini one.
Yeah, I want to get better at web slingers.
Also, if you yeah, I want to get better at it.
I would like to do it a bunch of times and figure out like how to do the satisfying things
that I supposedly can do.
I mean, your line, Scott, when we walked off was like, I don't think I'd be capable
of doing an episode after that.
I don't think I really could process what was happening.
I would have to.
Yeah, a lot of ride throughs, a lot of videos.
Also, just down that car.
They Manhattan also.
So it's just, I don't know.
I just I'm sorry.
What happened?
I think that might have helped, though.
I don't know.
Yeah.
But yeah, I just have all that stuff.
It's like it's overthinking.
And I'm sure they put a lot of thought into Toy Story, but like it feels like they didn't
overthink.
It seems like some of this or some of this older imagineering.
I don't mean because you never want it to be like it was only good before.
But we're talking about things in 2008 and 10 and 12.
Yeah, right.
And it's and we praise things when they are good when they come out now.
So it's not cut and dry like that.
But it does.
I do just think about this guy, Kevin Rafferty.
He seems like his aim is a lot, a lot of thought then in the most simple.
It comes back around to simplicity.
But so much is put into what seems like a simple, breezy experience.
And I feel like lately there's a lot more of these things that are like, oh, yeah,
the complication of it is showing.
And they think that's part of the appeal.
Look how much work we've done.
I had not done.
I done neither Galaxy's Edge nor Avengers Campus.
I was doing it for the first time with you guys.
And, you know, I had had I've read less about Avengers Campus.
I've been waiting very long to go to Galaxy's Edge and have read all the
waves of response on everything, you know, tried to do Rise without spoilers,
but certainly the response to the land and like the obvious complaints of like,
why are you not putting all the classic stuff in here?
Why aren't we getting to see everything we want to see?
Why is it a new planet?
Why is it more focused on the Disney or all this sort of stuff?
And I was like, I don't think that's going to bug me.
I like these Disney movies more than most people.
I just want to walk around Star Wars land and I get there and I did feel the absence
of all these things.
And then we walked over to Avengers Campus.
It was not very crowded the day we were there.
I think that area is probably super underwhelming if you have to deal with a lot of hassle to go
through it.
But the second we walked there, we saw three superheroes.
Like we walked there, we were like, oh, there's Shang-Chi.
Oh, look, Captain Marvel's over there.
Wasp is up there on the ledge.
And then we left and then we came back through to get like drinks.
And then we were like, oh, Captain Thor's there.
Loki's on the ledge.
And then the third time we came by, we saw like a different combination of three superheroes.
And you're just like, man, that really fucking works that you just walk through this Marvel
area, which is visually the least interesting thing in the world because all Marvel movies
look like like concrete military bases now.
Right?
All your favorite shades of gray and brown are here.
Right.
Like it looks very boring during the day and they don't have enough well defined
Marvel landmarks to even be able to replicate.
Like now that they've gotten rid of the Avengers tower and all these things, movies and whatever,
they should just fucking build the tower.
Well, it's a different it's the Marvel theme park universe, right?
Right.
That's how they so it's a different because Tony Stark's not dead in.
And so they could.
They should.
And like, but even still, the characters being there goes such a long way.
Oh, yeah.
Having them walking around.
And I think that so much of the Toy Story mania value too is just like they have these
other rides where it's like Astro Blasters is essentially just a ride of like the Buzz
Lightyear in universe Buzz Lightyear, the real man, not the action figure.
Right.
Like that's what Astro Blasters is.
Actually, yeah, it is.
Wow, that idea kind of is around the same time that they do that Star Command cartoon show.
And it's sort of like between that and the opening of Toy Story 2 and the stuff that's
now going to be retconned by the Chris Evans movie and quality.
Right.
But then you have things like Slinky Dog Dash or whatever, where it's like, well,
you're like covering like one tiny sliver of Toy Story.
There's so much representation.
These movies are so big.
There's so many characters that can do so many things.
This is the one ride where you just kind of get to see everybody.
Yeah.
And even though it's still mostly screen based, it's like, well, but it's just it's
top tier animation and really good voice work.
Yes.
Yeah.
Because like, yeah, if it's your movie, you want to see everyone.
Right.
It's just nice to spend time with everyone.
Like, you know, I came out here when the ride had opened and I was like begging friends
to go and they were like, why do you care so much about this?
I was like, you don't understand.
I haven't been able to see my friends for like nine years.
You know, it like really was a thing for me where it was just like for so long,
it felt like Toy Story 3 was never going to get made because of the legal stuff.
And even though I knew at that point it was going to open, I was just like to be able
to like sit there and see them again felt so big to me.
You know?
And they're behaving like themselves.
They're correct.
Right.
I in terms of complications, I think the complicated stuff is all behind the scenes.
Like I read an Internet Archive article from the website Design News and it's all about like
there's three big computer systems.
There's a system for the vehicles.
There's a system for the games.
There's a system for the special effects and they all work together and they all
there's a lot of automation going on.
There's a lot of like fail safes where it's like, oh, the way these ride vehicles move,
if they don't land in the same exact spot every time, that's OK because the computer
will auto correct it and you won't even notice.
To think that this cost, it only cost 80 million dollars to then develop this stuff
they had never done before.
And I mean, inflation being what it is, but like you hear the price tag that each rise
of the resistance cost 500 million and those are also very impressive, but it's almost
like I don't there are parts reading about how they execute everything on Toy Story
Mamia where I'm like, well, this is almost more impressive.
It makes it all the more surprising they don't refresh it every five years.
Because it's like the heavy duty work's already been done.
Yeah, all you need to do is really like do new animation and come up with a new.
Yeah, well, here's a yeah, because I'm going to propose sort of game by gaming in a little
bit and I think maybe one issue is like, what do you get rid of?
Not to say it's going to be forever, but like that, you know, is it just does that
Trixie slot have to be that one is for the new?
Not necessarily, but I also like I do think I don't know the inner workings of this,
but I do feel like they could be like we have a rotation of 10 now.
Well, yeah, like a start.
Yeah, like start tours.
There's no replete.
You aren't even thinking about replete.
Right.
I mean, it's seasonal or maybe it's this or maybe it's that or you don't know which
ones you're going to write, but like it just feels like you could go like this year
we're adding to we're moving this one.
Yeah, but nothing's ever like sort of permanently retired or just drove by.
Yeah, I think that like it's probably a victim of it being too popular.
So also, because they don't see the reason it's be better if they just like put some
static figures on the California Screamin of the Incredibles to like try to get the
numbers up on that.
You know, I'm also guessing that the updates, the adding Buttercup to Ham and the Dino one
were probably done at the same time as the originals and they just held on to them for
two years until the movie had come out.
I would not be surprised.
That was probably all done.
Now they'd have to like crack it all open again.
Right, because like Monsters After Dark was started like that was being developed
concurrently, right?
Right.
I bet the other time that that's like, let's slip it in.
Let's slip it in.
Just like you had a decade.
There's nine years between Toy Story 3 and 4 and that movie kept on getting delayed
and was a problem.
They only have more and more time to like throw stuff in there.
And now that the movie, like the characters have been well received and Forky is here
to stay, it's just like they want a Forky talk.
I want a game where you're throwing.
You're really just my best friend.
You want to hang out with Forky a little bit.
Are you throwing lots of Forky's?
I don't know.
No, you know what?
No, you should shoot forks.
Well, you could do that.
But also the other thing, obviously, is a Forky loves trash.
Yes, sure.
There's an obvious sort of trash game where you're trying to throw trash into bins.
I feel like.
Interesting.
You're trying to get trash to Forky.
He's in the can.
He keeps on popping up in cans and you're trying to.
Is it different kinds of...
I just came up with this idea.
So let's...
Well, no, but like it would have to be consistently the same trash, I assume.
Like, so would it be like crumpled up paper?
That's what I'm picturing in my mind.
Yeah, sort of a crumpled up ball.
It's the most basic.
Yeah.
Yeah, not banana peels or something.
Well, one thing I read that they didn't do, like they had a bunch of potential games
because, you know, they're trying to correspond to real with real Midway games.
Right.
And the one was the, you know, at not a simulated Midway, at a real Midway, you fire the water
and your horse or your whatever runs along the race.
They talked about doing that with Rex.
And I'm like, Rex?
That would be fun.
You got a fucking horse.
He said Bullseye is the horse.
That would actually be the like, that's the game is usually a horse race.
Yeah.
But I feel like Rex upstages Bullseye a lot.
Isn't Rex the bigger character?
Rex is a bigger character.
Yeah.
And I think that...
Couldn't they race?
Couldn't the both of them race or something?
Bullseye is another character who I think is sort of was given a bad shake.
I mean, that's probably fair.
Also that game, like the racing, you know, kind of game, nothing is destroyed.
A lot of these are destroying balloons or plates.
Oh, sure.
Sure.
It's such a difference.
Yeah, you'd have to like shoot the horses and then...
Right.
That's not going to be good.
Yeah.
Oh, there was an early pitch that was trying to knock down Mr. Potato Head and make his pieces come
off in a dunking booth kind of way.
And then that helps them land on...
I don't know if you want to shoot at the characters.
I think that's weird.
I think it's got to be these...
And it's not even characters at all, really.
Right.
Besides the army men who like want that, they want to get hit with the rings so they can
fly away.
They want it.
Yeah, and they're also like...
The aliens.
Wait, what did I say?
You said army men.
Oh, yeah, sorry.
Yeah, yeah, aliens.
Yeah.
But you do have like army men in that too where it's just like, oh, those are like kind of
the grunt characters, you know, where they're just like...
Build defined.
So...
Right, and they're just lesion.
But it does help that our hero characters are all sort of playing like Barker.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
They're not even really in it.
They're running the game for you.
Which is sort of what they...
Yeah, I think the idea was probably more like...
This is sort of in the line of the Simpsons ride where it's booths and the characters
are there and they stay at the booth.
Right.
And that was probably more the idea was something like that.
You land at a booth and like step right almost the way Mr. Potato Head is outside.
But then instead, it's these like brief appearances and they slide out of the way
because you don't want them around consistently.
All right, so let me throw out a couple because we can talk about secrets a little bit too.
Or how are you getting good at these things?
First things, ham and buttercup.
You're throwing eggs.
Right, ham and eggs.
It's like, oh, we're the seven miters of Barnyard animals.
What is the...
What's the secret here?
It involves the barn.
Yeah, this one I always forget because I know the volcano one and I know the...
The rocket.
The rocket, excuse me.
Yeah, but the barn one, I haven't been waiting to look it up and now I'm not in my right spot.
No, sure.
Now everyone's waiting for me.
I will say, at like the time they...
You're losing points.
Hold on a second.
Everyone, let's practice for a moment.
You're not going to be best in vehicle at this rate.
At the time they added this, it kind of warmed my heart because
buttercup and ham only get to meet at the very end of Toy Story 3.
Then there's like a little after credit bit when they're doing all the sort of like odds
and ends, little like blackout jokes in the end credits of that movie to
Randy Newman's Academy Award winning song, We Belong Together,
where you're like, oh, these guys are a good match.
Like, not just these two characters, but like Ratzenberger and Garfield.
And the similar comic energy.
There's funny to have these two guys, right?
Where it's nice that you're like, oh, you get to like watch the two of them being buddies.
You know that they're on the same page.
They're running a business together.
Right. It's fun.
Nice feeling.
It's fun.
As opposed to all the other ones where you're just like, well, obvious pairing, you know, like
Trixie and Rex, I guess is the same thing too, where you're like destined.
Right.
Here we go.
From the same line.
They've done more Trixie Rex stuff since this.
Yeah.
So this is the start of it, which is nice.
I found it.
You have to hit the 500 point gophers at the bottom of the screen and make sure to hit the fox on the
hen house in the bottom corner as well.
Next, you want to aim for the 100 point pigs on the lower fence.
Once you've cleared them, a cat will appear in the same general area with a 500 point value.
Continue to repeat the process and each time the cat target point value will increase
from 500 to 1000 to 2000.
So it's a very specific order you have to do.
Yes.
But look for this cat, maybe.
The cat is, yes.
And then it tells you you should have like 50,000 points by the end of this.
But there's nothing that like opens it.
There's no like big ticket item where I, in my head, like the bar opens up or something.
It doesn't say that on here.
That might be the case.
I just found one.
This is the one site I think I've been to before, but maybe, yeah, maybe there's a different secret
that I'm not even aware of.
These are like sequences and Easter eggs that like, if you don't do them in the game
or you aren't aware of them, it doesn't detract from your enjoyment.
No, which is a he.
It's just little secrets.
Yeah.
That maybe increase your score, but that's what I'm saying.
Maybe in the pursuit of it, you can end up doing worse.
That's why you're trying so hard to get the secret.
It's not dissimilar to on Buzz Lightyear.
If you know the color codes, like, oh, this color target is worth more points than this
color target.
That was the earlier iteration.
Yes.
But yeah, you would never know.
It's not like you get upset because it's just as fun to play without the secret.
But once I learned the secrets, I was elated.
Not this little one because I didn't know it, but the ones that I know.
Now, I think that well, here's we'll go in around two, which is Rex and Trixie's
Dino darts.
It's all kind of centered around a volcano and balloons are flying around and you're
hitting them with darts.
And the secret is thin strips of lava.
You want to hit those.
Lava balloons.
That causes the volcano to erupt with balloons.
Now, that one, I think we both knew and we're both trying to get it.
And we did both, I think, help each other.
I think it was a very good round for both of us because I think if both people in your
party are going for it, then it can benefit.
It's not just the person trying to get it.
Yeah.
And we didn't even get to the point because if you get all those balloons, then meteors
appear.
Oh, yeah.
I don't think I knew it.
Those are even more.
Those are worth more points.
So we did not get to that point there.
So that's an extra level of success.
Now, I've also seen this tip about it that potentially it is possible that you can do
better if you are flying solo.
If there is not a person in the seat next to you.
Interesting.
And I got curious about previous scores that I have gotten.
And I have two photos at different times where I took a photo of the screen after because
I got the cat, a rare instance of getting a cat and not getting Beaver.
Yeah.
And in both instances, I was by myself.
I'm sorry, just to clarify, you didn't get the Beaver, you got the pussy?
Yes.
I felt like it was being left on the table.
Is that officially the balliest thing that's ever been said on this map?
Failed to get Beaver did end up getting pussy.
Can't even say it.
They ended up pulling away from the mic upon seeing it.
This is Patreon only now.
This is Monsters After Dark, PTR Monsters After Dark.
Yeah.
I went down and I'm solo to get the pussy.
And it didn't work out.
You're so unnatural.
You're like, you winced while you said that.
He transforms into a different character as well, like different body language.
And it's like a whole thing.
It has to happen to have that word come up.
Staring at the ground.
I'm rubbing my hands together like I'm being a bad.
You're like, I can't do that.
I can't commit to this.
He turns to like Igor or something.
His eyes turn black.
Peter Laurie voice would be appropriate for that.
It's that special bottle at Napa Rose that he orders.
Something happens.
The Norbit.
The two times you've gotten the cat.
Yeah, were by myself.
So which indicate.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And I guess the logic there might be that the other person just gets in the way.
It's with sex itself.
Amen.
Did that episode go to a very strange flavor of Habsden is only a vacation?
No, no, it was masturbation only.
Yeah, Habsden masturbation based.
Habsden is just I can't follow what they're talking about.
Are they too horny or not horny enough?
What's the ultimate question from this for this podcast?
Strange reading on all of these guys.
Anyway, the real thing I'm saying, maybe there is something to this.
So don't go with your friends anymore.
Go by yourself.
And if you're with your friends, say no, you're not getting on with.
Break off your friendships.
Ended right then and there.
If there's a friendship that's teetering, take him to Disneyland, pay for it.
It's a nice exit.
Then they'll maybe have fun feelings for you, even though you say, hey,
I don't really want to do this with you.
Oh, the ride?
No, the full thing.
This is the end of life.
Toy Story mania ruined my life.
All I could do was play Toy Story mania.
I could do nothing else.
It had to be deep program.
Yeah, I was going to say, like, I would like if somebody sometimes,
like if you're on there with somebody who's like to I don't want to play
or whatever, just tell them they don't even touch it.
You know what?
It will only help me.
It's great advice.
Let me do the work.
Don't even touch it.
If you don't want to play, don't even touch it.
I guess the ride 2021.
I'm Griffin Newman.
Memify all of these.
Yeah.
Make us stare at everything we said.
Somebody does an out of context Twitter account for podcast the ride
where they just take quotes from episodes.
And I don't remember anything.
I don't remember anything.
But this one will be I'll remember everything from this.
Do you guys find I can't tell if I no longer remember anything
because I've crossed whatever threshold of hours recorded
or if it just the covid brain just done.
My memory is fucked forever.
It definitely accelerated the.
Absolutely.
I think it's maybe both at the same time, but I just really,
when people quote back stuff to me from episodes,
I have no idea what they're talking about anymore.
And I used to have a pretty good memory.
Yeah, I think we've had we would have to like talk about it a couple times.
It would have to become like a baby Aladar.
Right.
That's how I gauge it.
If it becomes a baby Aladar in our like we've mentioned it multiple times.
Yeah.
But yeah, that's what it takes now.
Maybe if back when we had all only done, you know,
one hundred and twenty five episodes.
Yeah.
But now that we're in whatever the hell we're at.
Mm hmm.
Yeah, no, it's I have a pretty good memory.
I just I yeah, a lot of stuff I go back.
I go, oh, I don't remember that.
And especially when it's out of context.
No clue.
Yeah, it sounds unhinged when it's out of context.
Absolutely.
Mm hmm.
I'll sound just fine, though.
I think the law makes sense and seem very clear.
Yeah, this stuff.
I'm not going to forget this episode.
I will never forget this episode.
Yeah, I am so sweaty, intense.
And all this vulgarity and well, you know, I'm never going to forget it.
I don't know if we've said we're recording in Scott's garage.
Correct.
We did lock the gates.
I did say this is our first time recording in the garage.
And you know what they say?
You never forget your first time.
So the cat ran and make it guys just come up to the garage.
The cat ranch.
Oh, Dennis Hoff died.
Did we mention bunny bunny ranch cat, whatever the hell that brothel is called?
Bunny ranch and the cat ranch are different.
Yeah.
Oh, excuse me.
Excuse me, Mr. Expert.
Yeah, so I don't know if podcast the right curse Dennis Hoff, owner of that brothel.
I don't think we talk.
Maybe we did talk.
I mean, you haven't done a second gate episode on the bunny ranch, right?
It's one of America's top attractions.
One of the lunatics.
We have not done a second.
We did that long second gate series investigating the Phil Spector, Lana Clarkson.
Right.
And then he died.
Yeah.
We were just asking for trouble with that 12 part series.
You also you you almost cracked it.
You guys came very close to cracking the figure out who really did it.
Yes.
Right.
It's always been a little in question to look at Specter and I'm like, I don't think so.
This guy.
No, he's too steady.
We got to get this guy out of jail and then God, we couldn't do it.
We couldn't free the innocent Phil.
It just doesn't line up with 50 prior years of extremely normal behavior from Phil Specter.
Pulling guns on every person he's ever known.
He never shot them.
I don't believe he would pull the trigger.
He had more practice than us who might accidentally pull a trigger the first time we pick up.
He was the best at not shooting guns in a year.
I'm going to look at that Twitter account and I go, are we Phil Spector truth?
I remember saying that one where we declared what will happen is there'll be a guest and
much like how you were saying that we said we never do.
Toy Story.
They go, well, there was the episode where you guys, I have to confront you about it.
You all believe Phil Spector was innocent and that's just not the case.
You said he was good at guns and we're like, I don't think we said that.
You said the made for TV made for HBO movie was David Mamet's most notorious work.
Al Pacino's finest performance.
Al Pacino's surprisingly textured in it.
I found that more offensive than you absolving the actual man of murder.
Very obvious.
Like, wait, so wait, do you want to talk about King Arthur Carousel or not?
No, that topic was that was a Trojan horse.
I just wanted to get here and say, I really think that he did do the murder.
We agree with you.
It's really confusing.
I heard you're on tape and it's on this out of context Twitter account.
What else do you want?
I guess here she's, I guess.
You guys aren't innocent either.
Yeah, we should.
I mean, we should.
It's funny this came up organically, but there was briefly the pitch that was going to be
Phil Spector's Midway Mania.
That was an early Kevin Rafferty idea.
Right.
You'd have to get those darts past the wall of sound.
Yeah.
And each scream was a different group that he very quickly alienated.
The transitions were going to be little tuning radio sketches like on that Ramones album.
You'd have to somehow shoot orchestral parts on To Let It Be, angering Paul McCartney.
Instead of the animatronic Mr. Potato Head, it's like the Christmas gift from Phil Spector going,
thank you so much for coming to my ride.
Your so open as a nicer future for all of us.
Never thought about that scary message.
That's everything you need to know right there.
It's the most fun Christmas set.
Wow.
All every one of these is classic.
Oh god.
And this is like muttering.
That's like whenever my family asks me to put Christmas music on, I put that on and it's a hit
and people go, oh, good choice, Griff.
As if I haven't done it like every year for a decade.
And then we get to that and there's just silence and everyone sort of doesn't know.
Like, should we talk over this?
Should we skip it?
It's a pretty album in the future.
The devil.
Should I do a spoken word on this one too?
The devil has shown up in the middle of Christmas to wish you well.
And everyone's like, uh oh, the devil's here.
I hope you have a great Christmas.
If the devil just hops from body to body on this earth, was he just, was he Spector for a while?
That was his 20th century body?
Yeah, he produced some fantastic records.
And then he also did some awful shit.
Great artists are dark.
A Christmas gift to you from me, a Jewish murderer.
So green army men shoot camp is round three of the attraction.
I'm not your mother, break those plates.
Oh yeah, I gotta get my guide out here.
There's no secrets in this one, I don't think.
Hold on, there is.
There's no secrets, just like Phil Spector.
It was an open book.
I would say, personally, this one might be the most satisfying.
It's fun.
The breaking the plates.
It's digital, but there's somehow a tactile feeling to it.
The shards, yeah.
Yeah, there's shards.
The next one might, the rings might be the most like, computer programming impressive
that they were able to like figure that out.
The arcs of it.
Getting up and over.
Up and over and landing and then clearing.
Okay, I have the secret here.
At the start, break as many of the higher point plates that you can.
Two 2,000 point plates will pop up on each side of the horizon.
Hit them.
They aren't static and will drop back down below the horizon if you don't hit them.
Once this step is finished, the front of the mountain will sync to reveal a hidden army
tank inside.
After the army tank reveal, a wave of four 2,000 point planes will pop up in succession
on each side of the mountain.
These two aren't static and will drop back down below the horizon if you don't hit them.
Hit all eight 2,000 point plates as well as the 5,000 point plate that the tank shoots
out at you and then repeat the process.
Make sure to hit all of the plates that the newly revealed tank throws out at you.
Wow.
I thought, I literally thought there was no secret and I feel like I've even seen things
that said, yeah, there's not really a secret on this one.
I guess the secret is so complicated.
It's very complicated.
But like a, the hidden, like the real army shows up.
Real military shows up on this ride.
Both heard it.
Blood red.
This is like DisneyEveryday.com has these secrets here.
I don't want the secret.
That sounds like that's doomsday.
Pretty intense.
Yeah.
See, this is a changing times, changing taste because this is what gaming with a perception
was in 2008.
If you could do all of this really quick, you'll get all these extra points and bonuses
and stuff.
And now in 2021, the perception of gaming is I have called a SWAT team to your house.
Because gamers, insane people.
They call SWAT, they SWAT.
They SWAT PBS.
So this is, this is, this is SWATting in this round.
Yeah.
Well, like, or like you could, you should be able to like dock someone on one of these
levels.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
The social, yeah.
It's like, here's the social security.
That's the CID game.
Yeah.
That's a good point.
That's only available on the Oogie Boogie Band.
But like, that's like, that's right there.
Like Halloween overlay should be mutant toys, right?
Of course.
Yeah.
CIDs toys.
Oh, that's cool.
It'd be fun to see them again after all this time.
How fucking cool would that be?
Put big babies staring at the moon in there.
Because Prospector comes in for like a moment at the end of the Woody and Jesse game.
But like, do a twisted Prospector game, Lotso, Gabby Gabby, the mutant toys.
And Treloquist dummies.
Yeah.
Dude, perfect.
Those, you could shoot those off of the shelves.
I think anybody would be happy to just watch them.
Yes.
They wouldn't die either.
They just would fall in that weird broken limb kind of way and stare back at you.
That'd be great.
It'd be really fun shooting them.
This tank reminds me too, when we were talking about how they were trying to figure out how
to do this physically, there are at some amusement parks like bumper tanks that will shoot,
you can shoot balls at each other.
And in theory, the tanks will then suck up the balls to use again.
They're the most cumbersome, clumsy, barely work sort of thing.
Yeah, I've always wanted to do that one of those, honestly.
I've never seen that ride in person.
I've seen those at like family fun spot kind of places in like,
middle of New Jersey and you were looking around and you're like, is this a death trap?
We gotta find one of those.
Does Jigsaw run this? Family fun center?
Yeah, we gotta get that.
We gotta find that.
We gotta go do that.
What's the ring toss is next?
Buzz layers, flying tossers.
I think this is my favorite one.
I love this one, but it is hard.
I find it hard to get the ring around the aliens.
It's a good burn.
Sometimes I get like real frustrated because I'm like just not in the groove.
It's the most challenging one, but that makes it fun.
It's such a difference in the physics from all the other ones.
But I also just like the being able to unlock all the animation from the aliens.
Oh, yeah.
So this is where I shined.
This is where I pulled ahead.
Yeah.
Oh, really?
There was a big jump in this.
I got a huge jump.
Yeah.
I was I've never done better this level because you have to get all the
aliens off of that rocket ship and then the rocket ship blasts off
and then there's a giant mouth opening.
Yeah, they call it a giganto bot.
Suddenly, it's a giganto bot with a big toothy mouth.
And it closes his mouth and opens it again and then it's more points then.
So you have to do what I was in a very good groove with shooting things
when the mouth is closed and the mouth open again and I was immediately back in.
You were always right there and I wasn't.
Yeah.
And that's where I got the points and I think it's the best I've ever done on that level.
And that is yeah, shooting it in the mouth is actually,
as long as you have the timing down, you don't have to actually
like the physics aren't a big problem because it's not like you have to get the ring off
over a small thing.
It's just shoot it in its giant mouth.
Yeah.
Giganto or mouth.
It's just getting the timing right when you're shooting into the mouth.
Yeah, yeah, it's simple.
It's simple because the mouth is large.
Right.
And then it's also in this level where you have to get these rings over the top of the rocket
and get it down and slide it down the shaft.
And time is of the essence.
Yeah, yeah.
Let's be honest.
Because you can getting that ring down to the base, which is a lot of pleasure once the ring,
when you see the ring slide down the shaft.
Sometimes you screw it up and you get really like flopped sweat again.
Well, sometimes you do too quickly and things just pop off real fast, you know?
Yeah.
And then, oh man, it's the dirtiest episode ever.
I don't know what you mean.
I was describing things that happen in Buzz Lightyear's flying concerts.
Classic Midway game.
Not sure what you were hearing.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
I just got called to dinner.
I have a crass brain tonight.
I just keep hearing things.
It's the garage man telling me you put the boys in a garage.
In a dirty garage.
A dog, a van driving by.
Honestly, it's so good to finally have some man talk.
That's right.
My wife's asleep inside and I'm just out here with the boys at night.
The garage.
The dimly lit garage.
Making like giggly little innuendos about the Toy Story ride.
What a naughty podcast.
On the gates.
Those are dirty things we said about the squeaky alien game.
Did we do bad?
Then you go to the old west.
You go to the old west with Woody.
And this is very engrassing.
And Jessie.
And Jessie, yeah.
Lest she be forgotten.
Well, and another thing not to be forgotten here.
You always have to nod to the great work of Mr. Jim Hanks.
False Tom Hanks.
Right.
Fake Woody.
He's the only fake voice in this.
Yeah, I believe so.
And you know, you could complain.
You could say they didn't spring for Tom.
And it is nice when you're watching the shorts.
Which not every short has Tom, but a lot of them have.
They have like, shelled out for him.
So it was always Jim for everything.
That was like very much the thing.
Tom Hanks has talked about this in interviews.
That he was just like, there's so much of it.
I just thought it would be a nice thing to like, give my brother a career.
Like he never will be lacking for work.
And then when they renegotiated for Toy Story 3,
part of the deal was that Tom had to do all of those shorts and specials.
They worked those all in.
Right.
It was like a new deal for that.
Because at that point, they thought 3 would absolutely be the last movie.
But they wanted some new stuff to last for the next six or seven years.
Yeah.
But maybe now he's off, like Robert Downey Jr.
He's off the hook because they killed Woody at the end of 4.
I think so.
Woody's noble sacrifice.
Right.
But it's, yes, even from the beginning, it's sort of like always been Jim for everything.
And even post shorts, I think it's back to Jim for almost everything.
Because you can complain about Jim or you can accept Jim.
Jim Hanks has been Woody more than a lot of people have been any character.
That's the thing.
I mean, it's like, is there a difference?
Yes.
But I like Jim Hanks Woody.
Like I prefer Tom Woody, but Jim Hanks Woody.
It does feel valid to me.
Yeah.
It's not like a Castellaneta Homer.
No.
It feels good.
Yeah.
It feels right.
It feels good.
It feels really good.
And you're going to love the return of Woody, voiced by Chad Hanks.
Oh.
That's going to be really great.
Woody got a little crazy on his adventures this time around.
Oh, Woody is speaking in poor patois, like inaccurate patois.
Woody is saying it's going to be a white cowboy summer.
What?
It's really weird.
He's questioning the vaccine for toys.
Yeah.
If I can just recommend to people quickly, there's a video of Tom Hanks on the Graham Norton show.
I don't know what he's promoting, but it's clearly done when he's filming Sully.
Because he's in like beautiful white haired mustache.
I've seen whatever you're about to say, I think.
And Graham Norton's asking him about like, do you do the voice for the dolls?
He's like, no, that's Jim and this and that and whatever.
And he's like asking about his process for doing it.
He does this impression of what it's like to do voiceover that I will not ruin for people.
That is so incredibly funny.
And it's one of those moments where you're like, oh, Tom Hanks really is just one of our best
performers ever.
The way he acts out an anecdote on a talk show is just kind of immaculate.
Yeah.
It might have been on that show.
I feel like another time on Graham Norton is when he did the full
Dragnet City of Crime rap.
Yes.
Which is also in print that he's so able to do it exactly right.
And with all of the vocal risings.
Remember that was sacrifice.
That's like, I mean, when Michael Keaton hosted SNL after like Birdman.
Oh, yeah.
And they did this sketch that was Taron Killen and Bobby Moynihan
trying to convince him to play Beetlejuice and Batman again.
And he's like saying no, no, no, no, no.
And at the end of the sketch, he just like goes like this, like cut it out.
And then he like turns to camera and he stares it down and he says, I'm Batman.
And he's just like right back in it.
And I get chills every time I watch it where I'm just like, it's just not a day's gone.
But he can just at any moment drop straight into it.
He knows the angle.
He knows exactly how much the arch the eyebrows.
He knows the exact pitch of voice.
And he just like he throws it out.
Yeah.
Oof.
Wow.
Well, he's coming back.
He's back.
When and when?
What is it?
Him and Ezra.
What's his name?
Ezra Miller.
Flash.
Miller's Flash from.
Is that next year?
It's either next week or next year.
I wouldn't be shocked.
Years ago.
I didn't see it.
Already happened.
They're in spite.
He's in Spider-Man 2 or something like Batman and Spider-Man.
And he's in Morbius.
He is in Morbius as Vulture.
Scott, Michael Keefe plays Vulture in the MCU.
He is also going to be in the Morbius movie, which is a Marvel character.
But it's Sony because Sony has the rights to Spider-Man and Sony is doing their own
Spider-verse that's independent of the MCU.
The Sony Marvel deal is so weird because part of it is like
Marvel gets to use Spider-Man in X amount of films that Sony doesn't produce.
Right.
Which is like him ending up in the Avengers movies and stuff.
Yes.
And then part of the deal is Marvel has to give Sony one ostensibly A-tier Marvel character to
use in every Spider-Man movie.
So it's like Donnie Jr. in the first one.
It's Samuel Jackson in the second one.
Cumberbatch in the third.
Right?
Feige gets to produce and direct the direction of it.
Right.
But then now they're making the Venom sequel, Morbius, like these spin-offs.
Jared Leto is Michael Morbius, the living vampire.
Right.
Which is that sentence do anything for you?
Does that sentence do anything for the movie going public?
This movie has been pushed back so many times and obviously COVID and everything,
but they keep on going like, let's just knock it back another 18 months.
Let's just keep kicking it back.
But they can't put Spider-Man in those movies.
So now what they're doing is putting supporting characters from the Marvel
Spider-Man movies in the other villain movies.
So Michael Keaton can interact with Morbius because he's in the Spider-Man movies that
are in the Spider-Man continuity with the MCU.
I like the convolutedness.
Yeah, it's very convoluted.
It's going to get worse too.
So much worse.
Yeah.
Tom Hardy Venom cannot cross over yet.
Right.
This is not dissimilar to in the late 90s.
They kind of peeled off all the street, like, you know, gritty, not super, super powerful
characters into the Marvel Knights line.
Punisher, dear.
The street level.
Yeah, the street level guys.
Just because those books weren't selling very well.
And so they gave them to people from outside of comics or they tried weird takes.
The Punisher is back as an avenging angel.
This sentence to God, does this do anything for you?
Yeah.
Daredevil written by Kevin Smith.
An award winning.
Like a landmark run.
Yeah, a landmark run.
And very, I haven't reread them, but I remember the time being very like liking those comics a
lot drawn by Joe Cassata.
Joe, great art.
Great art.
Yes.
So now it is.
It is just as confusing and dense.
And what's weird too is that then the Marvel Netflix thing is essentially doing Marvel
Knights again, where they're just like these characters can't sustain $200 million movies.
We have no other outlet for them.
So we punt them off to a different department of Marvel that Feige has no oversight over.
And you make lower budget Marvel TV shows with these characters.
And then now they're stuck in this netherworld where it's like, are they in shared continuity
with anything?
Those shows started out acknowledging things from the movies, but then the movies have
never acknowledged them.
And then there are ongoing rumors that they will be acknowledged.
Yeah, we know.
I know what you're talking about.
This is the end of this Toy Story episode, right?
We're almost at the end.
I guess we're almost at the end.
Yeah, the shooting gallery is the Woody's Rootin' Tootin' shooting gallery is the last
game.
Another game.
It's the last game.
I again has a real world parallel over at the other park, the shooting gallery, which when
I was leaving Disneyland the other night at 10 p.m. at night was very crowded.
Yeah, like always popular.
People trying to take the edge off.
Yeah.
Stupid kid yelling at me all day.
I want chicken fingers.
Do you?
It's brutal.
Yeah.
It's a bit, you know, it's such an epic ending because now I think maybe you get to that
screen and don't even realize you're next to more screens.
It almost like gets expansive like a big widescreen Western epic as you travel and
you're shooting the whole way.
But you know, you wear out here.
I think who doesn't in the home stretch?
I was trying to figure out is there a stretch I should be like, is there any scenario where
I like I'm fine after it?
I try different things.
I mean, I'll tell you a thing I do oftentimes is rather than like pulling the ball like
this, I sort of hold my hand out this way.
If this makes sense.
I don't even know how to describe this, but it's like I hope my hands straight out in
front of me and then I sort of notch the ball in between two fingers.
And so I'm pulling the hand towards me.
Yeah.
That makes sense.
Yes, it does.
Because I've tried different techniques is the one the way you want to do it like the
way you're biting my body.
Naturally, I think this we've gotten to the end of the episode where we have to talk about
how you handle a ball handle a singular ball dangling ball.
One ball is this.
This is how you handle one ball.
You like I think you want to grab the ball and then I use my whole arm.
That's how it naturally wants to go.
Right.
Because you blow out your wrist if you're just doing that.
But the wrist, you really the least impact is like holding as you're saying with two
fingers and then just like pulling it like this.
Yes.
This is the motion.
Yeah.
But I feel like I don't get as much.
I don't get as many balls that way.
I don't get as many.
I can't get it as fast.
I can't get going as fast.
I need like for that last run where you're trying to get as many as possible and it just
becomes giant targets to just like speed round go.
And again, you want to get it to a thousand and two thousand as possible.
I definitely like put an arm on the handle to try to give me resistance like something
to hang off of so that it's not like it's anchored and I'm like using like so I'm pushing
one way and I'm pulling another.
We should be filming all of these.
I know the all doing the same weird gesture.
Guys, the gestures are so funny if you were here right now.
If you've done it looks like something else.
They look like so nasty.
It's like an angry father like summoning a cat in the house or like a dog like get in
here.
That's really what it's not sexual.
It's just like get in here.
I switch arms once in a while too.
Yeah, that's a good thing.
Which does that throws me off.
The stranger sometimes I have to.
Sometimes what I do is like I sit on my left hand right before the other games and then
I pull so it feels like a stranger is playing the last round for me.
That's what I do.
It's not the first time also that we've all done these motions and then had people laugh at us.
That's a good point as well.
But it's just.
I really wish I didn't have to say I wish I could only hear your voice.
Right and then someone and then someone in sort of overselling that you did a great job.
No, it was.
Yeah, you should have like a hand be like it was fine.
It's okay.
We can try again later.
Let's not talk about it.
You're making the worst by talking about.
Let's just go to sleep.
Wallachian telling let's just go to sleep.
We're really still talking about this.
Why must we dwell on this?
I'm going to tomorrow.
It was hours ago.
I'm writing a play that I'm going to write a play.
I'm busy.
God, this is going to play great at the store later.
Who is that?
Jeff.
Tim.
That's just a general.
Oh, generally, this would all play well at the lab.
Tim Downs, a laugh factory guy, I assume.
Right.
I think, well, if Superstar Lima was to be believed, yeah.
Yeah.
It is canon, right?
I think so.
Yeah.
Whatever that club is.
Look, you get exhausted.
You get very worn out.
I mean, I didn't really happen to be that bad on this, but I for sure, you know, like two
minutes later, you'll be feeling it.
Five minutes later, you could be feeling it.
If you the listeners have any tips on wrist care.
Yeah.
And how to, you know, because we're all getting older.
Um, how do you make your wrist last?
Yeah, we need.
Are there pills we can take?
Everyone, yes.
Chime in on this.
Is there any, like, do you just agree with us that you're like, you're sore after it?
Or do you have some sort of technique?
Do you double hand it?
Do you have a looser grip?
Mm hmm.
Yeah, right.
Is there like a, uh, uh, web slingers piece of equipment you bring with you?
I was just thinking that.
Like you just attach it and you put a button.
Toys.
If you're a, if you, if this, if these kinds of acts are getting older or getting
tougher as you get older, does toys bringing toys reinvigorate everything?
There's some sort of like motorized suction device you could use, which has a very consistent rhythm.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And you could like just help smooth out performance issues.
Right.
And it's like themed.
It's a theme thing too.
So it could be different characters or.
The thing that web slingers gets right that you can introduce toys into the equation
and add some new dimensions and levels.
Repulsors or.
It helps with repeatability.
Gauntlet.
Wrist gauntlets.
All that stuff, you know, that spices things up.
Different bindings.
Yeah.
Suit of armor.
Different suit of armor you could wear.
I will say a weird thing about this ride that defies logic for me
is that I feel like a year or two after it opened, they released it as like a cell phone app.
And then also as a Wii game.
Right.
I think they did it for PlayStation Move and Xbox Connect.
It was that wave of motion controlled video game systems.
I bought it for the Wii.
I didn't like it right away.
I think I never played it.
Yeah.
What I bought, which I showed you guys the last time we zoomed was like I got this like plug and play thing.
Where it's like it's a physical cannon that you plug into.
The TV and then it has just this game loaded on it.
So it's a sort of lower res and the cannon is push button rather than the ball pull.
I thought by buying that and prepping for like six months before this episode, I'd get very good at it.
When you're there in person.
Didn't happen.
The thing is like I played that app for a long time until they just continued.
I have this thing now I play.
I remember being bummed out when they did that because I was like, well, that kind of devalues the ride.
If you're just taking the exact same game screens and like making it playable at home, then what's the ride got?
And then every time I go on the ride, I'm like, this is so much better.
It really just speaks to how the whole interface is the whole is the thing.
Yes.
It's not the graphics and anything.
It's just how they made it perfect.
Let's also call it out.
It's a 3D movie.
It's my favorite kind of thing a theme park can do.
It's a series of 3D movies, a thing that the at home versions never can get.
Right. I can't get it right.
Yeah.
Well, and you're not, you know, we haven't talked about Jason nodded to it very quickly, but the effects, the effects are something when those aliens fly around and there's a little blast, it's mainly blasts.
There's not a lot of like there's not too much going on.
There's surprises, but they're cool.
Yeah.
There's like, is there confetti or something that shoots or the balls like shoot out at you and it makes that like poof sound and then like you get a blast of air.
And it makes it all like more confusing.
There's like there's sometimes when you're playing, you get blasted with air.
That's like part of the all kinds of shit ends up breaking your face.
Right.
It happens.
Yeah.
We hadn't mentioned the cues.
There's a lot of weird stuff.
The cues in both California and Florida have both been reconfigured at different points due to changing of the areas they're in.
Well, because Orlando is now the weird fake Pixar campus.
Well, no, that's what it was now.
Not anymore.
Now it's Toy Story land.
Toy Story land.
Right.
They flipped it.
They never moved the building, but they put the entrance on the other side.
It's really odd.
I had not gone to do Toy Story land yet.
And they added a third track in Florida because it's just so popular.
Yeah.
DCA California Adventures cue is pretty bad.
That's one of the big open criticisms of the ride.
Love skipping that one in the Max Pass era.
But the potato head is all you got going for.
I mean, the potato head really elevates it.
The potato head can talk to you.
Florida has a lot more character to it.
I think Florida does more of trying to sell you on the like, here's the room.
Here's like this box he got constructed.
And like the giant viewfinder, like the Disneyland.
Tomorrowland.
Yeah.
Giant viewfinder things.
And then in Japan, two things.
Oh, yeah.
You got to say it.
You enter through a giant Woody head.
It's so cool.
It's a dream I've always had.
Put myself in Woody's mouth.
Oh, perfect.
I'm going in.
This area in Japan is called, I almost missed this, it's called the Toyville Trolley Park.
And we all know I love my trolley parks.
Yeah, that's cool.
It looks really neat.
It's a great design.
It looks very ornate, as is all of Tokyo DisneySea.
Looks amazing at night.
Yes.
But this is like, you'll see this repeated.
This is a big Japan travel tip that if you've ever done Toy Story Mania at Disneyland or Disney World,
you can't do it in Japan.
That will eat into valuable time.
It is like the one thing that is exactly the same.
Go look at the outside.
The outside is great.
But I saw travel guides that were very clear about, you've got to sacrifice that one
because there's so much that's unique to that park.
Or maybe you have to add an extra day.
You still have to have an ad.
You need to take it up to four days or beyond.
Just to be able to go seven days, you need seven.
You need seven.
I think you need a clean seven.
Full seven.
You just keep moving up.
It's going to be 12 before you know it.
Yeah, I mean, I'll say in defense, because the California one opened first, right?
It is the original.
Maybe not.
No.
No?
Really?
Opened.
This was a rare instance where they were developing both simultaneously.
Florida opens a few weeks before California.
I believe Florida's also was timed with a piece being added to the International Space Station.
And there was a Buzz Lightyear toy.
Yes.
In the imaginary story.
Right.
They put Buzz in space.
Yeah.
It's all strange that that opened first and how it's like it's this midway game ride.
But then they it's so it's midway mania in California.
But because it's part of the pier, but then it's just Toy Story mania everywhere else.
I remember thinking when I heard all this before it opened, I was like, is this going to be any?
It's weird.
It's midway games, but it's over there.
And is that just like plugging it in in a non-natural way?
And it's all like the odd.
Just something about the description of the ride.
Never sounded that great to me.
It's like games with it.
And then like immediately, first time you're on it.
Yeah.
Just fun classic like must do.
Defies logic, but it gets back to sort of the stuff we've been saying about just like
sort of don't overthink it.
Do the thing that's fun.
Show the people the thing they want to see.
You know, just make it clean and easy.
The rules.
Yeah.
Don't get in.
Don't get in your head.
Yeah.
Try to relax.
Simple.
Right.
If you're worrying too much about what, how other people think you're doing.
But you do.
You're not going to enjoy yourself because ultimately like you need to be enjoying yourself.
Right.
But also you want to make sure they're having a good time.
You have to do that.
Just not worrying about how they think you're performing.
Just worry about trying your hardest.
Yeah.
You know, you can't get too, you can't overthink it.
No.
Because there's this.
Yeah.
I mean, you have to be attentive.
Sometimes the rules change.
Sometimes they say throw this and then you move over a little bit and they go,
actually, you know, spin this or whatever.
I don't know.
I don't even have to sustain this anymore.
It's unsustainable at this juncture.
Things are at a different angle.
You know, but we're looking like with Mike and I just like worked really well when it was
pleasurable for both of us.
We made, we made each other better.
Right.
Exactly.
Yeah.
We were work, Scott and I were working together to achieve a goal.
Jason and I were perhaps being selfish.
What?
I say mutual midway.
That's it.
Griffin Newman, you survived.
I guess the right.
Well, I do.
I do have a thing I want to say.
I know.
I sure know that was just like be planning the flag.
No, I understand.
Come back to the station.
Right.
Uh, I, so I, you know, I, uh, this was so much fun to get to go to the parks with you guys.
And I joked about this when I was, uh, when I got there, but I was like, I was like having
the jitters beforehand of like, oh my God, I'm going to meet the guys for the first time
because it did feel like, I think people don't know this, but like up until going to the parks
together two days ago, we had never hung out outside of recording.
Cause all the good records are all, it's all these long episodes.
We all go like, and so then by the time you're done, it's like, yeah, we could go like get
dinners up some of it.
Like you're in town for a brief amount of time.
But I like message you guys.
I was like, I'd love to be on the show.
Then we did that.
We always like end up, uh, talking for too long before and after the record and turning
what's already a long session into a super long session planning a thing.
Yeah.
Then that after show just happened.
And then like the last time we recorded before the pandemic, you were like, by the way, next
time we should just make plans to hang out.
Like this doesn't have to be the only structure in which for us to hang out.
Then the world ended and it was very much a thing I was looking forward to is being able
to record with you guys again, but also being able to, uh, uh, you know, actually like hanging
out and then cross that friend threshold and whatever.
And to go to the parks with you guys was like the best version of that.
I didn't realize the three of you hadn't gone together.
So it was nice that I was able to.
In a while.
Yeah.
This was a big impetus for that.
I have the fits.
It was 20 months is what it ended up being.
Yeah.
Right.
We had seen you in person.
I feel I started with you in person was almost two years ago.
Yeah.
That's right.
The last time I was here was October, 2019 and it's now September, 2021.
Wow.
Yeah.
So like all these things I was looking forward to and you know, like, uh, listening to the
show was, was a thing that really helped my, my sanity throughout all of this, you know?
So I'm very appreciative, uh, to you guys, uh, as friends, but also just as, uh, uh,
people who make a good thing that, that helps people a lot.
But, um, I, I, I did in, in the run of listening to the show.
And as I said, I was listening some months behind go like, I want to do something to
repay the favor to the boys to some degree.
I feel like I, I, I need to, I'm just,
I have such an affinity.
I'm so excited to see them again in person and do all of this.
I need to, I need to come bearing gifts to some degree.
And then I, I caught up with some episodes and I got very worried that I perhaps had been, um,
sniped in what my potential gift was.
Oh, that's what's in your case.
I brought a secret to your rifle.
Yes.
That is perfectly sized just for this one thing.
It kills us.
And I had to message Jason and go, here's my gift.
Eat lead.
I've got the specter spirit now.
Um, a couple of weeks ago, uh, I, when we had these plans in place, I messaged Jason.
I said, Jason, like no spoilers.
I'm still catching up, but I might've ordered something and spent a fair amount of money on
it.
And I'm worried that perhaps this has already been purchased in exchange.
And I want to know if this ever happened.
And he said, I think you're in the clear.
Yeah.
This was maybe the most memory workout I had to do.
At one point in the park, Scott went to the bathroom.
He went, remind me what the thing is.
I, well, I messaged Mike about it.
Okay.
I know.
I remember you did ask me.
Yeah.
Right.
Oh, interesting.
Because, uh, I didn't, I, I had purchased this and received it before I caught up to
the point where it was invoked on the show, but I did in fact purchase a big,
he'd be alive.
Aladar.
Whoa.
I want to make clear was specifically purchased for Scott Gardner.
This is not for Mike.
This is for you and your son.
All right.
You have to accept this.
Okay.
Let me get a closer look.
In your garage.
That is for you.
It's a mint condition.
Oh boy.
Dino Alive.
Oh, these beautiful fonts.
It's great fonts.
The best of 2000.
It's a good box.
It's a very good.
Help me hatch.
Let me out.
Hatch and hatch again.
Feed me in quotes.
Feed me and I'll show what I can do.
Dirtiest episode.
Grossest episode.
Yeah, really gross.
It was gross enough before Aladar entered the picture.
And now Aladar's here.
And he's here to stay.
Hatch your prehistoric pet again and again.
Wow.
You can go, that's the miracle of childbirth over and over again.
He comes with the egg.
For the listener at home, he comes with the egg and you can have him hatch out of the egg.
This is going to be a great sex ed tool.
You know, teaching tool.
Your wife.
Yeah.
My son.
Exactly.
This is where babies come from.
Yeah.
So one day you came out of an egg and the first thing you did was pee and burp and I
thought it was so cute.
Very cute.
Very cute, yes.
And then on the back of these quotes, I'm Aladar, I'm hungry, burp, let's go.
Can you imagine?
Let's go.
What's the thing he says in the, stand together.
I think that's the actual.
But that's adult Aladar.
You do not own adult Aladar.
No, that's baby Aladar.
You own Dino Alive baby Aladar.
Oh my God.
Dino Alive.
He walks, he talks, he's amazing.
I will say.
I'd have to agree.
I ordered this, it took a while to come.
It thankfully didn't get lost like the one that you ordered for Mike.
But when it arrived, I like didn't know what it was and it was such a big box.
Do I have this here?
Hold on.
I thought I took a picture of it.
Was that your carry on luggage that backhoe in the overhead?
This was essentially a bag I brought just to carry baby Aladar.
Oh my God.
You see you carry the precious egg like a movie character cross country.
You had to protect an egg.
You were a father or bringing, you were a makeshift father,
bringing Aladar to his real father me.
Yes.
A lot.
It felt like the journey, the beginning of Disney's dinosaur,
where you're seeing the egg getting carried by all these different creatures.
Clive Owen and children of men getting her.
Absolutely.
People dying all around you.
I can't find the picture of this now, but it arrived in this like huge box.
And by pure coincidence, I couldn't tell if it was like a joke from the eBay
seller, but I think it was pure coincidence that it showed up in a box that had like
a big stamped warning of like careful live eggs handle with care.
Wow.
That's great.
They just reuse some.
Egg delivery box.
They were just being cute.
I don't know.
No, because it was like it was like stamped on there.
It wasn't like handwritten.
Oh, but like they may, but they still may have.
Might have.
The box for that branded.
No, no, it wasn't.
No, I see.
No, that was just the shipping container.
Got you.
It was not part of the product.
They were still being cute then.
And also, by the way, just there's so much disturbing on the box.
You never know what it'll do next.
There's a lot of every time going on with the box.
And then the more you feed him, the more real he becomes.
Just everything about it.
But then there's this little thing in the corner that says, try me.
And it's a hand that's putting up two fingers.
And under that, it says, touch the metal contacts.
I touch them.
Oh, wait, I should touch the metal.
Wait, what happens?
I think the batteries are dead.
That's OK.
Yeah, yeah.
It's probably an ancient enough.
Yeah.
This little diagram of the finger, more weird, lewd finger gestures.
So many lewd fingers in this episode.
Just put your fingers in, but then sort of curl them up
until you feel the contact point.
And you'll know when you feel it.
You'll know when you feel it.
There'll be no mistaking.
Griff, amazing.
Thank you so much for guiding baby Aladar's journey across the country.
I mean, I had to rethink my packing.
Wow.
That thing made a cross-country trip.
This is heavy.
Also, you're on foot going into a train station.
Train station, I believe.
Correct.
I took a cross-country train from New York.
This had to be accounted for.
It made it here.
I've got to cross two hotels and brought it here today
to its rightful place in this garage.
Strangers on a train remake.
And the guy's going like, hey, man, is that a fucking Disney dinosaur toy?
Is that Dino Alive baby Aladar in mint condition?
I was going to ask you to kill a family member of mine,
but you're too weird for me now.
Oh, man, wow.
It's amazing.
The miracle of life comes from making contact with the egg.
I feel so much life from this.
Maybe I love baby Aladar now.
I mean.
After all this.
It took this gesture.
Now you have to care for him.
It's hard not to form an emotional attachment when he's your responsibility.
You can't shut me off.
I have no opposition.
We between the lines, Scott, this thing is cursed.
Well, the last time we may have heard, we got to a baby Aladar toy that never made it.
It didn't have it still.
This is why I messaged Jason in a panic because I ordered this.
It arrived.
Then I got to the episode where you revealed that you had ordered it for Mike,
but it had been delayed.
And I was like, if I just spent all this fucking money.
It's the fact that this cost a substantial amount.
Right.
We had a list.
I didn't show that for the egg.
You show that for the egg.
The egg, the box, all that.
The listener told us, though, they had the same exact story where they tried to get rid
of the baby Aladar toy and it kept coming back.
Yeah, it kept coming back and they couldn't get the batteries out.
I think and the batteries had enough juice that every few months it would just go like
without warning.
I am remembering again, because memory little fuzzy at the moment.
I remember I think just recently I double checked with Scott because I convinced myself that like
de Griffin by a Nimgaloo and I asked you like, hey, the stuff Nimgaloo is covered in bugs and
you threw it in the trash, right?
And you were like, yeah, yeah.
That was you.
You put that in.
You couldn't remember if I had bought a Nimgaloo or an Aladar.
You knew both items had trouble arriving, but you could remember which one I had got.
This point that we're at, what we mythologize.
I'm going to open this thing up and it's going to say, I'm the one you tried to buy for Mike.
I got into all the packaging, made it through the plastic.
But there was also a point where I was like, if the one for Mike arrives and Mike gets it,
and then I bring one for Scott as a punishment, then I feel like an asshole that Jason doesn't have.
A punishment Aladar?
That's all right.
I think we all need to end up with one.
I'm just letting you guys have fun.
I'm just trying.
Everyone's having a good time.
One is going to burrow out from inside your stomach tonight.
This gift is so...
I have gifts for everybody too.
This gift is so much better.
I just brought little gifts real quick for everybody because I want to throw...
It's nothing big.
They have these 50th anniversary McDonald's toys celebrating Disney World.
And I went and got a few of them.
This one's for Griffin.
This is R2-D2.
I was hoping for Toy Story, but it did not happen.
Scott, I have here Lumiere for you.
Wonderful.
50th anniversary.
And then for Jason, I have a Walmart exclusive Funko pop of the Moon Pie Mastop.
Yeah!
All right!
I didn't know that mid-September was suddenly Christmas.
When did this change?
Mid-September.
I think this is 2020 Christmas.
I haven't felt like we've...
I think we made up for it today and now out of nowhere.
I had something for Mike and Scott I brought back from New Jersey that I forgot today.
And Griffin, I real quick bought you a pretzel at DCA because I was like,
oh no, if I bring that, I won't have anything for Griffin.
Well, because I asked you, do you want to split a pretzel?
Because we were debating how hungry we were.
And then the next thing I knew, you handed me a whole pretzel.
I...
I couldn't figure out what the mech-a-nation was.
The short-term memory and the long-term memory are both a little fuzzy right now.
I'm with you.
I'm right there.
I forgot you had said that.
Well, we didn't even get into the cheese thing.
No, but that's its own episode.
That's its own episode.
Jason's Cheese Polly's.
Not to tease the title.
Bummed out by the plastic cheese situation.
Mike, thank you for these good new anniversary toys.
Thank you for this egg.
Thank you for delivering the egg across the nation.
It already looks like right at home.
It looks like it always belonged right where you put it.
Underneath an out of time license plate.
It made of...
A bunch of visors.
Yeah, I do have a bunch of visors hung up in my garage.
Sports Almanac from BTTF2.
Anyway, yeah.
Thank you for that.
Thank you for being here, for getting us back to Disneyland, for a great hang the other day,
a great episode now, many great episodes.
Truly a thing I've been looking forward to as like,
oh, then I'll feel like the world is slightly normal again.
This is a great thing, great light at the end of the tunnel of all of that waiting.
I'm so happy we actually got to hang in the happiest place on earth.
Such a blast.
Let's exit through the gift shop.
Is there anything you'd like to plug?
I'd like to plug Mattel's Dino Alive Baby Aladar.
It's a great product.
More and more Dino Alives?
Yeah.
Mike, you buy a lot of vintage toys as well.
I kind of can't believe what good condition the packaging is in for this thing.
Yeah, sometimes.
Well, I just I revealed to you two days ago whenever we were there that I had bought some
Austin Powers McFarland toys that are 20 years old and I am like, well, these are like in pristine.
People just might just have them in the box.
Original shipping box.
Preserved.
Yeah, I am impressed sometimes.
Yeah, but yeah, look for them on eBay.
Blank check with Griffin and David where our podcasters found we're doing all the
John Carpenter movies that's taken us through the rest of the year.
And then Good Boys in 2022.
2022.
Would love to.
Yeah, and watch Masters of the Universe Revelation, a very uncontroversial show
that no one is upset about online.
I've had really, really normal reactions to.
I think it's really good.
Maybe even more so if you haven't watched the old show, then maybe you like it a lot
because you're not going to feel a lot of strange baggage.
But yeah, first five episodes of that are up now and the remaining five episodes will be up soon.
I think you got a gun to voice of Aladar next for the Dinosaur reboot.
God.
That's the next one to.
Yeah.
But people, I mean, people online are going to be upset if Baby Aladar doesn't look exactly
as cute as he did 30 years ago in the old movie.
If Baby Aladar is a little too woke now.
If Baby Aladar is woke in a new version of Dinosaur, yeah,
there's going to be a lot of people online upset.
There's an agenda behind his burping now.
They don't even let him pee anymore.
Like that's his thing.
Hey, find us on all the socials at Podcasts to Ride.
Merch is available in our Tee Public store for three bonus episodes every month.
Check out podcast the second gate of Patreon dot com slash podcast the ride.
Great.
Victorious week, victorious episode.
I feel like we feel like we all got the beaver today.
Oh, tonight.
I'm not going to say anything else.
It's all right.
So bye.
Goodbye.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson,
Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.