Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following haunt cast contains expert sniveling, crying for mommy, a ghastly
podcast topic mistake rectified, and a terrifying debate over how important it is to wait in
line.
All this plus, Lindsay Katai returns to talk Tower of Terror at Tokyo DisneySea on today's
most fiendishly fun haunt cast, The Fright.
Welcome to Haunt Cast The Fright.
You know, in the future, a Los Angeles Preservation Society will show off this very garage and
tell the people that three little theme park boys talked about CEOs and made for cable
movies.
My name is Mike Carlson, joining me as always, Jason Sheridan.
That is, will be the most notable episode.
Maybe the only one that survives, you know.
Yeah, you mean the Jay Leno?
Yeah, yeah.
Through the passage of time and as history moves on, a lot gets lost, you know.
But I like to think we talk about made for cable movies and Jay Leno on almost every
podcast, so it really doesn't break it down that much.
Yeah, no, that's fair.
A tiny amount.
Yeah.
Every, before there was the full episode.
Scott Garner here as well.
Yeah.
Could I just, if any of this is going to be preserved by historical society, can I maybe
try to wriggle out of the phrase little theme park boys?
Could I request that there be a rewrite on that?
Wow, that's just something a little theme park boy would do.
Wiggle out.
Yeah.
That is true.
Jason's right.
If you hadn't said wiggle.
Oh no, I said wriggle.
Oh, I don't.
I'm so wriggled.
Damn it.
I'm so damn it.
I'm so wriggled.
Any kind of, any kind ofiggling to get out of a situation sounds like a little theme
park boy to me.
Eagle is a theme park boy thing.
Little Figgle Diggle.
Can I Figgle Diggle my way out of being called a theme park boy?
That is how people hear us, I think.
They hear that voice.
Welcome to Podcasts Alright, hosted by me, Mike Carson.
In our minds we're like, hello there, this is Podcasts Alright here.
Michael Iser was a pretty good CEO, was he not, Jason?
That's right, Michael.
Let's talk about throughput per hour.
How many guests are hitting up that bad boy every hour?
Meanwhile.
Let's take a few calls.
All the listeners at home are just hearing like, I liked it when the big ride waited
for us.
And when people are saying, this is podcast I listened to, and they were talking about
Disney World's anniversary and they made a good point of it.
It was a swamp, it was a swamp before the wise were there.
Anyway, so I like it.
I subscribe for info like that.
Yeah.
Oh man, that is really, we are really realizing something.
It's a revelation, honestly.
I'm sorry, I didn't know you guys didn't know.
I guess we did.
I was a joke.
I was making a joke, I thought.
No, that's true.
That's how we sound.
That voice of course is the Lily monster to my Herman because it's haunt cast the fright.
Lindsay Katai, she's here.
Hello, I'm here.
Hi.
Last time I called you, what's Mary Steenburgen?
Sarah something?
Well, I said I was a Walmarten.
The Clifford?
Oh, okay.
Yeah, I was the, what's her face to your who's its butt?
Shoot.
Oh well.
Now it looks like I'm not a huge Clifford guy.
Well, I know that you're, there's no question that you're a huge monsters guy because I
was just re-listening to an episode from a couple weeks ago where I realized it's a recurring
thing.
I think it's happened more than once where I have said I've made a reference to the monsters
car and then you're like, Dracula, yes.
Yeah, Dracula is a Dracula.
Yes.
Let that moment pass.
The people must know.
Does not surprise.
It's a Dracula.
It's not a regular car.
Excuse me, the car, is that called the Dracula?
Sarah Davis.
Yeah, this is, this is what Lindsay hears.
Lindsay probably hears the word Dracula once a week.
Probably.
I mean, I for sure hear the word monsters multiple times a week.
Dracula I feel like because I'm not personally bringing up the car, Dracula very much.
Well, you're trying to get away from the monsters topic in general.
You're just like, it'll pass.
It'll pass.
Literally running.
Like in another storm in Orlando, you're like, if I just keep my head down, it'll just
roll over me.
I'm just going to let myself get soaked because it's inevitable.
Won't do too much damage.
Are there, is, are there any like recent Mike viewing trends, especially forced viewing
trends upon you that we don't know about?
Gosh, aren't there?
That's very on the spot.
I know.
And I don't think he would hide anything, but.
No, no, he would never.
He's nothing if not honest.
You hear this?
It's like a house full of Jack Benny.
This I understand.
Well, we had talked about.
We do watch Jack Benny occasionally.
We do.
Yeah.
Because we were talking about late shift, you know, you know, some men always have the
TV on and the sport game on, but that's not what, you know, Scott and I roll necessarily.
Actually I, I, um, this is sadly topical.
Not too long ago.
I think maybe the most recent time I was like, yes, I, you have shown that to me.
Thank you.
Was, um, Norm McDonald on comedians in cars getting coffee.
The Kojak story.
Yes.
There's a norm reciting a Kojak, like a scene from the Kojak pilot, which I think is funny.
And which is very funny.
And you've shown it to me before, but you were like, then like just repeating the entire
bit to me.
I remember that.
But then you just like kept going.
Even though I had said, I remember it.
Yeah.
You pretty much recited don't blame Conan in the late shift episode.
Oh yeah.
We're all like, yeah, I've seen it.
Well, so anyway, so what happens is.
But the listeners might not know.
And they wouldn't want to just look it up.
Oh, well, certainly.
Actually, he was just telling me about that because I didn't know about that.
She actually didn't know don't blame Conan, which is.
I did not know.
When there's something I know and I, she doesn't know, boy, is the party starting.
Boy, is that fun.
I look, I am the same way.
Yes, it is the it's the like it is a big green light.
If I ask Aaron, have you heard of this?
And she says no.
Well, that means let me let me set the table.
Let me put my bib on my bib in.
Michael is eating tonight.
Sharing things.
And I don't want to like well, there's a lot to get to in the episode, I'm sure.
But just in case this is a 20 minute tangent, the I just like the right before
we started recording, Jason was talking about a new Epcot lounge in which you can
get free cans of seltzer.
And Mike's response was really.
That was that's a little taste of for the episode.
Yeah, that's the that's that's again, that's the man talk that happened sort of off Mike.
So do you say I was real impressed with that because we you know, we were talking
about the Magic Key Lounge, which sounds like it's unimpressive because I haven't
been yet.
But then I hear there's a free you get a free can at Disney.
At the Blue Cross Blue Shield Lounge.
Blue. Yeah, Blue Shield of Florida or something.
I yeah, in the Norway Pavilion.
You need to go to a website.
Yes, in the Norway Pavilion, because the restaurant that I think for some reason
you know, why are these affiliated Norway and Blue Cross?
Well, health care.
They just had an empty room, let's be honest.
Well, it is because they haven't done like face character,
maskless face character, like meals, character meals have not come back.
Like that's where the princess dining.
Oh, so they have that empty room.
So they have an empty room.
And apparently you can pick one beverage and two snacks.
And so there's a variety of beverages, hummus and yogurt.
Wow. So that's pass holder only.
No, you just have to get I the the Disney Tours blog had the full rundown on it
and a link to the pass and insurance has to approve it.
I know what privatized health care is good.
Yeah, I didn't like it till right now.
That does seem well, yeah, if you're there, I mean, tweet us a photo if you go to this lounge.
Yeah, if you make it to the lounge and Club Cool's back open to.
So you can really hit out, get some freebies that Epcot right now.
Beverly is back.
Beverly flavor soda at Club Cool is back.
Drinkable sodas. Yeah.
So there's a lot of exciting stuff for someone to say exclaim wow at
or get very excited.
Really? Really?
Whatever I say, there's a new Beverly.
Oh, yeah, the new Beverly.
You mean are these soda like what's the new bad soda?
I'm sure someone listening doesn't know what Beverly is.
People listen to this podcast don't know what Beverly is.
Well, I didn't know it, but that's I guess common.
That's constantly like, what's that? You don't know that.
You don't know Beverly?
Because I just learned this.
Like you don't really like weird.
That's the this bad soda.
This soda dispensing place, free soda.
And it spits it out right away.
Yeah, gross.
But from around the world.
No memory of what Beverly tastes like.
It's an aperitif.
It's a non alcoholic aperitif is what it's labeled as.
And it's like just a very bitter soda.
But it's a it's a new version of it.
Is that what people are saying?
It's a new bad soda. Right.
That is like, oh, that's that's the new Beverly.
That is bad.
And Beverly is also back.
But there's a new soda.
There's one worse calling the new Beverly. Right. Right. Right.
Is it the sour plum one from China? Might be.
OK, might be, because I know our boy, Mr.
Mara, that is like it.
Yes, that is our new.
That is the thing we got our newest shared thing.
We on board is that we love watching YouTube.
Mr. Morrow and he goes to Mr.
Paging Mr. Morrow, which is the YouTube play on words
from the Tomorrowland people over.
Yeah. So we watch him a lot.
And he's the most positive guy and tries every food.
He's in the park just seemingly five days a week.
Always walking around the Disney World part.
You guys explained this all to me.
And you told me that there are episodes where
some of the highlights that happened to this guy are
one time he lost his hat on the Tower of Terror.
Yes. Tower of Terror. Oh, yes. Oh, hey, bro.
I forgot there was a topic.
And one time a bee got in his pocket.
And then you sent me a video.
And I think we were all surprised to learn same day.
Same same episode. All killer, no filler.
Yes. I think perhaps also in that episode is when he delights
in goofy, sprunging his whiskers.
Yeah. Or goofy or Pluto was it? Oh, Pluto.
I think it was Pluto. Yeah, definitely.
That's one of my favorite episodes.
There's a lot going on in that one.
And all of a sudden he's like, I have a bee in my pocket.
And he's like, it's like a real it may as well be Tom Cruise
flying that helicopter through the mountains
when you compare it to what happens on a normal, very serene
episode of Paging Mr.
Morrow. But we love watching his videos.
And yeah, so that's that's the biggest sharing TV show
I think we have right now.
That's what we're watching.
Yeah. A man who lost his hat and had a run in with a bee.
It's so calming.
He's honestly a delight.
He's he is a delight.
He just seems like a very nice man enjoying Disney parks.
He's none of the cynicism jokes that we try to do.
Yeah, I got enough of that from me.
Yeah. I hear he has a pure love.
It's like Duffy and Shelley May's love.
It's pure. He's pure.
I just pulled up his channel and I realized Jane and I also watch this guy.
So you didn't know how we are.
How we not talked about this?
Yeah, he's the best.
She was a lot and I catch it sometimes.
Well, you got to see the one with the bee, Jason.
Yeah, look, it's that's like the breaking bad with Hank in the parking lot
and the twins. That's like what's going to happen with this bee.
And there's a cliffhanger with the hat.
You don't know if he gets his hat back.
But spoiler alert, he does get it back. Oh, good.
So, yes, if you like a peaceful days later, I think so.
Yeah, they had the like the right to be shut down episode.
So I think that's a common practice on most rides where like once
it shut down, they can go through and get all the different hats
on Tower of Terror. So he's lost a few hats, though.
Yes. It's going to happen.
You're destined to be you're going to be friends with Mr.
Morrow as soon as this episode comes out.
I think I think we've been on a defunct land charity stream
with on the same bill as him before.
I didn't even realize it.
So we have we've been on the same bill, which is like marquee.
We have like our our.
Oh, man, this is like love and the doors together.
It was like Woodstock. Yeah, yeah.
I was like, if I was rich, I would fly Mr.
Morrow out here just to go to Disneyland with him.
Yeah. So one, that's the dream one of these days.
But it is like our degrees of separation, our Kevin Bacon game.
You know, if you're doing your theme park media, Kevin Bacon,
you know how many degrees we were like one.
It's not. Yeah, I was going to say it's sort of weird to even talk about it
on this podcast because of how quickly this may get to him. Sure.
Yeah. But we are legit fans.
But yeah, true fans. Yeah.
So yeah, that's that's our theme park things that we that we share lately.
I fucking cried watching his video talking about why he vlogs
and his vlogging journey. Mm hmm. Yeah.
So episode vocabulary so far, Beverly, Dragula, Paging Mr.
Morrow. So just like we'll just have a glossary.
We've done add anything else to the list that you the listener need to look up.
14 minutes, no topic. Real mention yet.
That's pretty good. So, yeah, you have a lot of.
Well, that's what the warnings are for. Of course.
We so that we have said it technically.
Yes. Is part of it.
And it's been said, but there's still another
perhaps brief tangent that needs to occur because we're talking about
the Tower of Terror, the Tokyo version specifically,
which is not the Twilight Zone.
It is certainly not Guardians Mission Breakout.
It's its own wonderful thing.
And I'm excited to talk about it.
But part of why we're doing this now and this year and with Lindsay is that
there was a problem last year.
Yes, yes, yes.
It was so mean, seemingly like well in the past,
you had requested to do the Twilight Zone Tower of Terror.
This is before Mr. Morrow lost his hat on it.
You were passionate about it for other reasons.
Somehow, for many other reasons.
Well, I'm a huge Twilight Zone fan. Mm hmm.
And the first time I went on Tower of Terror,
I went when I was 14 with friends and had a nervous breakdown on it.
Oh, jeez. Which is extremely embarrassing.
To what degree? What's the thing that happened?
Screaming for my mom.
She's there in the state or.
No. OK. No.
This was in Florida in 1996.
My mother was in San Diego.
This was a school trip.
I was with my peers, was so sure that my soul was about to be stolen out of my body
that I truly had a nervous breakdown and began to scream.
Wait, I'm sorry. You were.
Irrationally, you were.
It was not so much about the the the ride up and down, but more about
you thought that your soul was going to like a real problem
with the supernatural as a child.
Oh, whoa. Yeah. Wow.
Truly, I would have panic attacks after I saw it.
I wouldn't shower without somebody else in the room for three years.
For three years. Mm hmm.
Oh, my God. From the ages of 10 to 13.
So somebody had to just like just like chill in the bathroom.
Sit on the toilet.
I would literally have a panic attack.
Wow. Like couldn't breathe, couldn't stay in the shower,
would like start crying.
I was deathly afraid of showers after I saw the original psycho
and would like double check to make sure the bathroom door was locked
and like peek out for like.
Yeah. And this went on for a while.
What do you think age wise? Huh?
Well, what age do you think it's 12?
Stopped at 12, 12, 13.
Well, that's about when I saw it.
Oh, it started then. Yeah, it started.
Oh, OK. Yeah.
OK. Well, that's not because, yeah, you were what, like 14, did you say?
I was well, when I was afraid of it and somebody had to just like
hang out and read it in the bathroom while I showered,
I was like 10 to 13.
And the Tower of Terror, though, was.
Tower of Terror. I was 14.
OK. Too old. Sure.
Yeah, yeah. Too old to be happening.
I'm sure I have something like that, though,
but I can't think of it off the top of my head.
Look, I was afraid of the ride.
I was afraid of going on the ride. Sure. What it did.
I think the fact that you bought into the story is.
Against my will.
It was like, I know that I'm fine.
It's fine. And then, yet somehow the ride started
and I started to scream for my mom.
I want off this ride.
I want my mom fully screaming, crying.
And then it and then the ride happened and I was
and we get off the ride and I was like, that was so fun.
Let's go again, everyone. I'm normal. Everything's fine.
Wow. One of my favorite rides.
Still in the range to play it cool. One of my favorite rides.
Yeah. Hey, we're all still going to talk to me in San Diego, right?
Yeah. You guys are going to commend me for my emotional vulnerability.
Right. Yeah.
We're definitely doing that, right.
As 14 year olds in 1996.
This is a conversation that's been had and we're cool with. No.
Did you go on again that trip or no?
Do you remember? I don't remember.
I know I genuinely did want to because I thought it was fun.
I've never really been afraid of roller coasters
except for kind of later in life when sometimes I'll get afraid
that I'm having a premonition.
Oh, well, that's that has really been terrifying for me
because we'll be like on a credit coaster and you'll just turn to me and go,
I just want you to know I love you.
What? And I'll go, what?
She's done this multiple times.
And I go, I go, that's not the way to start.
Then like five, four, three, two, one.
And I go, no, what?
Yes, like very seriously put a hand on his knee or shoulder.
Like the end of a movie.
Hold eye contact and just say, I want you to know that I love you.
Like it's Armageddon or like the movie Armageddon or something.
The plane that you know is going down.
Yes. That's not what I want to hear on the start of a thrill ride.
No. And I don't blame you, but I can't stop myself.
This is also the plot of that final destination that we talked about.
The one character has the premonition
the roller coaster is going to go off the tracks and it does.
And then what if it does and I didn't say I love you?
Well, I guess what I would I be?
What I heard there was probably a pretty fresh
I love you in the last so many hours, right?
No, let's say if you have a premonition, you got to say it.
And I guess that's fair.
But if those are the rules of psychic premonitions
that have absolutely never come true.
But if there was a fresh how fresh is and I love you is in the last 24 hours
considered it's fresh for like a situation like that or it has to be right before.
I guess if I'm going off Lindsey's roots, it's like when you have the
because the premonition hasn't been had.
Uh huh.
You guys come right off of it.
All emotional logic.
Right. You had the fear that you're about to die.
You should say I love you.
I mean, I get I get it.
I understand. Does this make sense?
No, absolutely not.
But there is it.
Does it make emotional sense to my the like
most intensely afraid part of my brain? Yes.
I'll say this. It gives another dimension to the Incredicoaster
because I'm like, is Mr.
Incredible's like static figure going to fall on me?
Is he going to be reaching for the cookie?
But like his arm falls off and cuts my head off.
Like what could happen?
There's real fire in the fire part.
Yeah. Real ice in the ice part.
Right. Jack Jack.
Like I get blown up like Jack Jack.
I turn into a giant and then I get a helicopter.
Hits me in the head.
Which was my my fear at 14 that Tower of Terror was real.
So, yeah, you might.
So the story of the ride is what's going to get you.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
That's you're right. It's not it's a narrative.
It's not a ride accident. Yeah.
Well, with the within credit coaster, any time now that I've become afraid
of a roller coaster ride, it has been a much more like physical.
I'm afraid I'm going to die on this ride.
But at that incident was pure.
I think this ride might literally be cursed
and I'm not able to silence the fight or flight part of my brain that thinks this.
Well, my my question is, because I think it is a little in question
in in both the Twilight Zone version and the Tokyo version.
What happens to the characters?
It's something about you, right?
They're like souls getting trapped or getting.
I well, I was going to say getting disintegrated.
I don't think I don't know if that's true.
Like, did you what do you did you have a visualization?
Because I might not figure out what happens to these characters.
Oh, that I'd get trapped in the right.
Just like they got trapped in there.
Their spirits get trapped in the elevator to relive the moment over and over.
Like they're stuck in this purgatory.
That's with Harrison Hightower in this ride.
It seems to be like the moment that he fell.
Yeah. And it was cursed by the idol.
So so you think that over and over keep happening to you.
That I would just like live in the ride forever.
And they would add there's the movie star and the little girl and then
1996 era Lindsay.
Yes. And then
height of her depression and insanity, Lindsay Keite.
Wow. You just be added to the ride wearing like what clothes?
Oh, I read Honey, I shrunk the audience shirt
that I bought on that trip.
Oh, excellent.
I don't want to unlock this door with the key of imagination.
So I had said, oh, I want to do that episode.
But and that was early on. Yes.
And I completely in a haze of month, what?
Nine or eight of the pandemic, just like not even in my brain.
Yeah. Totally. And then I was like, you're like, oh, what episode?
Because then you were down in sand.
You were actually visiting your mother and you're like, what episode?
You're like, oh, Tower of Terror.
And you're like, hey.
And I was like, what?
Wasn't it on a zoom with all of us?
Well, Jason's birthday.
I one year ago, literally a year ago.
Every day. Oh, yes.
Yes. And I realized on the zoom and I got very sad.
Yeah. And I got legit sad that you were actually like
how you felt.
Lindsay was roasting me and to be funny into it.
And I could take a roast normally, but for whatever reason,
I was just extra sad that day.
I was feeling really sad.
Very sad. Yeah. Yeah.
It was much sadder in general.
Yeah. Going into like week three or
visiting my mom. You were there for a while.
I was alone and I totally blanked out.
And then you were roasting me, which was, I'm sure funny.
And then you were like texting me and I'm like,
I'm feeling very sad right now. I'm sorry.
So then I felt.
Then I felt bad because I was like, oh, man,
now I'm making you feel bad for scoring innocent points on me.
Like there was nothing like nefarious about it.
It wasn't like anything like underhanded.
But then I felt bad because I was like, well, I'm making her feel bad
about a very fun roast.
Like it's a very fun, you know, innocuous thing to be goofy.
And I was like, oh, man.
And then I got sadder because of that.
I felt sadder because now I had made you feel bad about a
fine goofing on.
I feel like you weren't much like my breakdown.
Taking it and batting it back.
It was like, I don't know, Jay Leno not riffing back at Jim
Kimmel during the 10 at 10.
And then whining about it to Oprah a year later.
These three little theme park boys would put in references to Jay's 10 at 10.
A screen card challenge.
Any of the different segments on the Jay Leno show,
a show that's a little bit forgotten in the history of television.
They seem particularly enamored, not with the Jay Leno Tonight Show,
but with the Jay Leno Show, the failed experiment in 2009.
And and they, of course, would eventually get into Jay's other four shows,
primetime shows that he did until he was 110.
The one that's on your life, Jay Leno, Jay Leno exclamation point.
Jay Leno exclamation point.
You'll get to it.
And for some reason, the Dean Martin show starring Jay Leno.
Very weird reboot.
He bought the rights.
So, yes, so that so that is why now we are trying to correct this.
Yes. I feel as if it's already occurred because I was going to say,
what would you like to say about the other Tower of Terror?
We need to give you the opportunity.
You've already said an amazing thing.
That was why I requested it.
Yes, because it was so traumatic.
I had a story because I'm a big fan of the Twilight Zone TV show.
But now I got out the whole reason I.
Right. So we've corrected a totally fine cosmic wrong.
Oh, good. I was just saying the one other shot that I of course remember
that you've called for a long time is that eventually M.M.C.
Oh, yes, will be done on.
I think we said Patreon, but who knows?
Yeah, the party is what we've talked about talking about before.
The party separately from M.M.C.
I think it was specifically the party. Yes.
I mean, I'm all about for once.
I am excited about subdivisions in our top.
Right. Yes. Comes to this.
Now I'm on board.
I would gladly do full party. That's.
Yeah. Especially for a page.
Is to tie. Yeah. Yeah.
So that eventually for their what specific is when you say M.M.C.
or you're referring to the 90s Mickey.
No, obviously.
Yeah, the 90s because the party should have a 50s on.
I have nothing to say about that.
Give me Christina.
Nothing to say about the Mickey Mouse Club.
I net. I still will call my shot.
Well, eventually we'll do a net solo music career.
So we'll get to do that episode.
We will. We have to do that.
But this is specifically the party.
And I'm not even that big of a party at Lindsay and Scott or the party.
They're they're the ones that know the most about the party.
I have to be honest. Huge, huge, huge M.M.C.
I don't know really anything about the party.
I'm excited to talk about it anyway.
I remember them existing.
And I remember that some of the M.M.C.
broke off into the party and did music that way.
And then also there was separately the M.M.C.
who just sunk a real talk. It's very good.
That was a couple of years later.
So I will learn about the party.
I'm excited to learn about.
You met someone from the party.
Yes. Correct. Which one?
Dee Dee. Dee Dee.
Because she is the voice of Pearl on Steven Universe.
And I happen the week I started Infinity Train.
Of course, this could probably be better safe for the party episode.
I'll be fast. The week I started Infinity Train, I said,
do you think that Dee Dee is just like wandering the halls?
And they were like, I don't know.
She could be here to record one day.
End of the week, there was a Steven Universe ice cream truck.
And there she was. And I got a picture with her.
It was so exciting.
Wow. That's a good manifestation.
Yeah. It's a premonition in a good way.
Such an amazing moment.
I did a song by the party in my fourth grade talent show.
It was a Dee Dee song.
Whoa. And you met Dee Dee.
And you thought maybe you could meet Dee Dee.
Dee Dee does cool things, evidently.
Dee Dee Magno Hall. Magano Hall?
Well, we'll know for the episode.
Well, yeah, we'll have that ready to go by then.
OK, so party coming.
Extremely nice.
So so yeah, tower like we're talking we can do any towers.
We can talk. We haven't done a full Guardians one,
but we'll talk towers specifically about Tokyo, Disney Sea,
which is awesome.
We've been in 2006, just to say a fact, not a didn't open with the park.
Opened five years later.
Big edition. Amazing edition.
By the way, I think, yeah, we do.
All right. So we did the Twilight Zone without you.
But I think this is a stellar attraction that you've been on for sure.
And it's I don't want to talk to you about it on the Tokyo episode.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. We tried to not.
We try. We say some of it.
We but we did a sort of a brief explanation.
We also started a hashtag to get Jason
a role as one of the characters on the ride. Of course.
Smelding. Is it smelding or smedling?
Smell smelding. Smelding.
Smell before the day.
Yeah. OK. So we'll get to smell.
We'll talk.
Slemding. I think it's a fell before all of this.
Slemding. Slemding.
Slemding. Snap into a slim Jim.
So we'll we'll talk about the characters.
But yeah, we have we've done a brief, hopefully brief.
If we go back, it's probably a half hour discussion about this.
I wouldn't. It is so.
Absolutely everything. Folks, if we haven't said this before,
Tokyo Disney Sea, Tokyo Disney itself is great.
But the detail like I've forgotten
way more about the details of Tokyo Disney Sea
and this ride specifically, then it like there's so much stuff
in the queue that you don't even notice.
Like I think we brought it up maybe on the episode,
but there are just a bunch of like busty
lady statues in the outdoor queue. So funny.
I don't. So fucking funny.
It's really funny because the main character that they've created
that looks like Joe Rody, which is Harrison Hightower, who's like
a monster. Played by Joe Rody in the commercial.
Yes. Like the live action thing.
It is Joe Rody. Yeah.
And he's like a monster turn of the century capitalist who.
William Randolph Hearst type.
Yeah. Who pillages from different peoples around the world.
Takes their valuable items and brings them back.
Yes. And then store them in this tower, oddly predating
the eventually Joe Rody guided Guardians of the Galaxy
mission break. Yes. The collector.
Yes. Pre collector.
He has collected and the blueprint for the collector.
Yes. And it's all all of his stuff.
I guess the like the there's a lot of like collect.
He collects stuff. He collects things, actually.
I think he goes to like different places around the world,
like, for instance, the Everest queue, which Everest is a ride he worked on.
And he goes and buys things from locals and then puts them in the queue
and decorates that to make that feel more authentic.
So he's somebody I think who ethically goes around the world,
takes things and brings them back and uses them for, you know, immersion.
And yes, very interesting way.
Yeah. Howersen Hightower is like goatee Spock, like mirrors, mirrors.
Spock, Joe Rody. He does. Yes.
That is a funny way to think of him.
Yeah. So that's I guess that's the goof is that it's funny
that he's the opposite of Joe Rody.
And in the queue, I guess if you were had like some like mad man
who would be like, yes, put busty women.
Yeah, busty stinxes. And you pointed it out.
I don't know to something like that.
First of all, I would never.
You were the one who pointed it out.
Mike playing it very safe because he was finally released from the dog house.
He's in the dog house.
He had to be slight at Lindsay not having her on the first Tower of Terror episode.
That is true.
He couldn't be on video Zoom because it was so damn dark in that dog house.
So damn dark in that dog house.
Yes, that is true.
But yeah, no, Lindsay pointed it out.
She goes, all these statues are like have big breasts.
Yes. I go, that is a very ridiculous, funny detail.
So you're saying this is like some some funny trashy decorating by this.
I'm sorry to go there, but this like this New York socialite
who's kind of a shithead. Sure.
Colinizer. Yeah, yeah.
But you're saying specifically maybe a parallel to a modern day New York.
Yeah. Businessman shithead.
I don't say his name. Yeah, I don't say his name, but like
a T.R. asterisk M and then one more asterisk.
I do. I give it to. Yeah.
It would only be it would be all more appropriate if it was like a golden toilet
was inside the Tower of Terror.
But like it's like it's not quite as good, honestly, not quite as gaudy.
The Tokyo Disney Sea Tower.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Well, it was an era where you couldn't be as much.
But yeah, it had.
Excellent taste.
But also clearly had his preference with the ladies. Sure. Yeah.
And then leaving the ride as well.
Just I read about I saw these pictures.
This was so funny to me. The gift shop.
I think ridiculous.
When you leave, it's like this video I watched earlier
is to remind myself what the ride was like pointed out.
It's like and then when you leave, it's it's sort of done in the motif
of this like bathhouse in New York.
And I and I was like, oh, my God, I can't believe I forgot
about the end of the ride, which is just a bunch of murals
of Harrison Hightower being bathed by different women of different cultures.
Like it's insane.
Oh, we're getting massages in a bathing pool.
And yes, like a bunch of them and being portrayed.
Oh, man. And it's all like done.
Like I feel like it all falls under like the like it's it's hard
is the right place because the character dies because of his arrogance
and what he's been doing. For sure.
Yeah. So it's like making fun of this type of person.
And it does it down to the detail, like down to the very small details.
And yeah, you like stuff that I don't even know.
Like the stuff that's probably not even mentioned online,
because like no one's even documented it down to looking for photos.
And like I, I was sure I'd forgotten
so many, many good details. Right.
So they've they have crafted and that's like I've said on the episode,
like the detail in Disney Sea in general is like you go on,
just look at plaques under like the elevated train.
And they've just written paragraphs and paragraphs of like jokes
and explanation and like backstory for everything.
That's like part historical part joke.
And like you it's just there's I bet you would never run out of like
learning some silly thing they made up for this whole place.
Set by how fast the line was moving.
Because I wanted to be I wanted to look at all of this insane detail on this queue.
Yeah, it's really yeah, it really feels like I don't have enough.
I have not seen enough.
And there's all these photos and like all the photos aren't online either.
I saw I mean, maybe there if you really dig, but I found a blog of the artist
who did some of them. Oh, wow.
And let me find his name here.
But it's yeah, on top of while you're looking for that,
when you're in the queue, talking about how he either will like
buy the artifacts or just steal them if the culture doesn't want him to have them.
Like he's stealing an Easter Island head.
And it's always him like grandly leaving,
followed by smelting, being chased by very angry locals,
trying to get their and their property back.
Right. And smelting is like on the verge of death.
Yeah. And smelting is always like more danger.
Obviously, he's Harrison Brunt.
Yeah. The Smithers to the Burns.
For sure.
The guy who is who did a lot of the paint is Kate Sean Sullivan.
And yeah, he did like stuff like the, you know,
that you can see that we describe that it's yeah, it's Harrison Hightower.
And I'm not sure which country he's in, but he's there's three women.
They're ones bringing him fruit.
The others bring him fruit and ones massaging him.
He's got like a blanket over his butt and he's like wearing whatever,
you know, ceremonial head.
He's on a massage table.
Yeah. Yeah.
And it's like, yeah, made to look like an old drawing as if he was a god being
service. Yeah.
At the end of this Disney ride.
Rendered in the most beautiful like this is if you haven't been to Tokyo,
Disney, see they really do.
They traffic in this like pre 20th
century architecture and artwork.
It's like they cover.
I'm not enough of an art historian or anything to call out styles.
But you see like just ornate paintings of every variety.
It feels like the Renaissance.
It feels like so many like different eras.
Yes. Oh, they just like like Sorin.
I haven't. I saw in Fantastic Flight.
Their version of Sorin was not there when I was there.
But you want I've watched videos since and like, God, just like the level
of architecture and like how Sorin's essentially a box in.
Yes. In California, you don't even see where you are really in Epcot.
And then here it's just these beautiful grounds with beautiful paintings.
And that's why I've like super encouraged people who aren't even major
into theme parks like you have to go to Tokyo, Disney, see anyway,
because it's like walking around a museum that has rides.
Well, it's literally that era of the United States with its architecture
and its fashion and everything.
It's literally called the Gilded Age.
All right. Right. Yeah.
It is like you would I would even add on theme park person if they were
had a decent amount of time in Tokyo, I would say like, yeah,
like if you're a theme park person, go to Tokyo, Disney for sure.
But just go to a Tokyo Disney Day one day to see what they've done.
To see it just to see the the level of theming and because, yeah, it is.
Again, it's another level that I would.
It's hard for me to picture a person who wouldn't get something out of it,
even if it was never expressed any theme park interest or desires.
Yeah, it is. It is.
And we fall asleep dreaming of it after you go.
Yeah, true. Yeah.
It's emotional to leave.
Yes. This ride building specifically, the the is inspired by
Gothic revival architecture and Moorish revival architecture,
which I read some site pointed out
was very popular around the turn of the century and in the late 1800s
as Europe and America and like the West was pillaging Africa
and the Middle East. Right.
A lot of this architecture.
So even the architecture plays into the story of this
globetrotting pillager.
It's co-opting. Yeah.
That's who was building at the time was a bunch of freaking colonizing tycoons.
Right. Like all the money in the world.
And that's like, yeah, like it's so weird.
Disney is an insane corporation.
But then like Joe Brody is like getting in some like historical facts.
And like, if you really dig into it, you go.
They're satirizing themselves in a way. Sure.
Maybe they maybe don't even realize.
Well, yeah, I'm sure.
But yeah, it's I was going to show you there's one other photo that
smelding is in there like in a hot air balloon.
They're stealing like that was one of my guys.
And then like a mummy or like a mummified corpse is falling on smelding
as Harrison Iteras, I get away in this balloon.
How much character you get out of these characters who don't really
appear that the Hightower is in the pre-show in the video.
Smelding is not at all. Right.
So it's but you get what they are completely from those paintings.
The other thing I want to say about the building,
it's the same same shape as the it's the this thing is largely the same as the
it's the T it's the Tower of Terror T
largely the same, especially as the newer tower,
the non original tower of terror is the one in the Paris one.
However, that level of architectural detail and just every
just so many turrets and moldings and balcony like you could just stare
at individual things on it for hours and hours.
I want to say this.
I think this is the most beautiful Disney building
that's supposed to look like a building.
I don't know if I'd say this is cooler than a volcano or cooler than any beloved
fake rocks, but I think a building building and I count the castles in that.
I think this is better than any castle.
Interesting.
It is beautiful.
Yeah, it is really beautiful.
Yeah, I might agree.
Hey, I'm sorry to throw castles under the bone.
Sorry. Yeah, that's the only thing that kind of makes me like pause.
I'm like, oh, but a castle. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's it. But I was thinking about it like what I I don't know.
Do I like any castle more than I like this building?
Hmm. That's an interesting question.
It's certainly an era that I love.
It's at the very least tied with the castle cake.
At the very least, it's tied.
Yes. There's a storyline for the building, too, of that, like
Hightower inherited the man, the family mansion, and then just expanded
and expanded and built tower and spa and grant.
And so this is like it is like in the way that
is it San Simeon is the Hearst property?
Oh, right.
It's like grounds or the Huntington Library in Pasadena,
the library and gardens and stuff used to be like an estate.
And now it's like a garden.
You can pay and go to the art galleries and see if you guys ever been to Hearst's
Castle. I have not actually.
I haven't either. I haven't.
That's stupid. We all live in California.
Why have we not been? It's a little.
It's such a Disney ish thing.
Yeah. Like, you know, they've I think not just for this, but other stuff.
Yeah. For sure. Pulled from Hearst Castle.
For sure. Yeah.
What's it near?
It's far, though, isn't it?
It's definitely north.
Yeah. But it's not like crazy for us to have tried to visit.
No, of course not.
But it's big enough that there's multiple different tours.
There's like an architecture tour, an art tour.
Like there is like a handful of different tours you can take of the property.
Six hours away. Yeah.
So the next time we're up there.
We're not young. Why haven't we been?
We had so much time. It's a good point.
I mean, but that could be applied to so many things in life, you know?
That's true.
But it's like this in particular, being theme park people,
you would think we'd go check out Sure.
Castle or like the Winchester Mansion.
I've never done some. I've never done the Winchester.
Me neither. Yeah.
Yeah, I know. We should.
So uncultured.
Well, it's a.
I haven't done the real.
You're talking about the fake ones.
That's what the whole thing is.
We're three cowards who just want to go on a simulated version of everything.
This is all about unpacking that.
Hosted by two,
two childless cowards in their 30s and one child having cowardly.
Not 30s.
You almost got out.
I'm starting to look proud.
I see you over there.
But I didn't make it out of that one.
Yeah, Hearst Castle six hours.
So, yeah, we're not going to get there.
It's too far.
Not going to happen.
So, yeah, he's gathered all of these items.
He's pillaged items, including from I didn't know this tie in this.
Didn't have it that there's a oh, what is it?
There's there's something that he steals from raging spirits,
which is the like ruins type roller coaster over near Indiana Jones.
Did I get the name right?
And that sounds like that's the one that's the one.
That's the one where the employee and I think I said this on the show,
the employee ran up to me while we were in the queue and stopped me, kind of panicked
and wanted to know how tall I was.
And then they had to bring me over and they kind of like we're talking amongst themselves.
And then, like in my mind, begrudgingly sent me through the queue.
Like I had just hit the limit.
You can't be taller than me.
Wow. And I was like, oh, good.
So like I was like kind of ducking the whole time on the ride.
I grabbed him and I said, just so you know, I love you.
Yes. And I felt much better after that.
I think you had to say it there.
Yeah, that's true.
This is a high risk of decapitation.
But like, yeah, I didn't I didn't realize that tight.
That coaster opened around the same time, I think, and they made a connection
where not only that, he's there's artwork of him stealing from those ruins.
Right. But then there's also high tower crates in the line.
So that so they make it one of those Disney things that they're seeding
and connecting the attractions. Pretty neat. Bunch of fun nerds.
Yep. Yeah.
But he so he steals a lot from all around the world, but then he goes too far.
He he pushes it.
He pushes his luck a bit too much.
And he goes to an African village and takes
this little idol guy, Shereekee Atundu. Yes.
And I think the the backstory that I now have learned is that
he initially is trying to find a gentlemanly way to get it.
And then they say, no, we this is our God.
Right. Very valuable.
We there's no amount of money.
And then he just takes it.
But unlike in these other scenarios where Smelding gets chased
and they throw stuff at him.
Oh, interestingly enough, in this instance,
they don't seem to want it back too much.
They don't put up a fight.
They're smoking. Go ahead.
They're like they seem like OK with it for some reason.
Yeah. So go ahead.
Take take Shereekee.
And he just doesn't think anything of it.
But we learn more about this story in this pre show room,
because it's like it's the format of the other towers here where there's the general cue.
You start in a garden, you end up in the indoor lobby.
You see a crashed elevator.
You see a crash. Yeah.
Which that's very cool, that particular facet.
Like warped door.
Yeah. With columns that have cracked.
The whole thing's just caved in.
Yeah. And the premise is like the preservation society is giving you this tour
and explaining what happened.
So they've got a backstory for it.
Yes, they've got a backstory for that, too, which makes a lot of sense.
Why would you even get to be here?
This is like we already know from that that this is a crime scene,
possibly a murder scene.
So why is there even anything?
And it's because, yeah, this preservation society has opened it to the public
because they're trying to save it.
It is a historical landmark, even though an evil guy lived there. Right.
Which I like that aspect of it, too, that there's all this signage
that's very old timey World's Fair, like come and see the marvelous.
And they even justify that phrase Tower of Terror with little quotes.
It feels like a carnival barker kind of phrase. Yes. Yes.
But Miss Beatrice Rose Indicott doesn't cotton to that.
She's the head of the preservation society.
She doesn't believe in such things.
Cotton. Yes. Yeah.
So lots of good names that I had not encountered before.
I didn't know her fit the head of the preservation society's name.
And also the reporter who enter, who like asks a question that you hear on the
the the recording is named Manfred Strang.
Whoa. I missed that one.
Jason to see I'm not going to declare them official
see members, but seems like they could be a good way in.
Ronald DeMore, you know, right.
Could be good audience, you know.
And hey, if you want to hire four writers,
you're listening to them.
Oh, well, three writers and one smelting.
Right. Right. Right.
Yeah. Jason, for smelting, I would get that going again.
I listen, Ronnie, I just play sniveling.
I will snivel my heart out in real life, too.
You look up sniveling in the dictionary.
It's Jason Sheridan, folks.
I'm not willing to wriggle or wiggle, but you're willing to sniff.
I'll sniff a little. Very.
So, yeah, this pre show room, it's the equivalent of the
Florida Tower terror or the former the rocket room
where you're divided up into a smaller group and you get a little like
a little backstory.
But it's not the Rod Serling video.
It's this neat little scene with a preservation society member
press and play on an old phonograph and which like now.
That's what's on the record is a you hear what it what is.
It's a final interview.
OK, where they the man, Fred Strang, S.
Isn't it cursed?
Isn't the idol curse the idol, by the way, apparently translates to
the name of the idol translates to believe the misfortune.
And on the Disney Wiki, there is a long
bio, there's a long history about the lineage of the idol.
Like, there is a long backstory. Of course, there is.
They went hard with all this backstory.
They did not have to go that hard, but they did.
Yes. Well, that's the as the youth say.
They were not required to go thus hardly.
But they did. Yeah.
Yeah. So there's like there's like a description for just the like
the fast service eateries.
There's like a lot of like stuff I've forgotten about eating a cheap piece
of pizza in Tokyo. Yeah.
Yeah. Everything is something.
So, yeah, he's scoffing at the idea that this curse is real.
But then is it that forgive me for not remembering the order exactly.
But there is a stained glass portrait of Hightower
in the room the whole time.
And then it shatters or changes or comes to life to life.
And the voice of Harrison Hightower
possesses the gramophone.
Is that what that's? Yeah.
Oh, phonographs to you somehow through what you were.
What is that for? Yeah.
The gramophone thing, the phonograph that you're listening to.
And he all of a sudden you're getting his voice through that.
And he has come to life in the in the stained glass,
the beautiful stained glass window that is kind of evocative of
Beauty and the Beast opening stained glass.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, for sure.
Mm hmm. It's beautiful.
And yeah, it transformed.
And this is also this is all like this still looks great
from my memory in person. Yeah.
And it's like already. Yeah. What?
Fifteen years old. Yes.
Oh, and the idol is there.
Yes. Yes. All next to it.
And the all time in the room. Yeah.
Displayed or nearly on this pedestal.
They did it 15 years old.
Yeah. It opened in September 2006, which is only five years after this park opened.
Again, they didn't have to go that like they just rolled out a new e ticket
five years in, which they had plenty of stuff.
Yeah, it's not.
We've we talked on the last one about like the Tower of Terror,
not the original so much, but in the other cases in Anaheim
and Paris, it is like we got to save this crappy park. Right.
Rush this ride in and in a lesser way here.
They do it. Let's like like we already had this amazing park.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
They didn't. Yeah. Exactly.
Didn't it? Didn't you go there? Right.
And it is like a clone of the ride itself.
But they went that way, way extra mile,
which is original story and mythology and just great art direction.
It's incredible thread and crazy magic.
And that is really the big thing here. Right.
Is that then you get through this, you get the stained glass demonstration
of what the fell high tower.
You don't really get the details yet, but you see
this green spirit light up and go all the way to the top of the tower.
And then there's a shatter and then he plummets down to the bottom.
Now we know what happened in the lobby.
And then the idol.
Well, it goes dark and a bunch of sparkly lights.
Yes. Like take its place.
This like very like original Tower of Terror.
Yeah. Where all these crazy lights come from.
He comes to life, smiles with these horrible piranha teeth.
He's so like affecting and scary and creepy.
And then, yeah, sparkly lights come up, only eyes visible.
And the room is only dark for a second.
And when the lights come back up, the idol has disappeared.
It is shocking. Yeah.
It is such a good.
It's a really good special effect that I still am not exactly sure what it is.
I know what it is, too.
And I was borderline disappointed in how simple it is.
I know generally what it is, but it's still there.
You want to do it, idiot?
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, it's so it's up on this pedestal,
but then it drops and it goes inside the bed.
There's a yes, faster than free fall.
Yeah, it's like so.
So, yeah, it basically while that half second is dark, it shoots into the ground.
Yeah, but it feels like there's some leftover light to kind of like quickly.
Your brain doesn't have time to even notice that.
So literally your brain recognizes that it has appeared.
Yeah, it's so instantaneous.
We speculated on how they did the effect, and it was all like way more complicated,
wasn't it? Or am I thinking?
No, no, no.
I think we were trying to figure out if it was some sort of projection on a base,
like the back of it might have been a base that had the outline of it or something,
and it like gave it some dimension.
We were like doing all these like tricks way too much.
But I think, yeah, I think maybe there is some sort of like your eyes,
like light stays with your eyes a couple like milliseconds longer.
So while the darkness is there, your eyes maybe even see it like lit up.
So you think it's there a couple extra beats.
Yeah, I think so. After it's gone.
And also its eyes being lit up within the sparkly starryness.
It's like, oh, it's definitely still there.
Yeah, there's like a couple.
But it's not. That must be a projection.
Are the eyes separate? That's what I was going to ask.
Yeah, I think the eyes that are lit up while the effect is going
are not the eyes of the actual statue.
Maybe. I think that that's a projection.
And that hangs for one.
Yeah, hangs for one extra second and takes completely takes your brain away
from like being able to recognize that the actual item is moved into the ground.
But then you say that like it drops into the pedestal.
But I still have some questions.
One is it looks too big to fit in that pedestal.
I agree. I have not seen it do it, but that's what I've heard it is.
Yeah, but I could be.
I haven't heard it from Joe Rody. So maybe.
I heard it from YouTube, which is notoriously reliable.
Yeah, so famously so.
There's another detail, too, that we didn't mention with this stained glass.
I thought this was really cool.
And it lingers for the rest of this pre-show room
when that energy field like appears and like drops
in the elevator shaft on the stained glass, it cracks the bottom where the lobby is
as if the stained glass cracked and then it stays like that as you're leaving.
Oh, like it affects the glass on the way.
Wow. Wow. Yeah.
As if the energy itself broke it. Yeah.
And it does. It looks broken after that. Yeah.
It is. There's a bunch of other energy stuff throughout the ride, like that.
You see the energy from the ground up in the penthouse,
then it travels to the elevator that's dropping. It's wild.
Yeah, it's again, I forgot more.
Why do you watching the YouTube video even is like feels like one
eighth the experience of being there? Yeah.
If that because you're just in a hate, you're just like you're not processing
all this when you're there, just like, whoa, that was cool.
And then it's so bright.
Like the details aren't really hitting you.
There's so much to take in. Yeah. Yeah.
Now, there is a thing you bring up like Joe Rody and like the tricks of the.
Here's something I was mistaken about, I think, until the behind
the attraction show came out.
So I'm looking at all these photos of Rody
the Imagineer playing this larger than life
villainous guy and in these scenarios where he's a god and where he's
being bathed by women.
And I'm like, OK, I know this is supposed to be like a shitty guy.
This is still crazy in an ego way.
Oh, right. So in all this stuff, I didn't realize until behind the attraction.
He didn't do this attraction.
He was completely a model.
And as he explains in the show, they asked him to do one thing.
They asked him to be a model.
They were going to do like a plaster cast of him for like this is going to be like
he has some weird word.
I don't know what it is, but it's on the outside of the building.
There was supposed to be one molding of this character and that was it.
And then suddenly, like, actually, we're going to do some paintings and stuff.
Actually, we might do a video.
Actually, the ride is opening and you need to come to Japan and film commercials
as an actor, you the imagineer are now a Japanese actor like Schwarzenegger
filming weird commercials for like a watch.
Yeah, yeah. He didn't do the ride.
He didn't. I did not remember that.
Didn't know that until this.
Well, it does make sense because of the collecting aspect, because it does feel right.
Yeah, it feels thematically.
And it's confusing because he did do Guardians.
I was just about to say, because like that's got his like classic like
we probably didn't need this much of an explanation as to what's going on with
the ride, but thank you so much for all the hard work.
Yes, it does smell like road.
And so I just figured.
But I was going to say it's interesting that like
before you told me that it's not his ride, I was going to say it doesn't have that
hallmark of him is like there's not there's the story.
But it's not like like that was already the Avatar backup.
Get the story.
Yes, yes, that is what I'm saying.
It's not that complicated a story of what happened to Harrison Hightower.
And yet I know a hallmark of a Joe Rody ride is the complicated backstory of what's
going on. And so I was going to say, isn't that interesting that that's missing on
this ride? And lo and behold, it's not his ride.
That's why. If it would have been there would have been twice as much stuff.
There would have been hands.
Of course, something where you had to wave your arm.
You have to rain your hands or they have to be scanned.
Yes.
Is that where there's like CG animation of the characters in this?
Is that from TV commercials?
I know. I don't know.
I saw that.
Yeah, we all watch this.
This is called the Tower of Terror, the mystery that is some
promotional piece that tells this backstory that tells you Harrison Hightower.
And you see smelting and you see this reporter and all this.
And it is this odd
Polar Express animation.
Yeah, it looks fan made.
Yeah, yeah.
It 100 percent looked fan made to me.
And but I think it's probably just a Japanese marketing campaign.
Yeah, maybe. Or it was like online.
There was a shot of something in the commercial.
Yeah. But then there's live action.
Yeah. Like you were saying, there's filmed live action.
Joe Rody as Harrison Hightower to inner inner cut.
I saw it in the review time, like short documentary YouTube video.
That's where I saw it, too.
Yeah. And I was like, what am I looking at?
It does a good job of explaining it.
And then there's a couple other there's an Attractions magazine right through.
And then there's another right through with a very literal translation.
A lot of the dialogue.
GM or LMG rides or something like that.
Yeah, this this
sour cherry, the mystery video, though, is so strange because it tells you the story.
Here's what happened.
But it's not the thing from the ride and it's not commercials.
I don't know what medium it existed in exactly.
But not only is there weird video game
animation, but there are live action actors as well.
This is one of the strangest aesthetic choices I have ever seen leading,
especially to this part where Harrison Hightower is crashed in his lobby.
Yes, 100 percent.
I had this thought, too, where, oh, my God, what happened?
Let's go check. They're reaching.
And there is a one man looks in with a lantern.
What happened? And he is a CGI man.
And then another man, a live action man,
leans in and they are right next to each other.
Where have you ever seen this idea?
Made me think it was fan made or something is I was like, oh, a fan made a composite
of a CGI waiter guy looking in a shaft and then inserted this actual actor behind
himself. And so I was wondering, like, oh, I wonder what that footage is from then.
But like, no, that was the commercial guy.
I think they made it.
It's just like you've seen live action actors and then cartoony.
Then with Roger Rabbit or Rocky and Bullwinkle or something.
I've never seen human characters with live action actors.
It's such a it's such a bizarre choice.
I'm amazed Decker didn't make it.
Absolutely.
That is absolutely the shot that jumped out at me is the weirdest one.
Yeah, right. OK, I'm glad this haunted you as well.
I was like, what am I? Who is that guy behind?
Who is this man? I don't know.
And what is the choice? Why do you decide that some are
who's a computer character?
Why is the main character, Harrison Hightower, computerized?
But then a reporter, this guy staying gets a cast and call.
Somebody's somebody's playing, staying.
And then on top of that,
all the line, the live action lines are done.
It's all white actors speaking Japanese, but dubbed over by clear,
like better Japanese speakers.
That's another strange layer.
Just look up this video. It's so bizarre.
It all adds to the mystery.
Right. And there's no there's no oral history of that.
As far as we know.
No, no directors credit.
We're creating it right now.
This video adds a good little detail to the story, which is that right before
his dreaded elevator trip,
somebody says, what about the curse?
And he says, oh, the curse.
Here's what I think of it.
And then Hightower takes a cigar, puts it out on the head of the idol.
Yeah, that is, in fact, the final straw for the idol.
Yeah. The reason it happens is because he puts his cigar out on its head.
One of the rules of the idol is you have to show it respect.
And that's not too respectful.
Right. And this is New Year's Eve, 1899.
Yes.
Which is also a strike of 12.
The sea connection.
There's that painting of all the sea members.
The idol is in the painting.
And that painting is supposed to be a meeting that occurred this night.
Oh, before.
Yes, before he dies, because both he is there and the idol is in the paint.
They're both in the painting.
So you're saying that all the other members of sea were there, were in the building.
Yes, they were at the party.
They were at the big party.
It seems like it was a real rager, not the MMC party.
A regular party.
Yeah. Disney party. Right.
And they all. Yeah.
So this really is we talked about in the actual sea episode.
This makes it harder for Ronald D.
Moore to make all these guys the heroes of a new show when they're all hanging out
with this insane colonizer thief
who is disrespecting idols of the party.
They're like, oh, yes, well, well, who better to know how to write that than
someone in Hollywood? Sure.
Shoulder to shoulder with villains.
So, yeah, it's the it's like we've said a whole movie now already.
Yeah, this could be a movie.
And all rendered so wonderfully again, like just the it's the best art direction,
the best lighting, and then you're let into the the boiler room.
I don't know what they call it here.
I don't know if it's still a warehouse is where it stores all the art that isn't up.
And then you've got even more giant or neat.
That's where that's where I was like, can we slow the line down?
I'm looking at all these tiny drawers.
There were so many drawers and every different load area had sort of a different
specialty. We went we were in one with just like rugs.
Yeah. And I was like, oh, we got the rug room.
But that's like incredible.
Like tapestries.
Yeah.
An area Disney I don't think has gotten into is like the ancient art of tapestry.
It truly is just a beautiful place and a very traditional.
This isn't like we're finding some weird level to think it's neat on.
It is a beautiful building and everyone.
Yeah. There's a set of eyes.
Well, there are. Yes.
There's a couple different places where you can see the idle presence.
Yeah. Evil green eyes.
So, you know, you're in for it when you get into this elevator.
But yeah, it's a the room feels huge.
I don't think it's so much bigger than the regular boiler room for this,
but it feels massive.
I'm sure it's massive, but it's probably about the same.
Exactly the same. Yeah.
Yeah. So because because it is taking and I was thinking maybe I don't know if
this is the end of the episode.
It is interesting, like taking a ride and taking the exact same ride and then just
completely making a new it's like if we were taking Haunted Mansion and just
going like you can have the exact same track, exact same thing, do whatever you
want with it, make it kind of scary.
Sure. Yeah.
Which is interesting.
Fucking go hog wild.
It is interesting.
Billion things in it.
Yeah. Like take the pirate boat and just go like whatever you want.
Make them elves just to make it an elf thing or a hobbit thing.
Has even more.
Yeah. Backstory.
Yeah, exactly.
Stopped. Yeah.
And even just the if you look at the outside of the building, it looks like
there's four elevator shafts, only three of them are working.
The one that is not an actual functioning ride vehicle elevator shaft is the one
like one of the middle ones.
And it's the one that can most clearly go from the penthouse to the lobby.
It's the one that he died in.
Crashed. Yeah.
Yeah. Lines up with the it actually lines up with the spot at the bottom, seemingly
where the elevator crash and it lines up with his penthouse at the top.
Also, the top of the T with this with these designed buildings, the top of the T
is because of the massive generators on top of the elevator shafts that run the
ride, the power of the rides, which I always forget about.
Yeah, I didn't know that.
Until I watched this review time video.
Yeah. But it gets pretty like, you know, then we're then we're in familiar
territory like like it does feel like the other towers.
Although, again, you know, like you're sitting.
Yeah. Yeah.
And not for me, because I this was the ride.
Oh, yeah. The spell for me.
Right.
Where Darren was like, are you really
going to come across the world and then not go on this because you're afraid of
the good you were afraid of the job?
She's never made me do anything.
This she's like, you have you'll be so upset if you don't.
And I was she's absolutely right.
And I did it three times ultimately.
But it's now why I'm able to do the other ones.
I'm more if I'm afraid of the other ones.
I just like what's going to remind you of Tokyo, which wasn't scary like at all.
Once you did it, it was extremely positive.
Mm hmm.
And even still, like if something because I think the drop pattern is more intense
on Guardians, but I'm like, now that view like now I flash to Tokyo in my mind there.
It makes me so happy.
Yeah. And it's a beautiful view.
And it's a clone of the California Adventure one.
So there is no fourth dimension room word.
Yeah.
So they do all of the work in the time
and the space they have on the original California Adventure.
And I would say that's it's sad to say it.
That's the only part of the ride that let me down a little bit.
And I think we both felt the same thing.
I was like, I'm so ready to be scared.
Because it felt like a whole queue is like so building, building up.
And then I'm like, oh, OK, it's basically
just the original California Adventure drop sequence.
And I know, but it's not as good.
A little less intense, people say, which helped me.
But it lifts you up in like so rather than than just dropping you,
it lifts you up again and then will just like drop you a few floors incrementally
and then one big drop. Yeah.
And they they change. It's just not as much.
Right. So we went on the regular version
because they have different versions, different times of year where there are
like more intense drop sequences, sequences, which why shadow of Cherokee?
Yes. Yeah.
And I forget what you have.
I don't. It probably doesn't matter that much.
Like a couple of months where there will be different, more intense versions of it.
Really? Yeah.
So we want to see a shadow at one.
You see when it's dropping, you see him, the idol
ripping the cables, the shadow of him ripping the elevator.
The rocket, the rocket plugging in the walkman.
Oh, wow.
So, yeah, so they've they've upped it a little bit because I do think
and I've said this probably a million times at this point.
Guardians up the game on the actual ride itself on these towers
because there's so much going on and to watch and listen to that.
Now all the other ones feel a little empty
because it's not like even kind of felt that way on Tower of Terror in Florida.
That's why I went to see Aerosmith instead of going on tower again.
To see Aerosmith.
Phrasing.
Yeah, I went to see Aerosmith.
I went to the concert and see Aaron life from boys from Boston.
I took a super stretch limo.
Eliana Douglas.
I went to see Eliana.
I saw Eliana.
David Wayne.
You fucked it up.
Jason and Lindsay went to Tower of Terror and I split off to go see Aerosmith.
And that's why because I because we go on it and everything leading up to it's great.
And the drop is great, too.
It's just that I could have one more treat.
A party you don't even I'd like that you commit.
Not even the name of the ride.
It's I went to go see I went to go see Aerosmith.
Yes.
Backstage pass backstage passes.
Rock and roller coaster.
Not whatever it's called.
It's called Rock and Roller Coaster Rock and Roller Coaster starring arrows.
Starring Aerosmith.
GeForce Records.
That would be even funnier if I said I went to GeForce Records.
I went to the studios GeForce Records to see my friends.
Records headquarters around here.
I might go to Peru.
Check out the gold albums and everything.
Yeah. My friends, Steven Tyler, the Edge and Scooter Braun.
Funny Carlos.
And Ringo.
The ride itself, though, we have skipped some.
Yeah, sorry.
There's like I mean, again, we're like
you know the drill with the Tower of Terror, probably where you stop at floors
and there's these things, but that this the the whatever the event is exactly
happening to Hightower is fantastic.
Yes, yes, for sure.
I mean, so totally lives up to everything.
Yeah, I skipped ahead.
I meant really, truly just the thrill part.
Still going up.
There's awesome visuals.
Yeah, because you see you then see the ghost of Hightower interacting with the
idol again. You see him disrespect the idol.
The idol is kind of seems still.
But then after Hightower is done with and dissolves and flies off in a very
Twilight Zone manner, then he turns to look at you and the doors close immediately.
Super creepy.
Again, when I had not quite gotten over the fear, that moment was like Jesus.
You were like, were you yelling for your mom?
Maybe. Yeah.
If anyone can relate, it's this lady.
Yeah. Well, you've let me know that it's if I did.
It's a safe space.
I'm like playing up at the beginning.
Really, your mommy is what you imagine somebody doing that.
I mean, anyone any age over 10, let alone 35.
I, of course, have not written this, but when I watched a couple video ride
through the first time the idol turns and looks at you, I was like, no.
I, I, there are other people said, like in the next scene, like, you know, they, they
do the fact from the California Adventure, Tower of Terror, where you see yourselves
and then this kind of wavy and ghosty, but it's that green energy.
The idol appears again.
It says the idol launches at you.
But I think to me it just looked like he kind of teleports.
But nothing was as scary as the idol just turning to you.
Yeah, absolutely.
Well, another this the the idol turning and looking at you just makes me think like.
So another fun and idiotic fact about me is that I refuse to look in the eyes of
Mara when I go on Indiana Jones.
I will not do it.
I have some kind of superstition about her
snatching my money and luck away.
I won't do it.
Right. And you were where you did you look at the what's the character in the Tokyo
version because Mara is not in the Tokyo, Indiana Jones, whatever it was.
I wouldn't absolutely never.
Oh, it's that smallest crystal skull.
Right. Yeah.
No, you didn't.
Yeah.
Do I not want to succeed in life?
No, I want to succeed in life.
Oh, you know what?
We went in single rider on those every time.
So I didn't notice if you were looking at the crystal skull or not.
Will you look a bottle of Dan Aykroyd's crystal skull vodka in the eyes?
As long as it promises not to curse me.
All right. I don't know.
Does it? I don't think it promises anything.
Premium vodka experience.
Premium vodka.
Promise is a smooth taste.
Smooth. Don't mix it with anything.
Premium spirit.
I would like a celebrity liquor where they're a little more upfront, where it's
like this is dog shit and you're going to have to mix it with juice, with on it,
with something like this is reasonably priced.
This is a mixing alcohol.
It's for high balls at minimum.
Well, maybe that's what ours is.
That's the one we're going to do.
Oh, we'll be honest about it.
It's a cash grab.
This is like drinking hairspray.
A bunch of OJ.
This is like you remember Skoll vodka from high school.
This is just as good as that cheap thing.
You got it like you got a guy by you.
That's the brand Midwest.
People would know maybe Skoll vodka.
But what's the name of our tequila?
Buenos ninos.
Thank you.
So it's going to be shit.
It's going to be awful.
But hey, we're honest.
But we're honest about it.
So we know ninos.
We don't lie to you.
Buenos.
Yeah.
We'll learn it.
It's called agreement.
Of course.
I have the voice of the idol here also.
Oh, I forgot to mention it's the same voice.
It's Richard Stephen Horvitz, the voice actor of Invader Zim's Jim.
So that means something to people who watch that show.
Hmm.
Congratulations to you then.
Very popular cult show.
Yeah. I used to watch it a lot.
Oh, you did.
Yeah.
I used to watch it.
Nickelodeon really jerked it around.
Like it moved it around on the schedule a lot.
And then it I think picked up a cult following from like Joe and Vasquez.
Yeah.
Well, I got to check it out then.
So, yeah.
So then you get to that standard drop profile.
It feels like it should be now with all this build up to be 30 minutes.
That's part of the problem is the buildup is so amazing that I think just subconsciously
I didn't even really realize it.
I was expecting the ride itself to be really better, too.
It should be like pirates.
Should be a 15 minute ride now through like hell, through hell,
through hell itself.
Question mark.
Yeah.
Where the vehicle gets shot up out of the roof and then caught by another encasing
right, takes you down to the ground, into another thing and it returns you to the
shaft. A Disney sea airship sucks the vehicle up.
They can turn clouds into ride vehicles now.
And then you ride a cloud to a different park that you didn't know existed.
Right.
All of a sudden you're at the top of the Tokyo Tower in Tokyo itself.
Yes.
Which we explored where you're a VIP, where it's VIP, not very important person.
Very impressive panorama.
Yes, that's from that's from our there's a there's a thing that looks like the Eiffel
Tower, but orange, but it's like orange in Tokyo called the Tokyo Tower that we
found because we had to go to the doctor and we the doctor, the doctor that was
covered under whatever weird phone number we called to get meds was over by the thing.
What is this?
Looks like the looks like the Eiffel Tower.
Yeah.
So it's a big tourist trap.
And there was like a little pirates dinner theater.
I know we needed we needed to go to that.
But I forget why we didn't.
I think we I think we're trying to get to something else.
But then it closed.
We shot ourselves in the foot.
Yeah.
Because it's like, oh, we got to get to this one place and try the pancakes or I
feel like we made a lot of decisions in Tokyo like that, where we're like, there's
this very cool thing right here and now.
But because we had already talked about doing this other thing, I guess we should
go do the other thing we talked about.
And then we'd get to the other thing we talked about and it was closed.
You miss the 45 minute window when Jiro makes sushi.
Yes, 45 minutes a day.
Should we go to this pirate thing?
Yes, we screwed up a lot.
But yeah, anyway, so the ride happens.
We did the ride twice.
We did tower, I believe twice.
We did one fast pass, I think, and one full queue.
OK,
which you got to do the full queue.
You do got to.
And it's sometimes it is long because a lot of these like the park is so popular
and the big rides have pretty long lines.
I know that goes crazy.
Maybe was 50 minutes.
You guys like I said, I wanted it to be longer so that I could look at stuff more.
Sure. You keep saying that.
I I this is one where I yeah, it's cool.
I still don't.
I did a fast pass every time and I'm glad I did because you get on the right.
I'll look at a video later.
Just talked about the fact that the ride itself is just fine.
And exactly what we have here.
The pre show is great.
No matter how good a line is, there's nothing where I'm like,
I'm going to choose to go through the line that one that doesn't go read to me.
Maybe I don't know.
Maybe one time is limited on vacation.
Well, I just think if you're there,
you should do it once so that you know what the line is.
That makes you miss all those murals.
Right. And the statues.
But then I probably did like other good stuff in the park because there's so much.
Well, we were there.
We did. We did.
We did. How many days?
How many days?
I think we did four days.
We did closer to what Tony Baxter said we should do.
I think I followed Tony's word.
In the end, same as Tony.
In the end, yeah, we followed his rules.
So, Jason, you got to go.
Yeah. Yeah, no, I know.
We got to go back.
Why haven't you gone?
Yeah, why haven't I gone?
International travel.
Yeah.
Well, you know, now we've been very normal.
With Lindsay, we've been dipping into these Tokyo tracks.
I feel like we wanted to save them.
But now it's like, look, we're hey, hey, it's on.
I'm listening anyway.
It's it's just yeah, you know, it is what it is.
I'm going to I will go through the full line.
I will for sure go through the full line.
I go through the full line on Men in Black Alien Attack to do the fake,
fake out like Universe and You World's Bear tag, which I think is terrific.
But the Universal Express line bypasses goes right past it.
Yeah.
No, there's some full life full cues you got to do.
I think this is one of the I'm curious.
The full listener opinion on this.
Do you like often not do a chance to cut the line in order to do the full?
Now there's a limit follow up.
It depends.
Do you at least do the cue once?
Right.
But that didn't even occur to me then.
Like I better we better do the cue.
That did not occur to me one bit.
Of course, it all looks cool.
That never, ever struck me like I better see the detail.
I better see the busty statue.
There wouldn't be the busty statue.
There wouldn't be any.
But also, even though we've been talking about how great this ride is for two
hours, still I have zero regrets about this.
Really?
Is there one?
The garden, the statues.
You really do not know what you're missing.
Is there one cue, though?
I don't know that you've been through that you would say somebody like you
got to go through it once at least or no, you would skip every like let's
hypothetical talk about this.
Yes, yes, yes.
OK, OK.
Say you truly skip all the cues.
I mean, literally you show up at that pre-show moment.
So like say it's Indiana Jones.
You're in the room with the newsreel.
You skip that whole line.
It's the Guardians.
You're in the room with Rocket.
You skip that line.
So like you're saying if I if there's somebody who'd never been to the park.
Exactly.
And there was the ability to do this.
Would you would you was a one ride?
You would say you have to do the full cue because it's really so cool.
No, walk there.
Really?
You skip every line that fucking rules.
Not even the full Indiana Jones cave.
The theatrical experience.
Some of them.
This like builds up the like, wow.
But I'm with a person who has I guess we're like with a guy or something.
Never, never.
Yeah.
I'm not saying I'm saying like Indiana Jones.
All right.
It's going to be an extra 30 minutes, but you have to walk through the long Indiana
Jones queue before you get to that newsreel line and the things on the ground.
And depends on who I'm with.
Well, you know, the person seems interested in it.
I don't know.
I like all this, but I like I don't know.
I still like skipping a line.
I want to know what this hypothetical person you're with has better to do.
Jason's mad at that person.
I'm mad.
I'm furious.
I do think this is a controversial opinion.
I think it's controversial.
Every line in a part, you don't do it.
But we're talking.
You're not even really walk fast through.
Literally never walk fast through.
Well, this is a man.
Well, I'm just saying sometimes it's like, for instance,
Guardians, when you do fast pass, you don't get to walk around and see all things.
But you do get a brief glimpse of everything because they just kind of I'm
just saying in this hypothetical scenario, you're literally just like it's like
you're appearing in that pre show room.
You can imagine.
Let me give this to you.
OK, I'm in this hypothetical scenario and I am the person saying, no, we're not
skipping this one. I think I get kicked out of the group.
Huh? But but wouldn't.
Who would?
Can you imagine being on the other side of that and like, sorry, what?
We're not going to skip the line.
But more recent rise like rise of the resistance.
That doesn't count.
That's a whole other.
OK, no, because a lot of line is the you know, you're getting the pre show before
you then get to the more line.
You would tend back thing is different.
Yes.
But I feel like, for instance, Pirates, the queue fine.
Obviously, skip that.
There's nothing.
Skip the smugglers run like Haunted Mansion.
You wouldn't say go in the Haunted Mansion queue.
There's a cool effect in there.
I would say go to the elevator.
OK, I guess that is my show.
Yeah.
Yeah. Haunted Mansion queue.
You're not really missing anything.
Pirates queue.
You're obviously not missing anything.
Smugglers run.
Skip it.
I think Indiana Jones queue, though, is worth walking through.
I think, yeah, Indiana Jones.
I think you have to see it.
We're talking once in your life.
One time, don't skip the line half an hour out of your whole goddamn life.
You stupid piece of shit imaginary person that Scott is, for some reason,
friends with.
I don't.
None of us know why.
This guy sucks.
High old Hightower.
Scott, I don't know how you put up with them.
One time spent 20 extra fucking minutes.
I hate him.
You think I like hanging out with this guy?
He's awful to me.
He's the worst.
He slaps me around.
He physically mistreats me.
He won't let me make insane the queue.
He's not going to Disneyland.
He's who I'm choosing.
Millennium Falcon.
You have to go to the queue there.
You mean the smugglers?
OK, the pre-show would cut.
Yeah, it's all boring.
That's me.
I would just go to Hondo.
There's not enough.
There aren't enough.
All right, fine.
That one. Yes.
No, you're right. You're right.
That one is a skip.
I agree with that.
I would insist I might insist that we go
through the full Guardians to see like Cosmo.
I think you have to do that one.
Yeah, I like Cosmo.
Outside queue, there's nothing.
Who cares about the sound?
OK, OK, that's fair.
Soren, you're not missing anything.
Some of these lines I enjoy being in.
I'm not saying I don't.
I think there's a handful queue.
But I'm saying you're saying this person can literally live and die
never seeing the Indiana Jones.
That's what we're talking about their whole life.
I want you to be born and leave this earth not having seen the Indiana Jones.
Not even seeing a rope and a spike.
A rope and a spike.
They're probably fine.
Wow, I hate this man.
I do not wish to know him.
I think there's a handful.
How do you picture it?
Does anyone see him in a does he look like Hightower?
Well, we talked about.
He looks like you in a mustache.
He's just it's like fight is a fight club.
It's fight club.
It's got to talking about his like Tyler Durden.
And this Tyler Durden doesn't even care about the fake out men in black line.
Wow.
Maybe you can learn a little something from them because he is.
This is going to be this is going to open up a can of worms.
I think I think we're I think we've started a new in a brand new.
Yeah, it is a controversial opinion.
It is if you had the ability to skip every line, you would do it for.
I think it is crazy.
I think it is for this part for this podcast.
You're a villain.
I'm not him.
I wink.
You're choosing for this person.
Oh, you're the villain.
You've been choosing for this for this whole time.
And I can't afford to lie on it.
You're making them say like, let's go on the lines before you pour the base on it.
Back to that first time you fought this friend, Scott, was it really just you the
whole time alone flashing to every memory of my last last six years?
This is interesting.
Friends with this person.
I think we I think we can make a list of unskippable cues for the first.
Like, have you never been on it?
Yes, yes.
Anyone come to I think middle ground here, but I'm interested to see what the reaction
is on the listener.
I know what it's going to.
I know what it is.
I've been in this goddamn rodeo before.
But there's the one you know what I think I think is the person listening who agrees
with me, who is not doesn't comment anywhere.
Oh, do you think they've been shamed?
They're worried.
I don't wish to know.
Well, let's make a secret email address.
Make yourself known and I'll fucking cancel you.
I'm going to cancel you so fast.
How about Scott?
Because I have Scott is pan at Gmail, which I've gotten a couple photos of Scott
is pan that still have to be revealed eventually.
But maybe Scott is right at Gmail.
You can control it if you want.
And a massive seems like it must be somebody it's probably taken.
Scott is right.
Sixty nine
at Gmail dot com.
Just got to make that number came up this episode.
So I'll make the G.
And then if you if you are a Scott supporter and you're worried because like
the bullies in our audience.
Oh, I'm not saying that they're in hiding.
I'm saying they don't even they just listen, agree with me and don't start
typing about it.
Well, make yourself known.
Make yourself known.
Make yourself.
I wouldn't say that, but I'll say I am so much more aggressive than any of you three.
That is true.
Person could always return at any time.
They're feeling a regret.
That's what we're saying, Scott.
Why can't they go?
Are they going to die?
The question is, no, you've been putting that on them.
That was the question is, are you saying they should walk this earth?
Never seeing that queue.
But why do I have that power?
Do I control his death as well?
Because we the gods imbued you with that power.
I think there's certainly extenuating circumstances where it's like, oh,
if it's a short amount, you got half a day there or you're you're it's a couple
day trip. If you have some sort of parameters on the trip.
Sure. Yeah.
So you and you have the teleport technology.
Of course, use the teleport technology.
If we're talking a queue that you there are there's a list of queues where you
have to see them at least once you can't skip it forever.
I think Indiana Jones is on that list.
Yes. Yes.
Really number one on that list.
But I also think you could ignore the list.
Wow. That's that's the difference.
That's the difference.
There is the list. We agree.
It's not all queues.
There's a list.
Scott says at the end of the day, he still thinks they're all.
Yeah. He says, fuck the list.
Like you'll help us put it together, but you have no problem ignoring.
I still have opinions on the list.
Right.
I still want to be involved in the list.
I was hoping I was.
Pirates is out.
It doesn't count.
I was hoping.
Boy, I know we end up in an argument.
I know we can't argument.
I didn't think so either.
I bring it is your it's your fault.
I'm a little combative.
I'm very I'm reactive.
I swear more.
That's true.
Team Creeps, which you have now all been on.
Much more body of podcast.
And congratulations on getting Scott and Mike to each read a book.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
It only took.
Snooty snooters.
Oh, smelting it.
I was on. I read three.
I was going to say more than they asked me to.
Jason covered an entire trilogy with us
and a very big trilogy in the world.
It was Fear Street.
It was ninety nine Fear Street trilogy.
He's reading one crime novel.
He's reading one of his crime novels a day at this point.
That's right.
Yes. Well, it's a Halloween season.
So I'm reading Spook and reading Ghost Story.
I'm reading Peter Strab book.
That was the which is the basis
our our love of old actors.
It was a lot of actors.
Let the movie version in 1981 with like Melvin Douglas,
Douglas Fairbanks, Jr.
Like it's all like these million year old guys.
Sure. But how?
Let me ask you this.
Have you listened to a really killer Synthy Baseline lately?
No, you haven't.
And I guarantee you, Scott, I both listened to some sort of synth bass today.
We all have our strengths.
We all have our enthusiasm.
Yeah. So that's I'm just saying if the podcast was about synth
baseline, synthy baselines, then you'd be on it all the time.
Yes.
But that's maybe yeah, that's easier to digest for some people.
I will say I'm just going to do some light roasting again.
Go ahead.
That Mike is in a better mental place, emotional.
Well, we'll find out.
We'll find out.
I did say you had a coffee, so it's a risk.
But so of you,
little Goldilocks present,
Scott read a book.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Three books.
Mike read a Goosebumps.
What's the difference?
What's the length of a Goosebumps takes maybe 25 minutes like a pamphlet.
It's like a yeah, it's like a map, a horror pamphlet.
I need to get like Hypno like a hypnotherapist needs to trick, like trick me or whatever they do.
You probably have ADHD, right?
You got some form of ADHD.
I got something. Something's wrong.
Like I can't read a comic book.
I find it very overwhelming to have to like keep track of the panels and the
sure the word bubbles and the visuals.
But I need a common
but hand me a layman's and I'll finish it on a plane ride.
I need a drawing to show me what's happening.
That's what is going on with me.
What does it look like?
Are there punches?
Mike has patience for some things and that is cues.
Yes.
Do any cue.
Yes. Do your homework.
Do your cue.
If it's a cue, I can handle it.
If there's enough stimulation for me in a cue, but not if there were
if it's cue on Star Trek, well, I can put up with his caddy business all day.
I love Q.
If there was a book that had the chapters
written on the walls of a queue at a theme park, that might be the best situation
because I'm very comfortable and not like fidgeting around in a queue.
It also comes with a lot of visuals.
Yes, that's true, too.
So, yeah, look, I'll get all visual.
I'm trying to grow.
I'm trying to get better.
Don't grow too much.
You can't get unraging spirits.
We can.
You can.
Yes, you can.
But you're not necessarily getting old.
All right. You know what?
Thank you for bringing us this energy that apparently you bring us.
The dark, dark energy, the haunt cast, the fright energy.
The dark. Yes, indeed.
You kicked us off right.
Lizzy K.
You survived the haunt cast, the fright.
Is there a let's exit through the gift shop
covered in ornate paintings of Joe Rody getting stroked by maidens.
And is there anything you would like to plug?
Sure. Check out Infinity Train on HBO Max.
It is a cartoon that I wrote for and is now
unfortunately over, but I highly recommend it.
And also check out my podcast Teen Creeps on which me and my co-host,
Kelly Nugent, review YA pulp fiction of the 80s and 90s.
Right on. We have all appeared on it.
Check out our website.
A lot of fun. Mine was recent.
So you'll find it early as you're scrolling.
So check it out. Yeah, that's the quickest one.
Go check out Scott's episode if you need a quick, like, weigh in because you know the other person talking.
And if you want to hear me say Book was good,
then go to my episode.
Book had no photo, no pictures except for the front.
As for us, you can find us on all the socials at podcast.
The ride merch is available in our T public store.
If you're interested in watching CGI characters interact with real human
characters inexplicably and go to YouTube and look up Tower of Terror,
the mystery, which we have no stake in.
I just want that to be viewed.
And for three bonus episodes every month, check out podcast, the ride, the second gate.
Or what was it?
Hunk has the fright, the cemetery gate at Patreon dot com slash podcast, the right
regular URL still.
Well, that'll do it.
I'm going to go relax after a queue length of getting yelled at.
Yeah, that's a scenario and I'm a man.
And then you may try to chill out until the episode comes out.
And then I get yelled at all over again.
Well, remember, Scott is right.
Sixty nine at Gmail dot com.
Scott Nation.
You're afraid of getting censored.
People are out there.
They're on the run from the opinion police.
Then
you can go.
John is right.
Sixty nine at Gmail.
I'll reserve it as soon as I get home.
Or you do.
Yeah, I don't I don't need to see him
anyway.
OK, do that.
And your support more scary stuff coming soon.
It's going to be fun.
October. So long.
Goodbye.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson,
Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit
foreverdogpodcasts.com and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify or
wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog
news by following us on Twitter and Instagram at forever dog team and liking
our page on Facebook.