Forever.
Dawg.
The happy hosts have received your sympathetic vibrations
and are assembling for an extremely cordial podcast.
A podcast that contains a weird video-screen face,
the cool-sounding phrase, celebrity scientists,
and extreme attic intimacy.
Join us as we continue to crawl through this ride
at a snail's pace. I'll see you all a little later in the year 2025 when we get to the end of the
graveyard. It's Haunted Mansion Part 4 on Hauntcast The Fright.
Whoever knows what to do, do it. One, two, three, pick wick. It's only me after all,
after this studious run of episodes, I'm the only one who went back to find out what we're
supposed to do. We've been doing these cold opens of yelling that we did it last time.
I crammed like I was on a test, but you're right. I have in previous years gone back and listened.
I did not do it. You're right. In the end, I listened to all the other intros because I
wrote a potential intro and I didn't want to try to copy it. God, we've been shamed. I am the one
who brought up pick wick in a recent segment that came up this year. Yes. There was an animatronic
contest, I think for the dormant animatronics who were just sitting around during the long
pandemic. I feel like shit. We have started things. Pick wick in the morning after that party,
you know? Man. Wow. Okay. But now I'm suddenly I'm feeling like a real, I don't know. I feel like my
relationship to these episodes has been at odds before, but now I'm feeling like an A plus student.
I did the homework. That's true. I've been stressed about the episode all day just because there's so
much information to learn and just because these episodes are probably the most tense of all the
episodes we ever do. The most book reporting. I've been feeling, but I mean, no, like just. But that's
what I'm saying. There's no, of course you have an actual book. This is my point every year. Who is
making it be that way? Well, not me. I'm as chill as Pickwick here. It's a regular episode where we
can have all the fun that we'd usually have on our show, which is called Haunt Cast the Fright. We
haven't said the name with this cold open construct. Oh, and also here, see, this is the kind of fun
we can have. We've kind of, we kind of haven't made good on the Halloween names. We sort of bailed on
it. And I thought we should bring, we did it a little bit, but why not? Let's make it Haunted
Mansion specific. And that's why I'm your ghost host, Scott Grimm, Grinn and Gardner. And then I'm
joined by Mike Cadaverous-Palerson. And then of course also Jason Shrouded in a deaf disguise it
in. Oh, I like that. Yeah, that is good. Yeah. So there we did that. And that's what I'm saying.
It's fun. We can have some fun. Here's what I'd say. And if the audience is what we're talking
about, so we've sort of stepped through the Haunted Mansion and it's sort of a point of contention
because Scott's initial idea was to do Haunted Mansion every year. I believe the way you envisioned
it was, eh, we'll goof around every year about the Haunted Mansion. Maybe as if it's the first time,
we'll obviously not try to repeat things, but what do you know? We'll just do a new episode every
week. Cover different aspects of it because there's a lot there. I don't deny there's a lot of this.
Why I thought of doing it. And then what happened was we started stepping through the Haunted Mansion
as if we were doing sort of, yeah, like a book report and then sort of the game, if you were,
if you will, is sort of like pulling us off course on the Haunted Mansion while Scott says like,
uh, is that it? Is that we done? Are we done talking about the chair? Like that sort of become
the game of it. Well, I don't think I sound that snippy, but, uh, that's, but maybe that's how you
hear it. That's how I would say it. If I was, if I was playing a character, um, following a lot of
when, what I usually encounter with that is a lot of no, no, no, no, no. Right. So that's if you were
playing our character, you would be doing that. You would say, no, no, no, we have to talk about
the material of the chair in the hallway. Maybe I'm wrong. Maybe that's not as loud as you guys get.
There was just, was one time it happened and I was like, sure God. Well, if it was over Zoom last
year, I don't know. The fall of 2020 is such a fog. That's true. But it becomes, see, this is what
happens. This is what's happening in the country right now. When two sides just end up on different,
like completely separate, they're polarized, you know? And I believe it actually makes it stronger.
It makes the polarization stronger. So your interest in getting us off course and, and, and into a sort
of a more fun, freewheeling thing gets stronger. Our desire, and especially Jason's, I still think
I'm sort of the theme park moderate here, but Jason, especially he gets stronger to want to make sure
to just, you know, to read the full Jason Searle book to us each year. Yes. It's important. You
have to read us the book. Or what else are we doing? It gets stronger. The two sides get stronger,
you know, as we go along. So I think here's what I think. I was thinking about this earlier today.
I think because this year we've sort of set a limit, I actually think this will give us some more
room, some more freedom. Oh, this is how I felt. By the way, now we've started on this note, but
I've been thinking all day. This is a, this is, I have not been dreading the haunted mansion this
year. Last year, big time dread. There was, as you said, Jason, there's a dread about a lot of things,
but, uh, but I think. Stronger than the haunted mansion episode. No, no. In October 2020, the
biggest thing that I was worried about was doing the haunted mansion episode. I think what it starts
to feel sort of, uh, like my parents taking me to church. That's sort of the tone that I feel like
I encounter where it's like, we're going to sit, it's going to be nice. They're going to do the
homily. And it was, it wasn't that a nice homily. It was very good. Okay. We're going to learn about
the foyer. We're going to learn about the history of porches. We're going to learn about railings.
It wasn't that nice. It's been very nice. I see what you're saying. I do think, and I just had a
mutual friend who I won't say who, uh, people love these episodes. I do think sadly the format
of you being tortured is popular. I think, no, I recognize that it's part of it. Yeah.
So it is unfortunately now become part of it. Now, maybe again, I don't need to force it. We don't
need to do the same thing every year. I don't want it to be contentious. So I, again, I think
this putting a limit sort of on today's episode, I think it's great even now of, you know, and you
say that because there's a little, there's kind of a plan because there's sort of like a stop point
where we think we're, we know we're not going to get to that this year. And, uh, I think that that's,
I don't know. I think that that's going to help things. We'll see, but yes. And now I do recognize
and I'll, you know, if you're going to do it, just do, I'll just call it out. Now I understand
that we're probably going to have to do the thing where there were like, there's like a new ribbon
that got installed this year. So there's an air filtration system that's new in the mansion.
Well, that's not true. That's gotta be the same. That's the pumping right into our lungs. That's
never, that's never changed. That's the Legionnaire disease. That's what, that's how that's. They
touched it. They banged on the tin. They fixed the leak in the roof of like a backstage area
that wouldn't even be where you go. You're walking us right into the new loading area of Disneyland.
That's why I think that's what I'm saying. Let's get it out of the way. I, what I'm saying,
what I, I don't think I'm not expressing enough positivity here. I appreciate that when I asked
you guys when what are, all right. And I was nervous about doing that. I think I played it cool.
When we talked about it, I was like, all right, now we've agreed that we're going to do the ballroom
and we're going to do the attic. And that you said, yes. So it was like, oh, you're kidding.
You mean it's not, the intention is not to only do the ballroom. Now I'm already delaying things by
saying anything, but right. But I just, I want to say to both of you, I appreciate that you said yes.
And that even as we talk about whatever we have to talk about now, that the intention was there
to keep things moving forward. Right. Progress you see, there's a lot going on in both of these rooms.
And I was more surprised. I think that there is more ambiguity in the attic than the ballroom.
The ballroom has like a lot of, a lot going on. Maybe one of the most substantial, if not the most
substantial audio animatronic based scene in any ride. Yes. There's almost like eight little,
seven or eight little different scenelets happening. Different stories happening.
Animatronics all doing extremely different things. It's not, because when you said that, I was like,
oh wait, okay, what else is there has more animatronics? Well, there's like,
now there's the stormtrooper room, but they're all essentially doing the same thing. The presidents
of America and all the presidents are all essentially doing the same thing. But here you've
got dancing, you've got duelers, you've got pick wick up on the, up on the chandelier. There's like
so many types of actions going on. So here, let me, I'm going to go, let me, quick negotiation here.
Yeah. You know, I don't know, it seems like Jason wanted to talk about the ballroom so we could just
start talking about the ballroom. I want to just make sure that Jason's on the same page. Okay.
Yes. Again, again, polarization. Pretend you're president Biden and I'm Kristen Sinema and Joe
Manchin. Hey, that's topical. How that puts us in 2020. That locks us in to, you're both?
I'm stacking my money from every like corporate baron that's giving me donations. You're both of
them basically? Both of them. Yeah. I love that you're willing to be, you're them. I'm the rest of
Congress that's trying to do something. It's trying to get us out of this mess. Okay. And I'm wearing
cat eye glasses and I got a funky sweater on and I'm a piece of shit. So when I say, can we move
past the ballroom? You'll do a big, big thumbs down. Yeah. I, by the way, we do these things where we
like, let's date stamp things the year that they are happening. I hope to fucking God, we don't
remember who the fuck Kristen Sinema is a year from now. Boy, would I be thrilled if that name
wasn't rattling around our social media unless you mute it, which I should. We'll see. Uh, is it,
it's Kirsten, right? I don't want, that's not a thing we need to know. I don't care.
I think it's for KYR. I just want to be accurate so we know which person we're talking about in a year.
And now I, for sure now I can't be shamed again next year. So I have to bring her up and we have
to, we have to of course check in now. That's now part of the haunted mansion is checking out.
Senator Sinema. Uh, okay. Let me, okay. Let me throw this out. This negotiation real quick.
Okay. Okay. So in the past we have done it on the rails. Jason, will you submit, will you allow us
to bounce back and forth from the attic and the ballroom as, as with, you know, uh, discussion
and jokes and humor and a little bit, maybe taking pokes at each other, like we generally do in a
fun way on podcast, the ride. Don't you think that's going to take longer than just knocking out the
ballroom and knocking out the attic? I don't know. I'm just saying for Scott, I think it'll be a more
pleasurable episode if we sort of bounce around in a way normally that we do. There's not, there's
not the seeking of permission to move from run, but again, I feel better on this issue already.
So I'm not so concerned as in previous years where maybe the intent was to get through three or four.
I think we're going to do it. All right. Okay. Well, if Scott, if you're, that's not a big problem.
I was drawing my negotiation. My, uh, I was just attempting to, uh, make peace early, but okay,
let's just proceed. If we all feel comfortable, is there any other rule we would like to lay down
now? Look, I'm just always trying to avoid being, uh, having no stop yelled at me, which I, which I
think, which I think has happened in the past with you as well, Mike. So if you'll, as the mediator,
sure. If everyone will try to not yell no stop. Is there a different command that I could politely
say? Like just a second. Oh, one second, one second. Please. One moment, please. One moment,
please. That sounds fine. Yeah. There's a better one moment, please. I'll say, uh, yes, we're going
to stately manner. Let's be polite here. Stately Wayne manners where I think of that phrase from
the sixties, Batman show. Okay, great. So, uh, one moment please is what we'll be using. We'll be
saying, okay, love it. Uh, that's good. Okay. So I, as far as that, I have no other thoughts on the
actual, uh, follow through. I think we're, I think we're off to a great start. I think this is, this
is very civil. It would be funny if this was like doughboys doing this and she's fucking idiot.
What the fuck? We're on the chair. Um, did you have anything on the, the new additions or did you
want to talk about so hard? So they added, um, yeah, they added the May, December portrait in
the loading area and they had, they added, uh, they just basically dress the area, but it's not
some crazy elaborate, um, um, overhaul or anything, but I do think it makes everything look a little
nicer in that load area. Um, I didn't really notice it. I gotta be honest. Really? Not so much. The
dressing screens, their dressing screens and extra candelabra. What does the dressing screen mean?
Like, um, like a folding screen you would see like, and, um, like to if somebody's somebody's
getting dressed behind it, if Austin Powers was getting dressed and like he had a cucumber and
like a silhouette potential for high jinx. It's not quite like that. Cause I think you can kind of
see through it at the way that they have them laid out, but it is kind of like that size and kind of
like laid out like that. Um, excuse me, right by the loading area. And then they have this portrait
that Jason just referred to, um, that changes. So it's like kind of little stuff. It's not like that
big Tony Baxter overhaul where he talked about how they were going to maybe use the scene from the
haunted mansion movie and load it into the Disneyland haunted mansion. But all I really have to say,
still open for that one. Obviously I am still open for that one. We're still open. You know,
maybe DeVito can pull some strings recently announced to the cast for the new movie.
In the new movie. I think as we record this. Uh, that's fun. Um, so honestly, I don't have a ton
of thoughts on the new stuff. I just think it's a nice little addition to the loading area, which
still is a little spare a little bit. Uh, it could be, it could be a little more lively, but they're
doing, they, they obviously recognize that, you know, it needs a little something. So what Jason,
what do you think? Uh, I liked it. There's a little cat statue whose eyes glow. I don't know
if that was new or I just hadn't noticed it before. Oh, that's a good question. I call it one or two
in the video walkthroughs. A lot of the haunted mansion heads are going to be,
or I have to be mad at some of these episodes when we go, was that there the whole time?
Cause that always happens to me on rides. Yeah. I mean, some of the stuff in the, and now one moment,
please, if I can transition us into the ballroom discussion. Oh, wow. Oh, you're just doing it.
You're, wait, you used one moment to move forward branch. This is an olive branch. I take it. I
accept. I'd shake the branch with you. Okay. All right. Okay. Okay. I honestly can't think of
anything new besides the loading area. I'm sure I'm missing something. Okay. Great. I feel like
everybody would have pushed it. Would I hit the throttle harder if we hadn't all talked about
then done this little treaty at the beginning. That's good. We got everything. That's the,
see, that's what so many of the, again, in this country, you know, that's really the sit down and
talk about it and go over rules and make proposals. And that's what, that's what Ted
Sarandos is saying. Let's just like all get together and, and let's not let content get in
the way of our general understanding. That's what he's saying. And then that's what I don't know.
I was going to make, try to figure out a Bezos joke where he just popped champagne in the middle
of William Shatner tearfully talking about going to space. Did that happen? Yeah. Yeah. Shatner was
like really moved to tears that he went in because he came down from the spaceship with Jeff Bezos.
And Bezos was very bored by Shatner crying and telling him how wonderful that trip had been. And
and a person just like, it was like, Hey, champagne. And Bezos was like, yeah, yeah. Like
in cut him off right in the middle of it. Billy boy. Really cold, really cold. Look, dude, I've
done this like four times or something. I think I don't even know anymore. That was a, yeah. And
Shatner looks real upset, real, real mad to be cut off anyway. So, well, Jason, Jason, yes. Well,
the ballroom scene, I, I mean, my pitch is just moving from sequentially through the scene.
Oh yeah. Okay. We'll see where it takes us. We'll see where it takes us. But that's the intent
to start. Because I think that first, you know, the very first like gag, the, the fireplace,
if you're not watching closely when you transition from the sounds room and then there's kind of a
black, you know, transition hallway, and then you rotate around to the ballroom, you might not
notice that there was a fireplace at all. And there's a little guy on it. There's a little ghost
on it. You're saying it's so quick in the ballroom scene. You kind of miss that too, right? Because
he's like hanging on the bus, like the bus, there's a bus next to him, right? That's the one you're
talking about. Yeah. He's hanging on a bus, which is one of, between these two rooms,
one of a few callbacks to earlier scenes in the mansion. I believe the bust is the same bust
from the end of the portrait gallery of the like stern looking woman. Right. And this is one of the
characters, cause there's many characters here that aren't like officially Walt Disney company named.
And this is one of those characters that's nameless. Yeah, that is nameless. That what I
saw was that Pickwick and Lyoda are the two main ones named. And then later on, uh, retcon, the
bride is named Constance. Yes. And there's other characters that are retcon named later, Victor
Geist, who is the organist in the ballroom, which again, uh, one moment please. Excuse me. I just
getting ahead of myself, but Victor Geist is the organist on the other side of the room. Let's be
careful here. Being very careful. Victor Geist, polite to the water. He was named later. He was
named later as well. Um, so yeah, so Victor Geist, Victor Geist. I did not come across the name
Victor Geist. Now you're making me second guess, but I'm pretty sure it's Victor Geist. I'm pretty
sure. So the characters in the haunted mansion are Madame Leota, Pickwick and Victor Geist,
just a very like character actor from 1968. Uh, yes, Victor Geist is the name of the organist and
he is, uh, and I know that because I have a Funko pop of him. Oh, uh, and he is, but he has had a
different name. Okay. Um, excuse me. Uh, just getting a little ahead of myself, but he had a
different name as well. Uh, alternate version Wolfgang Elias Furlong. Uh, so he also, it's Eddie,
Eddie's grandfather. Uh, but I, but yeah, so, so I'm actually impressed that Disney hasn't tried to
name like what you're talking about. These like little, little known ghosts, cause there are some
really memorable ghosts in the ballroom. Like what you're saying, like if you look and see the guy
on top of the fireplace, I was like, Hey, cause I was trying to do my best today to identify all
the ghosts. I wrote as many as I could see down and I was like, Oh, fireplace ghosts. Real fun.
I'm surprised he's not named a P Jordan Wanderfoot or something like that. Sounds like a native
American character. So I won't know. Don't name him. That's got an E at the end. So now
it's Britishy. Okay, good. Yeah. It is, it is like in the peripheral vision of like you as the
rider seeing it and even just in like the sweeping like panorama of this sequence. Yeah. You know,
I really think so. I've heard some people criticize like frozen cause frozen, the ride and Epcot feels
very spare and there's not a ton going on, but for instance, like secret life of pets, which I think
we all really liked that ride. There's so much going on in the periphery, which is really what
you want. You want like really like cool things that are very easily overlooked on a ride. That's
like too much. Too many characters is great. Yes. Too many characters. Something like what Jason's
pointing out is good on a ride. Something you can easily miss a big character or a fun thing
that you basically just like, huh? Oh, okay. That's a good ride. You know, that's a hallmark of a good
ride. Yeah. Well, you'll never catch everything. Yes. Yeah. Absolutely. So that's this room too.
I mean, what is this room? Like I am excited to be talking about the ballroom in general.
I do need to cut it. I forgot looking. One moment, please. One moment, please. You know,
can we change also? Can you also say, Oh, may I cut in? May I cut in an old time dance? Like a
dance? Like a ballroom dance? If I could cut in, please. Okay, great. Instead of interrupting,
that's what we'll do. And to go back, you'll say one moment, please. Uh, uh, this, I always just
called it the ballroom scene, but the official name in the surreal book labels this room, the grand
hall and on doom buggies labels this grand hall. I saw grand hall as well. Yeah. I looked up grand
hall and in old banner has houses and castles. These rooms referred to as great halls, not grand
halls. Well, well, well, but they were used for multiple purposes. Dining, uh, that's that makes
sense. The household, uh, entertaining guests, uh, one, uh, in cyclopedia, Brutatica, uh, casually
dropped in often where justice was served. Um, uh, yeah. And the, um, so guests dining, uh,
the one thing I thought was interesting that I hadn't seen a lot of places, but I think does
work for this ride, but the balcony, you are essentially on a balcony and great halls often
had what were called minstrels, uh, galleries. Uh, and that's Hey, nanny, nanny minstrels,
not America sings minstrels, you know? Uh, so we are, Hey, nanny, nanny, meaning what era and
place like literal, uh, minstrel, the tiny guitar, like medieval time, you know, like gesture,
gesture clothing. I'm just, I didn't, I'm nowhere in Sorkin. I didn't understand the,
I don't understand some of these, uh, Renaissance, uh, play kinds of old timey, you know, uh, uh,
like mead and a little guitar and, uh, mead, you know, and so like often little guitars are
always full of mead. When you were done with the song, you'd tip them over, glug from it.
You know what I'm talking about. What am I talking about? Cause I can't remember.
I think you're conflating Renaissance fair. Well, I don't know. Maybe it's not. I said the word
Renaissance. Who knows? It all just flattens flattening of history. My old favorite topic.
There's a guy with a little guitar and he's got me in the guitar and it's from a Disney cartoon,
right? Is it like Robin Hood? Am I, that's what I'm thinking of? Yeah. Hmm. Okay. Um, so the idea is
you're in your little car and you're elevated. So that's what, that's what I, the connection that
I made, although ironically we are being entertained by the guests. The guests are not, maybe they're
being entertained by us. They don't seem like they give a shit about us in that room. They don't know.
They're not being bothersome. They're not. Yeah. Like once you get in the attic, stuff's happening,
but like they don't care. The people in the ballroom are reacting to us. Although you know what? Um,
one moment please. Um, I'd like to go back real quick and I don't have a verbatim, but what's
interesting is the ghost host narration before you go in, it's like, says like the spirits are your
sympathetic vibrations. Like they're receiving them. Yeah. So it almost like says like, they feel you
coming. They're like into your vibe. They kind of like, like what you're putting out there and
they're willing to show up now and make themselves visible. That's sort of the read. I get from it.
Am I wrong? Well, these are the first like human, uh, shaped ghosts. There's other, there's like up
until this point, it's the knocking on the doors and eerie eyes on the wallpaper and a guy trying
to get out of a, uh, out of a coffin, but there's not, we don't see a bunch of ghosts per se full
on transparent translucent. Right. So, but so they're really like, you know, you have really like,
you guys have a really good energy. We're really feeling good about you. So like we will allow you
to watch us frolic. We will allow you all the stuff we do nightly. We'll give you a little peek
if you want. Cause long way for the ghosts to say they're cool. Let them be. They're cool. So the
ghost really should be like, they're cool. Don't worry. No, no, no, no, no. Well, you can have an
eternal duel in front of these people. Don't worry. They're cool. They won't freak. He said, he also
says they'll be assembling for a swinging wake. They'll be expecting me. I'll see you all a little
later. So he has to make an appearance. He's like, sorry, man. Sorry. I had to cut out somewhere to
go. Yeah. Sorry to bail. You're going to be on your own for a bit. Don't worry. Hang out. Right.
You're cool. Do you need anything? It would be nice. Is there, I don't know if there's, um, uh,
protocol for jumping way ahead for referencing something many rooms from now. Like, um, if you'll
excuse the, um, what's jumping, like if you'll excuse the, um, uh, like it's like being very
forward. If you'll excuse my forwardness. Okay. That's good. Yeah. Well, if you'll excuse my
forwardness, one thing that I like is that then way you really do lose the ghost house for a while.
And then it's, you're, it's many scenes without him until that, well, he almost forgot about him.
And then I really like the tone of that. Um, you know, that conveys it's, it's been a while,
but he's still happy to see, but like, but the connection I made with him towards the beginning
of the ride hasn't gone away. And he's kind of trying to soft scare you in that point. Um,
it's a little scary, but it's soft. It's soft scare. Um, um, so yeah, yeah. He, he gets out of
there. He gets out of there for two of the best scenes in the ride. So I think they were like,
well, these things can stand on their own. We don't need, you know, it's kind of like ultimately
rise of the resistance and Lieutenant Beck, who we love so much and is always mainly just in audio
for quite a while. Uh, and then we lose track of them. And then at the end he comes back and
you're so happy to see him again, you don't really see the ghost host per se, although that's in
question, I guess, what is the ghost host or not, but it's, I guess a similar format. Like they,
they're willing to say like, you were going to narrate you through this part, but if you're for
a couple of scenes, you could just enjoy it for a while. Yeah. So yeah, it is a similar thing.
Those might be by the way, those are my two favorite, um, theme park character. I mean,
I guess I'd have to put Rex at the top, but like, um, in terms of narration, I mean,
I think I have similar fondness for ghost host and Lieutenant Beck. Oh, interesting. It just
makes me happy to say the names, to think of them as a pair, to think of them hanging out.
Yeah, that's a good question. Um, I mean, like, would you put, um, old prospector from big thunder,
even though he doesn't have as much to do, nearly as much to do. I wouldn't for that reason. I don't
think I get a good picture of them, although I like that voiceover very much. So he needs, okay. So
for in this category, you'd have to have, you know, a decent lengthy amount where you're featured.
There's some, either some shaping the story or a very genuine, you're, you're a guide through it
with an, with an arc and, uh, surprising appearances and reappearances. Hondo and Naka,
does he fit in the same category? Cause he's featured fairly heavily. I like him a lot,
but what I don't like is that then the taste that I go out on the taste that is left in my mouth is
him saying, like, and you did badly here and here and here and after my cut, uh, you did quite
to now enter a hallway that is a, with flickering lights because of what you did. And that's also,
maybe he's faked you out thinking there's another fun adventure when he goes, something is out there
and you go, oh, moments in any ride ever. Is that the oddest moment in ride? You think like a fourth
act is starting and then there is not one. Like an alien is going to go, oh, something's out there.
It's an employee and they're ushering you away. And then I guess, so it's not, I wouldn't put him
in the top three. I think my number three would be Gary Sinise in space guides. I think I'm talking
about guides. Maybe is it right? Is that a different category? Is Rex a guide? I don't know.
Yeah, he's a guide, even though he is like flying a plane, but he's also sort of your guide as well.
He's, he's doing both. He's like, Rex is like a skipper on the jungle cruise, but it's a spaceship.
So yeah, I think I see what you're saying. Yeah. Good guides. So
a great guide. Ghost host leaves. I will say this as a criticism, I've talked about this before,
the sexy and we've talked, I forget the gentleman's name, the sexy ghost host, who is the Spanish
speaking. Oh, Marcos Brazos. Yes. Yeah. And his ghost. That's what we shouted last year. Yeah.
And now I'm sorry, the information's out of my brain. The information's out of my brain.
Listened to last year's episode. He's great. I almost wish he was a little bit more involved too,
because I kind of miss the sexy ghost, sexy Spanish ghost host as well. Yeah. On the ride.
And the guy, I, well, I don't have to say anything if I'm staying where we are essentially,
but I did, you know, this was alluded to in the Muppets Haunted Mansion episode.
And I knew it would be a pause here, but I think it is a good place to say in terms of
voices in the attraction. I do really like the safety warning when the ride has to stop,
which you hear almost every time you go that you get stuck somewhere briefly. I'd say in
almost every ride or at least every other time you go on the Haunted Mansion. Is that
a correct assessment? Yeah. And probably the most specific, like narrow Haunted Mansion reference in
that Muppets Haunted Mansion movie. Yes. Yeah. Yeah. That was a good old nerdy little like,
and a nod to the theme parkiness of it. And that's just the narrative.
Um, you know what I realized? I don't think we really touched on, on that
cameo in that special from Kim Irvine. We did not mention that. Yeah. Because it,
I think I was writing something down when she first came on screen and I heard Piggy go like,
come on, Kim or thanks, Kim. And I was like, what is this? What is this scene? What is this
Kim character? And Shane was like, it's Kim Irvine. What are you talking about? Like, and I was like,
Oh, I, yeah, of course. I like that being said. I like that that is a thing said, uh, sort of annoyed
Jason it's Kim Irvine. Yeah. I mean, she, she has her waning tolerance sometimes for like, I don't,
I don't want to hear about theme parks anymore. Uh, for a little, for today, for today. Oh, I got
to see that declared at your birthday, which did delight me. Her declaration. We are no longer
talking about theme parks tonight. I was, I'm, if you can imagine before that sometimes,
sometimes I had to, I think I'd been talking about Disney Genie too much. We just launched today.
But I, I, I'm glad it was nice of them to, you know, get Kim Irvine in there. Of course,
her connection to Matt and Leota and everything with her mother and her long time imagineer. And,
um, she's always, she's, she's in, she was in charge of like the snow or one of the people in
charge of the Snow White overhaul at Disneyland and the castle when they were like repainting the
castle and stuff. And anytime she does an article, she's like, so like, she really cares about the
history of Disneyland. And she also seems like she's terrified of all the fans being mad at a change.
That's true. But my thing with her cameo is I thought it was nice, but I was like, well,
they didn't really give her anything to do. You wanted a full, more of a full thing. Cause sometimes
they do that like cute thing where it's like a little nod and it just like, it's a brief mention.
I, you know what I am sometimes underwhelmed by cameos like that. And I'd be like, give them a
little more to do. Even just like an, it's a living kind of gag. So you want, she needs to say,
it's a living. She has to say, she has to do the joke from the Flintstones in the haunted mansion,
the muppets, we're already two properties deep, but now we're putting the, now it's the Flintstones
muppets, the haunted mansion. Sure. Jason's walked me into trying to like have to disagree with him
now about what I just agree. And I'm like, yes, they should do more. So she should look at the
screen. I mean, in the ballpark of it. She should, she should, or could she like, you know what she
should, okay, here we go. Let's brainstorm on this. Okay. She should be like changing something
around in the room. A real inside baseball. She should be trying to think of a new way to like
sort of showcase a scene or a room in the mansion. And then she turns to the camera and she says,
please don't be mad at me. And she's talking to all the Disney fans in that moment. Or Ms. Piggy
says, oh, watch out for this Twitter. There's certain Twitter accounts that are going to be
very upset. Are you, does this too, was this changed to woke? Kim, is this too woke? Kim. Kim's just
like close above her, like stressed out. That's kind of what's insane about people being mad at
Kim Irvine. This was even pre those kinds of, to the like wokeness changes. If she, boy, if she
thought discourse was crazy in 2005, like boy buckle up for everything. You'll be making people
yelling at you from changing it from Helvetica to Helvetica bold. If you were, if you thought
people screamed at you when you put other different kinds of little dolls in the ride full of little
dolls. Yeah. Guess what? The internet has only gotten more insane. Kim, we're all mad now.
That one really is like, I like to go to Disneyland and I like to see Mickey Mouse and I like to go
on the ride with the little dolls. Oh, well, you know what? They put Mickey Mouse on the ride with
the little dolls and he looks like a little doll. No, get the fuck out of here. I want to find out
who thought of that and I want to harass them for doing it for months. Well, I am packing my bags
and getting my copy of catcher in the ride and going right to that ride. The little doll, we did
touch on the little doll controversy. I think forever ago. I'm not sure we did, but yeah, if
you don't know, we're talking about insane small world, what 15 years ago, just added tiny little
doll versions of the Disney characters and a certain section of the audience was furious
because they don't belong there. I guess. I don't know. I'm not sure. I think they were maybe
thinking it would be like full size Mickey Mouse just on small world, but I don't know. They added
I don't think I care about that either. Yeah. It's pretty, you know what? That would be awesome.
Yeah. Now also was just hanging out and like a giant Mickey. Oh, I see. Yeah. Yeah. He's on one
of the little carousels with him. Is there a ride where they could add a giant Mickey and you'd be
upset? Not me. No. Well, maybe this maybe haunted mansion. I don't think I'd be upset. That might take me out of it a little.
Hmm. Where would we, where did you put them? In the haunted mansion? Maybe up on a chandelier.
Maybe I'm just thinking it because we're in that room, but huh. You know, in the spirit of
compromise, I'll say it's one of the very old kind of creepy looking original Mickey Mouse dolls.
Oh, with the nightmare mice? Well, with all the shapes are all weird. Everything's like,
like holes or like, like, well, the dolls they used to sell where he's a little more oval shaped
and kind of like, like, is it oval, but it's pointed. Big black eyes of death. Yeah. And it was like the
great depression. So it was like, ah, this is as good as we're getting, you know, he was like
malnourished Mickey. Yeah. Kind of like beat up. That I think, okay, that would be creepy. Then we're
getting into the haunted doll territory. And I like that. Yeah, I'm with you there. A scary Mickey
Mouse doll somewhere in the haunted. I'm not saying they should actively go do this, but if it
happened, if you went on the Haunted Mansion sometime and there was a Mickey there, how mad would
you be? I would love it. Yeah. What if Mickey's hand is reaching up through the dirt and a grave
and it's a glove. Yeah. Yeah. Comes up through the dirt. It's kind of beaten up like he's been
down there for decades. And the glove is a really ripped and it's a little bloody.
So like, you know, something bad happened. Maybe. No, you know what? Not decades. It's fresh. He
just got buried alive. Whoa. Something just happened. That's like art in a magazine. That's
like art in the Atlantic or the economist of like, oh, is the Disney company floundering? And it's
like Mickey coming out of the. They would have done that if the corporate raiders had bought up
the company in the 80s. Yeah. More like a dismal land pitch, perhaps. Or just like there was a
Kim Masters article in the Hollywood Reporter recently where it's like, all right, the Eiger
lieutenants and the JPEC lieutenants are all off the record talking shit about the other ones.
Oh, I love that article. Yeah. I read that whole thing. Do you read that, Scott? No.
You got to read the article. Okay. You'll you'll thrill at the dozen people who gave, you know,
rumors and gossip on background. If you like hearing or reading phrases like Bob JPEC's lieutenants,
Bob JPEC installs his loyal lieutenants, then you're going to love this article. You like the
phrase data driven. Well, this is your this is your Friday night, man. They forget getting is he
taking on like Scientology tactics? Maybe. Yeah. Making people dress in nautical uniforms. My
lieutenants, you see. That's right. Yeah. Yes. He's yeah, it's all boat. It's all boat based now at
the Walt Disney Company. That's why they're moving all the imagineers to a lake because it's going
to be a big boat. Lake Nona, Jason's least favorite place on planet Earth, Lake Nona. I
will be a big boat. I apologize. I told you like we discussed it off air and I came to the conclusion
like, oh, Lake Nona is a neighborhood, not just the name of this weird prefab development.
You thought it was like an office park. It is. Well, I mean, what they're building is like a mixed
use living work office park. But the area, Lake Nona, that's a town that people that probably
listeners of the show I have known with Lake Nona now that I have learned the full. I well, OK, so
how can I politely was there a polite way to apologize, Jason, for that little jab? I just
look at him at me. Yeah, just I just kneels you there. Apologies for the needling, sir. Oh, no,
that's OK. OK. All is forgiven. Thank you. I appreciate that. Water under the lake. All right.
Next to the next to the tarmac. Understood. OK. Where were we? Where were we? Where there's
the fireplace? I mean, do we do we let's talk about Pickwick probably? Well, yeah, let's move.
Sure, we can. We can move up. Yeah, we'll go into the up and then we'll maybe later come back.
We'll talk about John Henry. Too many plans for me. OK, just pick.
Let's talk about the north side. Pickwick and the their their sheet goes up there next to him, too.
Yeah, there's multiple beings up on the chandeliers. I don't know why they don't have names.
They don't have names. Somebody described them was like an ancient Roman soldier. Is that correct?
Yeah, they're kind of this is like a promotional images from when it first opened. And they look a
little he looks a little Roman. He looks kind of like a generic soldier. They're, of course,
paint a blue. You forget. I forget, at least, that a lot of these animatronics are painted the sort of
ghostly fluorescent colors. Yes. And then lights, specific lights are shined on them to give.
Right. But they're up there next to Pickwick. And Pickwick is I feel like Pickwick just because of
his placement doesn't get the play that other jovial fun characters in theme park lore get.
Obviously, the hard chords know Pickwick, but I think it's easy to miss Pickwick. Yeah, because
of his placement. And you can't he's also blue and he's being projected off so you don't get a clear
vision of him. He's not as close as the hat box goes. So Pickwick, you don't necessarily know.
Oh, that's a fun loving guy that I should have a lot of affection for unless you're maybe even just
looking on the Internet and you know the mansion lore. I think it took looking into this more. I
can't say that I specifically knew about Pickwick. Yeah. Previously, the I like when you look them
up and the basic synopsis you get is that he is a plump Dickensian ghost. Yes. A delightful
description of a character. Yes. Yeah, I saw that as well. I delighted in it. What's his real his
full name Erasmus Cromwell Pickwick. It is. That's what it's Erasmus. I think is how you pronounce it.
And Pickwick, it's debated is Pickwick a nod to the Pickwick papers, the first Dickens novel.
There's people also mentioned that Pickwick Gardens here in Burbank, a combination banquet halls,
bowling alley, ice rink in between Walt Disney Studios and Walt Disney Imagineering and Glendale
may also have been an inspiration. Yeah, they call it Pickwick Center. I saw it called Pickwick Center.
But the Pickwick Bowl, I think over here just sold. Am I correct? Oh, no, really? I think so.
For townhouses, it seems like no. No, no, no. Everything. Everything has to be like you heard
sold and that you didn't immediately assume townhouses, which is what everything gets turned
into. Yeah, yeah, I know. Also, you know, it's cool is already filled with listener townhouses.
Yeah, it was not like, oh, we're building there. You know, our bowling alley. Yeah, they're building
what's it called? The place in downtown Disney, Splitsville. Thank you. Yeah. No, no, it's
townhouses in that cool old bowling alley with like it's there's a ton of stuff in there and
people have parties there. And well, it's where I was trying to plan a nice, fun baby shower back
in March of 2020. That was my personal the thing that had to go away when everything went away.
And then there was the so there's the email to everybody like, all right, we're just going to
push this two weeks and then two weeks passed. And I didn't feel the need to send another email.
I think everyone understood the code by then. So I now I'm very sad that Pickwick, this is a
character who's the epitome of fun. I assume from the very little information about him.
Now he makes me think of a baby shower that couldn't happen and boring townhouses that are
getting built. So yeah, you will see when you every time you go through the mansion and you
see him on the chandelier, you'll think of COVID. I think I might. Yeah. The early day, the beginnings
of the pandemic. Well, that's not fair to poor Esmeth's pick. What is the name? Esmeth's Cromwell
Pickwick. It's an update they should do. There's people, there's ghosts of all eras in the mansion
and maybe they should throw in a couple of COVID ghosts in there too. Okay. Modern looking people
tied in the 2020s. They've got a phone with them. Kim is in charge of some of this stuff. So maybe
we just, yeah, talk to her. It just is a nod to what we've all been through. I think people
would appreciate it. Some COVID ghosts. Yeah. I think we've talked about before, yeah, where
these ghosts are from and exactly. They don't really tell you exactly. Like it's, it's two in
the past, you know, that's why you can enjoy ghosts. You can only enjoy past ghosts. There's
like a hundred year, like a hundred ish years where you go, oh, now it's a ghost and that's fun. And
you don't get depressed. There's not like a, I'm trying to think how to like pin a ghost to an era.
There's not a ghost with like Gordon Gekko's slicked back hair and a big cell phone. There's
not a ghost or you know the era. Now you're actually talking, now you're making a better
case for more recent ghosts. Yeah. I think that'd be cool. Just throw in like five, like a ghost
from each decade. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. So one of them, somebody who was on the plane with all the rock
stars, the day the music guy, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Have all of like Richie Valens, a big bopper and. Yeah. Why doesn't it be them? I was thinking like
to not pin and make it like one of their publicists or something. Am I, although is that even such a
thing? Did other people die? I don't know. I forget. I think, didn't I say that that would be a good
ride at a hard rock park? Oh yeah. Oh, that's great. Well, wait, did you say the plane ride or did you
say someone trying to get to the levy to find the levy was dry from the song, the music guy? No,
no. I think that was your pitch was just the Don McLean. You mean what you're saying? Yeah.
American pie. American pie. That's American pie. The ride. Yeah. American pie. The ride.
The secret to actually see the going to the levy, but the levy was dry. The levy was dry.
And then you flip on like, all right, well, time to drive home. Let me flip on the radio. Oh no.
You get the news. Yeah. And then the ride, and then it just kind of ends on a solemn note.
Uh huh. It's a long ride though. Yeah. It's a long ride. There's some God stuff in there too.
Yeah. Have you, uh, you've found faith in the God above something like that? Yeah. Okay. That's
a good idea too. When we get Binkowski on here, so much to pitch him. So much rock and roll stuff.
And then he'll pitch to us that we finance the new hard rock park and we'll all be so starstruck
that we're with the founder of hard rock park. We'll say, yes, anything, Mr. Binkowski, sir.
Then we're now we're like all the money we have in the tank. One month of Patreon, sir. Here it is.
Is that enough? Okay. At least to build it out of boxes or something. Yeah. Um, anyway, he's look,
Pickwick's fun. Um, this is a general thing about the room, I think to acknowledge about the grand
hall. I really love this particular, uh, part of the movement of like, I don't know what the,
the correct music terminology, but like this little section of the grim grinning goes sweet
that now we've, we've heard the song, uh, you know, like creepy and meandering in Oregon.
And now we're hearing it as this creepy waltz, which has such like discordant, like as that
verse goes on, some of those notes are like crazy atonal, right? It's a little, it's like sounding a
little experimental. That's some like, that's some kooky music for sure. It's the atonal. And then
sometimes we're like the original melody, you know, the note, it goes like a step down or a full
step down. Uh, it goes up, you know, they take, do different, there's different sort of notes
plugged in a little bit, which is very unsettling as you describe that. That's part of the feel of
like just being like tossed around in this creepy carnival atmosphere. Um, that's cool. Um, so yeah,
I had that thought as well, listening to this buddy Baker did the music, but not the, like the,
the lyrics of the song were exitentia, but the instrumental, and I think the arrangements was
buddy Baker. Um, it's just great music through, and maybe this is my favorite iteration, although
of course the ending, um, sorry to be so forward, but the, the, the like true part with lyrics is
a lot of fun. Uh, yeah, no, I think, I think if it's any part, I don't know, it's hard to beat
the first time you hear it, the slow version. Uh, if, if I may go back backward, uh, when it,
when you come into the mansion, when you first hear it, I think maybe that's the number one version
of, or the, yeah, the number one way I like to hear the song number two, probably full grim,
grinning ghosts, like jig, but the waltz is, the waltz is up there. Third, maybe third. If I had to
rank the ways I hear grim, grinning ghost sections of grim, grinning ghost. Yeah. And then upon
Wikipedia for the song and there's a buddy Baker asked a film organist named Gaylord Carter to,
uh, he'd done, he did the other organ tracks as well. Uh, like, so that first one that you're
describing, the organ was played by this guy. And then he, he basically described what you're
saying. This sort of like a tonal all over the place. You don't know where it's going, just like
improvise over this, uh, this carnival, this waltz, not beat, whatever this music bed that I made.
And he did one and it was too like, uh, simple or like not cracked out enough. Like he, he had to
go to a different organist who was less a perfect by the rules organist and say, just go crazy
on this. It should be so unsettling and avant-garde. Um, that's pretty cool. I never,
I've not thought about this music being composed and to like sort of the, the wild swings they had
to take somebody was more of a tradition. They should have gone to like, and I'm trying to think
who today they would have gone to like Trey Anastasio from fish or something. You know,
somebody really a noodler, a real noodler, like that type of musician. If they ever play,
are they the kind of band that would play grim grinning ghosts have bands played?
Oh yeah. 100%. Yeah. I mean, buck, we know bucket head. We've brought bucket head up on the show
before a bucket had a solo musician who wears a KFC bucket on his head. Uh, he has played,
I think the house of blues at downtown Disney and done groom grinning ghosts and a couple other
things. He was also briefly in guns and roses when Axel had the rest of the band kicked out.
Um, but yeah, he's played it for sure. It looks like fish has played groom grinning ghosts.
Yeah, that makes sense to me. Yeah. The very good ladies have covered groom grinning ghosts as well.
Ah, there's a bare naked ladies cover. That's pretty like, that's the kind of the end version
of it. Uh, very bouncy. Ska bands for sure. Most of, especially those orange county ones
we talk about with Jordan Morris. Have to imagine. Yeah. So there's probably so many covers of it.
Um, but yeah, I like the, obviously the haunt cast, the fright theme and stuff is all based
on this thing. Uh, our own buddy, Mike Carlson, our own buddy, buddy,
Baker, I guess the Roddy Baker. I think that's good. Right? Yeah, I think so. Um, obviously
musically it's good. I'm just, you know, I don't know past that. Yeah. Maybe was he nice? I just
want to make sure that's your say. Well, I don't, that's not on the Wikipedia. I'm concerned if I'm
being, yeah, they really, that should be one of the things controversy section. That should just be
on Wikipedia when it lists like age and where they're from and like, which is to say like nice.
And then it'll say yes or no. I just would like, it would be good to know. Well, he was the musical
director on Bob Hope's radio show. So if you get along well with Bob Hope, you gotta be a very nice
guy. That's a good point. Uh, okay. So great. Great. You know, he did the music for, you know,
that scary when Disney started putting out VHS is and there's that like laser Mickey,
do you know what I'm talking about? It's like a neon outline that is so frightening. Although I'm
just one of those people who is scared of every VHS logo that ever existed. I know what you're
talking. But he did the music for that. Definitely anything like that. Those, those just frightening
company logos always, which were often would have some just weird sounds like, and I, and I was,
I just didn't know. I was three years old and I didn't know what they were. Like, why, how
can I watch a movie and then there's all these things? So, huh? Yeah. I know. I know what you're
saying. It's just like the, yeah, what if we Google that? I want to see to know exactly what
you're talking about. Well, I'm sure you that Googling laser Mickey gives you a lot of Etsy
results for engraved and etched. All right. Well, we'll do that off air. We'll figure that out.
If I may cut in, if we could take a step back, not chronologically, but a step, but the bigger
picture and talk about this room as the world's largest peppers ghost insulation. Yeah. Yes.
John Henry Pepper invented, uh, uh, was a professor, a scientist. Yes. Uh, may I cut
in immediately? Uh, cause John, he, of course is, do we talk about this before where he kind of like
stole the idea? He's taken sole credit. Well, he's taken credit. Oh yeah. There's like five other
people who are also doing ghosts, the actual effects around this time. Uh huh. Um, but like
it was pepper and then what guy's name is Henry Dirks. Yeah. Uh, Henry Dirks was kind of the guy
who kind of came up with the idea. And then from what I was reading, John Henry Pepper was more
of like a entertainment scientist, someone who cared more about theatricality and thought that
was a better way to teach people on, you know, like a Bill Nye of his day or a Beakman of his day,
if you will. So Mr. Pepper was like, he, he liked to, you know, he was a science guy, I guess we call
him. Um, but he's more of a science guy. And, uh, I think that at a certain point they had both,
they had both like were, uh, uh, involved with, you know, I think they both thought whatever you
would do patent or whatever this idea, but then at a certain point it kind of became solely credited
to pepper and then Henry was pissed. Ah, he was mad. He felt like he got shot, like shut out of
the credit. And I guess to this day, he's right. Yeah. If he had a lot to do with it named after
the guy after a guy, then the guy who maybe didn't come up with the fundamental idea of it.
No. And, uh, to add insult to injury, he didn't get payments for like the patent because so many
other people have been like, Hey, I've been doing a traveling show, Fantasmagoria show for 10 years
with a ghost man. Like everyone went, no, no, I'm not using your technology. I'm using their
technology. Yeah. So there was a lot of traveling ghost shows this, this era, this is so confusing
to me or just hard to picture that like it's like optical pre digital, pre like, like largely not
pre electricity, but pretty like lots of electricity. You know what I'm saying?
Lantern shows and mysticism is the rise of mysticism falls right around this,
this time period because everyone was curious about the afterlife and like modern medicine,
still a little down the road. So everyone just like, Oh, you can stub your toe. Oh, you're fucked.
It was nice knowing you. Gangrene is coming for your ingrown toe ass.
Well, so yeah, I was looking up, can I find some pepper stuff? I didn't know. And he was like,
he did start to, I think people were going, all right, that we've seen the pepper's ghost. Yes,
we know about it. Right. You need some other tricks up your sleeve or not tricks, but you know,
serious science demonstrations up your sleeve. I somewhere saw that he, one of the things that he
did in his show, this, I don't think it was the closer, but along the way he would, he would
he would turn a dog into a string of sausages. Not sure how I don't like to see it. Jason's here.
That's what you do mentally to us. If you're bored by what we're saying,
if I'm just getting real hungry, but that's weird. But then he, he had a big stint of
convincing, trying to convince people that he could do a rainmaking. Like he was touring
Australia a lot. A lot of his act was done in Australia and he did a big rainmaking demonstration
in a town that was suffering an immense drought. And so people did genuinely turn their hopes
to the man who invented this ghost effect. Maybe he can make rain come to our town. That's so
sorely needed. And he'll do it using this big science kite. It was like, it was referred to
in a real book. I was looking at as a scientific kite, but the scientific kite was too heavy and
it didn't even get off the ground, much less create rain from the sky. So this was a bit,
and people just booed him immediately. And this was, and I think this was part of like a,
maybe a bigger collapse for Mr. Pepper because he also, there was another guy touring, as you were
alluding, there's, they had competitors, these kinds of optical magic guys. And there was another
guy named professor Anderson, the great wizard of the North. And he started attracting audience away
from professor Pepper and Brisbane. The Brisbane or is there more interested in seeing the great
wizard of the North because his tricks included beheading ladies, great turning boys into pumps.
I don't know what that means. Like a water pump, I guess. Okay. Like dogs and sausage. I understand.
That's like a thing in a cartoon, but a boy in a pump, those like shoes. Maybe I don't think they
were calling shoes pumps in those days. Possibly. Couldn't tell you. And now I will change a boy
into shoes. Marcus is now a Manolo.
But then also like what's Pepper supposed to do? Cause professor Anderson would give people gifts
for coming to the show. Like sweets of furniture, horses, coffee sets and gold watches. I now
question whoever wrote what I just read. Why wouldn't a horse be the end? You're saying all
you have to do is come to this magic show and you will get a horse. You own a horse now to say
nothing of the gold watch or like the couch. I don't know how you're getting the couch back on
horseback. That's as desperate as Six Flags giving away that crazy meal plan where you get three
square meals a day. If you buy an annual pass. Did you see that viral tweet about the, somebody
running into a woman who went to Six Flags every day, having gotten that pass and ate all her
meals at the Six Flags. It's not a bad idea if you live right there and you're on a budget.
It's crazy. But if you work at the Sunkist building, like you're set, like pop over,
swing by for breakfast. It's assuming that Sunkist headquarters that are next to Magic Mountain,
that's assuming that there aren't immense Sunkist perks or where they might be so loaded up on juice.
Oh yeah. There's so much said as it is. Well, there's not a lot of other options
outside of that office park. I mean, maybe they have a cafeteria, but there's the Wendy's and
the Six Flags and you kind of got to go a little farther. I think though nothing like the only way
that would be, I think better. That's like, it would have to be closer than my kitchen.
Like if the amusement park is closer. Yeah. I don't know what would make that or I would
have to not have a kitchen maybe. Yeah. That's a good point. I mean, it's still like, I'm trying
to think like if Universal had, we live very, very close to Universal right now, but it's still like,
is it worth like, say they had the same deal. You can get three meals at Universal every day.
Jason, okay. Let's ask Jason this. Well, I have to say when I was living at the Oakwoods in college,
the apartment buildings right down the street from Universal and I had a Universal badge,
because I was an intern at a production company on the back lot. I would go over Tuesday nights,
almost every Tuesday night for dollar fish taco night at City Walk at Rubio's when there was a
Rubio's fish tacos up there. You were right there though, but it was only once a week. Say your annual
Are you paying for, what was the parking? You didn't have to pay you out of badge. Okay. All right.
Well, that's pretty good. That's a good deal. All right. Let me quickly, quickly do this. Okay.
You live where you live now, which is very close to Universal. Sure. Very close. Will I give the
address or street? I wish it went in. Okay. I won't. But it's very close. You say you have an
annual pass, $250 a year, let's say. Parking included. So you can get pretty close up there.
You get, let's say 300 and every day, every day a year, you could go up there and have three meals.
There's three hours between meals. You can't get them immediately back to back and like take them
back. How often do you think you would utilize this pass with a free meal? Be like really just
like think about it. How do you think two to three times a week? Okay. For one meal or would you hang
out up there? I think some days I would hang out between meals and work on my laptop. If I'm just
researching in this scenario, I'm working on the podcast. If I'm just pulling pictures and professional
podcast, the Serle book. Yeah. Okay. So two to three times a week. Okay. That's like, that makes
sense. What if there was like a really very good filling sensible breakfast, but you had to go all
the way down. It's next to transformers. You're all the way, you're down all the escalators.
I really hate doing that track sometimes. Yeah. Okay. I know you wouldn't do breakfast. This time
of year when the weather's mild, it's fine. Oh, for the heat, that's your issue. Well, the heat and
yeah, the crowds. I think. Yeah. It's a little gnarly. I just did it for the first time successfully
with my son having to hold him. Oh wow. I had not taken him to universal, but not that not to the
lower lot because that is a two parent operation because one has to have the stroller and one has
to have the child and he boy, he got so squirmy on every flight. Like no, no, no, no, but he made it
great. It ended up working out. I can't say I'm going to do it super regularly, but as we talk
about food and I guess beverage at that park, here's a declaration that me and everybody I was with,
my friends, Tyler and Kia, they have this at Florida as well. I had it down in Florida. They
have it in Hollywood. The wait, is it the Island new bar? It's the Island new bar is the place,
but the Island new blar still spelled the full way IPA Island new bar IPA. We all declared it
the best beer in theme parks in any of them. All of them go give it a try. It's a big haul. You
got to get down to the bottom, uh, you know, and it's on the fruitier end. You might dig it Mike,
but not like so crazily. Uh, we were, we were all in agreement on this point. So there's a take that
I'm going to, I'm going to lock in. They might not have it forever. So I'm just, uh, to any
listeners, very enthusiastic, whether it loves it in Florida, loves it here. How do you feel about
IPAs in general? Cause they got very overexposed in the 2010s. I think not to, not to me. I think
I've only recently been drinking that. And I think it's a very like drinkable, but fruity, as I said,
like, um, I, I almost wouldn't even think about what kind it was. So it's not overpoweringly IPA
ish. I like, I like a little fruity. I like the two ends of this session. IPA, which is a lot less
alcohol or double IPA, which is a lot more alcohol, but very herbally and very earthy. This is like
almost, I think it's 7% or something. Okay. That's about average. I think. Yeah. Yeah. So they can
like thicken it for you, like thicken the, well, no, I'll drink regular IPA. Sure. But it was like
a double you're saying, I guess I don't really have much experience with double. I actually like IPA
a lot. Yeah. Like you got to go try it. And I'm immediately like my like taste budget, like, yeah,
give me that. I like, for some reason, IPA specifically not beer. Right. He does something
to my taste buds. I don't know. Some people get down there. Let's all go down there. Sure. I lost
my annual pass at Hornet. Oh no. I lost it. Yeah. That didn't service. You were already being, you
had so much shame coming into that episode with you didn't want to throw that one out. Yeah. No,
I lost. I think on the exorcist line, I lost it. Oh boy. First of all, okay. Well, yeah, I was gonna
end up being now pretty by loosening the rules. Now we're this is going to end up being three.
It's gonna be. Yeah, we're three hours. We're real quick. Real quick. That shitty little piece
of shitty paper. Oh yeah. Universal annual pass. What at this point in 2021, is this still in paper?
It's not plastic. It's insane. Wow. Yeah. It fades like after like two uses, you've like take it out
of your pocket. You're like, you can barely read anything on this thing. You have it on your phone.
It's crazy. I don't think so. Maybe you can. Maybe I'm behind, but it's crazy. It's the flimsiest
thing in my wallet. Of course it's gonna, it's like, I'm trying to think like what it was.
It's like you're carrying your social security card on you that you've had since you were a child,
baby. Yes. It's like that flimsy basically. I mean, the paper is a little bit more sturdy,
but the ink is rubbing off constantly. Like I've only had it for like two months and I could barely
even see it at that point. And then I just lost it because it gets too fun. I don't know what I was
doing. That's insane. That's the same. Anyway, I'm annoyed by that. I don't think I have a hard Disney
pass. The magic key. I think it is only on my phone. Yeah. Yeah. They not even give you one.
I don't think so. I don't think that. I mean, did you get your box yet? Did you get a box?
Your welcome box? Was that in the lounge? Uh, no, they mail it to you. You're a, you know,
if you, if you register within the first 66 days, you get a box. I don't have a box. What do you mean?
Shipping out. They'd still wait. So you don't have your box. I don't have a box. Okay. Few.
We're Mickey's little key kids. Yeah. We want our boxes. Mickey. Mickey boxes. Okay. Let's,
all right. Let's keep, let's keep going. Let's move forward. The hearst, I guess would be the
next thing. The hearst bursting through the door. The, uh, what little scene let's in the room in
the, in the hearst hall, the hearse. You mean that William Randolph? I'm sorry. I'm saying
the William Randolph. I wrote it down wrong. I wrote it. I did write that wrong. The hearse.
Shut this down. Shut this party down. No fun will be had here. Cool aid manning its way into the
room. William Randolph first as the cool aid man. Thank you for bursting into the room. Uh,
anyway, sorry. The hearse. The hearse. Yes. Bursting into the room. There is an early Mark Davis
concept art of ghosts arriving to the event out of a hearse, but this is a little more like,
yeah, the hearse is bursting into the room and ghosts are getting out of it. That is a real quick
transition though, from hearse, from dead in the hearse to party. Don't you feel like there's a
longer transition you have to make in the afterlife? Apparently not. Great. Let's get right to it. I
think you're right. I could die and go right to that ballroom party. You don't even have to get
like processed through, I guess if you ghost, you're not in heaven or hell. You're in, you have
unfinished business because it's a Casper rule. Oh yeah. So I guess their unfinished business was
we haven't partied enough. Yeah. Which I guess is fucking cool. Go eat, they need to eat more cake.
Yeah. So I like that. I like the idea of it, but it is funny because it's like driver,
take us back to where we were hanging out before. She's like, okay, dead, huh? Let's find some ghost
parties. Yeah. Yeah. Cool. Yeah. I'm on board with that. Has Andrew WK covered Grim Grinning Ghosts?
What do we think? I don't know. I can look it up. All right. Jason, you have more thoughts about
the hearse? No, I just think it's, it's nice. There's ghosts in between that and the big
table, the big table. If we want to talk quickly, move into the table. Well, may I cut in? Yes. And
I want to talk, there's, there's a, they have this, the gag, I would have, you'd call it, I keep calling
things gags. The effect to where like, you know, the ballroom dancers are kind of spinning in a
circle and then they're basically just, you know, dummies on a circular like mechanism that's
twirling them around. Lazy Susan. A lazy, big lazy Susan. Probably not accurate, but sure. But kind of.
I mean, similar. But there is that same effect going on over with a couple of different characters
that are nameless over by the, by the fireplace. And one of the characters has a giant like Captain
Crunch style hat on. Do you know what I'm talking about? I, I, yeah, I kind of know what you're
talking about. Again, this is like right in the periphery of your vision. Right, Scott, do you know
what I'm talking about? I can't quite picture it. There's Captain, I should have gotten a good
picture of him, but there's a Captain Crunch ghost. Basically. And I'm fascinated by him because he's
got that big like old time general's hat on and I'll show, I should find a picture of it here.
There's a lot of military kind of ghosts. A lot of various eras. The Roman soldier on the chandelier.
Yeah, the captain down there. Well, you know, I didn't say about in the Pepper's Ghost effect,
the set that you are seeing is also replicated off stage where the actual physical animatronics are
in matte black and it matches exactly. Yeah. So basically there's a, there's a big piece of glass,
which to this day I go through that room and I don't see the glass. Yeah. Yeah. I never say,
I, I know my brain knows all glad there's glass there and that's what you're seeing a reflection.
The ghost appearing, it's a reflection, but I don't see the glass. I don't never see it.
Someone shot it once. Was that true? Someone brought a small caliber rifle into the park
and shot it like the snowflakes in the inner space. And then they shot the glass, like crack the glass
that happened in inner space too. They, they, they fired at those snow at the like snowflake
atomized kind of things. Yeah. Whoa. And then, which that's crazy. You could just get a gun in there
at that time. And then in Florida a few years ago. Oh really? Like the guy's gun fell out on
like a dinosaur, I think something like that. Yeah. You probably wouldn't have been like,
you get scared on that ride. If you had a gun with you, you might be, you might feel a little
more secure. Oh, you're saying I should bring a gun. Yeah. Yeah. The picture of how terrified I
still am. That thing yells at you. Yeah. Maybe, no, maybe I don't need, it doesn't even have to be
loaded. Just like I hold it for confidence. You'd feel so confident, I think, and not way more
nervous about the gun going off. Not like Barney Fife on an episode of Andy Griffin where his hands
are just nervously shaking. Oh, Andy. Yeah, no, I wouldn't, I wouldn't be like that at all.
This is one of those weird like Snoopy, like it is a real thing and that they didn't, it was like,
like they, you would have to airlift in a new pane of glass. It is so massive. Yeah. So how could they
possibly, it's like that rides down for years if they wanted to replace it entirely. And then
somebody said, why don't you just drape a cobweb over it. And that's what happened. And that, now I
don't know where that is. I, I, I don't have any sense of where the bullet hole hiding cobweb is
in the ride. It was there for a while. Who knows if it's still there. I mean, at this day and age,
they could have figured out a way to seal it like a little cleanly. I, are you still, are you looking
up Andrew W. Where are you at? Oh, I know he has not done Grim Grin Ghost. I'm trying to find a
picture of this Captain Crunch. But this, this version, they only showed there's a lady with like
kind of an umbrella that floats around in that same loop. And then there's another guy kind of
has a bowler hat as well, who I like the look of him, but Captain Crunch Ghost is not there.
So we're saying, are you saying that there's, in terms, when you're saying that there's a matching
set, so all the, like you're up on the second level of the scene and all the ghost animatronics
are under you. So are you saying that there's like, oh, like in the case of the one in the chair,
the old room in the chair. Yeah, so like the rocking chair, this is like the, her,
sitting in a matte black rocking chair. And so that, so then that, from your point of view,
it looks like she's sitting in a real rocking chair. And I think it's so that the gleam of the
object doesn't like upstage her. So like, there's like, it kind of replaces it in the,
a lot of this is like how the mind processes these reflections. Wow. Wow. And then, so how does it
work when, because there's characters at a, at a table. So, but there's not a table over there,
but is there any, is there like a black facsimile of a table? Yeah, sort of a facsimile of it.
There's actually a good video, I should find the link to it, that kind of shows off these,
what look like really like underground pictures. Like we shouldn't be looking at this. Like,
yeah. Like, cause it looks. Oh, I found one here. Oh, this is crazy. Yeah. It's like,
it is like black box theater decor. Yeah. But it looks like they're at a big, they're,
they're involved in front of a big black box. It looks grimy. Yeah.
Yeah. Cause the stuff on the plates, like I, I, the, the woman at the head of the table is
blowing out the candles on the cake and the ghosts appear and reappear, but the stuff on their plates
also appear and reappear. Oh, is that right? Items on the plate? I think. I'm being shown.
I think some stuff appears and reappears. Some stuff is just there permanently. I'm trying to
show you Captain Crunch Ghost, it's not a possible screenshot. It's like down in this corner here.
There he is. Oh, I see. Okay. Okay. So I mean, it's like a, it's a Napoleon sort of,
yeah, that's a good, that's a good, better way to put it. I suppose if you want to go with like a
famous guy and not a cereal box mascot, I'm still not getting the name of the hat, right?
Yeah, no. Does anyone know yet the name of, of Captain Crunch's and Napoleon's hat?
We don't need to know these kinds of things anymore. There he is. Oh, sure. Yeah. Jason,
you don't kind of have that in there? I know that. Is that like what a, like a general would wear
or something back in the, in the day? What was Napoleon's rank? Seeing it as a bicorn hat or a
bicorn? A bicorn maybe or a naval cocked hat. Might be a naval cocked hat. Oh boy, both of those
things are good. It's a cocked bicorn. It's a cocked, it's a cocked bicorn. Got it. Even,
even the footage you just showed, I forget that that's where the old lady in the rocking chair is
because again, there's so much going on in here. She's like right next to the fireplace. Yes. And
then as I said, there's like a lady with an umbrella, there's a bowler hat guy all in that
little loop with the corn, bike, bike horn, cocked, bike horn hat. Yeah. Is that even right already?
If I lost it or anything, we've lost it already. Uh, yeah. No, I think, yeah, it's a cocked bike horn.
Um, lady in the rocking chair is from carousel of progress. Yes. That is a re-create. And,
and it's not the only reuse because, and now I don't remember which rumor if we, well, no,
we want to, wouldn't have come across it already. The, the pirate auctioneer or the one of the dual,
one of the dualers is the, I think the other dualer is also a pirate. Wow. Wow. Which is pretty
clever because it is reuse. Sure. But it's an extremely different context. And maybe if you're
tying it all together, it's a ghosts of those characters or their descendants or something.
Maybe. I mean, you, you set dress on the, the, the costuming, the facial hair, the hat,
like all the accoutrements are different. That helps hide it. Yeah. Yeah. For sure. Um, I,
in this neck of the woods, here's something that I think has not come up in any of the haunted
mansion years prior, although who knows. So if you're somehow listening to this as a series,
or if you're waiting to, I'd like to think that there's a listener out there who's waiting to
binge it until it's done. Like the way week to week, you'll kind of like, Oh, I'm going to let
all of succession air and then I'll watch all 10 in a row. Uh, maybe, maybe there's people who are,
in that case, you're not hearing this. Uh, let them know if you have a friend,
who's waiting to binge them all. Let them know I'm thinking about them. Uh, but I apologize if I
brought this up before, but, um, okay. So there's a couple, I mean, there's a lot of good specials,
I guess, where you get to see haunted mansion stuff up close and get closer to the ghosts.
Uh, there's this early, right when it opened, there was this thing with Kurt Russell and the Osmonds.
That's a pretty good ride through of the mansion as it looked in the sixties when it opened. Um,
but one of the, one of the best ones, I think where you get the most detail is the, the 35th
anniversary special in which it's a star studded special, Ernest is in it, Tony Danza hosts it.
Uh, the Muppets are in it. And there is this long sequence with a kid who goes on the haunted
mansion, who is scared as friends kind of peer pressure him, but there is, there's a pretty girl,
a pretty young girl who says, here, come along, I'll do it with you. This won't be so scary.
And if you guys watch this thing, do you know what I'm talking about?
I, I feel like that, that setup they used, I feel like I've seen that setup before and it
could have just been a rear of the special like recycled on Disney channel.
Like, I mean, yeah, it's a very stock where like, uh, uh, spoiler, the girl who he goes to the
ride with at some point he turns and looks away and then looks back and the girl is gone. Uh, she
was a ghost. Um, but I, I bring it up because, um, these, these actors who were in the sequence got
to dance on the floor of the ball. Like they're doing the ride from the doom buggies, but then
she kind of like snaps her fingers and then they're down there on the ballroom floor next to the
ghosts. So everybody involved in making this thing got to know how, how to do it. And then
got to know how it worked and got to be next to the ghost. Uh, this, this, this whole sequence
is fun. Charlie Fleischer is in it. Uh, the voice of Roger Rabbit playing a scary haunted
mansion guy. The crazy thing about it though, that I'm leaving out is the bookends to this
because it's this long, just like a six minute journey through the haunted mansion, uh, where
you see every scene and follow this young kid. Uh, to the point where when it loops back around
at the end, you forgot the initial bookend was this character is Woody from cheers.
In this all star special. And this is the cold open. There's not even a title card saying the
35 years of it just starts like an episode of cheers and all the characters except for, uh, Sam
and either Diane or Rebecca, probably Rebecca at that point. Uh, they're all there and like,
they're talking about Disneyland Disneyland memories. And then Woody like, Oh yeah, I went
there one time and he, and he flashes to this story and that's all on multicam cheers set.
And then this is shot like a film. That's one of the best things about this special to me.
Wow. Uh, you know, looks at all these rides. Um, but then this, so you're watching this random kid
actor and then at the end he takes the, all that's left of the girl is her ribbon and he's like
rubbing it on her on his face lovingly. And then it flashes to Woody from cheers shot
multicam style, rubbing up like a bar towel on his face and fondly recalling this ghost girl.
He met, which just combining the film and the video is crazy to me to begin with. Then also like,
I don't think cheers has supernatural stuff in the mythology. Otherwise, um, I don't think so,
but if you're, I mean, it's all the characters though, you have to count this as cannon. Yeah.
Yeah. Young Woody met a ghost girl and then told Norm about it. Wow. I have not seen this.
This is, I mean, the whole special, I think it is the best special, uh, filmed at the parks.
And it is, it's very unfortunate that it's directed by John Landis, but he did, he did a good job.
He set up the cameras. Good. Look, I watched American werewolf for the first time a couple
weeks ago. It's good. Yeah. My problems are not so much with the films he makes, but rather with the
people he makes anyway, moving on and the people he unmakes. Oh no. Oh no. Check out, uh, check out
the goat. What are you dancing with the ghost? One of the strangest short films ever made. Um, and
that I bring that up cause that's kind of in the middle between the, you know, there's the table
and then there's the ballroom dancing over here. Does anyone, do any particular dancers catch your
eye or they all just kind of say it's sort of a, it's hard to catch any details there. They have
like different colored hair. Yeah. There's like blue hair. There's like regular hair. There's like
yellow. Well, one moment please. One moment. I have more table stuff. Oh, please. Of course.
Yes. But all right, you may proceed. I have more tables. Oh, one moment please. I also have a few
more, uh, pick quick pieces of information, but Jason, please proceed with the table at the other
end of the table. Um, you know, the, the candles being blown out correspond with ghosts appearing
and reappearing the other end of the table. There is literally, this was pointed out in numerous
places, a great Caesar's ghost. Like there is a ghost of a Caesar of like a, of an effort,
like as in the phrase great Caesar's ghost. Um, uh, uh, another, uh, if you look closely
under the table, a ghost is sleeping under the table is sticking out from underneath the table.
Now I've never caught that, but when I was looking up what Mike was describing, this black box table.
Yeah. I clearly see these legs sticking out. That's really funny. I never noticed that either.
I'm wondering if that is again in great halls, sometimes very far in the past, some servants
at night would roll out little, you know, pads would sleep in the great hall.
Hmm. Under the table. Well, just on the floor in the great hall. I was thinking you were going to
say like, sometimes people would drink too much. That's what I'm assuming. And go under the table.
That could be the other that he, he had a little. I would think that's the gag. Yeah. I would think
they wouldn't like just sleeping in the middle of a party. Yeah. That would seem inappropriate. No,
they'd be working the party. Yeah. So I think drunk. Yeah. Too much mead. Too much mead.
That's probably what happened. And the plates, it seems like there's, um,
people would rearrange the dinner plates to make a hidden Mickey at one of the place settings.
Uh, debated whether the imagineers cared for that. Although in recent years, it seems like
they've loosened up a little. They were mad. They were like, please don't fuss with the ride
to like operation. Like, please don't. You mean like operation, not the imagineers in Glendale
or in future, like, no, no, they would be upset if the people that are day to day keeping maintenance
would do little things like that. Yeah. There's story. There are stories too of people like
someone found, uh, photos under the plates, like a photo of, of a person at the park. And it said,
on the back, it said, this is my mother. She died of cancer. And we always had nice memories here.
Please leave this photo. And they snuck it to an operations person and left it because in a lot of
those place settings, there's a picture under there of what it should look like in case it needs to
get cleaned or stuff. Right, right, right. So you could like pay, if like you see like a janitor
outside the mansion, you go, Hey buddy, come over here. I got 50 bucks for you. I got something to
slip into the mansion and they would go like, Oh, okay. Maybe that's maybe what happened. There's
a transactional thing. That's what I mean. Uh, of course the ride filled with ghosts is going to be
filled with stories. We hear the stories of happenstance, the ashes, of course. Yeah. Um,
but that's interesting. Somebody like slipped a foot. What would you want to leave in there
if you had to leave, if you were to pay off a janitor to leave something in there, what would
you choose to go to know like, Oh, there's something will be hidden in the haunted mansion forever.
Something of mine. Hmm. Well, photo is probably pretty good. You can probably slip a watch. If
you had a watch or some piece of jewelry, you could probably slip that on and an animatronic.
Oh, that's interesting. At first I was, I'll be honest with you. I'll walk you through my thought
process. I went, watch is stupid. And then he said, I'm the robot. And I went, Ooh, really good.
Or a ring. No, no, I think you were right. I'm wrong for initially poo pooing the idea in my brain.
That's actually pretty good. What about just like a, an X-Men shirt?
So when robots could wear it, you slip that on the old Mickey doll, but they placed in the
mansion like a gambit shirt. Yeah. Quick is wearing an XXL Rob Liefeld exports. Yeah. Yeah.
Cable cable pointing a gun goes for $300 on Depop. Yeah. Well, it's vintage. Yeah. Now
Pickwick's wearing it. That would be worth it. Honestly, for just like a couple hours before
somebody noticed one of the robots is wearing a retro comic book t-shirt carnage t-shirt.
That even doesn't have to be retro. That could just be a Woody Harrelson carnage.
One of the freebie Mr. Mercedes shirts. We got multiple years in a row at Comic Con.
Your freebie shirt game is so like, you still have that. It's a menace now. You still have a
thing we got 10 years ago, a free mega mind sweatshirt that you sleep in. When it turns cold in LA,
I'm putting on that XXL mega mind. I was not paying the daily. I was giving up promotional.
Ashton Kutcher screwed all of us and didn't pay us. Ashton Kutcher screwed us. Yeah. We got a
kisser David to a now defunct beverage place. We got, we basically, we, we participated in something
online called an idea jam where we did improv. We've talked about this before. And it was a
bunch of people we know run UCB and none of us got paid. And we got a gift bag at the end that
included a mega mind sweatshirt. It was in a star track. This is the original JJ Abrams star track
messenger bag. Marissa Strickland and I like quickly got rid of ours. I used mine and it broke
within a month. Like it was pretty, like the, these claps like snapped. Like didn't Marissa give hers
to you the messenger bag? No, mega mine sweatshirt. Oh, didn't you have two? I didn't have to. I,
I don't believe I've ever had to. I think I had the one. No, I remember Marissa got a message from
someone. She either went to high school or college with who was editing the videos and was like,
Hey, did you do something called an idea jam? She's like, yeah, this is the first I've wanted
to move forward on non haunted mansion material. As much as I'm curious how many mega mine sweaters
were in play sweatshirts. But if you want to ask, if you want to text Marissa and we'll wait for the
answer, I'm good. I'm good. I just imagine that the hat box goes with wearing a mega mine sweatshirt
for a couple hours and you got to see it. That would be fucking awesome. I did, I did get like
a bubble tea like three years later with that gift card. Yeah. I never used mine. I never,
you threw it in the garbage. It was at Hollywood and Highland. So it was a real pain in the ass.
Yeah. Not the best, not the easiest place. Anyway, so I'm done with dinner stuff. You had more
pick quick stuff. They've, they've expanded a little pick wick legend and like comics and stuff.
And I think this is from the comics. So there's a little more backstory. They called pick wick a
comic mole burglar. So they fleshed him out to be kind of a thief guy and he was very afraid of heights.
Yeah. And in the lore, he dies in the stretching room. And then when he's dead now, he is no longer
afraid of heights. Hence him on the chandelier. Now he's so excited because he's gotten over his
fear and he's drinking and having a good time. It was very complicated. So that's a little lore.
I don't know. It's one of those things where like there's like different canon that no one really
probably follows. Like does the big thunder comic really, do the imaginers really consider that part
of canon? I don't know. Yeah. Yeah. I, the, I, the haunted mansion really is the, it is the king of
attractions where the, all the info about the plot and characters and story are not in the ride
whatsoever. You know what I mean? Like all this, well, which like now I, I was sort of alluding to
this in a previous episode. I, now I kind of know some of the story and what the characters are
because of these exhaustive podcasts that we've done. Before that I went on this ride 70 times
with no knowledge of what any of it is. Well, the genesis of it, it was so long from when
Kenny Anderson was first looking, you know, working with, well to build a haunted house in
the Mickey Mouse park, the small park they were going to build in Burbank. And then finally getting
it built and open in Disneyland. That was like over a decade. Well, we covered that. And yeah,
that took the whole first year. Maybe we should refresh, should we all listen? Oh, that's fine.
If I may be so forward. So yeah, there's so much concept art. There's so many potential threads and
storylines and stuff got revisited or put back in. I think continuity, the idea, and correct me if
I'm wrong, listener or you too. I would imagine most of the people that put this together didn't
even like think of the concept of like continuity and even maybe like backstory. They were obviously
thinking of story, but they were thinking more of like, isn't it funny to have a big hat on a ghost?
Yeah. Like that was more about it. Okay. Like we're alluding obviously to there was a bride and there
was this and a little bit of that, but mostly it's like, isn't it funny? Great Caesar's ghost.
That would be funny. And they all chuckled and they all coughed cause they were smoking. And there's a
bunch of like Tom Collins. Come tell him, tell him, tell him what you said. It's a modern brain thing.
I don't know what maybe the last 20, 30 years to really like desire hard facts and tying things
together. I need to know why he's on the chandelier story. Oh, he was in the stretching room and a
fear of heights. Right. That makes perfect sense. Yeah. It's like, cause it gets, yeah, a newer,
a newer person that had a brain like that was like, I don't know why he fucking pick wick is
high up. Why is he high up? Well, how would he get, why would he even do that? He'd be on the ground
drinking. Doesn't make any sense. I must think of a reason for it. Uh, and then they came up with that.
He was a burglar. So now we know, and now you can rest comfortably. So enhanced going through the room.
Now that we know a pick book is a burglar is afraid of heights, a comic mold burglar.
Is that what I said? Yeah. And they've also changed publishers on the haunted mansion stuff. Who knows
how much is in prints right now today. We can name a couple of these carrot. We can name the
captain crunch guy. Yeah. General what? General general. Great. He's general ghost. And, uh,
why is he, why is he walking around in that circle? Do you know what I mean? Cause he only could walk,
uh, in like square shapes his whole life. And now he's walking around in a circle because he has the
full freedom to from being a ghost, general ghost. There you go. That's a, wow, that's a moving. Wow.
Okay. Next one. Next one. But they get that on the Wiki. Get it on the Wiki. Um, where do we go? I
feel like Jason is still, yeah. Uh, yeah, I, well, do you have all the hair colors listed? I don't
have all the hair colors listed. No. I mean, the big anecdote about the dancers is that due to the
reflection in it is, it is an inadvertently more modern, uh, dance because the women are leading
the men. Yes. It was a mistake is what I read. I assume that as well. Yeah. Um, if they, if, if
you were just looking at the animatronics, but pre ghostified the men are leading the women, but
the other way around, which it's, if you, like, if we said that this was a change that Disney made
this year, they would talk about it on Fox news for five days. If you suddenly, if you made up
that this was brand new, this would be a time. And I guess the women are leading the men now.
And at Disneyland now, even the ghost men are emasculated. Could we like Harry, like Prince
Harry standing behind his wife, his rotten. I think some of the ghosts are in tan suits too.
Like Obama, who I wish were the ghosts. Pierce Morgan is just blood vessels bursting.
Okay. We could really get this going. No problem. We could be on Fox news with the day after this
comes out. Yeah, we could be on Gutfeld and here are the three Patriots who have revealed that
Disney has quietly reversed the dancing position because of the woke mob. Here they are, uh, Scott,
Jason and Mike. Thank you. Three, three Patriots. Yeah, that's our, well, the tagline of our show
is three fearless men in their thirties and we're not afraid to stand up for our liberties,
especially within the theme park sector. Uh, Craig, I'd like to interject real quickly. I
just want to say fantastic monologue tonight. Okay. We were cracking up in the back. Anyway,
sorry. I shouldn't come on here and kiss your ass, but I couldn't know that you're Gutfeld.
You're the king of late night. I wish that was a joke. Actually, you're the highest rated
good. You're the highest rated show. That's true. What are you drinking there, Greg? Uh,
in your coffee mug, Ivermectin. Jason gets tired. Pretty good. Pretty good. This is where you'll be,
there'll be egg on your face in 2022. And we learned that Ivermectin is a complete,
was the cure for COVID. We've all been drinking cup after cup of it. Oh no. And it got rid of my
parasites. You ate so many hot dogs that were made from horses that needed to be dewormed.
Not the worms right out of the horse meat in my hot dogs and took away my COVID. I know it'll be
healthier, but you're going to miss those worms. They really, they give you that kind of sweet
bite. You say hello to them every morning. Hello worms. Morning my little horse. Hey Jason,
can't wait to be in you. Any more hot dogs today? What are the most famous ghost stories? It's a
wonderful life. That's what the inscription in the book says. No man, no man is a failure. Who is
friends? The friends are worms. Inside hot dogs. Inside hot dogs. They cut all those scenes where
he eats all those hot dogs. That's right. That's right. George Bailey, the man who eats the most
hot dogs in the world. It's like dipping it, like he's in the contest, dipping it in the water,
shoving it in his face. The Kobayashi. Jimmy Stewart pioneered that. Oh yeah. Dip it in the water
first. Or having me eat so many for the scenes. So I dip it in water so I could keep doing it
tick after take. Jimmy Stewart invented dipping a hot dog in water to be able to eat over 50 in an
hour. Oh yeah. It goes down so smooth. You're attributed to him. It's like you forget what the
weird hat is called. You forget that it's cocked and you forget that Jimmy Stewart
beat Kobayashi to the bun soaking. That's right. He was doing it in his late 80s too on the Carson
Tonight Show. Oh yeah. He showed everyone in the sound booth recordings for an American tail.
Fievel goes west. He's like, well you probably won't want to see this you youngins. Oh, dial
around. Fievel should eat hot dogs in the movie. Don't you think? All right, Jimmy.
If I may be so forward. Go ahead. If we, let's go north. I think my favorite thing in the ride
is the dueling portraits. I think it has been since I was a kid, or at least it was when I was a kid.
I thought that was so neat, so funny, so clever. I love that they glow red on the tips.
Yeah, you know, the red tip. I wouldn't have laughed if we didn't, if we were punchy from the
last bit. Yeah, yeah, yeah. I would have been fine. I would have been immature. No, I laughed.
Red tips. Anyway, go ahead. Bright red tips. The two men face each other with the bright red tips.
Like a dog. Like a very excited dog. Yeah, yeah, we got it. We got it. Yeah. No, I just, I don't know.
I don't have anything super intellectual to say about it. I just look forward to seeing that
so much and I, and it's the last kind of last thing in the room. So when you're leaving the room,
I keep like a kind of crane bat. Like, let me see if I can get one more shot in there.
How many can I see? Yeah, that's fun. I mean, this is really, this obviously, this room,
this room takes the ride up a notch. You get a little more adrenaline going when you're on it.
I don't know if that's really the way to describe it. Watching, yeah, you're watching the ghost
ballroom dancers and you get so much adrenaline. But it does. It's another level. You got to go
up another level. And I'm trying to think in this room, I like the duel. I'm trying to think, I mean,
I think now Pickwick might be my favorite, but only because now we've really spent time talking
about him and he's so fun. But I don't know. I like, I really like the organ and I, and I,
if you'll excuse me for being so forward, I love the piano and the next scene too. Yeah. So much.
So I think I always focus on Victor Geist, the organ player. Yes. The, the duelists, the painting
based on Mark Davis illustrations. Yes. Mark Davis originally. And this I think is where you start to
see the melding of the Claude Coats, the more sinister, uh, mansion ideas from Claude Coats.
It is. It's the transition. The transition into the more whimsical Mark Davis. You go back and forth
though, cause this is more whimsical, I would say. And the next scene is a little scarier and then
more scary. Back to whimsical. Yeah. Um, but Victor Geist, the organ, of course the 20,000 leaks
under the sea organ. Initially, is it still that organ though? Well, I read that it was,
it was the organ used in the movie that went to that walkthrough they used to have in tomorrowland
when they real quick needed to put some more stuff into Marland. Then they used it for the mansion
and then it was duplicated for all the other mansions around the world. So I think it's the
original. No, I think this is the original. I think I feel like so. Okay. Maybe I read,
maybe I was reading about Disney world then. Um, I also didn't realize until reading today is that
little ghosts, those are little ghosts flying out of the organ. Those skulls. Yeah. Yeah. Which they
did. Well, I think they recreated that effect very well in the Muppets haunted mansion. Yes.
Yeah. So on Patreon, um, the bat music stand, the music stand is large or Nate fat. Yes. And I also
didn't realize that either, which is a real nice fun detail. Um, so Victor and I like, I, again,
I told you, I like the organ. I'm always focused on it. I'm stupid and didn't realize it was for
ghosts. I thought it was like a cool, like glowing effect, but you didn't see it. Like they have faces.
Right. I didn't know that. Yeah. I feel like an idiot. Where Victor got, where did this name come
from? This seems like the most recent Victor Geist as we're, we're inching towards it. I only on fandom
found the name Constance Hatchaway. Constance, the black widow bride I saw come up a lot. Yeah. But
Hatchaway, I didn't see that often. It'd be a newer invention. Yeah. Potentially. Are you saying you
didn't see Victor Geist at all doing research, Scott? Uh, no, no, I didn't really. Cause I feel
like that was pretty common in the thing. Cause I was looking up like who has names basically,
which ghosts have names and he would come up pretty regularly. Um, it's just so like the name. I think
I know I actually do like it. I think it's just as I was saying is we are, we've named almost no one
in the ride except for Victor Geist, the organist, the Victor. And you feel like it's too like maybe
normal sounding almost. No, I just wanted the name all of it. I like, uh, if, like if we're going to
start there, then just like, we just named another captain ghost. Yeah. Yeah. Or, or general ghost,
general ghost, whatever his name was, alliteration. Yeah. But then I would just want to keep going,
like, uh, you know, like, all right. So the dualers, one's Sam Norton and uh, great. The other one's,
uh, Graham Carson. Yeah. Great. Yep. Done. I like, I kinda, I think I like Victor Geist for that
reason. Just not even scary or anything. It's just the name that somebody would have. Uh, uh,
and then the guy, the ghost under the table is a Louis Johnson. Great. Now we know. Okay. Um, and
he's drunk. He's not sleeping. He's drunk. Okay. Let's be clear. Louis Johnson is drunk. Yes.
There's ghost vomit gurgling out of his mouth and he might ghost choke on it. I, I saw that Rolly
Crump, uh, thought that this illusion he's criticized the illusion that's going on in here
as too obvious with like the, like the ghosts on the circle and everything. Like he thinks it's too,
a little too obvious. They should be, I don't know. I don't think so. Cause we don't like,
we're still sort of like finding new stuff. I feel like as a kid, I was, I never knew what I
was looking at or I forget if I've said this in a prior one, but I think I thought that it was like
translucent robots with nothing inside that they managed to build. You know how they've like,
there were those, uh, innovation, interventions, robots that were with no skin or anything.
I thought that they managed to do that. Or it was just like, he's a really ornate, uh, dolls or
not doll, but they're really ornate animatronics that are dummies that don't move with nothing
inside. Like that's what I thought for a long time when I was a kid, I'd never before the pepper's
ghost that it's a reflection occurred to me. So I was always, I really, I never had any idea what
it was for years. I think I thought it was some sort of projection. Sure. Like a straight
projection. Yeah. I think it's so I think when I was like old enough to know it wasn't real,
which I'm sure felt took too long. Uh, I thought it was some sort of like,
I probably wasn't sophisticated enough to think of like, Oh, glass and it's projected on it down
there. But I definitely thought, Oh, there's some sort of projector that's making me see it as three
dimensions. Well, there's a clip of Tony Baxter giving a tour and he says, everyone says it's
holograms because they just don't know how it's done. And it's just got, I guess, like a hologram.
Yeah. Because that's the other thing that you think of when it's like, Oh, a thing changes from
like one thing to another. Yeah. There's the, is that the same, like Tony does a full like walk
through kind of a fun? I think that's, that's what it is. The Roly Crumb thing though, there, he also
has a story about like, we had professional magicians come out and we did the pepper's
ghost for them and we fooled them because they had never seen a sheet of glass that big.
Right. Oh, huh. That's how they got, they just, it had never been done at that scale.
Yes. Interesting. Um, and then I would be interested to talk, hopefully eventually talk Tony,
cause Tony's also mentioned before, like wanting to like spruce up some of the effects in the
mansion. Oh, sure. And I wonder what he thinks, if he thinks this holds up. Um, yeah, maybe,
maybe just the sort of like circular nature. If I was plussing up, cause we, we, I like the mansion,
but we don't talk about improvements all that often. I guess maybe there could be a way to
just make the movements in the same way that like pirate, uh, pirates, the chasing is very like
circular. Like it's, it looks very mechanical. Oh yeah. Part of its charm. I mean, I don't really
care, but there might be a way to do it to make it look not so more fluid. Yeah. A little bit.
Oh, like to have maybe there's some like height variants or some of this a little like up and
down to it. Yeah. Cause like they have Bell and the beast dancing. Yeah. Like crazy in Japan.
Yeah. So if you could, if you can maintain the same kind of illusion, even in the same kind of,
I'm not even saying they should use like something that would make the ghosts even necessarily more
clear, even though I am, excuse me for being so forward. Uh, I do, I do think it would make sense
to like hat box ghostify a lot of the ghosts in the graveyard. That is my eventual opinion. When
we get there is that I kind of feel like you could overhaul all the ghosts to make them a little more
distinct in the graveyard. Yeah. Yeah. Or even just like per this, uh, there's like one that's
kind of fancy. Sure. Yeah. Oh yeah. Cause you miss so many and that's going to be, I mean,
we have to negotiate exactly how many episodes the graveyard is because there's so many, I am,
I strained to see new ghosts every time and I can never tell if it's something I'm just
misguessing for the first time or if it's a new thing, but there's fun stuff in the way back
of that graveyard. Yeah. And I would love to just be able to see some of it better.
But imagine if you're the, the waltzing ghosts, you're so used to seeing them waltzing in circles.
Imagine if you could program them to waltz in a circle, but then every now and then one of them
broke out and like, you would just be like, so a nerve. That's cool. It would be cool. I,
I really, there are, cause there's the people that are like really nothing should change,
but there's a way to maintain kind of the old feeling of even that effect. Cause the effect
itself feels classic. So I think there's gotta be a way to maintain even that kind of old feeling
effect, but doing what you're saying and scare the shit out of people, there's gotta be a way
to do it. I'm sure plenty of imagineers have thought about it, but I'm all for that kind of thing
too. As long as it doesn't completely feel like you're modernizing the ride. Sure. Like there is
probably a way where you do some insane technology and you go, well, that feels way off the haunted
mansion, which now like, like that doesn't feel like the tone of the ride anymore. Well, if I
may be so forward, isn't this a perfect bridge into the next room, the attic? Sure. Uh, let me
just check my notes. Go ahead. Sure. Sure. Sure. Well, y'all said we could go backwards, but
I think we've alluded to this take in the past. I might as well come in hot with it.
Least favorite room in the ride. Two digital, two digitally. Yes. Yeah. I agree with you about the
bride, but as far as the room, no, I, I've been one of my favorite rooms. I think the room is
very interesting. I think the, I like the story of the bride a lot. I do think that face something
needs to be done because that is the most 2006 ass. Yes. Yes. Yeah. Yeah. And that's a, but do you
not also include in that the portraits? Because I don't like the portraits and let me, let me just
say why, uh, you know, like I'm reading, I, I, I get this, this Searle book as well and I'm reading
it and it says at some point, like, uh, uh, you know, if you, and just to, just to refresh your
memory. Uh, so there's, there's a ghostly bride at the end of the room. Uh, and along the way you
see these portraits where her various, uh, grooms over the years, like as you shift perspective,
you see them beheaded. Uh, so she's like killed a number of husbands. Um, and in the book it says,
uh, you know, actually all of the, uh, the husbands were played by imagineers and I'm like,
yeah, no shit. These guys can't act in still photos. You can tell that these are pictures
from 2005 and they're all like smirking. They're all like, it's me. I'm an old timey guy, even
though I'm a man from now. I do. I, I, and now the rest of the room, I dig, I like, I, I, I, I'm not
anything pre the makeover I'm cool with, but this is, I think is a bad example of adding newer stuff
that doesn't totally work. That's interesting because I never struck you guys. I don't like
these portraits struck me, but value you're saying it. I've never actually focused on their faces.
Yeah. Cause I think, well, I think the bride in the, in the portraits and I believe in the motion
capture on the projection played by the actress Julia Lee, the voice is done by a voice actor
named Kat Kresslada. Um, but I think I am always the bride never changes except she adds a string
of pearls every time. Uh, uh, she, with the groom and I think I'm, my eye is largely drawn to the
heads being removed. Yeah. And that's cool. I have no problem, but I just, I think I just feel the
modern of this room. Uh, I, now see, I thought we were all, I thought we'd sort of alluded to this
before and I guess you guys agree with me on the bride that the bride's a little too current shiny
projection. I don't like shiny projection bride. What do you think about doll face 1990s upgrade?
Because this is, I don't know that they've ever gotten this, this bride, right? Chilling. I mean,
I, the interesting, the thing that's interesting to me about the attic is there is just so much
documentation of the attic. Like it's changed multiple times. There was always some sort of
attic. There was a lot of the spectral women, ghostly women, they weren't always brides. In fact,
a lot of them drew emphasis to the beating heart. As you come into this room, you can hear the
thumping sound of a beating heart and it just gets louder as you go through the room. Very loud.
Yeah. It's very loud, but I don't pick up on it when I'm writing the rep, but on video, you can't
not hear it. You're saying you don't notice it. I think I don't notice it as much because of the
transition from, uh, the grand hall into the attic. And you start hearing the piano, the, the
wedding vaults. Yeah. So that's pretty cool. Like that. Yeah. Like that's so interesting.
On the piano. Cause I don't think you can, I don't think, and maybe I'll watch it when I get home.
I don't, I don't, this, the faces don't stick out to me as being imagineer faces. Every time I'm on
I'm like, yeah, I know, I know you guys are so happy that you're dressed in old timey clothes and
I'm Thaddeus old timey. So you can just, they have that thing of like, you just know that it's not,
there's a smirk when you haven't been on camera a ton. And I feel it in these guys. They should
have gotten like more character actory. The first thing that they should have gotten grizzled as
Joe Crespeckler, the guy who played like that old man on those old onion videos. Do you remember him?
Oh yeah. The guy in the woods. And then they hired him to do like a Fox news style show. Oh,
I can remember that. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Like a very grizzled older character. It seemed like he could
be from like a different time. You know how in, I mean, I think of the master, there will be blood.
I guess those are the main, the, the old, the oldest set, VT Anderson movies, like, like every
person you see looks like they're from the past. Right. And then there's other period dramas that
are like Hugh Jackman, like, all right. He'd like, he's got us. He has the flare of this for sure,
but like he does, he seems like a current guy. You know what I mean? He would, uh, I, there's just
something of, and it's, it's hard to, uh, I find it hard to articulate where I doing this casting,
but it's, uh, you, I don't know. These people don't look like they're from the past. Less so
the bride. I think she's fine. Yeah. But these, these guys, I probably, you've probably now
ruined it for me. Good. Cause I think I will focus on it now. This is also going to be one of those
what there's, we're going to see, there's only be like two of them. They're going to be so fucking
mad at me. Uh, but I don't know. I, maybe people are the bride. Most people I would get bet the
bride is most people agree that it looks weird. That like shimmery act. It just feels like hat boxes.
I think people universally love, I'm sure people have some feelings sort of modern, but it feels
like it's in between the spirit of the older. Like, I think that you hit the nail in the head.
I think it's in the spirit correctly. It does feel very modern. I think the pictures never
drew my attention because there is so much going on. I think they did a good job putting in the
story of like, well, and each husband is progressively wealthier. So like the, uh, stuff,
the wedding gifts around each portrait just gets more and more elaborate as the time goes on.
And there's another thing I like in the mansion is that like, as the ride has grown and been
added to over the years, there are contradictions because it seems like the last husband is named
George and they've alluded to that. Like, Oh, that's the same George is on a headstone in the
stretching room, but the widow there is very old and the bride here dot clearly died very young
because as a ghost is appearing as very young. So that's like a weird contradiction, but in the
world of ghost stories and urban legends, there's often contradictions and often additions later on.
Dave Korsunsky If I, uh, if I could cut in what you said about clearly like she's going up in
social stature, this is something I wrote down in the notes that as I saw this quote, the bride
clearly gains in wealth and social stature with each wedding. Mike, do you, have you ever caught
this before? I have not. Thank you. I don't think that's clear. Did you know this before you read
any of this? Again, what we were saying earlier, it's good to have like extra extra stuff that
you never pick up on themselves out. I like it in the sense of, all right, go ahead, Mike.
No, I was just going to say, uh, I was just gonna say, I agree with you that there's a lot of stuff
and I'm looking at all the stuff at once. So I think you're right in the sense that there's
a bunch of stuff. Yeah, I did not put it in contact. I did not realize, ah, she's richer.
I didn't know that, but you're right in the sense that I go, ah, the face disappeared onto looking
at that box over there, that like wardrobe or whatever. Sure. The piano player like, so I am,
my eye is darting all over the place, not looking at a grinning Imagineer from 2005. I like it in
the sense, as you say, is I like it in the sense of like a, like the kind of thing Pixar would have
as a backstory for, there's a thing Pat and Oswald talked about, about how he learned how Monster Zink
is done in this kind of sixties mod style, because that was like, it was the boomer era and there were
a lot of babies. So that's where Monstropolis made their most money was in the city. So like, so that's
all their architecture was put up then. And that's why there's that vibe to Monstropolis.
You never would know that from watching the movie, but it's interesting once you hear it. This is
interesting once you hear it. But if it's supposed to be a story I'm following, I don't follow the
story. Well, I think the, the story that you could grasp just looking at it is like, oh man, she just
keeps getting stuff as she gets married. Like she's killing them and she's like getting, like she,
she is a gold digger. She's like a black widow. That's cool. I like it now that I hear it. I just
don't know that it ever communicated. Yeah. That's interesting. Yeah. I like, I like it. And now I
will pay attention to that. Now I got to pay attention. I got to pay attention to how rich
she's getting. And I got to figure out who all these Imagineers are. I do. It's like, this one,
I feel like I have the most homework now is the attic. Pay close attention. And I like the attic
and I look, it's an overused word on this show coming out of my mouth, but I like the attic cause
of say with me, the intimacy of the room. I like it because it's a cozy feeling room. And I've said
this before, I've said this on the horror nights about the us house from the movie us, you walk
into a room that feels kind of realish. It feels small. And I almost like, I want to hang out in
this area longer because of just that feeling like the most, like a real room I could sit in.
I guess, yeah, yeah. Maybe if we're supposed to be in a real house, a real mansion, maybe not all of
it seems like a place that's lived in or that somebody lives in this area for sure. A lot of
the, yeah, a lot of the mansion is like an abstraction of a house, you know, the sands room,
like what exactly, what is this room? What's actually this room look like when the lights are
on? Who would have this? And the hallway is like, it's really cool, but like the hallway
also feels kind of like an abstraction of a house. Yeah. Yeah. In the sense that we don't get a real
strong sense of where any of the doors go. We're not going through the doors. We just know they're
there and we know it's suggesting this, but the attic is like, ah, yeah, it's an attic. And we're
like low to the ground. Stuff is close by and large. There's a lot of crap in it. It's very dirty.
It's very dirty. It's a lot of crap. Are there collectibles in here? Are there action figures?
Are there Mike's little friends? My little friends in a box? There used to be very early on cobweb
effects, but it seemed like there were too much of a pain in the eye or people would fuck with them.
Like that would graze you. Yeah. I never heard this that you, yeah, you would pass the doomba,
you would pass through it and the cobwebs would like brush against your face. That's nuts. They
would do really great. They have like, they do it at knots still in the mazes where there will be
like kind of strings or something with a little like just to kind of graze you to make whatever
the effect is. And they also do a lot. They do a lot like in the wax works maze at knots
as you're leaving through like these crazy, you know, the giant barrels of wax, you get little
drips of water to make you feel like the waxes is hitting you. That's good. Which is good. I mean,
it's a very effective thing. It's just tough to do on like on a mass scale year round in a ride.
These little, these like very subtle touches. And it's not Disney 2021 to do that. I feel like.
No, no. It's like, I wonder even if the, you know, getting poked in the back is Disney 2021.
Is there, what's the most recent poking in the back that Disney's even done?
I feel like they don't like doing that anymore. Tough to be a bug. It might be tough to be a bug.
Yeah. The two thousands in California adventure putting it tough to be a bug had the poking,
right? Right. But have they poked anyone lately? Have they poked, are they poking us?
They're not poking us. They're not, there's not the universal water effects. Slight of passage
strapping you into that. It's very kind of odd and intimate. It is, but it's not, you're not getting
poked. You're not feeling, it doesn't have a story. The Akron, the mighty Akron isn't poking you all
year. It's breathing. You're not feeling it's teeth against your face. Yeah. It's not, you're not
feeling it. It's red. I'm sorry. Wow. I'm sorry. So sorry. You want the brush of the mind, the,
cause you know that Akron's red tip is quite mighty. They cut that scene. The mightiest you've ever
there's been. One of the new sequels is called the red tip.
Avatar chapter four, the red tip. You know what's going to be interesting with the yearly nature of
these? Will there ever be, and maybe we can make the guess. Will there ever be a year where there
is a haunted mansion podcast, the ride and a new avatar film. Well, when's the one we beat it?
Will we be done? Oh, that's a good question. Is it 2022? I think it is supposed to be next year.
Is it scheduled for winter next year? But we know what happens with this guy. But they have shot them.
They've shot the footage. I know they've shot them. Multiple of them. Not all of them, but I think
at least one, if not two, I've seen the pictures of Sigourney in the tank. I've seen pictures.
I've seen the pictures in the tank. I haven't seen the pictures in the tank. So you can look up tank
pictures of Sigourney in the tank. Look up Sigourney Weaver tank. Sigourney in the tank.
You're going to get pictures of her in a tank top in alien. That's all I'm getting. That's 100%.
And I'm getting tank tops that you can buy with her on it. So I'm getting nothing. None of this
is what I need. Water tank is what I think you have to add now. Oh, she's not a military tank.
Oh, I guess I've seen this. Yeah. So they've shot it. There's a bunch of balls in it.
Yeah, the motion capture. She's not the same Navi. I think she's new characters. Oh,
we're a new character. So I think maybe next year we will be anticipating Avatar 2.
Maybe. I guess I'll feel. The water? The seed bearer? The seed? Which one is it?
Looking it up. Which one is it? Let me look it up. Yeah, Avatar 2. And we'll know the names of the
children by then. That's right. I don't know. I guess they're pretty specific here. I don't know.
I think it's getting like a six month bump. I will say I don't think next October that we will be
two months away from Avatar 2. I don't believe that. Well, they just delayed almost every Marvel
movie three or four months. Yeah, that's what I think it's going to be like that. Like at least a little kick.
And Indiana Jones got delayed another year. Everyone's excited to meet Kingo.
Oh, yeah. They're trying to get Kingo. I've seen this name. I don't know. People talk about Kingo.
I don't know. What is the name? Who is that? What is that from? Is that Kumail?
Oh, Kingo is in the Eternal. Kingo is one of the Eternals. Ah, okay. They were making jokes because
they all got silly names. And when they were like crazy Jack Kirby drawn comic characters,
like, yeah, you expect them that silly names. But when it's just a bunch of actors on a gray
brown beach. Oh, okay. I see. I see. Well, that's what's locked this in when it's Kingo mania next
year. We've all now lived through two Halloweens with just nothing like every child that came to
my door was Kingo. That's right. So mark that down. Is that what year is it? 2021? Yeah. Haunted Mansion episode.
Should we? This is this is good. The first sequel, which could be the Way of Water,
opens in theaters December 18th, 2020. Well, that's your shit in an app. Okay. So should we
start the next year's episode by declaring how many weeks it is until Avatar 2? Oh, that's good. Oh,
okay. A weeks. Okay. Okay. Because if he keeps his word, then we will know the Way of Water
in. This is tough to calculate. It's like a month and a half. Right. So six weeks. I mean, yeah,
wait, whatever it is then we actually don't even have to calculate it now. If it is six weeks when
we start doing if you're if you believe he's correct now, then next year we will be six weeks away from
Avatar 2, the Way of Water. And then after that, the Seed Bearer and then the Tolkien Rider and
then the quest for Ewa. So yeah, next year we'll say Avatar 2, the what is it? The Way of Water
is six weeks away. But I'm going to say maybe I'll give him some credit and say it's not I'm going to
say four months. We will start it by saying it's sort of a spring. No, I'm five, five, it's five
months away. But no, but then they'll but then they'll do it may. I think it is may 2023,
kicking off the summer blockbuster season. Yeah, I guess that makes it five and then add it in that
six weeks, six, six and a half months away. That's my okay. All right. No, I'm lying. They kick off
that summer blockbusters like March 30th now. I believe it will release on time. You might be
right. I believe that's just that's what I'll guess. I don't have any hard evidence. I will make a pledge. I will
sit down and finally watch the first Avatar before the second one comes out. All this time, all this time.
It's the Kron talk. You've never watched the movie. It's all this time. Mighty Akron. I can't wait to meet
Colonel Miles Quaritch. Mm hmm. The Unumtaniom. We'll see it all. Oh, Kate Winslet is Ronal.
That must be new. Yeah, that's right on the first results page. Dr. Max Patel coming our way.
I don't know Edie Falco is in it. Hmm. All right. Look, we're not here to read the Wikipedia. We're here to read
stuff we learned from other Wikipedia. Yeah, from Honam
Mansion Wikipedia. Okay, so here's part of what's feeling my take on the attic. I do. I before I ever
like looked into it specifically, I just remember having the feeling of I liked this room and then I
stopped liking this room and it became once I did the math and realized oh in 2006 there was this
update and there's some digital stuff. I guess that's but I also had the memory of like weren't there
scary jumping heads in this room? Weren't there more like loud screechy jump scares in here? I had
that odd saying I was always scared by those so I was almost relieved to not have those anymore but I
remembered like I think this room is a little scarier and a little darker because there wasn't
this glowy stuff like the portraits and the and the bride was done differently. And then I
then we went to Japan a couple years ago. In Japan the room never changed and I think if you guys go
in the future, if you remember going, if you watch a ride through Mike, it's what it was because
they're on a mansion essentially Orlando for the most part without some of the
except for this because they redid it in Orlando and not until you know I just think it's better.
There's less going on, it's more minimal, it's just the creepiness of the room.
It's scarier, you've got guys jumping out at you, there's it's pretty like cruddy and on strings but
there's a bunch of bats flying around, there's a big bat circle that used to be in this room and
it's not anymore. I just like got off with Aaron and immediately we're like that's that one room
we don't really like is they didn't redo it in Japan. Well I'll say I think the this might be a
case of the story behind this story might be more interesting because if you read online
the upgrade was supposed to be done for the what would 2005 be the 50th anniversary of Disneyland.
It did not get done in time due to shifting priorities and management changes so eventually
they get a management person who was very friendly to Imagineering and they very quickly got this
implemented and in there and done and so this seems like oh I want to hear this behind the scenes
because you always I have always heard I would have first been to Disneyland in August of 2006
so this was my first experience with this mansion was seeing that upgraded bride but like I think
I think this coincided with the outing the ousting of Paul Pressler. But you're saying that the story
of a bride with an axe is less interesting than the story of management changes in the theme park.
I think in our interest the management changes are often very interesting. Was there any mention of
anyone's lieutenants in that story? Well I'm sure there were lieutenants fast and furious on all
sides. That's true I'm looking at this now and I was like oh why why is Scott telling saying this
and I can't I have a memory and I remember it's because Haunted Mansion Holiday was happening when
we were there. Oh right yes that was something you found before we were I wasn't there at the same
time but you were you were basically surprised when you got there that it was Haunted Mansion Holiday
because they don't do it in Florida. Right. They do do it in there and there's more Sally representation
in that version too there's like a better Sally animatronic. Wow. And yeah because it's the because
it's a little like there's a little more like the longer there's there's more to the like first few
rooms there like in Florida. Yes yeah yeah. The first section I should say. Yeah which I love those
rooms are. And I just I just took a look and you're right so so basically yeah in Tokyo it's the attic
is the lighting is much lower and there is that like head popping out gag that you get at the
end of the graveyard scene. Yeah. Are they in evening wear? Do they make them look like tuxedo
cop because I saw pictures of like ghosts screaming I that would scream I do and kind of had like
tuxedo cops if they were ghosts. They're so dark it's hard to tell. Yeah. And then the but the bride
is a like an old or animatronic but the bride looks way better it is a much creepier even
it's like less analog but it's cool and the big beating hall is like a little bit more like
beating heart. Yeah I think it's scarier. And I have seen that I've seen like that with the classic
looking bride from the Disneyland version it's interesting because because I could see it I could
see a better version of the attic for sure than the way it is now that maybe even marries the two
marries it like because I like the idea that it's like kind of uh bridging the gap into the
graveyard and then you get because it's not as scary I would like it to be a little scarier
it isn't that scary now. No. Yeah I don't think that yeah that digital bride is not
scary it's interesting it's not the worst thing in the world and in a ride that was more full of
stuff like that maybe I wouldn't completely but I think it fights with things that were done 40
years prior and don't feel the same. Yeah but I bet there's a way to tonally make the room
even without the heads I like the heads jumping out but it's kind of the same thing at the end of
the graveyard so I think there's a way to do it I think there's a way to like darken the room a
little bit and add some like maybe like mystic manner style special effects that are creepy
because I love I am I'm a sucker I said this probably before maybe I'm a sucker for
the stupid player piano thing with a ghost like shadow and they do the similar thing they don't
really have a shadow on um pirates but it's similar there's a ghost playing a piano yeah
essentially on pirates love it we watched the ghost of Mr. Chicken the Don Knotts classic to
bring Mr. Knotts up again on the show uh you already did Barney Fife in this episode I did
not plan to talk about Don Knotts twice um but as you wear a Grandpa Monster shirt I'm wearing a
Grandpa Monster shirt in honor of one of the craziest things to ever happen to podcast the ride
oh man yeah wow and we should have talked about it up top but oh my god Daniel Roebuck, Jay Leno from
the Late Shift is playing Grandpa Monster in case you didn't get the Google alert that you all had
set for both of those things Grandpa Monster and Daniel Roebuck uh my goodness what news I thought
somebody was joking I saw it on our social media somewhere I thought someone was joking how how
something so perfect to cur right and the house looks all beat up and they all look a little
weird and grungy like it's not super slick and it's like oh man this is gonna be great
this is now I'm not so sure about that I'm not sure about the filmography of Rob Zombie but I
how did he land Sherry Moon Zombie I don't know how he got that one the casting coup in the century
but man Roebuck is grandpa what a time to be a lot yeah yeah will it come out before Avatar 2
yes I think so yeah I think we see that first I think they're gonna turn that around pretty
quickly is it going to theaters or did people say it was speculate was going to peacock or
I think we'll be the city walk opening night IMAX well we will I think I don't know I actually
don't know it's going to Zomber Rob Zombie's personal streaming service ZOMBRR yeah yeah
Zomber yeah we'll be reactivating our AMC A-list memberships so we can hit up Monsters and The
Way of Water you know so we can you know punch the cinema's finest year not since 1999 the
the best movie year has there been such a strong um um I've lost my complete adictory and thought
but yeah I the I I do agree with you that that vibe is better overall that's my I hope this is
not a snooty opinion well in Japan actually it's but I just like I don't know that's it's uh I
swear I'm not putting on airs here I just I do remember liking the room and then I stopped
liking the room and then I went to Japan and I liked the room again yeah I think I part of
the attic with me is just like the desire to go in the middle of the space because like you're
going through the yeah the hallway and stuff so I guess you're in more in the middle of the action
there but but the rest a lot of the ride you're on the periphery you're on you're looking in and
the attic you're going right through it so like you imagine I know there's not as many ghosts they
added a couple ghosts I get maybe it would it would diminish the bride reveal at the end of the room
ghost count but I love going through the room as opposed to because even like the the um
Madame Leota room you're going on the outskirts of the room you're not kind of going I know you
it's not easy to do that but you're not going up right by the ball you're going like on the corner
you're like yeah scraping the wall as you go through so like there's something fun with the
attic about you're going you're going right in the middle of it yeah which I think that's very true
ultimately is really why I like the room but yes I think the vibe could change and put the old bride
in or put a new yeah a new hat box ghost ish turn her brightness down yeah that's all I gotta do
too bright you wanted a little diver uh you know what I saw and I don't know if it's where the
bride is now or the bride used to be there is a room there's a tiny room that they used to use
as a break room right behind it it was also the room where they would service the organ pipes or
clean the organ pipes they could access them um but it was the break room for people working a
position called utility and that was the person whose job it was to kind of like hide in parts of
the ride and make sure people weren't fucking around like people weren't getting out of their
doom buggies or getting too fresh in their doom buggies and so they they would hang out in this
room that overlooks the graveyard like this is where they would take their breaks at wow and so
next year we're going to cover the evolution of that break room uh when they got a microwave
install when they were the kinds of coffee machines they had when they went from a coffee
made to a puree what was the bulletin board like oh how would they list things like as far as like
you know employee like hangouts or something hey i need a shift covered i need a shift cover
were you allowed to list personal things like your band is is playing in fullerton
would you uh would were you allowed to like pass a note about how you could make some money on the
side by allowing guests to give you a picture of their loved one and sneaking into the mansion
or a shirt of an x-men character management catch on to the bribery scheme the bride is wearing a
uh tod mcfarland spider-man spider-man shirt and victor geist is wearing a shirt featuring the
x-men character forge did the wood on the bulletin board did they take bets on when avatar 2 was
going to come out has it been has the bulletin board been around that long right yeah all this
2012 it's a hell of a tease for the next next episode yeah there's a note saying like hey did
anyone catch leota the spiel kind of glitched and she started talking about avatars something
something about avatars and miles quarrich and the way of water did anyone catch that or was
that or was it just me is that one day leota had a premonition and everything that we know about
avatar 2 comes from she got possessed the hides of march or march kuri and retrograde it would just
happen that face looks like you could easily program new faces i could be wrong and technology
might not be that that way but like it feels like you could maybe like give her an avi face for a
couple months so you're talking okay so your idea is haunted mansion if we're getting tired of
haunted mansion holiday night for christmas overlay haunted mansion avatar holiday the way of
haunting or may have spookiness haunt mansion colon rise to the challenge right right yes rise
to the civaco yes uh uh yeah so so maybe make her like have a navi face and then you could just get
a little tie in there but it looks you can redo that bri the bride easily reprojects and the bride
is naffy the bride is navi wearing a like 1800s human wedding veil that's right yes you have to
make all the people in the ballroom taller because the navi obviously famously very tall like nine
feet tall oh yeah oh and then old like navi pickwick is gonna bump his head navi pickwick
okay ceiling there's a hole in the ceiling then you have to make a hole and navi pickwick's head
is like through it or whatever and i think the easy way to do it i think is get get a gun back
in there and start firing okay fire a giant bullet hole in and now navi pickwick has somewhere to go
he has somewhere to go navi pickwick you know what you know what might solve the problem we go the
other direction prequel this man human man used to be much shorter and the human did navi used to be
much shorter prequel james prequel another five what do you think so they evolved they uh grew
yeah they got taller they got taller okay well i'm for that too maybe they're short no we have to
make the human shorter though they started out at three feet okay that's what our shrink so we still
need new robots shorter shorter pickwick navi were the shortest species in the galaxy take out their
chest they're all leg and head take the chest of the robot out and put the head on the legs
i think that solves the problem okay so we got it okay well then we've called it in advance of
maybe this film will come out in 2022 and then in 2023 following the success we'll do the haunted
mansion avatar holiday and we'll review that and then that's going to set us way off course we're
gonna have to do all that yeah we'll have to do all that um but that's okay um we still have
hatbox ghosts graveyard maybe two parts maybe one um and then what are the names of the three follow
you home ghosts they have names too right they do have names they have to wait and see yeah oh they
oh they yeah i think those have retcon names they have like new names yeah yeah so you'll find out
their names in two to three years that's right three years put it on the line we'll negotiate
that later yeah um but for now you survived haunt cast the fright i think a very genteel
addition yes of this of the of the site and i'm glad we talked about it we we we were very well
mannered very well mannered yes um yeah i i mean i think that that couldn't have gone better
all right so we'll see where the mood's at next year and the mood i think it all depends on
avatar 2 if because if it's close then we'll be feeling so warm uh yeah if if avatar 2 doesn't
come out on schedule i don't think biden gets a reelection i don't think he wins it all depends
on he's got a he's got to push camera he's got to fix the i mean right now he's got to fix the
supply chain yep he's got to get those boats to the docks and get us the the toys and food and
goods that we need well and then it's yeah thing after that wherever a camera is shooting there's
a supply shortage of those ping pong balls you put on people for motion capture he has one more shot
to go and the ping-pong the water ping pong balls yep sagorny has just been bobbing in water for
weeks waiting for the last they only need like five right the tank is mostly full and they have
to add the last five balls to finish the final shot but the cargo she's just sitting off shore
been sitting offshore waiting to dock for three months yes she's in the water tank at the universal
studios hollywood backlot she's just bobbing in there she can hear horror nights happening she's
pissed oh my god she wants to go see those mazes and the the balls are right off the coast of long
beach you know yeah look folks we gotta get those ships in we gotta make those we gotta get the
ping pong balls we gotta get people want to see moat cch pounder moat we gotta we gotta
stimulate the economy with tonowary cliff curtis man cliff curtis is the leader of the reef people
cch pounder another fine ithaca oh wow wow yeah i got that ithaca spirit the kids at the college
they go get it they go get ice cream phosphate and then they go see moat
it's not that far-fetched this bit is not that far-fetched where he's
rattling that off he loved it they got at least one ice cream
pilot like that was the bit we thought was hard i forget the name of the president biden will
talk about it he loved it well i was gonna say the one ithaca ice cream pilot lays claim to fame for
inventing the ice cream sundae now to a dozen places in america uh claim they invented the ice
cream sundae yeah i think so so pepper's ghost situation yeah yeah fucking pepper
fucking hog do you think he can make rain we're on the real prestige that article was like it's
the start of the celebrity scientists or something they call the collection of people you were
referencing celebrity scientists yeah a great lineup uh all right well hey what a what a
haunt cast the fright it was um i'll cut this if you don't want to talk about it i i think it's
amazing that at the start of haunt cast the fright you weren't engaged oh yeah sure and now you're
engaged to a guest from the haunt cast the yeah uh and i will i don't want to doubt anybody is that
griffin is it uh uh is it jakey's is it jakey's i don't but a guest from this month of podcast
now engaged that's true yes to our host mike carlson one of our hosts will soon say till death
does honk has the fright have to do that i think honestly you know lindsey was really on the fence
about it until i said that she was the lily to my herman and that's maybe the greatest expression
of love a person could give another person so if you at home are like sort of like i need to
express my love to my partner put it in terms of the monsters and the monsters characters
because i think that could really like kind of tip it over so that's yeah that's what we also to
kind of put a a little you know because we started the month with lindsey and she was telling us this
thing about that you she she has to she if she like divines that a final destination three type
accident might happen oh yeah yeah and she has to say i love you yes she has to like grab you say
i love you before the ride begins right it stresses the hell out of me because she does it like all
out of the blue i'm like yeah hey we're going on this fun thing and all of a sudden the tone shifts
and i go oh my god because like i try to fight that oh my god urge every day of my life about
a number of things but all of a sudden that hits me anyway as you so that's not what happened it
wasn't that you were like it wasn't that you were like waiting for ghost rider and it was looking
especially rickety up on the lift hill and then she grabbed you and this time said i love you
let's get married this time i'm married yeah please ghost rider let's get married uh no it was not
that that had nothing to do with it uh no no you did propose that the freedom center though
because you both love free enterprise that yes that we sort of were just imagining yeah put money
into the economy with a wedding we were just sort of thinking about our shared libertarian beliefs
and uh you have to cling together in this world that's coming apart at the seams we were just
thinking about how you really want everyone to be allowed to carry a gun on a plane and on a and on
we don't like all this regulation mansion ride exactly yeah so that's yeah i mean i'll look all
of it plays a part for sure so i don't want to discount anything there's not one thing but
sure um yes uh engaged how about it engaged how about that such an adult thing to do for now for
scott i'm getting i'm trying to gain on scott here you know he's the most adult of the three of us
i entered at mary i entered the podcast married then then child midway right then child after what
haunted mansion part two right i mean i'm sure these are real distance markers of which and yeah
boy so a haunted mansion right at the the cut right before haunted mansion four engaged um it'd be
i'm not saying there's plenty of time for it to fall apart before haunted mansion five i don't
i don't want that to happen well it would be a story if it did well yeah i mean if yeah if
lindsay hears me maybe at once ever like hears me on an old podcast say to jason like you know jason
you're like my the count grandpa monster to my hermit or something she'll get jealous and feels
like i use the monsters thing a lot and maybe not as special as she thinks it is then yeah it could
be over by next haunted mansion yeah it's possible kind of 50 50 whether i was going to be eddie or
grandpa so i mean i want i think i've called you uh eddie monster before on the podcast uh so i went
with grandpa yeah uh what would you prefer honestly i mean either works look like my adult development
lately is that my lower back hurts like hell the last 10 days was that true yeah that's a new
development my knee has loosened up with uh stretches and physical therapy as my knee has
gotten better my lower back feels like shit your lower back that is the most old man is a real old
man that is the most old man place for something to hurt i know it's awful because then you'll have
to like lean over and hold it while you're walking terrible watching he's watching aw rampage the
other night lying on an ice pack oh man yeah we've grown up a little bit while doing the podcasting
these next phases of our lives and jason has grown up 60 years who are it's getting a lot of good
from 25 to 65 oh grandpa is right yeah uh well let's keep with the the the monster metaphors where i
uh we're we're i'm so excited for you i don't speak for jason's excited for you as well
congratulations mike congratulations lindsay and let's in monster's metaphor you are to our eddie
monster you are our widow's peak because what's eddie without the the famous widow's peak
nothing yeah that's his trademark uh now although you know a good argument for jason being eddie is
that many times over the years jason would come up to lindsay and they'd go hello my me and daddy
and that's a fact that's not a joke he would do that it's a real thing and we go oh god
in a while in the old day a couple of years ago you know it's hard when all your family's back
east you know you look for parental figures hello mommy and daddy you guys are older than me
oh my god
well
he'd go well you know like you know older like i'm younger than you too and i'd be like you're not
that much it's not really that much but look i get it i get it you want to feel baby 85 jason
i get it you know old man scott july 85 uh like boy there's kids there's kids now who were born
in october 85 turning to dust 1985 now when i used to say final fluid gone vertebrae ashes jason looks
at his like a birth certificate and it says he was born in 1965 now he keeps aging decades back
there's some sort of curse put on him it's like the reverse of the marniwik fly photo
yeah something happens like a witch it put a curse on you and you keep aging an extra decade every
year my painting's getting younger and i'm getting older oh man all right let's get out of here you
can you can find us on the socials hey next week we flip back to regular podcast the ride the
horrors are over uh then uh you can find us on the socials that podcast the ride merch is available
in our t public store and for three bonus episodes every month check out what is back to podcast the
ride the second gate at patreon.com slash podcast the ride so chill out everyone the the frights are
done and as for this series we'll see you uh uh with a certain famous haunted mansion denizen in 2022
hell yeah forever dog this has been a forever dog production executive produced by mike carlson
jason sharridan scott gairdner brett bohme joe cilio and alex ramsey for more original podcasts
please visit forever dog podcasts.com and subscribe to our shows on apple podcasts
spotify or wherever you get your podcasts keep up with the latest forever dog news by following
us on twitter and instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on facebook