["The Cemetery Gate Theme"]
Welcome to Haunt Cast the Fright, The Cemetery Gate,
where today we pay tribute to the ultimate masters
of horror, Bush Gardens.
I'm Scott Garen, you're enjoyed by Mike Carlson.
The scariest place that I know of.
Is it Transylvania?
No.
Is it the depths of hell?
Well, and they're great filmmakers is the primary thing.
And that's really what we're,
I think that they'd be great in any genre,
but clearly they mastered horror
is what we learned with today's topic,
Jason Sheridan, I'm sure would agree.
I, you know, when you're running down the list
of big film production companies
of the late 20th century, early 21st century,
you got your A24, your Blumhouse.
And of course you have a Bush Entertainment Corporation.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
They're entered, they're, yeah, well,
they're content silo, which will eventually
lead to Bush Plus down the road,
but they haven't announced it yet.
And I'm, I already prepaid for it whenever they got it off.
I sent them an envelope with money
for when they have a streaming service.
Yeah, right.
So that's waiting, I wrote a post-it note,
here's what it's for.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
Hopefully they get it moving.
And one of the first things on there
presumably will be today's topic,
R.L. Stein's haunted lighthouse 4D,
which is one of those that I think requires the explanation.
This is a 4D film by R.L. Stein,
maybe it doesn't, actually it kind of explains itself,
but I guess the point is that it,
this played in the early 2000s in 4D theaters
in a Bush Gardens, a couple of the Bush Gardens locations
and in a couple of the Sea World locations primarily.
So this is made for Theme Park 4D Entertainment.
And at this point, because I feel like maybe
I caused this topic, or I think we found it organically
in an episode last year and then I was re-listening
to the episode and we talked about that and I said,
oh, that's right, there's that,
maybe we should do an episode about that.
And this is where I wonder if I owe both of you
and the audience an apology.
Well, no, I think I share the blame too,
because I discovered it last year and I got so excited
because on paper, this is one of the most interesting
creative teams in a theme park ride.
We got, I think we got tricked the way
that Bush Gardens got tricked by that,
the sheer volume of talent involved in this production.
So both of you owe me an apology.
It's only you. I never wanted to do this.
I was intrigued by the idea, of course,
but then when I had to watch this thing,
you both, so both of you, if you would,
I'm gonna ask you now, right now,
to say it in unison that you're sorry.
I'm sorry. I have no regrets here.
I'm not gonna go, I don't need to put up a stink
in this case and you were right to never believe in it.
I mean, look, up until when I go, okay, what is this thing?
And I put it on and I went, oh no, what?
Like by the end of it, I was like, oh.
Yeah, that's what you, cause you kind of get the vibe
immediately, you're like, okay, this is like early 2000s.
Yeah. Yeah.
And it's not, it's not abhorrent, I don't think.
Like it's not the worst thing.
It's, it's a lot of it is technically correct,
you might say, but like it is, it is for the,
the strength of the creative team,
you would think like, oh.
Yeah, for sure, for sure.
But I will say this and I don't want everyone to be like,
oh, we got to turn this as a skippable episode.
It is not a skippable episode
because I have found something that I'm very intrigued by
that there's not a lot of information about on the internet
and maybe somebody can help me out,
but it has to do with the SimEx, iWorks,
did I say all that right?
Yeah.
Entertainment group, which is like,
they produce a lot of 4D entertainment.
They have many different theaters.
They do like the 4D movies that you see
that have chairs that move, they can do that.
They can make a ride version of something
and they have a whole expansive film library.
I don't know if you guys looked.
I ended up on the website.
Okay. Yes.
And it went on and on.
I didn't know where to begin.
Yes.
I just went far enough to see the many pages
that you had to click through to ultimately get to
Yes. Haunted lighthouse.
It seems like they're burying this film.
That does, it does seem like they might not be
I'm so proud of this thing,
but we were gonna go, of course we have to talk
about the film, but I think by the, at the end here,
you'll see why I got so excited.
Specifically one title.
There are a couple of things I'm intrigued by,
but there's one title that I love more than anything.
And I, yeah, if somebody knows more,
we'll find out after this episode.
I haven't flipped through the website.
I don't have a guess.
I don't know what's exciting you so,
but yeah, there's a lot in store.
I have a little game to play.
Oh, great.
I think we have a stacked of a lineup
as the lineup of people who made this film
that intrigued us so.
Right.
And because that's why we found it.
It might've been in the tower of terror episode.
That's my guess from last Halloween.
Oh, I actually think it was the European vacation.
Oh.
Because pirates in 3D was one of the
Not 4D? Is that not pirates 4D?
I saw a poster that said 3D.
It may have gotten upgraded at some point,
but the Eric Idle, Leslie Nielsen movie
that was at one of the European parks among other places.
It was a lot.
It held out there for a long time.
This was in a lot of American parks,
but was bailed on mostly in the 2000s.
But it was still hanging in there.
Yeah, you're right.
I think in Phantasialand.
Yeah.
And so I looked up what else like they had
because the Bush Entertainment Corporation,
the current name is now Sea World Parks and Entertainment.
Like, so they-
They wanted to be closer identified
with the beloved brand Sea World.
Yeah, who doesn't?
We all do.
Not a beer company, a company that tortures sea life.
Treats sea life poorly.
And so-
Even having corrected some of the things.
Of course, yeah.
That still is their primary line of work.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
So I remember hitting upon it last year.
We talked about maybe doing it for a haunt cast.
And then I think, yeah, other stuff came up.
And that actually turned out to be a sign from the universe
that we now have discovered.
That this thing is fine.
It's fine.
It's not bad.
It's not atrocious, but it's just a little dull.
I think because you start, you hear the title
and you know from the title that this comes
from Master of Horror, from Master of PG-13
or less horror R.L. Stine.
Of course.
We got accolades right in the beginning.
Who just turned 78 years old, I believe.
Oh my goodness.
Did everyone know he was that old?
No, no I didn't.
I'm now re-cursing him by mentioning him on the show,
but I just, I didn't know he was actually that old.
He must've been, yeah, in his 50s
when we were reading his 25 page books
when we were children.
Yeah.
Thin, paper thin books.
How was he so tapped into youth culture
despite that time being his mid 50s?
That's a very good question.
He knew, but he knew what I wanted,
which was a short read because I was a bad reader.
A comic book brained idiot
who could get through 25 pages in a night.
Honestly, that's probably the genius of it.
The design of the books were really good.
The books stood out and they were quick.
That's always a perfect cover.
Excellent covers.
Perfect recipe.
Fantastic covers.
Excellent covers, great branding.
Great, like looked good on his shelf,
everything like very consistent.
Right, so like a 55 year old dude,
that's how he figured it out.
It wasn't that he was going down
and hanging with kids on the boardwalk or something
and learning youth culture.
I should hope not.
He was dressed like Steve Buscemi in the 30 Rock meme.
Yeah.
Which somebody can make that right now please.
With R.L. Stine.
Yeah, of course.
Those books might've read faster
than a lot of the comic books of the 80s and 90s
because there was still a trend at the time
of a lot of very soap opera exposition,
like over over-dialogue, obscuring the art, I feel like.
Well, look, we could go off the rails.
We could go off the rails.
Yeah, there's just tons and tons of description
and what characters are thinking
and it's a little too much.
Now that's different than compressed storytelling,
which is what comics used to be more of
and then like a Brian Michael Bendis took it
and he sort of decompressed it
to make it look more like television
and then you get so much less story
and so much less content.
So that's a debate we can have on a different episode
about which version of that is better.
Scott, you going out town?
Yeah, I'll let you know my next vacation plans.
Pros and cons of comic book decompression storytelling.
Put a bookmark in Bendis until the next,
which with the baby, look, we're looking at,
it's gonna be like three years from now.
So you got a minute.
Okay, sure.
All right, well, it's gonna be quite an opus then.
Get ready.
Mr. Sheridan's opus.
So look at that, bam, R.L. Stine, part of this.
I said that maybe it came up in Twilight Zone,
Tower of Terror, because this is theme park entertainment
that shares a director with that attraction
because the pre-show of that,
I don't think I've known for terribly long,
the Tower of Terror pre-show was directed by Joe Dante.
This film is directed by Joe Dante,
like Gremlins and Gremlins 2 and Small Soldiers
and Looney Tunes back in action,
which was made in the same window of time as this
and the burbs.
I didn't know that he directed several police squads
and I'd like to say I think that's extremely cool.
Yeah.
What a neat credit, what a cool show.
So, you know, he lit us up.
We like, though, I think I'd maybe declare Gremlins 2
in top 10 movies for me.
Of all time, yeah.
Yeah, so, and then you've got stars
from what is probably, one of them has to be
in all of our top 10 movies, I would think.
Oh, of course, yes.
We got Back to the Future people in this.
Right, two of them.
And that must be what, yes, yes.
Christopher Lloyd is in this film as an old, crazy sea man.
Yeah, that alone, I can understand why this excited,
like, you go, okay, Joe Dante, theme park exclusive.
Christopher Lloyd is a crazy sea captain.
Yeah.
Well, this has got to, if it's bad,
it's gonna be so spectacularly bad,
we'll get content out of it for hours.
Mm-hmm.
That's what you might. It's great.
And if it's great, then we've discovered
one of the great fan, we can be real snooty
at parties and gatherings for, like, oh, my favorite movie.
It might, well, there's, you might not know it.
It got a pretty limited run.
It was called Haunted Lighthouse.
No, no, no, no, not The Lighthouse, not that one.
No, no, no, I'm aware of that one.
It's not that.
It has better actors, I'd say, than Defoe.
Just tearing apart the Criterion closet, trying to find it.
You have it, right? You have it.
It's 25 minutes, though, but you have it.
The story of the ghost children, Edgar and Annabelle,
and the curse finally being broken.
Everything off the shelf on the ground.
Well, fuck you.
It's the only, it's the first Criterion closet episode
that ends with Storm destroying the Criterion closet.
Really good.
I'm burning this thing to the ground.
Haunted Lighthouse or nothing.
But yes, not only Christopher Lloyd,
but Leah Thompson is in this as well.
So you light up at that for some reason,
because then what I started thinking was like,
well, wait, at first you're like, oh, whoa, oh, my God.
So this is a theme park exclusive,
Back to the Future reunion.
And then I'm like, wait, but like, they didn't really,
they weren't in the movie together.
You're saying they two are the characters.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, you know, he's kind of, you know,
Lorraine comes into the garage
and he's kind of trying to look the other way.
There's a great try to not interact with her.
Right, but he does have a good reaction
off of when she's like hitting on Marty.
He's got a real funny.
Yes, that is very good.
Yeah, perfect reaction.
Is that the only scene?
It's possible.
With Christopher Lloyd and Leah Thompson.
He's like sneaking around.
He's always trying to avoid her.
Right, right.
When it's old Lorraine in part two,
he's like in the bathroom,
he's trying to get to Jennifer.
He's on the outskirts of the house
trying to break and enter.
Yeah, they never see Doc, the future family.
So.
It's probably imperative that Lorraine
not really know about Doc.
Right.
That's a good point.
Does Marty even tell her, like in the pre-time travel world,
does he ever say, by the way,
I'm going to the doctor's house.
I'm going to the scientist's house today.
Or is that info left off your mother's worry list?
Yeah, he probably doesn't say that.
Yeah, it's concerning to hear.
Yeah, I mean we've talked about this.
There's Rick and Morty's based kind of on it.
How weird it is.
But yeah, I think that's good.
Christopher Lloyd, who you might know
from the Rick and Morty promos,
probably his most prominent role is as Rick,
live action Rick.
That's your old act?
Or in this older film where he played this guy, Doc.
I think it goes, I go number three, Doc.
Number two, Rick and Morty promo.
Number one, Sebastian Jackal from the UPN show, Deadly Game.
Yes, yeah, of course.
Of course.
He's got an all white suit on it.
And we'll get there too.
Christopher Lloyd selects.
So, but anyway, but you hear that and then like,
but wait a minute, that's almost like,
that's like if you were getting excited about like,
how Marvin Barry is reuniting with Jennifer.
Well, I don't think they really cross paths.
But yes, Trey is back to the future people.
Yeah.
Who else is, there's other, I feel like the luminary list.
Michael McKeon.
Oh my God.
Who kind of, it's kind of a tonal shift
when he shows up and gets line at the end.
Like they cram all the jokes in the last like two minutes.
Yeah, the only time there's any life to it
is the last like minute or two.
It's when they're doing some bits.
Yes.
You kind of suspect that maybe he brought
some of that to the table.
Perhaps.
Like he's got to keep this interesting for himself.
What can only be described as a perplexing cameo
by weird Al Yankovic.
That's true.
Yes.
Extremely, because he does not really fit
into this list that we've given.
Other than that, like it's, you know,
think about who makes cameos in Gremlins 2.
Like I guess Joe Dante likes oddballs.
Right, that's true.
So sure weird Al would show up for a second.
An interest in 3D film.
What with his state fair exclusive 3D movie, Al's Brain.
That's true.
So yeah, you got a weird Al.
You got Rachel Hunter from the Stacey's mom video.
Is that right?
I believe so.
Wait, so who's that in the Stacey's mom video?
She's Stacey's mom.
Oh, that's Stacey's mom.
She has it going on.
Mm-hmm.
Wait, so who is, who is she in this?
Oh yeah, I have it written down here.
Rich Widow.
Yeah, yeah, Jason has it.
Rich Widow Feeny.
Which I don't, when does she show up?
I'm not sure.
She's listed on the IMDB.
It's not coming to me.
They talk about her.
It doesn't really pay off.
No, it doesn't pay off.
My guess is maybe she was cut.
She might have been cut.
Yeah, wait a sec.
The big name.
Behind the scenes, the other big name.
R.L. Stine has a story by credit.
The written by credit goes to Sam Ham,
who was the co-writer of the Tim Burton Batman
and has the story credit on Batman Returns.
Yeah.
And is currently writing the new Batman 89 comic.
Oh yeah.
They're continuing Batman from Batman 89.
In the same way that I wanna do Batman Forever Two,
they are now doing this for the original Batman,
but in comic book form.
So you get Billy Dee Williams Two-Face in the comic.
Oh, that's cool.
Which is cool.
Okay.
Yeah, because it's a specific world.
And now that we're fracturing all these things off.
And Burton is different than Schumacher.
Yes.
In Ferrier, obviously.
Of course, yeah.
People are like, Batman Returns is the best one.
Batman Forever is the best one.
And we all agree.
But let's not lose the idea of a Batman and Robin Two.
Of course.
Where you amp up the ice puns too.
There's like three per line.
You just go, you almost like one person draws it,
one person writes most of the dialogue
and then someone else spends a full year doing nothing
but thinking of ice puns for Mr. Freeze.
Oh yes.
That is not a joke at all.
People put that one down, but that would be so good.
It's gotta be a whole other level.
The Pattinson.
Or why else bring it back?
So moody, so moody, this Pattinson trailer.
I'm sure I'll like it.
I like everything with Batman in it.
But let's get some puns back in there.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know?
Elsewhere in the Luminary,
I think this one might top all of them.
Because, so this is a, you know, we'll get into it maybe.
But it's about, basically about two modern children
who run into two children who have a little more
of a backstory, who are not like, who seem normal at first
but then there is more than meets the eye.
And there is a young actor in it named Bobby Edner.
And I looked up Bobby Edner's credits and guess what?
We got a little bit more music video Luminary,
early 2000s music video Luminary
because I'd like to show you Mr. Edner's work.
And I think you'll recognize what this is right away.
Okay.
Oh yeah, of course.
Oh yes, he's that kid.
Wow.
He's the dance, he's the Michael Jackson dancing kid
in Alien Ant Farm Smooth Criminal.
Wow, now that's huge.
That might be the most impressive credit
of any that I've just said.
And he certainly does some dancing in this.
Yeah.
Doesn't it connect that you're like, wait a minute,
why is that dancing part in there?
Well, I guess you got, when you got the master,
he was a little dancer.
You got the Edmeister.
Wow.
You gotta have him do it.
Stacey's mom and the dancing boy.
Stacey's mom and.
Even though she's not in it,
but Stacey's mom and the dancing boy.
The idea that Stacey's mom might've been in it
and then this kid.
He's disgust.
Stacey's mom is disgust in the movie for sure.
It's a plot point.
But it's possibly cut.
Back on board.
We should have done this last.
This would have fooled our spirits so much
during quarantine.
Discovering both these two facts.
But I don't know if it would have,
but it might've bummed us out because I don't,
it was so jarring to rewatch the alien ant farm video,
which I regret having not revisited for too long.
Nice to have you back in my life, old friend.
Oh yeah.
But seeing that the kid is dancing around in a mask.
Oh wow, interesting.
Which is I guess a Michael Jackson reference.
Because I guess around that in the later years,
he was in a mask usually.
That was his mask period.
But that went way over my head because I just,
now we now masks, now we're all Michael Jackson
is something I like to say as often as possible.
Well, not freedom fighters like Eric Clapton,
but yeah, a lot of us are.
That's what he's trying to avoid.
I don't want to be like Jekko.
I like Kanye's doing the new mask.
The Kanye's doing that real weird rubber mask.
The Carl Havoc mask, yeah.
Yeah.
Look, we talked about, he stole that from Will.i.am.
Will.i.am, we talked about this months ago.
Will.i.am's been in the rubber mask game
for almost as long as Batman.
And I laughed about it.
My whole thing was he's doing a mask
at the end of the pandemic.
And now it's not at the end of the pandemic.
And let me tell you,
Zupermask is getting as many likes on its tweets as ever.
That being two.
So there's been no dip for the Zupermask social footprint.
Scott, let me ask you a question.
Will, to prepare yourself for Ghostbusters Afterlife,
will you be revisiting the alien ant farm video
for the song Movies?
Where they do address the Ghostbusters.
This has come up before on the show, I believe.
We talked about Movies last year, I think, you and I.
And I don't think Scott maybe didn't know Movies
off the top of his head.
Maybe, yeah, do I know it because you brought it up before?
It was, I believe, the first single from this album,
which I didn't have,
but it was not as nearly as big of a hit
as Smooth Criminal, the cover.
Of course, yeah, yeah.
So they are Ghostbusters in it, huh?
Both these videos played quite a bit on MTV and VH1.
But the alien ant farm, Smooth Criminal,
I think more for sure.
Oh yeah.
VH1 countdown, I mean, we talked about the VH1 countdown
with Amer Halim that I used to watch.
Amer Balim.
Amer Halim.
Amer Balim is the guy, he would host it,
and I would watch it for a year.
My family would watch it for years.
I watched other, I was probably more up on the AJ Hammer era.
Okay.
Yeah, I just remember like, he's like,
and then coming in at number three,
Paul McCartney's Lonely Road from Driving Rain.
And I'm like, oh wow, it made it to three, yes.
So good, keep climbing, Paul.
I watched it the most, I think,
when Meredith Brooke's bitch was on Dethronable.
Yeah, she was on there for like a year straight,
I feel like.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I like that song, I'll stand by that song.
I like that song too.
Yeah.
Jason, what do you feel about it?
The song again, Bitch.
I'm a bitch.
Yeah, I do like that song.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's a little crass, but I like it.
I should try.
I should try waking up tomorrow
and singing that to myself in the mirror
and see how I feel.
See what pep that puts in my step for the day.
Oh man, can we just talk about the top 10 countdown
for the rest of the show?
Well, then we'd be back to what I,
that's what I'd be doing right now at Erin
if I wasn't recording a podcast.
Sure, yeah, yeah.
I used to watch like 2001, 2002,
I was like a counselor at a summer theater camp
and like eating breakfast before I went in.
I would watch on VH at one,
would just play music videos for like two or three hours
in the morning with like some commercials,
but very little interruption.
Hmm, well that's what you want.
Yeah.
I don't know, I want rankings,
I wanna know where everybody's at.
I wanna know the arbitrary.
Oh, I like the rankings.
Made up, decided by MTV executive Van Toffler ratings
are based on nothing.
Yeah, let's just go, we'll just,
we'll start reviewing countdown weeks.
We'll go back to April 2001 and see how we feel about it.
If somebody, yeah, yeah.
I'm gonna say REM's imitation of life on this same countdown.
I mean, that's good.
It is good, yeah.
Yeah, mm-hmm.
There's all the detail packed into it.
Anyway, we're here to talk about
something that's slightly longer than a music video.
So yeah, look, that lineup of people,
you gotta be intrigued by that.
And I think like, do you guys have in your head
like what you pictured this was before?
Like, I feel like I picked,
I also think I thought it would work for Haunt Kiss
the fact that I thought it'd be scary.
And I guess it's not, look,
realizing, oh, it's a family thing.
I shouldn't have been surprised.
But I think I just maybe wanted more.
I thought I'd feel more Dante in there.
Well, there is, I do remember,
I think I saw this when I went to
Busch Gardens Williamsburg, not this one,
but there was another 4D theater attraction
that was ghosts, but it was like a kid touring a castle.
And then there's all of these like weird old British
servant ghosts.
And it was weird just by, it was a little scarier
just by the nature of the location
and just all these ancient British character actors in it.
So I did, and again, I think maybe that was another
self-produced Busch movie.
So I was expecting it more along the lines of that.
This is much more Spielberg-y.
Yeah, I guess so.
Yeah, like the wonder and discovery.
Yeah, the score is very like adjacent to all those scores.
And can I just say this, there is so much score.
There is so much, there's so many stings.
There's so, it just doesn't stop.
Little twinkles and little ah,
can you believe the haunted house that we're in
and these children are filled with mystery and wonder.
Like that's the whole thing.
And then at the end, there's a little like comment.
Like you're going to, you would think,
oh, Christopher Lloyd, Michael McKeon, Leah Thompson.
You think there's going to give you
some comedy stuff here.
Very little.
It's mostly stings, it's mostly wonder.
And then 3D effects.
I think I found what your, this has to be what you were,
what you saw when you went.
It is called Haunts of the Old Country.
That's it, that's it, yeah.
Old D, old, O-L-D-E.
A ghoulish, this is a real, this sentence fights itself.
A ghoulishly thrilling tour of Great Britain's castles.
It's a sort of, it's exciting and then a little formal.
Not the most accurate.
You know what the other thing that might have made this
a little grungier is this was like made in the 90s.
So like the 3D much rougher,
the Haunts of the Old Country.
The Haunted Lighthouse feels like it should have been made
in the 90s, but in fact, it was 2003, it opened.
2003, yeah.
I mean it has like a filmic quality, you know,
it's still like, I mean it is film, I'm sure.
But it's got that vibe of,
you can definitely see what they're going for.
Of course.
It's just boring as shit.
It's just so boring and sleepy.
Agreed.
There's just no subs, like as if you just took all the like,
like spices and the garnishes from a Spielberg
and then you just use that and then that's the whole movie.
Let's be fair to it for a second.
Is some of the issue here, what literally was removed,
as you're saying with spices being sucked out of the dish.
Keep in mind that we are watching this on YouTube
with a perma-stamp watermark of Cymix Iwerks in it.
And then also not in a 4D theater.
Yes, you're right.
Because I think maybe basically the compositions
and things that happen would be a little more interesting,
the stuff in our face.
And then of course the water effects
because from any literature I found about this,
I think it is full of splashing.
You're sopping at the end of this.
And I'm not sure there's even a lot of other effects
up its sleeve.
I think this is, and hey, it's largely at SeaWorld.
So you wanna get wet, you wanna be in your splash zones.
And this movie was a big splash zone.
But you can, if you watch it,
you can kind of tell where the 3D moments are.
Oh yeah. Kind of?
Kind of, yeah.
When the frisbee comes at the screen?
Excuse me, I misspoke.
You can really tell that.
But in terms of other lighting.
Frisbee floats ominously in front of a camera
for five full seconds.
Yes, there's rats.
I'm sure they do the rats.
I think there was a rat thing.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The chairs were wired.
I'm sure, look, I'm sure you're right.
Because when you're in the theater and it's dark
and that score, like it's blasting the music.
As we know, I like a Vegas pool party,
douchey Vegas pool party.
Any music loud is good as far as I'm concerned
in a situation like that.
So if I'm hearing that like nice imitation,
whatever John Williams, whatever score in there.
Any music, this qualifies?
Like the score to haunted lighthouse,
if loud, that you love.
If I'm at the Hard Rock rehab pool party in Las Vegas
and they're blasting the haunted lighthouse score,
you know I'm gonna get fucking riled up.
That's just what I'm all about.
You gotta go request it.
Yeah.
Go request it.
Like when you really got the party going
at hell at the moon with your request of life as a highway.
Tried to get the guy to play life as a highway
at hell at the moon, did not know it or was mad.
I don't know.
That feels like it would be a grand slam.
Yeah, it was.
I didn't do something like snooty like play
check my machine or something by Paul McCartney.
I felt like life as a highway was just a chance.
True, I guess.
It's not so crazy.
Like am I making, I feel like in my memory
I saw it get looked at and like grimaced at
and then crumpled up.
I'm happy with that memory, real or not.
It's funny, real or not.
So yeah, what you're saying is correct.
This would obviously be a lot more fun
if there was not a stamp across it
and we were watching it in a theater
it was equipped to be shown in.
That might be filling in.
That's probably what if you came out of the theater happy
it was probably for those reasons
and maybe less so the storytelling
and seeing a boat dance at the end of the movie.
Yeah, there is a copy without the watermark
that is clearly a handheld camera.
Yes.
In one of the theaters.
So pick your poison.
You either get the stamp of the distributor
or you got these shaky handheld camera
at SeaWorld or a Busch Gardens.
Yeah, and I get it.
They don't want this thing getting out there
because if they bring it back
people aren't gonna go see it in the parks
and that's a draw.
I already watch it on YouTube weekly.
Yeah, it's already been bootleg.
It's already on Pirate Bay.
It's been torrented like crazy.
I know what everybody's been doing.
So I get it.
Pirate Bay, that sounds like the spot for it.
Pirate Bay 4D.
Captain Jack would be thrilled that.
Captain Jack is who Christopher,
one of Christopher Lloyd's,
is the new Christopher Lloyd character
brought to fruition in this film.
Is he as beloved as Doc Brown
or Uncle Fester or Reverend Jim?
I guess it's up to you, the audience,
to find this watermarked YouTube video
and decide for yourselves.
Yeah, we're not gonna post it.
We refuse to post it.
I mean, I liked him.
I feel like Christopher Lloyd still gives his all.
Yeah.
On stuff like this.
I can't say enough about this guy.
This guy, I don't know why,
he deserves an Oscar.
Give him an Oscar at this point.
I just watched Nobody a few weeks ago.
He's in Nobody with the Odenkirk movie.
He gets some fun stuff.
They gave him fun stuff to do.
Mm-hmm.
He's in something else too.
He's in that Affleck movie.
He's in that Affleck movie,
which I am kinda like, this looks kinda nice.
I think I might like this.
Sure.
Well, he's, you know, it's one of those careers
where he's in all of the best,
all of our favorite movies from growing up,
and then all of a sudden he's not,
he's in weird stuff you've never heard of
and seemingly will show up for whatever,
not unlike who, Mike, you brought up
in the last Main Feed episode that came up, Bruce Willis.
Right.
And that leads me to the game portion.
Oh, good.
Of the episode.
Good, good, good.
The, we're gonna play a little round of Lloyd or Willis.
I'm gonna say a title.
And now this could be, and these are all pretty recent.
I believe these are all from the last decade.
I tried to pick the most generic titles possible.
So Stacked, Pamela Anderson, Stacked is not on this.
Stacked we would know.
Yes, we would know.
We know that that audience, you know it's Lloyd.
Lloyd is on the sitcom Stacked.
Right.
Now some of these, one of them might've been said already,
I might not know, or one of them might've been said
in the Bruce Willis thing last week.
We'll find out.
All right, Making a Killing.
Are we gonna buzz in or the rule, or is this just informal?
It's informal, I suppose.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I think it's more just,
I believe that is Lloyd.
I'm gonna say Lloyd too.
That's Lloyd, yeah.
Fire with Fire.
I think that's Willis.
I think it's Lloyd.
Willis.
Okay.
All right, if we are keeping score.
I'm winning, yes.
Yes.
Precious Cargo.
Oof, that sounds like Willis to me.
Yeah, I think Willis too.
That is Willis and is a two-hander with Mark Paul Gosselaar.
Hell yes.
Yeah, hell yes.
Check it out, go to your red box and find it.
Okay, Cold Moon.
Ooh, Cold Moon.
That's gotta be Lloyd.
I think almost nothing.
I think Lloyd.
That is Lloyd.
Nice.
The Cold Light of Day.
Willis.
Lloyd.
Five to three.
Mike has a handle on this.
Cold Pursuit.
Willis?
I think Willis.
That is a trick question.
That is a Liam Neeson movie you've never heard of.
Oh, is that the Trucker movie?
Could be, who knows?
That's a very good, is he working for Ralphs?
Is he ever pulled the cold goods?
He's like an ice-gro trucker.
Oh, that kind of trucker.
He's an ice-gro trucker.
Wish you were dead.
That, see, that could be either a funky indie comedy.
That's exactly how I'm doing all of them.
And it's been right so far.
Yeah.
I'm gonna say Lloyd.
I think Lloyd as well.
That's Lloyd.
Yes.
Out of Death.
Willis.
Yeah, yeah, that's kind of the pattern.
And then this is a tough one.
Deadly Games.
Is there a Willis Deadly Games?
Is it, could this one be both?
I don't believe there, there very well could be,
but as far as I know, this is Christopher Lloyd's territory
as he plays, where he plays the great Sebastian Jackle.
We've really, we've suddenly, like,
there'll be one of those where like,
we'll really, we'll pull the wool over the audience.
Maybe we won't, because I'm saying this,
but like, we'll eventually do Deadly Games
and one comment will be like, yes, finally, Deadly Games.
Waiting for the, maybe the episode should be called
Sebastian Jackle instead of.
That's a more exciting title, I think.
All right.
It's gotta be the episode with Brent Spiner
playing a very Joker-like character.
Oh, cool, okay, okay.
I was thinking about you, because I recently,
and this was like, I polled, like, well, it's my birthday,
I wanna watch this, and Jane had suffered through it,
I watched Master Disguise.
Oh, right, right, right.
And Brent Spiner is the bad guy.
Right, yes.
Yeah.
He has, yeah, he's got like a little,
it's an interesting thing, he does Independence Day,
he does that, and then he's the cruise director
on the Walter Matha Jack Lemon movie, Out to Sea.
He's the snooty cruise director
who like is the bad guy of that movie.
So he like pops up around that time in a lot of stuff.
And then he's in Independence Day Resurgence,
despite obviously being torn to shreds
by alien tentacles, clearly.
There's deaths that are ambiguous,
and then there's ripped apart by.
Well, he's not ripped apart, he's choked out really bad,
and then they shove his. He's in a coma, right?
And then they shove, well, they don't say,
they just shove his face, the last time you see him,
and correct me if I'm wrong,
they shove his face up to like the glass.
Yeah.
And he's like talking to them, and then it pulls it back,
and that's the last you see of him.
I guess maybe he's not torn to bits.
Yeah. I guess suppose.
I guess it's a rough recovery.
I assumed he was dead from seeing the first movie.
But.
One of the many great surprises and thrills.
From, yeah.
Man.
Spiner's back.
Weird Chinese milk product placements throughout
on the moon base.
Right, right.
As a Hemsworth on a moon base drinking a milk
you've never seen in your life.
You know, be an extreme close up.
Hey, that milk paid for half the movie, Scott.
It wouldn't exist without the milk.
Yeah, and I gotta try this milk.
This milk is like a catalyst in so many movies nowadays.
I gotta try this milk.
They've stopped being okay with characters
just sipping it on the way to something.
It has to be the plot hinges on the milk.
Right.
Getting, the characters get stronger.
The grand milk.
My bones.
All right, well now we've done about everything we could do
besides talk about the movie,
and maybe our backs are against the wall now.
God damn.
Okay.
Yeah, so the movie,
most of the movie is just, you know,
Christopher, I mean, Christopher like tells the kids
a little legend, like a ghost story basically,
and then they meet a ghost boy who's not a ghost boy yet.
He reveals himself, I mean he is, but he reveals it later.
Yeah.
And then they go to.
It's in modern times and we're in Cape Cod,
and there's a story that Captain Jack tells,
and then the people from the story show up
almost instantly.
Yeah.
Yeah, and you gotta go ahead.
Well, I was gonna say, my, a big,
there's a couple things that stick in my craw about this,
and I think the biggest one is,
what are the two kids' relationship to Captain Jack,
and where are their parents?
Yeah, no, yeah, don't see parents.
Maybe that was Stacey's mom.
They're alive, they seem to be alive,
because as he tells the kids at the end,
tell your parents not to order the Scrod,
one of the funny fish names that you can say in a comedy.
Again, it is a Christopher Lloyd character
who's old and creepy and being visited by children
away from their parents.
Like, the young people cannot stay away from the,
like the filthy shack where old Christopher Lloyd
does his business.
Well, he's obviously one of the most charismatic,
engaging actors of all time, so it makes sense
that he's like a cartoon man in a lot of ways.
You know, somebody on IMDB had a similar complaint.
They said, you know, this thing isn't too terrible,
but I think the main problem is it's too short.
That was a review they had, and they said
that they wanted other things fleshed out.
They had questions.
Yeah, they wanted to know more about the shack.
Yeah, I don't know what they said about the shack,
but you're on the same page.
When he tells that kid, keep an eye on the old shack,
I'm like, oh, my dream.
Was it an old man's bait shack?
Sounds great.
That and I'd imagine like spending a bunch of time
in a lighthouse would have its appeal as well.
Although, you know, when the kids do do that,
they do, both of them experience a thing
that I was occasionally scared of as a kid,
which is falling down, falling through a banister,
like putting your weight on a banister.
I was afraid of that too.
It wasn't one of my main fears as a kid,
but it definitely would come up every now and then.
I feel like the banisters in my childhood home growing up
were like practical, but not the sturdiest.
So I feel like maybe I tripped on the stairs once.
Do you have that weird, is it lemmings?
What am I thinking of when you go in a mall
and you're very high up and your brain just kind of
keeps going like, throw yourself over.
Like you have kind of have a thought,
it's not serious thought, but it's like,
or not really throw yourself over,
just like, you know, you could fall.
You could fall all the way down there.
I have these weird thoughts like that
and I used to have similar thoughts with like the banister
and the railing in my house.
Yeah, they say that's healthy to have like
an occasional thought like that and then not acting on it.
It shows a sign that you're in control.
Right, I'm in control.
I mean, do you ever have like when you're in a situation
like if you've ever seen like a musical performance
like an orchestra or something and your brain just goes,
throw something at the orchestra.
Yeah, it's like what I used to talk about in the past,
like, you know, drive next to an empty store front,
empty Starbucks or something.
It's like, drive your car through the window.
What's the harm?
No one's in there.
No one's gonna get hurt.
Scott, what have you thought?
What have you tried?
What has your brain told you to do?
Well, this isn't bad, but I feel like now I'm stuck on it
and I have to say it.
I think there was a,
this has been rattling around in my head for decades
and there's no way to prove whether or not it happened,
but I've chosen to believe that it did.
And it's akin to what you were saying.
I think there was some scenario where I was on a class
field trip to see some enriching performance
from the great, much lauded, many times award winning,
honored at the Emmys this year, Debbie Allen.
Oh wow.
Like a whole elementary school class went to see something
that Debbie Allen was doing
and something that I should have appreciated.
But I was eight or nine, so I got very bored
and I started looking at the program instead.
And I think I might've had my feet up on the chair
and it was just, but I was also within eye range
of Debbie Allen.
Like she, this is not a movie.
She's in the room and she's there.
And I believe that what may have happened is
that I was nudged or elbowed by someone next to me like,
hey, and I think that Debbie Allen may have stopped
what she was doing to stare at me
until I stopped looking down at my program.
Wow, really?
Being so disrespectful to this Debbie Allen performance.
That's wild.
I think that I may have, or it was all a coincidence
that I've been imagining this for a long time.
Wait.
I would need footage to know.
Well, there's no way to know.
So you were just, you were standing on?
I wasn't standing, no.
You were just looking down at your program.
I was just, yeah, I was bored.
Like, I'm gonna look, I'm gonna read this.
I'm gonna see what ads are in here.
I always looked at the program.
A Pauly Shore character at dinner,
like a Pauly Shore character at like a nice dinner.
Feet up, like reading something when you should be like.
Bare feet, cleaning my feet with spit.
And like polishing it with the program.
Okay.
Well, yeah, I mean, sure, you might look at a program
during a performance, but this was an intimate,
but whatever this was, whatever Debbie Allen was doing
for these children in 1994,
I have no idea.
But I've been horrified for decades.
Wow.
That I angered.
And anytime Debbie Allen comes up like at the Emmys,
I get bummed out.
I'm enjoying the Emmys,
Conan's messing around, having fun.
And then Debbie Allen is given an award.
And I'm like, oh shit.
And I get sad about what I,
how I might've offended Debbie Allen as a child.
No, I get that.
That's a guilt.
No, this is a different thing that we were talking about.
This is just pure guilt from doing something
where you made like an adult mad and it was like embarrassed.
I know it's a different thing.
Just as soon as you, that's how much it is on my,
and I'm so glad that I vented it now.
Because when you said something about interrupting
a performance, I just got lost in,
I have to bring up this Debbie Allen thing.
It's haunting you still.
This is what haunts me.
This is a month to get your fears out
of my biggest fears that I made Debbie Allen angry.
During a one woman show,
she was the only person on stage by the way.
Yeah.
So she may have stopped the performance cold
to stare angrily at me.
She's an executive producer credit on Craze and Anime.
Did you know that?
I didn't.
She directs a lot of TV shows.
Okay.
So that's why I haven't gotten any callbacks.
Does she have a Twitter?
Can we tweet this story at her to see if she remembers?
Oh no.
Why?
I mean, you can apologize.
Well, yes, I would like to do that.
And if Debbie Allen's already a subscriber
to haunt cast the Fright, the Cemetery Gate,
then I apologize to you profusely right now.
I was but a child.
Wow.
I mean, look, if she hears,
I mean, hopefully she would have a sense of humor about it.
You were but a child,
but I feel like we can make this happen.
I feel like we'll find her.
I was but a child, but I was also a real but,
and I'd be willing to say that to her.
I was a but to you.
She'll appreciate that I think for sure.
Wow.
Okay.
So that's out.
That is out.
Not the good boy the listeners thought he was, I guess.
There's a lot more darkness in some,
one of our hosts passed than we thought.
Unattentive on a field trip, one woman show, eh?
Man.
Relaxing.
Hmm.
A reason for ending my subscription?
Well.
Respect Ms. Allen, please.
Bad behavior from one of the hosts 30 years ago.
All right, you guys keep,
because I might just be thinking.
Yeah, yeah.
We'll just, Jason, I'll keep talking.
So yeah, so the kids are outside the shack
and you get your first, wait,
is there an earlier 3D gag than just that weird frisbee?
Frisbee.
It's one of the weirdest versions of this I've ever seen.
It is.
There's weird, there's a number of moments in this
that go on just like a bit too long
and you start to get a little antsy.
Yeah, and then this one,
like the frisbee hovers in the air and it looks,
and again, we're looking on a low resolution version of this
but it looks like an orange version
of like the T1000 from T2 or something.
It looks like this bizarre shaped object
that's hovering in the air for way too long.
It looks like it might be like alien or something.
It's the same vibe as when that skull cartoonishly,
where when Arnold's skull, metallic skull,
hovers up towards the screen for a long time in T2, 3D.
It's exactly that, but a beach frisbee.
But a beach frisbee and then it hits the kid in the head.
In the head, that's pretty funny.
Pretty good, this kid gets hit in the head a couple times.
What Debbie Allen should have done to me.
Throwing a weird T1000 organic frisbee.
A time warping frisbee at me.
Organic matter frisbee, organic matter metal frisbee.
Dance shoe, a morphing dance shoe.
A soft shoe.
I just appreciate if it was soft,
but whatever she wants.
I prefer not, but I might deserve more than soft.
Or she would have done the next 3D trick,
spit a bunch of water in your face,
which is what this kid gets.
I like that we know we have water effects in our theater
and we know we're doing 3D.
Because it's usually a splash in a body of water
or something, but a man spitting at you.
Yes, Christopher Lloyd spits on a child in this movie.
Baaah!
And it's real gross and it's unexpected.
So yeah, that one's a weirder thing to have happen,
but the effect is I think less weird than the frisbee.
Yeah, and then he said they discuss the widow
who's worth 14 million clams.
Right, and he's like,
Christopher Lloyd gets like old gaga over that.
He gets gaga over it and then he takes two
like giant taxidermy, like a mounted swordfish.
Right.
Like I gotta go see her.
And it's like, what could that be?
What are you doing with those?
Yeah, it's unclear.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's when he leaves the kids at the shack.
And then...
What's the shack at that point?
It's like where a Baywatch station,
where like a lifeguard station would be,
but what does he do?
Why does he have that?
It's bait and souvenirs and like, yeah.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
So he's a captain,
but he's trying to make some money on the side, I assume.
He's probably mostly on the beach.
They establish he rents boats.
Right.
Because he gets on a boat at one point to chase after them
because they've stolen one of his boats
to go to the lighthouse.
Mm-hmm, yes.
This is, you paid so much closer attention than I did.
I kept trying, I had to keep backing up to say,
Winters really tells the old,
the ghost story at the beginning.
It just like did not get through.
It's just, oh, there it is.
Oh, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
And I didn't, I just couldn't make heads or tails of it.
There's a very, and I don't, again,
I don't know if it's because of the conversion on YouTube,
but there's a quality to this movie that feels like
it's one of those movies where they had to dub
all the dialogue again.
I looked up behind the scenes information about the film,
Joe Dante's complaints about making 3D films in that era
because he then later made a movie,
and I don't remember the title.
I feel like a movie that was in theaters,
and I'm not remembering it,
but he said how much he preferred doing it
in the digital age.
He said, because I made this thing for a theme park
on a lighthouse, and it was 70 millimeter cameras,
and they were so loud.
Oh, right, yes, yes.
There were six people to move them anywhere,
and we had to loop all of the dialogue
because those cameras were whirring so loud.
So you're exactly right.
That is one of the stranger facts about this movie.
It was shot in 70 millimeter,
which is like the thing, that's what Paul Thomas Anderson,
Quentin Tarantino, it's like we're gonna shoot in 70,
we're gonna have some prints at the best theaters
in the country.
This is how we would like it shown.
Because yeah, originally all that,
yeah, they used that back in the old days,
but then they would use that for,
because the first time I saw stuff large format,
was IMAX at a museum downtown.
So you would see, I think we saw Everest,
and it was a crazy giant screen,
and they had shot on big film cameras.
I would assume it might be probably the same issue
with that, was it fake snow sounds and stuff?
Were they adding all the sound?
I don't know.
Mountains space under the sea.
Like those early IMAX.
I think a lot of IMAX stuff, it's all sound design,
because the places that they go to do those,
to also mic it nicely, I feel like,
I think those are heavily sound design.
I don't really know.
A switch I think happened at some point though,
because obviously they were using large format
for like scenes in the dark night.
I know they have like smaller IMAX cameras now,
which they shot like Endgame on and stuff,
or the two Avengers movies.
It makes me queasy in IMAX theaters,
when it goes from widescreen to suddenly
it's an IMAX square.
Oh, you like it to be consistent.
I just like a widescreen.
I like a cinemascope, I like a widescreen.
I loved it in dark night.
Oh yeah, I was just.
Suddenly, and I was like,
how are they gonna do that transition,
and then it's just a cut, it's like Soarin'.
I thought it was so cool to just like,
what's it gonna be?
And I don't like those morphs in Soarin',
as much as I like just the cuts, just cuts.
I agree, when we saw it, City Walk,
one of the opening, maybe the first or second day,
and the first like shot where there's panning over the city,
the audience gasped.
Yeah.
We were all like, whoa.
That feels like a conscious aesthetic choice though.
And I feel like now where so much
is just thrown onto IMAX screens.
It's less impactful.
Yeah, maybe that's true.
No one's gonna be more careful.
Some of those are just blown up,
and they weren't necessarily shot for that large.
Nolan would be so mad that we're not.
We didn't watch Haunted.
You reviewed Haunted Linehouse 4D
without even seeing it with the rat effect.
When his wife.
You judge this film.
When his wife is playing him the podcast off her phone,
because he doesn't have a phone, I've heard,
he'll be listening to the Patreon, and he'll be so upset.
Sorry, Mrs. Nolan.
There's so many people who apologize too.
So then, I mean, so yes, they meet these kids,
and then, and who, like, you're, all right,
it's a ghost, got it.
I think you know that pretty fast.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You've heard about some ghost kids,
and then you see a kid, oh, it's probably the ghost kid.
But there's that one effect that's pretty great
of that shark that's slowly getting closer behind them,
and then suddenly bursts through the painter,
or you think it's a painting or something.
Yeah, and then right after, the kids are like,
isn't clear, where the ghosts?
Like, kind of, I feel like the ghost kids
are supposed to be a little sinister and a little dark,
but I don't know that they're sticking the delivery
on some of their lines, but I like when their eyeballs
pop out and their head gets real big,
or they become fish-headed at one point.
Yeah, so the kid, to prove to the living kids
that he's a ghost, decides to like, maskify his head.
He becomes the mask, but without the fun green face.
And that's a still that, you know,
when we will get out there,
that's an image that might let you know,
you're, however you feel about the boy
with the stretching neck,
might tell you if you wanna watch this
on YouTube in full or not.
It's a little creepy, but I guess you're,
you're watching this and going, what did Dante respond to?
And I think it was probably, I wanna play with the toys,
I wanna pull these effects out.
Maybe there's some like quickie version
of silly fun gremlin-sy effects.
But I think it just aesthetically doesn't,
it's all, so much of it is in that just blue gauze.
A really, yeah, blue like haze of a weird haunted house.
Like they stretched that blue, like,
sandwich wrapping over the camera lines.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'd say it's a real caked in.
And that really, when you're watching on YouTube
on your computer, which is what I watched,
it's a sleepy, I really want some,
that blue hue is just so inviting for you
to go right to bed.
Like you wanna go to sleep.
I never, I didn't make it through this without a pause.
Yeah.
It'd be only being 20 minutes.
I needed a, all right, quick break.
I checked the time, like the, like,
how much, it's not, hit up on the Roku remote
to see where the slider was at.
Little time check.
So, yeah, you meet some ghost kids and you like,
you know, they do scary stuff.
They get fish heads.
They, it suddenly gets kind of malicious seeming, right?
Or what's the plan?
What do the ghost kids want?
Jason, help us out here.
They, well, they, the parents never showed back up.
The parents told them to wait at the lighthouse
no matter what.
And it appears that they waited so long they died.
And at some point they get to the conclusion
that they need to activate the beacon,
reactivate the beacon in the lighthouse.
To let the parents know that they're out there.
Yeah, to let the parents know.
I mean, they're, like I said, both kids,
human kids fall through banisters.
The boy, he really eats it.
And then like, he's like, I'm okay.
And it's like, really?
Cause that seemed awful that fall.
Yeah, yeah.
And then the girl, it kind of, she, she,
the sister falls and like catches, she, she,
there's a spear gun and she like gets like, you know,
gets to do the kid's trope of equipping and using a weapon
that was all in all kids entertainment.
Be prepared to get a weapon and be prepared to use it.
And then also you might be hanging from a rope
and have to kick off the walls at some point.
And that, that was just go-to.
Maybe it still is a go-to in a lot of kids entertainment.
But they do the shot, they do like a shot of her hanging
from the rope and it's the same angle as the stretching room.
Yes, you know what I'm saying.
Oh yeah, yes.
You're like, it's a real dark.
Yeah.
Is that what's happening?
When I was paying, yeah, when I was half paying attention
to it, I went, is she, what?
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
I went, that's an, oh.
It was business with, cause the,
the brother picks up the spear gun earlier and he's like,
let's kill those ghosts.
Like he was bloodthirsty.
Dark film, isn't it?
Yeah.
And of course both the parents die and become ghosts.
Like early on, that was another fear of mine as a kid.
My parents would go away for like a nice weekend together
and not come back.
When they went to see.
Well, I thought the Poconos, but sure, at sea.
We'll go with that.
But they, they do get them back.
They do return on this boat and these two ghosts ominously
float back to their children.
And the parents are Michael McKeon and Leah Thompson.
Leah Thompson chooses to play it like a woman,
a regular woman who's slightly from the past.
And McKeon is like, well, well, my children, I,
he's just full like theater character.
The sketch comedy, like past guys.
Yes.
Yeah.
Because he makes a joke about the kids being
a little homicidal.
And it's like, I think I kind of see where
that joke came from, but it didn't.
Maybe there's supposed to be more stuff like that.
Maybe it was more gremlin Z and then if you could,
I would venture to guess that someone in Bush or SeaWorld
is like, but this is for all family audiences.
So take out anything interesting about it.
Yeah.
It's just, I mean, the kids, like, they definitely thought
the 3D is going to do the heavy lifting,
the 3D in the score, not the kids getting to like,
be weird or quirky.
Like they're like, don't worry.
The 3D is the thing.
Yeah.
That's going to sell it.
So again, we're missing that, you know, we're missing.
Yeah.
And for Tampa Bay and Williamsburg,
it got people in out of the humidity.
Yes.
It's the whole middle, maybe 13, 14 minutes is a blur.
I remember the end and the start.
That's exactly where I'm at.
Yes. Yeah.
But yeah, I think it picks up when you get Ghost McKeon
who is very thankful that his children have been brought
back to him in the ghostly realm and says,
there's no way to, that I could ever repay you kids.
Although you might want to know about the sunken galley
and references made to a treasure.
It's nice to hear McKeon say pirates booty.
He's enjoying, he's like,
He's doing a little fun voice there.
He's having fun in a children's thing.
Yeah.
That's what you, you know,
should expect out of an actor.
He says great Scott man to Christopher Lloyd,
which I'm assuming is a little nod.
It would have to imagine.
It would have to.
To which like in like one time,
in every screening there was one guy who was like,
ha ha ha ha.
And like nobody then looked around like,
why aren't you all laughing triumphantly at that?
Yeah. It's from the movie.
They have been put to sleep by the free six ounce cups
of bush beer available at various locations
throughout the park.
Should you get free beer there?
That is an occasional promotion that they have done.
Really? Still?
I think they did bring it back.
Well, at Williamsburg,
I do remember once taking a monorail to a brewery
from Bush gardens.
Oh, that one is connected to a, I don't know.
Yeah. And I don't know that they still do it.
You could take a little tour
and then there was a tasting at the end.
And I remember thinking the brewery smelled awful.
And then when we went to get on the monorail back,
they're like, sorry folks,
monorails, it's going to be a little while longer
while we get the other car to come.
And so we were like stuck in the cafeteria cafe
at the brewery for like extra time,
like burning off our, like an extra 30 minutes
of your theme park day at a stinky brewery.
Wow. What a rave review.
Stinky brewery.
Also, I've been to plenty of microbreweries at this point
and I'm like, they don't stick,
like what the fuck was going on at the Bush brewery?
Is there a weird smell when you go by there?
What's the one on the-
Golden Road?
No, no, no, the big one.
There's a big plant.
It's not like a brewery.
Oh, there's a Budweiser.
There's a few Budweiser ones in the valley.
Yeah, like in the valley.
The one on the way to, oh, the valley one.
Cause, oh wait, well there's the one off the 405.
That's probably what I'm thinking of.
Like kind of north in the valley,
which had a theme park connected.
Bush Gardens, yeah, sure.
Yeah, yeah.
And you can still see the track when you go around,
like where the little people mover cars went around.
This is a total detour,
but is there some sort of theme park proposal for the zoo
that somebody just put up?
Oh, I haven't really looked at that article.
Yeah, I've heard that.
Yeah, the LA zoo in Burbank.
Not far from all the things we talk about.
Yeah, that's kind of exciting.
I like the zoo.
There's a vibe there up there.
Don't mess up the vibe.
Right.
Yeah.
The theme park stuff sounds fun.
I think people might be upset about it, but not us.
Yeah, yeah.
You know where we're at.
The dumber, the better.
Which is I think why we probably all enjoyed
the final scene more than the rest of the movie.
Yeah, I think that's right, yeah.
Because with all of the pirate's booty,
I guess the kids get some probably, I hope.
And then Captain Jack gets to shift his shack.
It's a different kind of shack now.
It's a swordfish shack.
He opens a restaurant.
So now, yeah, there's this line of butt.
Scrawd, it's really hopping.
I think it's tough to get a table.
I believe it's partly the lighthouse.
Oh, I see.
He built it into the lighthouse.
In the lighthouse, okay.
Because I think that's the last little bit.
Gotcha, okay, okay.
When they sit down to eat.
Yeah.
Oh yeah, that's right, because oh yeah, yeah.
Up on the lighthouse, if you look close,
it says the word fancy on it.
They've just stamped the word fancy.
That's funny.
That's how you know there's been a changeover.
But it's really, yeah, it looks like a fun,
it looks like a real Joe's Crab shack, eh?
Yes.
You know, this shit on the walls,
and Lloyd's having a good time,
and even the ghosts can't stay away.
They show up, and there's this big full cast dinner,
and you go, oh, they did get a second day
out of Leah Thompson and Michael McKeon.
You're kidding.
Two days of shooting.
Yeah, and there's, he go, and they go,
Michael McKeon tells Christopher Lighty,
can't eat because, or they can't eat,
because they're ghosts, and it goes right through them,
of course, and then Christopher Lloyd says,
he knows what that is, and then they do a real long shot,
I feel like, of Michael McKeon giving him the eye.
Like, hmm.
He's talking about poop, he's talking about shit.
Captain Jack's diarrhea.
Fish-based diarrhea.
He's thinking about Captain Jack's diarrhea, you're right.
That's probably the comedic high point of the movie.
Well, a catfish spits in Christopher Lloyd's face.
That is good too, you're right.
That's weird Al Yankovic with a perplexing stutter,
comes out and delivers.
It's like Renfield or something.
Yeah, that's a good reference.
Despite being in current times,
and just a waiter at a seafood restaurant.
Yeah. Yeah.
He's playing a kind of a strange monster kind of guy.
He's like a lackey.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So he comes out and you go, is that fucking weird Al?
And it is, yeah, it is.
And you're like, is it enough to save it at the buzzer?
I don't know.
Depends on how much you like Al.
You go, oh, okay, that's good Al.
Yeah, and I checked, I think I did check.
I go, oh, is there gonna be more scenes here with Al?
No, it's over.
He brings in a pot of catfish surprise.
What's the surprise?
Take off the lid of catfish spits in Christopher Lloyd's face.
That's pretty good.
It's pretty good.
It's like a hearty vomit too.
And if you imagine getting just one more nice copious spray
before you head out into that humidity.
And then there's a, soon after this,
there's a really funny song that plays.
It is, I wrote it down.
It's worth playing the song.
I described it, this is what the ghost kid Edgar is doing,
like a really intense dance to.
I described it as the most public domain song
I've ever heard.
I shazammed it, like not expecting any results
and nor did I get any.
Okay.
Yeah, I tried to find it.
It's just like, it's like 20 seconds long too, right?
Yeah, it is perfectly.
It's like the kind of music that ends lifetime movies.
You know, like what can we do that has lyrics
so it seems like a real song, but is generic enough
that clearly we paid nothing.
Here, wait, all right, they're all laughing at this.
["Can't Touch Me"]
It's invisible but I can't see it.
Can't touch me but I can feel it.
And it's scary but I can't do it
because life is impossible without it.
Life is impossible without it.
And the boat is dancing, you alluded to that earlier.
And the boat is dancing.
Life is impossible without it.
Yeah, I don't, who is that?
What is that?
Did they write it for, were they inspired by a sequence
with a diarrhea joke told to a ghost
and then a catfish spitting in a man's face?
Yeah, what is that?
Life is impossible without it and it is 3D effects.
3D is 3D fun, that's what life is all about.
I'd be tempted to agree.
It lights up my life and it's been fun to think about here
even though this film is in, well, let me read a review.
This was on IMDB.
This is a terrible film.
Joe Dante should be ashamed of himself.
The lighting is awful and the acting is bad.
Now I don't know that I would desire to be that mean
to the movie.
I think it's been perfectly pleasant to talk about it.
But I just think it was not, did not deliver.
You are picturing with these actors and with like,
wait, we're forgetting, there's a much better reunion
with the clue, we got two clue people.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's great, you can't add for like, people, great,
80s, 90s filmmakers and actors and then you get this,
which is just kind of tepid.
Yeah, I mean, watch the first and last scene.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I think so.
I think you could do a 30 second cut of this
that's pretty solid.
Topher Grace is working on a 30 second cut of this,
like the way he cut all the prequels together.
He's cutting just the first and last scene together
to make this better.
Topher Grace?
Yeah, wasn't it him?
Topher Grace did a cut, really?
I'm pretty sure.
Okay, no, that's fine, good for him, that's fun.
If you want more Haunted Lighthouse in your life,
head to eBay where you can buy this hat of the logo
and even the hat is a little lackluster.
Yeah.
There's two of them online for sale, $20, $25, buy it now.
Appears to be the only options.
Too much for my blood, too rich for my blood.
Yeah, for a bit.
Yeah, Topher Grace, I'm correct,
edited an 85 minute cut of the Star Wars prequels.
Okay.
Wow.
Where do you see that?
That is how it is.
I don't know if that's, yeah,
maybe that's not commercially available.
That's like Soderbergh cutting a black and white Raiders.
The Lost Ark.
Yes.
Yeah.
So. Just as cool.
Just as cool.
I think, I don't know, well, I don't know.
Maybe I'll try to do a 30 second cut
or I'll forget or get busy.
Yeah, okay.
Either way, the things remain the same
in the world ultimately.
But as far as, so that's this movie,
but in the realm of Cimex Iwerks.
Some Cimex Iwerks, yes.
So they have a lot of stuff they do.
If you go on their website, they show like,
they show some cool stuff.
Like they do, they have like a thing you could do
in a museum or an exhibit where you can build
like part of a boat and they projection map,
like the sea around the boat.
Did you see the picture of this on the website?
No.
Which sounds like, seems like pretty cool.
Like you could do that with like historical things.
They could probably use it at the Ark encounter.
Let's be honest.
Mm-hmm.
If you want to scare the kids
into knowing what it's really like.
They have a recent thing they've done is Thomas and Friends
4D Bubbling Boilers, a 4D Thomas the Tank experience.
Okay.
Which you can see some of on YouTube and that's fun.
But they have a lot, there's so many films
as you saw scrolling through.
Yeah.
Some, yeah, some are just like 4D experiences for movies.
Some are original things.
Like there's something called Mars Coaster,
which is the most generic Martian characters.
And then it's just, you know,
it's just the end of the Simpsons ride in a simulator.
Are you looking at Mars Coaster?
I shall, I will, yeah.
Yeah.
And there's something called Craig T. Nelson
presents Super Speedway the Ride.
Whoa.
I tried to find a video.
I didn't try that hard on that one.
So that might be out there,
but that's like Craig T. Nelson
intro-ing sort of a 3D like racing movie.
This is, I like this world in general
because I think by now, you know, we've educated our audience.
Some of this audience has been with us for a long time.
And you know, we know Disney, we know Universal,
we've covered it, but like, this is what I'm interested in.
We got to talk Sally Dark Rides,
Yes.
And Cimex Iwerks, the companies that are making
weird, obscure, not as corporate,
not seen, not liked entertainment.
No one has an opinion about these things.
We'd be the first ever covered.
Hundreds of thousands of people
have seen them, experienced them.
And there's, yeah, there's a lot there.
Yeah, we will do more on all of this
so I won't list all of them,
but there's one that caught my eye down the list.
And you cannot watch a preview of it,
but there was a poster and a name and I got very excited
and I was correct with my assumption.
The name of this is Dragatar 3D.
Dragatar, D-R-A-G-A-T-A-R 3D.
When I said, okay, is Dragatar a takeoff of Avatar?
Well, the first sentence,
visit the mythical planet of Andorra.
What?
And jump onto the back of a native dragon
as they soar through steep canyons
in their search for the crystal sphere.
Avoid huge dragon eating plants, zoom through ancient tunnels
and discover a hidden volcanic valley
filled with boiling lava and a nest of ghostly snakes.
Feel the freedom of flying through clouds and waterfalls
as you battle the evil Dragatar.
Oh, now I like that.
Dragatar's the bad guy.
You're going to be an Avatar
and you're gonna fly in this and this one.
No, Dragatar is your enemy, kill him.
Yeah, so you're on a native dragon
and Dragatar is the bad guy you have to defeat.
And it says, will you defeat him?
Strap in, come along and find out
on this Drag-a-ful adventure.
I guess wonderful is what they're like.
Drag-a-ful.
Whoa.
Dragatar.
Avatar is not Dragatar.
You hate Dragatar.
Kill Dragatar.
Strap it in the throat.
And Dragatar is not like a fun drag show Avatar thing.
That was the only other thing I think it could have been.
Yeah, yeah.
It was a good idea but for something else.
Right, so Dragatar 3D, there's no video preview.
Now a lot of these things have previews
or you can find the whole video
and the graphics on them look like Sega Dreamcast.
And it looks maybe like we're dealing with
like PlayStation 3 level graphics on it.
If you look up Dragatar 3D,
you'll be able to see the page and go right to it.
Well, I did and you're right that there isn't a video
except there is a really brief video
with no footage from this attraction.
All it says is, Cymax Iwerks Entertainment,
please contact us for a preview.
Well, right, so.
Exactly, we have to do, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, we're doing it.
I think this is one email we would be sending.
To whom it may concern.
And like you have, like they have the little like
contact us thing on the bottom right,
that little red icon right here is for contacting.
Oh, jeez.
So we need to get.
We gotta do it.
Yeah, we're gonna have to,
we're gonna have to find out more about Dragatar
because I don't even know where Dragatar is being shown.
Maybe nowhere.
There's like no results for it.
Right.
Really besides this.
This must be, this might be fresh IP.
Dragatar might be fresh IP.
That we could use.
Could we add a live show that we're dying to do
and are hopefully gonna be doing soon and later.
Like we premiere a real attraction that we didn't make.
Yeah.
We license and lose far beyond what we would have made
to do the show.
We're way in the, we're like,
we have lost thousands of dollars for this.
I'm sorry to tell you Jason.
Let's do that when we're in town.
Let's not make that one of the travel ones.
Well, it depends on where there's Dragatar hunger out there.
Yeah, it depends.
Be loud.
Make your city the loudest.
And we'll bring Dragatar 3D to you.
Oh no.
Dragatar.
You know, I think.
So losing thousands to go to Singapore
because of the Dragatar fans.
Jason, when you see the world of Andorra,
you're going to understand that this is worth it.
You know, some of the 3D stuff
and not even 3D theme parks,
because I understand parks have varying budgets
and I think it's cool when any park like commits
to like a 3D attraction.
But even some of the 3D movies
and especially the stuff you find on free streaming services
always reminds me of that Tim and Eric bit with 80 miles
and the character Grum.
Do you remember Grum?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like a very unpleasant looking CG character.
It's what should be great.
They should partner with Tim and Eric
and do a Grum ride too.
But mainly, oh my God.
I mean, the unfortunate thing about it
is that like if we were to,
like everybody would just have to like kind of, you know,
like sway from side to side and duck and make it a,
this is a ride.
Right.
Well, we could do, we would show Draguitar a couple times
so everyone would get familiar with it
so they know when to go left and when to go right.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, we'll give the audience a chance of like,
hey, there's no line.
Do you want to go on again?
And they do it right afterwards.
But of course everyone, you'll be checking your phones
in little sealed bags for this.
We don't want people bootlegging Draguitar.
Oh yeah, well yeah, it's not online right now.
We don't want to ruin this company's business,
but also in case there's anything a little not too PC
in Draguitar 3D.
We don't want you going and canceling Cymax Iwerks
or us on Twitter right away.
Or Draguitar himself.
Or Draguitar.
Kill Draguitar, but don't cancel him.
Don't care.
And or your three modern day philosophers up on stage
guiding you through the world of Andorra.
That's us.
Well, we're truth tellers.
We're truth tellers.
That's true.
Oh man.
We've always tried to be, you know,
the theme park worlds, Lenny Bruce and Bill Hicks.
Oh yeah, yeah.
We've always thought the way we're so honest with our.
Plato.
Opinions about rocks.
Cut through the bullshit.
Is what I always wanted to do with this podcast.
Yeah.
I always say like, oh, I wanted to go to like
free press events.
No, I wanted to cut through the bullshit.
That's what this was about.
I think Dennis Leary also in our spirit
would also make his real opinion known
about the fish head effect that is lackluster.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Same thing.
Haunted lighthouse 4D.
Same exact thing for sure.
We're telling you the truth and the truth is
Draguitar 3D exclusive debut.
That is the best.
We're really good.
We have a real theme park ride.
We could.
Will only be seen in this show.
Even just a sizzle, a proof of concept, something.
You know, we should really say this off mic,
but what we could probably do is get a link to it
and then like at least just take an iPhone video off
our phone and play it.
Yeah.
Live show.
Yeah, do you have airplay in the booth?
Can I airplay?
Yeah, yeah.
We should have checked this attack.
Sorry folks.
Who like Draguitar?
Hey, you want to see Draguitar?
Or Draguitar might be on Pirates Bay.
Who knows on the Torrent sites?
Going to the dark web, booting up tour to find
who like Draguitar.
To find Draguitar, yeah.
All right, well Mike and I will go to the Pirates Bay
and try to find it.
Jason, wait here and send a beacon if you need anything.
Hopefully we'll be back and we won't get lost
in the Pirates Bay forever.
Yeah, don't worry, Jason.
We're gonna come back.
Don't worry.
Well, I have lost now.
Do you think the Pirates Bay is a real nautical destination?
Yeah, we're gonna go there.
Are you going in the hacker's version of the internet
where you're zooming through digital skyscrapers?
It's like Reboot or something.
Yeah.
Mixed with a little nautical too.
Cyber pirates.
Yeah.
Yeah, and we'll be talking to ourself
with our special guest, Johnny Mnemonic himself.
Not Keanu, the real Johnny Mnemonic.
Well, you know who Johnny Mnemonic is.
You survived, punk ass, that's right.
You know who knows the internet better than anyone?
Sebastian Jackle.
That's for sure.
This is a cyber show, Deadly Games.
It's also maybe a good in,
like how many things has Christopher Lloyd asked
to play Doc Brown in?
And how many times does he say yes?
Always.
Every time.
The answer's every time.
So why am I even bringing this up?
Well, maybe he would really get a kick out of,
we have him on the podcast in character
as Sebastian Jackle.
Yeah, I think that's a great idea.
Our guest today is a hacker who's been known
to get involved in some Deadly Games.
Oh yes, I'm here.
He's here to talk about story book land canal boats.
Please welcome Sebastian Jackle.
We had a takedown notice from Dick Clark Productions
or whatever unexpected TV production company
grinded those out.
Byron Allen's company.
Ah, damn, why didn't we look this up?
Byron Allen bought the rights to Deadly Games
10 years ago in a big package.
There was that profile of him a couple of years ago.
He's low key one of the richest people in Malibu.
Yeah, he's the smartest in the world.
Yes.
He's one of the smartest show business,
he's like-
He's in Deadline every day.
He's in Deadline today.
Oh, was he?
Yes, always.
They post every article about every,
if he goes and gets breakfast, Deadline hears about it.
We should get him on the show.
I'd love to have Byron.
All right, so guest dream list,
or just priorities, Byron Allen on the show,
Sebastian Jackal in character unless he's known
by Byron Allen, Johnny Mnemonic,
and live debut of PTR licensed Draguitar 3D.
Draguitar 3D.
Okay, well, you survived Haunt Cast the Fright,
The Cemetery Gate, Haunted Light Us 4D edition,
but the rest of the adventures clearly are just beginning.
And what was that song again?
You can't live, because you can't live without it.
You know, you can't live without it.
Is that it?
I think so.
Oh yeah, that's it.
Yeah, Mike, start working on the orchestration for your-
For the parody version of it, or the homage version.
Yeah, just a cover, just a cover, yeah.
Yeah, all right.
Okay, well, thanks for listening,
and I'm so sorry, Debbie Allen.