Forever.
Dog.
This is not a test.
This is your emergency podcast system announcing the commencement of a purge episode sanctioned
by hot cast the fright.
Commencing at the theme song, any and all body topics, including murder will be legal for
90 continuous minutes.
Blessed be our guests, J'Kees Neil and Halloween Horror Nights, a Universal Studios seasonal
event reborn.
May God be with you all.
Welcome to haunt cast the fright, a theme park podcast hosted by three men who would use
a real life purge scenario to switch clothes with the robots on Pirates of the Caribbean.
My name is Mike Carlson, joining me as always, Jason Sheridan.
Twelve hours.
All crime is legal for 12 hours.
That's right.
I think I could get in and out of there.
Easily.
Yeah, we get a few outfits.
Scott Garner here.
Are you already scheming for what outfits you would steal from which robot?
Well, I'd want to wear isn't there one balancing five hats?
And then I'd want to like just to get bang for the most clothes.
Let's get under those five hats.
You would steal the five hats.
Jason, do you have a pirate?
You would his outfit?
Um, I well, maybe the one with the pigs, the one who's rolling in the slaps rolling in
the slop.
You know, it feels appropriate, you know, for the night for the events of purge night
to then have a slot code on.
You would do all your murders wearing the pirate's outfit covered in and explaining
like, guess what?
Guess what?
This is that would be like your version of like, do you know how I got these scars?
Or did you ever dance with the devil in the pale moonlight?
And with like 15 minutes left, I'll flip it.
What do you mean with whatever unscrupulous Susniana collectors are out and about doing
deals of like, oh, flip it for money.
Oh, I thought you were going to flip like the phrase on its head.
And I was like, oh, you're going to or the or your clothes.
Yeah, flip it inside out.
So I look nicer.
Yeah.
So the mud is on the inside comes up the second siren when the second siren sounds.
I want to look right.
I'm glad you know more of the rules of the purchase.
I know the rules, but I'm I'd had the I'm a little rusty.
So it's a thing where I have seen cumulatively one purge movie pieces of every movie adds
up to one movie.
But I know a lot about the lore about the new founding fathers.
I know about the new.
Let's let's bring our guys.
He knows probably more actor, podcaster, you know him from Marvel's What If and Culture
Kings.
This is J'Key's Neil.
Oh, what's up, fellas?
Hey, man.
How are we doing?
Pretty good.
We're getting ready to be in here.
We ready to talk some rides, everybody.
Yes, we are.
Thanks for reaching out.
We never know who's a theme park guy.
Oh, yeah.
And you get us up.
But now we know we're always happy.
We want to know all of it.
We want to know everybody.
We hear.
Yeah.
It's kind of wild, too.
I I went to I've been a theme park person my whole life.
I went to Disney World the first time in my life at 21.
OK, I became a Disney park guy.
That's an adult Disney.
I'm always impressed with that.
Yeah.
Because you didn't have the little kid like brain for it.
If I ever have kids, you know, listen, ladies, if you want to have a kid with me, I'm telling
you now, telling you now, we ain't taking the kids to Disney World until they're at
least 13.
I don't think it's a place for kids.
I think it's a place for adults.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
A lot of people listening to this show are like, yes.
Yes.
They pump their fist at that.
Almost all the times I've spent like significant hours I've spent away from my child so far
as 18 months have been at theme parks without him.
Yeah.
So much leaving him to go on kiddie rides.
Disneyland, I'll take the kids.
Disney World is a vacation.
That's for me.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
They got to be able to handle it and roughen it and like, you know, do it.
You were saying you're going, you're going to go, you're going to do nine days, you're
going to do a big like kids have to be ready to deal with a big, a big old.
And they can't.
They're not.
Yeah.
They're finicky.
You don't want tantrums.
When you were 21 and you went.
Yeah.
You look at like the handful of things you were like, whoa, this is this is so.
This.
All right.
So I.
So I went it was my graduation present to myself.
I had just graduated college, Columbia College, which I'm sure you know you're from Chicago.
And it was also me and my girlfriends at the time one year anniversary.
So we went together.
She went when she was a kid, but she hadn't been since she was like 12 or some shit.
And I went and I didn't know what to expect, but I was excited to go Magic Kingdom.
I don't remember exactly the first park I went to, but I think the first fireworks show,
I was like, oh man, this is like dreams at the time was going on.
This is the way this is always so I was like, oh, this is like crazy.
This is dope.
And then I saw Fantasmic and I was like, I love this shit.
Fantastic was the coolest.
I mean, I'm from the South Side of Chicago.
I don't see no shit like Fantasmic in Chicago.
Like you're watching this and this show, all these this water and then Mickey's down below
and then a little fireworks and he pops back up at the top and I'm like, this is the best
thing I've ever seen in my life.
I think that's the moment I fell in love like with the Disney parks and Disney in general.
I get that the music, I assume.
Also very memorable.
It's great.
Do you ever listen to Fantasmic theme just in the car?
Not in the car.
I have. I have.
OK, sure.
Sure.
In the last 24 hours?
I mean, you know, add a couple, add 10 hours to that, you know, and then you got the answer.
No, I've listened to I've listened to them.
I mean, it's good music.
It makes me feel like I'm in the park.
I've been in Disney World five times now and like I miss it sometimes.
So every once in a while, I'll like listen to like the firework theme music or some shit.
And I'm like, this is cool.
This is cool. Yeah.
Yeah, that's I mean, we have you seen like and maybe I'm introducing something that'll be like
you'll get sucked in loops.
They have just sort of like long multi hour loops for sort of like walking around in Tomorrowland.
The area music.
Yeah, the background music.
No, I have not done that.
All on YouTube.
I don't know if I can.
That might be that might be that's dangerous.
It is dangerous.
Yeah, I hate loops.
I like it's a small world.
Is the worst ride of all time.
Like I immediately fall asleep when I is my nap time.
Whenever I go, I go every time I go to any Disney Park.
It's a good that is a 15 minute allotted nap here.
Yeah, I was just talking up.
I like take a little nap on the Mexico Bo ride or I accidentally fell asleep on the Haunted Mansion.
Yeah, my first time after pandemic, a little ride nap.
I've been advocating.
Ride nap is quintessential for a long day at any park.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
And there's like that we've talked about it before to the Orlando air conditioning.
Specifically, there's something about getting from humid inside.
There's a weird smell to it, but I like it.
I don't know how to even describe that smell.
You know what I'm talking about?
I know what you're talking about.
Well, in the Orlando elements, you need the ride naps because the heat and the sun and
the humidity will just beat you up.
It will beat your ass.
Oh, yeah.
I was first time I went in.
Oh, it was June, which is dumb.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, so hot.
I was I remember at one point I was just like in a tank like my little like tight tank tops
that you used to wear.
And I'm like pulling my shorts up like it is hot.
And I'm from Chicago.
We got humidity.
Oh, yeah.
Like that Florida.
Yeah, that's another.
It's crazy.
You were just saying, too, and we'll get to like the scary stuff in a bit.
But you said something that we all like gasped right before we started recording.
That you have done a voice that is currently being used somewhere in Disney.
Well, we don't know anything about this.
So, yeah, reveal it here.
Yeah.
So I have a voice at Epcot right now and is actually Donald Duck.
But but not like the traditional like not that Donald Duck.
So in DuckTales, DuckTales came back recently.
And in that TV show, there are episodes where Donald Duck shows up
and he puts a voice modulator in this and then he can speak regularly.
And on a cartoon that's Don Cheadle.
Don Cheadle was like, I ain't doing this shit for you all for Disney World.
And so I got it.
You're a voice match for Don.
But you're a voice match for Don Cheadle as Donald,
which is funny because my role in Marvel's What If is also a roadie.
So for whatever reason, people think I sound like Don Cheadle.
Or I can do his voice well when I try.
But I guess I don't know.
I don't want to put you on the spot, but like, do you what do you have any like?
What do you do to make yourself?
So I mean, like, it's been a minute since I've done it.
But like so Don Cheadle, like Don Cheadle, like first, like he like softens his voice up.
And, you know, he'll he'll he'll say,
hey, we all about that superhero life here, you know, like he'll
I mean, it's way softer than my voice.
A little hushed, a little hushed.
Yeah, very slick, very together.
Very slick, very together.
Tony Stank Stank. I like that. I like that.
So like just a little like little like little swag, but
articulate slag is swag is what I called it.
Wow. Yeah, that's really good.
I hear that when I when if I have a job, then I'll like listen to it
and like really get into it.
But like, yeah, I got that, which was the cool.
I've been very lucky over the past two years booking a lot of dope
veal things and the coolest thing I've booked,
which is nowhere near as much money as I made for other things.
But the coolest thing I've booked is the thing Epcot.
Yeah. Where is it? Yeah.
What's the thing?
I so that I don't exactly know because I haven't been to actually see it.
I do know that it is so they were doing
it's like a new interactive thing in one of their new building
because they are revamping that quite a bit.
Or we may be in the play pavilion.
Is that which maybe is not open?
Is that? Well, it was open last year.
OK, OK.
I know they had it in something last year because I recorded that
in summer for Christmas of 2020.
OK, OK. So it is DuckTales World Showcase Adventure.
Does that sound right?
That is exactly it. I think it's coming.
Oh, it's not open.
Twenty two. Oh, it's not even open yet.
It's not open yet.
It was supposed to open twenty twenty and it was one of the things that got pushed back.
OK, you missed it then.
So I haven't missed it yet.
Maybe I should go for the opening day.
It's gotta be dope.
Staying outside. Disney World yet, apparently.
This is the thing about voiceover, especially for animation or animated stuff.
You'll do it a year plus before it even drops.
So you kind of forget about it.
I had no idea it didn't open yet.
You probably did in there like, oh, it's opening in like three months.
You're like, oh, cool. OK. Yeah.
Yeah. I was like, well, I'm not going.
So yeah, I kind of just I didn't forget about it, but I didn't like follow up
to make sure it actually opened.
Yeah. We're we're we're it's in the World Showcase.
Does it say where it specifically is there?
I think it's going to be throughout World Showcase,
because there used to be like a Phineas and Ferb like kind of
scavenger hunt sort of thing.
Kim Possible at one point in time. And Kim Possible.
So I think this is then technological upgrade where very cool.
There's spots and the Play Disney Parks app is involved.
They were very hush hush.
There's probably more information on it now, because when I booked it,
it was very hush hush.
It was just this. These are your line.
Working for Disney is crazy.
Like these are your lines.
This is your own password to log in.
It will self destruct in 24 hours.
You will never be able to go on this site again.
You is and I'm not even joking.
Like, that's exactly how they work.
Wow. But you're I mean, it's crazy.
You're Donald. That's pretty.
It's crazy. It is crazy.
Parks. It is crazy.
I don't equate it as I'm Donald Duck.
Like that would be the easiest thing to say is, yeah, yeah.
Donald Duck at Epcot.
But because it's not the Donald Duck voice, you know, so people are asking you
to do that voice, which is nearly impossible.
We've been tested and we're forced.
It is impossible. Yeah, it is.
It's very hard and it kills your voice.
Whoever kudos to whoever does it.
I think he has I heard some intel that he has like a limit.
He says like clock starts now.
I can't do it.
Literally can't do it.
Yes, to certain with Tony and Selma.
I think that's smart.
Yeah, because they may be pushing your limit.
You're like, hey, give me give me a series.
Do three. Do ABC.
You probably like you get in the A.
And that's it.
Yeah, you can't blame him.
Yeah. Hopefully they'll just replace Donald's voice permanently with with you.
That would be nice. That would be a listen.
Disney, I know you listening.
We know they're listening.
They don't like to respond.
They don't like to respond, but I know you listening.
I know by they than people who work at various stores and restaurants
and parks.
It was that counts as they've met a few inside.
We've met a few people who are like varying levels of varying levels.
Yeah, like inside by working.
Some levels that have made us go, oh, no.
What do they hear us say? Oh, no, that's fine.
I know what you're talking about.
Hint to me, what level were we?
What level? Oh, I don't know that it meant illegal.
Play legal. Yeah.
I wasn't as scared as Jason made it seem.
They also talked to somebody who has the last name, Iger.
We were.
He's that's talk about varying levels.
He's not even the CEO.
Is that who cares?
It's even not even anything to brag about.
Yeah. And I hear it's because we said some bad stuff about him.
That's gone.
I hear he's trying to get through our back catalog before he finally leaves.
That's why he's extending it by six months.
He's stuck on the city walk.
Yeah, he's stuck.
A lot to get through.
City walk gag.
He can't get through it. Yeah.
Yeah. OK, so let's talk scary.
Oh, yes. The Halloween season.
Yeah. Do it.
When we asked if you had thoughts about about scary stuff or haunt
cast the fright here, the scary month.
And you and you sure did.
It seems like you're like you're into haunts in general.
I mean, I'm into it.
I listen today is a Thursday.
Tomorrow I'm going to the Hayride.
OK, Saturday I'm going to Knott's Berry's scary or not scary.
Oh, great.
Two weeks ago, I was at Horror Nights.
I mean, I'm there.
I love it. Great. I love it.
Fresh from it. Did you did you do Fright Fest?
I haven't done Fright Fest in years, which is funny because I have Six Flags
season pass.
I have a crazy story with Fright Fest that I can tell you guys.
We would love to hear pretty.
We love Fright Fest on this podcast.
So Fright Fest. I used to love Fright Fest.
Obviously, Great America.
Sure. Yeah, we we had Fright Fest at in Gurney, Illinois.
And I so we were there one time.
And this is back in the O.G. days where like they could touch you and shit.
And like they was really they were really trying to scare you.
It was not sanitized to the degree it kind of is now.
Rule wasn't in place recently.
I thought that was always a rule.
No, they used to.
I I specifically remember.
I mean, they couldn't like molest you or like,
but they could like tap you on your shoulders and like really get in your face
and like put their little hands on you and stuff like that.
It's crazy. Yeah.
So we were in line for a maze.
It was me and like four people.
And we get in line.
We're kind of like as we're like at the back of the line,
like we walk in with the back of the line.
And as we get in line, this girl solo gets in line behind us.
And it's a long line, about our 10 minute wait
and like about 10, 15 minutes of us talking.
She like reaches out to she like injects,
interjects herself into our conversations like,
do you guys mind if I go in with you?
Like, I don't want to go into this ride by myself.
It's like, oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So we got to know Jasmine,
you know, because like I said, it's an hour long wait.
So we're talking, we're laughing, you know, we're chopping it up.
We're enjoying the wait.
And we finally get in.
And then like they put it, they take us in in the group.
It's like a group right in front of us and us.
So it's only like eight people because that's before they used to cattle you into.
And we're in there.
And then about 30 seconds into like the the actual like maze,
something jumps out of us, out of us and grabs her and takes her back.
Whoa.
So we're all like, what the what?
But like, we don't know this girl.
So we kind of just like, uh, and now we're on edge.
Now we're on edge and we're walking through and like we're like, what do we do?
And so we just kind of keep going and we're just so now now we're extra jumpy.
Yeah, of course.
And then like toward the end of the maze, this girl pops out and is Jasmine.
She's like bloody now.
And she's like she was a part of the fucking ride.
Wow. She was a part of the maze.
She was a part of the maze.
Like she's like, help me, please.
She's calling our names specifically and like,
and then like they like grab her back and like, you know, apparently kill her.
But yeah, she was a part of the ride.
And I was like, this is the dopest thing I've ever.
Yeah. Experience.
I was maybe like 15 at that point.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Especially ago.
It was pretty dope. So yeah, what a job.
She only does that probably like twice a day, twice a night.
Yeah. I wonder like how many times they had.
I'm sure now because because you're saying now they just like everybody kind of walks through.
Yeah, it's sort of really hard to do it now.
Yeah, because you'd really have to like make sure everyone was in groups.
And then there's like that have to be an interval between groups.
Yeah. Yeah. They probably can't do that, but that is such a great trick.
Pretty great. It was pretty great. Yeah.
I loved it. So I love RayFest.
I have not been to the one out here yet. OK. I should go.
Yeah, we we we did go two years ago and
there's a lot of teens and a lot of fog.
And yeah, you know, I don't want to I don't want to ruin it.
But we're going back next year. OK.
And it is
junky, but good. OK.
I mean, that sounds like Six Flags.
Yeah. Yeah.
There's if you're worried that the Tasmanian devil is still not well represented, he is.
Oh, still everywhere at Six Flags.
Magic. Beautiful. Beautiful.
So, yeah, you were saying
you were into that stuff.
You're into Disney Haunted Mansion.
Yeah. Love that.
Mansion. Love it all.
And I I love the haunted like live stuff.
Was not a fan of haunted movies for a long time.
But OK, I'm starting to get back into them.
But like live in the flesh, I'm there for it.
I'm there for it. It makes me want to fight.
I don't know.
Oh, they love to hear that. Oh, they love to hear that.
I would never touch a scare actor.
OK, I'm a professional myself.
I get it. But I guess I like that.
It gets your adrenaline going. Yeah.
If you had to, if it came to that, you would be ready.
I'm ready. I'm ready.
Now I make a joke out of it.
Like I'll go through horror nights and I'll like, dude,
like the fake like fights just like as a joke,
like just to make people laugh around me.
But like it's it's a good time.
It's always a good time. I love it.
Yeah, I get that. I it's not I don't know if I've ever thought about like,
oh, this is fighting energy for me.
But it's definitely like I just like sky.
I never sky dove or anything, but it feels like that.
Or you're like, it's a safe way to get your adrenaline up.
It is a safe way.
I truly do think it's fighting energy.
People are jumping in your face.
Yeah, I know you're close to fight energy as you could get.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Think about it.
If a stranger jumps in your face on the street, there was.
Yeah, I'm trying to think of like the closest.
I've never been in a fight.
Believe it or not, a guy who does a theme park podcast has not ever had a real fight.
Oh, man. We got to get you.
We got to get you in the fight.
You know what? Oh, that's right.
Mike loves fights.
If we can get me into fighting for real,
I like pro wrestling, but real fights.
This is your path to become the Rogan of the show.
In two years, you look like him.
The hair is gone.
HGH and I'm getting in fights after Horror Nights.
Yeah. I mean, look, if we lack for content in a couple of years.
Yes, I will do it.
You know what to do for the for the seven dollar tier.
Yeah.
I need that extra two dollars.
Closest I've ever been to a fight, it was at a wedding.
Oh, wow. I think it was like not so long.
I'm just trying to think of it. Yeah.
And it is it's it is the same feeling.
It is like a like your body's like, I'm ready to do something with all of this.
Yeah. Yeah.
And it is. Yeah. When Frankenstein attacks you or I can imagine, though,
I wonder, like, obviously not.
I usually only go to these big corporate, these not scary, the universal.
I wonder, there's got to be still places that can push you around a little bit.
They're 100 percent. Yeah. Yeah.
The desert. There's some weird ones like 40 minutes off the strip
that I've never been to that I'm like, they probably they they they mess with you.
There's some somebody I've never been to this and I would never go
because I'm not insane.
But like there is somebody I don't know the name of it, but they were like, yeah.
And like their goal is to torture you, like to get you to mentally break.
And like you're there for like four hours.
And yeah, like I'm not I'm not that's true fighting.
Now I'm ready to fight. Yeah.
You're ready to fight. Yeah.
At that point, there's no choice.
There's no choice.
I think a lot of those you usually have to sign a waiver.
But there and there was one downtown for years, downtown L.A.,
where they're like, OK, so they start by putting a bag over your head.
And then they lock you in a room.
And I'm like, OK, I already am uncomfortable.
Like, that sounds like a nightmare.
Yeah. You're you're you're off kilter already.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That makes sense.
The indie haunt circuit.
That's a question.
Are you going to start before the
your UFC days?
Do you? Well, before a 40 year old man gets into UFC in a few years,
although, you know, other 40 year olds have tried it.
Do I do the Indy Haunt?
I mean, I've done a little at last week.
We talked about how I failed at one.
I had an anxiety attack before doing an escape room. Oh.
But threat of a minotaur like it's going to be a really
I wasn't afraid of the minotaur. It's not really that's not that's a miss.
There was an issue. Yeah.
It was you were having this other issue.
But it's certainly in my head turned into that you were like flat.
You had very vivid nightmares of a 30 foot tall.
For the fun of the podcast.
Yes. The narrative is that I was afraid of the minotaur.
But not the communal hoods that had been passed around.
No, they did pass hoods to us to put on our heads to get walked in.
Yes, because it was a horror escape room.
So they walked you in with a hood on.
And I was having some claustrophobia in regards to the mask.
And then the idea of a 90 minute tight quarters.
It was not the minotaur that was scaring me, although
it didn't help that it was a minute.
Yeah, I'm sure. I mean, this sounds awful.
Yeah. I mean, my friend was fun.
My friends did it.
They sounded like they were in a ball because it was literally happening
outside the room while I waited in the most pathetic way possible.
All right. But here is here is the only part of the story.
Not that matters, but that like dictates whether you were right
or wrong in this situation to say it out. Did they escape?
They they did escape.
They had a lot of problems with the first room.
And it's one of the escape rooms, I think, where like the mad scientist was like,
well, why don't you look over here?
Why don't you come over to the right side of the room?
Yeah.
I mean, to give you a hint.
Yeah. So I think they did.
But I think it was maybe I think they said after they were done
that it was clear that at a certain point, at a certain time,
the whole game clicked into easy mode.
Oh, OK. OK.
I think that's how they put it.
So they did.
They would have escaped earlier if you were in there.
That you know what?
Someone in the group was being nice and said the same thing.
We needed you, man.
We got to the wire, bro. We got to the wire.
We'll have to do it again with you.
I got to do it again, unfortunately.
I have to conquer my fears here.
But in the yeah, I've done a little of the indie haunt scene.
But the phrase that we just made up, the indie haunt scene.
They're willing to regard it. It sounds cool, though.
When we did the Delirium show, we had to like hide under a bed
because the good robot told us to us he was dying because the bad robot was coming.
Yes, we did an immersive thing that it was like very intense.
And like you have to like roll under beds while like officers come.
Some like that sounds fun to me. It was fun.
Yeah, that was very fun.
Yeah. Climbing in our rope.
Yeah, you guys swung on a rope.
We got went on a different path and had to like crawl into rocks and stuff.
But there's this thing.
Yeah, there's a thing called Delirium and there's a horror version of it now,
which we probably should go try as well.
But OK, giving me you know, I mean, mental note.
I love that. I've done some more and all that type of stuff.
I bet you would love this. Yeah, probably.
It's such a long thing, but it's not yet not in the tight quarters.
And I don't know if there's a minute term, but how's the stuff this year?
But I guess most of it you're about to do.
But you did Horror Nights. I did Horror Nights.
Yeah, man. Horror Nights.
Horror Nights is weird, man, because I do enjoy it.
Like the first time I ever went to Horror Nights was 2013.
I was fresh out to L.A.
I moved in 2012. So
and at that point, it wasn't like I went off peak season.
I always go off peak season and it was fine.
Like it was still kind of like we're putting groups in instead of like cattle.
And then like around 2016, around that time, I don't know.
Like everybody just decided, you know what?
I'm going to do Horror Nights, too.
Even though it's been around for a long time, it's gotten so much more popular.
It feels like in the past, like four or five years where it's kind of miserable now.
So like it's really miserable because it's just too packed.
I'm talking lines of like two and a half hours to get to be just cattle, Dan.
So I didn't go to Horror Nights and like 17 or 18
because I went to Horror Nights in Orlando, which was great
because it's so much bigger.
Yeah. And it just seems like a party.
It's a party. It's a 100% party.
Yeah. So fun.
And like and they also had I mean, I think now they I know now they do.
They opened up Wizarding World during Horror Nights.
But at that point, they weren't.
But in Orlando, they did.
So you can go into like Wizarding World and it was like horror themed still, too.
It was pretty dope.
I went this week.
It was just as packed as like there's
COVID never existed.
It was just as packed as it's ever been.
Just like off putting for sure.
Just when even if there's not, you know, even if there's no actual danger,
you're just like, I've not been in a crowd of this nature in a year and a half.
It's pretty wild, man. It's pretty wild.
I will say this.
If you are lucky enough to afford it.
Do express. Yeah.
We got there and we saw the line and we was like,
let's pull the trigger.
We still did it after you were in because Mike didn't get to Mike was too late.
It was sold out. It was sold out.
Yeah, we we we did it literally as before they opened the doors at seven.
Oh, yeah, that's why we saw how packed it was like to get in. Yeah.
Hey, the lines were always to the security line.
So we was like, let's just do it.
And when I tell you I'm an asshole when I when I get to express lanes,
like I do a Vince McMahon walk and everybody
like who's like I do, I do a straight power walk, man.
Yeah, it is my thing. I love it.
I think it's so funny.
And eventually I felt bad because I was like, this is terrible
because they shuttle you in front of that entire line
and like just put you right in and you're walking past two hour lines
and cut it all of them like Fastpass is a little different because you,
you know, you eventually merge in with the real line.
And sometimes you can have your own line. Right.
It was none of that.
And you're going by the people that have waited the longest
because they're the front of the line. Yeah.
So it's not even like you're like the back of line.
It just got. They don't know. They don't know.
They don't know. They don't know to pay me.
These people set up the fajita effects like chilies.
But for theme part, like they like everyone in the line waiting
can see the express going to the front of the line and just going like,
oh, I should do that. I should have done that.
What can I ask what the fajita effect is?
Do you know? You know what this means?
Yeah. So the fajita effect at places like Chili's and stuff is sizzling.
They put it on the sizzling skillet in the plate.
And they purposely from the kitchen to the table, take a circuitous route
so that it like wafts the smell, wafts throughout the room.
And then they sell more fajitas because people feel like, oh, I should order that.
I'm a big Chili's fan and I actually didn't wasn't familiar with that right away.
Yeah. So that's also is the fajitas at Chili's have to be superb, correct?
I can only imagine.
They're fine. They're fajitas. They're seen everywhere pretty much.
They smell amazing.
They smell better than taste. Yeah.
Yeah. OK. So so you did front of the line, which yeah, that is the way to go.
If you can do it.
Way to go. Otherwise, it would have been a miserable night.
So that's kind of where it is now.
And that was September. I went on the day of my birthday, September 30th.
So going even now, now that it's October, closer to Halloween.
It's crazier, doesn't it? Yeah.
It gets crazy. Yeah.
We did it last weekend.
And I mean, the only other thing I could say you could do
is get the frequent fear pass, which is like 200.
Yeah. And then just go like the last two hours every night.
Yeah, that's smart.
And then that's like way down the line will be way down that way.
I guess you have to figure out parking if you want to save.
You can park down on Lancashire, my guess.
Walk up, take the tram if you want to be frugal, which believe me,
I've done it a few times.
Yeah. You also you can also take like the bus there.
You know, I've done that.
I mean, I live close, so it's not that hard for me.
But subway subway stop, right?
So my stop is right there.
You know, red line. Yeah.
So there's ways you can do it.
There's ways you can experience it and not be miserable.
Then this year, were there highlight?
We talked a little bit about it last week.
What were your highlights at Horror Nights at Horror Nights?
Um, the Frankenstein maze was very good.
Frankenstein maze was very good.
I actually like I wasn't expecting to like it because it was
seemingly like the most unpopular one as far as the way time.
No, it's zero weight. Yeah.
So that was pretty cool.
I should at this point, I've started to forget.
There was a Pandora's box.
There was Halloween for Halloween for Pandora's box.
There was the ghost or the haunting hill.
I think Hill House. Yeah.
I would think I think Frankenstein was my favorite thing.
Jabberwocky's, which is not horror.
But oh, you saw that I did not get to see the show.
Oh, really? So good.
It's so, so good.
Is there any horror?
Because, yeah, this I mean, people probably know this is a dance troupe.
But like the it is do they Halloween it up?
Not really.
They do like a like what?
Like a 30 second, maybe a minute long like to do to do to do to do.
They'll do like a little dance to like that or some shit.
You know, like, yeah, it's not is not horror based at all.
It is just straight up.
It's a show and a reason to sit down for half an hour.
So that that was the theme.
Yeah, I don't know.
I'm having a hard time remembering, which I guess is not a good sign.
I don't know about for you.
Like, oh, I was talking I liked Halloween for I like the end
when the five Michael Myers attack you.
Oh, yes. Halloween Halloween was fun.
I tend to like the ones where there are more.
Actual people instead of like fake.
Yeah, popping out at you.
When there's actually a human, because that's scarier.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So those are those are the ones I enjoy.
And there was a lot of Michael Myers and the Michael and Halloween one.
Yeah, because there were yeah, there were like five at the end
in the House of Mirrors that scared me.
Yes, that was a good one.
That was definitely a good one.
And in general, when you're in these mazes, what is your strategy?
Because I've seen I've seen people do a lot of different things.
My strategy still is a pretty cowardly one where I would prefer
if I was behind a group to not get the scare,
even though I can see the scare coming. Yeah.
I've done that strategy before. Yeah.
I've definitely implemented that. I hate being last.
They've been last.
I've done a couple of indie haunts where when I'm last,
there was one like creepy clown that followed me for five minutes one time.
And like at first it was funny.
There was cool.
I was like, I bro stuff.
Leave me alone.
But yeah, so I don't like being.
I don't mind being in the front.
Yeah, the front rarely gets it like.
Yeah, right. Right. Right.
The front really is always like two, three or four, like behind
because they'll see the front coming and like they don't want to blow their load
on like the first two people.
So they'll like wait like just a couple.
But now it's hard for me to like the last few times I've gone,
I've gone with like people I've dated, I'm dating. Sure.
And so I'm just like a shield at that point.
Well, you have to do that.
You have to be the shield in this scenario.
Yeah, I'm the shield.
I've been the shield lately. OK.
So it's been hard for me to have a strategy because I have one shoulder.
Your full body you can't access.
Yeah, I have a whole side of my body I can't access.
So, you know, like there will be sometimes
where I'll like get surprised and actually jump and scare.
But most of it is just like, oh, there's something right there.
Try to get the other person to get off my body. Yeah.
I've seen people do and I saw we had one person or a group in front of us do this.
And then a couple of years ago, we ran into Justin Michael and Betsy Sidaro.
And they did this, too.
They hold the line themselves in the maze in order to clear
the people in front, maybe from a full room.
So then they go into the room completely alone.
So they get the scares themselves, because now there's no one in front of them
because they want fresh scares each time.
And somebody did it. I think it was on maybe it was the Exorcist.
I forget which one somebody did that to us.
And I noticed the behave. I knew what it was because they were in front of us.
And then I was with my friend, Tim, and he was like, what is it?
Oh, they're trying to hold because they want the full scare.
And it is smart if you're like, if you like that type of thing. Yeah.
That's pretty smart.
I was like when Betsy and Justin were first doing it, I was like, what are they doing?
It's crazy. What? We're going to get all the scares like.
Yeah. But then I go, oh, don't you see, Michael?
It's precisely the idea.
Just the scariest man I know, Justin Michael said to me. Yeah.
Most fearsome person.
Scariest man. And the cool thing about that is like nobody's going to be
really mad at you because everybody's so disarmed.
You're not even realizing like, right. Right.
These people ain't moving.
Yeah. Like in front of me. Go, go.
You ain't even like clocking that that much.
Yeah. It's not like a drive through. Right. Right.
But yeah. So that is another strategy.
I guess. Cool. Yeah. It's not.
It's it's good because also, like, I do wish you had a little more time.
Is what we were talking about in the old days where you could kind of take your
time a little more versus now how they're just like you're literally just speed
walking through them.
The I will say the last couple of times I've been to the hayride.
Which I really enjoy, actually.
I think the Hayride is pretty fun.
Griffith Park. Yeah.
OK, OK. Yeah. The Hayride is pretty fun, but they also have mazes there, too.
Oh, really? I didn't know that. OK, OK.
Just like two or three.
And every year they have the big one, which is not a it's a true maze.
So it's not like, oh, you have a you have a you have a like
direction to go is go in, find your way out.
That's the that's the maze.
And so because of that, like you get I mean, you get lost.
Yeah, sure.
Like so you will get multiple scares and they so that's actually very fun.
I do. I actually have not done that.
That does sound really scary.
I'm going tomorrow, so I was hopefully they'll have it again,
because that's always generally my favorite thing to do there.
But and then like once you do finally find your at least the last two years
I went finally find the end,
you have to basically go through a birth canal.
It feels like where like you're walking and then it's tighter
and you're squeezing through it and it's just like all up on you.
And then you finally pop out outside.
Can I make of what leaves corn corn?
This canal is made of human body parts.
It's big plastic.
OK, it's not like inflated, like garbage bag material.
Exactly what? Yeah.
I see. Yeah.
It's like a big balloon or something you're going through.
Oh, interesting.
They have that at what's there's there's I think it's paranormal
ink at not scary farm.
That's sort of how the end is, I think.
I think I'm probably messing messing around.
And you've not been to nots. That's great.
I'm going Saturday. OK, yeah.
That's great. Yeah.
There's an outdoor there's a hallway.
Did you do terror tram?
This? Yes.
The since since the topic is the purge.
Yes. I'll spoil this for people because it's been open for a while.
But there's I watched the walkthrough.
I actually watched someone live streaming at opening night.
But it was like five thirty in the afternoon and the sun hadn't set yet.
So I've seen the terror tram in broad daylight and also in pitch black.
OK, scarier in pitch black, I'll say that.
But there is one there's that outdoor hallway of like netting
and people in what I believe are called ghillie suits jumping out.
But I was like, oh, my God.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, that got me a couple of times.
Oh, I got me a couple of times.
The tram was generally not as exciting because it's very short.
Yes. Or once you get off the tram.
But like once you get to that part you're talking about
the first that was my first real like, oh,
oh, no.
Oh, yeah, it got me.
So, yeah, if you haven't done Halloween Horror Nights
Universal Hollywood, the the the tram tour drops you off
on a part of the back lot that you wouldn't normally be walking around.
It's like towards the end of the the typical tram route.
And it seems like they still do it in the same place where you're going through.
Now Whoville's gone.
They don't have to make a demented Grinch world.
Like, how do we justify clowns?
I don't know. How do we justify Christmas here?
We don't have Jack Skeleton as our property.
We do a scary Christmas without all of the scary Christmas characters
that everybody knows.
That's a mystery.
So but it is, you know, it's scarier stuff on the route
because you got the Psycho House and the Bates Mattel
and then the War of the Worlds plane crash set, which is really, really brutal.
And the theme changes of what this is, they seem to incorporate
different horror properties into the videos that you watch on the way down.
And I think Chucky's been part of it or I forget all.
Chucky was a part of it.
My favorite one, I mean, since this is what we're talking about, was the purge.
Which is this year.
No, it's not this year, but that's my favorite one.
They had this year is no theme, really.
Oh, I mean, overall, overall.
So we have purged down there and stuff like. Yeah. Yeah.
So there was. Yeah. So what?
Twenty eighteen. Is that right?
Was it was the one you're talking about, which was like the whole
like theme, basically? Yeah.
Like they've done Chucky and they've done the purge
as the theme of the terror tram at some point. Right.
Right. OK. Yeah.
Well, this year, it's the second time it's the purge.
It's mostly the purge. Is it mostly the purge still?
They're calling it the ultimate purge.
But then Norman Bates is also hanging around.
Yeah. Confuses it. Yes.
I like. Wait, why Norman still?
Yeah. You're absolutely right, because I took a picture of it.
Me and a friend go watch every purge movie in the theater.
So when they come out.
So like I took a picture of the ultimate purge and sent it to her.
So I forgot that probably because most of it didn't feel like the purge.
Like the shit you're talking about when they jumped out at you.
They don't. That's not the purge.
Yeah. It could in theory happen in a purge.
It does. But you know, a lot can have any.
The purge is just general.
I guess if somebody wanted to dress up his leaves and jump out of a bush,
then I can and then slink back into it.
I guess that is the reason not kill you.
Just scary.
We stole the ghillie suit.
This is not my property. It is a crime.
We have 12 hours. We have 12 hours to jump scare anyone we want.
That's what the new purges move very suddenly.
Yes. In ways we've been trained to move, but still like our weapons
never get that close to you.
But we jerkily move.
Everyone's trained to move in a very jerky fashion
that is unnerving to watch a human do. It is. Yeah. Yeah.
So I think that's what made me fall in love with Horror Nights.
And I to talk about the purge a little bit.
I don't want to jump ahead or anything like that.
But like I was pleasantly surprised by the movie.
The first one, the Ethan Hawke one.
I thought it was going to be a steaming pile.
And like it was actually very good. I was like, this is good.
Like the concept is like interesting.
And the movie was well executed and you you root for him.
You hate people. You like people and shit.
I was like, OK, I like him. He's good.
I watched it a couple of nights ago in preparation for this, having not really.
I did watch Election Year and I remember absolutely zero of it.
So I can't speak to Election Year.
I remember being entertained by it.
But yeah, pretty is a real movie. It's pretty good.
The first one is like a true like story.
And yeah, yeah.
My qualm with it maybe is that
it does become like a people are trapped in a house
and people other people are trying to kill them and get into the house.
It becomes that kind of movie.
And it's a good version of that kind of movie.
But I am just so obsessed with the premise
and that America would adopt this purge plan.
Yeah, that I just want to see like periphery.
I want to see congressional hearings.
Like how did they get to this point?
Well, that's what did the various parties think?
How did it make like how did that vote go?
Yeah. What was the debate like on CNN and the lead?
Or podcast saying, sounds like maybe there's something you need to watch.
The first purge.
I was wondering if I should.
The first purge is exactly that.
They do go into dry.
They go into logistics. OK, OK.
They go into the logistics.
You see what? Because all right, here's the thing.
If the purge happened in real life, who we are?
No, I know we can.
I mean, somebody, I guess, would murder people.
But we're going to be fucking on the streets and stealing and shit.
Like we're going to be murdering people like for the most part.
People still don't have it in them to like it seems like in the purge,
in the purge verse, 70 percent of people are murdering at least.
Yes. And we all have a secret.
No, of course I would.
Like most of us would do it.
But in reality, probably it's just like it gets a little kooky.
It's a little kooky.
Like, you know, because in my mind is like, all right, I murdered this person.
And then what tomorrow I got to go like to, you know,
Ralph's with your nephew. Like, I don't want to like.
Oh, how they happen.
Huh? I killed your auntie last night.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. You can't do that.
It was legal. It was legal.
It was legal. You know the rules.
You know, they said on TV and everything in the first one,
they have to all still live in the same cul de sac.
They all live in this fancy neighborhood together.
And like, yeah, what's and then things do go very badly.
So, yeah, what's the rest of the year like for the community?
Bad, terrible, horrible.
Yeah, really. But the first purge, the actual movie.
So not the first purge movie, but the movie that's called the first purge,
which I think is the purge for or something like that.
Yeah, you're right.
Because election year kind of wraps it.
I don't want to spoil anything for you, Scott.
The election year kind of.
Ironically, the purge election year had a happy ending.
But then in 2016, in real life, Americans voted for a real life purge.
Yeah, the movie had a happier ending.
Then they go back to see it.
And then there was a TV series that's ongoing, I think.
Or did it get canceled?
I think it got canceled.
And then whatever idea he had for the third season, he's like,
I guess I got to make another movie.
Like, it seems like they're always like, you want to keep making one release?
And they're like, hell, I wasn't going to.
But then I had an idea.
Purge ever after or purge forever.
If you want the things you're explaining,
you want to see is basically purge two through five.
Where it's just like murder and debauchery.
And then you even get one in there that explains like that, you know,
this is the thing we want to do.
Oh, it's not working. What can we do to make it work?
And like, yes, boardrooms, schematics, overheads.
Yeah, I watch a whole movie where there is no purging.
Just watch like kind of just a dry like a film.
You want like the Senate parliamentarian?
Is that what the position is?
The one who's making all the problems.
Right. The one who like says, oh, yeah, you can't pass this bill today.
And they go, oh, I guess that person's right.
The negotiating with I want to see who the the fucking who are these best
cinema and the mansion.
Yeah, I want to see who's holding up the purge.
Like, what do they want in return?
They don't want anything. They just want chaos, I guess.
Yeah. Right. If we give you this, you want to see who's the Mitch McConnell of the Purge?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And where does he where does he land?
I forgot that there was there weren't
I didn't realize that the founding fathers of the new founding fathers of America
is a party.
I knew that premise that that is exists in the better that it is.
You have Democrats, you have Republicans, and then the new founding fathers
show up and like, no, no, no, we're wiping the wiping the room like in a maze.
You're all gone. Yeah. We stand for purge.
And it did. Yeah. Boy, it works, too.
It fixes. I mean, listen, they I guess I guess it works in their in their world.
You know, three hundred and sixty four days of the year.
Everybody's happy.
Somehow like somehow unemployment goes down specifically.
It's not just because there's less people.
There is less people.
And they get a little into the later ones.
I remember it's like, oh, they they explain the less people part.
Yeah, there's some other stuff going on.
Well, there's a lot of there's like a big seasonal employment
and like post purge morning blood sprayer downers.
Yes. Yes. Yes.
If it does, even if you only work one day out of the year,
you get up severed arms in real life.
They're employing Frank Grillo just constantly.
So they have like eliminated unemployment for one guy who works,
seemingly works a lot.
So there was a thing going around Twitter a while back.
It's like, here's like eight action movies Frank Grillo did in the last two years
that you never know.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Very funny.
I wonder, is he in any with Bruce Willis?
He has to be. Oh, yeah.
That shows up. I'm this too much of a sidetrack.
But Bruce Willis is movies.
He works. He works like how are we like on a completely?
There's one of the biggest movies of all time, and he's made probably
20 movies we've never heard of in the last two years.
Well, him, Nicholas Cage and Schwarzenegger are no less of stars.
They're all as famous as they were and are in hit movies sometimes,
but also sometimes they are maybe a lot of times they're in movies
that don't exist, essentially. Yeah.
Wild. Anyway, I can't think of the last Bruce Willis movie I saw was Glass.
Oh, yeah.
But I don't think I've done one since Over the Hedge.
Oh, just just because.
No, no, no, no. You got to read a few here.
Out of Death Survive the Game.
No, these are words.
Midnight in the Switchgrass. Nope.
Breach Cosmic Sin.
Now, these is first movies.
These are from 2021. Oh,
we all have nothing to do but watch stuff and we haven't even heard of
seen a YouTube video promoting one of these.
I thought it was Grillo, but it might not.
It's a different guy. I think.
All right. Just just a few more.
Just indulge me, please.
Hard Kill.
I've I've actually heard of that.
It's Tracy Morgan in that.
No, no. Who's in that?
So that's Jesse Metcalf.
I don't know. I haven't heard.
You just think you've heard of it, maybe because that's like you're like,
how a movie must have been called Kill by now.
Movies have been going for many years.
I will say that.
You're going to that.
He plays Chalmers in Hard Kill.
Chalmers Chalmers.
Simpson's name. Simpson's name.
Survive the Night.
Trauma. I've heard of Survive the Night.
Trauma Center.
No, wait, I think I know Survive the Night is the name of like
that's what they called the Purge event.
One of the years of following our.
It's all tied together. Wow.
That's kind of that phrase.
Oh, no, it's really.
It's a pretty common phrase.
Survive the Night. Yeah.
And that we should say that at
Universe Studios Hollywood's Horror Nights,
the Purge has been used a lot.
The Purge is very popular.
When you put some of this up.
Yeah, there's been so many Purge things.
There's been a lot since.
So I went to the first one in 2014 because the first Purge movie is 2013.
I think it's 2013 and there was a scare zone simultaneously.
I mean, that's the same year.
So I definitely.
I mean, at this point, that was almost 10 years ago.
So I vaguely remember that.
But I remember when like the Purge was like the like the theme of horror.
Seemingly.
And the reason I loved it so much because I saw the movie
and it was one of those fun things where you kind of get
where you see a movie is like, hmm, I wonder what that would be like.
Right. If that like that as outlandish as it is, is somewhat conceivable.
You know, like Michael Myers is not conceivable, like Jason is not conceivable.
But like that, we can see a world where shit falls apart.
It's like, yes, conceivable, right?
Or since the movies started coming out.
Exactly right.
And so like.
Like being in the in in horror nights, you know, before they let you in,
everybody's just kind of huddled in the front there.
And so as is getting time to open at 7 p.m.
once 7 p.m. hits, the first thing that hits is those sirens.
So you kind of like, oh, shit,
kind of like push that like.
And then you hear tonight is the founding, like the same message
they do in the movie is what they do.
And then when it's like blessed be the founding fathers and a big explosion
goes up, the doors open and fucking all the scare actors go at it.
Yeah, it was dope as hell.
It was dope as hell.
I was like, oh, this is cool as shit.
That sounds really good.
It was very fun.
And now it's time for it is 7 p.m.
like in the movie. That's nuts.
Yeah, it really it really worked.
And like the people I were with, we were freaking out because the thing that too,
when they do the chainsaws, you can actually smell the gas.
And like it was pretty it was pretty dope.
So at first it was great.
Now it's just kind of like the go to the well.
We have this lying around.
Yeah, we have this lying around.
You know, I guess it works.
So and I still enjoy it.
It's still fun. But now it's pretty old.
But like Orlando over like, yeah, about eight or 10 years,
they did they've done two scare zones and one like haunted house out here.
There's seven different.
Yeah.
I heard things right over the years.
One year there was a scare zone and a maze like in the same year.
Yep. Yeah, they kind of like I'm trying to think of this year they had
like they sort of the Bride of Frankenstein Lives was kind of tied
into the scare zone with like the Cirque du Soleil performers.
Yeah. Kind of. Yeah, kind of.
Things were a little muddled this year.
Yeah. Yeah.
Horror Nights, which was fine.
It was fine. Yeah.
But they there were no like true scare zones.
It felt like where like, you know, you're in this section
and this is the per section. This is this section.
Well, yes, to be super clear also, because I haven't been
and I'm still parsing this myself.
A scare. There's mazes in their scare zones and scare zones are like
general areas of the parks that are not just like thoroughfares.
Like you're going to walk through here and there are going to be chainsaw
people or people jumping out of here or whatever.
So it's like it's the equivalent of like they would turn
like like Main Street would be a scare zone.
Sure. During the day.
It's pleasant. Yeah.
So like that's how is.
So it's just like the areas you walk through to get to stuff
or the different lands or whatever are scare zones.
And not everything is.
There are certain areas of the park that are just a place.
Right. A lot of a lot of the upper lot of there is.
They tell you on the map which places usually are scare zones.
Notts has the very robust scare zones this still this year.
Oh, good. Excited for that.
And that's like to you.
Not as good because when we were going on the scare zone,
all of a sudden, like fog got pumped.
Like, first of all, we were like, we're the only people out here in this area.
Then fog pumped.
We walked through the fog and then we're like, there are 20 scare actors
just for two of us.
And we just walk through scare actors.
You're like, that's pretty good.
Yeah. And they followed us for a little too long. But
a little a little.
Sometimes I be following you to and after a while you like, I bra.
There's like, yeah, you're like 20 seconds ago.
And if you left, it would have been perfect.
But this extra 20 seconds, I cannot I cannot appreciate.
Yeah. So, yeah.
So like two years ago at Horror Nights, they had a full.
Did you say you went to two years ago? No, I went.
I went 2019. I went the year before COVID shut down.
Yeah, it goes. Was like one of the.
Yes. I've seen Ghostbusters because like they had a full scare zone
when you would walk down by like Transformers in the lower lot.
You would have to walk from basically Transformers to another section
on the back lot to get to Ghostbusters and get to two other mazes, I think.
And there was a hole in that tunnel.
Yeah. And it was a scare zone.
Yeah. It was really cool.
And that was Purge, I think. Right. Was that purge related?
Yeah. Was that what that was?
I should double check that to make sure. Is that toxic tunnel?
Was that what that was?
Isn't there one thing that there was something called zombies or mutants?
Maybe that's what it is. Toxic.
Yeah, I got to check.
That's where someone accidentally hit me with a lead pipe.
Yeah, they can't listen.
Like, you know, the scare actors when there's not purge,
you know, they get close and this stuff.
But the purge specific scare actors, I mean, kudos to their training
because they are literally trained to push it an inch
in like in front of your face.
Oh, this hit me somehow.
Like I hit me and I looked around and no one was like I was like 15 feet.
I was like, you know, on purpose, man.
I'm really like Nick, like Tonya Harding style or.
Yeah, it was that it was I was OK.
But I was like that's what was supposed to happen.
Yeah. That guy got like maybe it was like his first night.
And he's like, I'm going to take a swing.
And then it flew out of his hand.
Hit me in the leg.
Maybe you didn't tip somebody or I didn't tip it or look.
I knew it was a tip at horror nights.
Was there a was there a thing outside at the end?
I am always conscientious of tipping.
Well, when you go through a maze, you're just supposed to have some
like small change, small bills in your hands and you're like, yeah,
for each Adam in the chaos and they'll pick it up after you're gone.
It's a strip club.
You don't know the money on the ground when you go through the maze.
You didn't notice all the money.
You're just throwing money at Michael Myers.
You go through each maze.
Thanks for the scares. Oh, that was a good one.
Thank you. Just look at the movie.
I was wondering why the website fax section said like, arrive early,
make sure to allow time to park, consider express, bring ones.
I think, Jason, I think you are correct.
It was called the toxic.
The specific one we're talking is toxic tunnel.
OK, but is it so different than the purge?
I don't know. Yeah.
Not a guy with a pipe and a mask where the purge, I guess, just fits
like something universal needed.
It's just that we need a property that is mayhem and people run around
and scary masks. Yeah.
Which is what they were doing anyway.
And now they can say, oh, yeah, that's a theme.
That's a purge is what that is.
And it allows them to have like realistic weapons like lead pipe.
Yeah. Right. And the chainsaws, like they are really revving those things up.
I'm sure they're not real, but they smell it.
Yeah. Well, they take.
Yeah, they take the blade off of the chainsaw.
Oh, that's why it still has the grind. Is that right?
Yeah. They yeah, they take the blade off.
And also my girlfriend used to work in universal.
She ran into someone she used to work with and he's like, oh, yeah,
I'm back in the room. I'm working the hard night shift.
I'm in charge of the chainsaws.
Like there's a guy whose job is just to make sure the
chainsaws don't kill people. Make sure they're all gassed up.
Yeah. Oh, the blade is on this one.
Oh, the blade. Yeah.
OK. Yeah. One out of every ten.
That's a big job.
So they take the chain off.
Those masks are scary. Those masks are creepy.
Oh, yeah. Like the the white.
I mean, you know, I'm a black.
I'm a black man. So white mask scare me.
But the white, the pretty blonde white.
I'm like, that shit is terrifying.
Yeah. Yeah. It's terrifying.
They are. Yeah, it does all play into that.
Like in the I've kind of only recently seen that first one.
But since that is like upper crust shitty snooty housing development
and that is it's this like sneery like and that main guy
who is like depicted in various mazes, like the sort of like
the buttoned up suit.
See a little patch. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
With the long smiling mask.
Like, yeah, yeah. I love this.
He is he's referred to in multiple different ways.
He's called the polite stranger.
He's also called the smiling perjurer.
And one wiki page listed him as the appropriate gentleman.
Yeah. It's the polite stranger, the thing where you sit in your hand.
You know what I'm talking about?
I know what you're talking about.
Sorry to be lewd. Sorry to be lewd on the podcast.
Like you mean, and it goes up and it goes down.
No, no, no, no, no.
You know, you know, that's it.
Scott, you're thinking further.
You're thinking of the proper gentleman.
That's what that's called.
Up your butt as a gentleman.
The stranger takes the front, the gentleman takes the back.
I see. OK, OK.
Now I know. Yeah, yeah.
Now, you know. Now, you know.
Scott, I'm going to edit yours out because that was lewd.
That was the talk about that.
I thought you were saying no, no, no, no.
You sit on your own hand and put it up your butt.
You sit on it for so long, it eventually goes up your butt.
Look, I mean, somebody has for sure done that.
People probably do that every day, but I'm sure they have.
I was talking about.
So what's this gentleman Jason was talking about?
Oh, that's that's the guy.
Yeah, the general smiling guy.
Yeah. Yeah.
But like I reading, I mean, the the fandom page for Halloween Hard
Nights, it's so funny to see all the scare actor characters listed out of like
teeth mask perjurer.
Yeah. Big Daddy's Minions.
It's weird, though, because like the reason and like this
the last movie that came out this year,
which I was very high for when I went to go see.
Oh, no, I was very high when I went to go see it.
It was a delight. I enjoyed it.
You would not, Jason.
I couldn't. I like these.
What I've seen of these movies, like I want to do them all the way through.
I really like this world.
I think they're they're very current.
It's like a great example of like genre movies that you can force, like topical.
You put the topical stuff into.
Yeah. And it works and it feels very modern.
The first purchase was very topical.
It involves like Black Lives.
And like that is very top.
And this last one is very top.
It might as well be called Purge. Trump is president.
That's pretty much what it should be.
He's blown out. They were so psyched when Trump got elected.
Now we can put it all in the movie.
Put it all in there.
Yeah. Yeah.
Because the election year does seem like they thought
the other result was going to happen.
Of course. That's exactly what they thought.
And this was like this was what could have been.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
But the reason the first I mean, they use
just the first one, really, because the first two through
the rest of them.
Gets a little wild.
Like, yeah, people are tripping out of their mind.
The murders are a lot more brutal.
There's a lot more sexual assault.
There's a lot of things in and that purge world that aren't
universal horror night.
Yeah. Right.
But the first one, there's nothing really in that outside of killing people,
which we love murder.
So we can kill people.
Murder is fine.
We can put that around all your kids.
Murder is cool.
So that's easy.
So that's why you get a lot of those characters or you get big daddy's minions
instead of big daddy, because big daddy was fucking people.
Oh, is that right?
When does big daddy come in? What's what movies?
I can't remember.
Is he in multiple names?
They don't they don't name them in the movies.
I yeah, just in like the credits or like fan pages.
They probably have to go through like when they're like looking at the new movie
or something, they're trying to apply it.
And they're like, OK, let's get the politics out of this.
Let's get the message out of it.
OK, but can we keep all of the murder?
Yes. Yes.
We cannot say anything political.
Yeah. OK, good.
I think one of the reasons, Scott, the first one you're saying,
like is a little more tame and all was it had a three million dollar budget,
which is very small.
And then it made a box office of eighty nine million dollars.
So a wow, a grand slam.
So there's a case scenario.
Yeah, it is like, yeah, it's a how it does become a all in a house.
Like a lot through a movie kind of the easiest.
So the budgets for the the following ones kind of went went pretty high up.
But I think all pretty successful. They keep doing.
They still keep doing.
I mean, I don't know how this last one did because, you know, pandemic and everything.
And the last one was pretty.
I also want to preface this by saying this.
I really love the purge movies.
They're very far. I enjoy them.
I have, like I said, I have a purge friend.
We go see each movie with.
But like, as I say that, make no mistake, they aren't they not.
They aren't like great movies.
Sure. Yeah, they are.
It's not like, you know, they are.
You know what you're going into,
like as you sit down in the theater to watch these movies. Right.
Or so I think they just keep making them because they're just fun movies.
And like you said, it's very easy to put a topic on it.
And although I don't know where they can go after Purge forever,
it does feel like that felt like the end.
It feels like like a Blumhouse is like, come on, come on.
And he's like, no.
And then there was an interview where it was like, well, I kind of had an idea.
Like there was something in use on the TV show.
So yeah, yeah.
And the way it and I don't want to spoil it.
I mean, Purge forever is self-explanatory.
Sure. It's like, is it in a town
where they've decided like, oh, we're just going to like or is or a whole state?
What is the reach of the place where the Purge?
No, I guess it.
They don't do very well with
it always stays and just kind of like one part of the town or whatever.
I guess the last one does kind of go to different
states or whatever.
But I would probably say it's a national movement.
I see. It's a national movement.
Yeah. Yeah.
It's a metaphor. It is 100 percent.
If I can.
It's a metaphor for one. Yeah.
The first one was very much like, what if the future was like this?
Now it's kind of like, damn,
y'all been living it.
What if this is a solution for getting out of it?
Yeah, it's pretty crazy.
So I don't know what they're going to do in the parks, you know, because.
It's very fun.
It seems like they're going to keep going to that well.
I don't know how they can heighten it in the parks.
It feels like what you're saying is the correct me if I'm wrong.
It never got better than that first seven p.m.
siren with all the scare actors for me.
No. And I guess part of that is because like I went
to the first one and to multiple ones after that.
So maybe if you go for the first time, I don't think they're doing that anymore.
We're like, you know, the open of universal is the open of like the purge.
They haven't done that in the past couple of years
because they even did that like three years in a row.
But that first time they did that specifically felt super special.
And it legitimately freaked me out.
It freaked people out because you were because as you're walking through,
there is like a hundred scare actors, all purge related.
Yeah. Like just coming at you with chainsaws and bats and swords
and like all types of like the weapons that they had in the first purge movie.
Because pretty well.
Yeah, that sounds like because we've talked about like when they're adapting,
either either they're a excuse me, a ride or a themed experience.
Like, what do you want from it?
If you like this movie, what do you want from it?
That sounds like the ultimate version of what you want.
So until they are, if they don't do that, you're just getting OK.
Little tastes of it.
But it's like, you're not like maybe I would assume too, with like, you know,
we've seen this many times, nothing, no property stays dead.
So maybe it needs like a five year break.
I think that's probably best.
Yeah. It needs a nice break.
And then the sirens can blare again in five years at Horror Nights.
It is. You know what I equated to?
And I not purposefully did this, but it actually works.
For whatever reason today, I decided to watch Final Destination three.
And then it made me really it made me think about that franchise
where because they put out about four or five of those.
Yeah. In a 10 year span, too.
And then after a while, you're just like, OK,
like, we kind of got to stop doing this. Right.
Where else do we go with this? Right. Yeah. Yeah.
And and they did.
They there hasn't been a final destination movie in like 10 years until
there is now one being filmed.
So now it feels like, all right, we kind of went away from that.
Well, for about five, 10 years, it will feel a little more fresh now.
You say, yeah. Yeah.
Give the audience a little just, you know, a few of us have done improv training.
They say rest the game.
The game. Yeah.
This means to, you know, put whatever thing you're doing on hold for a few
a manner of minutes or seconds.
Seconds. Yeah.
Scream. That happened with Scream.
Yes. They did a bunch of Scream movies.
They did a TV show, an MTV, I think, kind of only tangentially related.
And now there is like Scream sort of like the David Gordon Green
Halloween's where it's like everyone's back.
They've aged in real time. Yeah.
And there's a new generation also dealing with the killer. Yeah.
So which means, you know, when
the purge comes back, Ethan Hawke will be back in it.
Senator Charlie Rowan.
All our favorites.
All your favorites.
Big Daddy, Frank Crullo.
But they'll all be a little wiser, a little older, a little gray.
Everybody's got beards.
I'm poking through the masks.
I'll say this to the listeners.
I don't know that the TV show is as good, but if you want something
a little less gruesome, the two season purge TV show that was on USA
by nature is less brutal than the movies because it was on broadcast cable.
Yeah. Yeah.
The movies are.
I mean, like after the first one, the first one isn't so bad,
but like the rest of them are brutal.
Like they are pretty pulpy and schlocky. Yeah. Yeah.
But then that what I could tell, because I threw on a second of the TV show
and it just like once you've once you're at like
Canadian TV production value,
you kind of like the pulpy sound of it.
Yeah, I felt like maybe it'd be interesting to watch some of the show.
And it's like so much slower and it's not all boring.
And then like you just watch a trailer of election year and like, oh, yes, a style.
Like I think it's meant to be movies probably.
It is meant to be because it's supposed to simulate a night, right?
Which is much easier to simulate in a movie as opposed to over a season.
Now, I haven't seen the actual TV show, so I don't know if they're still doing like
I don't know how I'm sure it's probably like they lead up to the night
and maybe the aftermath, I don't know.
I mean, I'll probably watch it. Flash forward. Yeah.
Dreams. Well, everything else we can do where the movie is very,
it very easily lends itself to say the start of the movie is the beginning
of the purge and the end of the movie is the end or the start of the movie
is the beginning and the end of the movie is the end. That's it.
That's it. It's pretty tidy to have a siren that begins your movie
and a siren that ends your movie.
Yeah. The fans commence.
Should I add the siren at the start of the episode?
I think you should.
I think you should. Yeah. All right. I'll do it. Yeah.
Yeah. But also you should leave you asking that question into the.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Looking here.
That you're like, ah, pull behind the curtain. Yeah.
And the intro has to be.
Oh, that's to be the intro. Oh, yeah.
I wrote it already. Oh, did you?
Great. Oh, wow.
Scott wrote the great.
I love it.
You'll have heard it already. Yeah.
Oh, the creative process at work.
I'd be remiss if we didn't mention
one of the more infamous Halloween Horror Nights purge
a little Halloween Horror Nights.
Whoopsie. That happened a few years ago.
Oh, I know. Yes.
I found this on L.A.S., but it was on most news websites at the time.
So in one of the purge movies, they recreated this in the park
in one of the scare zones where an auctioneer is auctioning off
victims for purgers to then purge.
And the auctioneers are very crass and bawdy. Of course. And
a this is from the L.A.S.
A trio of 13 year old girls and their mothers are not very happy about
a universal Halloween Horror Nights actor who referred to the girls
as hookers and sluts during a press conference yesterday.
Two of the girls and their mothers, along with feminist lawyer
Gloria Alred, said the incident occurred while they were visiting a hut
based on the purge anarchy, according to The Hollywood Reporter.
So if you are at a press conference,
if there is a press conference being called with a number of people
and Gloria Alred and it is about you, you fucked up.
Yeah, that's a person I'd like to never say my name.
Yeah.
Listen, I will say that's one thing I do appreciate about Horror Nights.
I, Fright Fest is probably the first, like, big entity of like horror
that I went to as a as a teenager.
And I don't remember them being able to curse and stuff like that.
Obviously, and I cursed at Disney is not even a real Halloween.
But like the.
Yeah, we've never even talked about it.
Who cares about it?
Yeah, yeah.
It's boogie.
Very nuts.
It was scary.
I will never pay for that in my life.
And I love Disney.
I will never pay for that.
Boo bash.
Yeah, boo bash.
You're going to pay for the boo bash?
Nah, nah, nah, nah.
But they like could get crass.
Like I remember Chuckie like cursing people out one year.
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
And, you know, we mentioned it already.
It is on game for purgers to say stuff like that,
because, again, all crime is legal for 12 hours.
So they're not really thinking about decorum.
And nothing about decorum at all.
Yeah, there's a lot of stuff in those movies that it's like, oh, we can't really.
Even with the horror night standards, we can't we can't really do this.
Yeah, you should probably like ID everybody.
Make how old are they?
All right. What am I allowed? OK.
There's an age limit.
I thought it was I didn't think it was as young as 13, but maybe I think you can go younger.
I saw a very young child going to the house in front of me with her assume with father.
And some of them look very excited to be there.
Well, that's what I'm like, like, like this the whole time.
And I'm like, child appears to be not fazed at all by any of this.
Yeah. I don't know if it says more about me
that if I would have heard that live in the park,
I would have lost my mind laughing.
I mean, it's absurd.
Because I think I mean, like to I think.
I mean, maybe you have to just kind of say on the ticket, which nobody reads,
like, hey, this is going to be going to get some profanity here.
You're going to get some of these things, right?
This is this is PG 13 or, you know, at high PG 13.
This is TV 14. Well, yeah.
The problem is, no one reads the ticket.
Well, I mean, yes, the protestors, actually, and nobody reads the ticket.
But like you said, it makes sense that they would say wild shit.
I mean, maybe don't call sure.
And a hooker in a slut.
Yeah, but it makes.
But if I would have heard that, I wouldn't have like thought it was as jarring.
Well, if I like if like because, you know, they have the new on the regular day,
they have the New York Street performers.
Yeah. We're like, hey, look at this guy or whatever.
Like, if one of those guys called me a dickhead, I would have loved it.
Yeah. Look at this guy.
Look at this dickhead right here.
And I'd be like, whoa, what? Oh, yeah.
We have the Starway called you the evil Starway.
Oh, you know about this, that the escalator turns.
Yes. Mean.
During or not. Yeah.
This escalator. Yeah.
Talks about you and like not like it's not life specific, but it does get mean.
What's the thing about because they reference drugs.
They I was on it.
They do not mention weed anymore.
They mentioned it multiple years in a row, at least not in the I was doing the whole thing.
Like a couple of years ago, whenever we did it, it was like in like no smoking on the
Starway. And that goes for weed.
Yes, I remember that. No.
It's so funny. It was great.
I again, I was like, whoa, weed and universal.
They said weed. Yeah.
They did not say weed this time when I was on the Starway and I was crestfallen.
I was so upset and I mentioned it to Tim Chang, who I was with and I was like, Tim, they
usually say weed about weed.
And he goes, what do you what?
He goes, it's legal.
I guess. Oh, yeah.
That kind of hurts.
Yeah, I guess it's not.
No, we. Nark.
Yeah.
I guess. Hold on to the handrail.
That means you hookers.
I mean, I guess if you if you're going to call anybody a hooker, call everybody a hooker.
Don't just single out.
That's safer.
That's a single out of 13.
And it specifies that like the actors like, come here, come here.
Hey, OK.
And also at least just go because we're pro sex work.
Go. And that's a good thing.
And we're fine with that.
Yeah. Right.
It should be legal outside the 12 hour.
But you have to be 18.
We went. We made mom and we say go, mom.
Oh, it would be to be a working mother.
You get to perch.
Instead of be perched, you get to perched.
Get it out of your system.
Yeah, I can see why.
I can see why mom was mad.
I can see why.
I laughed. I'm not going to lie.
I laughed. It was funny.
But I can see why mom was mad.
One hundred percent.
Well, and the moms, they didn't immediately call Gloria Aura.
They tried to complain through email and phone calls.
We're getting no response.
And one of them's like, well, yeah, we could try.
The ultimate record.
I know someone we could reach out to.
Yeah.
Did they did they settle?
What happened?
I don't I think it was probably just like an apology or whatever.
I would only got an apology.
Like like in the way they just stopped doing Bill and Ted.
They might have stopped like doing the auction or like just told the actors
like, all right, I'll back that back.
They got to go back with the megaphone and call the auctioneer, a hooker and a slut.
And then it was even revenge.
I was going to say, are they like Donkey apologized or something?
Another character.
Can you imagine them like specifically calling Eddie?
You busy? So we need you to voice something for us.
It's really going to help us out of a bind.
I make one movie every five years.
You think I'm going to come? Right.
It will count. This will count toward your contract.
OK, this is one movie.
It's a whole movie just to do Donkey in the Park one day.
Well, that actually their their contracts for the first Shrek movie did specify.
That's how they ended up being the actual voices in Shrek 4D.
It's specified they had to do any theme park.
And then, of course, it was another massive hits that, like, of course,
they renegotiated for more money as they kept making Shrek movies.
Hey, we haven't said officially R.P. Shrek 4D in Orlando.
I just saw that. Yeah.
I just saw they're closing it down.
And look, I don't know what they're going to put in there, but I did like Shrek.
I did like Shrek.
Listen, I'm a fan of a show.
I love a show. Sure. In part, it's a chance to rest.
It's a chance to get some AC. Yeah.
It's a chance to actually, you know, we're we're performance.
It's a chance to see some performances or see like some content.
I love I love a good show.
So I really enjoyed the Shrek 4D.
It was cool. Yeah, they put it there. Yeah. Yeah.
They got rid of it out here already.
But yeah, the last is do we know this Shrek 40 will be somewhere
around the world still, right? Oh, there's got to be a few places.
So showing in that giant castle, it's in a much better venue
in one of the Asian parks. I don't remember which one. Right.
So Japan, I think that's the only other universal, isn't it?
No, there are. There's a couple.
There's a couple like Beijing, Beijing, Beijing.
Just open Singapore. The other one, Singapore.
Or is there Japan? Am I wrong?
No, there is. There is. OK. OK.
So Saka Saka. Yeah. OK.
That's interesting. That's cool.
So they're all right.
As long as Shrek will be somewhere in the world, we still wear in a world.
He's big in Japan. Yeah.
Any great music, Curtis? Yeah.
I think that's what that's one thing I really love about horror nights.
While I'll keep going and I'll complain how long the lines are
or shell out two hundred dollars to get express, of course,
absolutely asinine how much it is.
But I do like that, like unlike other horror based things,
they are taking properties that you know,
and then you can be a little bit more adult.
Sure. I'm a better word. Right. Sure.
You know, they could take it too far, which they obviously did.
But they can also have Chucky running around in this.
I mean, I think they're used to kid or as a short actor.
But it's like somebody like three feet tall.
I remember one year. They do Chucky, really?
It's somebody like three feet tall, like, wow, running around with a knife.
Get the scares on.
And it is funny, but it also kind of freaks you out
because you just like see this thing coming at your kneecaps.
Oh, yeah. They're all the old house of horrors.
I think I said this, the first haunted house I had gone into in years
was like six years ago, and they had a guy playing Chucky.
They had someone playing Chucky.
And at first they made them look like a robot, like with some like jerky movements.
And then Chucky just came to life and threw a knife in my friend's throat.
And I was really freaked because I had not been in a haunted house
in years ever, maybe a very mild one when I was like little, probably.
Yeah. So it's what you were saying, though, about theme parks, not being for kids,
because then it finally feels a little bit more like now you have options
for something that's a little bit more adult.
Because like Universal Disney, I have to cater
to tiny children and families.
Of course, we get it makes sense.
I don't want everything to be like murderous and body.
But I like magic.
Of course, we all love magic.
Equate murder and body.
Those are two equal things for me since the two were.
The two were since.
Sex and death. Exactly.
And I want a little time for both of them.
Yeah. In my parks.
But it just does a certain time and a place.
There's a time and a place for it is what I'm saying.
So, yeah, you get that with horror nights.
Yeah, you do.
I mean, I remember, I don't know, my first horror nights.
They literally had go go dancers like in cages down in that area.
This is when The Walking Dead was very popular, too.
So it was the first year they had The Walking Dead maze.
And like down there in that area where like
the New York is near or something like that, they had like cage dancers.
And like, I'm like, this is why.
This is wild. Yes.
That will only usually barely ever dance on the line.
That's the whole isn't we.
I was forever ago that we talked about the horror water world, slaughter world.
Yeah. But isn't there kind of like a leather babe in it?
Basically, yeah.
I don't remember the specifics.
They can find a way to work in some sort of like body burlesque
to any franchise. Yeah.
At our nights. Yeah.
They can't.
Uh huh. They can't.
He's already got the bride.
So there that's to you.
And I don't quite know how they would have done it for Ghostbusters or us.
And the licensing thing might not have been allowed.
Yeah. Us is hard. Us is hard.
Us is hard. Ghostbusters, I don't know.
Yeah, probably. Dana, I guess.
Zool? Zool?
Gozers? Oh, Zool.
Yeah, that was dancing to Gozers.
We'll just recreate the Dan Aykroyd scene in the first.
Just got to say, just got to say,
just have just have a whole bunch of people going and unbuckling people's pants.
It's instead of a room full of mannequins and one of the move,
one of these ghosts starts going to town on the Aykroyd statue.
There's five Aykroyd statues in this room.
Yeah, they don't even do it to the guests.
It's just a Dan Aykroyd statue.
The statue doesn't move.
But his eyes do.
That's right. That's the only thing, the eyes just keep rolling.
A recording of his actual voice coming.
As I assume the noise he makes.
A Crystal Hive vodka endorsement in between.
What do you think Aykroyd sounds like?
That would actually be very funny.
Yeah, I was going to ask you, probably wrapping up soon.
But what is there a thing from like if you were envisioning purge?
Yeah. What would you do? Would it be a ride?
Would it be a walk? What would it be?
So are we keeping this in Horror Nights?
Can we take it anywhere you want to be a theme park?
So if I was if I was to do it now, now that you know,
Universal has limitations, right? Yeah, of course.
And I also know an hour ago, I said, man, I would never do the shit
where they like and touch you and do all this.
But, you know, I'm a hypocrite.
So like that's the type of like purge that I would you want.
I would do like sign the waiver. Yeah.
Get the get the waiver, put it in the area and make it a night.
Like, sure. Make it overnight because they have that.
They have an overnight thing was designed to scare you.
So make it an overnight.
Make you feel like you are fighting for your life.
And you get to hide places and see if people catch you.
And like if you get caught.
So there's it. So I would make a game out of it.
If you get caught and you get killed, then you're out.
You know, and then you go to like then you go to like just,
I don't know, the holding area where now you can just relax
for the rest of the night and drink and have fun or do whatever.
But I would want it to be something where you can feel a little sense of the danger.
You can feel people actually chasing you.
Somebody can put their hands on you,
which I know sounds daunting and crazy, but like what you're there for.
That's what you're there for. Right.
You might get messy. You know what I'm saying?
So I would do something in that realm.
They can lock you in a room.
Like shit like that.
Well, or things like that. I guess I should ask if I could curse.
I'm so sorry. Oh, no, we're good.
Just like a horror night.
Yeah, just like their team.
But only in October.
October.
So I think that would be my ideal thing, because I think the fun.
And then it starts exactly how it starts.
Seven p.m. The sirens go off.
We hear it and you have to disperse.
It's if you've ever been asleep no more.
I have not, but I've heard.
Yes. Sleep no more is a five story immersive theater
where you can go anywhere and things like that.
I would make it something similar.
So I don't know if I would do it outdoors, because that would be indoors
and it would be something similar to that, where you can go
anywhere in this building, people can grab you so you can hide.
You could do what you got to do and try to strategize surviving the night,
which is for those of you who forgot, a Bruce Willis movie.
Is it?
Double check.
Twenty twenty one.
It came out.
Another one.
Twenty one came out an hour ago.
Exclusive to to be.
I have the night to.
Yeah. Ready?
So yeah, that would be my I think that would be my ideal thing.
I would I would want to make it an immersive thing
where you truly feel like you have to survive tonight.
Yeah. Gamifying it is interesting.
Yeah, definitely. Like making it.
I don't know how you would figure that out.
Maybe you could even have people reintroduced.
It's a point thing even.
I don't know. Something like that. Yeah. Yeah.
Because I guess if you get killed in the first five minutes, you would be salty.
Sure. So maybe like if you get killed, you you get to.
And then obviously the actors will rotate.
The scare actors rotate.
You become a per you become one of the bad guys.
Maybe you can become a perjurer.
That might get dangerous.
Yeah, probably.
We can't do this completely flesh this out on my.
Yeah, we have to sit and really crack this somewhere else.
There's a foundation there for something like that.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
I think there was maybe it was 2019 or it was going to happen in 2020
and it got canceled.
But there was going to be an overnight kind of not officially Camp Crystal Lake.
Yes. Sort of thing.
I thought about doing it.
Yeah, because you could buy different levels of ticket where they'd be like,
oh, you would roast, you know, do s'mores.
It would be like a camp.
You would have a tent.
There would be s'mores, but like certain zones like
and you will go to sleep in your tent and then a monster will pull you out of your
sleep like you will go to sleep and you will get up my coolies and scary like
pulling like run.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I still try to sleep.
How could you go to bed knowing it was oh, boy.
I mean, like the thing the thing with those is is mental.
Right. Yeah. Like, yeah.
In your heart of hearts or deep in the recesses of your brain,
you know, they're not going to kill you.
Yeah, yes.
But like, there is an element of that where like it gets to a point
where you start questioning like, am I in danger here or this doesn't?
I don't like the way this feels.
Something can go wrong.
Yeah, I could be the first accident
of this event or something like that, right?
Well, which I was thinking, I mean, maybe you were talking about
needing to put the franchise aside and bring it back.
What if the way it comes back is there is a successful it's a movie
where the purge movies exist in the world of the movie.
And this this scenario now is a thing where you can do a fake purge night,
but then it becomes thanks to a bunch of narrative wills.
Yeah. Yeah. But it's real.
Like an adaptation sort of meta.
Yeah. Yeah.
They were going to purge becomes a real purge.
That's fun. That's good. Yeah.
Do that with the movie. This is the end.
Where you remember the movie?
Yeah, I changed Franco and Seth Rogen and all those guys were playing themselves.
Yeah, they were going to do a sequel to that movie.
And the sequel was going to start with them at the premiere of This Is The End.
We start the whole concept of the movie.
So the sequel is going to start with them.
Like one was a movie, but two really happened.
And they didn't obviously they didn't do that.
But I read like that was like the plan for what that was supposed to be.
We've got that a little bit.
There's something like that in another one of the great horror franchises,
somehow untouched by Halloween Horror Nights, the human centipede.
Oh, where in the second one, it's I think like a guy who sees the movie
and is obsessed with it.
And then he gets the actress from the movie to be in his right.
Yeah. You can't say it paid.
I don't know why.
I don't know. I don't know.
You can't say it paid.
I don't know why Universal is not people like they want to hire up scared.
Why not have a 40 person human centipede?
You're demanding that. Yeah.
Get a centipede. I think it would be fun. Yeah. Yeah.
Well, if they bring him breaks to give him a chance to breathe.
Yeah. Make another movie.
Yeah. There's another movie, right?
There's been a couple of years since they've made one of those.
And you just you shop the title and you do what they do with you.
Just call it centipede.
But everyone knows. Oh, good.
Yeah. And then you play the human centipede theme just on a single piano key.
Yes. Can I pitch this to?
Yeah, of course. So I pitched what I would do for the Purge.
That's me. Yeah. For Universal, if they're going to keep bringing the Purge in,
which this is a very easy franchise for them to marry to Horror Nights.
I get that. I get it. And it's fun.
I'm not I'm not like it's so boring now where it's like this got to go.
Sure. It's still very fun, especially if you're not into the movies
or it's your first time going like they get you.
I think what they should do
because we know Disney is listening, but we also know Universal's listening.
So we do NBC, NBC.
I know you all hear this.
I think what they should do is allow the Purge
scare actors to go loose on the other scare actors in the park.
Like, let's see, let's see, let's see.
Like somebody from the Purge grab Chucky and beat the shit out of him.
And like see it like you sitting there watching like, are you seeing what I'm
seeing? Like that? Yeah, that would be fun.
Like, yeah, because like that is the world, right?
Like the Purge is supposed to be real and all these other things are moving into
these. Like let the Purge free. Let them like go do some stuff.
Yeah. I'm walking line in the month. Let them go into the ride.
Yeah. Like let them free.
I think that's the only phase.
That's the only logical thing they can do at Universal.
You've learned. I think you're taking what you learn from that first Fright Fest
line and applying it to the defying X.
Right. Defying expectations for the for the this is actually I mean,
that's actually very good.
Yeah, that's a natural heightening of that magic.
The Jasmine with you in line, like which is just a magic trick.
It's playing with your expectations.
It's the event and something totally shocking happens.
And it's like, yeah.
And it was still mess with us and things like that.
Like nobody's off limits for them.
And obviously the people who are also actors, those are planned events.
But for people watching, they don't know that.
Right. I think it would be dope.
I think that's their I think that's their next step.
If they want to keep it going.
It's a great idea.
So let them go like kill the indominus Rex and
the right around.
Let them go to Jurassic World.
Putting arrows in their throat.
Yeah.
Found it, father.
This is so fun. This is a blast.
Thank you so much for being here.
This is a pleasure.
Survive podcast, the raoncast, the fright.
Oh, perilous one of scary one, a body one.
And thanks for bringing us this topic.
Let's exit through the we haven't horrified the gift shop.
Yeah, you're right.
Um, the gift shop.
The good thank you for a few.
Perfect. Let's exit through the gift shop.
Is there anything that you would like to plug?
Oh, thanks to plug.
Yeah, you know, I think it's really hard because
like I've been doing a lot of veal things, like I said, so come out.
So we have to look at in twenty twenty three.
So I think the easiest way to say for things that I'm not allowed to talk about yet
is social media. Once things pop, then I'll like let people know.
But there's a video game coming out that I might be in.
There's a couple.
There's a feature that I might be in soon.
I might. I am. I record.
And there are things coming out that
that that are that are going to be viewable and able to watch.
So I'm excited for some future stuff.
Nice. Do you want to plug your social?
Like, yeah, yeah, yeah.
At Jackie's Neil on everything.
OK. And also in these streets. Nice.
So you can always find me in these streets in Burbank.
Hey, well, you can find us on everything as well at podcast, the ride.
Merch is available in our public store and for three bonus episodes every month.
Then this month it is haunt cast the fright, the cemetery gate at
Patreon dot com slash podcast, the ride super fun.
The purge episode is now complete.
Your haunt cast thanks you for your participation.
Insert this audio.
Brrrrrrrr.
Was that the siren?
Oh, that's just my mouth.
The prayers don't sound like it's over.
That was fake.
This is a trick. This is a purge trick.
It's actually 658.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson,
Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts dot com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.