Forever!
Dog!
Warning!
The following podcast contains 50 years of dream wish magic that will enchant you, workarounds
for that pesky US Constitution, and multiple members of the Nixon administration.
It's the 50th anniversary of Walt Disney World, and we're looking back at its creation here
on Podcast The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, hosted by three theme park fans who should be enjoying Disney
World's 50th birthday, but instead we're in a gigantic fight.
I'll tell you why, I'm Scott Gardner, and I think of it as 50 years of magical dreams.
But Jason insists that it's more like 50 years of enchanted wonder.
Don't even fucking look at me.
God, well this is not...
Alright, fine, we'll all turn our backs to each other, and that's how this will be did.
Should be joyous and fun, but I guess it won't be.
Mike Carlson is out of his mind.
He thinks that it's 50 years of wishful enchantings.
It is 50 years of wishful enchantings.
It's crazy to not even imagine.
All the enchantings that have happened over the 50 years, that's the thing that takes
precedent.
Yeah, but it's...
But I mean, the basis of so many of the rides is a dream coming true.
And if you want to tell me that those dreams are not magical, then we're not looking at
the same Disney World, I guess.
I guess we're not.
But all the different robots that have...
I'm trying to think of a way to say enchant singular, and it's not working again.
It doesn't.
It's impossible.
I think I'm quick sometimes on this show, but not when it comes to enchant.
No, it is a wedged word.
You can't enchant.
Think about all the animatronics that enchant you daily in the parks.
Enchant.
Yeah, the ice...
Yeah, the contemporary resort.
Look at it, it will enchant you.
That's all thanks to the good people at US Steel.
We can all agree that US Steel is great, and thank them for all the Disney World magic.
I think that's where we can find common ground today.
It all feels...
You're right, we can settle this hedge, but with our common interest in US Steel.
We love US Steel.
Whether you're into magical dreams, enchanted wonder, or wishful enchantings, none of it
would be possible if it wasn't built on the back of steel.
Sure, they almost didn't get the two hotels open in time.
They promised, but they figured it out.
There's a lot to do.
We have a lot to do here.
We're celebrating Walt Disney World's 50th birthday, 50 years of magical dreams.
I'm just going to assert it.
Magical dreams, that is it.
And that's the only way we can move forward.
I win.
Yeah, and it's today.
It felt like we had to do...
As this episode is being released, October 1st, it is 2021.
This was 1971, of course.
Can you believe it?
It feels...
It feels insane.
Mainly, I'm like, oh, that's what something that's 50 years old feels like.
Well, then I guess a lot of music and things I'm interested in are ancient.
Yeah.
It made me...
That occurred to me.
But we should look at the positive side of it.
It is the 50 wonderful years.
Yeah, yeah.
You should...
Stop thinking about your own mortality, really, which is what this is about.
Don't think about that.
And don't think about when you first went.
It was only like, what, 20 years?
That's, I think, the weirdest, because if you like...
I don't know if you guys are doing this at all, remembering other anniversaries
and how long the amount of time seemed for a 20th or a 25th.
Who could even imagine that amount of years?
No.
When you have only barely hit two digits in your age.
And now 50?
Yeah.
I mean...
Where has the time gone?
It's like at the blink of an eye, you know?
It's like, yeah, 91, it's the 20th anniversary.
Which one is the...
Is Castle Cake?
I've already forgotten.
That's for the 25th.
So 96.
That's just that.
25 years since the Castle Cake.
25 years of Disney magic.
25 years of Castle Cake.
Grab yourself a slice of memories.
Will Sandy Patty, the gospel singer, be back to sing a medley of the original song
25 Years of Disney Magic mashed up with Zippity Doo Dah?
In 2021.
I have a feeling no.
I have a feeling no as well.
I guess they've returned.
I think when we talk anniversaries, I start to like human...
What would you say?
Humanize the amount of time.
Yeah.
So when you say 50 years, I think of a 50 year old person.
And I go, well, that's sort of...
Look, that's on the back nine at least.
You know, that's not...
Even if you lived too long.
Sorry.
And you probably were over 50 for that reminder.
Look, we're getting there.
I'm just saying, like, best case, you know, now you can live to 90.
But still, it's like I start to think of that and go, it's an older and older person.
That's OK.
Nothing wrong with it.
But it does.
You do feel like, oh, OK, now we're getting serious here.
Well, are there...
Let me just look up celebrities born in October 1971,
because that'll be just a living manifestation.
Oh, my God. Snoop Dogg.
Oh, my God.
So when you look at Snoop Dogg, Snoop Dogg
equals...
That's a good example.
I usually...
Disney World should be so lucky to be in Snoop Dogg shape.
Yeah, sure.
I...
Sacha Baron Cohen, good.
Winona Ryder, good.
There's a lot of...
Yeah, sure.
Yeah, specifically, I think October...
All these people are really...
That's the age of them.
Hmm. Well, that's the fact that I don't know.
They're all looking good for their age.
They all look great.
As are you, Disney World.
Yeah. I'm not worried anymore.
Now, Chris Kirkpatrick from Nsync.
That's...
Seventy one, really?
Yeah, people in Nsync are 50 years old.
What?
That doesn't seem right.
That can't be true.
Chris Kirkpatrick, he doesn't look as good.
He's aged prematurely from worrying for decades now that
he's going to get his ass kicked.
By Eminem.
Of course, yes.
Worse than those little Limp Bizkit bastards.
That's right. That's right.
Oh, yeah.
Wow. Seventy one. You're right.
Somebody in Nsync is going to be 50.
That's not right.
That doesn't...
Now I'm back to being upset.
Yeah, that was weird.
I was upset.
Now I was good.
Then I'm... Now I'm upset again.
I will say I don't think that he's like the physical specimen
that some of the other people in the list were.
Yeah.
But I don't look at him.
First of all, I don't look at him.
But if I end up looking at him accidentally,
like right now on this Wikipedia,
it doesn't seem... All those pictures from August 2008.
I don't know. I don't know what to think.
This Chris Kirkpatrick thing is throwing me for a loop.
He's at the... If we're on the same page,
he's on the screening of Gone Country 2 in August 2008.
Yeah, and I'm just distracted because of all my fond memories
of Gone Country 2.
Of course. Yeah, yeah.
I know.
It's hard to focus on him when you're thinking of one of your favorite movies.
Yeah, Gone Country 2.
I'm sorry. Oh, I mean television shows, obviously.
Oh, is that right?
Yeah, I was kidding.
I of course know that it's a CMT reality show.
Oh, OK.
With, of course, Sebastian Bach and...
Dee Snider.
Dee... Yeah, and Jermaine Jackson and Lorenzo Llama.
Country.
Oh, country stars.
I think that's the idea.
I think it's all people who are going country.
Right.
Oh, I see.
And it's named after...
And I do like this song legitimately, an Alan Jackson song called Gone Country,
which is making fun of like a singer, songwriter,
something that might have been like doing a folk thing.
And then they decide, you know what?
I'm going to make some money and I'm going to go country.
So it's probably based...
Maybe that's the...
We got to look into Gone...
We have to look into this now and do a whole thing with it.
Obviously.
Sure.
Sure we do.
Alan Jackson, of course, does the Five O'Clock Somewhere with Jimmy Buffett.
Yeah.
Of course.
Wrote that song.
And that's different.
That's not a folk singer going country.
That's not the target of Alan's scorn.
No, of course not.
And Alan wrote that.
That's Alan's song, not Jimmy.
He just invited Jimmy on.
And Jimmy's...
One of Jimmy's only chart topping appearances.
Oh, I think, yeah, maybe his biggest hit technically, yeah.
When he was appearing.
You're kidding.
Why haven't the charts been kinder?
To the song Fruitcakes?
To Math Sucks.
Didn't submit them on time.
Didn't submit the song for consideration on time.
They're on Island Time.
Yeah.
I just forgot.
Charts sounds like numbers to me.
You know what I think.
Get out of here, numbers.
Math sucks.
Okay, so picture Snoop Dogg in your mind.
Picture a lineup that's Snoop Dogg, Chris Kirkpatrick, and Walt Disney World.
Yeah.
And that is those are the faces of 50.
And I think they should feel good about themselves.
50 years.
First of all, before we go into the past, because I think we're going to do some talking about
how it all got started, how things were before the 50 years began, right before the clock began,
and how the whole place got started.
What do we know about what they're doing to celebrate the 50th?
What's happening here in 2021?
I can sum it up in a paragraph.
Go ahead.
A very short paragraph.
Okay.
Okay, all the weenies, all the big icons at each park have a little light show,
have a little lighting.
I saw this.
New lighting.
They're beacons of magic, of course.
Yeah.
So everything's that you mean the castle, the...
Tree of Life.
...the spaceshipers...
Space Earth.
...Tower of Terror and the Tree of Life are all...
They light up gold sometimes.
Yes.
Ratatouille is opening at Epcot.
Good.
Ride from another place.
Showing up.
And then there are 50 golden statues scattered about the parks.
And now I'm not the most religious man, but my knowledge of the Bible is that golden idols
usually don't end well.
They're all going to get struck by lightning.
Yeah.
They will anyway.
It's Florida.
That's true.
I'm sure there are storms.
Lightning conductors?
Maybe that's what they're there for.
Lightning rods?
Lightning rods.
To keep it away from the guests.
So guests don't get hit by lightning.
So Timon gets hit and not a guest.
Sure.
Yeah.
Are any of them literal golden calves?
Are any cows...
Oh, oh, uh...
Is it Clarabelle?
I don't think Clarabelle.
I think they had the foresight to not have a literal golden calf.
Home on the Range characters?
I'm sorry.
I don't think there's a lot of Home on the Range or Brother Bear appearances.
Not a lot.
I guess the Disney cows are not that popular.
They don't tribute that cow with Mickey Mouse ears on the side.
Right.
Yeah.
Who I don't, despite us doing the epiz...
Mini Moo.
There it is.
Right, right, right.
Took me a second.
That's what I want the statues to be, is all nods to the most obscure things that we like.
Like Mini Moo the cow.
Like Leonardo Columbus, who of course led the tapestry of nations parade.
I mean, we'd love to see a Dream Finder, obviously.
Yeah, yeah.
We'd love to see Sandy Patty at the F.
The Gospel Singer.
Sandy Patty and Sandy Dunk.
Or no, Sandy Dunk is a more Disneyland celebrity, I guess.
I'm going to say, yeah, I don't want Sandy Dunkin.
I don't want a golden Sandy Dunkin anywhere.
I know you're upset about Sandy Dunkin, but...
Always.
They make a beacon of magic of Mini Moo's grave.
Does Mini Moo have a headstone over by the Fort Wilderness campground?
Oh wait, that's right, isn't it?
There is a...
There's a plaque at least, I think.
That's correct, yeah.
And a cow grave has to be fairly big.
So there's enough real estate to light it up.
Gold, sure.
Yeah.
Very nice.
They should do it.
They need to do it.
So we'll look into that too.
Is that where you're done with your summation of events?
Yeah, because Charon and Guardians were delayed at least a year
due to a pandemic halt of construction.
At least.
I'm being generous.
Yeah, who knows?
It's really mysterious when those things will finally get finished.
Scott, there is something they announced today that I'm very excited about.
I know.
You know what I'm talking about?
We might be thinking the same thing,
and I credit the Facebook group for making me aware.
And I feel like, is Jason maybe not aware?
Because you might be talking about it already.
I made Jason aware of this already if we're talking about the same thing.
Which is a food item.
I've gotten it a couple times, yeah.
Multiple people have sent this to Jason today.
Very good, everyone.
And do you want me to read it?
Yeah, go for it, yeah.
Uncle Orville's great big beautiful tomorrow Sunday.
Chocolate and vanilla soft serve brownie hot fudge and whipped cream
topped with red, white and blue sprinkles served in a bathtub.
A little bathtub full of ice cream.
This is the most Jason-y thing.
Clock's ticking.
I got a trip coming up and it might have to be my first time.
Where is it?
There was a big announcement of all these food items.
They do say where the things are.
It's at Anti-Gravity's Galactic Goodies.
Okay, is that in Tomorrowland?
Yes.
I believe it is, yeah.
I believe it's the ice cream windows that kind of connect to Merchant of Venus.
I think that's right.
I assume it's also in Tomorrowland.
Yes.
Look, the acknowledge has to stop somewhere.
I don't know the shop names.
I'm sorry.
I'll try to.
We'll come up with some awful reason to have to learn them.
I wild away precious hours of my youth at Merchant of Venus.
It used to be the shop for Alien Encounter.
Jason's wild youth at Merchant of Venus.
Crazy stuff.
No, wild.
W-I-L-E.
Oh.
Wild.
But wild.
It was wild, I'm saying.
Oh, it was wild.
Yeah, absolutely.
Yeah.
There used to only be two places.
The whole property, you could buy Star Wars stuff.
MGM Studios and Merchant of Venus.
Can you imagine?
No, I can't.
Well, then a lot of magical dreams have come true.
Yeah.
Make that much more, it's everywhere.
It's everywhere now.
So that's good.
There was an entire block of snack announcements, many of which seem bizarre and disgusting to me.
Yeah.
The one that jumped out, I have the tab open, is the Mission to Mars.
There's all these snacks that tribute things that aren't there anymore, classic things.
And Mission to Mars, this extinct attraction.
What do we think here?
It's up in the upper right.
Burger topped with bacon and macaroni and cheese.
Sure.
On a bun dusted with crushed cheese flavor puffs.
It just seems like to hold it.
You're asking for trouble.
You know, here's my thing with that.
Obviously, that's one of those like fun, we're enjoying the excess, we're going to pile stuff on.
I will say that generally with Disney World Fast Service,
I'm not so sure they'll nail that, if that makes sense.
The best you're ever going to see it is in this photo.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
They posted.
Yeah.
So when they get, I could imagine like a different place, maybe going like, you know what?
It's pretty gross, but it's fun to eat that once in a while.
But I don't know, a Disney World hamburger with a lot of, I don't know.
Yeah, I don't, I think part of it is a lot of the food items like this are for Instagram.
Well, yes, yes.
And some of them, like Scott and myself and Griffin all tried the big chicken sandwich
when we were down at Disneyland for the day and enjoyed it.
Griffin got the peanut butter and sandwich with bacon.
That seemed like bad news.
Yeah, but you and I both like the chicken sandwich.
I did.
Yeah.
You just need a strategy.
You have to go in with a strategy.
You got a knife and fork, at least I had a knife and forked it for a while.
Right.
Winnowing it down until it was a slider.
A manageable, yeah, slider sandwich.
Do we talk about how then the person came up to take our trays and said,
are you finished with your experiments?
No, but I forgot about that.
I like that.
We were all questioning, do we like this?
Because it's all over the map.
We liked our thing, but it was kind of difficult.
Griffin was maybe on this, maybe didn't dig what he was eating.
And then that, are you finished with your experiments?
All right, sealed the deal.
This place is good.
Just with that one line.
Yeah, that is good.
A Disney-fied language for taking your trash away.
That's great.
Love it.
You know what?
We didn't talk about this either.
We were back in Galaxy's Edge and someone was still doing the
cave fabe of it in Dock Andar, where I had a country bear shirt on.
And she was like, ah, what is that creature on your shirt?
And I was like, oh, well, it's a bear that does a show.
She's like, ah, yes, he has some sort of instrument.
Or and I was like, yes, he does.
And then I was like, I asked the question about the lightsaber.
And they're like, ah, the Galactic Federate.
There's a slowdown in the shipping of the galactic freight.
And we don't have the master Skywalker's lightsaber in stock right now.
And I was like, hey, OK.
And I was like, I was trying to play along a little bit.
I was very tired at the end of the night, but I was like, oh, good.
Somebody's still doing it.
Because even opening day, it felt like people were over that.
Begrudging.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Quick to go.
That's all fun, though.
Yeah, I know. I liked it a lot.
I guess there aren't bears in Star Wars.
I never thought about it before.
Yeah, there's not.
Yeah.
Things that look kind of like bears, but not bears.
But they're missing it.
Somebody should get some bears.
Eventually there will be bears.
Yeah.
Ship of bears should crash land next season on the Mandalorian.
I am hoping when I order that ice cream Sunday that I will order it.
And in addition to calling out my name that it's ready,
they will scream no privacy at all around here.
At the very least, you can do it.
Yeah, I certainly will.
And then raised it up so people knew why you were doing it.
You could get a big applause.
Yeah.
Could you bring it?
Yeah, you should bring it on the actual show ride.
Could you eat the Sunday in the theater?
It's kind of a crapshoot with a lot of theme parks, food or drink, you know, sort of thing.
You could smuggle it in your sweatshirt.
I mean, yeah, that would certainly be progress for me having a great time.
I mean, yeah, then he could see the tub and then hold up the tub to the tub.
Yeah.
That's worth waiting 12 minutes to eat the ice cream.
Eat the melting ice cream.
If the show's not ready to go right when you walk up to it.
The brownie will inevitably only get staler.
I'd like to see you have one of these a day and try different places to eat it.
One on the People Mover, one in Carousel of Progress.
Yeah, look, there's a lot of sweets to cover in.
Yeah, you're right.
Scott's got a list of more things, I assume.
There are more.
While we're on it, I just want to say the thing I'd maybe like to see,
and you don't even have to unless you want to give a photo for this to be done with,
but just a picture of you shrunk down bathing in the tub.
Oh, wow.
Oh, yeah.
Well, I'm not the most Photoshop savvy, so I can provide the elements
and if someone could make the new creation.
You know, you probably could do is just put the Sunday with the bathtub on a table
and have somebody who you're with.
You try to get like a forced perspective where you're far away in the distance.
So it looks like your head is just poking out of the bathtub.
You could do probably a very simple version like that.
That's more up.
Yeah, I like a practical solution.
It's more of my speed.
We love practical effects here.
We always talk about that.
And that's what this is.
This is not CGI.
This is practical.
This is the way that special effects should be done.
So that's good.
Yeah, yeah.
But I'm not going to say if somebody wants to do that.
Sure.
OK, don't do it.
And if Jason wants to do a little pose of like arms up behind the head, like, ah.
Yeah.
I mean, they should sell like the big Uncle Sam red, white and blue hat.
Like that feels like they're leaving money on the table,
not making more exclusive like Carousel of Progress based more Uncle Orville.
Well, all of them, all of them.
The mysterious disappearing child,
like a shirt about like, where did the third child go?
You know, they are leaving money on the table.
You can use that phrase even if the money is only like forty two dollars.
Yeah.
Are leaving the forty dollars on two dollars of my money.
Yeah, it would be yours.
Yeah.
The wall we've got money on.
We've talked before about having the John collection,
the clothing John wears through the through the eras.
And then he would you would buy all of them.
There's one pretty funny piece of Carousel of Progress merch,
and it's a vinyl mation, but it's the Mickey or vinyl mation one.
Yeah.
And it's John like wearing all four outfits like at once, like he's split in the fours.
And I do respect the attempt, but like it's not the prettiest looking like toy.
No, the vinyl mations with the Mickey shape are already sort of unappealing looking.
Yeah.
To make it weird.
A bunch of those.
That's like if the Johns from all the eras from the 20s and the 40s and all of them, like all
like collided in some temporal catastrophe.
Like the thing.
Yeah.
Like people kind of go so hard by the thing.
They all tried to show up at the same era.
They got these things, time machines now,
and they all tried it at the same time and landed in the same spot.
And we all say like they all say, kill me now.
This is painful.
I don't want to live.
You have no idea the pain it is to exist like this.
I ruled that electricity now more than ever.
Oh boy.
A great segue into the experimental prototype community of tomorrow.
Yeah.
I mean, yeah, let's let's get into let's let's let's go backwards.
Let's say this carousel of progress can turn back to 1971.
You know, this was Walt's dream and just like the carousel of progress and it was a crazy
dream and had he lived, who knows what he would have done.
Who knows what bizarre tendrils the dream knows what sort of Howard Hughes living on
top of a casino we could have seen Walt Disney do.
It's something in reflecting on the 50 years and on Walt's relationship to the place,
which just to reiterate, if you don't know the timeline, Disney World opens in 71.
Walt Disney dies in 1966.
He was alive for the some of the planning.
It was it was all his dream.
He wanted to buy Florida land and do something there.
And it was it was kind of this ultimate vision.
This like, you know, Disneyland times 100 and just that he didn't that he didn't overlap
with it.
He never got to go there.
And I've just thought about how this felt like Walt getting one in at the buzzer, you
know, the fact that he's making movies about it and talking about it, essentially on his
deathbed.
I learned literally on his deathbed.
It's one of the last things he was talking about.
I mean, how many people like did something this significant right before their death?
Yeah, it's a good question.
I don't know.
Yeah, it does feel right, right at the last second.
We've got David Bowie album, Lazarus or whatever it's called.
Yeah, yeah, I haven't really heard it.
I like David Bowie a lot.
I didn't really hear it, but I like that it happened.
It's sad.
Covering with me.
I think I saw a music video.
It makes me sad.
I came up on my shuffle a couple of days ago, one of the songs and I go too sad and I turned
it off.
Part of it.
Yes.
Yeah.
The right down to the wire.
It's not like weird and like tin machine bad or anything.
No, no, no.
Not the worst.
But yeah, he took care of the worst decades.
Yeah.
But sometimes.
Yeah, I'm never in the mood to hear his death album.
Yeah, makes sense.
Well, then and how often is that the case for your Johnny Cash's?
Yeah.
When Campbell's who will come up in a little bit that they're making these sad warrens.
Yvonne.
Warren's Yvonne.
Walt Disney, though, gave us the right before he went out, gave us the place that's given
us all the joy, the most joy.
It's why we're all here.
It's why I know you guys.
It's why everyone's listening to us.
Thank you, Walt.
Let's just give Walter a big thank you wherever you are.
Thank you.
We do have to mention begrudgingly gave us the East Coast Disneyland as it was all been called.
OK, yeah.
Because his real passion project was the experimental prototype community of tomorrow,
the original Epcot.
Progress City.
Thank you, Walt, for inadvertently giving or like kind of just begrudgingly giving us
Disney World because you wanted to be the king of a city.
Yes.
So I was curious because I know little bits in peace.
I watched the Epcot like one hour presentation a while ago,
but I wanted to look up more stuff about Progress City.
So I got this book from the library.
It's another Sam Genoway book called Walt in the Promise of Progress City.
You got a tabbed up book here.
I got a tabbed up.
A book on our hands.
And also the book, I believe also a reference point for there's a very good Defunctland episode
about Progress City.
Oh, yeah.
And I read the Progress City, like the main chapter about it in this book,
and I stopped because it was giving me the Willys.
Whoa.
Wow.
Because I mean, like less Willie giving is the first quote I came across.
How much Willie giving can you take?
Well, I mean, I got to brace my it is the season for it.
It's the scary season.
Well, and this is the you notice it's October and the next week,
maybe we start giving you the Willys.
Yeah, that's true.
So watch out if you hate Willys.
Because if you hate Willys, watch out.
Do you think we should save some of it because we want to do a full
walkthrough of the Epcot special.
Do you think we should save some of the progress?
City stuff.
So we'll touch on it.
Really, it's it is interesting.
It's really in depth.
But the funniest thing, if you follow the threads back long enough to
the genesis of Disney World, there's a quote in this chapter that is kind of
like a very early touchstone.
And it says Walt Disney said, I don't believe there's a challenge anywhere
in the world that's more important to people everywhere than finding
solutions to the problems of our cities.
Now, that's a very boring sentence.
And but clearly kept this man up at night because Walt just hated what
cities had become like it were just overwhelming.
He especially hated traffic despite the fact that he was a man who
constantly worked with automobile companies and built his studio in the suburbs of Los Angeles.
I think Jimmy Buffett hate I hate traffic, too.
Don't you hate it when you can't get a place fast?
You know, I hate to pit them against each other, but Jimmy Buffett has he's about
reinventing lifestyle, too.
And he has a brand of physical properties and there's a lot more of those than there
are Disney places.
You know, that's true.
We're talking sheer numbers.
Yeah, he's lived longer, too.
And might be immortal.
We'll see.
But like everyone was very complimentary to like the urban planning that kind of went
into the genesis of Disneyland to the point that like Ray Bradbury, the author, a close
friend of Walt's suggested he run for mayor of Los Angeles to like get stuff done.
And then Walt said, why would I run for mayor when I am already king?
So I know that's kind of a joke, but also you can tell.
You can tell it's kind of not.
Yeah, yeah, half and half.
Yeah, complex.
Sure.
If you made it that far and you and there was something as risky as Disneyland and it
worked and worked spectacularly and everybody's telling you how well it's working.
It's what I was.
We were talking about earlier or some other episode where it's like there's obviously
a pattern for like major success when you're like in a company and it's like a major success
and you become very, very rich and well known.
You start to like set your sights on something that feels like it's way out of what you
started like Jeff Bezos wanted to just like destroy small bookstores and make a lot of
money and figure out a way to like ship people things fast.
And then all of a sudden he's going to be a moon man.
He's going to be a Mars traveler.
And you're like, wait a minute, that's not.
And Walt Disney's like, I wanted to put sound with cartoons.
Also, I want to fix cities, cities need fixing.
And you're like, huh?
Why don't you want you make robots, you make robots for us to look at.
But he aims way bigger and then the company doesn't know what to do after he dies.
Exactly.
They come up short and we just get a new theme park place and that's great.
So and maybe better.
Yes.
Yeah.
I think so.
I don't know.
Yeah.
What state would progress city be in today?
It could be really weird.
Well, I mean, look at the look at the states of the other municipalities they built.
Toontown looks like shit.
They haven't painted that thing in years.
They're demolishing it in front of the guests.
They're demolishing it right in front of our eyes.
It's clearly rife with divorce and missing people and stuff.
There's private investigators popping up all over the place.
Everyone's rushing to become a private investigator.
That's what's happening.
No one wants to be a building painter or a bricklayer.
A five and dime.
They got rid of it.
Yeah.
Right.
All over the place.
Factory worker.
But it is fascinating because, yeah, as a kid,
and then, of course, Walt wanted to build another park.
It's cool, too.
Sure.
You don't know about any of this.
Right.
This is very strange.
But yeah, it is interesting.
Yeah, I'm trying to think where to start on my end or where to throw it.
I know that obviously with Disneyland's success, there's the desire to do another one.
People are telling him that east of the Mississippi is a whole other world
that you are not really taking advantage of.
There's less flight at the time.
Probably most Disneyland guests come via driving.
And there's maybe the desire to, well, if we put something over on the other side of the country
and that's accessed via driving, maybe we get a whole other crowd.
So he's scouting places in the late 50s and early 60s.
And I didn't know some of this stuff, like where he was looking.
Yeah.
That Niagara Falls was a possibility, which today is like trashy tourist insanity.
And it's pretty, it makes a lot of sense that just thematically that you could end up there.
But I think, you know, weather is a roadblock for a lot of these places.
I saw a story about St. Louis.
Yes, I saw that, too.
Being on the table.
It was called, what was, Walt Disney's Riverfront Square.
Well, that was the indoor one.
Oh, yes.
They were going to build a giant multi-block like indoor theme park.
Wow.
Right. But that was before that was before Disney World as well.
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
Okay.
Oh, wait. Now that wait. Yeah. I caught a little.
There's some attraction that was maybe repurposed from that.
Does that ring a bell?
Like, yeah, what ended up getting built that was there were Disney World originals came from.
It was going to maybe Hall of Presidents could be.
I mean, that's obviously an extension of great moments of Mr. Lincoln.
But like the Country Bears was an opening day attraction.
So happy 50 years, Country Bears.
We'll get to you soon.
But that like that was for that weird resort Mineral.
Mineral King.
Yeah.
Do so.
There were all these oddball plants.
I also want to say Disney opened up a bowling alley in Denver.
I barely caught this.
I don't know much about it, but that didn't really satisfy anybody.
And they didn't really embrace the name.
They didn't say definitively this is Disney's bowling alley because it wasn't really good enough.
And didn't do well enough.
I missed that.
That was just like one sentence.
And I looked at a book, too.
I looked at a book called Reality Land with David Koenig.
Yeah, maybe.
Yeah.
St. Louis.
Do you know more about that place?
Because I don't.
Well, I have some notes about this from one of these articles.
The only thing I saw about it is that he was getting down the road a little bit.
But if you're going to be in St. Louis, you're going to have to deal with Bush at some point.
Like the Bush family, the beer and the head of the Bush family told Walt he was crazy to build a theme
park in St. Louis and not sell beer.
Right.
And thus he cut off the negotiations.
I will not have be I guess he I make fun of this whole we got to trust Walt's wishes and not have
beer in the park.
But I guess if that's where he was at in the 50s, how dare you, Bush, give me a revenue stream,
a constant giant revenue stream for the park I want to build?
It does seem like there was a lot of conflict in the man about the image of Uncle Walt and the
family friendliness and the clean, no smoking, no drinking sort of thing.
And then the Walt who has to live his life and go about his life and drinks scotch and smokes
Chesterfields.
Yeah.
Which he like it's funny if he was that protective about it because I don't get the sense that he
was like a drunk.
Right.
Am I wrong?
I feel like he just like did what anybody of that age in that time would have done.
I don't there's not a lot of I don't I haven't seen a ton of documentation of like and then like
Walt had to be escorted out of the tam o' shanter or anything like yeah it seemed like it was just
one video with that.
It's only there was TMZ back then eight millimeter cameras running separate sync sound off a
different little pack.
Walt like shirtless across the street where the party city is now just like screaming
you let me back in there I'm Dopey's father.
I'm a Dopey.
I'm the king of party city.
That's where they got the phrase from.
That's what the brand is named after.
Wow.
Just yelled it one day.
So yeah I don't know I've never seen anything.
Yeah he was just as drunk as every other older man of the time probably I guess.
I think I don't know weird though.
What you got anything else about that St. Louis?
Well the St. Louis thing I think there's a couple like legends because like what the
beer thing is one thing but then there also I think was a report that it was basically
Disney was going to pay for the rides and attractions but they wanted St. Louis to pay
for the building itself and then they St. Louis didn't want to do it.
St. Louis redevelopment the corporation and then declined to pay for the building so Disney
was like we're out.
They're always looking for like.
Classic yeah they want other people to pay for stuff they want to pay for everything.
Eventually that happens in Orlando we're like okay we'll do it but we want roads widened
and we want to be able to govern however we want and change the structure of a city's work.
We want the laws we want to make the laws here.
So yeah.
So they don't go to any of those places and they end up in they start ending up in Florida.
I think Walt realizes there's a lot of property there and that it's maybe kind of cheap there
and it is like considered this vacation place and people are retiring there.
He determines he doesn't want to be on the coasts because he doesn't want to deal with
hurricanes and he doesn't want people in the park in bathing suits.
There's another little morality.
Well he didn't get that wish.
You know I don't look Walt there's a lot of he's a problematic figure in some ways he's
a great figure in some ways but I can really get on board with this no bathing suit policy.
Can really appreciate that I like to keep that keep that clean.
And had some good ideas.
Yeah yeah that was natural you know disasters and weather patterns also like made him not go
with like New York or New Jersey DC Baltimore areas because the park would have to be seasonal
and closed part of the year.
Oh yeah which almost everything is we've talked about parks there but that's pretty much the
deal I gather from great adventure and those kind of things.
Yeah I think as the years have gone on more and more stuff have
invested in Halloween and Christmas endeavors but very limited usually not seven days a week.
And then maybe February is a bust.
Right.
Yeah.
They just don't do anything.
So they they settle on this plot of land that is pretty much swamp.
I think he also didn't want to like kill off a bunch of orange groves and I think he just
sensed that people would not be willing to get rid of orange groves because that's the pride of
Florida.
So we end up with this land that is not a lot.
One fact I learned from this book Reality Land is that there was a helicopter trip where
they went and saw the site and he said I think that's it.
That's the site.
The helicopter stopped to refuel and they people got out and heard the radio and heard on the radio
that JFK had been assassinated.
I have that too.
That freaked my shit out.
I was so like it wasn't until they landed in New Orleans later that day that supposedly that they
they heard the radio that JFK had been killed.
Geez blissfully only people unaware.
Little helicopter bubble of happiness.
That was his first time seeing the Florida property in person that day.
That's a weird confluence of stuff.
That's that's pretty nuts.
Yeah that is crazy.
And which I've seen at least the book I was reading or articles are sort of like it was a sign more
than ever that Waltz needed to forge ahead with his vision of a new better America.
Like I don't know.
I think that's random.
I think I don't know that it was like this is the end of an era and I need to be the person to take
us out.
I need to reverse the brain of this president being blown up.
It's only I can do it.
The narratives not just of the 50 years of Disney World but the creation of it and the
shifting narratives of not just what they were going to do and how they set out to do it and
most than the biggest now after 50 years what Walt intended to do are wild.
Like if you try to find a straight line you are not going to find it.
I found another book that there's a book called Walt Disney World the first decade.
It's a big coffee table book.
You can find it very easily very cheap on eBay.
I have that I think.
And yeah and it's you can borrow it from the internet archive like an hour at a time from
their digital archive and in the introduction to that they are already 10 years later erasing
the narrative about progress city.
There is this the slightest mention of it and then they're like but of course you know we wanted a
vacation place for children of the vacation kingdom of the world like they the narrative is
already shifting by the time Epcot the park is built.
Yeah of course.
Mostly water skiing.
That's mainly what it was about.
Yeah.
Leisure.
A leisure place.
Yeah the myth that I mean I guess it makes sense because like you're not going to put in the book
like and then this mad man decided to build a city but we decided no that's silly.
So we gave you figment and then or whenever figment opens.
Yeah.
But yeah I get I mean all this all this yeah the the cartoon character of Walt is a very
it's still I'm trying to think like we were just talking about Walter not which is funny
that he's being drawn he's at Knott's Berry Farm because there's a lot of crazy stuff about
him but no one's paying any attention so but you can still buy a little Walter not
like a little Walter not character.
I don't know if you can buy it or can you?
Oh I thought that's what you said I thought it was a piece of merch.
No there's like a bust in the but that's in the weird that that's in the independence hall.
I thought they were selling it.
Weird thing.
The there's a funny thing there which is there's like there's like some general like political
stuff like here's you know you can buy little postcards of all the presidents up through
Clinton when this series stopped being made or you know just a little patriotic even just like
sparkly USA or whatever but one thing Aaron noticed was a like a big plush area with red
white and blue stuffed animals and there were plush donkeys and plush elephants and actually
I think I phrased that wrong because there were a lot of plush donkeys and they spot for plush
elephants and there were zero they were a long sold out.
Oh okay got it.
So if you're a democrat pursuing the independence hall in Buena Park plenty of donkeys for you
but if you're if you're raising a young republican who you want to give an elephant to.
It makes sense it makes sense because you're going to Buena Park you really have to be looking
out for independence hall it's not right in the in the action.
Yeah.
So no you gotta like yeah it's it's this weird if you don't know knots yeah it's like across
the you have to go through a tunnel across the street and end up at a perfect recreation of
I still independence hall.
Couldn't quite explain how to get there I know vaguely where it is but don't take my word for
it like I wouldn't be able to direct you I don't think.
You're going through secret passageways like turn Washington spies themselves.
You want to feel like you're living in turn.
But speaking of of secrecy and kind of doing things on the slide and this is some of the stuff I
wanted to talk about so I mean yeah there's the progress city plans but he there's you know I
think there's a lot of stuff that Disney wants to do there he's not even sure what he even says
that's by enough space to hold all the dreams that haven't even been dreamed yet.
But the the main thing it was what Disney is still fighting all the time in Anaheim in
California which is which is space and the fact that they bought because it was such a crazy
plan Disneyland so they bought what they could and as soon as Disneyland was open and working
lots of shady stuff popped up on the outskirts and that's the thing I you know now I feel like
yeah it feels shady around there and there's your like but I feel like it's mainly like
yeah we're cheap of hotels I do wonder it seemed like it was like much shadier maybe in the 50s
60s like way more low rent yeah yeah or just like odd opportunistic weird dirty shitty places
charging too much money I don't really know yeah I mean it's hard to say I think there was a lot
more motel kind of things but I think there was a lot more hotel motel places everywhere and a lot
of the older pictures have like featuring a cocktail lounge with the singer Mickey Harry
like you know there was just an expectation of like roadside motel and like stuff to do yeah more
chain hotel stuff there now I would imagine that that real estate people would eventually be
were getting bought out by bigger places yeah over the years so even in the last 10 years I feel
like there's been a lot more like suite hotels or like right mid-range hotel like nicer mid-range
hotels kind of popping up I wonder if anyone has it that would be fascinating to know what businesses
were on that street for the first 10-20 years that really would be fascinating cruddy shit that
opened up around Disney yeah or was there anything cool like who not like maybe well there was I
think in some episode I discovered there was a Nixon's hamburgers yes yes exactly Nixon
had a hamburger place his brother what was he yeah so that sounds good I don't know so you
can't hate on Nixon burgers but no no you but mainly he just didn't want that probably he
wanted like he didn't want it to be that there is your magic kingdom here and then as soon as you
walk outside of it there's a bunch of nuisance stuff and stuff that where they have to regulate
the height lines and it might intrude on the park visually he doesn't want any of that he wants pure
wilderness around him so I like that he doesn't go let's buy twice the space he buys it's like
125 times it's something so crazy yeah well I'm making that up no I'll tell you what it is it's
twice the size of the island of Manhattan a line that everyone from the book publication people to
the uh celebrity guests on that opening day uh special yeah have been told to say yeah that's
in there a lot there's some like uh you know some listeners might be hearing some of this early
Disney World stuff for the first time or you're hearing certain elements of it for the 100th time
and uh I was watching the 15th anniversary special uh with Aaron my wife who at some point said like
how many more times do I have to see him in front of this fucking map I've seen so much footage of
Walden the big map yeah pointing and it's the drears size and choice vanattans and 24 man look
at me I'm just five miles tall and I they do they use this stuff a lot and probably as she
intuited because it's some of the only footage of him associated with the Disney World there's not
a lot marrying him to the place because he didn't really get to be involved right there's no he's
not walking walking those streets or anything yeah yeah nope no pictures like that uh so he
wants to buy up all of this land uh but if he does it it's gonna raise red flags and the land value
is going to skyrocket uh and he's it's gonna be anaheim all over again so he has to invent all of
these shady made-up companies to start buying up all of the land on the cheap uh which is this one
they don't hide from this is like part of the charming mythology that they themselves yes they
like out even though if you break it down it's pretty iffy right I think so for sure yeah yeah
but this is part of the this is one of the iffy things that yeah is you're saying like they're
like isn't that cute yeah those people are getting ripped off like scott said they're gonna feel like
they got ripped off if they find out later on that i'm gonna get ripped off they didn't you know
charge the uh buyer enough uh yeah yeah you are withholding information from the person you're
buying the land from you were not you were not being honest about what your thing is so I wanted
to know a little bit more about this jay-z you might have found some of this too but I was like
what were these companies and there's one that has a little charming spin that they love to say
the ones that I saw some of them are just like did they just pick like these names because it
didn't sound like a white guy buying in a white guy's company they also had the thought that
you're having as well yes yeah because one of them is the latin american development and
yeah yeah yeah no that sucks yeah yeah yeah yeah no for sure I think they're like this will throw
them off the scent mm-hmm they'll never know that the whitest man is buying this well disney co
what do we what words can we throw in that also has the ring of king feature syndicate of like very
bland very boring by the time you've heard the full name so you stop investigating all right sure
latin american what was it uh to hamahawk properties yeah no it seemed right definitely yes
but then you're having fun then they throw out mt lot company mt lot yes now that's like a cute
disney thing I do like that I can't be mad about that I like nnt theme park company not a or nta
theme park company like that would be funny isn't that cute like they're kind of telling
them what the what it is but they're not saying it use not like the last name not not oh yeah
that's better yes not a theme park run that together as one word maybe put like a que on it
and then while like name well dresses up as the care guy who owns it like shaves his mustache off
and he puts on a wig hello there or he could just like if he doesn't want to shave he's got to be
on tv the next week he does it as a lady and he's got like a handkerchief in front of his
nose oh right right right oh my the vapors yeah yeah see that's cute I can't breathe
the other thing is bad this is this would be cute just to like wink at everyone buying the land
I'm just you know we did voices we know he did mickey of course yeah that's true another voice
though perhaps not there's one clip of him in a sound booth that I also like the map I've seen
him doing the like ah I forget what he's doing they did it one time if I'm giving them the benefit
of the doubt of the land buying I think a lot of the land they were buying you could describe as
hostile land like nature does not want man to be here it's filled with alligators and bugs
and swamp yeah you know uh and I think like some of it maybe like still not used for that reason
I think they own some land that is not developable developable uh and then but just hold it because
it's you know blocking other stuff from yeah infringing a lot of sinkholes maybe subterranean
sinkholes at places uh I believe that's why some of the other hotels that were supposed to be around
the seven seas lagoon as much as they try to shoot a depth test or a girder down there the earth keeps
eating them really there's a there was a phrase in one of these articles where it was like all right
they had to get started and he had to drain the land and I was like Jesus yeah that's so intense
where did they drain the swamp it makes sense but for for just looking and I go that seems hard
yes yeah um yeah there's in terms I love the stories of the inhospitable nature of it I saw
I saw a story about um I several stories that involve the need to show up with a gun because
you may have to shoot a snake to bits this happened more than once these kind of boring
stiff shirts going down there to deal with like let's do our redistricting and get 3d creek open
it but they also have to be like Indiana Jones's like this is some wild stuff I saw one story about
people having some functional meeting in a trailer and then stepping outside of it oh my god the
biggest snake I've ever seen bang bang bang shooting the snake to bits this is such a brutal
I've never really thought about it was blowing a snake to kingdom come um and then the guy goes
back into the into the bungalow and says you gotta come out you're gonna see I just had to shoot this
snake it's nuts he brought him out wow that is huge thing comes back to life it was not dead oh
my god kill it kill it Michael Myers snake oh yeah her whole movie not actually dead and then
oh just just this is the same story about a guy who I I mean that's a I've got more stuff about
this gentleman general joe general joe potter but uh but he for sure is just like like snakes would
just like dive down from tree branches you'd be hit you're like out in a out in a fan boat
trying to get away to the land and then oh my god snakes he just got to be ready to snipe them
just get attacked by snakes 24 seven that's insane it's so crazy you look back at old movies and
stuff for old like catalog you're like wow they sold guns at hardware stores and it's like oh uh
stories like this it's like oh I see why they sold a small caliber gun at a hardware store next to
like the hedge clippers for the snakes you know would they even world like I can just imagine
they're all like short sleeve dress shirt guys big like big cigarette or cigar gun don't even
like like cigar doesn't even fall out of their mouth as they just unload around at a snake
barely wins which is that the best way to do it no it can't be right no it's like a grabber they
are yeah what a tough target that is and then like clearly the blowing the snake to bits and
then you didn't get it indicates that that person doesn't know the the anatomy of a snake not that
I do but I'm not being called upon to shoot one no yet but yeah he's like he's like I don't know I
got the the tail and the head but then like you probably missed like vital organs that keep it
alive yeah I'm not an advocate for snake killing it's their land I mean they should have been
there they you know it's their land uh stolen from the snakes um but the all the guys should
have just had flamethrowers like the thing like in the thing like currussle the thing they should
just all have been equipped with a big tank on their back and a big flamethrower I guess like
the end of once upon a time in Hollywood aliens too aliens yeah lighten up the inside of the belly
a lot of movies so they just like step outside to get like continue smoking and then they go ah
shit and they just shoot up the swamp with with the fire I saw that story about
Dick Irvine and Admiral Joe Fowler getting swallowed by a gigantic crocodile bigger than them
but luckily they brought flamethrowers right right lit it up from the inside until like that until
I got until all the heat forced them back out of the mouth in sort of a monster scenario yeah yeah
so started guardians of the galaxy too when Jarax ends up in the alien's belly and he gets out I
guess he cuts himself out he doesn't flame throw his way out yeah same thing except for Joe Potter
Joe Potter or Joe Fowler what former military man wants to be yes clear about this sorry yeah
Admiral Joe Fowler is not uh General Joe Potter both uh very important in the genesis of Disney
world yeah I remember this uh weirding me out the first time that I went to Disney world because I
knew Disneyland and I knew that there was the Mark Twain and I knew Mark Twain is and that's
American and it's this nice nice boat named after Mark Twain and you go down there and the boat is
called the Admiral Joe Fowler just kind of what's with the scary military and then later this other
boat ends up both of these military guys who helped build Disney world now there's boats named
after them yeah something about seeing the military word this is no slight on anyone serving I think
it just like the just the word they just like remind it always reminded me of war when I'm
trying to get on a nice boat yeah well it was in the air when Disney world was being built and
conceived so the helicopters that's what this episode was about in Vietnam for context this
was a different time what you have to understand is then yeah Fortunate Son plays yeah yeah yeah
this might not tell the tale and on Spotify in a white room with people love it's gonna be
speaking of aging and everything it's gonna be sad when people are too old to make documentaries
about the 60s and they can't drop all of these no yeah yeah 60s songs into them anymore that's a
good point I don't know people might forget gimme shelter that's a good point although the
rolling stone again I said Jimmy Buffer might be immortal Mick Jagger might be immortal
he's showing up gotta show him I'm no charlie look at me go that was certainly a slight to their dead
drummer I think for sure not me not this year oh I'm not going out like Stan Cheryla he was my
friend too oh I just got many a rowdy night with a Donald and Stan Cheryla I just got some fresh
blood injections because it's easy sleazy that is he might have made the only song that is actually
that is the song of the weird era where we thought the pandemic was over and then not
he gave us the anthem of the most specific sliver of time and it makes sense that the
anthem was really stupid yes it's all been a very stupid time why you better believe I
listened to easy sleazy after I got my second shot we all were on the drive back windows down
yeah I don't know has this come up on the show yet I don't believe so I don't think I think people
already I had to dive for what was even the name of that song I had to when you said easy sleazy I
know exactly yeah but I didn't remember the name Mick Jagger has a solo song yes it's not a rolling
stone song because they want any part of it they released a song called living in a ghost town at
the start of the pandemic right which was not related to they didn't write it for the pandemic
but it just it lined up perfectly and they released that but then Mick Jagger released a solo song
called easy sleazy right well may we had to wear a mask it's all these like streamed lines of yeah
I took a cooking class it's like basically like yeah like a Jimmy Fallon sketch
but Mick Jagger wrote it as a serious song I'm obviously he's kidding a little bit but yeah if
you haven't heard it please listen to this now easy sleazy that's what general joe potter and
admiral joe faller that's what they described as like murking snakes like they're in their dead
shots you know they served you know can you tell him easy sleazy easy sleazy that's what they would
say I would like to talk about general joe potter um uh Fowler can get his time feel free I just
him as the the snake killer I mean just what a cool sort of like I uh just apocalypse now
she'll know it all figure fictional yeah and all of its yeah this guy is credited I never knew any
of this really till today that this guy is credited with the big infrastructural plant like
like the big moving of heaven and earth that it took to turn swampland into a vacation destination
and he was given this task because of his military experience where he helped plan the invasion of
Normandy he's like figuring out supply count and how are you gonna move these massive vehicles
from here to there he laid the infrastructural groundwork for normandy and not it was like not
that distant of a memory it hadn't been that long no it was not even building this castle not 50
years no no less than 50 really recently yeah and then it was like yeah he was planning normandy then
he was planning out where all these tourists were going to take a shit yeah equally important of
course they did have to make sure that his office was very far away from the um you know non-fiction
movie department because still some bad blood with werner von baron oh sure yeah that's a very good
point I he uh uh he was the governor of the Panama canal zone fake that's fake that's his
that phrase or thought about it or what was going on in the Panama canal in the 50s literally he
went his jobs were he was that and then like I think I might retire and then I'll just consult
on the New York world's fair and that's where he met Disney but he went from the he was it was the
the fair and then right before that he was in charge of the Panama canal where he was responsible
there were 40 000 people living in the Panama canal zone and one of the things that he had to
deal with on a daily basis was malaria and it's why among the many things that this guy did for
Disney world he helped figure out how to keep mosquitoes away this is all things videos about
this why are there no mosquitoes in Disney world and a lot of it is due to this guy because he's
like I was there I was there in the Panama canal I saw people die every day in front of me they'd
throw up their insides and then but he like the the thing that he knew was if there's water you
got to keep it moving still water you're getting mosquitoes left and right so not only all these
bodies of water we got to keep things pumping everything's got to be rivers and streams and on
the flow and even he consulted on the roofs to make sure that water wouldn't get caught on a roof
and fantasy land because then mosquitoes would start showing up he figured out garlic powder
that was that is I think still used to keep mosquitoes away it's a garlic thing like a vampire
he was also he fought the vampire he was in transylvania yeah from 1960 to 1963
I have a thing on that on the swamp and the bugs yeah so Bay Lake which is on the other side of
the contemporary connects to the seven seas lagoon okay they had to do what they call everything is
that thing that's it's it's surrounding all the hotels and it's in front of the magic kingdom that
is that's the seven seas lagoon and then it's connected to Bay Lake which is a larger body of
water and it had to have a lot of work done this is from that Disney world first the first decade
book to restore the lake to a pristine state meant draining three and a half billion gallons of water
and removing an eight foot thick layer of muck covering the lake bottom but underneath all that
muck was a pleasant surprise pure white sand which is spread along the lake shore to create
beaches do not go on the beaches in 2021 now with the lake basin refilled it was stocked with 70,000
fingerling bass not only did this add fishing to the list of recreational opportunities in the
vacation kingdom it aided in insect control so a few birds with one stone whoa the fish help with
that's crazy yeah and still but just fish in there that's what so but we don't know if that's a
general joe invention maybe it's not credited specifically to him but it does seem in his
purview yeah yeah i think that's absolutely something he was he was part this is like
that is like a heady stuff all of this this is like changing the fabric of the land so what do
they call the thick terraforming the thing you have to do in space to be able to live anywhere
like this is a mild version of terraforming that had to be done before the 100 skyway and the tea
party could get built yeah and if wall was alive he would be in the bezos like i'm sure i'm assuming
bezos and musk are all talked about like terraforming mars that's gotta be that has
to be part of it if you want to live up in one of these places you have to change the makeup of
what is possible on the actual surface yeah because musk is like well you have to terraform it
then people are like oh what does that involve uh you know it's uh what else uh yeah yeah i was
talking to royland the other day he has no further information about sometimes you listen to him
talking you go is this guy know anything buddy you know what he did sell a flamethrower so that was
cool wait what he sold a flamethrower you could buy yeah but it didn't really work and it was
kind of like not that different than the one you use to kill weeds yeah yeah but there was you know
the boring company they they make little tunnels and he sold a flamethrower a couple couple years
ago that's that's pretty sick it's pretty honestly i gotta say where i'm sitting that's pretty sick
pretty sick bro uh just take a flamethrower to mars and i'll probably just like carve it up
and build tunnels boring company done barcode is gonna do it live in tunnels on mars yeah
it's got calms all kyle mooney character you're doing there
but the character's right let's be honest it's a correct character um so oh oh also in terms of
like bizarre nature uh like okay other things that were there at the time gators armadillos
uh and i heard a quote from marty sclar that one of the first times he went they were on a boat and
they passed by what became discovery island the weird abandoned zoo and that the only thing that
was there at the time was an illegal hunter shack just like a weird tin facility of people trying
to hunt deer deers boars and turkeys something about that island man just people want to
trespass on it like it's just the allure of it you know oh yeah yeah then and now um something
magical on there i guess uh but yeah this is illegal hunting shacks and snakes you gotta shoot
up uh what a bizarre what a bizarre place um and not only all that not only just like the the taming
of nature that had to be done there's also all of this weird infrastructural stuff yes because
like and i'm out of my depths to talk about like the zoning and the city stuff but they like
they should have been bound to all of these rules that anything in a city would have been
bound like like like there's all this zoning stuff that they didn't want to have to answer to
yes so they invented a city structure to not have to do any of that is that basically correct well
and they would use the the epcot movie as like and we might build a city you know they might
that you would use it as like a carrot to dangle so we need all the cities owning stuff we need
control we need control like it's unusual for a resort property to have full control of like
localized area this is what i have it says disney lawyers employed chapter 298 in the florida code
which allowed for the creation of independent drainage districts aimed at promoting the
development of florida's swampy lands thus in may 1966 the reedy creek improvement district was
born the rcip would have near total control over the land a problem though is that the united
states constitution guaranteed certain legal and political rights to all citizens even those within
a drainage district disney's solution was to create fake company controlled municipalities only
permanent residents would be permitted to vote and disney would grant permanent residency only
to a select group of employees and managers who were also loyal to the company which is insane
yes and this gets you into some stuff we were talking about this on the second gate with
celebration florida you guys made me aware of this thing that i didn't know that they've had
employees live in trailers on the property so that they can vote and they will vote the way that the
company wants yes in this fraudulent election to circumvent the u.s constitution i love that yeah
from that passage by the way there was a problem though the u.s constitution states what a problem
the disney lawyers also kept telling well like this was this problem with the epcot city it's like
you can't let people live here permanently or they will want to vote and control the city they live in
so it's like well they'll live here temporarily and it's like
so that would temporarily everyone lives everywhere temporarily you can't make these
people gerbil like you can't make these people animals in a zoo like the human zoo yeah he had
this other i also just saw this that he uh he he wanted to basically uh progress city would have
had no retirees you can't be retired there because you have to have a job you got to be working and
contributing to progress city or to disney up the road or something on this land and maybe in the
future i will build another city where retirees are allowed but not progress city because if you're
retired you're making no progress yeah and it it's wild and um that's where now we're getting loony
no no retiring here it does and again it's so funny to think about because you're talking
about committees maybe think of this section for the getaway book uh roy set up a central committee
to work on the amusement park walt was not included in the group there's mark and there's an
anecdote in here for mark davis of like walt was focused on the city he did he the secondary project
was the amusement was the east coast disneyland and he would get annoyed if people tried to take
too much of his time to talk about the park i also think that that has i mean i think there's people
have written about i think it has something to do with why the park isn't drastically drastically
different than disneyland because he was like yeah yeah just make a very similar park like he was
because he was not so invested he was here he didn't care he was he was much more about new stuff
so instead of being like a totally new different park he was like yeah yeah you guys do whatever
you want so either some world where there aren't other magic kingdoms like at all or they're just
like well there are but they're touches them there yeah exactly like it's just like yeah because they
they were talking about tokyo before like way before it ever got built like there was already
some chatter of other parks elsewhere yeah but i doubt well all any anytime i've ever read about
walt he seems like a guy who's like very adamant about one thing until they go hey you know we can
make a bunch of money and it should be and he goes all right fine so like yeah like they're
probably he would have like franchised disney out and focused on his city and then terraforming
venus or something you know well i'm going to a different planet than this bezos character
i'm gonna figure out some life elongating schemes so that he is still around i mean he was you know
like okay wait well they're all the frozen the cryogenic stuff is not true he's not frozen but
was he looking into cryogenics at least that's a good question that i don't know the answer to
because our current billionaires are doing this and this is a minor fascination with myself as
well reading about all this futurism stuff about life you freezing yourself yes me freezing myself
uh i just read that larry king for years had said he wanted to freeze himself but his family talked
him out of it so larry is not frozen and but yeah right though i don't actually know do you ever seen
if walt expressed the desire to actually have himself frozen or that's just i hate some of his
behavior at the end of the his life definitely seems like a man who wants to you know leave
a lasting impression like he it seems like he feels like the specter of death is following him
frankly like some of his behavior so i have to think at some point he thought like how do i out
live this sure because i the funclan talks about like he was drinking more at the end of his life
well sure and he went in for some surgery and that's an unrelated surgery and then they found
the cancer right because he had a horrible cough but yeah there's no like document like documentation
i don't know i don't know of i don't know exactly yeah saying like and i'd like to be frozen can we
get a freezer and put me in there it could be in one of those two biographies according to mental
floss.com that somebody maybe not him i think he was on his deathbed and someone from the studios
called cryogenics place and asked a lot of questions a lot of very interesting questions
and that apparently uh the okay wait he never specified it in writing and when he died the
family didn't go for it two weeks later they froze the first man oh really so this was the first wow
so he was maybe in contentia if he had like gotten it out and verbalized it he could have been the
first man frozen that's pretty crazy not not just to be frozen he could have been the first wow that
is crazy uh that would have i think that would i don't know which company that was i don't know
if they're still around i mean there's there was an expose because baseball player ted williams was
frozen and there are two ways i understand to be frozen one is your whole body gets frozen or they
separate the head and just freeze the head i think correct maybe i'm wrong about it being ted williams
but there was the um there was an expose on one of these places and they just had like heads hanging
around people mistreating the heads yeah and just like a fucking sleazy creepy weird fake biz i don't
know if it's totally fake but like truly not some sort of professional thing where yeah they take
these like human bodies that have just passed away uh they treat them well i don't know if it's that
story but there's a simple there's some cryonics kind of situation that i liked because it was up
in in chatsworth which is closer to where i'm from where like there's a forest line there's a cemetery
where they got some space at the cemetery to do some experiment on there were 10 bodies in there
and then it was all investigated and looked into after the funding had been cut and people walked
in it was just this horrifying room of like melting it just wasn't like oh my god yeah
refrigerated treated probably and i drove up there not like it was a whole podcast about it
i don't remember specifics very well but i was like i gotta drive up there just to like know the
vibe like even to feel what it's like to go off of a road and then get into a building where this
ice and corpses melt that is the creepiest shit it is i know a family friend was living with someone
who was frozen and was there at the end and was like weird x-files shit of like people lingering
in the final few weeks like just like this weird shadow company lingering while the
the gentleman was like slowly passing away and it is just hearing a little bit about it you go this
is just so creepy i don't know i would be fascinating to know how many of these places
are still around i think by and large the community that is actually trying to end aging
which is really what a lot of these people's premise is that like you're trying to deal with
diseases and like trying to cure diseases but really the thing is aging aging is the thing
our cells get weak and they can't fight things off anymore so i don't i think that freezing is
going out of fashion pretty fast we're not this has been if we're talking if the first man was
frozen frozen in 66 is what we're discovering uh that's older than disney world yeah uh happy
56th birthday freezing yeah i don't think it's going too well for you i think the proof would
be in the pudding and the pudding is melting yeah yeah i think there was another story a few years
ago about like a cryogenic startup where like oh no the power went out and all everything melted
like it's like the best minds are not focused on this you know there's a lot of other things
yeah i guess perhaps if somebody is i wonder what the best cryogenics place maybe they do have a
corpse that has been preserved and once they figure the aging thing out they can do it but it
feels like they're all about it feels it doesn't feel nearly as good as the austin powers technology
i don't think that's possible at all pods do you think anyone uh ever looked into freezing
themselves because they watched the first 12 minutes of austin powers didn't continue to watch
the fun comedic romp that ensued they just saw it as like a technological leap forward i watched a
sci-fi thriller the other day something about power it was about the power probably a free
thing it was called the power of freezing power for you yeah i think it's got to be one person
who got away maybe it was larry maybe larry king watched it i i'd like to be frozen now please
one frozen since you mentioned it i believe disney's remains were cremated and are in one
of the forest lawn cemeteries in the san fernando valley which again we're not that far from i i
enjoyed a uh a nice iced tea earlier today in the shadow of the hospital where he died
oh sure it's not well they've got that walk up starbucks in the yeah they've got it i just
rode my bike it was very pleasant i didn't go there and think about well now i feel bad i didn't go
there and think about wall here while we're doing this episode i should have like bud you know
bent down and said a little something said a little something poured out some of the ice
team can i see the drop tile ceiling where he explained how the city was laid out in his last
week yeah yes that well this was another general joe potter thing that he went to see him on his
deathbed in the last couple weeks and that he's using the ceiling and saying well then that's
going to be over there and that'll be the hub you see and he's like pointing at an empty ceiling
and saying this plan this is nuts so yeah yeah this i can't even imagine that it's truly surreal
austin powers is more real than what you just described to me now like mere mere feet away
from where we are right now in his defense terraforming swampland building a major
international vacation destination they got pretty close they got pretty close oh yeah what he did
easiest stuff yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah where they landed and i thank them for it it's truly
wonderful but the metaphor i kept thinking about is like if you set out to make a thanksgiving dinner
and very quickly you abandon the raw turkey and the entree becomes mashed potatoes and that is
the main course the mashed potatoes are the main course the secondary the side dish is now the main
course and over the course of 50 years the mashed potatoes just get more and more elaborate
and also more and more you're like sweating while you're saying this you're getting like really
worked up talking about these mashed potatoes because all the stories about it's like yeah the
this this this was secondary the the amusement park theme park was secondary jim hill i think
pointed out that essentially it was the icon the weenie was the magic kingdom to drive uh people's
eye to drive traffic tourism dollars tourists to the florida property when the city was going to be
the main focus it probably makes sense to get people down there with something to do sure yeah
amusement park and not just like come to the city with no olds with old people come to the logan's
run city yeah no retirees i mean the subtext of that is they killed the old people right yeah i
think so they were euthanized you think yeah yeah here's the general frozen general will freeze you
here we'll show you the freezing machines and no they're actually they're they're turbines wall
just big fans wall marty spotter writes in his book walt entered the office and said we need a way to
get rid of the old people not me no the ones not in control the ones who haven't done anything with
bob gur was like well i just built a big fan and i just roll them in i don't know
let's call it the magical chamber of dreams yeah sounds good that's got a nicer ring to it than
euthanasia and then we got went to the shore we went to the sherman brothers they needed a song
for the fan yeah went to the magical machine yeah there's some animator somewhere who's like well i
i animated the two cats in the arista cats and then i well i helped him come up with death panels
he said you've got talent help me with some numbers issues do it all the way you solve
health care is to not have old people we don't have to support them oh man um speaking of
insanity though there was all this like um how okay so jason you said it that uh they finally
they start getting the project off the ground they're gonna build something and the uh the
state is kind of well i don't know you need to follow these rules and you got to uh you know
you should abide by this and that well let's show you this movie and this movie has walt in it he's
gonna talk about his dream and then it melted everyone's icy hearts and now like okay whatever
you need what would you like to do and suddenly disney had the power they had no uh state or
county regulation on buildings airport construction they could have built an airport though they never
did uh a distribution sale of alcoholic beverages didn't have to apply for the regular stuff for
that and they even had the right to build a nuclear power plant anyone know that i hadn't heard that i
hadn't heard it either yeah they were like and still and this is like a florida law legislature
thing and i don't think it's all companies i think it is like on the books in florida that if the
walt disney company wants to build a nuclear power plant on that property they can do it and it for
sure still does exist because every once in a while a state senator will come around and say
maybe that should be out of there even though it doesn't seem likely that here in 2021
disney is going to suddenly build a nuclear power that's not doesn't seem like the way the
winds are blowing they did build a nice solar power plant with the shape of mickey's ears
that's cute and nice and forward thinking nuclear power they're probably not going to do
however even though it was just this minor thing that i think the senator kind of dropped ultimately
disney still sent in lobbyists so like to keep the option open yeah yeah yeah yeah still put
in money to say actually we would like to still have that right you gotta have a little wiggle
room you know you gotta let industry grow i mean that is the give and take of all these parks but
like especially the stuff about disney world because wall was encouraging his you know i think
we said earlier like the florida property will give us projects for decades and he encouraged
the imagineers to like think past your lifetime and that's a good i think that is you should tell
artists that you know that i think that is good but then it's funny to see the way the parks are
executed where it's like you are lucky of attraction you have a handful attractions that last 20 30
years or so and then the other thing is he wants industry to fund all this stuff to to make all
this stuff and they're not thinking past their lifetimes industry is thinking about lining their
pockets and the way you line your pockets changes as industries evolve and change so it's like
oh i don't that he was a man of conflicts for sure could he have built an atomic bomb also
might i mean i don't know the full blow a bunch of dust off of a big book in the florida state
legislature but yeah is it possible on the books is like what was allowed to build one
nuclear bomb every decade and like would he have hit would he have hit universal orlando with the
bomb during construction that was legal according to some sort of charter sorry you know business
cost to be one business so they want to keep it open for that reason if they want a torpedo sea
world or sesame place is expanding let's get these fuckers out of there yeah if they wanted
to build a big drill machine yeah it can like go in a subterranean fashion under one of their
yeah like um like uh cranes ships that he would use from the technodrome to the surface area level
yeah they'd have that big drill on the front they got disney got real nervous when ninja turtles
started using that because they're like that's really close to our copyright they locked them
down locked them down in mgm studios in the early years yeah good point let's cut a deal you come
dance around in our parks and we won't say anything about this subterranean machine you blew the cover
on you know um while they were fighting the state they were also benefiting a lot of the
developments in the state because the florida highway system was being rapidly like expanded
and built like interstate four and the florida turnpike and then where they built where they did
it was proximity to uh yeah yeah to those roads thinking like you know there wasn't really there
wasn't a major airport yet no in orlando so yeah those highways are super important to them and
why they put it there orlando was still mccoy air force base and then gradually shifted to more
and more civilian flights and it's still the the three-letter code for orlando is mco it's still
i never knew that it's still a holdover front it was an air force base but with the drawdown
as vietnam was wrapped up that air was no longer in there needed an air force base on florida wow
and now yeah no white room with land and get on the mickey's magical express
white room flame i guess not anymore well for a short while longer oh is it still going right i
thought it was still going to the end of the calendar year okay i apologize for not knowing
um so where where are we now i mean this is all such madness what they had to do this
it's also like in addition to yeah terraforming essentially they're also
they they got to do hotels for the first time and they've never they've never done that because
the disneyland hotel was this other corporation running it and they were just licensing the name
initially now disney runs a ton of hotels they did not at the time they had to learn some stuff
about it i saw this weird fact that there was a in the lead-up to disney world opening in like the
year prior they saw that a guy was opening a little hilton inn on i drive he was like prepping it
he's an independent owner and disney went to the guy and said hey can we run your hotel for you
as practice like this is this odd little where you'd go to the hotel and you wouldn't even know
that disney was running the joint and did for like 18 months after the opening of disney where they
they made got this big deal we won't just leave you out to dry this will be our hotel for a little
while we'll just like learn and watch and figure it out and train people in here and then uh so
that they were more able to do contemporary and polynesian that's great that is why like was like
were the imagineers like dressed up did they running it like how were they incognito like
oh yes hello nothing to see here
uh yeah i think so um yeah yeah doing like uh broad uh like custodial characters and like
john cleese and faulty towers all fake english accents and stuff yeah yeah uh yeah conical
prat falls uh the stupidly large key rings well yeah they had to see how guests would react to
prat falls from the hotel staff they just needed to know all the different angles of it day to day
prat falls are going to happen at some point in the calendar year so if a bell boy is holding
too many bags and the bags open how will the guest react you wouldn't know unless you tried
unless you ran it and tried that if there's like a monkey running around who like took the little
bellhop costume and put it on and then was running wild in a room yeah something i assume happened
in a disney live action film around that time was yeah it was dunc- dunston checks in based on an
old older movie which is the movie you just described just assume it's if it if it was in
the late 60s and kurt russell was in it there's probably a monkey movie oh yeah kurt russell was in
uh chimp hotel from 1962 yeah yeah very popular that jane goodall research you know was just
hitting and you know susan placette and kurt russell in chimp hotel walt disney presents
chimp hotel which is coming back on disney plus there's going to be a full yeah three season
arc of it um yeah the follow followed up of course by uh the the bananas bellhop yeah right of course
yeah well you start with season one you don't have three negotiate contracts so yeah of course so
yeah well we're excited about that i didn't know that i didn't know they were like testing hotel
running a hotel there's a whole like even like hiring up was apparently pretty difficult because
just like this notion everything that they figured out in california and what was by now in motion of
like it's the disney look and the disney way of being and its cast members and its friendliness
and all the cus like just like hiring people i think they had trouble shifting people to like
teaching the disney way just sort of creepy thing to bring up i guess but just this like
manifested itself in that people would show up at disney say i want a job and they wouldn't really
know like what the kinds of jobs they were even filling speaking of monkeys there was a guy who
was like you're hiring okay great went to his truck brought out a little train monkey and did a
little act and thought like this is so i can do this in disney world great amusement parks yeah
yeah carnivals this is an amusement are you not amused wow is like an organ grinder type of a
situation or yeah i think so wow how yeah just thought like you could use this couldn't you
he was right they should have it still yeah they there hasn't been a live monkey in a part of an
animal kingdom i assume for a long time yeah but not in like a city environment that's true yeah
costume right that's what we want it's kind of crazy to think about um you know uh not that
central florida was a total backwater but it was a bit off the beaten path because
they had to build a factory where like uh port orleans is now to construct the modular hotel
rooms for the two hotels oh yeah but then they had to build the monorail like the concrete beams in
tocoma washington and then get them across the country wow so it everything is they're kind of
learning it as they go along and with hiring i guess that's how they ended up with uh like
about 5 000 cast members on opening day when they ended up with 10 000 guests so that's a
cast member for every for every two guests wow yeah yeah yeah jeez yikes um yeah i think like
i think a lot of it was very difficult like they didn't like who's going to build the monorail
who's around that can do that just like all the functional stuff and they'd only done this
once before i was also reading how they everything at disneyland was built
sort of in this bob gurway that we talk about where i don't know i did it and i did a little
drawing and here's how it worked i worked it out and then it was there there was no plan and put
there was no like here's a book of how you do this ride or that ride because it all just sort of
happened and kind of nobody thought it would happen again so reproducing everything i think
was a big hassle yeah yeah it is because obviously now like they probably could get
they probably have like down to the centimeter every single ride in a database yeah oh yeah
have to i mean exact dimensions of everything and every uh character in it and every exact
paint color and yeah you could 3d print a disney park right in like a couple days but it is fun
it is like hey did you take notes on how we built the other one no no i thought about that
i do yeah i guess we should have saved some of the drawings huh that was that one okay well i
kind of remember how it is i think osha comes along after the opening of disney world oh right
yeah i'm not saying it's because of the opening of disney but it they weren't subject to it for a
while right right so yeah that is why it's just wild because so much stuff i mean just not even
taking it out of theme parks i just like you go you drive through a city you go how do they figure
out how to do a city how did you figure out how to make one of these tall buildings i feel like
such an idiot yeah because i'm like if you really think about just logistically how our world has
been constructed i go i'm the dumbest person alive i have no clue how to do this and then in
in the span of human history it's relatively it's not long that this stuff was all created and so
it's interesting getting a little like microcosm of it from disney world going yeah this it is
funny how you just take so many just like mundane things for granted just because they exist and go
they always knew how to run a hotel or build a monorail but they did not they truly were kind
of clueless i know i think that all is yeah streets yeah what streets huh i'm like the dumbest man
alive if i really start to think about stuff when i go i don't know how this works i don't know how
i passed by a pothole then i was like why aren't why isn't it all potholes that was our streets
built there aren't potholes everywhere all the time exactly yes um so dumb i'm dumb i'm yeah i'm
real dumb jason no not i'm reasonably dumb yeah i i i don't think i could uh yeah build a city
or anything like that but i read a little and i cannot apply it in real life no application for
the yeah um i well what have we missed on the way to opening day because we got we want to
get to opening day roy you gotta give it up to roy o disney because he he kind of made it all
hat he had first off he had to put up he was good with uh his brother's crazy schemes uh and then
you know kind of resigned himself to like we gotta do this and i want to do this in his honor
well i postponed his retirement postponed his retirement yeah uh also died a few months after
opening day of disney world in december of 71 yes like my work here is done and then like heaven
took him away he slept for the first time in 40 plus years or so and it was instant yeah yeah well
and the whole the engineering story i believe goes into this how he was always the money guy
and then this was his chance to get involved with the artists and the engineers and like the people
doing the fun stuff and he apparently had a lot of fun he saw the other side of it he saw the stuff
that walt got to do he got to do it and i think he died with a with a lot of joy and he of course
is why it is called walt disney world right his first moves was to we'll put the full name in it
so that people are more likely to remember the man as if it was gonna say like really
i guess right yeah his name is disney your name is pretty splashy like uh yeah on camera a lot i
so much footage of him yeah um not all people likely to be forgotten oh walt disney oh i thought
it might be a different guy because this is on the east coast oh okay it's him i see i see not
jonathan q disney oh okay got it um so yeah i mean it seems like his drive really
caused it all to happen and that's why there's a statue of him at the park correct and the magic
is sitting on a bench next to minnie right gotta ask mike yeah well jealous pisses me off yeah
that old man doesn't deserve to sit next to minnie his true love though he was a money man like
get bern and tracy you know never got divorced but well you know that was real love i don't know i
don't care for it yeah well maybe the golden one they're putting in will be your shot yeah they
should it would just be it should be the exact same statue but without roy and you can sit there
and take your own photo that's what i would prefer um hello um uh so yeah he roy makes it happen um
they set october 1st 1971 as the day partially because um they are remembering the mistakes of
disneyland disneyland opened in the middle of the summer it was extremely hot which caused all of
the famous problems that they ran out of water and the women's heels are melting into the concrete
just added to the mania that it was so hot and the disaster that was disneyland opening day we
did an episode about it you can go check that out um so they didn't want that so they they picked
october when the weather is worse uh when school is back in session yes the friday it's kind of
i don't know is it a friday i don't know that it's a friday now it's friday this year was a friday
okay good i didn't get it right uh so just kind of like middle it's not a weekend uh they think
they wanted to downplay it a lot and this is funny because it's sort of how the opening of
galaxy's edge played out where they're saying you're sensing from a lot of places this is
going to be pretty nuts you maybe don't want to be part of this maybe people stay away and then
they did and it was like oddly because we were there first day of galaxy's edge it was oddly
sparse everywhere but galaxy's edge and that's sort of what happened with disney world too they
it worked too well leading to that problem of a cast member for every two people uh and
it was so it was initially like very initially i think there was it's not like it got it was that
dire but i think it opened with a feeling of uh oh what if this didn't what if we didn't
successfully do the east coast outreach what if people aren't interested in this
yes or hopefully this is just like a result of people being afraid of crowds but maybe we
messed it up they roy did think that before he passed away like that was keeping him awake
maybe alive the stress was coursing through his body keeping alive but yeah it was kind of a bad
first couple weeks i i believe seemingly yeah i think they i think it turned around by the time
thanksgiving came around i think the thanksgiving holiday they were like oh wow there's a lot of
there's like 50 000 people in the park yeah yeah i think no it like it exploded pretty quickly
thereafter and then with thus leading to like giant lines of cars they'd have to like block
parking lots and say nobody could come in so cars would just pull off to the side of the road and
wait and then they'd see a car leave and they go all right well then i can go in and they'd go to
the turnstile and say that well i saw car leaves that means i get to go well no it's not as simple
as that what why not so like furious campouts and like i think i think it was like pretty rough in
terms of crowd management for the first little run yeah there's a funny helicopter story um the
website this day in disney history has a couple of good uh did you find this too um uh it has a lot
of interesting facts and pictures and stuff there's a story about card walker and don tatum
two executives going up in a helicopter and seeing lines and lines of cars and getting very excited
at all the people coming and then the cars started to turn the wrong way and they realized it was all
the cast members going to park it is really like from this from these stories to the opening day
special contrasted with disneyland it is night and day it is so like call that opening this opening
day special is pre-recorded it starts with just part of it yeah they were out like we learned
about we will film this over the course of three days instead of trying to do some big live thing
and it was done way later this was done after october first right just kind of like yeah it'll
just be we'll just ramp up slowly over a month no big weird special where people are on drugs and
cheating on their wives it is why yes that it's the difference nighted like the disney world
special open that we i don't want to jump ahead but like it opens with a four minute glenn campbell
music video largely glenn campbell it is so much glenn campbell yeah watch this special if you want
to kind of follow along with us the grand opening of all disney world 1971 um yeah it's real sleepy
it's so sleepy today is mine today is mine and it's the whole song and it's the first and there's
shots of disney world but not as many as you'd think the first four minutes of the opening day
special would have fields it's a lot of fields in swampland and then he keeps coming back with very
boring speeches like you're i was just sitting here going shut up man play wichita lineman come
i like some glenn campbell songs yeah that's exactly um but it is it's it's real meandering
and just kind of like spirit and hope and americana and that's the that song is what i wrote like it's
like there's a feeling there's a feeling rumbling beneath this land and then they don't really show
you like yeah right and it's not like sky buckets and there's some disney songs but you're like i'm
not sure why this was the choice yeah the the contrasting it with if you haven't heard our
disneyland opening day special you can even just watch that special it is crazy it is it is uh it
is punk rock the disneyland opening special it's like cinema verite yeah it's like very yeah and
like kind of with it's like harsh black and white i think that adds to it uh that you can't always
make out what's happening yeah it's uh it's like a very distinct visual palette and this is just
this like 70s tide commercial it is just yeah so yeah bland in every way they're just like i don't
know what it was with the 70 maybe it was the it's it's post vietnam let's say it let's calm
everybody down things are hectic everything just got so like sanitized and gentle yeah yeah calm
well i think in 55 television was still very new like it was still the early days of the medium so
they so to do a major broadcast for this giant event and then by the 70s it's like all right we
figured out how to like cut variety and cut like you know live events down to something that like
it's very clean but then it's like experience doing it and it's not just it's just not by the
seat of our pants anymore but it's too clean that said there are there's a couple versions on youtube
one of which i i think the one has more commercials in it from the time and that's a lot of fun
like getting to see of course we've we yeah we talked about that the eastern airlines uh add with
orson welles narrating of like fly eastern airlines to disney world walt disney world
there is a certain airline
um yeah uh it's something this special i would say if i had to choose between this or really any
other special you know hey look i love my old disney world specials i watch these all the time
i would not put this towards the top of my favorites it is me andry oh yeah that is for sure
boy some sleepy musical numbers i you know hey i think we all like julie andrew's plenty i don't
i don't need to see any of those numbers again no no no bad job or anything it's just all boy she
she entered she's introduced like on the monorail and the the noise of the monorail is just as loud
as her voice which is really funny uh and then she does like yeah like a weird like disco zippity
dude uh like not even disco like kind of i don't know i guess a little dance it's just it has like
boo boo boo in it right yes so it's like i don't know what this is and like hip 70s varieties kids
dancing with her yeah and i don't ugly colors i don't believe anyone would wear in reality yeah
and then fucking bob hope shows up oh man that's really the core of it is the miss as they call
the spirit of eternal youth now there cannot be an older looking man than bob hope in 1971
man lived to be 100 he lived to the ripe old age of 100 100 years old and he had it is you know it
wasn't youthful was his brain no it was not no he's greatest ideas none of those forward thinking
ideas this man tell a lot of body half jokes like like half set up half punch line like i don't
it's not all the way there if you don't know this footage it is i will give it this it is possibly
the craziest setup for a stand-up comedy routine that has ever occurred oh yeah the monorail
landing in the inside station of the contemporary hotel the monorail door is open bob hope
walks down half a flight of stairs and does his stand flanked by two guides with a like riding
crop plaid style right guides uh and then he's and and the you know the contemporary hotel if
you've been in there is just very like uh i mean it's a pretty just big open concourse but it's
also like kind of angular depending on where you are so you feel like his angle is weird and
everything's pointed weird and diagonal and it keeps cutting to balconies where everybody's like
leaning in these weird ways and the sight lines aren't that's the funniest that people are like
they walked out of their hotel room and they're leaning over the the balcony on the 12th floor
trying to watch a comedy routine one of the strangest rooms i think ever it would stand ups
been done in yeah it wouldn't shock me also if it was all not like shot at different times because
of how odd it is i don't think i'm sure some of it was but it's like it's so disorienting that if
you told me that like the place was empty except for bob hope and the two girls there yeah you
would be oh yeah it makes because the audio is sweetened the laughs are sweetened for sure oh yeah
not enough not enough it still makes it still makes it sound like he's eating shit with these
jokes yeah a lot of them truly don't well you want to you want to get into it you just have them on
your i don't know i don't know yeah okay right i have them tattooed yeah you have a tattoo
with shitty old comedy talk earlier this week with the the two hour 45 minute late shift get
ready for some bob hope now older older and oldier older and shittier yeah uh he goes so he looks
there's a couple creepy jokes he looks these girls up and down and they have to be seven
17 or younger i don't know maybe 18 with that we can't say yeah i guess not they're very young
looking that's all i'll say documentation i don't want to i know you want to defend bob hope's honor
here i understand always great man he like looks one of them up and he goes oh boy they don't build
mice the way they used to which first of all let's just break this joke down the they're not might
the the because they're a mouseketeers what is he talking about here it's unclear like it's really
unclear what he's in disney world it's so he could have just said like they're a mouseketeer maybe
if i'm punching the joke up it's like you it's just really what is he doing what do you have
the follow-up to that like joke that didn't about like meet me yeah he says like meet me in an
adventure land meet me in adventure land and the audience is like tickled by that yeah but he's
this old man is saying hey let's hook up in adventure land that's the joke yeah he's saying
i'm gonna hook up with these two young women in adventure land later and he did and he they
charted a private jungle cruise boat mr eternal youth who could turn it down who could turn out
done the charm of a probably in his late 50s but seemingly in his early 80s he couldn't do it he
impregnated both of them and they raised their children together as friends and the children
are friends and they have bob to thank for them that's very nice so beautiful story there's a i'm
cutting i'm cutting around here i just like when he like really lazily goes hey what a building
hey i know we think it too he's right i mean it is a great building we really like the building
well it's really two buildings leaning against each other i want to congratulate the architect
dean martin is that the strongest joke no no is that the strongest joke because he leans because
he's drunk yeah because he's drunk and like leaning like leaning i guess so yeah you know the way you
lean and the way you don't ever lean when you're sober it is only activated by alcohol right
leaning and that's the thing we know about dean martin is that he leans a lot that's the first
thing that comes to your head when you think of dean martin is he leans a lot so the guy was tall
but from the how often he's leaning you'd think he was five two that's a pretty good there i
push it up yeah yeah you could go i keep going i keep going he's better than i was around to do the
a hack scenario with bob hope if only the young gun giving him the john wayne when john wayne
paints i don't have that one well and john wayne doodles he really doodles yeah yeah because there's
like a weird mural and the mary blare he's the mary blare western for some reason the futuristic
hotel has a western themed mural and you have to know this already to get the joke right and he's
like saying john wayne painted this that's the joke uh that one doesn't go with that i don't feel
like the audience gets that the sweetened audience this is just like reference this is their big
references at the time it's like yeah we were if we were nowadays talking about like i don't know
like oh i'm feeling real malignant in this so like i don't know i can't i'm feeling real malignant
i haven't watched it i just know it's a thing what's what are the other things who painted the shung
chi these are the two things people talk about bts tickets for their tour i'm going to see bts
the ride on the monorail smooth like butter i got the sweetie mail at mcdonald's
boy what a meal huh what a meal rough flight out here i'll tell you so much turbulence and
all the people on board i'll tell you what i had after you know that a lot of venom
i'm just thinking let there be carnage look up the google the name of the i was praying to the
patron saints of newark that flight was so rocky who could go for a licorice pizza
oh if only cryogenics worked and we could have a hundred and twenty-five year old bob
hoe truly would be the spirit of eternal youth oh man we could we could ride for one bob hope for
ity special be able to buy a house yeah that's true the old economy economics of comedy back
in the day well look the economic economics are not wrong because now it's a bunch of weird
shit that most 10 000 people watch or listen to back then this special that were like kind of
boring right kind of bad stand up and not a you know boring glenn campers this is watched by
a 52 million people yeah yeah those numbers uh um but no the topicality it's it was different
you know you it is such that you sometimes have to do research to figure out what the joke was
as in this case which is he's referencing the different lands he says they got a place fantasy
land that's like spiro agnew winning the national open and at first i'm like all right national was
of what does that mean okay context clues golf could be golf when he was on the simpsons
he asked you the mayor what's the mayor's name quimby got it and then he made a joke about mayor
quimby being a bad golfer uh so okay that must be with that is spew agnew was nixon's vice president
so was spiro agnew a bad golfer i look up spiro agnew golf and it turns out that about seven months
prior at bob hope's own golf tournament that uh there was a foursome and the foursome was
bob hope willy maize baseball willy maize a pro golfer named doug sanders and the vice
sitting vice president spiro agnew and that is that is a foursome at this golf tournament
they all tee up this is the first this is hole number one spiro agnew takes his first shot
immediately hits two people in the stands an older husband and wife they happen to be if you're going
to hit people make sure they're married helps to keep the lawsuits tight here so he goes up to the
woman charms her like i'm so so well if there's anything i can do kisses her on the arm just
denoted that d wow the vice president hit me with a golf ball and kissed me uh then he goes all right
and everybody charms everybody applause applause great he goes back to the tee uh tees off again
immediately hits somebody else hits them harder and worse uh yeah a woman half that age who had
to go to the hospital and get an x-ray for it it's like dick cheney shooting the guy on
hunt and hunting he was the he was a pioneer vice president's in farming other uh wow well and you
don't even know the half of it because it turns like the year prior he uh hit somebody in the face
he shot a golf ball into somebody's face persuading dick cheney's bullet and the person who he hit in
the face was doug sanders the other guy in the foursome who they still wow this guy still
voluntarily after being hit in the face by him is like yeah sure sign me up i'll go out that's wild
three people three uh people in the stands with two balls so that's the best joke in the set it
kind of is yeah bob was there he knew it he heard the screams he saw the bruises personal connection
autobiographical yeah wow that's okay that's a good joke this is an honest set and that's why
an honest joke at least and that's why it was so funny yeah like people wouldn't be upset with him
like they're upset with malaney now because he would hope was more honest than his standup
jesus i'm just saying you know you felt so betrayed yeah i know i thought bob hope would
never betray us with his comedy uh real quick side note i have collected money at bob hope's
house i didn't get to go like in in but i went to collect money from um uh being crowsby's second
wife who i was working for oh who you were yeah that's right well because the house if you don't
know is again not far from where we all live and do this podcast and it's like yeah this is
unbelievable this is this crazy insane yes and there's a three there's three whole golf course
in the back golf course on it yeah and to luke lake over here so good christmas displays my
parents would take me to sit sure this is bob and delores and delores supervises it and remember
all this because you'll probably run out of ideas and do a second gate on your podcast about this
that's it it's a title you should use by the way second gate that was when i was nine right and
she was they were right um so that's what that joke was and any other jokes that we want to
name check did anyone else do any deep dives into what a joke meant no i'm glad you did because
i actually yeah ignored that one and i think that you got the juiciest one because the other ones
yeah also keep in mind that after all that he he's a horrible golfer uh injuring people every time
he plays and then two years later he's the first vice president to resign due to criminal charges
spiro coming stay tuned that's coming back around later what criminal charges will come back up
later in this episode oh my god okay how much how far are you anticipating two more hours
it's entirely possible um well if we're done with bob hope who by the way comes back in an even more
boring segment of the special god yeah they just give him like a little a non-comedic monologue a
wistful monologue at the lake i was reading i was reading how a lot of people were very annoyed
with bob hope over the years like johnny carson was annoyed because he would he would like bring
something up like oh so bob i hear you just came back from a tour and he go yeah
on the show not a giving comedic partner yeah it seems like we just get drag on a talk show great
thanks for coming yeah there is um something in the special directly in my uh line of interest
which is the 1,700 so no sorry 1,076 piece marching band led by the music man creator composer
meredith wilson and they play 76 trombones marching down main street uh there are indeed 76
trombones in this ensemble uh and uh i it is very funny that they are uh playing a song
from a musical about a con man who hoodwinks like average american joes into spending a lot of money
the opaque of walt Disney world uh but as it is it's just a music man is that what you're saying
yeah he's not it's a funny selection even though like they do occasionally here on main street
uh yeah that's true no they play the more con manny song yeah they no they play their joe and t song
that kind of is often played removed from it but there there are stories about um people in the
marching band like you know kids in the marching band and stuff and like the one kid you know their
busk was really late arriving and roy oh disney came out and shook their hands and said hi and
then meredith wilson sent like letters saying like thanks for being a part of this like like
to everyone in the in the band seemingly to uh people in the band wow yeah and as we know i
marched in a marching band down main street when i was in high school and i did not get a letter
from the real from the real wilson meredith wilson who was possibly dead although you know
probably dead at this point we played late in the evening by paul simon and i did not get a
letter from paul simon well but paul simon also wasn't leading your band down main street i maybe
he was no well i don't know maybe he was i don't think he was i don't you would have led with that
as the main part of the story yeah i guess you're right i wasn't first time ever he led a marching
theme park it's possible in the late early 2000s paul simon was leading a marching band down main
street in disney world it's eclectic the music's eclectic yeah um yeah so uh yeah it's a weird
special i mean that i'm glad you're charmed by that marching band thing but it also lasts for i want
to say 25 minutes most at the end of the special yeah most of the back half of the special
which marching band on television doesn't really yeah this isn't like drum line or something
drum line is awesome like a real hold on energy performance before the marching band there's an
orchestra so pretty dynamic people sitting perfectly still in chairs playing instruments
before the walking instruments man yeah it's it's uh it's quite a special there's also some
sketches where jonathan winter shoots his wife with an arrow oh yeah these jonathan winter sketches
brutal i would say yeah yeah this feels like the first like improv on tv in the early 70s
i could be wrong this could be scripted but kind of his thing was that true it was yes jonathan
winters would improvise uh a lot but these uh these don't land i would say no and he plays a
final tracker final swamp man yeah there's some characters some characters but buddy hack it does
drive her with the love bug yes along tomorrowland's b-way route against actual race car drivers oh with
chick hern my uh beloved uh basketball announcer of my youth la guy right yeah surprised to see him
in a florida thing right so yeah that's nice so yeah there's some hat you get some hack it he's
got energy at least you know and he's in the music man he is he does shabu be that's right so you got
that connection yeah very exciting more music man content you know did he dine on like chopped
sirloin in a pear with uh meredith wilson at the contemporary or whatever gross food they were
serving at the time uh and i hope you are prepared you got trouble for the future podcast to ride live
music show i'm working on it because yeah you will be performing that i did it at karaoke i did it in
the one week we did we're all hanging out without this yes you did yeah that was a beautiful week
hopefully soon um so that's that's the founded that's the founding of it that's the special
that that takes us up to 1971 and now we're up and running and creating magic and memories for
generations to come it's 50 years of of incredible moments occur after all this and i think it's safe
to say that disney didn't peak at the beginning with glenn campbell monologues and lengthy marching
band performances so many wonderful things happened in the intervening years and that
is what we wanted to close this episode with is determining what is the greatest moment
in the history of the walt disney world resort or the greatest thing that ever happened there i
don't know i don't want to like completely define i don't know what all of our answers are and and
i don't want to shut anyone out but we do want to determine in 50 years what is the best stuff
that ever occurred there and i guess is this a situation where we all present something and
then the audience will decide where else having obviously correctly picked the three we've narrowed
it down to the three um and there there can only be one um is that fair to say i think so yeah that'll
be the best obviously it's going to be real hard to do this but yeah you go we i think that'll be
the yeah it's going to be personal to us obviously i just want to add that i think so yeah yeah uh we
it's impossible to um you know take ourselves out of the the running and our our our memories and
happy moments we've had and you know we'd like to hear your ideas of what the greatest moment in
disney world history is you might will be incorrect one of us will be correct but we'd still like to
hear them anyway of course yes try uh but so that that's what we're doing between between the three
of us we're going to figure out what's the best thing that ever happened on the property does
anybody want to i don't want to start you don't want to start too proud too much pressure uh i
could jason what do you think um i could go where do you want to go okay richard nixon
there's a lot of richard nixon stuff and oh well the career is the criminal
yeah so i didn't want to be you know very basic and go with i am not a crook richard nixon of
course delivers his famous line i am not a crook at the contemporary hotel in uh 1973 in front in
front of 400 managing editors of the associated press so that was was an associated press thing
yeah in the lion's den now uh there's some interesting stuff on the nixon library website
that they could nixon seemed like he wanted to be at the opening of disney world and there was
scouting there was a scouting trip to go wow and there is a page of potential remarks that the
president could say yeah that i did this is like possible speech possible speech stuff said yeah
uh he did not end up going there was a lot going on in 1971 nixon had just accepted the invite
to china uh that was historic um the the uh uh group called the plumbers had just broken into
the offices of daniel elsberg who had released the pentagon papers in september uh whatever they were
attempting to do failed uh i a big troop drawdown in vietnam occurred in december 1971 there we go
so it seemed like it would have been poor taste for the president to show up that said the white
house did send an american flag and who was the representative hr haldeman the chief of staff who
would go on to spend 18 months in prison for conspiracy and obstruction of justice student
was rolling watergate criminal charges as we mentioned earlier wow hr aldeman brought a flag
to the opening to the opening haldeman is credited on imdb in the opening special and i could not
find him i was wondering if he was possibly in the crowd shots of the um marching band or the
marching band is he doing a character with jonathan winters um uh but yeah i don't know
if he's in the crowd of the bob hope thing but uh nixon kind of a big seemingly disney dork i would
say like like i would guess that nixon is you're going dork i'm going with a disney nerd like us
like he was like he was at the opening of the monorail he drove the monorail he uh is from
orange county originally seemed like he wanted to be at the opening of disney world he's buried
15 miles from disneyland well that doesn't mean he's a disneyland dork i think he was buried with
we might be buried that close he had a lot of former disney people on staff like disney corporate
people he had former jungle crew skippers on stand like toke holvig the the voice of goofy was
involved in the break-in he went to jail for several years people like they drop pins disney
pins on his grave every day he's a pin collector in the after as far as after the afterlife i guess
and while he was not there for the opening ceremonies or anything nixon and his family
would go a number of times over the years not just for the i am i am not a crook speech uh so
i am going to award the best thing that ever happened is this moment where richard nixon
and his grandson meet dreamfinder and figment it's a perfectly symmetrical picture uh it's
wow that's crazy i didn't know i've not seen that picture icons yeah wow icons meeting uh there is
also i think a less iconic photo of uh nixon uh standing in front of spaceship earth yeah i've
seen that okay and if you zoom in you will notice that the buttons on his suit are different so this
is a different day this is either a different day from the same trip or a different trip when
nixon was hitting up ebcot center i sorry to cut you i'm obsessed with the idea of like nixon disney
dork like did you listen to the new jim hill and lentester what they were talking about the new rides
by the way it's my gruff is uh is my nixon have you read mice chat today
i believe they were trying to get a hold the nixon library i think they mentioned that they like
he really liked watching movies and they were really trying to get a hold of like the disney
nature movies to show in the white house sure he uh he's obviously a fascinating uh character uh and
i can see that being the greatest moment the greatest moment was the accords
nixon nixon uh-huh and figment and dreamfinder oh man this is throwing me for a loop i feel like
i'm gonna call an audible here and switch what i'm gonna say do you need a minute
well no i can i'll talk through it um dreamfinder dreamfinder talked him out of bombing the uh dykes
in vietnam cabodian really grant told him to bomb it and flood the areas oh man nixon disney dork
that feels like if we did more characters on this show that's like well all of a sudden like the
not like a knock at the door and we're like who is it oh richard nixon nixon too many characters
i'm glad this harmonica show still seems kind of ethereal and weird and not just character moments
that just say that tokyo disney's anniversary merchandise contains the return of final mission
for both just like i am not a crook always yes you yeah mike is doing it only with peace signs
which is the way to do it always peace signs up yeah they announced the 50th desserts these look
like some delicious treats the iridescent croissant donut it's got blue icing and sprinkles i don't
know a way to celebrate 50 magical years of dreams look clearly it's working for them but i don't
understand why they keep making the ears out of different colored walls uh chapek
i love that that's gonna be a recurring character i think bringing back capital punishments just for
by president's orders chapek straight to the chair
uh okay so there are many significant yeah moments that happen obviously uh the nixon stuff
john lennon signing the papers to dissolve the beetles at the polynesian saint is with may pang
as long one of his long weekends with away from yoko uh i guess i'm gonna steal away from that i
was also thinking i was gonna do maybe you know we mentioned earlier alan thick sings the christmas
song with the ninja turtles that was also cut from my an insane if we both thought it it's
got to be in content yeah we play this on our original christmas specials episode the alan
thick ninja turtles santa claus is coming to town rap it's crazy i really did almost think about
saying that and it's like that should be it too and it's like how do i stack up these important
moments with all these cultural figures so it's like maybe that a fourth in the pole like that's
the honorable mention is the alan thick i mean if maybe just by virtue of both of us thinking of
it because it is a hell of a yeah yeah but you know what i better watch out dude i'm talking
about your moves you better watch out freak out santa claus is coming to town that's a whole maybe
christmas second gate is that song i think sure i mean look if you i would love to just do uh all
the alan thick musical numbers i think that is also five that i'm so fond of i think maybe that's a
we call it ninja turtles and alan thick and it's a catch-all yes because there's there's a ninja
there's a ninja turtle christmas special that's oh with this with the what do we get splinter for
christmas yes and there's a couple other things too that are in the ninja turtle uh so the thick
and turtle catch-all is coming in the christmas season i think the thick and turtle connection
the big thick big turtle christmas a big thick turtle christmas is coming this christmas ever
so you know what i gotta say i'm gonna i'm gonna go on to all that important stuff all the all the
stuff happened i'm gonna declare the most important thing that happened in disney world is the
the video of my mother and i singing gregoria stephan song that is on youtube if you don't
know if you haven't heard the episode i talk about it they used to be able to make a music video
and uh there's a video of my mother and i in the year like 1990 and i am grabbing my crotch the
whole time because i am scared and i don't know the words two cameras on you the pressure two
cameras it's a beautiful 1980s-ish like background singing one two three four come on baby say you
love me five six seven time uh we'll repost this this is maybe the most i think this i wanted i
wanted to pick something personal yeah um and this is this is probably this is beating out another
great clip that we have not put up anywhere yet is that my sister and i dancing on the deck of the
pollination with these like light strands and i hit myself in the eye very hard with one of them
like i just knocked myself out of commission really hard and that's a great moment too but
it's not as iconic as me singing with my mother at age five grabbing my crotch the entire almost
almost the entire time yes is that disney mgm studios yes the spot of this yes it was at mgm
studios you were you could make your own music video and you'd pick the song and then uh you
could go in there i think they probably too was the limit of people i haven't seen a lot of other
people with this exact like video so i'm sure they're out there um but i have to pick it
personally and that's the most iconic thing for my life so yeah yeah post that and um ironically
as an adult grabbing your crotch makes you nervous but back then you would be nervous
and you would find comfort grabbing crotch wait wait say that again i know i've been trying to
think of it and i just didn't stick the landing on that wait what is it i was saying your crotch
business as an adult would make you incredibly nervous and sweaty and as a kid it would be a
source of comfort you're saying now if there was a video of me grabbing my crotch i would find it
indecent yeah it would just be a source of a video of that would be neurotic anxiety body video of an
adult man in his 30s grabbing his genitalia yeah well if it's in like if it's in the context of
like a hip-hop performance then it's fine but as far as like me at 37 because i'm afraid
i think i meant any crotch business in general like generating neuroses yeah no if i was off
by crotch business if it's the same video only i'm in my 30s with my mother grabbing my crotch yeah
that's weird you're right i agree with you yeah um okay so you're locking in your own my own
personal grades it's nixon it's mike carlson yeah his mother uh it's icons and that's sort
of what i was um well let me here let me frame it this way in my my highfalutin way we were
talking about the the founding of walt disney world and how it all comes from a great man
walt disney trying to create a hub of technology and innovation uh but thankfully uh you know
nearly halfway through the run through the 50 years a better man shows up by the name of
michael eisner and uh he has a more achievable dream because the other shit didn't happen he
didn't make the progress city but eisner thinks that it can be something else the disney world
can be a hub of the arts and that's what it became under his watch a place where architects can do
some of their their greatest masterworks and a place where uh performers and musicians even
can have a have a backdrop uh to play against and these things uh dovetail came together in a in a
beautiful way in the most beautiful way in the most important piece of art produced on the property
uh i am talking about uh with the backdrop of the yacht and beach resort hotel uh the uh mmc music
video for the song king of wishful thinking you know if you i you are you familiar with this one
this like pops up enough i feel like is like a disney world oddity or do either of you know what
i'm yeah you know the one that i'm i'm talking about uh so and i think some of our audience
might as well if you don't uh look it up look i'll play a second of it but it's not really going to
you know be anything because really you need the visuals you need to be in disney world but
nonetheless because i wanted you know i want to hear the song first of all the the original song
itself by the way king of wishful thinking by go west is a masterpiece uh so it's just nice to
hear it and nice to see the beautiful resort uh we meet our our hero and our musician uh blaine
so it's blaine from the mmc this is a song by blaine and uh blaine is waiting in a restaurant
uh that's also at the hotel presumably where people are wearing island casual clothes and
there's lots of like teal and turquoise curtains even though the mater d is like a fancy tuxedo man
right and he asks if anybody's anybody else is going to be joining you and he is sad because no
it's an empty chair um there's a line about cutting me to the bone and then his the guy's
reflection is in a knife uh i'm not sure where to pick it up i'm here i'll just i'll just do it
from here and see where we land or maybe like chorus number two well first of all here i'll
pick it up from here there's our there's our yacht and beach club lighthouse uh
beautiful instrumentation
there were at that uh uh that mgm studios thing where you're in the ship that's getting stormed
on they're using that uh-huh he's in a row boat out in that lake i don't know what that lake's called
uh blaine is killing it blaine's dynamic as hell yeah yeah that's not how it's gonna be
i'm really building to one moment mater d's checking it on him
me
mainly that that he's like he's in a boat in this thing uh and then the the boat the line is you've
made a hole in my heart and then the boat has a big sign that says my heart that's the name of the
bow and has a hole in it um later he he's the song is about him being a king and then there's a card
that comes up and he's he's the king he is the king of wishful thinking it is a happy ending
the girl of his dreams shows up at the end that's great and you get to see beautiful views of a
beautiful resort uh it's uh it's it's a hell of a jam and uh i i think it's a uh formative foundational
piece of art that was thanks to eisner being like a benefactor um you know like as with you know
george harrison financing the monty python movies of course yeah yeah he eisner set up a
playbox for great artists like blaine to play in and that's why my choice is blaine and the
rest of the mmc with king of wishful thinking look wow great that's great yeah um so and you know
we'll throw alan thick in there as well i don't want to split the votes but you know we might as
well so we got alan thick and ninja turtles we got blaine we got uh mike and his mom and we got
nixon and i think the it's mainly spread yeah yeah i think so but it's all icons and it's an
important place that brought golden greats to it throughout its first 50 years and here's hope and
for for a lot more uh i guess that's it make your choice on on twitter uh um and with that you
survived podcast the ride wdw 50 edition um next week things start getting a little spooky
haunt cast the fright is back oh yeah what spooky offerings will we bring to the table we'll find
out soon uh you can also as always uh find us on the socials at podcast the ride vote in that poll
merch is available in our t public store and for three bonus episodes every month check out podcast
the ride the second gate at patreon.com slash podcast the ride speaking of which uh there is
something else celebrating an anniversary on this exact date and we will be covering that over on
the second gate because they've like tried to they've done a lot of anniversary they try to open
things on october 1st as much as they can right and we can only do this episode on actual october
1st but there's more to come so just a little uh tease for that um and that's that uh any other
closing thoughts about this wonderful place uh i just want to know uh what nixon thinks of al
lutz and the controversy and that's what i'm wondering i don't think he was real
it was a sciop al lutz was a number of people operating former user name cia
and i also would like to my nixon to get away from mcgruff if you yeah yeah figure i figure out the
way to try to move it away um and speaking of icons visiting the park i think the the the best
way to go out this is something that i discovered on the 15th anniversary special where people are
wishing uh disney world at that point a happy 50th 15th birthday but why not a happy 50th as well
uh so let's close out here with a very special disney world birthday message from one of the
greats oj simpson
thanks juice thank you forever dog this has been a forever dog production executive produced by
mike carlson jason sharridan scott gairdner brett bohme joe cilio and alex ramsey for more
original podcasts please visit forever dog podcasts.com and subscribe to our shows on apple
podcasts spotify or wherever you get your podcasts keep up with the latest forever dog news by
following us on twitter and instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on facebook