Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast contains important updates fresh from Orlando, Florida.
You'll hear breaking news about slightly inconvenient marathon routes, new kinds of dessert moose,
the functionality of apps, and the relaxing lure of the bench outside of the hall of presidents.
It's Disney World Scoop with Cub Reporter Jason on today's podcast, The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride.
For an episode that will make you say, Jason had more treats than I would have, but less
than I expected him to.
I'm Jason Sheridan, joined as always by Mike Carlson.
Yes, I'm here.
I'm going to take a quick guess and don't tell me if I'm right because I want to be surprised
during the story because I don't know anything about this.
I'm going to guess you had an average of 1.5 treats a day.
I think that's about accurate.
Oh, is it?
All right, great.
But not evenly distributed.
Like some days, like maybe one.
One day it was six.
Yeah, something like that.
And one day you had like four salads that were healthy to offset it.
Yeah, yeah.
That doesn't sound right.
In Disney World?
I don't think so.
I'm just kidding.
It was for a comedy, Scott.
Scott Garner.
That's that's his voice.
Yeah, yeah.
OK, interesting.
So, yeah, some days retreat plentiful and some you just didn't have time.
You're rushing around.
There's so much to do.
Oh, yeah.
You had no you had no idea.
I'm still very sore.
So are you in theme park shape yet now or not?
Yeah, I am.
He is.
He made it.
By the grace of God and the fact that I walked, I clocked it 60.1 miles in one week.
I will say this.
We don't know anything about your trip, really.
I will say I clocked like a mood from you as you came in that you might be like still
tired from the trip, maybe irritated from the trip.
Am I correct?
Yes, but not from any of my traveling companions.
OK, that's but the trip itself was stressful to you in some ways.
The trip was wonderful.
This was folks.
I'm freshly back from Disney World.
As of Sunday, I was down there with family with my dad, my brother and Jane.
And we had a very nice time.
It is a little nuts down there right now.
It's a little wild.
Gotcha.
OK, so there was aspects that were stressful.
Yeah, totally out of our control, out of the front line cast members control as well.
They were all wonderful as always.
OK, the front line.
Front line cast members, we thank you for your service.
It's like a war zone at some point.
Gosh.
Oh, my God.
Did everybody come back with all their limbs?
I'm getting concerned now.
Well, oh, no.
Yeah, everyone did.
But I well, where to start?
I mean, yeah, I don't know.
I was down there for a week.
I was down there Sunday or just on Sunday to Saturday.
And a lot of stuff was going on down there.
There was a marathon the day we got there, which played a role that we did not,
a number of roles we did not foresee.
Did you accidentally find yourself in the marathon running it?
We accidentally found ourselves.
Jane and I got in on a red eye at five in the morning Orlando time.
I thought it was interesting that you did the red.
I remember you saying you were going to do that.
And like, I don't know, that doesn't that seems like something that would make
Jason Osegan irritable.
No, I actually you think that, but I actually sleep better
on the red eyes than sleeping like the six a.m.
to two a.m. or two p.m. on the East Coast.
OK, OK. So you did sleep.
Do you sleep on the plane?
I slept a little and then I was up for like 15 hours on two, three hours sleep.
And that was too ambitious.
Yeah. But we yeah, we were staying at the beach club and we got down there and
found out that, you know, the beach club, you can walk to the boardwalk on the one
side and then you can actually walk to the boardwalk on the other side of the
building, too. And both sides were coned off because there is a run dizzy marathon
going on. OK, so so yeah, to illustrate this, to re-illustrate this,
you're you're talking about the place where the Abra Kedab bar is in the former
Ample Hills. That's the boardwalk.
That's the boardwalk right by Epcot Center.
It's on the lake, which I'm blanking on the name Crescent Lake.
Thank you very much.
It's named something very boring and not Disney Crescent Lake.
Let's all learn it. It's by the Swann Adolphin, a little bit in the distance.
And normally you can easily get everywhere from a big loop of all the Epcot area
hotels and how you can walk to Hollywood Studios, too.
It's a little bit of a trek, but you can walk to it.
Right. So you're saying there were cones and runners preventing you from getting
to from what? Give me a point A to point B that was blocked off.
From like from the the pathway to the international gateway of Epcot.
OK, there's a little hill after the like as you leave the Beach Club,
you walk up a little hill that is coned off.
OK, so you can't get to International Gateway or just not get to the international.
So you can't enter Epcot Center.
But that turned out not to be a problem because Epcot didn't open until 10
or 11 anyway because of the marathon.
Oh, OK. And he had that.
You didn't check times when Epcot Center opened?
I checked times, but I like early early on, like I made park
reservations back in the summer.
And that was the other big thing.
That was a big point of contention in my family.
Like this park reservation system sucks ass because it's so like you can park
copy after 2 p.m.
But if you run into a thing where like, oh, this park is super crowded.
I think my dad said, oh, normally we would leave and go somewhere else.
But it's like, oh, we don't have the flexibility anymore.
Yeah, we don't have the flexibility.
So OK, so that first day, this is what you're describing the first day.
You had the expectation we're going to get up pretty early and go to Epcot Center.
Or we were going to go to Disney Springs.
Also didn't open until 10 or 11.
Right. So did so what happened was, did you what time did you get up
and what time were you?
You literally discovered that Epcot was not open by trying to walk to Epcot.
By trying to walk.
Well, no, we were just trying to walk to the board.
We were just trying to kill time because it's like 6 a.m. at this point.
You're just wandering around.
We're just wandering around.
Or very early in the morning. Very early.
What's there to do? Nothing's open then.
No, I mean, we had gotten coffee at the airport like we had coffee.
We had some breakfast.
And so we just thought we'd, you know, wander around.
And that was my mistake.
As we said, you know, on the Toy Story episode,
don't don't ruin your arm trying to play the practice games.
My knees started to hurt before we stepped into any part.
And been in a park.
Jason, the first two and a half days, my knees were just awful.
Both knees. Yeah, both knees.
What happened to the other one?
Because it started it started to take all the weight.
It started to do all the heavy lifting.
What about your lower back?
My lower back was actually fine all week.
And that was the other thing.
The third day I woke up in my right knee felt the most normal it has in 2021.
We're going to need to start doing like, you know, the news will do.
It used to be what what terror level alerts are we at?
And then it was it was covid and how much we're going to have to start.
Like on the Twitter, we need like a map of your body and where are the red zones?
Or it's just orange today.
Well, that's the thing after this week.
I feel terrific.
Now we're green. It's all green.
Great. Yeah. All right.
So listen right now, it's full green.
But last I don't want to alarm you, but last week, major areas of red.
Yeah. So, I mean, I still like did pretty long days at the parks.
I was just taking a lot of breaks and like pounding Tylenol.
And how many Tylenol?
How many Tylenol a day were you pounding?
Two to four. But it's like the eight hour.
It's like taking a handful of Tylenol.
It's for like arthritis and back pain.
Oh, gosh.
So wait, so you would have two to four, but they're extra strength.
Yeah. OK.
Are they big? Are they comically big pills or anything?
They're a little big.
Like a horse, a salt lick or something.
You're only supposed to take them like every eight hours.
So like, yeah, I think the max I would take them was like twice in a day.
And you're like an old like an old cop in a movie or at least like popping pills
to get through a shift.
I am. Conversely, my father, 68 in the best shape of his life.
You said that before. I thought about that.
I kept thinking about that after you said it the first time and how it's
you said like he walks 10,000 steps a day.
And I was like, I mean, the average that they recommend for any human being.
Yeah, I that's should be a pretty low bar.
I feel I'm happy he's in very good shape.
Not bad. Well, I don't know that.
Yeah, but I don't know that like a lot of people do that.
I don't know that. I think a lot.
I think a ton of people do 10,000.
That's like a very famous thing that like most people do.
I don't know that everybody gets that every day.
No, no, no. But it's a thing to aim for and it's by and I mean, it's not so insane.
Do right.
It's it's yeah, it's not.
I mean, if I look at mine, I probably only hit it once or a couple of times a week.
Yeah, I feel maybe I'm just saying because I said this because during
covid height, it was like what else in the world is there to do?
I feel like by getting those step counts is like this is the only activity
available to any human being.
You're just revealing to us that you do 10,000 steps every day.
Well, I was walking the you know, I'm walking the baby.
I mean, running around with him and taking him on to there's an update for the listeners.
My son is into turbines,
he which are the spinny things on the top of your house.
They look kind of like a chef's hat.
I think he likes it because it's on the top of Cookie Monster's food truck.
So I'll take him around and show him all the turbines that there are to see.
And this is, you know, I hate to compare.
I think he likes the turbine tours more than you could even like Disney World.
I think it's about the same.
Everyone is an E.
It's beyond an E ticket.
It's a what's a K ticket.
It's a P ticket.
That's great.
You told me he was in a turbines like two weeks ago and I was like,
oh, he's going to grow out of that fast.
I bet. But no, he's still he's still in.
It's a little on it's a little on the decline.
Now he's there's a new phase, which is I bought a bag of pebbles.
You might have passed on your way in.
It's in the yard. Oh, I didn't notice.
He picks up pebbles, moves them from one spot to another.
Now, watch out turbines.
Pebbles are hot on your tail.
Anyway, when I was little, I took a bunch of pebbles and threw them in my mouth
and tried to eat them.
Be careful. Whoa.
That's the story my mom tells where I'm like, I take my little child hand
and just shove it in my mouth.
Wow. Yep.
Is she at all worried with the new Ghostbusters film coming out
that you might get some new ideas about where to put some Ghostbusters
and what kind of sheets to give?
Oh, that's a good question.
Is she worried all over again?
Is she worried that I've bought the new Hasbro Plasma series
Ghostbusters figures and I have Trevor and podcast
the characters from the new movie Ghostbusters Afterlife and that I've used
napkins or paper towels to make them a little bit.
She hasn't mentioned it.
But look, there's been advances.
There's better thread counts and there's more, you know, crimping
in paper towels here and there than then when you were a child.
But basically the same materials, you could burn up Trevor
just as easily as you could burn up P gone.
Good point. You know, you're bringing up a lot of
Trevor's essentially the same as Spengler, right?
I can tell you I'm going to I'm going to get I'm going to get, you know,
in so much trouble, but I will.
But I'm going to do is I'm going to get like really cheap toilet paper and do it
like the flimsiest, most flammable toilet paper and rap podcast
the character from afterlife in that toilet paper and then pretend
he's sleeping a little bed.
And that's my rebellion.
I feel bad. I feel a little bad for podcasts, not getting the
the level of thread count that your friends from the 80s got.
Yeah, the cartoon podcast.
Yeah. Sorry, podcast.
You're part of my mid to late 30s rebellion.
Whatever you want to call.
Flimsier, possibly more flammable.
Yeah, possibly.
If there are still many steps removed to actually being a flammable problem.
Good point.
She hasn't brought it up, though.
We'll see. Be careful.
Let's all be careful.
Anyway, that was that came off of walking.
I carry my kid around to see turbines walking your dad.
Where were we?
You're so he walks a lot.
Yeah. Your knees are in.
Are shot already. It's day one.
It's six a.m. You're wandering.
You can't even get to the front of Epcot and your knees are shot.
Yeah. So I as the week went on, I learned like, oh, it's not
it wasn't the like quantity of walk.
It was the uninterrupted walk.
I could walk a lot all day long.
I just had to take some breaks.
I just had to like stretch when we were in line.
I had to sit down and that sort of thing.
And that was helpful to learn.
I'm seeing a new physical therapist who's a lot more on the ball.
OK, encouraging me to track these sorts of things.
Was he saying did he give you any tips before?
Like, you know, do missions, stretch while you're on mission space?
Because like you're going to go.
I told him I was going down and he's like, is that Disneyland?
I'm like, I don't really want to get.
I feel like I feel like Mr. Physical Therapist.
This is work for me. This is work.
Don't make me do it.
Vacation, you know.
Yeah, no, I did.
He gave me a lacrosse ball and a resistance band
because he's doing a lot of foam roller kind of stuff.
Lacrosse ball kind of serves the same purpose, but easier to pack in a suitcase.
I got to go to a physical therapist for my Achilles tendons.
So I mean, I'll give you the info.
OK, let's see if it covers my insurance covers it.
You all shouldn't make fun of me for walking.
Look at me here.
Hey, I've been playing highly competitive tennis all summer.
You know, I'm trying to stay fit.
I think you mentioned that.
Yeah, maybe I did.
I think and I think I do how you blow out your Achilles tendon.
Andre Gregory and I were playing tennis.
Up at his cottage.
Perez walked up to compliment you and Andre on your tennis.
That's correct.
You said, sir, you'd be interested maybe in hearing about a certain plane.
A certain plane.
And he said, that's a wonderful.
Andre said, it's a wonderful plane.
Anyway, the debut of the Andre Gregory.
It's wonderful.
There's arm gestures with it.
The little gesture is more.
Let me just tell you, it's more about it.
Perfectly Andre Gregory.
Yes, I guess.
I've never seen this man.
Yes.
OK, anyway.
So, yeah. So, yeah, my knees like loosened up as the week went on.
And and then just kind of fell into the like normal, like
we get theme parks kind of fatigue.
Yeah. So you so that was good.
So that turned out to be the normal fatigue.
Yeah. So there is still an error that you like.
Mike's initial question was, are you coming in?
You're coming in a little irritated.
And a lot of the things you've said have confirmed Mike's suspicion.
Yeah. I mean, I came from I had physical therapy a few hours ago
and I feel like I got my ass kicked.
So that might be causing the irritation.
Was it because you had to explain Disneyland versus Disney World to the therapist?
No, that's all right.
No, he gets it at this point.
It's the tall castle.
I don't know. I don't want to do this.
And you, it was gray.
They're both pink now.
Don't get me started.
It's the 50th, 50th goal.
That's why there's the gold Dumbo in front of Dumbo.
That's why there's all these weird golden idols everywhere.
Yeah. Yeah.
The 50th was going on.
I don't I don't know what they decide some limited food items.
And the, you know, the space
where Earthlights looked terrific in person.
The Tower of Terror, like lit up in like its glory as it was.
You know, the hotel looked great.
The castle looked fine.
I knew Hots Tower, Knots, Gassel.
Is Tower of Terror a new lighting package?
It's got the because they're like they're projecting.
They're projecting.
Oh, is that the icon?
All the weenies get a projection.
Got it.
The gold, it's the golden icon celebration.
Right. I don't know.
There was a real there was an official name for it
that we said on the show like six weeks ago, and none of us remember it.
That left real quick.
Yeah. Yeah. Yes.
OK, well, I guess I like that.
So that's a castle like shit and the other ones look good.
Yeah. Yeah. I didn't see the tree of light.
Yes. Yeah.
I don't know. It was fine.
I saw like a little bit of that new like the fireworks show at Magic Kingdom
that everyone was complaining when that premiered. Right.
Right. Why? Huh?
What happened? Why was I?
I just think like people really liked the previous one.
And this one just happily ever after was the previous one or no.
Well, Wishes was like two or three.
Wishes is a forever.
It was forever ago. Yeah.
Happily ever after.
Believe, believe you're in chance.
It was believe you're in chance.
The celebration of your beliefs.
That that show was fine.
But my I'm going to this is the first of a few hot takes.
Let's hear it. I liked Harmonious.
Oh, the Epcot show.
Right. The new Epcot.
And that's the one that people were really cranky about.
And people seemed cranky about it.
Jane legitimately moved by it both times.
We saw it because there's three hunchback songs in it.
Is that hunchback heavy?
And they're like very nice arrangements.
And it's it's still pretty like abstract and ethereal.
Like there's there's a bunch of stuff.
There's there's a Latin that some countries kind of like one to one.
Like hunchback is France.
Coco is Mexico.
Then it starts to break down and it's like, well, there's Lion King in here.
And there is it's still the Africa refreshments next day.
Or like, oh, Aladdin.
Here's a song from Aladdin.
For Canada. Yeah, I.
Do they play the John Resnick song from Treasure Planet?
I'm sorry, Michael.
We didn't. Or the Jennifer Love Hewitt song from Hunchback 2.
Did they do that either? No.
No. Can I ask you that I
sorry, listeners, the sorry, certain type of listener.
What's the show? I don't know what.
I know that there's big barges that people don't like in World Showcase.
And it's like illuminations where they light up all the World Showcase
provisions. But beyond that, what's different about it?
I mean, it's still kind of got like
a message of we're all one people sort of thing.
It's like, like, what is but what physically is it?
Is that like the the barges and the like squid
arms that move?
Yeah. These big arms that come out of the water and they they shoot water
fountains and they shoot fireworks.
One of them like rapid fire shoots fireworks.
This what I really liked about it.
I thought the music was pretty good.
There's so much pyro like they shoot pyro over you.
Like you were surrounded by fireworks and so much go off throughout the show.
I was like, oh, this is awesome.
Like, OK. Yeah, I just thought an improvement in on whatever was
was it still a limit?
Is that got forever?
Ever was after illuminations.
Yeah. I've got forever.
We saw when we were down there a couple of years ago.
Yeah, it kind of sucked.
Yeah. The one time I saw it, I think I was standing with you.
We were it was so smoky.
Like we were by one of the like explosion.
Well, we were we were passing a joint back and forth.
Oh, yeah. We're. Yep.
I could have called that.
I know how you guys roll all that talk of what kind of pill was Jason popping.
Fucking time.
Oh, man. Where do I get that?
Is that like this?
Like, do I need a dealer for that?
Take a leave when you go to bed and when you wake up,
takes them from your Nana's house.
Oh, geez. You guys, I've been living.
I've been you know what I've been doing.
I've been taking extra strength melatonin and biting it in the middle.
So I only get half. Oh, wow.
Yeah, that's how Scottie's been rolling these days.
I've been doing a little of that, too. I'll be honest.
I've been that's it's own podcast.
The pill boy pill boy.
Gummy boy.
It's the chalky.
It's not the fun kind.
Just the, you know, chalky tasteless.
I have a theory why you liked the Upkot show with all the pyro
because you felt cozy and warm because of all the heat.
Well, I guess it was a little heat.
I just they I thought there was just some very unique like fire.
Like I'm I don't I feel like I don't have a palette for like I like fireworks.
But I don't do people are like shows good.
This shows bad.
Like, yeah, I don't I don't know.
I don't know art, but I know what I like.
And I like this one.
I always like the illuminations. Yeah.
But yeah, no, I thought this one was good.
The barges, too.
They put the 50th logo on them, like on screens during the day.
So they looked a lot less like imposing like 2001
monoliths in the middle of the lake.
Not scary industrial equipment.
As I said, when I went down there, there were people on my trip
who pointed at those and said, what ride is that?
That is not a ride.
That is a not functioning yet light show.
Yeah.
These squid arms sound cool.
I know I like the squid.
Yeah, they were shooting water around.
They were shooting fireworks like, yeah, I thought it was cool.
Yeah. Well, you're one of the first people in theme park media
that has given us a good review, I feel like.
Yeah, I guess I just enjoyed it.
I mean, I was with someone who was like tearing up,
like when the Hunchback Q started. Right.
Take it back.
But she was very sincerely into it.
I was like, well, great. It's working.
It worked for someone.
It worked for one person, at least.
And it gets through to just one guest.
It got through to one guest and I enjoyed it too.
So you got to.
Well, call me when I'm not here or I'm still here.
John Resnick song is playing in Epcot.
I'll be I'll be moved as well.
Well, that's good.
I mean, so so that was a nice surprise.
It sounds like. Yeah, it was a nice surprise.
Less nice surprise.
The crowds are back.
The holiday crowds are here.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
And I think when we we initially had this booked for
same week in November 2020,
and we pretty quickly canceled it in like April of 2020 or May of 2020.
And early November, we had gone down
like when I was elementary school and it was very different
Disney World at the time, and it was pretty deserted.
But early November, often still a slow season.
Usually, usually, I think we would have hit less crowds
if it had been the week before.
But who's to say it seemed like all the crowd predictions were like
this time of year, it's not going to be too crowded.
And then as it got closer, every blog I was reading was like,
maybe a little crowded this week.
And and anyone we talked to a few people who live down there.
And they're like, yeah, there's a lot of people here this week.
Right. Like that was the conversation
we kept having the marathon crowds
that first night at Epcot.
It was so crowded and the crowd was getting sloppy and sloppy drunk.
I seemingly just rowdy and wow.
These marathon scumbags.
So wait, the people the people watching the marathoners
know doing the marathon because we're drunk.
Well, because between 10 p.m.
and midnight, they get Epcot to themselves.
That night.
So like around nine p.m., like people are already like
they had going all day.
So they had a lot. It's going right to their head.
So they're they're they're all having major ego trips.
So they know they're getting hammered all day.
They ran and ended at like 11 a.m.
OK, so they've been drinking around the world all day
and they have free rein and Epcot to do with whatever they want.
They're allowed to do whatever it's like a purge and Epcot for them.
I guess those two hours. Yeah.
They can have sex on its face.
You've heard they can do whatever they want.
I'm in it on and on top. Sure.
They're very athletic.
They could run up the side.
They're so fast, like Sonic the Hedgehog running up a structure.
Oh, yeah. God. Yeah.
So these zombies, you got to watch out for these guys.
Yeah. So swim across the lake and by the end of the neck.
Did you do they have the numbers on still so you could identify like,
oh, there's no no, I think they might have had wristbands or something.
But like, no, I don't think you could knock them out.
Wait a minute. But when were they?
OK, they have got to themselves.
But where are you? Where are they annoying you?
Because they're if you're not in Epcot, they're already like,
well, no, the marathon was going on in the morning
and then just threw out the day at Epcot.
It was so packed because they were just like stuck around
or came back for like the marathon, you know, exclusive party.
OK, so it was just packed.
And we went back to Epcot later in the week.
A second day and it was it was so crowded.
There was a line to get in the Mexico Pavilion, which I had never seen before.
That's what it was over the summer for sure.
What's that? Definitely that way over the summer.
Was it? Yeah, I think that's saying it's been that way.
With like wraparound. Yeah.
We had like a lunch reservation and we got to get inside.
And yeah, it was it was my brother had gone on ahead to check in.
And he's like, oh, I saw a cast member and they let me in the side
or like they they were like, oh, you can just cut through that door
if you have a reservation.
Oh, OK. Yeah.
That was that was the only time where,
you know, I didn't really feel like covid skittish.
But like that pavilion with those crowds was a little like this.
This ride, relaxing ride next to the rest
next to the restaurant we were eating in that restaurant.
This whole vibe is usually a little more chill
this like shoulder to shoulder.
Sure. Yeah. Well, and also, I think everybody still is like adjusting to
the certain things and level of crowds that, you know, a lot of us haven't done,
even though things have been reopened.
So, yeah, I'm sure it'll like it'll, you know, mess.
Yeah, I feel like I definitely had that when I was there
over the summer, just like, boy, I haven't been in a crowd like this
in a room like this and a lot of that.
Well, better get extremely drunk.
That'll that'll be my way of not thinking about this.
It was good exposure therapy.
I'll say that, like just getting thrown into it.
And like it was very easy to fall back in Disney World routines.
People pretty good about the masking indoors.
Usually some walked in without a man.
They they, you know, people are telling, hey, please put that on.
And usually it was just someone being like, oh, God, I forgot. So sorry.
OK, you know, defiance, not defiance.
Other than these marathoners, other than the marathoners.
Fucking I don't know.
Deviant sickos.
I don't know who the rest of the sickos were the rest of the week. But like
wait, can I get a quick question?
I don't know. I'm sure you would tell us you did it.
But Scott, I believe in this pavilion you had black ant salt.
Is that right? I bought it outside.
That's the pathway and then there's the one closer to the lake.
Yeah. Yeah.
Salt with actual black ants ground up in it, which I talked about on the Patreon.
Yes, I've been thinking about this because we just bought the dog
treats made out of crickets. Oh, OK.
So that makes sense.
It seems like the thing a dog would want to eat.
And then there's the nutrition. Yeah. Of it.
You haven't thought about lining a drink with it.
I haven't thought about it.
But I did. I did say to Lindsay when she was like, oh, yeah, they have like cricket food.
I mean, we all Scott eight ants. Yeah.
But without realize, I really thought it was a theme.
It's like interesting black ant.
And I guess the theme of this salt also is that it tastes terrible.
So is it so thick?
And like I pointed out, I ended up with like a unibrow of like I drank it
in such a way that like black ant salt connected my eyebrows.
Looked like Bert.
So you did not have any salt.
I did not have the answer.
No, honestly, I had forgotten about the answer until this very moment.
Well, do you want some of Edwin's trick cricket treats?
If it's human grade, I'd give it a shot.
I got to check the package.
I don't know if I've ever eaten cricket.
I think they've got like a lot of different like insect things in that Mexico pavilion.
I think you can get in that tequila bar.
If you pay like a bunch of money, you can get like crazy drinks
and like some different bugs.
Yeah. The whole spread things.
But a bug drink.
I think I could totally be wrong, but I'm pretty sure Mr.
Morrow did a YouTube on this.
I see. Paging Mr.
Morrow, and I think he got to like sample tequilas, and then they had different
like bugs as well.
They have them were any of them alive and then flew into his pocket.
Not on this episode, which that would have been amazing
if one had turned out to be alive.
Didn't it happen again?
I heard it. Yes, it did happen again.
I forgot which episode.
We have a second Mr.
Morrow bee pocket. Yes.
Incident. Did you see Mr.
Morrow? I didn't see.
We were all looking out for like Mr.
Morrow or or any of the many professional wrestlers who went into Orlando area.
Half of them do.
I love the parks.
No, we saw I got recognized a couple of times.
Shane and Soren.
Very, very good.
Shane was working at Soren.
We did the Deluxe Hotel guests.
We got out, got 10 to midnight another day of the week.
And that was awesome because then the park was empty.
Yeah. Oh, good.
There were no dirty runners around.
No dirty runners.
No, just one.
Who are they kidding?
Just one 36 year old man limping.
But you forget how big Epcot is.
Halfway around, I think we clocked it.
Limping. I'll get to it.
But yeah, we're still on day one.
Stats. I'm jumping around.
Yeah, Shane from Soren.
He was working Soren during that.
Hello, Shane.
Garret's event.
Thank you for taking care of Jason and taking him on a thrilling adventure
over the different parts of the world.
A cast member at Runaway Railway who popped out of a side door
asked me if I had a podcast and I said, hi, how do you do it?
We talked for a second and then he disappeared as quickly as he
appeared the first time.
I didn't catch his name.
I unfortunately missed.
It wasn't goofy. I wish it was.
What's wrong with your knee, Jason?
I walked through Pizzeria Rizzo.
I've seen Pizzeria Rizzo now.
It does look very cool.
I missed Malia.
They were not working.
They were at Epcot or not Epcot.
They were they were working at another park.
What I I messaged them to see if they were around.
There's a very there's a very supportive listener and fan of the show.
Works at Pizza Rizzo, which is the Muppet themed restaurant in Disney.
So it's been been debate about whether Pizza Rizzo is good.
Would you say Pizza Rizzo is good?
Oh, I didn't need it. I mean, I walked around.
Yeah.
Had a Mama Melrose reservation, a Sheridan family favorite.
Next time I'm in Disney, I will I will eat it.
Yeah, I'll try it next time.
And then we'll do an episode.
Hmm. I think we should settle this hash.
Yeah, we should finally settle that debate.
So you had mama.
You had Mama Melrose.
Mama Melrose. That was good.
And you've had that. Is that a regular tradition?
That is a regular tradition pretty much since I was like a child.
Really? You feel like? Yeah.
And is it a say you get a different thing each time?
Or is there a thing you've been ordering?
Yeah, I feel like the menu has gotten pretty paired.
A lot of the restaurants had kind of smaller menus right now are kind of paired down.
OK, so what did you get there?
Chicken Parmesan. OK.
Do they have pizza? They have pizza.
Pizzas. Yeah.
I've actually never been there.
So Mama Melrose, you've been maybe when I was a kid.
Yeah, I don't think we did.
We went to the bron.
Lindsay, I went to Brown Derby now, like a couple of years ago.
I forgot I was trying to get in last time I was there.
And then some runner came by, pushed me down, made me drink water from the from a puddle.
It was such a flash. I don't even know.
Then I looked up the sun number.
Watch out for runners, folks.
So so wait. So, yeah, you're I know you're jumping around here.
So this is Hollywood Studios.
Is that the second day?
So the first full day. Yeah.
That my my my idea was that like my my dad and brother hadn't seen
Star Wars yet.
It's the galaxy's edge. The galaxy's edge.
They hadn't seen it at all.
So I was like, OK, we'll get up early.
Resort guests get in to the park half an hour early.
Yeah. And so I was like, all right, we'll just go back and stand by.
Rise of the Resistance. It won't be that bad that early.
Right. Two things happened.
One, I forgot there are thirty six thousand roughly hotel rooms on Disney property.
Oh, right. Yes.
So the crowds at eight thirty, eight forty in the morning were already like
pretty substantial to get in that park.
I think as we were going the turnstile, I looked
Rise of the Resistance had like a 70 minute wait.
It's like, OK, there's no virtual queue in here.
Well, there's no virtual queue. Right. Which sucks.
Because what happened within like the time it took us to get in the front gate
and get towards Star Wars, it broke down.
Yeah, of course. Yeah.
The breakdowns are so bad on this thing that it breaks down.
And every time we would look, it's like, all right, should we try?
OK, it's it's broken down again.
And so by that point, by the time it was up and running,
it was already like 90 minutes or two hours.
Yeah. And all the individual lightning lanes were gone.
So we tried to buy a lightning lane for it two days later.
Two or three days later.
And the lightning lane is what just in case anybody doesn't know.
That's the new version of Fastpass for e-tickets.
High. The big rides where you have to pay an extra what?
Five, ten, fifteen, twenty dollars.
You'll tell us in a second. What's the price?
It was.
Per ride.
So you now piecemeal have to purchase right.
That of a free thing, let you cut lines before. Right.
Jeannie, you individually.
And there's two things.
Jeannie Plus is just for like the mid level rides.
Rides that are mid, they say.
That's what the kids say.
But high level rides like Rides of the Resistance,
you have to pay an additional fee per ride.
And really quick, when this when we're starting, Mike,
you asked us to test the microphones, just to make sure your levels are OK.
Jason's test of his microphone was, yes, yes, lightning lane.
And I shuddered like, oh, right.
This we have to talk about this now.
I he's in a lot to say.
So I'll jump all the way to the last day we were there.
Yeah, we bought a lightning lane for seven doors, mine train.
OK, am because that I've never I've been now to Disney World
twice when that's been open.
I've never even been in the ballpark of being able to do that ride.
So it is really oddly bonkers.
Yeah. Or I'm just there.
There's just I just have other priorities and I don't have the two hours to do it.
Yeah. And it.
Very long wait.
It is fun. It's more fun than you think.
But it's not worth that wait.
OK, it was worth, you know, I think we just wanted to do it.
We had the time.
So my dad, like I showed him how to do it.
And he got up, had no trouble buying it at 7 a.m.
for like a 10 or 1030 return time.
Mm hmm. Like for the day before, I was up at 7 a.m.
to try to buy Rise of the Resistance Lightning Lane.
It showed me 9 a.m.
I didn't think we'd get there in time, but I hit it anyway.
When it refreshed or like took me to the next page and said,
did you mean two o'clock?
And I was like, I didn't mean to know.
Let me refresh it again.
It's like, ah, you wanted to buy five o'clock.
And I'm like, oh, my God.
Like so by 705, the resort guests access ones were gone.
I tried again at 9 a.m. and just nothing.
I just couldn't get anything.
Now, does it? So does it say what price or you never even got to that part?
It was about $15 per person.
They changed. So there's not a price that they give to all of these.
So on the right, it's like the universal thing.
It's the plane ticket.
That's what I was saying a couple of weeks ago, or it's like it,
depending on how popular things are.
We are getting into health insurance territory.
That's where all this is going, where it's like dense systems
you have to learn. Oh, right. Right. Right.
Expenses impenetrable.
What's that? Why did that go up?
And Scott, you're preaching to the choir because by day two, I was like,
I hate that. Like, this is driving me insane.
And I think I'm pretty reasonably knowledgeable about this stuff.
Pretty reasonably. Yeah.
Well, I loved the detail that Jane, your girlfriend,
that declared that you have been talking about this too much
when we were out at a party.
I needed like, please, can we talk about something that is not Jeannie?
I yeah, she probably thought I was talking about it.
Too much there.
Well, I'll say, OK, so that's the lightning
blade kind of a crapshoot for that.
So they're they'll probably come out to visit
in next year or the year at some point.
I was like, we'll just do it in an hour.
Like a lot of stuff we just ran out of time on.
I'm like, whenever you come, we have it in Anaheim.
We'll just do it there.
Would you pay for Mind Train, then?
I think that one was about $11 a head.
And it's it's they go to these obscure amounts like.
All right. So Big Thunder today is 1290.
Like this is this is crazy. The stock market.
It's trying. Yeah, it is a stock. It is. Yeah.
But something was only seven.
Maybe it was a runaway railway.
I'll say that that first time.
So the first full day when rise went down, we did stand by for runaway railway.
And that was a pretty smooth wait.
I think it was posted like we might have waited 50 minutes.
It was posted 60 or something like that.
The wait times kind of all over the map.
Some very inflated, some right on accurate.
I had also paid the 17, 18 dollar annual price for the touring plans.
Like right. Wait time app, which shows you like this is what's posted.
You'll probably wait close to this.
That was usually pretty accurate, too.
And their crowd calendars.
Were also accurate.
I just didn't know a six out of ten meant like, stay the fuck away from this park.
Sure. So so so touring plans, which
they'll have a do they have they have like people in the park that are guessing
or not guessing that are actually they're just going through and clocking it.
And then they also have like users submit it times. Right.
So they're giving you the real shit.
So they're giving you the real time.
It's like having a man on the inside. Exactly.
The corporation's not lying to you. Right.
Yeah. Len is like deep throat.
One test is touring planes. He's given you the real shit.
But so the first day we rode that, it was fine.
The second time we met went back to Hollywood Studios.
It was we we were just all so tired.
Like we waited an hour for Tower of Terror.
And that was a bad sign with Tower of Terror and Rock and Rollercoaster.
We're both an hour.
And it's like these never like it's really crowded.
These are pretty old rides at this point.
You know, sure. Sure. But this is all I feel like I was there in the summer.
It was all everything was north of this.
You're saying in November you were not expecting this.
I kind of wasn't expecting it.
My family has often gone in the hottest part of summer
because they usually have like they're
no one wants to go to Orlando with that temperature.
Sure. Sure. So but we do. We're used to it.
So this was this was a change of pace for us.
We want to see it all decorated for Christmas. But
so you you were correct.
You would warn me the extended queue for Runaway Railway is brutal.
It's the cement outside.
So it's boring.
And that so that was Friday.
We did that. And that was like my brother tapped out.
He was like, I'm not he's like, I'm just going to walk around the park
and then just maybe ride something, maybe go back to the hotel.
Jane, by Friday, she she fell into
I guess my family goes pretty hard.
I guess we do pretty long days.
But by Friday, he was like, I don't want to be rude.
I want to go to the pool.
And she was. Yeah.
So I was standing in this little miserable, like cute like my
did it solo. I know I did.
I did do it with my dad.
Your dad at least said company.
And and my that was the only time I lower back started to her
was just standing on the concrete.
And then while Jane is texting, I'm going to the lazy river.
I'm doing the water side and storm along Bay.
I'm going to take a bubble bath.
And it's like she made the right call and did it.
This is a lot of this has been occurring to me throughout this episode.
Really, anytime anybody goes, I love going.
I spend I do this podcast.
I spend the whole year thinking about Disney World and watching Disney
World videos. Yeah.
But there is something about I this this is not a relaxing place to go.
I don't know if it ever was really.
But now today with your lightnings and your genies,
yeah, your COVID protocols and your book at 90 days in advance.
I it's all so like you have to be like Jane and just declare this is relaxed.
I will carve relax time out of it.
No, and it took her a couple of days to she she was like her family vacations
were that she'd be like, it'd be so it would have been rude growing up if like
I had split off from my family and my families were like,
yeah, if you want to go get a coffee, by all means, just meet up with us later.
Or like, you know, oh, if you want to go back to that's fine.
Yeah, go have some rest.
So she felt like she couldn't say it.
She couldn't say it from six when she was wandering around at six a.m.
and didn't get to go to the get to go to bed.
Yeah. Probably wanted to be like, can I go to bed? Yeah.
And I was I thought I was slowing down too, because I was like, yeah, my
I cannot clearly go as hard right now with my knees.
Can I OK, so you were saying by the end of the trip, your knees were better. Yeah.
Is it because we've talked about this much like Superman gets his power
from Earth, Yellow Sun.
We've talked about before where Jason has never as more energy
that we've ever seen, like when he's on Orlando, he is the most energy
you ever see him.
So were you actually be charged by the humidity and the certain air
conditioning smell and all the rides? It just took a couple of days.
I think it was probably that.
And just like after like so much time at home after two years, you know,
like there was a number of factors. Sure.
So all of that combined to heal you. Yeah.
OK, that's good.
Here's my other take.
I don't think this one will be disputed, though.
I run away. Railway rocks. Yeah. Yeah.
We obviously I do the episode, but Mike, I guess you got to do it first.
Of course I will.
That'll be a glowing episode, I think, unless we're now putting you in a corner.
But I I don't know.
It's one of those two that you like it never sounded
obviously never sounded bad to me.
I feel like I read a synopsis of it and went like, oh, sounds nice.
And I was like, when you set the bar at like pretty good,
I think it's better than pretty good.
It's sort of like I was shocked how much I loved it.
I think it's a fantastic.
I was too. There were so many neat little tricks.
There were so many fun moments.
I mean, Rise of the Resistance is its own sort of blockbuster production.
But this one was just kind of more fun,
but also has a lot of technology and and cool stuff.
Yeah, it still gives you I think it's cool that families and kids
can have an attraction that's less scary, but that still has what rise has,
which is like a ride can do this, this and like I got on this
and I thought it was this kind of ride and then this happened and that happened.
It's just cool. There's like a friendly one of those two.
Yeah. And so and so the other newish ride
a ratatouille.
Oh, yeah. I I I liked it.
I like the vibe.
It's kind of where I was at with it.
I really like the vibe.
I liked a lot of the theater tricks.
I like I like the size tricks like going under the stove and stuff like that.
But I rode Runaway Railway first, and then I rode this.
A few days later, I rode the clone of a ride built in 2012 or 2013.
You know what I mean?
Like it always if I had done Ratatouille and then Runaway Railway,
I think I would have thought highly of it.
Yeah, I think.
Yeah, I don't want to like play down Ratatouille.
But from my experience doing it in Paris,
it's like, I don't know, having I think it's
you're doing it post Runaway Railway or post Rise.
It's just it doesn't top, though.
You just have to expect that it's you.
You can't expect it to top those in terms of trackless rides.
And I don't think it really gives you the thrill of those.
It's neat. It's interesting.
It's worth going on.
But I might venture to say it is the lesser of the track,
the Disney trackless rides.
I didn't get to do Pooh's Honey Hunt, but that seems pretty spectacular.
Mystic Manor have not done, but obviously that's an incredible ride.
Beauty and the Beast looks pretty amazing.
Like, I don't know. I think Ratatouille is pulling up the rear, unfortunately.
I'll say the the extension of the France Pavilion is very charming.
Oh, that's that was when we when we did finally get into Epcot Center
on that first like half day.
I guess it ended up being a full day for me inadvertently.
The very first thing we went back there and got like crepes and hard cider.
And like that was nice.
That was nice after sitting around on the beach.
At in the cold, waiting for the marathon.
Yeah, it was right there.
Now, imagine Remy having to run around with a bunch in the middle of a marathon.
They would pay no heed to the genius rat of our times.
They'd stomp on his brains if they had to.
Yeah, they didn't have to. Right.
They would point him out and they go, everyone run over there.
That's what they would do.
Willingly get a lower score. Yeah.
Low score.
Get a worse time in the marathon so that you can stomp on a rat instead.
Right. Hey, we did get to use what there was a Alice in Wonderland
photo spot by the the Boardwalk Hotel that was set up for the marathon.
And we definitely got to take advantage of it for the movies.
No, the the original movie.
Oh, OK.
Oh, then who cares?
Cartoons. That's not my Alice, man.
I want to trip out with the M.H. himself.
You want to go in through the looking glass with the M.H.
He's now known on this podcast.
Yeah. Yeah. Good old M.H.
with the brilliant original Johnny Depp voice.
That's right.
The same voice ever.
He we must protect this man at all costs.
I keep I keep getting talent.
If you scroll like Instagram, like like, I don't even know what you.
Sometimes you scroll like Instagram stories or something.
You get stuff that like is just recommended to you.
The amount of times I get a close up video of Johnny Depp playing
in the Hollywood vampires on Instagram, two or three a day, I feel like.
I'm not getting that one.
Sometimes a duplicate.
It's the it's I'll tell you what's causing this.
It's Mike saying bad boys of Boston so often.
That's part of it.
Phone is like, I know, I know what it like.
Joe Perry, Johnny Depp playing guitar.
Well, Joe Perry's in the band.
He's one I thought he was one of the OK.
He's one of the three more Hollywood vampires are Cooper three.
The big three, the Trinity, the Holy Trinity,
Burr, M.H., Cooper, M.H. and bad and bad boy B.
So, yeah, I get like Johnny Depp with like ten scarves hanging out of his pocket,
like with the guitar strap real low.
And he's just like playing some blues.
I get videos of that almost every day.
If I start scrolling, it might be YouTube gives that to me, too.
At some point with all those scarves, he's asking for an accident.
If there is like a wet stage for any reason, somebody spilled a beer
or something or Joe Perry's sweat all over the stage and the wrong
the scarf goes into an amp or like Depp is going to get electrocuted
doing one of these shows.
He should not have that much dangling off of him while handling an electric
implement. And then these Twitters are going to go saying that it was cancel
culture that killed him.
It wasn't it was the scarves playing guitar.
It was the scarves. Yeah.
And you'll get a video recommended to you of it happening gritty as it may be.
So you can prove that that's how M.H. died.
Michael, I'm sorry to disappoint you.
I did not get a chance to see the bad boy.
That was my next question.
And I knew it. I could feel it.
I could feel it that you didn't get to go see Aerosmith.
I didn't go see Aerosmith.
They were I think they'll be around for a while.
They were refurbishing the big guitar.
I saw that the big guitar was being refurbished.
They're putting in they're investing money.
Are they still playing the song pink outside of the ride?
I couldn't really tell. I tried to ride it once.
It had a 60, 70 minute wait.
I looked I had looked up.
There is usually a single rider.
I walked up and I said, can I do single rider?
And they said, no, it's so long.
Single rider would actually be longer than the regular line right now.
Oh, my gosh. That's great.
I mean, look, it's very popular.
I would do it again.
It's better than Tower of Terror.
And I would do it.
Excuse me. I would do it.
Over Tower of Terror any day.
So I get that. That's all I'm saying.
I think that was a take that wasn't in the episode we did about it.
I think you're so bad boys of Boston drunk now that you're like
you've notched it up year by year on the show.
It is a very good.
It's great. I like it. It is great.
I'm not sure Aerosmith is the reason I like.
Although I don't know.
I mean, that pre show is pre show is so fantastic.
Yeah. Yeah. And the ride is great.
Hey, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Hey, wait, wait a sec.
But we'll get to our fans like that.
Well, we do we care.
We're band cares about our fans. Yeah.
Yeah, that's right.
Oh, we got going to take it with all this me.
And they're stuck in the like, don't want to miss a thing.
Armageddon like era forever,
like they're that version of the band forever. Mm hmm.
Aren't they mixing? They're mixing.
They're mixing walk this way for some reason.
Now they have this way. Three.
Well, yeah, right. The third version of Walk This Way.
Wait fourth, because if you count the Super Bowl one with Brittany and in sync.
But is that later? Nelly.
Or is it the same year?
Yeah, it was Nelly, was it?
Oh, that might have been after. Oh, you're right.
OK, so if you're tracking the Walk This Way
sequels, three is rock and roller coaster remix.
Four is Super Bowl with Nelly.
Exactly. Yes. So.
Wait, does the kid rock one cat?
Oh, which way run DMC at the VMAs?
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
They burst in the back.
They walked all the way from the back of the opera house.
A lot about Aerosmith.
They do. I guess I know every iteration of Walk This Way.
Oh, wait. And you have to count the one that they did with Moe at Moe's
Tavern at Flaming Moe's. Yes. Yes.
You do have that number three. All right.
So there's six relevant versions of Walk This Way. Right.
And the fourth is in the Disney Park.
Jason has checked out and checked his notes long ago.
I think he took a big yawn too, I was talking if I didn't if I my eyes
didn't deceive that way down to his laptop. Very tired.
That's right. It wasn't because of what we were saying was boring.
It was because you're tired.
I want everyone to have their fun.
I want to get your fun in.
All right, boys, get your jolly.
You were conserving. Let's talk about my knee.
You were conserving your energy to go on.
I was conserving my energy.
You're rusting your eyes.
So you can stretch. What else? What else?
I mean, yeah, I so the crowds were were a bit of a dance.
I mean, we still had a great time, like I said, but it was like,
I think we were I had to remind myself a few days in.
It's like, oh, my dad and brother really like this stuff,
but they are much more willing than I am to go like, oh, yeah,
we don't need to do that.
Jane is like, yeah, I don't need I could skip that.
I sure. Does that tear you apart?
Is it tough when that's your be your ganged up on?
No, because I was I mean,
no, because I was ready to skip like walking back to things like
that was one of the reasons I was like, I do not want to walk all the way back
to Sunset Boulevard to see Lightning McQueen's Racing Academy.
Even though that would be very funny if I as a solo 36 year old man
said to Lightning McQueen's Racing Academy.
Let me get can I just throw some questions out right now?
Sure. Yeah. Abra Kedare bar. Did you do it?
Didn't know. OK. Was there any talk of it?
We talked about it at one point.
Jane, Jane, we met up with a few friends of hers
at various times when we were down there, because she lived in Orlando
for a long time, still knows a lot of people down there.
But we I think at one point I talked about meeting
her her friend Kathleen and her husband, Eric. Hi.
I know they're listeners.
Hi, Kathleen. Hello, Eric.
We met them at Geiser Point over at Wilderness Lodge,
which is another recommendation I have. I haven't been there.
That is an outdoor bar, outdoor restaurant bar.
I like the sound of this.
And the electric water pageant
parks in front of it.
Great. Oh, yes. All right.
I'm there next time. So that's great. It was great.
I mean, they were wonderful dinner guests.
And then they were like, oh, the show star.
You should get over the end.
Like, I've never hobbled faster.
But it was delightful.
It was like a perfect view.
Yeah, you had a perfect view right of the pageant.
It was all the classic floats.
And then they had a little fiftieth display.
Oh, there's a new thing at that.
Yeah. Wow. That's so and the some stuff in the app works
good like they had.
If you looked up the electric water pageant, it told you, OK,
it'll be at the Polynesian at eight twenty.
It'll be at the contemporary at eight forty five.
You know, it told you each time.
And I was a little surprised by that because like
the app is a pain in the ass
and an additional pain in the ass with all the genie stuff.
Yeah, yeah, like it.
So but Kaiser Point.
Yeah, we like that a lot.
That was very fun. OK. OK. OK.
What? Oh, another friend of hers we met up with was doing the Monsters
Inc. Laugh Floor show, which is a show where they control like live
animation and they're improvising.
And I had never seen it before. It was delightful.
It was really fun. And the crowd loved it.
All week, all the shows I saw Hall of Presidents, Carousel of Progress,
let's show Carousel of Progress, Country Bears.
The audience were into them.
OK, good, good.
The audience were a little sleepy at Carousel of Progress.
But Carousel of Progress running great.
Country Bears running great. OK.
That means none of the robots heads fell off.
Nothing fell off.
You know what? This is, I think,
almost boring enough that we haven't even addressed it on the show.
Old old Joe's in the hall now.
Old Joe. Forty six himself doing kind of nothing, right?
He gives the oath of office.
He just he does less than Trump.
I think so.
Trump said a little something in the video.
Maybe Biden said about that.
But like, yeah, they definitely Trump has now been moved to the very back
behind noted psychopath Andrew Jackson.
His dream that they hang out together.
They just talk shit in the corner.
Then there was, can you believe what they're doing to a beautiful hall?
Never seen anything like it, frankly.
And frankly, you're seeing it a lot these days.
You're hearing it more and more.
And you're hearing it more and more.
And you don't love to see it.
But other things you do love to see.
I was waiting for the I believe you
coined the term cheering and booing.
Oh, yeah, sure. Uh huh.
Damn.
As they finished saying Donald Trump, one party real quick went like
like to get it in.
But not because now his name is said because previously
they went out of their way to have him say his name and not write the narrator.
And they still say like, we are saluting the idea of the president.
That's what Walt liked was the idea.
So Walt didn't necessarily support and wouldn't necessarily support
all the men on the stage be there from the past or very recent.
But
so they that's very well, you know, we're going to do, you know, we got to do.
OK, great.
And nobody can stop us.
It was so fast.
I was like, was that sarcastic?
And I asked Jane, like, do you hear that clap?
Were they joking?
And she's like, oh, no, they didn't have masks on the whole show.
No, that was very sincere.
They a lot of patriotic attire on.
And they were clapping for him for sure.
I will say that I because I was down there in that
window of time before kind of the spike happened again.
And it probably got a little bad as I was leaving Florida in a way.
And I was a little disease concerned sometimes,
sometimes from the attire of the people around me.
And which because no mask sometimes married with a shirt that, you know,
yeah, has like, I don't know the American flag, but with different colors,
like where a stripe is blue and the rest is not.
We'll come back to that.
Oh, boy. Oh, wonderful. Oh, great.
But I you know what?
At the time, I was like, well, this is making me a little stressed out.
But I in a way, I appreciate that they identify themselves with this clothing.
They let me know to try to stay away unless I'm in, say,
the line for runaway railway and have no choice but to pass by them
10 or so times.
I made it back without issue.
Sure. Yeah, that's that's a new it's a new stress, isn't it?
Down there. I get. Yeah.
I mean, like I said, the the we just kind of fell back.
I think we all kind of fell back into it.
Like even Jane and I had been very like anxious and cautious
for like the last 19 months or whatever at at this point.
And I guess, right. Crickets falling back into it.
Yeah, I know. We've we've all the cricket.
Found out about the treats.
Oh, all right. Oh, no.
Mm hmm. Anybody getting hungry?
Oh, which crickets coming to get me?
Honestly, it's mad.
You ate my brothers. Yeah.
And we yeah, we've tried to.
It doesn't seem like the other distractions in the garage have been an issue.
But I think people can hear this cricket.
Is there a way to stop the cricket if I go like, hey,
you just kind of like hit the wall like I hit it?
Yeah, maybe.
Well, you did.
It did work.
You did. You think you're on a whore.
Quiet down, you goddamn cricket.
Now, if only there was a trick like that for those marathon runners.
Yeah. The only thing I can think of is just putting them in jail.
That's the only thing I can.
Hey, some of us have been awake since five.
Some of us got in cartoonishly early.
You were mad because they were like
they were bragging about how their legs worked that day.
Well, they were showing me up. Yeah, I did.
They did eventually.
I mean, we walked around the boardwalk a little that morning.
Yeah. But yeah.
So shows were working well.
There were a number of times where it seemed like all these added fees,
all these additional costs they were not putting into ride upkeep
because Carousel did break down the first day we were at Magic Kingdom.
People mover broke down a lot.
Splash Mountain was down the one day.
The Wi-Fi for carts were down in Tomorrowland at one point,
like food carts or like we can only do cash.
And there was a number of times I either had experienced this
or overheard like we can't take magic bands right now.
And it's like you spent a billion dollars on these fucking bands
and you can get the Wi-Fi to work.
And also they have ramped up selling, you know, the magic bands
in in shops because they're not free right anymore
or they're about to not be free anymore.
I hope that magic band access is part of the Biden infrastructure bill.
I hope that that'll be addressed.
Oh, sure. Money that's been allocated for that.
We all split here.
This is I got the one.
This is Goofy has a lot of ice cream.
Oh, and then Donald dropped his ice cream.
Oh, wow. So that's what that is.
As a story. Yeah.
Yeah. Mine has a story.
When we were able to pick them online back in the summer.
Extra charge.
There was an extra charge, but everyone in my family was doing it.
And I was going to get Yacht Club Mickey because he looked very jaunty
and his yachting gear.
And everyone in my family was like, are you going to get there's a Goofy ice
cream? Are you not going to get the ice cream one man?
Like your family was saying my family was getting grief for not.
Come on, ice cream boy.
Get the ice cream on the ice cream one.
Come on. Just don't try to lick it off your wrist.
It's not real. Yeah.
Mike, an unfortunate turn of events in terms of things that had to be sacrificed
did not make it to beaches and cream.
My thinking was that this is open to the public,
you know, so I can get into it.
But like you can only get to storm along Bay.
You can only get to the pool area if you are still along.
Storm along Bay.
Storm along Bay next to Crescent Lake.
Yes. Yeah.
We all know geography.
Yeah. So I.
But you had OK.
But are you saving treats for the end or can we get or because like,
did you have ice cream? Can we talk ice cream?
Yeah, we can talk ice cream.
I also did not make it to Gideon's because we didn't go to Disney Springs.
Bang, bang the door again.
It might start the cricket, but it'll get your anger out.
Now, that is generally very upsetting to me.
I you know, it was high on my list.
But by like Friday night, we we did.
We needed the boathouse.
I was texting you texted me a photo of the boat outside.
I was there in my mind.
I loved it.
I was telling you the setlist of the dueling piano.
Thank you for that as well.
Playing.
What was it?
I forget.
Definitely got Layla in there.
Yeah, yeah. Layla was definitely in there.
Great time.
Slow one or fast one.
That was after they played the new Eric Clapton anti-lockdown song.
Yeah, I assume.
They started with a jaunty version of Leonard Cohen's Hallelujah.
You can do a jaunty?
Bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum.
And that went into a party party like it's 1999.
OK, great.
Then too much words.
It's 1999, but sure.
Yeah.
That that was nice.
It was a little maddening when we were outside on the dock
and there was a stage like next door.
And so at one point we could hear the dueling piano,
the Christmas carolers and the aqua cars getting launched into the water.
So that was a little bit of a cacophony, a cacophony of noise.
You could take a number of those things out and just if the story was
I was near a dueling piano bar and it was maddening, I would buy that 100 percent.
I mean, we weren't too I mean, yeah, we were outside.
We were excited.
We hadn't really eaten outside that much.
So why didn't you go to Gideon's?
I don't understand this because I was just because there was a line
like down the block at Friday at like 1030 at night.
Is Gideon's the Gideon's is the Disney Springs one.
It's the cookie place.
Sorry, certain type of listener.
Harry Potter type kind of fun like a cult book.
Oh, yeah. We have stuff.
And yeah, giant crazy cookies with a lot of chocolate chips in them.
Yeah. And Mr.
Morrow goes there a lot.
Sometimes he doesn't get in because it's too long of a line.
But I watched the I try to look for those videos specifically,
the ones where he goes to Gideon's or anyone else.
We were looking at other vloggers going to Gideon's.
And I thought about going like at the first day at Disney Springs,
but I didn't want to be a situation where my dad and brother's plane got like landed.
And they're like, we're on our way to the hotel.
It's like, OK, I'm in an hour long cookie line at Disney Springs.
Sorry. But would would this is your family.
Would they have been surprised?
You get them cookies?
No, I don't think they would have been surprised.
They have limited time cakes there.
They have like only like, you know, cake will be available maybe just one day.
And then they like supposedly the way I know about this from these vlogs,
they have like they don't even tell everybody they're the recipes for the baked goods.
It is like they leave stuff out for the people making it
because they want to preserve whatever the magic of Gideon's recipes.
You watch a number of vlogs about a cookie
and cake place across the country. Yes, correct.
So imagine what it would be like to have recipes that you could not.
And yes, you got on a plane.
Yes. And sometimes I don't like it because they don't do a good job
of showcasing what they bought.
Sometimes they're just sort of eating it and they don't do give like good glamour
shots because I like it when they go.
They order like they'll order like Mr.
Morrow does a very good job.
He orders like a big peanut butter coffee and a big cookie or a big piece of cake.
And then he goes out and he watch a video of a man with to have with a coffee.
How good could the shot of coffee not as big as good as like when you do
the chocolate chip cookie where you have a peanut butter coffee on draft?
Yeah, that's what I say. Yeah, that's pretty fun.
That sounds good. I was just saying visually.
Yeah, I know that it's not as visually interesting with the coffee.
But but you do want a little bit of a close up, a glamour shot of,
you know, like when you do a fast food commercial, you get that great look.
Got the water on the outside of the cup.
Real laugh. You know, the condensation is gathered. Sure.
Well, what I need, I need in any movie, I want to see the main character
getting ready for the day and I want to see an insert of a little and the coffee
pouring in and maybe a quick shot of the egg fry, because otherwise, how do I know?
How do we get there?
And how do I know this is an artsy film?
It's true. And with the close up of the delicious or if one of my favorite
comedians has taken some of his favorite comedians around in cars,
I need to see a bunch of close up shots of that coffee that is not the coffee
that then they're drinking at the time. A different coffee. Yes.
The filter goes into the machine.
Many Lovazza shots and then cut to Jerry.
Martin Short and Jerry Martin Short drinking not remotely the coffee
that they showed in the inserts. Exactly.
That's my Andy Rooney.
Sure. That show.
You make me the real coffee.
They should have shot for the real coffee.
I was watching Jerry Seinfeld's show, not the Seinfeld show, his new show.
And I like it better.
First of all, the old show was annoying.
These characters that no one they were unlikable.
They fought all the time and were never made up and were friends.
These stories are easier to follow.
A car goes from one location to another.
Coffee is purchase.
A good time is had by all.
Yeah. So Jason, of course, does Andy Rooney, you know,
we're stealing his spit here.
We can all we're all Rooney's for our own.
We're all areas one way or another.
The Rooney enter the room.
The charm of this show is Clifford's and we are Rooney's.
We're Rooney's. Oh, I like this.
The Rooney verse.
It's like, well, let me explain how it works.
The listener you see is
as you probably guess, it's about theme parks and themed entertainment.
For all the Andy Rooney and Aerosmith talk, I'll be
the Martin Short and the.
The unsuccessful Martin Short movie from.
Why aren't there Aerosmith robots on the ride?
The rock and roller coaster.
It would be much better if you saw them at the end and not just on a video screen.
I don't like it.
People want to see Bradley Whitford playing his instrument, whatever that may be.
And why isn't Joey Kramer's coffee being sold at the gift shop afterwards?
Joey worked hard on that coffee and it's not being carried in stock there.
I mean, if they have celebrity endorse like products,
they should be selling them at that gift shop.
Let's be real. I want to see a nice close up shot of Joey Kramer's coffee
going into a cup and then different coffee being.
Why won't Jerry Seinfeld drink Joey Kramer's coffee?
What devil's bargain has Disney made with Joffrey's?
Whatever that coffee is, why are they every 10 feet?
Who is this Joffrey anyway? Joffrey.
And it won't return, Mike.
I tried. I picked up my phone and type Joffrey into it and
I pressed dial and no one picked up.
Why do the in-room packets claim they make a full pot, but it's pretty weak?
Well, that is the show. Yeah.
You've made I mean, coffee grips.
Look, we'll get to Gideon's.
I mean, you've reignited my excitement for it.
But like just now or. Yeah, just now.
Do you feel regret now?
No, because I was very tired.
Like I was pretty exhausted
and I had to wake up the next morning and pack and then try to get to the Magic
Kingdom to make sure we got that lightning.
Like we had purchased.
Oh, that's what I haven't talked about yet.
The so Monday we went to Hollywood Studios.
Tuesday went to Magic Kingdom.
I bought a Genie Plus for everyone that day to test it out.
To see how it went over roughly 64,
sixty three dollars for four people.
OK, which is like a steal.
Yeah, I get I mean, it it does.
Imagine doing that like every we were there for seven days,
like every day for four feet, like on top of hotel and airfare,
airfare and tickets.
So, yeah, and I didn't I didn't use any of the like
I'll tell you some stuff and we'll make you a day because I knew like this
would drive my family insane like they again, they're not maniacs like I am,
but they are old pros.
They've they've been a number of times, you know, since we were very young.
So they like know the score and like, excuse me.
So Genie Plus, you're saying also as the element of Genie where you can tell it
what you like and it will try to plan stuff for you.
Yeah. So that's free.
Like anyone can do that.
And that's what I said.
I will I will mess around.
I will let that plan a day at Disneyland for me.
But I was not going to subject my family on every few year vacation.
Well, it hasn't come out here.
It's not even launched yet.
It's not launched yet.
But I'm looking for the challenge.
It will be because they pulled the virtual queue from web slingers.
Right. I hope they don't pull it from Rise of the Resistance because,
yeah, it was just such a shit show.
That seems like such a mistake, because I even think about that with the rise
where it's like because it breaks down so much, having just that is like a fast
pass then to get it if you were in a time when it was down.
Yeah.
So it seems much easier if the thing's going to go down a few times a day.
You know, it's the issue, though, the one issue with the virtual queue when we
we did it for Ratatouille, it called us back.
We were watching the groups, you know, get called.
And I was like, I think we'll get called at like 110.
It seems like like we could see it counting down.
They're calling them very quickly.
They called us around 110, 115.
We had two o'clock lunch reservations
at the Mexico Pavilion, which I mapped.
That is a half a mile to get to.
And so we got off Ratatouille at like one fifty five.
So like you kind of got a haul at like the app is not smart enough
yet to not schedule like conflicts.
It sounds like I'm going to beat the shit out of this app when I'm doing my
you probably versus.
Yeah. So it sounds like, yeah, there's a lot of bugs still to be worked out.
Yeah, it is. But you're going to crush it like a bug, like a cricket that you devour.
Never shows up in this garage again.
And that quiet a cricket down. I can eat a cricket.
I can do anything.
Conquer a powerful. Yeah.
So when we were at Magic Kingdom, what I used ended up using
the Genie Plus for was
Jingle Cruise.
I'm trying to I've forgotten now what I use it on search.
I used it on Jingle Cruise, then Pirates right after that worked great.
Like the one expires.
We use the one was able to get the one next door immediately.
So, OK, real quick, that works like Max Pass or Fastpass
plus where you're scheduling times you're doing.
You have to do it on the fly.
So you get a window fly.
So in the morning.
Hotel guests could do it starting at seven a.m.
Regular guests could do it at nine a.m.
And it's just like the old original Fastpass first come first serve.
So it just as seven o'clock is gone, eight o'clock shows up.
And so in the morning, it was great because, yeah, we did Jingle Cruise.
That was very fun.
We had a very fast talking skipper.
He had some good jokes.
I don't know how he talks that fast all day long.
So we got off that and then we were able to get another one.
And then like for five minutes later for Pirates of the Caribbean.
But then the next thing available was like Hornet Mansion or
no big thunder like three hours later.
And then so two hours after
I booked that one, I could book Hornet Mansion.
So ended up doing like later in the day, doing Big Thunder Mountain Railroad
and then Hornet Mansion.
OK. Were you checking?
I was checking. OK.
And stuff was showing up and going away.
Good. We're still checking.
Because you can. Yeah.
Because with that old system and I assume the new system, you can like refresh,
refresh because people get rid of the attract, like get rid of their reservations.
Yeah. So you can sometimes score enough for is hard to as much easier for people.
Harder to get because there's just a lot less.
It's just a lot more people. Yeah.
So but then it was a matter of like, well, now we have to kill Todd.
Like I think there was a slight gap between
one, a couple of like Big Thunder and Hornet Mansion.
We're like, well, we have to I guess we'll see all the presidents.
We need to kill a little bit of time.
Yeah. You have to go pay your respect to.
Got to pay the respect.
Forty six great men.
Every one of them.
My brother went, I will sit in this rocking chair next to the thief.
He was like, this is not worth it.
Wow. To wear a mask for 25 minutes indoors.
To watch this show.
I don't want to see.
I like this. I like this opinion.
I respect this opinion.
He called it just because, yeah, I mean,
I don't know that that park.
It's funny. I think Magic Kingdom, Animal Kingdom, where the I guess we went on
Tuesday and Wednesday. So, yeah, less crowds those days.
Magic Kingdom, you you realize when you're there, like, oh, there's so much to do here.
Animal Kingdom, you have the opposite reaction where you're like,
there's so very little to do here.
And we just kind of bucked up and, you know, waited in the Avatar standby lines.
OK. And then it started to rain very hard.
And that Pandora, huh?
On Pandora. Yeah, it rained.
Yeah. When you were on Pandora, it rained.
Yes. Are you trying to clarify?
Is there a joke you're getting?
I was just wondering, is it you said it rained when you were waiting in the Avatar?
As we were walking into the line for
I was wondering for Navi River Journey, it started to pour rain.
Yeah. OK. So I just wonder, like, does it does it rain there?
I just want to know what's the climate like?
Yeah, I guess because the way of water is part of it is going to be part of it.
It is. And oh, we got to use the halfway through the flight of passage line
bathrooms were real. Oh, I didn't do that.
Yeah. How were those?
They were they were serviceable.
They were very practical and a godsend for me, at least.
Yeah. Yeah.
Well, I just remembered I just remember that I got to do the secret star
tours bathroom when I went. Oh, yeah.
That VIP tour. Where is that?
You did not access the public.
There's like a little door on the side by like the overflow queue.
You can just go in there for employees only.
And then the guy let us use the secret little bathroom.
C3PO. Yep.
Peed on C3PO or peed in our 2D2.
Isn't that already? Yeah, wait, that's not a runner.
That's our history with. Yeah, we had the P rope.
I already there was a. Yeah. What was it?
What was the name of it? I don't know.
It was a good joke. Go back and listen to it. Yeah, you'll find it.
Jason, something that you we were not texting you a ton on this time.
We're giving you so can you bang the wall for the cricket?
Oh, yeah. Yes. So sorry. Here.
Wow. Now, it didn't work that time.
Didn't work that time. Hmm.
Do it louder.
Nope. I think like one big one, maybe is OK.
May hmm.
This is a real genie situation where sometimes you win and sometimes you lose.
One of the one of the few text messages that was exchanged involves the Epcot
so does location club cool.
Oh, which resulted in the in the text exchange where
is there is discussion of maybe we do an episode about Club Cool.
And so I was curious if you had done it that way, that would refresh your memory
of the soda attraction.
And what you text back was, oh, yeah, we did it.
We you know, we made it by the skin of our teeth,
which I just I just immediately responded.
I like that getting to Club Cool is a skin of your teeth scenario.
I mean, I was a white knuckle.
Guys, I'm the do.
Have I not said it enough?
These are sodas from around the world.
If we don't haul ass, we're only going to drink two or three of them.
I mean, look, like everything else, when we were down there, there was a line
to get in because, you know, there were still lingering covid protocol.
There were still some spacing or like
the Tower of Terror TV room was pretty empty when they sent us in.
But Club Cool, your party got its own soda fountain.
And there was like soda fountains.
Everyone was kind of spaced out.
This is so you could kind of take your time. Wow.
But you can put your mouth on the thing.
I just did load up on sour plum.
Yeah, China's sour plum juice.
It's just sour plum.
Delicious sour plum.
We'll get into that more on a future episode.
But get ready to get a special VIP
invite to a certain cool.
We really shouldn't have done that.
People are like running their cars off the road.
Now they got so excited. Sure.
When when?
It wasn't even I mean, the park was open for a few more hours.
We were just all exhausted.
And it started raining again.
And the crowds had kind of picked up.
So it wasn't a skin of your teeth situation.
It was the end of our patience, I guess.
My dad had already bailed like 30 minutes before.
He had already gone back to the hotel.
Explain to him that you get to drink sodas from around the world.
I could I could I don't I think his eyes would have glazed over
as soon as I said, did you know, though, I had to deal with 36 years of me going,
like, did you know, like the facts?
Well, yeah, that's what like if you asked my dad, if my dad walked in
and you said, what are your feelings about Disney World?
He would say positive things.
Boy, wonderful trips we all had as a family.
And that boy just what a sprawling operation.
It's great.
And then you peppered him with like one percent of what we talk about
every week on this podcast.
He would just fall asleep on the concrete.
He would drop like a fly and say,
likes Disney World, but oh, my God, the the the Mundania, the Arcania.
But that's but that's dads.
That's not for them.
That's just their generation didn't get caught in this stuff.
They were busy being successful.
Oh, no, my dad and mom definitely got caught in this stuff a little.
But but I mean, his complaints were more like, you know,
it was a pain in the ass to be on hold for two hours to make dining reservations.
30, 40 days before we left.
Yeah, it was like there was some stuff with the the hotel.
I mean, the beach, we were in the beach club villas,
which was the vacation club, like the the suites.
Just just to have a little extra space.
And it's an odd thing at Disney.
Like you may as it's usually often less to book a suite
than book two hotel rooms next to each other.
That makes sense. Yeah.
Yeah. So there's just not that many of them.
That's the only thing you kind of limited availability.
Grab them way ahead of time. Sure. Yeah.
And the the vacation club members get them first dibs on them
and then whatever inventory is left, they put up on sale.
So so like there was some weird like,
I don't know, some finagling with that.
I mean, we figured it out.
But like, I think housekeeping, housekeeping was not making the beds.
They would like put in new towels and like,
I think they referred to it as a light cleaning.
But it's like, oh, we're not making the beds right now.
And it's like, oh, oh, OK.
That's a pretty common.
I don't know if it's a covid era thing or just or a waste thing.
I feel like I've encountered that before.
Well, I heard Disney would like they don't change the sheets
unless you're there for like a really long stay.
But like I had usually like encounter like they at least made.
I don't know. But but it's beds.
Shit list one runners, shit list to make the beds.
There are three.
Castle doesn't look as good as tower.
You want that tuck on the side?
You want that talk on the side?
You love to get tucked in.
You try. You wish Snoopy was there.
Oh, also the towels.
I think this is common across all the hotels.
The towels are awful, like sandpaper.
Yeah. Treats, treats.
Yeah. I think I ate.
Wait, I'd like to back up and do tells like a lot longer
and then a little more about the Tylenol.
No, no, no treats.
The three T's of the episode.
I'm trying to think what we ate at Topolito Terrace one night.
More tea.
That's very good.
That's on the roof.
That's on the top floor of the new Riviera Hotel. OK.
We had like salted caramel gelato.
OK, then like deconstructed like.
I think it was like a peanut butter pie or deconstructed like.
Oh, it was pumpkin mousse.
It was deconstructed.
So it's the same like crumbs and then like a sauce.
And then like little puddles or little.
Make your own basically.
They basically make your own.
Should be called the ingredients of as opposed to like deconstructed,
which sounds cooler. Yeah.
OK, so those are do you split as a group?
Yes. OK. Yeah.
Kind of split, split those.
When Jane and I were at Animal Kingdom,
oh, saw kite tails, saw the infamous.
Oh, kite tails.
Which they run.
They do run in moderate rain and light drizzle.
OK, it was fun.
It is. People love kite tails.
Yeah, because they kind of dive bomb.
They're these big kites and they kind of die.
They get to the ground.
They look like Disney characters.
I think I didn't know what the kites are.
OK, they look like Disney.
Puma's in the air and he's flying around
because he's attached to the back of a boat of a jet ski.
Yeah, like a jet ski.
Excuse me. Jet ski kite flying.
And then to get the thing out of the air, they just let it crash
into the ground, basically lands really hard.
Gently. And this has been noticed.
And people love it.
But people seem to like the show too.
Yeah. Yeah.
So and you saw them.
I saw them.
And also we went to Chester and Hester's Dinarama,
the big carnival game area.
OK. And I won Jane Stuff Triceratops.
Hey, looks like the ride vehicle of the Triceratops spin
ride. OK.
And I got it on my first ball.
That's Primo boyfriend shit, man.
Pretty good. That's what you want.
Well, on that day, Jason had big dino energy.
Big dino. Hey, there we go.
You know, she tried the second gate.
She didn't she she bought a ticket, didn't win anything.
And I was like, I'll try.
And I got it all.
And I surprised myself. Played it cool.
Let me try. Let me do a little this.
Oh, look at that.
I just won you something.
Well, she she she did make the mistake when we were walking through that area.
She was like, do you want to play a carnival game?
And I went, no, not really.
And it started to keep walking.
And she's like, I was like, pause for a second.
I was like, do you want to play a carnival game?
Very good. Very good.
Look at these two.
She had put a lot up with a lot of my belly aching about my knees at that point.
So I felt I my my emotional intelligence was slowly starting to come back after the
sometimes excruciating pain.
Oh, my God. You're like Terry Funk and Beyond the Mat.
Oh, yeah. Getting assessed by the doctor.
And they're like, I mean, I rallied.
Hey, I know. I I shook it off after a day or two.
So wow. It's like I've heard a lot about your knees.
Can we talk about something else? Yeah.
Well, Disney Genie, I don't think the system works at all.
It actually did work.
Genie Plus worked in his old lightning manes were mixed bag.
But I didn't like paying for it.
I mean, that was my dad's big complaint is it's the complaint everyone has.
Like this used to be free.
This used to be included.
Yeah. Yeah, sure.
And now you have to pay for it.
And we were like biding our time where it's like, well, we're staying at the deluxe
hotel like, do you think they'll they should just toss it in if you're buying a package
or at least maybe this is coming during the slower times like, you know, like the park
hopper where it gets cheaper the more days you buy.
It's like maybe by a discounted version of Genie Plus, it might make the you know,
I think all as I said, I probably said this before this all the systems are being set
up now to make them flexible enough to get as much money as possible out.
So if that's to keep selling, I feel like maybe they won't do something like that.
But we'll see. Maybe.
Yeah, we'll see what the backlash was.
There were a lot of there were a lot of guest relations.
Blue umbrella stands set up everywhere and everyone was having problems or was confused
by Disney, Genie.
OK. And the guest relations at the front of the park, because I I knew I went I went to
the guest relations on the last full day we were there to cancel a dining reservation
because I knew the trick. If you told them it was due to a health issue, they won't charge
you the fee for canceling.
So did you say my knees hurt?
Well, I was saying what Jane was hip was hurting at that point.
And then my dad had a stomach ache.
We all had started.
You guys.
The deconstructed from the deconstructed.
Make it back in one piece.
This was a one piece.
I mean, by the end of the week, we were just like, I don't have an appetite to keep eating
theme like the mix of theme park food and nice food.
It was just like that's bullshit.
That's when you stand up and you say, I will take one colonial dinner for four for one.
We're all getting that's even though we're all at one table before the flight.
We're all. Yes.
That's when you that's when you go.
You were there for work.
I was there for work.
And then you don't even use stuff.
They aren't a bread meant for four people.
I opted for something.
A plate of fried clams and a side of macaroni and cheese.
Something healthy.
Fried clams.
Does that count as a treat?
They're fried.
So fried, though.
They are fried.
Yeah.
So that's a less healthy way to prepare anything.
We had.
OK, this was a 50th anniversary special in one of the animal kingdom stands.
I think it's at a few stands.
They take a Mickey ice cream bar and then they dip it in like a blueberry, like a crispy
shell on top of that.
I like that.
And then cover it with sprinkles.
Oh, give me a show me a photo of that.
And then give me a bloggers video of that.
I realized, uh, Mr.
Sheridan, Paging Mr.
Sheridan, they had cinnamon, cinnamon sugar pecans, which I'm a sucker for cinnamon
sugar pecans.
And they're like, sorry, we're all out.
We only have almonds.
But if you go to this stand and like down the way, they might have them.
And they did.
What a story.
What a thrilling story.
I'm a sucker for cinnamon sugar pecans.
But when I get there and they only have almonds, that's worse than the coffee inserts
not matching on comedians and cars getting coffee.
Almonds are utilitarian, not and not meant as a treat like the sweet, tasty pecan.
Almonds are functional.
Sad news.
Here's my here's my real Rooney.
When I tried to get the Uncle Whirlpool bathtub Sunday, I was informed it was sold out.
It had been for a while.
Oh, man.
That's the reason you went down there.
That was brutal.
That was brutal to find that out.
That was so excited for the Uncle Whirlpool bathtub Sunday.
Yeah.
So Uncle Whirlpool, the character from Carousel of Progress had his own Sunday.
It was just a bathtub with ice cream in it.
Yeah.
A little plastic bathtub, but I guess it was very popular.
I settled for a Christmas sugar cookie milkshake.
Oh, wow.
Pretty good.
So settle.
Yeah.
So was it crushed sugar cookies in a big vanilla milkshake?
I think so.
Or it's a little it had a little bit of something.
I think it was mostly like sugar cookie, like soft serve.
Was it in it?
Was it in any fun thing or anything or no?
No, it's just a cup.
Oh, it had a big like cardboard, like like a boba straw, but it was like thick cardboard.
It didn't melt like those straws sometimes are like so thin.
Sometimes the paper, they have a lot of paper straws.
Yeah.
One day I had a Mickey pretzel and I asked for a sprite, settle my stomach.
One large sprite, please.
Well, no, I just wanted a bottle that I could reach like a bottle.
And he went, it's a 30 ounce cup with no lid.
Is that OK?
Oh, because you wanted a plastic bottle.
I want a plastic bottle.
OK.
You should.
Did they sell ginger ale anywhere?
Well, I kept I did.
I had that thought, but no.
Not really.
Outside of the bars, maybe.
Why doesn't Disney World have ginger ale anymore?
I have ginger ale.
Could be pecan flavored.
I'd be a sucker for that.
When I was a boy growing up, we had pecan flavored ginger ale every morning for breakfast.
We milked it from a cow.
It would settle our stomachs.
Two or three mornings in a row, I had a baked good called a chocolate twist at the hotel.
That was delicious.
What is that?
It was like chocolate chips and it was like a kind of like a chocolate croissant,
like long croissant kind of thing.
But then it also had like a glaze on top.
So chocolate chips, a chocolate glaze on some sort of like a pastry.
Yeah.
OK, seems pretty good.
Yeah, that was a breakfast.
Hmm.
That was your breakfast.
That was breakfast with coffee.
Yeah.
OK, regular coffee.
Uh, I drink my coffee with cream.
OK, but not like peanut butter coffee, I'm saying.
No, not peanut butter coffee.
Don't don't take the knife any further.
I want you not to sleep well tonight because you're regretting that not going to Gideon's.
Do you understand?
I spend every day watching videos.
Pouring to live through your Gideon's experience.
Well, I guess I'll just have to go home and drown my sorrows in Reese's Christmas trees
and white chocolate Oreos, which I purchased at Target.
Oh my God.
It came back from the strip.
But I didn't have any sweets in the house.
How big of a bag of Reese's did you get?
Huh?
Reese's trees, those little trees.
Like, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
The shape ones are like surprisingly, I like regular a lot too.
The shapes are better.
Yeah.
Is that because of the different distribution between?
Scott, you know, we're talking about the distribution between Reese's.
You know how they have like around Halloween, they have like a Easter,
they have like an Easter egg shape.
Reese's peanut butter cup.
Yeah, I guess so.
And they have a tree at Christmas.
And those are for some reason more delicious than the regular cups.
You're talking about distribution.
I mean, peanut to chocolate distribution.
It's more the eggs are superior.
I if you'll recall, I came back from a break in recording once with like three
packages of Reese's peanut butter eggs because Carly was Carly was on this second
one. I was like, would you like a Reese's peanut butter egg?
We get it.
Being a gentleman again, being a gentleman again, winning prizes left and right,
taking my girlfriend on the family vacation.
Oh, the ultimate man.
Well, you've seen it.
You're a gentleman for us seemingly because it seems like something is in a bag.
Oh, yes.
I had to bring you both gifts.
Oh, boy.
I like that we do this.
If it was a Gideon's cookie and it was a fake out, I would like I would like scream
like I was an Oprah's favorite things.
Of course I went, Michael.
Do you think I'm a fool?
As if Oprah said, yeah, you got a car.
The same.
Well, before we get to the end, we'll say that's more positive now.
More towels.
So I've got a top five prepared.
Oh, go ahead.
Yeah, this is the top five reactionary clothing items I saw.
Oh, no, no, I see.
I see what's going back.
Number five shirt with a vertical American flag that just said relentlessly patriotic
under it.
Okay, good.
Right.
Yeah.
If you're that, then why are you hanging the flag the wrong way?
Number four shirt with vertical American flag with the thin blue line stripe.
And next to that, it said the word grandpa.
Number three, the two guys with masks that said this mask is as useless as Joe Biden.
Okay.
You wear it and bought it.
They wore it because they needed their treats.
They need it.
They had to have this.
They couldn't.
They still had to get to Disney World.
They suffered through.
We are that.
We basically are the Boston Tea Party.
This country is founded on rebel rousing, like going to a place where masks are
required and getting the mask because we have to.
But there's protests on the mask of the president and the mask that I paid for
with my own dollars.
Yeah.
They were.
What a statement.
They were so proud of themselves.
They high fived all day.
Probably runners.
Yeah.
It sounds like runners to me.
That was the funny.
That was the additional funny details.
Those two guys wearing those masks looked busted.
They look like shit.
Number two.
Is the guys Borat lived with?
Number two, the tween girl in an I survived liberal indoctrination t-shirt.
Wow.
Gee, Jesus.
Just thinking about the whole process of like, gotta make sure to pack this for
my Epcot day.
Yeah.
They probably right for inside the magic.
Also,
why do I not name it?
What did I never.
I love harassing.
If you don't know, there is this right wing Twitter account that used to cover
theme park stuff, but now exclusively treats about Johnny Depp and Amber Heard.
And I think I now exclusively reply to their tweets and I can't stop.
And I don't know why they don't block me.
I love when my likes get so I get so many more likes than their original post.
Right.
I feel like I'm at Gideon's.
What?
That's that's my magical moment.
They had one the other day that was because the news story was like Kathleen.
No, Patty Jenkins and Ryan Johnson Star Wars projects have possibly stalled due
to difference created differences with Lucasfilm.
And her headline was like, fans are celebrating.
At these projects have stalled.
And I'm like, at the end of the trilogy, the ding, ding, ding, ding, cut to every
planet.
And the number one reactionary clothing item I saw at Disney World, the shirt that
read family, faith, friends, flag, firearms, five things you don't mess with.
As if just the list would have been fine.
You don't need further.
I my my guess is that at the end of that list, it's not going to say things I hate.
Things I could easily live without.
Like, I get that you like the family and the firearms.
Just just in in line.
And I'm just like, have my phone out, like in the notes at just trying to get this
down. Jane, like, looks over, sees what I'm doing and she's worried.
She also starts just to make sure we get it.
I'll go from the front.
You go from the back.
Go for it.
No, this is all a copy to cover.
I mean, yeah, I.
I don't know. I mean, truly, what you said before, all of these people, there was a
moment with every shirt or mask that you described where it's being gingerly folded
into a suitcase.
Can't forget this like a vacation.
Can't wait because I will say I was down there on Veterans Day.
This wasn't just Veterans Day sightings.
You know, some people had normal like just a basic American flag or an army shirt.
Like, no, this was throughout the week.
I would see these things and I wrote, oh, I'm sure.
Hey, look, I saw stuff like this at Universal Studios Hollywood on, you know,
June 3rd.
Yeah, like this.
It's around here, too.
Sure. I mean, there were other like unique shirts, like the person who had a drinking
around the world shirt with each pavilion and a checkbox and what looked like very
fresh Sharpie marks on each checkbox on the back.
Well, they're there. My salute.
That's that's a patriot.
Those are the heroes.
The shirt that said talk Disney to me instead of talk dirty to me.
That one. Well, that's a shirt for all of us, I'd say.
Yeah, great. Disney does.
How about that? Good.
Great. You can go to any Disney gift shop and buy it because they're the ones selling
it. Wow. Really?
Like a crap Etsy thing.
Well, now I'm a little bit afraid of what Disney is becoming.
Yeah. Even it's a little it's innuendo for them.
Yeah, it's innuendo for them.
And the larger merchandise overview that I got, it was pretty much everything was
available. It was a little more homogenous than we were down there a couple of years
ago. Right.
Yeah, you were. But that said, I couldn't come back empty handed without stuff for
you guys. Oh, boy.
So, you know, as I said earlier, happy of late at Disney Plus Day.
Oh, you were there for Disney Plus Day.
Oh, yeah.
It's a pin. It's a really big pin.
Now, Disney Plus Day.
Now it'll be written about in the history books, but in case you don't read, in case
you're avoiding being indoctrinated, like that shirt where the this was if you are a
Disney Plus subscriber, you got an extra half hour in the parks.
And that was that in Disneyland, too.
Oh, yeah. I'm not sure.
But I thought about that.
You know, you're there for this thing.
It's probably going to make it even more crowded.
Oh, yeah. Because then what happens is because they don't want to leave the hotel guests
out. The hotel guests got in an hour early.
OK. And then the Disney Plus subscribers got in half an hour early.
So that means by the time you get into the park, Rises of Resistance is already 120
minutes. So, yeah, so that that was probably why it was especially bad at
Hollywood Studios that second day was that all the Disney Plus Day stuff.
I heard an interesting thing.
The Star Wars stuff at the merchandise out sells like the the rest of the merchandise
like three to one, I think, at Hollywood Studios of like the regular park.
You're. Yeah, the regular park.
It seems right. Sure. Yeah.
Very popular.
But we now we can always remember.
Never forget.
Eleven, twelve.
Never forget Disney Plus Day 20.
Yeah. Twenty. Never forget to celebrate the stories you love.
And you know what?
If there's a story you love, tell them now in case anything happens.
You don't get to celebrate it.
Leave a review date if something happened, you can celebrate the stories
you love anymore. Leave a review of prop culture before.
These are just as prop culture Mickey stickers.
They were given out a lot of Mickey stickers everywhere.
I think. OK. Mitigate the crowds.
Calm down. You got to hand those to us directly.
Give some give those to your child.
Oh, thank you, Mike.
You can give them to yourself.
Not a sticker fan, honestly.
But then, of course, the the PSD resistance.
I got to the rise of the resistance.
You each got one of these. Oh, oh.
We had wrapped up.
Is that Star Wars packaging?
Hmm. Hmm. Can't tell.
Just looks like, OK, let's see.
Yeah. Oh, OK.
Oh, God, Jason almost.
Oh, and you know, I've done something in the on a random.
Yeah, that's another thing my son likes is random PVC pipes.
Yeah, I get that out before we started recording.
Oh, yeah, I can feel this is OK.
Oh, boy.
I haven't gotten to it yet.
It is a little bell.
It's bad. Oh, you tweeted about that.
Oh, this is red, actually.
So what the good merchandise
that they had going, it's called the vault collection.
It's all like replicas of like early merchandise.
Yeah, yeah, this is good.
So I had to bring back the gift you would either receive from
or give to your grandmother
when you went to Disney World in the early days of the park.
Absolutely. Yes.
This little it's a white bell with gold trim
and a side view of the castle that feels very 70s in its design.
And you know what this like I often think about like, where did I
where did this like endless fascination with Disney World come from for me?
Like, when did I just like fall in love with the place
or know I needed to go there?
And I remember that I had disposable Dixie cups to wash,
but brush my teeth and then rinse with.
And there was there are Dixie cups with essentially this picture
and this style of picture, like kind of like,
you know, limited color scheme side view of the castle.
And I just I would brush my teeth every night when I was six and go,
what is that place, mommy?
And well, we'll take you there someday.
Truly, it was these cups.
I'd flip out if the cups existed, if if if these
were ebayable. But so this this kind of gift just takes me back to that
where I first was like, I must see this castle and I must go
and then go again and again and again and then have a podcast
where we like complain about the things that they're
they're doing near the castle that we don't like.
And anyway, all that to say, thank you.
This is thank you very much.
Very much. Yeah.
Oh, no. A great trip.
Some, you know, crazy crowds.
And some crazy app stuff.
But we had a nice time overall.
Yeah. And some crazy appetizers as well.
You're about the clams. Oh, oh, yeah.
I think we try to add Topolino. We had appetizer.
Escargot. Oh, really? Yeah.
Well, ooh, la, la. Look at this. Pinkies up.
Look at this.
I didn't know we were nailed to it.
You can say had at the the food and wine.
Oh, so you didn't blink at all when I said cricket.
Yeah, we're talking about bugs here.
Yeah, I would ask. I've never had Escargot.
I'm in there twice in this trip.
Yeah, well, they had a little
the the France Food and Wine booth
had a little croissant with Escargot and her butter baked into it.
Oh, how would you treatify Escargot?
How do you is there if you if you're in a chopped scenario
and it's the dessert round and you have to incorporate Escargot?
Well, I think I essentially had the treatify version
at Topolino Terrace because they baked a puff pastry on top.
So it's soaked in herb butter on the bottom
and you pull it out of like a muffin tin, essentially.
And then the snail is like on the bottom.
And then there's a puff pastry on tops and it's like very buttery.
Wow. Wow. Sounds pretty solid.
What about Escargot cookie at Gideon's
where it's full of Escargot chunks of Escargot baked into the big cookie?
I think I think you could.
I mean, if it kind of reminds me the texture of like some mushrooms.
So I think you could work with that in like a chopped scenario.
I don't think that would be the worst thing to be given.
OK, it doesn't have an overwhelming flavor on its own,
but it absorbs flavors. Right.
So you play around with it.
Hmm. Do you think we've done it?
I guess so. Why don't they have Escargot?
They should have it in everything these days.
We used to have it in everything when I was a boy.
And the YouTubers need to film the Escargot cookies better.
I need to see a close up of that mushroom like surface.
That's what I like.
I want to see the mushroom like sheen from the Escargot in their YouTube videos.
YouTubers, make sure to film the bread surface when you go to these restaurants,
because that was definitely a high point.
Numerous places doing interesting bread right now.
Mr. Morrow needs to eat more interesting bread.
He's been eating the same type of cupcake for over three months now.
Why don't they sell interesting bells at theme parks anymore?
Well, what's this? You got it.
I almost bought the spoon and thimble set, but I thought it was a little busy.
The spoon was a little over designed.
That's extreme. That's a ton more grandma for sure.
Yeah, I wanted it. Rooney's not grandma's.
I wanted a more boring spoon, although I was impressed.
They did have a Disney pin of the spoon and thimble
and they sold the back scratcher.
If you remember, they used to have the plastic back scratchers,
which my grandmother had in her house.
And so they sold the plastic back scratchers
and then they also sold the pin of the back scratcher.
My family's crest was a spoon and a thimble.
Why don't more people have family crests?
I don't understand it.
You know, in my time, they used to end podcasts by saying,
you survive podcast the ride.
Why don't they do that anymore?
Why don't people find us on the socials at podcast the ride
or buy shirts at our tea public store? They should.
And why do why do people never subscribe to our Patreon
at podcast the ride, the second gate at Patreon dot com slash podcast the ride?
I guess people are just cheap these days or they've spent too much money
at theme parks on Jeannie and lightning lanes.
Nothing left to give to the little guys.
Yeah. Theme park broadcasters and podcasters.
And why don't and why does 75% of the people listening
do not know that person we're impersonating?
Why are they not know why?
We're doing I don't know.
Why don't people get what this is?
Just because this voice hasn't been on television in 20 years.
I've been in the ground for 20 years.
For some reason, people haven't read up on me.
I used to be on television weekly.
People are typing old crank into YouTube like they should be
because of the podcast, the ride curse.
There's a chance I'll be killed again.
Somehow people die twice anymore.
I guess they used to and I was it.
I wasn't killed the first time, but I just died of natural causes.
All right. Why don't people in podcasts when they're over?
Why do they keep going?
Forever.
Dog. This has been a forever dog production executive
produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm,
Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit ForeverDogPodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter
and Instagram at ForeverDog team and liking our page on Facebook.