Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the second gate, the only theme park podcast where we make our
guests demand sanctuary before they're allowed to enter the recording.
I'm Jason Scharton, joined as always Scott Garner.
Yeah, it seems harsh, but you know, it's sanctuary, I think from the PC police.
You're feeling pursued by the PC police.
I mean, we are the modern day truth tellers, modern day philosophers, you know.
Yeah, it's our role.
We're not making that Netflix money, but you know, what are you going to do?
Mike Carlson also here.
I'm here if you would please refer to me as Judge Michael for the rest of the show, because
I am, I feel like I am the judge on the show oftentimes, but today I'd really like it officially.
Hell of a character to be associated.
What do you mean?
What are you talking about?
Fun uplifting, the fun uplifting songs of Frollo.
Who says I'm not just inspired by the judges of the show Hot Bench?
You know, it's Hot Bench.
Hot Bench is a show where there's three judges and they make a determination based on, I
think small claims.
Most of these are small claims.
Most of them are small claims.
So yeah, I'm not, I'm not in Frollo inspired.
I'm the judges of Hot Bench inspired.
Sure.
Oh, you never miss a Judge Gini Pirro book signing.
She's in LA.
She's great.
Is Judge, is Judge Joe Brown still on?
Judge Joe Brown is still on, I believe.
He's good too.
Hot Judge.
You've not done yourself with obscure references.
Hot Bench.
Oh my God.
I mean, Judge sounds good.
That sounds good too.
It seems sort of the bad teacher mode.
A hunky judge.
Oh, now we've learned.
This is what happens.
The lights do go out.
Like, am I dumb and Hot Bench is something that people know?
I think so.
It's like on TV everywhere in the world.
All the time.
It's indicated and it's in the afternoon.
Mom watches Hot Bench.
I think so.
I came upon Hot Bench a few years ago and I'm not a huge, don't get me wrong, I'm not
going to try to present myself as a huge Hot Bench fan.
I just am aware of it.
What is Hot Bench?
It's a judge show.
There's three judges and they make, you know, they solve small claims.
Like Judge Judy?
Yeah, yeah, but there's three of them.
Judge Judy is seemingly the producer and creator of Hot Bench.
She's a bad bitch.
Yeah, yeah.
She's outsourcing.
She's a bad bitch.
She's building an empire of bad bitches.
Judge Patricia, Judge Michael, and there is a Judge Michael.
And then Judge Tanya.
Those are the judges on Hot Bench.
Is there a Frollo in that bunch?
I don't know.
I don't think so.
He's a pretty harsh judge.
But so anyway, no, I'm not an expert, but all the Hot Bench fans out there make your
voices heard because I do believe it's a popular show.
Alright.
I doubt this.
That other voice you heard are guests today.
Oh my God, we're recording.
That's right.
We are recording.
I probably like paused for the light.
That's the exciting world of podcasting.
She's a singer.
She's my partner.
She's holding our little buddy Garfield.
It's Jane Clare back on the show.
Hello.
Happy to be back in person.
Yeah, thanks for being here.
For the first time.
I'm in person with dog in hand.
That's as nice as it could be.
So you thought just because we were casually at medium energy or less discussing a judge
show that somehow this was not riveting content for this podcast.
I thought because the whole light situation, I was like, oh, they're definitely going to
like that might be cut.
That's that.
I don't know.
So I'll get the lights right in the garage.
I think we'll we'll like judges.
We will determine we will review the evidence.
What is compelling content?
Are the lights flickering in the garage?
Compelling content as compelling as learning about Judge Tanya Acker and then and then the
three judges, meaning Jason Scott and I, who are kind of like the hot bench judges.
Oh, yes.
Same amount.
Hot podcast, hot podcast judges will determine.
And I think it's going to be my my guess is it's going to be cut.
The audience won't even know we're talking about.
For to have any thread of sense.
Some part of it has to be in there.
Yeah, I guess that's true.
Maybe now we're editing magic and then look, we're good.
We'll dry.
We have to drive eventually to the Hunchback of Notre Dame.
I'm like afraid to talk.
I don't know what to do.
Eventually.
This is a reality.
It's all in.
Keeping it in.
Let's get let's let's cut to the chase.
You're here.
You're back.
We're excited to have you.
And you're and you're here to talk about a show that you were fond of.
I don't remember if this came up when you joined us before over Zoom.
I think it did.
It must have come up then.
We planted the seeds for this Hunchback of Notre Dame live show from Disney MGM Studios.
What can you tell us about this, about finding this, about your your fondness for this?
Yeah.
So this show I didn't realize, but it had such an impact on my life.
That might sound silly, but let me give a little context.
So that show opened in 1996, the same day, things like June 21st, same day that the show
that the animated movie came out.
It was like a dual thing.
And I had just moved to Orlando.
I was four.
So I was little and we got passes to Disney World and we would go like every weekend.
And I lived there until about 2000.
So like almost the entire run of the show closed in 2002.
So like almost every weekend as like a four to like 10 year old, I was seeing this and
like it still makes me cry.
It is the most beautiful theme park show I have ever seen.
And like the way it blew my mind and like rewatching it brought back like all these
kind of like, oh my God, I forgot how that affected me in this way and this way.
And so it really, I hold it in a really special part of my heart.
I think it's not something talked about a lot because it was Jason was saying like it's
a little out of the way.
Well, yeah, I was out of the way.
When we first started dating, I saw that you had the notebook.
Yeah, the candy.
Not the notebook.
The candy is marketing moves.
The VHS clamshell notebooks.
You had the hunchback.
I have the hunchback one.
Yeah.
And I joked that like, oh, that was kind of like the history years that I kind of like
blanked out on like Pocahontas and hunchback.
I mean, I saw them and they were hits.
Sort of.
They're not Little Mermaid.
They're not.
It's an Alan Menken music.
Steven Schwartz lyrics like Power Team.
But you remember Little Mermaid, Beauty and the Beast.
I think that was kind of bigger.
And yeah, hunchback is pretty dark.
But I think that's why I love it.
I remember it coming out.
I remember like having some Happy Meal toys from it.
It was just like it just came after the Golden Age of Animation.
And then Hercules and Mulan hooked my attention more because there was a lot more fighting
in them.
And I was a boy.
I was a young boy.
Like swords and swords.
Yeah.
And Pocahontas and hunchback a little more complicated.
I had a fifth grade history teacher who was so mad at the historical revisionism of Pocahontas.
Any chance she had to rant about Pocahontas.
I mean, it is pretty messed up.
It's pretty weird that like, yeah, the real Pocahontas was like 12 years old when the
events happened.
Yeah, the love story they created is kind of sus.
Because that was a little weird.
It's probably important to tell the kids that that might not be accurate.
Well, speaking of things that need to be covered before we get into it.
Now, Hunchback is it is on Disney Plus as is Hunchback 2, which I didn't didn't know
that existed.
Oh, I hold that thought.
I have a feeling.
Most of what I have is about Hunchback 2.
But we'll deal with that later.
Yes, that's fine.
Yeah, I did watch it today.
And I think it is on the right side of history, but it is complicated.
I mean, it is a lot about like prejudice turning you into a monster and accepting people who
are different.
But you wanted to clear some stuff up.
I want to clear some stuff up.
OK.
Also, I could talk for like hours about just the musicals.
So like, I just want to like every little thing.
I'm like, oh, and this means this.
And it's so like, yeah, yeah.
I don't want to talk too much, but I really could talk about it forever.
So there is a certain word that they use.
And it's from the movie.
And that doesn't make it right.
But that's why it's in the stage show that they refer to Esmeralda as, you know, a word
that wouldn't be as PC today.
So like, we'll get that out of the way.
We won't say it, but it's there.
And then used a lot in the movie.
Use a lot of movies like a character description from 1830.
She describes herself as one.
So like, OK, there we go.
We got it out of the way.
And then also in the show, during the topsy turvy scene, there is like a moment where
a woman is in like a big fat suit and that's supposed to be like goofy and funny.
And that's also not OK.
I don't know if you all even noticed that.
But there was like, like, it's VHS.
There's a lot going on.
Oh, no, I meant the live show.
I guess I'm talking about the live show.
No, no, you're like watching a copy of it.
You're just like, yeah, there's a lot going on in that show.
There's not like a pro shot version of this so much.
So yeah, I'm certainly missing things.
Some are like they move around with each character and some are like wide on YouTube.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, I feel that.
Right. Yeah.
But yeah, but I mean, it's all 25 years.
I mean, stuff has changed a lot in 25 years.
Yeah, I just wanted to get that out of the way so I can talk about how much I love it,
even though there's some problematic stuff, people don't like come for me.
Yeah, sure.
No, you're not endorsing the kind of more like antiquated language used.
No, no, no, no. You're not endorsing throwing a baby in a well,
which almost does to his punishment.
Yeah, that is it is the the criticisms of the movie at the time I looked up
were very interesting because it was all it's too dark for children.
Evangelicals thought it was anti-Christian
because Frollo behaves like them.
What were the other complaints?
Oh, the one of the biggest, this is so odd, Demi Moore voices Esmeralda.
And they were so mad because she had just done strip tease.
And now she's doing a Disney movie.
Oh, that's another thing we should cover.
There's a lot of white women playing Esmeralda.
Oh, OK, I can't say that. I'm so worried.
I'm going to say the word that you told me.
She is she is she is not a white character.
Yes. So like got to get that out of the way now, too.
I just want to cover bases.
Or sing these things.
This is what was going on. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You're there. You're endorsing Topsy Turvy.
And OK, yeah, I'm endorsing the whole show.
Yeah. You know where to start.
Um, was it was this also am I reading into your
like early love of this show as being like you're probably not
watching a ton of you're not like on Broadway every weekend.
You're not. This is probably like you falling in love with theater
and live performance.
Million percent.
Like this, Jason said imprinted on me.
I think that's the best way to say it, because I mean, this show has
this show has everything.
Literally, though, there's like combat, there's dancing.
There's like amazing singing.
There's puppetry.
There's like heavy storytelling.
There's like empathy.
There's like people dancing their ass off and then like belting their ass off
and like just like interaction in the audience and like the props that they like.
And as I like a four or five year old, I am looking at this
and fully like finishing the picture in my head.
So it's like this whole world that I'm in.
And like the way they utilize the stairs for different things,
like in my mind, I could switch with them that they were no longer here,
even though it's the same prop.
Like it was just so magical.
And so like I understood it and could really just go there and like.
Yeah. Well, it's OK.
So it's it's teaching you about like the suspension of disbelief.
Yeah. And a theatrical experience, because this more like any live show
has that we're like we're representing this environment minimally
or like or sort of abstractly.
But this one, especially because it sort of uses
I'm going to miss.
I don't know about these comedienne del arte type.
This just came up recently.
I don't know the right thing. But you know what I mean?
Like the whole thing, there's moments of it that are presented
as a troupe of players telling the story and puppets.
It's not so much that you're fully transported to the to the world of Paris
at this time, like it's all theatrical.
Yeah, 100 percent.
And and I think that it's cool that they do that, because it's also like
within the show, it's a storytelling, but then the whole thing is a storytelling.
You know what I mean for the audience? Right. Right.
And yeah, it's yeah, there's a lot of great theatrical.
I mean, in terms of like this stuff we really like, I was very impressed
of like, oh, they spend some money on that.
Like this is like a fully staged.
This is an elaborate set. The costumes are so good.
Detailed costumes, like the full performers singing acrobatics,
pyro, just just all the stuff, all the like commitment level stuff
we like to say it to see.
It's also very much a product of its time where they had so much confidence
in the animated studio.
They're like, this opens the day of the movie.
We're not nowadays.
You got to wait and see how the movie goes.
And then maybe something will slowly show up in the park,
although they're getting the Marvel stuff in like as stuff.
Yeah, but that's a little easier.
And then you can pretty much count on that stuff being successful.
Yes. For the most part, this is like they had their footing with a couple movies.
And now it caught up to like, OK, so we need things instantly
because this is going to be beloved by all children and part guests everywhere.
Yeah. In this case, maybe not so much.
Not everybody grabbed on to hunchback.
Not the way it is one of the first where that was not happening
as much. Not immediately, but on a 70 million dollar budget,
it made 350 plus million.
So it's insane to call that a bomb, I guess.
It's certainly not a bomb.
Yeah. From what I saw and I was surprised, apparently Hercules
was when the box office downturn started on these movies.
Ah, what did it make a profit, you know, or did it just kind of it was like
was I feel like I remember it just like kind of even like not bad.
Did OK. I forget.
But that that was another one where they got it in a parade
very quickly, like maybe opening summer.
I was like, parade.
I remember Hercules victory parade. Sure.
They also I know were mainly covering the Disney MGM Studios version,
but I recall the the Disneyland version, the festival.
Yeah. Yeah. Which was like also the like an insane scale,
this massive and also sort of creative in its staging, where it was more
outdoor theater in the round.
It felt like a Ren fair kind of event.
And I hadn't really watched it until today.
I don't think I saw it in person when it was happening.
But like Quasimodo does stunts a guy in a suit with the limited
visibility of the face and and then the hunchback.
You have a hunchback on top of you and said you're the guys
swinging down ropes and climbing everywhere.
You could climb on this thing.
I was pretty blown away by the scale.
He does not also sing because he's a face.
He's not a face character.
He's a man. I don't really know that show as well.
In the this is a big difference between the two.
And I was curious in the in the Disneyland one.
It's like it's more of the mascot style.
So you're not seeing the performers face.
Thus the big ballad Up There is sung.
Out there. Oh, my God.
How did you say? I'm sorry.
Out there.
Up there. Oh, come on.
There. No, this is why you're here to correct this.
I just watched it, too.
And I still made that mistake.
But that song is so epic.
I really am worried I'm going to get a song wrong now.
Don't fuck up, Michael.
This is the Bible. These songs.
You better not.
This is the one thing I actually am really like not protective of,
but like a little bit like it's just like in your.
Oh, read me out if you need to.
Great.
No, feel free to yell at me.
Share Mike apart, damn it.
Give Jason a break.
This was.
No, I'm just kidding.
Well, no, I one of the reasons this came up again
was at some point during the pandemic,
I think it was after you had been on the show
and this came up in conversation and that you you love the show.
I know we'll have to have you back. Talk about this show.
Some some click baby blog
describe something the Walt Disney Company was doing was like devious,
like something evil done by Hades himself or Judge Frollo.
And I was like, who the fuck is that?
Like I was like, what is this reference?
I was like, I didn't even know the character.
I couldn't remember.
You remember Judge Frollo?
I didn't know the name off the top of my head.
I was like, who is Judge Frollo?
Jane, did you break a glass in your hand?
She was a little.
I don't remember. I mean, it's pandemic.
I remember half that shit.
What did you say?
Who is Judge Frollo?
I do get mad sometimes when he tosses stuff out like musical terms
and or like like reference something like, how dare you?
That's a this musical and this is this and open here.
Like, how dare you shit on that? Like, yes, because most of the musicals
I like were like, I don't know, before the war century old.
Yeah, I'm more like contemporary.
Is there the word review in the title?
Yes. And there might be a year. There might be.
I yeah, I was watch.
I was recently watching H.M.
Maxis the three that's that's entertainment series,
which is just a clip show movies of the old MGM movie.
Yeah, they put those in theaters.
It just be like, here's all the here's all the famous musical sequences
from a bunch of musicals.
You go to the theater to see.
Can you imagine to go into the theater to see a clip show now?
An irate 1979 Frank Sinatra already looks like a mummy,
like and he seems to be so annoyed that he has to do this to introduce these.
He only hosts it really?
Well, it's like him and then Elizabeth Taylor and then Fred Astaire.
Like it's like remember the good old times we had.
Yeah. Years ago.
Not that long ago.
It's not that long ago, but some of those early ones when they're figuring it out,
I can't I can't endorse like a Mountie.
Like it was like a guy in a Mountie outfit and then a woman.
And they were just like making eye contact for like two minutes singing at each other.
And I was like, this is not a movie.
This is not very this may as well be a photograph.
I wonder what that one is.
I don't know offhand. What's the scary Mountie musical?
It's very it's very bizarre.
So so I like a little after that and a little before like Stephen Schwartz's time.
But I can't you can't argue with Stephen Schwartz on his own.
And did Godspell and Pippen and Wicked.
And so with Alan Menken, like I was who did this.
Yes. OK. Yeah.
Schwartz and Menken. OK.
Yeah. He did like the lyrics, right?
I guess.
Schwartz did the lyrics, Menken did the lyrics and rewatching it.
I was like, wow, these songs are very good and they are very musical theater.
I can see how you eventually would jump into that.
Maybe more so than some of the other ones.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. And I mean,
I think too, I mean, I was raised like cult Catholic, like really,
really traumatizingly bad.
And so I think there was a little bit of like familiarity with it
and also how Esmeralda like really fought against it and like
how Quasimodo kind of showed like empathy and kind of like those bad people.
I think maybe I was like, oh, good, I'm not alone.
Like, but yeah, I don't know.
And that a church could be fun.
A place where you swing around on ropes.
We'll get there one day.
Now the rafters of the actual building, not the masses aren't fun.
I'm saying like he swings around up top.
Yeah, he's like he's spider man.
He's the Spider Man of the church.
I think that's the movie.
Oh, Jesus.
Spider Man of the Church.
Oh, my God.
You know, that's not an improvement.
No, because I don't.
I'm not really I don't really.
You weren't a big Spider Man fan.
You know, can we talk about the Spider Man thing?
Well, I yeah, I kept getting him Spider Man stuff like for his birthday and stuff.
And he was like, OK, well, by the way, who told you that Spider Man is my favorite?
I was like, you did. You always say Spider Man is your best friend.
He's like, I say he's a friend.
He's a friend. And I'm like, what do you know?
He's like, well, Marvel is like their mic.
I know the X-Men are X-Men are my family and Spider Man's more like
so Mike feels an attachment to Optimus Prime.
Oh, so what you're saying, I'm not even sure even you are calling Optimus Prime
your family or friends. No, no, I wasn't.
And I have if there's he's more of just like a cold, distant father figure.
Like a mentor figure.
Well, now you're back in family territory.
Yeah. You're like a professor.
Yeah, that's what I merely mean by him.
I don't think of him as my friend, Jason.
So wait, wait, hold on.
The movie is short of it.
Mike's not crazy. He doesn't.
He thinks of Optimus Prime as a father figure, not his actual father.
Now on to Jason's thing.
No, I'm crazy. Family.
Let's get back to me.
I know. I'm just about to.
I'm just trying to figure out exactly who Jason in the Marvel
universe considers his family and friends.
That's what I'm trying to get back to.
Yeah, I think Spider Man, I'm always concerned about him.
Like a right like like you're worried about your friend in the Marvel universe.
My eyes are glazing over anything about Marvel.
And I'm just like, how do you think I feel half these episodes?
We can have a side.
That's a little break. We'll do our own.
Let's split. Let's get a splitter. Yeah.
We'll record our own.
Well, for me, it's my best friend's Gambit.
I probably you know what?
It might be him too.
Oh, my God. You guys have the same best friend.
Maybe Cable.
Are you going to fight over him?
Cable's like the friend.
Are you guys going to fight over your best friend?
Is this going to happen?
Oh, my God.
Gambit showed up in both.
What's that paper thing that goes back and forth?
The shoes. No, no, no.
The little thing you do with your.
No. Good guess, though.
The little thing that goes.
The little thing in your hands.
Were you a fortune teller?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, exactly.
Yes, that Gambit was in.
They they both got Gambit when they did that.
Maybe Cable.
Cable is a very funny one.
Cable had a lot of guns and.
You showed me that Jubilee box of that toy and she was cool looking.
Oh, yeah. Jubilee is cool.
She's like, yeah, she's like a cool teen.
Yeah, because over the weekend, I dropped what I was doing
because Mike let me know that these action figures were on sale.
We're ready for preorder.
The X-Men 92 ones.
And I I usually am pretty I'm pretty picky with what I bought.
But I dropped what I was doing to.
You see Garfield's face.
Oh, yeah, yeah. Do you want to take a photo?
Oh, sure. His tongue is full.
But if I get too loud, he looks up at me like, how dare you?
OK, well, when he goes back to the other.
Yeah, when he goes back.
So so Jason finally had to tell you Spider-Man is not my best friend.
Well, I felt like shit because I went and like got him this really cool.
No, no, this was like an amazing gift.
It was more like you don't realize how much you talk about Spider-Man.
Yeah, like I full stop thought that was your dude.
And I was like, cool, I'm going to get this shit going.
Like this guy's it.
And I go like balls to the wall.
And he's like, so who told him like, oh, fuck.
Like, well, you got me the Spider-Man comic that came out
the month I was born.
That's very thoughtful.
Yeah, which we did.
We then we also did look up the X-Men issue,
which is a beautifully painted cover, but it does say life death on the cover.
And that's half right.
So it was a little grimmer.
And the Spider-Man cover was more fun and dynamic.
So it was the right choice anyway.
OK, back to Hunchback.
Back to Hunchback.
Spider-Man, the Spider-Man of the church.
Spider-Man of the church.
Well, well, this is something I was saying long ago about the in the
in the Disneyland version, he's like it's the character head
and you don't see the face.
It's not he's not two random guys sing out there.
There we go.
You got it.
Next to him, it's a strange arrangement.
And in this version, the Florida version, it is a guy.
It's a guy with like not such crazy prosthetics.
Wait, no, I got to say, because sorry, I'm sorry.
I cut people off and I'm trying to.
No, no, no, no.
I was watching this again.
I watched this like maybe 10 times since we talked about
we were going to do it this week, like literally on repeat.
And since I performed in theme park before, I was like, oh, my fucking God.
Like these people had the hardest tracks in this show,
like in a theater that isn't fully enclosed.
So it's hot as hell, human as hell.
And they have multiple layers on.
And then they're also like, OK, Quasimodo, he has it's covering
like his nose and like the top of his eyes.
And he also has like a hunchback on.
He has to walk a certain way and character.
At one point, he lifts up as Merelda.
He does like stunt shit kind of.
And he's belting like out there, which has one of the highest notes
in the bridge for like a male musical theater guy.
I see your eyes glazing over.
No, no, I'm thinking about him singing.
The word is I'd treasure.
I'm contemplating if I could hit it.
You guys are changing the key, but yeah, you guys are so good.
You're so good.
We have a piano note to help us out.
If this was Spider-Man, Try the Dark, I could sing these songs.
Oh, yeah, of course.
This is different.
It's like two last minutes.
Blake, who falls from the sky.
I don't want to get you off your track, Jane, but let me.
But I have something applicable to say, which is this.
Disney did do a live version, a theatrical version outside of the theme parks
in theaters of Hunchback and Nunchuk.
I don't think it made it to Broadway.
They did limited runs in test market.
They did it at the La Jolla Playhouse.
It was at La Jolla for a while.
And yeah, it seemed like pretty popular, like one of a bunch of awards looked like in San Diego.
And I'm like, who is in it?
I wonder if I'd recognize a name and the only name I would care about in Broadway world was on it.
Patrick Page, the Green Goblin himself played Frollo.
Yeah, he did.
Legend.
Yeah.
He did a good job.
I'm a freaky little judge.
I'm just a little judge.
I'm a bad little judge.
He's the man, yeah.
Yeah, and then in the original movie, it's, what is it, Tony Jay?
Is that right?
He's Frollo.
Right.
Yeah.
Oh, that's who Patrick Page was.
Oh, wow.
That's very funny.
Yeah, I think you pointed that out to me once, Jason, actually.
You were like, could we, like years ago.
Well, we looked, I think, was he in Hades?
He was in like, yeah, he was in a big hit.
He's been in so much stuff recently and he's done a lot.
Yeah, this movie, the movie is interesting because
Demi Moore is the speaking voice of Esmeralda.
She doesn't sing the song.
And then Kevin Klein is the voice of Phoebus.
Phoebus.
But he doesn't really sing that character.
No.
He's like, actor.
Yeah, he doesn't sing.
And then besides Jason Alexander, who is great, who does Broadway and film and TV,
it's a lot of theater people in the movie.
So it's a very Broadway heavy kind of ensemble.
And Tony Jay was like in the Royal Shakespeare Company.
And then what's the name of the guy that's escaped me now who voices Quasimodo?
I know his last name is Hulch.
Oh, it's Tom.
Tom Hulch?
Yeah.
Is it?
Okay.
Amadeus fame.
Oh, yes.
Over my head.
But yes.
Yeah, he's Mozart.
He and I was watching like a behind the scenes like documentary type thing about the movie
and they kind of he helped like inspire Quasimodo a little bit because the animators would put down
their rough sketches of things and then have actors come in and not look at the actor,
but like look at the animations.
And as soon as they heard his voice, they were like, holy crap, like this guy's Quasimodo.
We're going for this.
And I think he's like such a beautiful singer and such a beautiful voice actor.
I mean, Quasimodo here, I'm going to make a really bold statement.
Quasimodo, big dick energy, huge fucking horse cock energy, because here's why.
Here's my yeah, I said a horse cock.
Never been on the show before.
I don't think that phrase second gate, baby, getting fucking wild.
We edited out the part where Mike was blown out of his chair down the block.
Is that bothering you, Michael?
Yeah, that's fine.
I said the is the steam coming out of your ears?
I mean, let's go ahead.
You can't see it because the Cardi B song.
The dirty Cardi B song.
I said the title of it once.
Oh, my gosh.
The radio safe version, which is worse.
Yeah, it is worse.
So big dick energy.
Here's why.
So Quasimodo, right?
He meets Esmeralda and is kind of like, holy shit, this girl's awesome, right?
Kind of falls for her.
And then she's like, hey, I kind of fell for this guy.
Also, he's injured.
Can you help?
And Quasimodo takes one second to do a little Heaven's Light reprise,
which also is an amazing song.
Heaven's Light.
We have to talk about that.
But so then he helps her and him kind of takes a second about it
and then goes and puts their hands together and is like, you know what?
You two belong together.
I'm going to be good.
He gets through it.
He's such a fucking man.
Really, he's such a man.
He does the right thing.
He's empathetic.
I know what you're thinking over there.
He's also not needy.
He's not needy.
Which is how it's very attractive.
He's grateful.
You say, yeah, you know what?
Yeah, that guy is good for you.
Go for it.
Yeah, he's fucking rad.
I'm not worried.
He's not jealous and he helps the guy not die.
He's a G.
I said to Jason, I was like, did this shape the kind of...
I've always really been into very emotional and very empathetic guys.
And I was like, well, I don't want to say I'm into you
because you look good in the laundry bag.
Because you're an ugly dude.
Because you look like shit, man.
I was like, am I a Spirelda and you're quasi?
And then he was like, it doesn't really bode well for us.
And I'm like, well, that's not really what I mean.
But empathy is the one word to describe that character
and really sweet and really gentle.
And I've always been attracted to...
What is that stern look?
I was just thinking about how a doctor once told me that,
well, posture is very important.
If people don't watch their posture,
they end up with hunchbacks when they're old.
They walk with a hunch.
I manifested this.
Jason, do you recall the doctor at an early age telling you
that you might grow up to have big dick energy?
Jason has big dick energy.
Can I say that?
Yeah, all the things you said, it doesn't...
I'm glad you said it because I think it.
And I don't have the courage to say it.
You're that dead.
Top of the world.
Yeah, no, Jason, very empathetic.
He plays it cool.
All that's what I'm...
I don't know if he plays it cool.
That's what we saw all the time too.
I don't know if this is too personal,
but our first date, we always talk about our hands.
Remember? Can we say that?
I was at two.
No, yeah, you can say that.
So on our first date, there was a moment where I got a little
anxious because I have a slew of mental health problems,
but I got really anxious.
And at one point he was like, hey, hey, it's okay.
And he put his hand on mine.
And from that moment, I was like, oh my God, this guy is different.
He's so nice.
And I always think of that because sometimes we'll be talking like,
remember our first date and you play your hand on mine?
You've always been so comforting and like, I don't know.
Thank you.
I love you.
That's nice, you guys.
So he's got all of it, is what you're saying.
But much cuter.
Thank you.
You're as handsome as Phoebus himself.
Jason is the looks of Phoebus with the dick of Quasimodo.
That's what we're trying to say here.
I scared Garfield.
Garfield is not wild about this.
Laughs or laughs.
If Jason even coughs a little.
Yeah, Garfield.
But I can cough as much as I want.
Yeah.
If Jason has a big cough energy.
A big cough energy.
Well, he does have a big cough energy.
He has a big, deep cough.
He scares the bejesus out of Garfield.
It scares me too.
It scares Mike.
Everyone in my family has it.
And also like I have an allergy, reoccurring nasal drip.
And so it hasn't been too bad lately, but yeah, Garfield hates it.
He will either run to the other side of the room or he will come and check on me.
And he's helping by walking all over my chest.
He'll stand on his chest or go like make sure he's okay.
Stare at him.
Just like stare at him in the face.
If you're like sitting down.
Or just mad dog me a little.
He loves you.
He loves his daddy.
Is he, would you say that he's anything like
the jolly, the goat?
Oh, I was gonna just say he's like, he's like Esmeralda's got, well, yes.
And we're, or maybe we are the gargoyles.
Yes!
Oh my god.
Who encourage Jason to go get out there.
This is not true because there was no scenario where like he was watching you from.
Right, doesn't that one to one?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, no, no.
We never had a scenario like go get him big guy.
Yeah, you can do it.
But then they get him all psyched up and then he doesn't even get the girl.
And I think that's kind of mean of them.
They're like, hey, she loves you.
And he's like, no, she doesn't.
The gargoyles as a kid, I recall, and don't be mad at me.
I don't think I loved the gargoyles as a kid.
And I love the side characters on every movie.
They were always my favorite.
And I think these might've been the first side characters that like let me down.
I agree with that actually.
I do.
What do you mean?
The lovable buddies are the stone gargoyles that are out there.
And is a stretch on their like, you know, you got to get cute buddies in there somewhere.
Who is this going to be?
And then it's in question whether other people can see them or not.
I was just going to say it's a thing that he used as like an adaptability because he
stuck up there alone.
So it's all kind of in his head.
But the goat sees them at one point.
Animals are crazy.
They can see shit all the time.
They know.
Animals.
They say stuff.
Yeah, animals in general.
Ghosts and such.
But I think that's interesting.
I think that's also kind of a dark thing.
That's a mental thing.
He helped himself.
He must have just developed because he's like an adult.
He's been in there for like decades.
That poor guy, man.
Yeah, there's a Ninja Turtles mini series, spoiler alert, where all of them are dead
except for Michelangelo.
And the brothers are just like hanging out with him in his mind.
It's really depressing.
Jesus.
Really dark.
It's called The Last Ronin.
Here's something I learned about the gargoyles.
They are voiced by these musical theater actors.
Jason Alexander, you know the other names are probably Morse, if you're a theater person.
I remember not knowing who they were.
They just weren't mainstream celebrities.
But you know who always wanted to get mainstream celebrities into these films?
Jeffrey Katzenberg.
He knows the formula.
He knows if there's a celebrity anywhere near this thing, millions of people will flock to it always.
Guaranteed.
No matter what.
So he's like, we got three fun gargoyle characters.
We got to stack the decks.
We got to get the funniest nuts out there in the world of comedy.
And his idea, his pitch of who the gargoyles would be were Letterman, Arsenio, and you know what's coming.
Jay Leno.
Oh my gosh.
You imagine.
I would have.
If that had happened, I would have just said to you, those were my favorite characters in any Disney movie of all time.
You know what I always say all the times that the gargoyles are the best characters ever, ever in any.
The alternate timeline.
This is an episode just called The Gargoyles from Hunchback.
There's a parallel universe where that happened, like for sure.
Yes, I believe that.
Yes.
Well, they're also considered naming the gargoyles Chaney, Lawton and Quinn after Lon Chaney, Charles Lawton and Anthony Quinn, who had played Quasimodo previously.
And they were concerned.
Disney Legal was concerned they would get sued by the estates.
I had to wait.
That was the problem.
Not that like all children would blink their eyes audibly at this threat.
Lawton.
Mommy, can I have a Lawton doll?
Please give me a little children.
Little children chuckling at the references in the theater.
Like a little smart smarty pants child, like chuckling like a clever reference.
Little de font Leroy child.
He knows who Lawton is.
That's what Jason did when he was a little kid.
I wouldn't know anything about this.
Little Lord, if we had a big lolly and that like the bloomers or whatever in the hat.
A lot of pearls.
Red sheets, like big red sheets.
Very apple cheeked.
In 1930 when he was going to the movies.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, and to okay, I'll say something like nice about the gargoyles in the movie.
I forget her name, but the female character one, that was her last thing ever.
She was like an old actress who had done a bunch of stuff and that was her last ever
role.
And I think that's that's nice.
And I do like that they have a female one because she's really funny.
Like she's kind of like this rough around the edges kind of funny older.
Yeah, she's got like a lean stretch type energy to her.
Yeah, she's fun.
I agree.
She is fun.
Yeah, no, I think that's very funny.
I think I like the gargoyles maybe more now than the costumes are cool in the show.
I think that is a really cool.
Yes, the represent because they have some weird stuff to represent throughout this show.
Yeah.
And to like make the make them move.
You do it's awkward move in the movie.
It's awkward.
They have to hop around everywhere.
But yeah, that that was a successful element of the show for sure.
The goat is a marionette.
The goat?
Yeah.
Uh, make them like them on and everything, baby.
I'm really gassing you up this episode.
Thank you so much, dear.
It makes up for the hundreds of others.
Anyway, there's a little goat puppet.
It's the worst represent or they they they did have to make some cuts.
I mean, this is a long show for theme park.
It's about 30 minutes long.
It's a long 30, 30, 30 minutes because there's a did you guys see it?
Sorry, I cut you off.
God damn.
I'm really gonna say I mean, watching the movie, they got a lot of the hellfire brimstone stuff,
which is, you know, you're at 90 degree Florida heat.
Maybe you don't want to hear about sin so much.
So it kind of makes sense why they would have.
But I feel like the horse isn't super rep.
You you said you were scared of the one about the horse.
So horse comes out at some point.
First of all, the puppetry at the beginning is so cool because it leads right up to the
actual actor characters entrances because like the quasi moto puppet,
they have go up stage left to the stairs and right when it gets to the top and disappears,
the real actor comes out and I was like, damn, that's cool.
So they also have a puppet of Frollo on the horse and then it comes out in real life.
That horse, I would like nearly piss myself when that shit came out because it's like
rushes to the end of the stage and almost looks like it's going to go like over the stage and
it kind of goes back and I'm still trying to figure out.
I think there's like a person under there and then I was like, is it Frollo?
But then he gets off the horse right after.
So it's not anyway, that horse scared the shit out of me, man.
One character is riding another essentially like, yeah, how do they do it?
Is it like a classic horse costume with two people?
No, no, it's like it's like it has wheels.
Right.
Oh, so I think it's a puppetry up through the head and there's like a person in it
because you see the feet.
Right.
It's cool.
Like it looks cool.
It's scary as hell.
It might be, yeah, it would be like an interesting design.
Like if you take off the skin of the horse, you'd be like, oh, I see that.
As a kid, it was like so big and scary and came so close to you.
I'm like, yeah.
Yeah.
You're not scared of this thing more in general.
Like you were just like, ah, the magic.
No, I was scared of everything.
Okay.
Still kind of scared of everything.
Yes, you don't use similar to Scott.
Scott, you of course don't like big things and small spaces and Jane is very similar
or like big.
You don't like big things above me.
Above me.
We went on the Jurassic World ride after that.
Jesus Christ.
The upgrade at Universal Hollywood.
Hell no.
You barely made it through.
Yeah.
You know, I was like, you didn't have to do this for my account.
It was like we were just, you had visited me at Potter and watched one of my shows
or some shit, right?
Yes.
And then after we were like, no, I was like, yeah, no, I can ride it.
And we were in like the calm part and you were like, Jesus.
And I'm like, because I also have some mechanophobia.
Have you guys learned about submechanophobia?
No.
There's this video that I've not been unwilling to watch it.
I don't want to know about.
Do we have the same shit, man?
Similar.
So submechanophobia is the fear of like a mechanic thing or something underwater.
So like the Jaws shark or the Jurassic Park when you're going through the world,
whatever the fuck.
If you're going through the normal part and there's like the ones in the water,
I started like freaking out and he was like, this is like the calm part.
I was like, I know, but they're underwater.
It's freaking me the fuck out.
Like, what is the ride's a recipe of all that's all these things.
I fully had like a mild panic attack, but I was like, it's cool.
What is the actual fear?
Is it that it's just going to do something or is it just literally there?
Because it's like this creepy.
It's going to emerge from that.
It's there and like being underwater is such a like mysterious thing.
And it's just like a weird thing.
But yeah, I don't know what it's called, but I have a fear of things hanging over me.
Like if you remember World of Disney and Disney World before they like changed it,
how it held is hanging like the cats and guys.
Well, I remember there was a John Smith sitting in a chair and it was huge.
And one time when I was younger, my siblings were assholes.
They are going to get in trouble.
Are they going to jail?
Oh, no, no, no, I don't talk to them.
Stop me, please.
What is the story?
What were you building?
They were like, hey, come over here.
And I was like, what?
And they were like, look up.
And I was like, oh, my God, I was right under it.
And they knew I was scared.
Like that shit scars me.
I hate big things hanging over me.
Like Secret Life pets, that the big the big brown dog.
We went on that ride and I was like, oh, my God, don't get me off of this.
He's on a girder at some point right above you.
I was literally like, this is awful.
And I'm there going like, haha, I know.
What's that?
Can I?
I hate to bring up the go back to the bad memory.
But was John Smith sitting in what kind of was he just sitting in a chair?
Yeah, it was like he was like sitting in.
They were you guys.
You need to show pictures of this.
There was a carpet with Aladdin and Jasmine.
That makes sense to me that they would be flying.
But why is John Smith?
Did he have the same like was he laughing like a Mary Poppins?
He was just in a fucking chair, man.
Why are you going hard on this?
I'm just curious.
I'm just curious because I want to know about the chair.
As well as he was floating, why would he be floated?
The carpet makes perfect sense.
I was just trying to figure out if that was just.
Why is he up there?
Did every character up there?
So it didn't the carpet just happened to work better.
OK, so that just was an example.
Maybe that was the only one that actually made sense.
I think it's maybe the spirit of nature.
Like he was blessed by Grandmother Willow and it gave him the ability to fly into the rafters
of the store.
Does that work?
He could.
Yeah, it does work.
I mean, OK, he can fly in the store.
Got it.
He has powers to fly in the store because of the special flying grand.
OK, Grandmother Willow herself.
But only in the chair.
Only in the chair and only in the chair in Orlando.
Right.
Yeah.
Not in Anaheim.
Not in like mood shadows in Malibu.
He was not blessed.
They could not float in the chair there.
Got it.
OK, I'm comfortable now.
OK, good.
I'm really glad.
We know the why of this.
Well, what's some other stuff about the show or the adaptation of the show?
Like are there songs we've missed or they're like big staging?
I mean, just the massive bell.
We got a big bell.
You got a big, big cauldron.
You got a bit like that.
Like, yes.
Yeah.
Dump a bunch of fireworks on the.
He throws like a wooden beam.
I mean, it's not wood, but he's like sanctuary.
That was exciting.
Like throwing the beam.
Bictic energy.
And then they pick up the beam and use it as a battering ram.
Like it's.
Also, and I was going to say, man, like the choreography of having to do that and go
upstairs and running and like using this.
Like if you just watch one track of that show, it's wild.
Like.
Yeah.
What does track mean?
So like in Beetlejuice, I was the Fantasia track.
So like the Esmeralda track or the it means like the role in the show.
So like the chorus, it could be like, oh, I'm doing like sometimes like, oh, chorus
three track, which is different than the chorus five track.
It's just like which role you're doing.
They just call it.
You have to be at every point because it might be other role.
Maybe for a second you play this character and then you change it.
Yeah, well, because the the like ensemble, I think really have they all have hard jobs.
The show looks I mean, to me, it looked really hard.
But the ensemble really does carry a lot of it because they're in it from beginning to end.
They are props sometimes they are like atmosphere sometimes they're dancing.
They're like doing the puppetry like they do so much just to keep the show like alive.
So I got to give a shout out to those people because damn they worked their ass off.
Yeah. And there's not really a lot of moments where they get off stage.
They're on the whole time.
Catch a breath, have a drink of water.
There's not a lot of that.
I in the gig.
Let's be honest.
Yeah.
Frollo gets a lot of time to rest.
I was impressed because it's in the movie and they they replicate it almost exactly in the show.
In the topsy turvy day number, the person does a handstand and the different costume falls over them.
That's very easy to do in animation seemingly, but they did it with a practical costume and I
thought that was very impressive.
I loved that as a kid.
So it's like his bottom part of the costume.
He's got like a upside down head hanging from between his legs.
And then there's a full skirt over it.
So then when he goes and does the handstand, the skirt falls and it looks like his legs are the arms
and then the head and then the skirt.
Wow.
It's cool as hell.
That's very clever.
It's like those Katy Perry quick changes.
Oh yeah.
She saw the show too and it really inspired her.
I could see that.
That would add up.
That would be hard to believe.
One of my favorite discoveries about the song topsy turvy day is that he explicitly says
topsy turvy day.
It's topsy turvy day.
January 6th.
Topsy turvy day.
What?
I looked that up too.
Yeah.
I'm like wait, I'm sorry.
Is that in the movie or in this performance?
He says on the 6th of January.
Join the Bones.
Topsy turvy day.
Join the Bones and Thieves and Strumpets streaming in from charters to callous.
Scurvy names are extra scurvy on the 6th of January.
Whoa.
So it was topsy turvy day at the US Capitol.
Why a goat man can be the speaker of the house.
That's right.
Yeah.
Why a wall that usually isn't smeared with shit is smeared with shit.
Everything is topsy turvy day.
It's the day we crown the QAnon Shaman.
Lord.
I was in the car listening to the soundtrack today and it went by and I went what?
I go I got to like we wanted to pull over and like rewind it and then I did.
Yeah.
Looked it up.
Geez.
I also that one I was like this is pretty close to a different topsy.
One of my favorite topsy's.
I almost said the top of the show said it's topsy turvy day which is different the turning turtle.
Right.
Everyone please make sure you know the difference.
Topsy turvy is not turning turtle.
I just want to make sure everyone knows that from Mary Poppins 2.
How do you feel about the topsy runner?
If you're ranking your favorite runners from the show where is the topsy runner?
It's in my top three and I don't think I even bring up as much as I want to.
Topsy's come up I think four times in this show.
Meryl Streep's character from Mary Poppins 2.
You pull your topsy.
That's not Stephen Schwartz.
That's Mark Shaman.
I don't know I didn't see that one.
That's not Stephen Schwartz.
Yeah.
Turning turtle.
Don't encourage.
Turning turtle which is different than turtle turtle.
Yes of course.
At the turtle club.
Thank you.
Did you know when you were coming on how many connections would come back to this show?
I mean late night in the 90s ninja turtles.
I thought you were going to say turtle references.
Turtles.
Oh yeah.
We all know that when they filmed the turtle club scene they had to give a speech and address
a recent topsy turvy day.
Well I saw an article going around that.
I'm gonna make like champ gestures.
Yeah I did it.
That's one of my favorite things by the way.
When people do that and they put their hands together and like do like the celebrations.
Do the celebrations.
That's so funny to me anytime I see that for some reason.
Well I feel like Phoebus.
I feel as victorious as Phoebus himself.
Phoebus.
I mean he kind of does nothing.
Phoebus has been Phoebus energy.
Oh yeah I think he has small dick energy personally because.
I feel small dick energy but big Phoebus energy.
Yeah exactly.
Big Phoebus energy.
Who has bigger Phoebus energy than Phoebus.
Exactly yeah because he's kind of douchey.
He's kind of douchey to Esmeralda and I'm kind of pissed she falls for him actually
because uh anyway wait hold on can I say one more thing about Esmeralda?
Sure.
Yes I have to.
Every woman who played that role I just have to be like you are a Wonder Woman because
that bitch comes out she dances does the fucking splits she swings around like a stripper pole.
She does like that acrobatics she's like doing all that shit and then that bitch sings um
god help the outcasts she runs down that fucking runway when she belts that note and I'm like
yes like queen and she has to do that and be a dancer and do this and like that's hard to find.
Sure.
And is the right character type like I was just like damn these women are insane like they are
so good just want to shout out to Esmeralda.
You want to be these you're out there like you this is planning the like I want to perform in
this kind of setting.
Exactly after we watched this show I would go around I don't know if you remember on like a
Sunset Boulevard in MGM I call it MGM and like there were by the bathrooms there was like this
little kind of platform thing I would always go up there and I was like five six and start singing
and dancing and people would come over and clap like I was like yeah this is like what I do right
like even though my family oppressed it until I was uh I guess still kind of uh
sorry mom if you're listening this I love you very very dearly um.
Hi Audrey.
Hi Audrey we love you.
Very curious how you figured out how to listen to this but okay.
Mom and grandma oh shit your G's.
Grandma is not hearing this.
I mean fist bump hit my glasses but mom and grandma you the OG's everybody else.
Well the jury's out who's the jury's out.
The judges will decide.
Frodo will decide who is an outcast of your family.
Me.
God help you then.
This is all sinking into your child Ray meanwhile I'm on the other side of MGM studios just like
wow Casablanca I'll have to rent that from video update when I get back to pencil.
Like all the golden age of Hollywood stuff stuck with me and some of the movie musical stuff I mean
all the Gene Kelly singing in the rain stuff.
Well it's interesting I mean we're.
I know that you brought.
Of course yeah BuzzFeed Berkeley yeah.
Yeah well I didn't see that I didn't see those until a few years ago a lot of the BuzzFeed
Berkeley stuff but some of them are on hvm acts now.
Sure.
They got bub bub Z.
Bugsy.
BuzzFeed is not topsy.
Uh yeah this is like because because we had the first those the little mermaid beauty and the
beast Aladdin lion king was my time to perform them in the living room these songs.
Nice.
So now I was and there's video of it there's video of me there's video you know what the
best video we have is actually me doing the whole Muppet movie.
Wow.
Just me so I mean with the record playing but I'm just standing there with the microphone doing
the song.
Grabbing your junk.
I was not grabbing my junk in this video I don't think maybe just a little bit but not not like
I was in the other video.
You felt safe you weren't experiencing fear.
Yeah this was just my grandmother's living room.
Yeah.
So yeah but.
That's sweet.
In front of you can't do it in front of your grandma.
No and I knew yeah I knew that too I knew I couldn't be lewd in front of my grandmother.
Uh so yeah so these Pocahontas and then this and then the others yeah they they weren't
I was I was I turned self-conscious then for these and then they just didn't they
ended up not resonating as much so it is interesting to go back and listen to
Hercules and Pocahontas and this to go home this is a good song.
The music is just so good and they get the best like singers like Judy Coon sang for
Pocahontas and she's like a Broadway like legend I mean.
The Pocahontas songs resonate with I just remember that they have more of a sense memory
for me they're more of like these songs I kind of have forgotten more and I think it's just
because the movie I was like so I was probably scared of it I wasn't like scared but like I
was just like ah it seems unpleasant to me when I watched it as a kid.
I think you're it is not crazy to as a child watch the song Hellfire and want to get it out
of your brain as quickly as possible.
Can we talk about Hellfire just yeah of course sadly not included in the no they cut it but
that shit is crazy so basically Frollo's like I'm horny she must die and he literally says in the
song it's not my fault and like she'll be mine or she will burn so it's fucking wild also like very
familiar to what I grew up being told like so I think that's like I don't know I just scary
Catholicism if you do anything as a woman you're really bad you should feel very guilty just from
birth you suck you can't do anything Frollo is a terrifying character like they have set him he is
essentially committing genocide for years for decades he says like in the movie and then this
Hellfire song is like yeah it opens like that I mean it's good it's good but it's terrible but
it's beautiful but heaven's light though that's kept in the show I cry like I will cry right
now thinking about it it's so beautiful he's just like longing for this thing and like love
oh I don't want to talk about it okay I'll cry um oh I was just gonna say with any of these um like
Disney 35 45 minute versions of these shows which they really started what was the first was the
Beauty and the Beast the first one that was kind of around for a while I think it was because like
they because they then this is sort of became a template for the shows because obviously Aladdin
they did forever and they're doing one of the Frollo's gone closed it yeah uh hope maybe come
back I don't know but uh it's almost like sometimes when I'm watching these and over the years watching
them they would be from the movie so you would take it for granted like the production of them
if that makes sense in the sense that it's they're so strict to the actual movie as like when I was
watching them as a kid or even now you just kind of go oh yeah it's like an abridged version of
the movie not even actually appreciating the production aspects of it as much at least that's
when I was younger when I didn't have a podcast to think about this type of thing you go oh yeah
yeah it's like being the beast we saw that okay I've seen that in the movie okay I get that yeah
but to adapt it to adapt it is like a got a major pain in the ass and then to also like
truncate it has to be a pain in the ass too how do you do it all and give everybody all the stuff
they want from the movie yeah they love so I'm saying I appreciate all of these versions a
little more because it's got to be kind of hard to do all of it harder than I would even imagine
well and what's interesting too is because they dropped on the same day that means they were in
rehearsals and learning music that wasn't even out to the public yet unless they released the
album before the movie I don't know that but they would usually a little a little early I think you
know what I mean like they're learning about these characters in this story that isn't even out yet
so from like a performer perspective I mean that would be really cool like this isn't even out yet
and I'm gonna be this character like that's pretty epic like you're playing them alongside them that's
cool yeah yeah well go ahead no no no um one more thing that Esmeralda is like she's awesome um
the the singing voice of Esmeralda in the movie is the only job this girl ever did and she like
fell to the face of the earth I guess they found her like singing somewhere in LA when they're
making the movie and they were like do you want to do this she sings it very like soft and tenderly
and doesn't really belt it and then the stage show it is like balls to the wall she is belting to
Jesus she is like here is my high note hire me right now and I'm so glad they did that because
it is just so much better but as a little factoid that girl like sang the song and then was just like
bye really wow huh seems really good it's so weird right she's such an iconic song that everybody
like everybody knows everybody knows that song everybody I know knows that song my musical theater
friends know that sure sure um I don't want to give Jason an emotional heaven's light can't talk
for a second moment but I do want to make you aware if you weren't already of something that
happened alongside of the release of the film which was the release of the McDonald's McChicken
Cordon Bleu meal um the uh you know you got quasi cups and there's Phoebus on there if I want Phoebus
on my fries and you got uh this this item is a McChicken sandwich with ham with like a thin slice
it's french yeah the movie is french yes yes cronk monsieur yeah mcronk monsieur
fries ph i-r-e freedom fries you gotta do some champions with that yeah yeah
oh yeah wait wait never mind don't do it later do it after uh you got ham you got gar
yeah you know all right ham lettuce tomato garlic cheese yeah of course yeah explain no further
McDonald's in 1996 I'm sure yeah and pull off a delicate flavor combo and smoky bacon
flavored sauce not bacon itself likely on itself brought to our local rest stop
they hired they hired flavors from around the world from around the horn every there was uh
every McDonald's they hired a french chef to sit in the kitchen and cook these yeah that's how
they did it and then they had to pay the rat on top of his head and there was tope to pull his
hair and control him they didn't have to pay him they didn't know he was under there oh okay
they had to put up with it they had to hide him yeah yeah yeah inspectors came smoky bacon flavored
this is a bizarre I just like this aesthetic on cups and this weird like cross I but I don't
Jane are you excited but like were you would you have been at McDonald's at this time and like yeah
hell of a chicken cordon bleu um I was a little fat kid I remember like getting an order of like
two big macs and two extra large fries one time and then like vomiting it up so I don't know
that would quite be my thing I remember like characters being on cups and stuff
yeah I think I still wouldn't be I mean I was again I was like four when this came out so I
maybe was a little right that might be too early as far as they're not eating a ton of chicken cordon
bleu I've had some good chicken cordon bleu I've had some bad chicken cordon bleu in my time
you know I think they should really I think that uh uh they should make a reference to it on Rick
and Morty and we can get that sandwich back oh yeah it's all in Star Wars chair like why
was it Szechuan sauce and not McChickenCordonBleu like let's get the McChickenCordonBleu back
this smoky bacon flavored sauce is very jealous of Szechuan sauce for its in my movie idea sauce
story where all sauces are alive and uh and their desire like the toys is to be consumed
and especially to be viral to go viral smoky bacon flavored at a shit year yeah yeah Szechuan
people are gonna get choked up with those Steven Schwartz lyrics about the sauces
so descriptive he fits so many adjectives in there yeah um so that's uh now look I also don't want
to sidetrack too much but uh I look I I've been skeptical in the past of the entertainment value
of this the Disney straight to video sequels I don't think I've ever had interest I'm like I
bet that's not going to be any fun to watch uh if I could quote the tagline for first Hunchback when
it came out uh Hunchback 2 join the party what the hell I recommend Hunchback you never you never
did it despite enjoying the show I think I was like a purist like I was like the sequels suck
like oh that you're correct that's no that's right in reality that's right in in my strange
poisoned brain no I love it it's just I I recommend I recommend it to you guys I recommend it to
everyone here's what here's the thing of well okay first of all it's a it's a smooth 60 minutes
nice if you take the credits out somehow qualifies as a feature film
despite being 60 at the directed by thank you Michael Eisner big dick energy
I so he
threw me so I'm flustered now uh uh Hunchback 2 it's if you if you get tired of if you get
exhausted by animated films where that they feel like the characters have to be moving around all
the time or like say words and then say more words without pausing arbitrarily for a while
in the middle this is if you if if you want a different flavor like a smoky bacon flavor of an
animated film I I was shocked by I like got through six minutes of it just like I want to get a get a
taste of what this is like and then stop and then I was like I gotta I bet I paused and I showed a
little to Erin and she's like can we I gotta go to bed can we save this for tomorrow like we made a
point of we we watched Hunchback of Notre Dame 2 as a family it feels like it was made in like
Croatia in 1981 by two people it's so bizarre it like could not feel lit if if you didn't know all
these characters already from a real Disney movie and you just and you've never met any of them
before you just say this is the strangest thing of ever it's like it's so bizarre and one of the
weirdest things everybody's back and these are big stars Demi Moore is back yes yeah that's usually
why I didn't like watching the sequels I genuinely didn't know that they always didn't there was
always at least one right hold out if it wasn't quite the Robin Williams level although they
ended up getting back for 11.3 but like it's funny but the he was right to not do it but I somehow
I think by then they'd cracked the contract we have to get them so Kevin Klein's back Jason
Alexander's back um there's this weird I think I've got I've had Phoebus on the brain because of this
weird part where it's not the festival of fools it's a different thing there's a different festival
that looks exactly the same like if you trade they just traced over the other one and that's
some festival where everybody yells in the town square their love like you have to like you know
so like like oh can I yell your name at the yes so it so Kevin Klein is saying how I want to see
you standing there yelling I love my husband Phoebus what the fuck is the strangest phrase
I've just been obsessed with the name because of that just like weird I don't know so audience
just watch watch Hunchback 2 if it's at me on twitter if you really like like a five second
part or just a screenshot I really recommend how you know how like there's you're in a funhouse
mirror and you look weird and distorted but maybe there can be like a reverse of that such as when
quasi looks at himself in a bell and then it corrects him and you look you get a sense of
what regular quasi would look like which is still not great but he's just kind of this like okay
it's like what he would look like if he got some corrective surgery
oh I'm gonna cry like it's corrected quasi oh anyway don't change quasi your big dick energy
just how you are did it did his dick correct it was just a bell illusion did his dick correct
his dick sucks now
yeah he gets perfect everywhere else but his dick that's like the trade-off that is yeah that's like
the guy was sky couldn't be in the garage with him because of the dick is too big in a small place
Michael you're really fixating on like dicks everyone's talking we're all dick crazy today
all right all right fine someone open the forbidden door Michael ran right through
hey I have permission yeah hey do it I'm all about it um also you get uh uh recently mentioned
Michael McKeon as evil magician Sarooch I think I love it I think I like Sarooch Sarooch is great
he's a much he's like a way muted Frollo he's like almost the same but not nearly as scary
there's a song that's just like out there but not as good there's a song where the the uh uh the
the gargoyles uh like egg him on and like hey he's great but it's not as good as the one in the if
you just want like a watered down I feel like it'd be interesting for you loving the movie you might
be furious you're you're like you're you're gonna unleash Garfield at me after you watch it you
might be mad at you he sits and just slowly closes his eyes there's no attack in he doesn't bark or
bite he just started licking like a normal dog like he'll give you kisses he started kissing
Jason and then he started doing to me the fuck you know are you got it first yeah he fucking
loves Jason man uh you know hey it's my my comrade you know he's the only the only guy
who likes to sleep more than I do and that's pretty impressive he'll sleep until like noon or later
like whatever really when is how long can he go without a bathroom break forever really he we
won't only once or twice is he like woken us up he wants to sleep eight o'clock seven in the morning
every morning for five years yeah well never know what that's like with this guy yeah thank you um
just sleeping I don't know that we'll be able to get uh Jane to I don't know that I'll be able to
pull the like honey we're let's watch hunchback too because I already pulled the oh my birthday
I'm like I want to watch master disguise another if you're if you're stepping through
maybe the same year at least early 2000s yeah cheap not full length feature films
I think they're part and part of their I think you can't watch one without the other I say
master of let's get this set up at the new Beverly they do the double features here in LA
35 millimeter yeah yeah let's let's get the prince if there ever was such a thing of hunchback too
yeah and you know some of those you know watching two great movies in a row sounds nice but then
you're there for a long time because great movies are long often you're out of like you would be in
and out of master and discover master disguise plus uh hunchback too before other people were
out of the one one movie an entire dune is passed and you've watched two quality films instead you
could have a pre-show of turning turtle the scene from mary pavins too to just to get the length
longer oh yeah like when they use the old like yeah yeah let's go out to the lobby shorts you
just put the turning turtle that's right yeah there or like an old like droopy dog short
yeah that sounds good folks if you're gonna turn turtle do it out in the lobby do it in the lobby
enjoy our feature presentation can I ask a quick question this might be too personal
we're moving to side when you decide to watch a movie how does it work is there a negotiation
uh like because yeah I we're all guilty like with me and jace yeah yeah sorry um we're all like
sometimes i'll be like i want to watch this very annoying thing and then sometimes we're pretty
cool with each other i feel like well we early on when we were dating you you made it clear that
you weren't like the biggest movie buff i hated watching movies it sounded like you i kind of i
can't i'm better at it now you are better at it now but you had made it sound like you went on a
lot of dates with guys who insisted you watched pulp fiction and i was like yeah i know that i
have seen that i should probably not tell that story basically a guy stopped hooking up with me
because i was like i don't think i like that and he just dropped my ass and i was like you
weren't even that cool anyway but i was like i don't think i like this and he was like how dare
you it's pulp fiction it's like the best and i was like bye like the fuck man yes that's very
strange and inhuman so i don't that's crazy you do that for pulp fiction that's you you do that
for boondock saints that's the line in the sand yeah that's the coolest yeah yeah but for like
watching stuff so a lot of times we like test out a show or something together right and if one of
us is more into it i'll go i'll watch this without you and you can kind of watch on your own is that
cool okay yeah like we don't really have a lot of shows that we're like we must watch together
the one thing we must watch together is this youtube channel called las vegas inside and out
shout out to dale and paula mckenzie yeah this is i don't think it's ever come up this is every
sunday morning we watch this there it's an elderly couple in las vegas who review all the casinos
and the hotels and stuff and they like everything and a lot of their coffee is clearly coming from
the casino website but they're really good sports he has like a sub character named
durango dale that pops in and she does paula's kitchen what do you mean a sub yeah what does
that mean like like a cowboy voice like and then durango dale and they'll cut to him he's like hey
i'm durango oh wow he's got personas yeah because he kind of buries this lead i think he's like a
little self-conscious about it but i think it's fascinating because he he was a vegas performer
he was a singer he was a country music singer for years like decades as well just no just as
no he's just like digging around and like so his name is like in 10 foot high letters on the dune
sign and it's like why aren't you i want to know all about you like i think this level of argument
for something we just learned about uh 50 seconds ago they sent me like merch they've sent me yeah
they sent pens and stickers and stuff and shit we we kept an eye out for them in vegas oh yeah
they sent me yeah last year i got them to send a birthday video last year no i i joined their
patreon i was like hi because they were doing like personalized videos and shit i was like hey
oh it's my boyfriend's birthday i was wondering if you could do a video and they did you're so cute
this is this is such a it's an old other niche it is like in the world there's the theme park
media world that a lot of people may never know about there's also a massive world of vegas
vegas media people reviewing slot machines like reviewing casinos reviewing slot machines there's
footage on youtube of just people 30 minutes of someone playing a slot machine and it's our
favorite thing to watch when we get balls high at night we put this shit on and we are cruising
so yeah we don't watch a lot of movies but we watch a lot of uh and there's also a lot of those
we watch reviews of slot machines yes we love that we've all watched all five seasons of riverdale
yeah can i can i ask when you're reviewing a slot machine what are the things that people talk about
he watches those ones more than i do i like just like the i also like to walk around once
i i'm just if i'm doing if i'm if i'm doing like working on the computer do they review the graphics
do they review the mechanism by which you would the big one slot as opposed to the three i think
i'm in a three slot at one point in time there's a big trend in the graph video graphics sort of
like i played a blake shelton slot machine a few years ago and they have more of like a kind of
a mini game like sheldon or young sheldon because there is both i wouldn't i'm sure there is both
yeah there is no there's big bang theory there's a big bang there's for sure young blake sheldon
there's a giant dune setup there's a dune slot machine already wait is that real are you joking
there's there's a big timothy chalamet uh dune slot machine right next to this is willy wonka
machine yeah i think there because there's there's definitely sharks there's like guys who are like
and this is how you bet on time and i don't really like those but like i like the videos where people
like all right i have a hundred dollars in free play i'm gonna see how much i can win we love
free play yeah you can't really walk away with free free play you can generate money that you walk
away with but you can't it's credit it's credit to play so you guys glorifying gambling judge
frollo would have his way while you fire these gamblers soon will burn we should be so lucky
like sheldon's slot machines
is
we saw them at a pizza place uh yeah we were sitting next to them at picnic tables and i was
like is that fucking guinstevani doing homework with her kids were they getting along or did it
seem he was like do you finish your pizza do your homework like he was he was a little oh no but he
he said something real sus member he was like he was a little firm a little too firm about
getting his daughter and i was like did you hear him say that was it his daughter was it uh gavin
rostale's daughter no i don't think he would talk to gavin rostale's daughter i actually have no idea
but i just remember his energy being weird and hers she is beautiful guinstevani is ageless like
whoever does your work girl 12 out of 10 well we were about five like five ten minutes from the
voice sound stages so they might have just come from you're eating pizza on the sony lot actually
he was eating pizza i was just with garfield i don't know you had something to go to and i don't
know it was a weird it was a weird like situation where i was like what the hell is going on right
now like it wasn't yeah it was weird well yeah one of us was eating the dog was investigating
give him a scoop yeah i mean i i went to voicemail he doesn't return my calls anymore
since i made fun of his arms weird arms this all his scoops are about some dead actors estate sale
and some old some puppies selling these aren't worthy of the front page yeah we need we need hot
scoops yeah not these old dusty scoops garfield what do you have to say do you have anything to
say garfield is sleeping here he's kind of sleeping sitting up and he really is he's got
yeah we were talking about if he would say anything on mike but he he he did you hear him breathe he
just breathed uh i did not sometimes he breathed he's sleeping he looks from he looks a little um
um like a uh mogwai from gremlins he does look a little mogwai yeah yeah very cute um it's a long
does you're like you carried that out like a note and because i was like wait which one is that
again and i was like oh that was finding it wait is that the little guy you got me for christmas
it's the guy i got you from christmas so i have these like three little i keep talking i know you
got it but i have these three little guys that i didn't know who they were before i met jason what
do i have i have rocky raccoon i brought you stuff back from like i call him rocky raccoon i know i
got you rocky rocky raccoon we were down there for marvel opening day gremlin what is his name
gizmo i wish you got her a plush from the beetle a beetle song what is the third
oh the third is a pork a pork so i didn't know what a pork was i didn't know what gremlins were
i didn't know what rocky raccoon was and now i know you didn't know we're done
are you there best creature in the galaxy
oh i'm laughing he eats them
garfy still quiet hunchback of notredame musical at disney mgm studios what else do we have to say
about this performance about this uh this production well i had a thing that i i think
one of the reasons because i asked my dad i was like do you remember seeing that he's like and
we both had the same like i think we saw that and i looked up a map from like 96 97 and it's it was
the it was in the back lot theater um and it was kind of behind the muppets and now that area
appears to be uh nothing on the map or at best it's like access roads show building stuff for
uh galaxy's edge and you demolish right right yeah yeah i don't remember seeing this i was
definitely there twice when it would have been around and i don't i unless i totally forgot i
don't believe we saw 96 to 2002 i don't think we have a run not nearly as long as disneyland
i think i think like and that was a big thunder ranch one right yeah yeah that's what it was that
area sort of stayed but sat vacant for a long time and you'd see it from the train like that
looks like a big exciting venue for a live show what is it not that yeah it's an empty place
and now that is also that is part of galaxy's edge right so these hunchback spots have been
torn down um does this make you do you think it had its time that's a big good bit's a pretty big
run it had a really good run i think because it was a solid show i mean i was watching clips from
when it first opened and then like 2000 2001 2002 and they had it it was like set there you go every
show was like solid i don't know like they really figured it out and didn't have to change a lot
because i think sometimes with theme park shows you start one way and there's like oh you work
out the kinks but this show i think they like nailed it and then went until the contract was
over with whatever disney wanted or whatever yeah probably a expensive show to operate that many
like actors probably well there's special effects and there's stunt work i don't have to pay people
for stunt work like stunts and puppets yeah i mean they're really the only thing that i could
think to add to a show like this to plus it up would be topical references if the gargoyles
would have who's the guy to do i guess it's the jason alexander i think it's the jason alexander
gargoyle but all i think the gargoyles i guess could have done it i'm like glaring at michael
right now that's fair but this is just my taste this is my personal taste uh is that if they
could have made you know jokes about cloning sheep uh or uh whatever else happened in 1996
six or seven uh yeah that would have been i'm sorry to stay on the in this area but the
the invention of viagra great you'd have to dance around it but yeah you couldn't say what it might
might be a way to allude
there's that pill that makes the guys harder than we are hard and stone
yeah that's exactly what i'm talking about that would have i think they could have probably gotten
a few more years out of the show if they had done something like that and uh and really because then
the people would come you'd always have reason to come back which is genius of the aladdin show
is there was always a reason to come back to see what genie was going to roast this week
sure everyone would leave saying well we gotta come back we gotta come back we gotta reason
first yeah we gotta come back yeah to see what it appears that what replaced this um well this
replay there was a pocahontas show in this space beforehand and then like it was a little hard
to tell what replaced this because but it seemed like the verdict was just special events it was
a special event stage that kind of sat empty unless they had something going on corporate
event or something yeah in this area yeah disneyland one too this was a hunchback like uh
somehow torched the no nobody could follow it salted the earth nothing could grow one more thing
at the time they also had this ice cream bar i'm saying this for my mom because i talked to her
about this i was like mom do you remember the show and she's like oh i'm gonna start crying and i was
like yes thank you but um she was like there was this ice cream bar and it was called like the
hunchback bar and it was like ice cream dipped in caramel dipped in chocolate and like they sold
it with like mickey bars and for a while when the show was running they had it and then they stopped
so i wanted to mention that and also i'm looking up yeah oh yeah i couldn't find a picture of it i
looked and then also i wanted to say they sometimes would have sign language interpreters and they
would have usually like a guy and a girl and they did every character and like so amazingly well and
that was my mom was like those people were so good i could cry like the show was just really
overwhelming in a good way to watch like everyone just like went hard so i think watching on youtube
like i'm i'm just honestly so sad that you guys will never get to see it i'm not being sarcastic
like it is i'm sad you will never get to see it like live it was so good wow is it um would you
say that even the the movie itself is like your favorite movie still of the disney of like well i
really like alice in wonderland mostly when i'm high i like to watch alice in wonderland because
i'm like this guy gets it um which doesn't even have any slot machine the guy who wrote it i don't
know oh louis carol you mean yeah okay sometimes i'm a little dense is that what a delivery
what a delivery on that thank you um i think like this caterpillar gets it or something yeah well
the caterpillar because i guess he's hookah and yeah and i whenever i go on the alice ride if i go
by him i'm like pay my respects so yeah i think um hunchback's probably my favorite i would yeah i
think i'm back to my favorite i like alice but that's a newer thing that's a newer i'd never
really watched all day through and then like more recently i watched it and and man get
fucked up and watch alice you will feel so crazy like dumb and dumber come out and you're like what
the fuck is going on like again i am sometimes not the smartest um dense and denser
a lot of things but jason is more book smart and so sometimes i say some really dumb shit you know
just because jason could name the actor robert mitcham it doesn't mean he's smart okay he just
said no some hard lesson to learn michael i came with like 35 that that's sitting just because
he knows some old actors don't don't get the idea i know new stuff that he doesn't know i teach him
new stuff oh yes yeah we know because he'll come into the episode with some phrases that we don't
know and like well where's he getting that i don't know what's gonna pass it off i you well just
casually slip it in as if we won't just like get a radar on it like what was that he said a thing
what was it that's a cool phrase he said sicko mode once in life
i say like i would say nagarfi you getting so hypey you go to the hypey house i say to him
he starts jumping around i say hypey hype house who made who made hypey hype house what is that
from well hype house that's where like the influencers live they live in hype house like
yeah that's what an influencer's house is called again so hypey it's like a dumb dj like party thing
this is scott's house we're sitting in that garage of scott's hype house yeah i guess in
this setting this is a hype house and we've all yeah we're in a hype house we've all got as cool
as he can right now we're in a hype house i see i think i get it we're in a hype house we've been
getting hypey jake paul and logan paul are in the living room they're beating the shit out of each
other they don't get along one of them is convinced they're in combat sports now and apparently are
so some people might not invite them to their hype house but i look when you know two beasts
are gonna go sicko mode what am i gonna say now oh boy levy eugene levy talking about hype house
that's what i'm i'm just my transition into a levy is the beginning uh uh jane by helping us
celebrate the hunchback spirit you have gotten us all hypey this evening jane clare you survived
podcasts the ride the second gate thank you so much thank you uh let's exit to the gift shop is
there anything you would like to plug um i released some music over the summer i released an ep um
that's streaming everywhere uh jane clare j-a-y-n-e i'm sure you'll see that but um yeah so if you want
to stream that um i'm on instagram so okay i have to say this because it's really bothering me i
you are the only one right now like i like redid my instagram and all this shit so my page only has
like 100 followers so i'm telling you that right now so i don't look like a total loser but it's
um at jane clare official j-a-y-n-e please follow it so i um i shouldn't be worried about this my
therapist is working on this with me but get your stats well i'm just saying i'm working again i'm
working on it my therapist is like stop getting validation from others and i just refuse um and
then i'm also on twitter i don't i don't understand twitter i always try to post pictures
and jason is like twitter isn't a picture place i'm like yeah but like garford looks cuter i look
really hot like you can post pictures on twitter you can post pictures but you're like why isn't
getting more likes i'm like you'll get more likes on a picture on instagram like it's like
i know or i'm just like i don't this isn't yeah i don't know but i am on twitter jane clare eight
um okay great go up jane's stats but that's not but not so they're really meaning validation
because we need to let's that's a message we should take from yeah quasi he found what he needed
inside himself yes although in the second film he does find love with a beautiful magician's
assistant what okay whose problem is that she is too beautiful and people think that that's all
she's good for is to stand around i'm not as marlowe i'm that one what's the character's name
do i forget she's voiced by jennifer love hewitt the memorable voice of jennifer love hewitt who
sings a song that is kicked to the credits you get there you're gonna have the credit wait we
have to have the credit song of hunchback what's the credit song of what is the credit someday by
all for one someday i totally forgot you're right when we are wise there's a beth middler sings on
the uh she sings god help the outcast yes she does but all for one singing someday my we sang
it in like high school choir and um so that's how i really know it but uh it's so good it is good i
was like this might be my favorite version of any of the songs just the all for one yes for sure i
had to get that in there sorry i had an amount of your amount of excited finger wiggling at bed
middle and beth middler had a song in there also i had in my head so i forgot to mention that yeah
betty makes me hypey the seer hunchback i got hypey i don't know god that's so funny what he said
then we gotta go out on that i'm not gonna talk madeline is the voice of jennifer love hewitt's
character yeah madeline and is the song better than her single bare naked that she released
in the early 2000s
yeah i was a big yeah big guy makes me hypey yeah j l hui that's what i've always called her
that's right the ghost whisper yeah she's a witcher what's the name again madeline
madeline yeah and she is a character name she michael mccann the evil magician thinks that
all she's good for is being as a magician's assistant standing there and looking pretty
but she wants to be a tightrope walker okay and spoiler she gets her chance just when phoebus
needs her the most all right my favorite mathematically correct sure that's my favorite movie
i'm so pleased okay so you know don't even no plugs for us watch hunch will go to disney plus
watch hunchback of notredame 2 send me any parts that you like because i want to see all my friends
again i gotta watch this tonight we're mostly the old friends but also i think so you'll all be
furious and me probably i don't like it spirit i get the giddiness that i have magician's assistant
double feature billy toffett oh my god no this i cannot apply he made me watch that too oh i did
make you watch billy toffett this makes me so uncomfortable like did this come out like 20
years ago like and he's like no that's the problem wait what that would excuse some things but
yeah yeah yeah hunch back to check it out join the party thanks for listening everybody
thanks for getting hypey bye bye bye