Five, four, three, two, one.
Hey, Disney Imagineers, get bent.
We've got a new favorite set of ride makers
and it's Sally Dark Rides.
This is podcast The Ride, the second gate.
I'm Scott Gardner, Mike Carlson with us as always.
I'm with you as always and I wanna back up
what you're saying.
Eat shit, Disney Imagineers.
You are nothing but dirt to me.
You're nothing but dirt, dirt in the dirt.
That's what I say.
After what we've learned, what we have to bring
to the table today, a great set of rides
from a great set of guys, which also includes
Jason Sheridan, hi.
Hi, yeah, this will be fun.
This has been like a recurring company
that keeps coming up on the show
and a number of times recently.
Yeah, exactly and then that's sort of what we're doing
here today.
So just to say it at the top, we are focusing
on a group called Sally Dark Rides.
If you're an avid listener and you really pay attention,
you might have heard us talk about them.
You might have heard attractions come up here and there
that they did.
Basically, what has kept happening is
if there is a non, typically a non-Disney,
non-universal place that has a dark ride
that is somewhat strange, very often it is made
by Sally Dark Rides.
They've been in it for decades and what's happening today
is we're gonna talk a little about the company
and some of the stuff they've done,
but mainly the three of us, we have each picked
a different strange ride from the collection
of Sally Dark Rides and we're gonna sort of surprise
the others with it.
I think we might know the tiniest amount,
but mainly we're all, we're doing a little potluck
of dark ride information and I'm excited.
I'm excited to share mine.
I'm excited for what you guys have.
I truly have no idea.
Yes, I got very excited doing this
because there's, if you don't know anything,
yeah, we kind of mentioned it,
but this company has done so many things for decades.
So going back through, there's so many things
that I was like, well, maybe I'll talk about this,
maybe we'll talk about this and there were literally
10 things I could have picked, I feel like,
that we could have talked about,
but I decided to pick something that I have experienced.
I'll say that as a tease.
Oh, that's good.
I didn't realize Sally was behind it.
This is how much Sally is in our lives,
is that I experienced something as a youth
that Sally was responsible for.
So I say thank you to Sally for what I will be sharing.
When I was very young.
I think I have a guess as what it is.
If I can say, I think one of the notable things about Sally
and I wasn't quite sure what to call this,
and then I got their latest email newsletter
because I'm on their listserv,
because in 2020, a lot of the theme park industry
conventions had to go digital,
so anyone could attend them throughout the world.
And I watched some presentations and visited digital booths
where you could look at pitch documents and blueprints.
And so there it is. Digital booths.
Digital booths, that's right.
And they're Ioppa, one of the trade groups,
is having an in-person convention this year.
Actually, as this episode is coming out, it just passed.
But Sally sent out their email promoting it.
And a big part of the email was discussing
their turnkey process.
And this is their language.
From dark rides to animated productions,
we use our turnkey capabilities
to create unforgettable attractions from start to finish.
And then there's a little graphic
about how they designed the story,
the design of the attraction, the build of the attraction,
and the installation.
And a lot of this stuff, too,
is customizable to people's budgets,
parks' budgets, and park spaces.
And I think this is where they make their bread and butter.
This is where smaller parks can get a little taste
of a bigger park dark ride experience.
A little taste.
Wait, what does turnkey, though, mean in that context?
Okay, turnkey is a phrase,
it literally means a product that is ready to go.
You are handed the key, and it's like you were given a car.
You put the key in, turn it on, it's ready to drive.
Got it, okay, okay, yeah, yeah.
So all set, like a fully furnished house or apartment.
This is their way of saying,
listen, park that never deals with stuff like this,
we got it, don't worry about it.
Yeah, so if you're cutting a check
to put a Ghost Blasters in your park,
a Ghost Blasters ride, one of their rides,
they're ready to go.
And in addition to the original properties,
they have IPs they work with.
They've been commissioned,
they have made proof of concept stuff
for like Aardman Attract, like Shaun the Sheep,
or Five Nights at Freddy's, a video game that
gets brought up to us a lot.
And they had the Goosebumps license for a while,
and even made, here, I'll share the screen real quick.
They even made a slappy animatronic of like,
here's what the pre-show animatronic would be.
Oh yeah.
There's like a little carnival barker, Slappy.
Slappy is the dummy.
Yes, the Knight of the Living Dummy, I think it is.
Yes.
The haunted ventriloquist dummy
shows up in a bunch of Goosebumps.
Gotcha.
He's not Caesar from Twilight Zone, he's Slappy.
That's right.
Yes, he's not Slappy.
So they've worked with IPs,
so they would make a ride fully ready to go
for some of these IPs, and just in some cases,
these have not been commissioned anywhere officially
and not built.
Yeah, that's correct.
They have a big, on their website,
showing all their Ioppa presentation,
their booths through the ages,
and in the 80s, they had done Care Bear shows
at a few parks, and they even had a design and concept
for a Ghostbusters ride, but not the one
that Bally's was making that we talked about
on a previous show, the Filmation Ghostbusters,
the one with the gorilla.
The one with Tracy the Gorilla.
The other Ghostbusters.
Yeah.
Wow.
This was a mind blow that came from,
this might have been from a friend of the show,
Kyle Mooney, who told me that they,
we know that thing about how there was the Ghostbusters
and then the real Ghostbusters,
and they had to call the Ghostbusters cartoon
the real Ghostbusters because there was this other
Ghostbusters property.
This is sort of known.
What I didn't know is that the other Ghostbusters
involved a gorilla and that it was based on a film
that also had, Ghostbusters existed already
in live action form before, I mean, really,
they are the real Ghostbusters, honestly,
if they were to it in two mediums
well before the Dan Aykroyd version.
It was like decades before.
I believe they called them,
one was the real Ghostbusters
and one was the original Ghostbusters.
Is that right?
Maybe.
I don't know about original.
I think it was a TV show.
I think it was like a chintzy,
like Sid and Marty Croft produced a TV show.
Oh, okay, okay.
It was a black and white thing.
Oh, you're right, not a film.
No, yeah, 1975 kids.
Okay, okay, yeah.
Okay, like less than a little over a decade.
Yeah, that's so, I actually missed that.
I would like to see that
because I was a big fan of both
Ghostbusters cartoons as a child.
Yeah.
I liked the gorilla one.
I have zero familiarity with the other.
I do not know the other one whatsoever.
Yeah.
We had toys.
We had toys from the other one.
I just always, always purchased dirty at a garage sale,
but we had the guys.
I didn't have, I'm jealous of that.
I gotta get my hands on those.
Or somebody's gotta make new versions.
NECA or Super Seven's gotta get on making me
an original Ghostbusters line of toys.
So yeah, Jason, yeah, they've done, I saw that.
There's like a weird Care Bear show I watched from the 80s.
The bears look nightmarish.
The show is-
Was that me?
Does that exist somewhere?
There's a show.
Dorni Park?
Yeah, Dorni Park.
It's a robot show.
The bears all look like something's wrong
and it's really, it looks scary.
At least just the way the video is,
but I'm very impressed by that.
There's like Flintstone rock and roll show.
I don't know if you saw that.
It's Fred and Wilma and Dino playing instruments
and it's just a little Chuck E. Cheese Flintstone show.
Where did that exist, do we know?
That might have been at the Bedrock,
the Bedrock, what is that, like the little roadside spot?
Oh yeah, it's kind of a desert play, like now abandoned?
Yeah, something like that.
I'm pretty fuzzy on this.
I don't think I know, I don't have my facts straight
about this Flintstones thing.
I don't either.
I saw a little bit of the video and I was like,
well, that's weird.
So it's just, you can find so many bizarre things
in the, like on the website too.
It's just a lot of it's on the website,
a lot of it's on their YouTube
and you can get a little history for just how much stuff
this company has been involved in.
This is, here's my big theory I'm gonna present.
If we want to, as we're want to do sometimes,
put things in rock and roll terms.
When we got to introduce Tony Baxter in our live show,
we called him the Mick Jagger of, I don't know,
of attractions, I don't know what the general umbrella is,
but I think that's correct.
He's the rock star, he's the icon.
He's never listened to a Rolling Stone song,
but he is the Mick Jagger for sure.
Through context clues, he would understand.
Yeah, yeah, I think he understood
that kind of reference, yeah.
But I think Sally Dark Rides,
I'm gonna invoke one of my favorite bands
and say that Sally Dark Rides
is like the sparks of ride makers.
They are, they've been around for decades.
They are this odd, it's this weird singular body of work.
It's like incredibly strange and they don't chase trends.
They've just been plugging away quietly.
Sometimes some of the things spike,
oh, I've heard of that one, but then they just,
it's back to the grind.
They keep cranking out their odd body of work.
Or it's like whatever you wanna fill in
for the syndrome I just described.
They're like the Zappa of ride makers.
Whatever, it's the weirdo oddball
doesn't need to be part of the mainstream.
Although they might, if people from Sally Dark Rides
listen to this, they might not agree.
We're not trying to be some cult entity.
We're trying to sell rides and be a business,
which they are and do very well.
Well, like, yeah, Sparks wasn't out against
doing a song, a Disney song or something.
Oh yes, they happily did.
Yeah, I'm trying to bridge that
because it's like they do Justice.
Songs for terrible movies, like the movie Rad,
which is in a, I think they perform in an amusement park.
So this is fairly accurate.
Justice League, that's a big property.
Six Flags, a big park, a big franchise.
So yeah, so they do stuff like that too.
Justice League, well, they have hits today.
Justice League Battle for Metropolis is their,
the rhythm thief.
It's a 2000s entry that's surprisingly strong.
Reese's Cup Fusion, I guess, would be there.
When do I get to sing My Way?
I'll try to keep forming these.
Yeah, yeah, that's good.
And it's, there's so much stuff.
We were talking a little bit about just picking one each,
but there were a couple things.
I don't know if you guys, if this is too,
am I getting ahead of myself?
I found just a couple quick things that I just,
I love so much because I'll say this
about what my choice is today.
It is not a dark ride.
So maybe I'm already blowing it.
Maybe I'm blowing the rules here.
I apologize.
I had to do it though.
No, no, no, and they,
I think there's that brand Sally Dark Rides,
but I think it's also the Sally Corporation.
Yes.
So they are not, I even thought about saying that,
that feel free to pick as your choice
for your little book report, a single animatronic.
There are those.
You're gonna say some quick hits.
Mine's such a quick hit.
I might as well just throw it out very quickly.
Actually, there's two, two single animatronics.
I was, it blew up my brain to find out
that they made the animatronic of Lyndon Baines Johnson
that's at the LBJ library in Austin, Texas,
which I saw in person when I was 15.
It's one of the weirdest things ever.
It's a pretty standard kind of sleepy presidential library.
Then you're around a corner and then there's LBJ
leaning up against a post telling stories.
I always thought it was so strange.
Then, oh my God, they made it.
And then check this.
I feel like this is gonna be very well received
with all you guys, if you didn't see it already,
they made an animatronic of Elsie the Borden Cow.
Oh, oh baby.
I knew Jason loved the Borden Cow.
How could you not?
Dairy mascot.
I hunted for a video of this, but I couldn't find it.
Oh, damn.
Beautiful photo.
She's, yeah, I don't, she's a lovely cow, I guess.
Elsie's iconic neck wreath of daisies.
We all know this about Elsie the Cow.
And then they supposed that Elsie the Cow,
this is what, if you're looking at a photo
of Elsie the Borden Cow, you would know what it was,
but maybe not if you hear it out loud.
But suffice it to say,
fantastic animatronic for a great IP.
Fantastic.
So yeah, Quick Hits.
I found that just that they, yeah,
they do like little shows.
There's a show in Nashville,
or I believe at Nashville in a hotel,
I don't know if you guys saw this,
called the Cross-eyed Critters,
where you can do karaoke with three animals.
Like an animal band.
And I don't even, that's not even in my list.
You'd think I would have wanted to play that the most,
but it's just, that's just how much like
different kinds of experience,
different types of experiences they're doing.
But here, let me, they've been doing stuff like this,
or sort of outside of the genre of like theme parks
and stuff for a little while.
So here, let me do this.
I don't know if you saw this.
This is an animatronic character named Sally at the piano.
Here we go.
["Southern Nights"]
She's talented, good-looking,
and an entertainer par excellence.
Meet Sally, our piano playing lady.
It's a department store mannequin.
It's not even like her to me.
Sally's realistic, good looks, lovely voice,
and piano playing finesse have surprised and delighted
many restaurant, hotel, and lounge guests across the nation.
This is 1984, so it's not all that surprising
to see a robot singing and playing the piano.
Like Sally's been doing here at Gene's restaurant
in the Tudor Hotel since Tuesday.
The Tudor Hotel?
She's fantastic.
She plays good music.
She's attractive.
First class all the way.
All right, calm down.
Thank you.
She's always sober, doesn't take breaks,
and even comes with a warranty.
And they zoom in on a newspaper that says,
and give the lady a screwdriver.
Sally is a guaranteed winner.
Available for booking into your place today.
So play it again, Sally.
Wow.
Terrifying.
Just a terrifying mannequin robot playing piano
in like a hotel or a department store.
This was sort of their big idea, I think, at the time.
Terribly dead-eyed and kind of like,
but also creepily made up.
Like it looks like a made-up corpse.
And I called the Borden cow lovely,
but they call this robot lady lovely or attractive
like three times in this video for some reason.
Sober.
She's got a damn blush like the other piano players.
I think, yeah.
Not gonna drain this bar of its booze
like everyone else we hire.
But you might think, okay.
Family musicians.
Sally has probably thought,
okay, that's kind of an odd thing.
We probably won't do something like that.
We won't update that.
You are incorrect.
How about DJ Sally in the year 2021?
Yes.
It's like Sia hair, Sivir bangs.
And she's just like lazily listening to headphones
that she's holding.
Much like less.
Kind of like silver, like Lady Gaga costume.
And then a DJ booth that has the Sally Dark Rides logo on it.
Yeah.
And this is not, this is basically it.
The robot actually is less good than the original.
She doesn't do that much.
But obviously they're thinking the same thing here
is that if you wanna rent a robot to DJ a party, you can.
That's what Sally Dark Rides or Sally Corporation
can do for you in your party or hotel.
So that's a little quick hit there.
I love it.
Do you think they've ever entertained the sex doll market?
Do you think they've ever had discussions with,
yeah, they must have.
Yeah, they call it some other brand.
It's like they translate Sally into another language.
And then like, so it's a related name
but you wouldn't recognize it immediately.
But, cause I watched this very miserable documentary
about like individuals trying to make realistic sex dolls
in their garages.
Like, and this is from, it was very seedy
and British and from 13 years ago.
So you're watching all these like robot creatures
that wanna be put out of their misery,
little like spasm for no reason and just start like,
like their eyes roll back in their head,
like they're possessed.
Unpleasant.
And I just know these people would be toiling away
in their garage, putting, using hammer and nail
to make a realistic vagina.
They're like, if only we could get Sally.
There is.
I really upset you with that.
It was an upsetting, it's an upsetting thought.
It's an upsetting thought, yes, for sure.
But there's gotta be a file folder in a file cabinet
somewhere that's like in case of emergency,
like there was probably deep in COVID,
they were like, if we don't recover,
we have to maybe pivot to a different market.
And they thought about it.
There were days when deep in the pandemic,
when they were like, well, maybe,
and they pulled it out and somebody like the boss
like hit it out of the, like, Bill, we're not doing that.
I told you, it's not that bleak yet.
He's like, you're crazy.
The company is gonna go under if we don't do this.
And there was a huge argument.
And then like, luckily like cooler heads prevailed
and then the company sort of got back on track.
But there's no, there's no reason,
there's no way they haven't thought about it.
That is plan Z, understood?
Yeah. Not plan B.
You don't wait for, you don't pull that out
after eight months. Yeah.
You do it after 10 years of zero business.
It's a suicide mission.
We'll never be able to make Yosemite Sam animatronics again.
Are you crazy?
You can't come back from that.
You can't just suddenly switch from sex dolls
to Paw Patrol.
Are you out of your mind?
It's like a fist fight ensues in the Sally offices.
Look, Yosemite Sam as is, is like waist height.
So if we had to take the existing robots.
No, no, no, no, god damn it.
Change their function.
You sick freak.
You never mix the IP with our weird sex ideas.
Mute his Zoom window, mute his Zoom window.
We'll call him Sequoia Steve, we'll change it.
What did you, wait, what did you say?
That's wait, that's a brilliant idea.
Now it works.
Yeah, now, yeah, of course, of course.
This all has happened.
Every bit of this has happened.
I mean, it's an immense body of work
with strange moments throughout.
Let me list a few just to like get them out of the way.
The ones that we're not gonna talk about for a while,
but just to give you a sense of a little bit of the history.
I mentioned LBJ.
We've mentioned Justice League Battle for Metropolis,
which I think was considered a surprisingly good dark ride.
Six Flags First Reel committed venture into that territory.
So that's a big success for them lately.
They have come up on other episodes
because of a ride called Mine of Lost Souls
at Canobie Lake Park, which we talked about
when we did New Hampshire theme parks.
In the same episode, we talked about,
I was so delighted by this ride,
the great Humbug Adventure.
This shooting gallery ride with Scrooge
where Humbugs are real and you got a fired lasers at them.
I forget, or it was like chocolates
or I don't remember how it works.
A ride, I don't remember how much we talked about it
with Kelly Nugent and the Santa Cruz Beach Boardwalk,
but they did a ride called the Haunted Castle up there
that I think people are fond of.
Two Hershey Park rides,
which we gotta delve a little deeper into Hershey.
We can maybe we just piece off these rides
because they did a fascinating ride and its replacement.
First they did Reese's Extreme Cup Challenge
with like a X Games type event,
which I remember having like very creepy humanoid
Dick Vitale-esque play-by-play announcers.
Yeah, yeah.
And then they remastered it.
They remastered it like the Paul McCartney,
like the collection of the solo albums.
No, no, the solo albums that came with a bonus discs
of like McCartney and McCartney 2 and the Wings record.
Right, right, right.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, then they flipped it around
and turned it into Reese's Cup Fusion,
which I don't know a lot about offhand.
I just really liked the name.
That one might be,
probably the least essential or interesting stuff they do
is like a lot of parks shooting gallery rides,
some of which, you know,
as we found with some of what Knott's has done,
maybe you do need the Disney caliber and budget
to really pull those off,
although we found some charming other examples,
but I could be wrong.
Reese's Cup Fusion might be as great as its name.
It's a very good name.
Big one too, oddly they haven't talked about it so much.
And if I were them, I'd be bragging about this nonstop.
They were part of the ET adventure.
I mean, that's as big of cred as it comes.
It's kind of specific.
I think in a lot of cases,
they don't make the ride vehicle and mechanisms,
but it's stuff like animatronics and scenic design,
which of course with that attraction is the best stuff.
And I found somewhere specifically where they said,
it's animatronics in the queue.
And we know what animatronics are in the queue.
We certainly do.
The ET adventure, our good friend,
recently refurbished apparently is what we saw.
Oh yeah, right, right.
Nutanicus is fresh and doing great.
So, I mean, incredible.
Like they were, these guys were part of making
our best friends, Magdahl and Orbadon and-
Flop Glopple.
But the big one and probably why they came up
the first time for us and the hardest,
and frequently it's hard to stop bringing up this attraction
because it's so intriguing,
a little ride from a little place called Hard Rock Park.
And that ride is called Knights in White Satin, The Trip.
The psychedelic dark ride based on the movie Blue's song.
I mean, we, right, this, we just like, we talk about it,
it comes up so frequently.
It's just like, solid candidate for weirdest ride ever
to exist anywhere.
Gone too soon.
Yeah.
Maybe at the top of my list of things that I like,
am sad I never got to ride.
Never, top five at least.
Yeah.
Because it was so strange.
And the more and more I thought about it,
looking across the room, I can see the,
one of my manic pandemic purchases of the odd shaped
Knights in White Satin, The Trip coffee mug from eBay.
Um, I, um, I, I think,
I thought about this ride a lot since we did those episodes
because I think it was kind of ahead of its time
because what came after it?
The Navi River journey, a kind of weird, ethereal ride
meant to invoke, I think Joe Rody said like all,
or serenity, like feelings that don't often necessarily
come up in dark rides.
And then every six months or once a year, what happens?
Meow Wolf opens a unique idiosyncratic walkthrough attraction,
ride attraction, and everyone goes wild for it.
And what preceded all of that?
Knights in White Satin The Trip, baby.
Yeah. Trippy, for adults, abstract, psychedelic.
Yeah. It's pretty, uh, it's pretty heavy
and pretty different.
Groundbreaking. Yeah.
Yeah. Um, I mean, to think that we wouldn't have
Navi River journey without it.
Well, everyone's favorite.
I should say, I don't think you can draw a straight line,
but just in terms of like what's in the air,
like what the industry is doing.
Like a wavy line, man.
You can draw a wavy line.
Or some relaxed lines.
Yeah.
Candles.
Mm-hmm.
Um, you know, we, Mike, you've mentioned this here and there,
how we probably do need to do more with Hard Rock Park.
I think there's another shot at it,
especially because like, you know, we were so,
that was our whole thing with that episode,
is we were so like stressed and like,
finding how many materials were there,
like more than we usually find for stuff.
Right.
And I don't think we even scratched the surface.
And I say that partially because I just, due to this,
I was like, well, I got to rewatch a video of
Knights in White Satin The Trip, which is pretty,
I mean, parts of it you could be highfalutin' about,
and then it'll just like pass by a box with a mirror in it,
or like a wavy spiral.
You know, like what is this?
Sure.
But anyway, I just watched a bunch of other
Hard Rock Park videos, the like abandoned video of it,
I think you guys told me about.
I was so amazed by, correctly hyped.
It's so creepy around there now,
but then I watched a, just a,
their fireworks show of Bohemian Rhapsody.
Oh my God, which Hard Rock founder, creator,
John Bukowski is on record saying somewhere like,
it's the best nighttime show there is.
We're doing better than Disney and Universal.
And then you watch it and just like,
sort of correctly timed, just like burst,
like splooges of animatronics.
Mama.
Of fireworks, rather.
At that point, yeah.
What's that?
Like mama, and then explosion.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, but it won't be quite like,
mama, like it's a little like, mama.
It's a little, a little off throughout.
Half beat.
And then you're wondering where, like,
where are they gonna go from here?
They've been doing pyro the whole time.
When it gets into the head banging portion,
what do we do?
And here come the lasers.
Oh good.
Green lasers all over the lagoon.
And it's, and the fireworks are so much louder
than the music.
It's just, it's such a funny.
Yeah.
It was great walking down Hard Rock memory lane.
So yeah, I think there's,
Hard Rock, goodbye yellow brick road,
I guess is what they would say.
Oh yeah.
Hard Rock Park anthology.
The, yeah, the unbuilt stuff.
The, it's very funny to say unbuilt about a park
that was demolished almost as soon as they unlocked the gates.
But their plans for like,
hotel condos, shopping, kind of like,
city walks or shopping area and like all the unbuilt lands
and like the, the wedding chapel, you know,
really, really terrific.
Sally Dark Rides is probably gonna do more for them.
They were gonna build a life-sized animatronic
hairy shaping.
Wow.
They got the rights to Flo and Eddie.
Those look exactly like what I assume
Flo and Eddie look like.
Well, the Velvet Underground ride doesn't have a huge line,
but everyone who wrote it immediately went
into the theme park business afterwards.
That's true.
There would be no Navi River Journey without that.
That's what we're saying.
We got rock metaphors.
They all work.
Just more.
I mean, we were robbed of just more rides
based on specific songs.
That is, I wish. That's probably the craziest.
That trend.
Life in the fast lane.
And the ride, I also watched,
I forgot that they had a ride where you board into,
your roller coaster car goes into a Ferris wheel,
which lifts it up into the drop.
And on the Ferris wheel, it's playing Gary Newman's cars.
And then for the like 45 seconds of roller coaster remaining,
they play everybody wing shung tonight.
It's incredible soundtrack.
All right.
So yeah, we'll find a way.
I mean, we got to do it bigger and better
than we did it before.
And maybe we have to reach out to a certain person.
I know, we're saying that too.
Yeah, yeah.
Tap the vein.
Anyways, so that's some of the great work
of Sally Dark Rides that we knew.
But we were here to discover stuff in the catalog
that we didn't know about.
And we each picked something, rides or a show apparently,
or I don't even know where Mike's going with it.
Where do we begin?
Does anyone want to volunteer to go first?
I will go first because I inadvertently realized
that I picked a semi-timely ride
because Thanksgiving is coming up.
And I have picked what may be the only Thanksgiving themed
Dark Ride in the world.
I'm assuming I would be interested to hear
about other Thanksgiving rides.
I'm of course talking about the Sally Dark Ride designed
Gobbler Getaway.
This opened, Gobbler Getaway opened 2006.
That holiday world in Santa Claus, Indiana,
a park we've been told about a lot,
I believe was in the news a long time ago
because an urban legend started that they had replaced
the water fountains with soda.
And it was just that, I believe you could get free soda
at soda fountains if you, it was one of the parks.
It's like parks.
Parks going like free parking, free, you know,
free soda with your meal.
Like it was one of those things that got blown
way out of proportion.
It was just brown water.
Yeah, it's just brown water.
It's just very hard water.
So holiday world is a park where like each section
is themed to different holidays.
There's like a Christmas section, a Halloween section
and a more recent Thanksgiving section.
And so Gobbler Getaway, I'm just gonna read the description,
the simplified description on Wikipedia.
The ride is centered on the fictional
Jamestown evoking autumn falls,
where the residents presented as pilgrim fathers
must gather turkeys for the year's Thanksgiving.
Guests are equipped with turkey collars
that you use to tag birds as they pass through the town
and the environs.
At the conclusion of the ride, guest scores are tallied up
and a winner is decided between the four guests
in each vehicle.
The vehicles are called Trotters.
Wow.
Go to your Trotter, go to old Jamestown.
So that's, it's in the past, it's in early America?
Yeah, kind of early America
because the ride itself is, you know,
pilgrim-y kind of people, but then as you are in the queue,
there is an animatronic of someone telling you
how the ride works and the animatronic of course is grandma.
There's that Sally style, oh my God.
They really, they make some like, just mannequin,
like scarily realistic.
What is, sorry, sorry.
Bring that back up, Jason.
Yeah, we gotta see that gun for longer.
Is that the tagger, the collar, what is it?
I'm gonna bring up another picture
because this is 2020 grandma,
so of course she's wearing a mask.
Oh my God.
Thanks grandma.
So no, that is the turkey collar.
It does look like a gun,
but you're not blasting the turkeys,
you're calling them, you know?
Okay.
So wait, okay, so she's got grandma here,
I just wanna paint the picture.
She has one single cookie left out on her plate
by her little table on her right
and then she has a big glass of milk
and she's holding what looks like either a card sorting gun
or like a police radar gun to me,
but it is actually a turkey calling device.
And a big cat, she's got a big cat on her lap.
It's also like kind of like a Klingon phaser.
Yeah.
Like what a Klingon would use to,
what their phasers look like.
It's not, I'm just not used to seeing a kindly old grandma
holding anything weapon looking.
Yeah.
So this is shocking already.
I mean, this is already shocking and great
and I can see immediately why Jason picked it.
What an image.
What is this?
So turkey collar implies that it,
does it make a turkey sound?
Is it like a duck call?
Well, it makes a infrared ride zapping sound
as all of these attractions do.
So you're saying that's not a real device.
That is a made up fictional device.
Yeah. A turkey collar, like a bird collar
is usually like a little,
looks almost like a kazoo or a whistle.
Yeah. They put it in your mouth.
And certainly, I don't think theme parks,
nowadays certainly not, but ever would want,
you know, to like get in a ride vehicle
and stick this whistle in your mouth.
Yeah. Like Toy Story, Minway Mania,
but instead of like pulling that string,
you have to like put a gun in your mouth and shoot or blow.
That's not as good, I think.
Doesn't work.
Can I, can I go, can you roll back real quick?
You said it's not Jamestown.
It is a fictional Autumn Falls.
Is that what you said?
Yeah. It's Autumn Falls.
Do you want to see a little footage?
Do you want me to play some?
Yeah, of course I'd like to see a little footage.
And I have to give both the Knights of White Satin,
thankfully preserved,
because Sally has a YouTube page
where they have a pretty good quality ride through of it.
And this is Holiday World a few years ago,
put up a POV ride through of Gobbler Getaway.
So let me bring up this video real quick.
The last Autumn Falls.
A UV vibe.
Turkey Town USA is the unofficial name.
Pretty calm so far.
Looks like the poo ride at Disneyland.
A lot like poo. Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Doors swing open.
That's so much like poo.
Oh.
A goofy guy with an apple barrel.
Like tricorner hats.
Yeah.
But not specific.
You got to get, it's not actually real what happened.
All right, you got to help them find these turkeys.
They're really good at hiding.
Okay, so we're going to shoot a gun at them.
Well, we're going to call them.
We're going to, I saltly refer to it as tagging the turkeys.
Okay.
So yeah.
We're not killing them now.
We're rounding them up to be killed soon.
Well, hold on to that.
Hold on to that thought.
Uh oh.
So there's a cheery horse here.
This is interesting.
Why this?
I thought this was going to be more historically accurate.
I'll be honest with you.
Even invoking Jamestown, I thought perhaps
a lot more like slaughter and people dying of diphtheria.
Yeah, exactly.
I guess that's where they had a lot of lost colony with pro a toa.
Yeah. So now you're in the tree.
You're in like a straightaway barn.
Love this art design.
That's a very appealing bright red.
Yeah.
I mean, just design wise, this is very good.
There's a woman with a wash.
She's got a big thing of wash to do.
Yeah, there's a lot of targets everywhere.
I'm just going to let it.
Yeah.
So now we're in like a shop area.
Very Roger Rabbit.
Where like mayhem is conveyed via like one big circle going around
your door, your heart, the guys struggling to hold your car.
Looks like it smacks the door open.
Mm hmm.
We're just talking about that with some I think I like it.
Yeah, I agree.
I am.
So.
All right, wait for it.
Happy Thanksgiving, it says.
Oh, there's an empty table.
They lift the tray.
There's no turkey there.
Yeah. And he's he screams happy pizza day.
And now the turkeys do a musical number.
Oh, my God, I like that.
They're all lined up as a big science is happy Thanksgiving.
For a turkey toad.
There's your scores, I think.
You know, the score levels.
Yeah, I'll bring up.
I have the picture of the score levels and, you know, I think
they're pretty forgiving.
I feel like they're pretty like giving of, you know.
That's still a little blurry, but.
It it they are.
So it's like one of those stakes.
Yeah, low scoring.
Gobbler wannabe.
Just another turkey beginner turkey
caller apprentice turkey caller master turkey caller.
OK, all right.
That's some historical accuracy that we're dealing with apprentices.
That's true. Yeah.
So there you go. That's close to the original.
Yeah, I really I'm not even sure why they had to invoke like old like Jamestown.
Like, I don't know.
Oh, yeah, there it is.
That's the the turkey toad.
The scores are like 200.
So this is like a low scoring game here.
I mean, I looked at there weren't that many turkeys around as far as I could see,
just looking at it once.
That's a complaint that I would have had watching that right through.
Yeah, I feel like I saw about seven turkeys in, you know, eight show scenes.
Yeah, it's like if you were going on Men in Black
and there was one tiny monster in every room.
Yeah, a lot of targets on like wooden beams or like bushes.
Yeah. Give me more turkeys.
Well, sure. I mean, obviously, yes, this is a budget conscious decision
because obviously, like you'd want a full they were going with the Mr.
Toad, the least the most like 75 percent of the first part of Mr.
Toad style or Winnie the Pooh, a lot of flats, a few animatronics here and there.
But obviously, cost was a factor.
So I suppose that probably influences the decision to have about 10 turkeys
and have the score reach no higher than 2000 points.
Yeah, I will give them credit, though, that like the the colors are
the day glow colors are very bright.
The black lights of it's very bright and the dark areas are very dark.
And like often both those effects can be difficult to achieve.
Yeah, it looks good in video for sure.
I like colors are appealing, as Scott was saying.
And I definitely like it.
And as a kid, I would have liked it.
There are still like I still am kind of conflicted about shooting rides in general.
I saw that they also are just making I don't know where it is.
They're making a Sesame Street ride that also has a shooting element.
And it doesn't isn't there one that exists already?
Like, did they make it in fact?
Maybe there's one in Spain, I think.
In Spain, maybe that's what I'm thinking of.
Maybe that actually is open already.
And I thought it was opening. Yeah, you're probably I think it isn't
because it was not English, the video I was watching.
So you're probably right.
It's a cookie. Is it cookies are shooting like cookies on Sesame Street?
Yeah. Or flashlights.
Their concept art for the Five Nights at Freddy's is that you have a flashlight
and you shine it to scare the animatronics away.
Like Monsters Monsters Inc. in Tokyo is like that. Yeah.
So, yeah. So I guess I guess what I'm saying is, as I talk this through,
maybe I like it that there's not a ton of stuff to shoot
because then you get to enjoy like the tinker and you get to enjoy.
I don't know if there's a shoe cobbler in there, but I assume
that's the type of business when we walked.
We went through the end there right before the feast.
Well, the work in these shooting rides can detract from just
actually sitting and enjoying it.
And I guess with what you want is a trip into the seventeen hundreds, then.
Who does want that? Yes.
Oh, my gosh. Just to see
the tinkerers at work, to see a traditional mercantile.
All a bustle.
Yeah. So so I mean, that's a great choice, Jason.
Is that so? That's something.
Yeah. Is that what's the closest to a Thanksgiving ride there even is
before that we saw that?
Like, do we even have one that comes close to being like that with pilgrims?
Or I don't think so.
Carousel of Progress hits like the other holidays, right?
Like, it's right.
Fourth of July at one time.
Another time.
It's Christmas at the end.
Is it Halloween?
I think at some point in one of them.
Oh, yeah, they're dressing up.
They're dressing up. Yeah.
Oh, yeah, because the kid has the spooky little mask on.
So so wow. OK.
Not a very represented holiday.
Is there anything else we'd like to see in a in a Thanksgiving holiday?
I mean, like, you know, the I don't know the reason to do it,
but is there some way that the turkey itself could be your weapon
and that you have to like shove your hand up into?
It's not just holding a little gun
that you have to like manipulate an entire turkey and get your full,
you know, get it to the waist deep.
Mm hmm. That's a good. Yeah, I think they could definitely pull that.
I mean, look, I think Sally's willing to work with any idea we have.
That's the sense I get.
So what you're saying is possibly probably possible with the budget
and sell in just talking to Sally and hashing it out with budget.
What's budget going to going to be? Yeah.
Yeah. Key, as long as we have somewhere to put the door.
Yeah, I would want I guess you don't really want historical accuracy
for this period.
So, I mean, maybe it's a new Thanksgiving ride.
I mean, you do want it, but if you're trying to have fun,
you don't want the horrors of the realities.
But so a new Thanksgiving, like what's what's happening now at Thanksgiving,
maybe like a some sort of a robot show
with just like mom and dad trying to fix a turkey
and singing Thanksgiving songs, maybe something like that.
It's a quaint little show.
If you were shrunk on a Thanksgiving table, that could be something.
And then you're like, OK, that's going down like a gravy rapids.
Like you end up in the little in the in the gravy boats
or in the little like lake that you make with the mashed potatoes.
All right. All right. Now you're yes.
Now you got me. That's thinking, OK, gravy boat like it's Pirates of Caribbean.
But the water is gravy and is legit gravy that you can drink.
Oh, the ride is the gravy boat.
Yes. Yes.
There you go. Full gravy river.
Yeah, full gravy river.
And you can drink it.
You get a little cup before and you get to scoop the gravy out
while you while you while you ride down on the boat.
Go ahead. Dig in.
Put that way. You got a ladle for a reason.
Maybe there's some very tedious message about like,
it's like, well, you know, there's the family you're born with
and the family you choose.
Like it's laid on really thick about like orphan Thanksgiving and like,
oh, it's the family you choose, you know, and
and everyone, you know, the table looks like shit.
Everyone messed up. Everyone brought the lights.
There's no turkey.
Yeah. And you have to go like you have to go up on the mashed potatoes
and you kind of circle the drain like there's some sort of a circuit
like you're kind of going in a loop down as you kind of go into the mashed potatoes.
And then Dad takes a big spoon and we have to go down.
Dad's body and inside his body.
Oh, yeah.
But then he has indigestion and throws you back up.
Yes. So we go to be stuck going the other way or just like
or just like becoming part of Dad.
Yeah, you're going to be you are in cells now.
So you go down a splash mountain style esophagus
into Dad's stomach acid and it's choppy.
It's choppy. And don't drink that.
Now you have your ladle in your cup, but do not drink the water in Dad's stomach.
It's highly important.
They tell you all this in the pre-ride video.
So I hope you're paying attention.
It's a lot of bourbon in there, too. So.
Yes. You got to watch out for your like
aunt who talks too much.
It's like she's just on a tear of like, I'm surprised
they even give the kids Thanksgiving off anymore.
I'm sure they'd like to get rid of this holiday, too.
Like they got rid of Columbus.
Your aunt is also Paul Linde.
Like they got they canceled Columbus.
So upset.
So, yeah. So then, yeah, you go in the toilet.
You're thrown up in the toilet.
And then I guess you another yet another splash mountain down through a toilet.
Again, don't drink.
Don't drink that water either.
It's not gravy. It's not gravy.
Well, she's got she's got thoughts on splash mountain, too, for sure.
Oh, no.
Yeah, watch out.
Turn quick turn.
Don't go that go the other way.
So you learn that it's better to be in the sewer for Thanksgiving
than listening to your aunt and her opinions.
Yeah, so that's what you learn from the ride.
Purposeful holiday loneliness. Right.
Quick, sit on the couch with your teenage cousin and their boyfriend
who are just looking at their phones and not making eye contact with anyone.
So it's a scary ride, I guess, is what we determine.
The real horrors.
Yeah, it's a haunted mansion.
It's much scarier than Haunted Mansion.
It could be.
Or and it could you could do a shooter with it.
And it's more wholesome.
Like you have a can of whipped cream and you're trying to.
You're trying to whip cream everyone's pie slices like.
Oh, well, that's cute.
Yeah. You should come up with a bunch of different sketches for that
and just send it into Sally Unsolicited to see if they would just kind of take you
on to come up with different Thanksgiving themed ideas.
Are you talking about comedy sketches
or like the scrawlings of a madman with no artistic drawing talent?
Scrawlings of a madman, I think. Oh, OK.
I prefer you to send in just Unsolicited to Sally.
I think a crumbled pile of odd Thanksgiving.
Like self taking pictures of yourself, like at the table with a pie
and pointing to things and like a makeshift gun that you've made up.
It's like all pieced together in a sloppy way and it's impossible to follow.
Someone.
But where did where did a 36 year old man find construction paper?
Hobby Lobby.
Yeah, his favorite store, his favorite store and company.
Hold on a second.
Oh, your aunt, excuse me, your aunt's favorite store.
She brought us all cuneiform.
She brought us all like stone tablets for Christmas. Sure.
All right. Well, there's a lot of Thanksgiving.
I think Holiday World, I don't know much about this holiday world,
but I think they could build a full Thanksgiving Springs, you could call it.
And there's infinite ideas and Sally Dark Rides should be doing them.
Yeah. All right. I'm up next here.
I've mentioned this on the show before.
A place that I got to go as a kid once in a while, even up through
I want to say for junior high or high school and Chuck E.
Cheese we had around the corner.
We didn't go a lot, but it was always there. We drove by it.
There was one place that existed in Lombard, Illinois,
that was a real special occasion that we would go to.
And it was called Enchanted Castle.
OK. And like Enchanted, if I really search my feelings, I have obviously
I love Chuck E.
Cheese and all those characters, but I was most excited to go to Enchanted Castle.
It was like I would turn into Cartman and the Casa Bonita episode.
Like, that's how cool Enchanted Castle was.
And Enchanted Castle had more arcade games.
It had like go kart rides.
It had laser tag.
And what I forgot up until I was doing the research,
their own animatronic show and their own characters.
And Sally made this like thing that looms large.
Yeah. Wow. Yes. Company.
And certainly in my teen years, when I was going to Enchanted Castle,
I did not see the show.
But when I was younger and they had like, you know, it's the same
thing as Chuck E.
Cheese, a pizza party for a birthday.
I absolutely saw this.
Now, it's different on the website than it is from the videos I was looking up.
And I'll show you here what they have on the Sally website.
They call these characters.
Gwen and the Magical Music Makers.
Oh, this group. Oh, my.
And I love them.
It's like, I guess, like Gwenevere.
She's like a blonde lady with a crown.
And these are dragons.
These are four dragons.
One is at a piano.
One is a trumpet.
One is at like a little drum thing.
And then the guy in the back has got like a little mandolin.
And he's close to like a mule, like a few of them have kind of like
all shucks teeth, like Mater or Goofy.
Exactly. Yes.
So so they're I'm pretty sure they're all dragons.
But yes, they don't necessarily look like scary dragons or whatever.
So what I think has happened and I there's no believe it or not,
there's no oral history on what's happened to Gwen and the Magical Music Makers.
But I believe they are now called the Jammin' Jesters.
And there's no video I can find of the original show,
but you can find video of the newer version of the show,
which is what I have here.
And I'm like, my memory is sort of to the like left,
very left side of this enchanted castle is where you would go into this big pizza room
and you would eat and watch a show.
So this is these I wish I had the original videos of what they were.
But those don't appear to be well preserved.
This is amazing, by the way.
This is like how like we maybe commented before,
how like every TV show ever has had their version of Chuck E.
Cheese and often they aren't accurate.
They don't feel like true to me.
They don't. And like you so rarely see a non Chuck E.
Cheese animatronic band at a pizza place with kind of a thin theme.
And this is just it.
Like a little a Renaissance dragon and princess band.
This is this is straight out of this would have been on a TGIF show
or on Tiny Tunes or something.
This is like I'm amazed this exists.
Yes. And I'm amazed that even when I talked about Enchanted Castle
last time on the show, it actually didn't bring back the memory
of the full animatronic show, because I guess the so many of the time
the last times I had gone, which has been over 20 years at this point.
And it's still, by the way, Enchanted Castle still there.
This is still he still exists.
So I think these are still these shows are still going
as the jam and jesters. But yeah, it's wild.
So there's two videos I have of two separate shows.
I don't know which one is like the birthday show and which one's a general show.
But here, I'll give you a taste a little bit of what like
what the starting out song is.
And.
Can you make heads or tails of these allegations?
It's I think it's well, I know one of the because it was their tagline
Enchanted Castle, king size fun for everyone.
Yes. What they would say on the on the commercial.
So I think it's some variation on that.
So at this point, yeah,
it opens up and you get to see like now newish versions.
Now, when Guinevere is like in the back
and there's a tiny dragon sort of on a little podium in front.
And there's the addition of some characters on the side here, like
you'll meet him. His name is Wally Wizard.
Welcome to the Enchanted Castle, where there's king sized fun for everyone.
And why was the finest restaurant
and the finest restaurants are usually French?
So Wally has just said that the finest restaurants are usually French.
He's letting a bunch of eight year olds know
that all this American cuisine is garbage.
It's bullshit.
Yeah, the way we all we all still agree that French food is the best.
Exactly. No matter what.
That is Wally's philosophy.
So here we go.
Bonjour, I am your
mate, Wally the Wizard.
It is with the greatest pride and the deepest pleasure
we welcome you tonight.
Now we invite you to relax.
You just pull up a chair as the castle proudly presents your.
Wait, hold on a sec.
Yes. Yes, Jason, you have any questions?
Um, that, I don't know, just that delivery and vibe seemed very familiar.
OK, all right. Well, hold on. Let me play a little more in case.
I think this is I don't know what you're thinking,
but let me see if you're on the same page.
OK, were you thinking Wally was going to sing be our guest?
Um, I I had some money on it.
Yeah, yeah, OK.
That was a pretty safe bet. Yeah.
OK, yeah. So Wally performs be our guests.
A wizard with a silent big dopey dragon named Toby.
Name Toby. Yes.
So they do. So they do that.
And that's strange. That's certainly strange.
And I don't know rock band.
This isn't a rock song. Right.
So OK, so music choices I find interesting on this in the other video.
And this is going to be a little bit imprecise when I when I started.
But we'll go get there.
So basically, this little dragon's name is cute.
See you. T.E.
And some of the dragons do a little routine.
Oh, this dragon looks like Robbie from dinosaurs.
Does he not? A little bit.
He does. And the bay and cute looks like baby dinosaur.
Yes, very similar.
So they do a little like who's on first routine of like
cute. She's cute.
Yeah, she sure is.
But what's her name?
Like they do a whole thing like that, which, again, no child.
I didn't enjoy that routine as a child.
I don't know who keeps making this bit go on and on.
Maybe an Animaniacs.
I kind of liked it. I liked that. Yeah.
Now you might say, oh, was that was a great segue, Mike.
That was a good example.
But Animaniacs is going to come into play right now, I think.
I can't help it.
But what can I do when you're cute?
Get your show.
With these two dollars, I'm the only cute girl.
No, no, no, no.
So cute is performing the Animaniacs song that Dot sings
called I'm Cute.
I don't know. I don't remember this song.
This song. I remember this song pretty well.
And I was like, oh, is that like an old song, old time song?
No, it's an Animaniacs song.
So this show is has Animaniacs and Beauty and the Beast so far.
Now stealing everything, stealing everything.
Now, let me let me go to this other video real quick.
OK, so we so far we know that this show has Beauty and the Beast.
It has Animaniacs.
What do you think might come next?
Does anybody I mean, it's impossible to guess, but so I'll just play it here.
The full end of Abbey Road.
Now, this is a video that's very close to the robot,
so you can hear every whirring gear and every head turn,
and it's really distracting.
Yeah, they're an inch away.
They're an inch away.
This video. But OK, let me keep playing just in case you don't know the song yet.
This video.
But OK, let me keep playing just in case you don't know the song yet.
Join us.
I don't know what this is.
I feel the first second.
We're getting to a chorus here.
We got magic to do just for you.
We got me with the place to play.
We got hearts to the farm.
Hearts to warm.
Here's a feast to tip my storm.
So other than this video being terrifying, this song is Magic to Do from the Stephen
Schwartz musical Pippin.
Right.
We're kids love Pippin in the year whatever 2020 whatever this video is from to do.
Kids love Pippin.
This is second Stephen Schwartz Pippin reference in one second game month.
Exactly.
Yes.
So there Magic to Do in this video, which again is so creepy.
You can see like Guinevere's like her mouth is falling off as she does like she sings.
She is awful.
She's playing it like a like a piano type or an organ.
You get some more up close personal time with the robots, which I do like.
It's weird.
They just shove this big dragon out the door of the cave and he's just on the carpet of the restaurant.
Yes.
He's not elevated.
None of them are.
They're all on the carpet.
It's like a fucking house show.
It's like a punk band playing house show.
Toby also barely clears that curtain.
Like the curtain is still kind of on him in both videos.
So yeah, you get close ups of cute and she does a little song that's not very good that I don't think is I think might be an original song.
Speaking of who's on first routines and cute, I guess it's time to ask the question is cute cute.
The answer is yes.
Cute is cute.
Yeah, I think he is cute.
I guess so.
I'm not creeped out by it.
I've seen worse.
Believe me, I've seen worse.
Do you want cute to talk a little more up in front in the video here?
And let's see.
We can really judge it here.
Yeah.
It's my pleasure to introduce our newest and youngest center here.
Just a little bit of a thing.
She is ladies and gentlemen.
May I have a large round of applause for the wee little dragon.
Cute.
Wait a minute.
I'm not that small.
You're pretty small, cute.
I'm big enough.
Look, I wouldn't buy a plush of it.
I wouldn't sleep with cute, but I don't hate cute.
So that's something for me.
That's pretty good.
Yeah.
All right.
Cute is cute.
Fine.
And now, yeah, there's some more songs in this.
Later, Guinevere does.
There's no business like show business.
Oh, great.
For some reason.
Things kids love.
Kids love this.
And so let me play this.
There's another song.
Not sure if you'll.
Well, cute, that's how I got started, you know.
How extraordinary.
Hats in the room and pigeon in the hay.
Is not my idea of a perfect day.
When you're extraordinary, you gotta do extraordinary things.
Do you guys know that song?
No.
That is that's from a musical, too.
I just can't think of it, right?
It is from musical.
The musical is Pippin.
The the dragons who are names jesters and who have the word jammin in their name,
like a rock band would do, who play multiple songs from Pippin.
Pippin.
This is a very Pippin heavy show and in a chan.
A channing castle jammin Pippin dragons.
Got it.
Yeah.
So I don't I wish I knew what songs they played when I was little.
It could have been Pippin.
It could have not been.
There's no way this has changed since you were.
Well, I guess there's been a general change into the jammin jesters.
Right.
You never saw you've never seen the jammin jesters in person.
I don't think so.
I would have to really go and find like an enchanted castle person that knew the
history to know when that changeover happened.
But maybe that maybe the old band did maybe going in the magical music
makers did all Pippin songs.
We don't know.
So maybe that didn't like that.
That didn't change.
But don't see why they wouldn't.
They will be more likely to have.
So I love here.
I'm more of a show.
When I'm going to show going real quick playing the song and I want to watch
everyone just focus on how unnerving it is to watch the robot sing.
The company.
There's no business.
I know.
This looks exactly like the sex dolls in the British documentary.
I see.
You she's got like a zombie like there.
She's got weird like like flushing threads.
You got Joker scars.
Yes.
You got Joker.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
So this is great.
Now for our grand finale.
A reprise of magic to do.
Hit it.
So here's a bunch of characters that I have gotten reacquainted with from my
childhood.
Thank you.
Sally Dark Ride.
Sally Corporation for this.
Next time I do I have to go back to Enchanted Castle.
I have to see what show what Pippin songs they're doing this month in 2021.
I got to go to Lombard.
If anyone's around there and you got to go check out and see how many Pippin
songs they're still performing.
Please let us know.
Calling all Lombarders.
Go get a camera way up in Gwen's face at the Jammin' Jester's show.
Yeah.
They might.
I mean maybe that was done by an employee.
I would maybe not recommend getting that close to the robots but maybe they don't
care.
That was an upsetting video.
It is.
Yeah I don't know that the security is so tight at Enchanted Castle.
I don't think kids go there anymore.
I think they like I think they've pivoted into they've made the pivot that Sally
has contemplated doing.
This is entirely like looky-loos who have dirty thoughts about Gwen.
It's possible that the whole animatronic market is now just for older creeps.
It's possible.
I hope it's not.
Go where the money is.
I hope little kids still like animatronics.
Oof.
Well, wow.
Frightening childhood memories unlocked.
And if you thought we were out of the woods in terms of frightening humanoids you thought
wrong.
I don't think anyone thought that but we're diving even further in with a ride called
Vipa Salt Kraken.
Oh.
I gravitated to on the Sally website just on name alone.
I'm like oh this could be fun to just pick and I don't know what it is.
I don't even know the language offhand.
Now I know that this is Swedish.
This is a ride in Sweden.
Right off the bat.
I'm just going to say this might be the weirdest ride I've ever run into.
I saw a little bit.
I saw a little bit of it and like I it was so immediately interesting that I dove into
it just out of force of like oh my god oh my god.
You can't not.
And then like halfway through it I was like oh shit this is was this what Scott picked?
It has to be like this is the most interesting thing I've ever read.
And then I looked back and I went oh shit Scott picked it.
Alright I'm done I'm done I'm done.
Well you know you needn't have done that.
It doesn't have to be a surprise.
But I'm glad.
I hope it will be in Canby for Jason and for the audience.
Because boy this is this is something.
Vipa Salt Kraken.
This is okay so first of all this is at a park in Vimrby Sweden.
A park called Astrid Lindgren's World.
Who is Astrid Lindgren you ask?
Well Astrid Lindgren is the author behind the tales of Pippi Longstocking.
So this is a whole park devoted to Pippi Longstocking and similar byproducts.
Now here's where I'm confused because we did a whole month where the point was to find weird European parks.
And nobody came across Astrid Lindgren's World and Vipa Salt Kraken.
I don't know how we missed it.
This is shocking.
Yes this was shocking to me.
An author has an entire theme park basically.
One author's properties are in a theme park.
Who has you know like a little bit of media.
There's many strange upsetting Pippi Longstocking movies and shows out there.
Do you remember that from oh go ahead Jason.
Oh I was going to say Pippi Longstocking when I was growing I always thought of it like Anne of Green Gables.
Like there's a lot of adaptations of this.
I don't really know the original source material.
I know I believe they're from other.
I think Anne of Green Gables is Canadian.
Is that right?
I think so yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah that's I think the vibe of the ride that we're going to talk about.
I just in general like Pippi Longstocking I just remember being a rant.
Do you remember just when we were kids how if you would like put on a channel that was for kids movies
or you'd go to the kids video section at the library and there weren't as many things back then.
Now there's just like there's such a massive oversaturated kids market.
But when we were kids it was still kind of the creepy 80s.
So Robert Altman Popeye counts as a kids movie.
Right.
And Pippi Longstocking is there for kids.
And like I just remember any time diving in it like because it was one of the 10 movies you had to.
And I was just always like what's wrong with this.
Pippi Longstocking is weird and I don't remember why.
Probably a audience remind me what is up with Pippi Longstocking.
Put a scary video in my feed.
Unless I'm wrong.
Am I I just remember always being like this is scary.
What is it?
I hear I have a guess because I always as a kid associated Pippi Longstocking even though this isn't correct.
She was a little girl.
I always associated her with Raggedy Anne and Raggedy Andy.
Because they all fell in the similar genre to me in my kid mind.
Big bright freckles and pigtails.
And we've established that I don't like this for adults to dress up.
Which is so I could not go to this park because it is adults playing Pippi Longstocking and live shows.
I mean it seems this does not seem like some demented park to me.
It seems very charming.
I would say not even nearly as scary and seedy as Popeye Village in Malta seems to be.
As much as I'm dying to go there I would really like to.
But yeah it is strange.
It's all devoted to the kind of like pleasant if scary to me works of this author.
And this ride.
I don't think there's a lot of like dark rides here.
So this is sort of a I don't know it's an outlier.
And Vipassaltkraken is a translation if he translates to English that is we on Salt Crow Island.
Yes.
Oh.
Salt Crow.
Which is that does that mean seagull?
Is that what it is?
What's a Salt Crow?
I have no idea but this is a very popular show or book series.
It is very popular in Sweden.
Do you know about this already for some reason or you just from from your perusing of this stuff?
No no I just I looked up like just to make sure I looked up the name of your thing just to make sure.
But I didn't go as deep as Mike.
I just saw like a beloved Swedish story.
That's what I yeah I like I was like would people know this for some reason because apparently this is a hugely popular show from the 60s in Sweden.
One season was made.
One season 13 episodes.
In 1964 I believe and there were like four TV movies after it and this ride was made in 2007.
That's how popular like what one season television show dead let's say Deadly Games on UPN.
Say that was being like every year you just gather the family around and you watch Sebastian Jackle with the family around Christmas time.
And then 50 years later they were like you know what it's time to make a dark ride.
Sally Dark Rides made a Deadly Games dark ride.
That's like I think they would and they will.
I think we're going to be part eventually we're going to be part of proliferating the myth of Sebastian Jackle and it's going to get made.
So that's the ride we get from them.
That's how like popular a one season show is in Sweden.
I know in Europe they don't like one season doesn't mean a failure necessarily.
That's out of you know it's not necessarily a failure if you do one season in Europe.
Well and I think they also cut this into like a movie basically or a limited run series like it's been repackaged in various other ways.
What could be so popular that it's like that a ride of it is made a very realistic accurate ride where all the actors look exactly right.
That this is made over 40 years after the event.
What are the events of this transformative beloved Swedish show?
Let me read the IMDB synopsis.
I have a guess and I want to see it.
Go ahead.
I want to see it.
I was like I want to see if I'm right.
Well either you're going to be right on or we're way off because you're way off.
Well yeah.
All right.
What is it?
The Melkerson family decides to leave the city for the summer to rent a house in the Stockholm archipelago.
They come to enjoy the simple life there and all adventures that come their way together with the resident family the Granck Vists.
So I say that maybe you were right because like if you guessed a pleasant time on Salt Crow Island then that was correct.
But did you have another guess?
No it was going to be about like kids maybe a full family experiencing the simple life in some sort of countryside like that that sort of little house on a prairie.
I don't quite know what time period is this like modern times that takes place in.
I'm not even sure.
I think it might be modern times but they go to Salt Crow Island where it is not like modern times where it's the you were like slower.
Modern times in 1964.
Yeah.
So it's the 40 it's it's 60s nostalgia for the 1910s.
The vibe of it is very this is where it might be good to just start to look at the the animatronics or what have you because the vibe of it is very like I mean it's very von Trapp.
It's very Brady's I guess.
Walton's like to me whether that's right or not.
Yeah I think Jason's right on with Little House.
That's what Aaron said like yeah this seems like if like something is low stakes as Little House on the Prairie and just like it's a night it's about a family that supports each other in a simple time and they then love gets them through.
And this it's all so strange to make because in America rides are made out of Indiana Jones and Star Wars like movies with a lot of action and stakes and I guess in Sweden people are just dying to go have a pleasant time on Salt Crow Island.
So you know you're right you get in a vehicle it's like I'm just a pretty generic kind of like a you know a little machine that takes you around just like a two you know it's I guess it's sort of like the Pinocchio or Snow White but not themed it's just a car and forgive me for just I'm just going to sort of step through this you know when VO is interesting I'll play it when not I'll just show you captions and read them but you can.
You can do narration in Swedish and in English you can choose and Sally has provided the English narration the conceit of the show and of the ride is that an older woman is narrating from the future so from the 80s I guess about her time with her family on Salt Crow Island.
I wonder what God was thinking when he created this island.
I guess he thought I want rough great cliffs green trees, oaks, birches and meadows of flowers.
I wonder what a what a heady statement to then have a nice answer like you can imagine in a very different film or show I wonder what God was thinking when he created this island.
Like Dr. Moreau or Jurassic World.
I bet it was nice his thoughts were nice.
This is a big big difference from what I think of like modern Swedish pop culture exports is just like the bleakest like crime like I might be a different country but like the snowman like I'm not sure who made the snowman yeah yeah.
I mean I would be right of that but I don't want anything from the movie in it I just want like it's me the snowman come with me I'll give you all the clues.
Yes it's up in the air whether author Joe Nesbo has authorized Detective Harry Hole for licensing purposes but I'd love to see it.
I refuse to say how late it can't be it's always Harry Hole to me.
What?
Detective Harry Hole.
So, in a pretty cool effect the woman morphs from older to younger. She's like looking at a photo album of sea wait but she said sea crow.
It's sea crow or I don't know look it's salt cracking that's what I know.
I'll let's let's just see where this goes.
Yes, because I want the whole island to flow with pink thorn roses and white hawthorn in big drifts on that day in June when Marlin Melkishon arrives there.
Next bridge is Sandflgan.
Next stop, Sea Crow Island.
Do you know what I think? When we get there, we'll sit on the top of the tower and we'll sit in the sun.
So here's a let's pause on this frame so you can see these guys and the subtitle translation will eat dinner in the garden.
This is the equivalent of you round the corner you've seen Mara you whip around oh my god there's Indiana Jones and he's shutting the portals of hell for us.
The equivalent here is a multi-generational family in the in the front of a boat looking at an island and thinking about what dinner they're going to have.
Yes, and the dad looks like George's boss in the play now and this late season Seinfeld.
I can't think of the character's name.
Oh, that guy. Yes. Yeah, not Mr. Wilhelm.
No, I know who you mean.
The guy who doesn't care about anything.
Yeah, yeah.
And the family, I mean, it's sort of, they don't all have blonde hair, but a lot of them do.
There's a similar vibe to a lot of them and when all of the characters, while I find these characters less creepy than other Sally humanoids, they also are all kind of squinting in an unsettling manner.
It's just like really narrow eyes and if they are feeling joy it's hard to tell because they're just a little cross.
It's like as much joy as you could have back then when you work hard.
And they, I don't know, this kind of like, especially the kid is kind of like a children of the corn sort of deal.
Oh yeah.
I'll keep playing. I'll read the volume a little.
What if it rains?
The sun always shines on Seekro Island.
And the dog is a Bozman.
Our house is called Carpenter's Cottage.
It's what they call a nice old weekend cottage.
And then the people on the ride, the real people, look exactly like the characters in the show.
The robots were dressed up and put on an actual ride vehicle.
I mean I can see why it resonates with this audience.
But then, and truly like, if you look up a picture of Vipassol cracking the joe and then the ride, it is exceedingly accurate.
I mean this is like being in a slightly animated wax museum.
It's pretty amazing.
They also like, now that you start getting into like gadgets and you know, wicker chairs and here's an old stove.
And at this point you start feeling, well, it's very carousel of progress, isn't it?
It's like a, it's a family growing up and inventions affecting their lives in various ways.
Coughing at a stove.
Maybe there's an owl in the chimney.
And then there's an old man balancing with a, like some iron implement to get to fish the owl out of the chimney.
I think this is, I think there was a pretty clumsy, I don't know if it's the dad or the grandfather, I'm not totally sure.
But he's got the wackiest face.
I mean this is, he's the comedian of the show I guess.
This one looks like, like a Peter O'Toole animatronic was melted a little bit.
And now he is balancing on one foot on a roof and he's just like bouncing back and forth and that's the show scene.
See, I gotta give Sally credit because there's not a lot of companies turning out theme park rides that achieve like Knights in White Satin, ethereal, abstract.
V-Pod Salt Kraken, pleasant, the interesting joy of daily life, the little moments of daily life.
Yeah, the last scene was just that the oven was, something was burning in the oven.
That was the first scene you see.
You know, a lot of rides do not show you that. Jason's right.
Again, yeah. Indiana Jones at this point, there is a, you're in a scary temple and there's rats and bugs around here.
There's the potential of an owl being in the chimney.
Yes.
Anybody can buy, I like what Jason's saying though.
Any company could do an adventure or a war or a battle.
But who, how do you, even, even Walt never really married like a ride with the pleasantness of like,
Even like the scene in the scenes in Carousel of Progress where like all the inventions are like the doors are open and shut and like, and he's talking about the rat race.
There's nothing as stressful as the rat race in this ride.
I say with Carousel of Progress, too exciting.
Too much going on.
Yeah.
Too much drama.
No, I don't have room for drama in my life.
I want to go to Seacrow Island.
I agree.
What should I hold on to?
Hold on to the poker.
Then does he get electrocuted?
If someone saw us when we are supposed to eat, they would think we are insane.
Yeah.
I don't know what happens there.
If someone saw us when we were supposed to, when we were going to eat, we would look insane and then a table is picked up and slammed down.
Mm hmm.
Don't really know.
But I feel like.
But again, the like, you'll never see a happier crew than the families riding this ride.
They know what it is.
They love it.
It's the table shaking scene.
Yeah.
He's writing in the diary again.
Steiner lives with her grandfather, old man Sordaman.
She has a raven called Jump Along Jack.
Yes.
Yeah.
Jump Along Jack.
This kid is after me.
A kid is teaching English to.
Not English, teaching language to a raven.
On our street in town is a lady with 48 kids.
Now you're lying again, Steiner.
Yes, I'm lying.
No one could possibly have 48 kids.
He just has 45.
And that was like a little skit being done essentially between two children dressed in their Sunday best with a big St. Bernard between them, listening eagerly.
And the Steiner looks like an old lady was put in a shrinking machine.
Steiner is like a stern 80 year old, but child size.
There's like a woman in like horror movies or like kind of.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Who am I talking about?
I forget her name. She's in the she's in Poltergeist.
Yes. Yes. Who is that?
Yeah. Yeah. It's a.
Whatever her name is. Yeah.
It's a little girl version of that actress.
Frustrated. I can't think of the name.
And then look at that big creepy speaking of Joker smiles.
This dog.
What a massive mouth on this dog.
I like him.
That's a mutant dog of some kind.
What's the name of the.
Who's the raven again?
Jump along Jack.
A little raven named Jump along Jack.
And there was a dog there.
And of course, the crows.
What a time.
The children would tell jokes.
They were just kidding, of course.
I want everyone to remember these were the most exciting moments of the summer.
We're showing them to you now.
The scrapbook ride.
Scrapbook ride.
What a day.
What a life.
Says an old man at a typewriter under a tree.
But then.
Now a bunch of bees conveyed with lights are sort of buzzing around him.
Not so serene anymore.
Then you go to the best subtitle in the ride or in any ride.
Melker installs a water flume.
Now it's just an old man.
He's got like a big wooden rig that's kind of like water is going to pour down into the kitchen.
And then you kind of travel with it and you see how it works.
Wow.
OK, so it goes into the window.
Very good.
And then into the sink.
And the children are excited because Melker has done a good job installing the flume.
You know that I'm like halfway through that Netflix show Midnight Mass and it takes place on an island.
Off the coast of New England.
And there's a number of islands like that off the coast of New England where it's like only a few dozen and maybe a few hundred people live on the island.
There's a few ferries every day.
And you know, it's modern.
They have the Internet and stuff and iPhones.
But like a lot of stuff moves really slowly because such a pain in the ass to get everything from the mainland.
And I'm going to say Midnight Mass, too much religious phenomenon and supernatural weirdness happening.
I just want the simple island life of V-Paw Salt Crack.
And I want an American adaptation of that.
Seacrow Island is where you belong.
The whole thing is like the it's like the beginning of a horror movie where things are still a little too still.
But then they aren't.
They're perfectly still.
Just as life should be sometimes.
Wow.
Man, Jason, you've got to get this on DVD.
Let's see.
This is a big salt crack and fiend.
July 1960s.
More diary entries.
He has really done some hard work.
There's a little kid goes nuts with the paints.
Oh, what a mess.
But he stands proudly of the he doesn't know it's a problem.
He's expressing himself in his little diaper and socks and smock.
Lovely diary.
Just being a kid.
I got my prints.
Yes.
Then the old grandpa is in a tux.
This is a wedding.
I think he falls off.
I love us.
Wait, did I did I miss something?
Well, I just the tux the tux.
The tux.
Yeah.
Uncle Melker.
Why do you always swim with your clothes on?
It is strange.
A lot of people.
I don't know.
It is strange.
A lot.
Then you go through a door and it's just stills from the show.
I will always the woman ages up again.
It's the structure of Titanic.
You see, it's all of story that a woman is telling in her autumn years.
But why?
But that story is a little violent and a lot sexy.
And we don't want that kind of arousal.
Why does sea travel have to be so dramatic?
Yeah.
That old woman in Titanic should have kept the story to herself.
Tell us a nice story, lady.
Right.
Where was the accidental paint mix up?
The synopsis of this ride is lice little hiccups, but no one got hurt and we all laughed about them afterwards.
It's kind of nice.
I like that.
It is. I'll be honest.
It is kind of nice.
And because it's so unusual, I wish I.
I wish I.
Yeah, it's I wish there were at least a few more rides that were as mundane as this.
You know, it's almost it's like if you think about it, it's a similar amount of mundane to the Winnie the Pooh ride.
Right. But you think of Winnie the Pooh as being more exciting because you get to see a living tiger and a donkey.
Yeah.
And he trips out.
He trips out.
And there's a yeah, yeah, yeah.
There's nothing nearly as exciting as that in this ride.
But it's like so this is sort of like if the Winnie the Pooh ride was all humans, it's like what is what who else does Christopher Robin hang out with?
What's Christopher Robin's uncle like?
That's what this ride is.
Well, they made a movie about that and America went not interested.
No, thank you.
I wonder how it did in Sweden.
Maybe it I think that the Salt Cracken fans were like finally a return to form.
This is like if they were to make a ride out of Jason going back to the shore for a vacation, it's like, ah, Jason relaxes with a crime novel in a lounge chair.
Ah, look at this saltwater taffy for sale.
Don't mind if I do, says Jason.
Where are we going for dinner tonight?
The fish house or the Italian restaurant?
Those are the those are the options.
There's a number of both.
It took a minute to decide, but ultimately we were pleased with Italian and we did the fish house the next night.
We did not consider this a hiccup.
I met a crow fellow.
I have a crow friend named Jump Along Jason.
Out of swordfish, but you should have gotten there earlier.
The specials always go fast.
Yeah, that's nice.
This is really nice.
I mean, you know, I came into it describing it as weird or even like thinking about or what are my angles here?
How can I say how this ride is creepy?
But having kind of lived in it with you guys, it's been it's been very pleasant.
I feel calmer for having visited Sea Crow Island and I bet all the guests at Astrid Blingren Park.
Was that it?
I bet they all were just as relaxed.
Yes, Astrid Blingren's world.
I mean, it's so pleasant.
Can I ask, did you know did you stumble on another of Astrid's IPs that might have been interest to this podcast?
No, no.
OK, let me show you real quick.
This shouldn't take too long.
But here's a character she's created.
Carlson on the roof.
Wow.
Well, you were enjoying the antics of Velker, whatever up on the roof.
And there's now there's a Carlson to go on the roof too.
Yes, here they are.
I'm not exactly sure.
But apparently Russians love Carlson on the roof as well.
This article says here he is.
I think this is Carlson on the roof.
This is like a little he's like a red headed Ed Asner.
He's like a little red headed as there he has like he kind of like flies.
He's got like a propeller on his back of his overalls.
Yeah, to get up to the roof to get up to the roof.
And I know this is familiar, but I've never investigated exactly.
Carlson, by the way, is spelled K.A.R.L.S.S.O.N.
Not how I spell mine.
But still, I feel a kinship with Carlson as long as he's not problematic.
I haven't read the books.
Wait, read that description.
Hang on.
Yeah, yeah.
Here we go.
It says I am a handsome, remarkably wise and reasonably plump man in the prime of my life.
Carlson on the roof.
Now, look, fellows, I wouldn't describe either of you as reasonably plump, but I were you to be this.
I could see either of you like proudly owning this.
Yes.
And we would definitely if we were that, we would have a little propeller on our back of our overalls as well.
I guess next year for Halloween, I should go as Carlson on the roof with the propeller.
So anyway, the costume is bombing hard.
You're explaining it sweatily all night.
And then you go to little Sweden, deep in Los Angeles, rarely talked about area and like Carlson, put him on the roof.
To the roof.
And they lift you up there and then they, your real name is Carlson.
Oh, you're the king of little Sweden.
Live here forever.
Rent free.
I mean, it sounds nice what you're describing.
It sounds nice.
It's all nice.
What a wonderful.
I don't know.
Maybe I got to read some Astrid Lindgren.
Everything is nice.
Astrid is nice.
I think we don't go digging as with America, not America, England's most popular female children's author who has pretty not good things about her lately.
Hopefully Astrid Lindgren is nowhere near that.
And it's just like a nice good step in it.
By the way, yeah, for us to not have done any research and talk about a woman who was born in 1902, Scott.
I think in Europe with all the things that could have happened in Europe.
Dangerous, very dangerous.
Well, Sweden stayed out of World War II, right?
Weren't they in neutral territory?
As far as I know.
So that's a good start.
Well, I'm not seeing anything.
Let me see.
Animal protection.
Look, I haven't gotten to children animal rights or opposition to corporal punishment.
So far, so good.
So far, good.
She made a speech called Never Violence.
Never means never.
That's true.
That doesn't mean just sometimes.
Oh, no.
This.
Oh, God.
I was going to say this section of her Wikipedia says the scourge of redheads.
Oh, no.
Shit.
Carlson on the roof was.
To do character assassination of dumb redheads.
She did.
You know, Vipassault Kraken seems like a nice palate cleanser to like the the antics of Carlson and Pippi, you know.
Right, right, right.
Too mischievous.
Yeah, calm down.
There's no mischief in Vipassault Kraken.
Maybe the weirdest ride I've ever found.
I don't know if you guys agree.
But I would venture to say if we were to list the three weirdest rides we found being theme park fans doing this show, at least one or two of them would be would have been made by Sally Dark Rides.
For sure.
I mean, boy, oh boy.
We thought we thought it was an odd body of work and we didn't even know the full extent of it.
Well, well, we might have to go digging again.
Audience, tell us your favorites.
If you're aware of other rides they've done that we should be aware of.
Let us know.
But this is great.
I think this is because we wouldn't have ended up in Astrid Lindgren's world or a holiday where these are or the or Lombard.
They're all like these.
They're their works are spread out disparately all over weird parts of the world.
But they all add up into an insane greater whole.
They have that Sally voice.
You know, they talk about an artist, an artist as a voice and the Sally company as a whole as a voice.
And I like that the voice is everywhere around the world.
Yeah, that's nice.
It's fantastic.
I mean, so great job, Sally.
Keep on keeping on.
Keep it weird.
Keep Sally weird.
You survived podcast Ride the Second Gate and keep it tuned here to podcast the Ride the Second Gate for three bonus episodes every month.
Perhaps more Sally to come, perhaps more Hard Rock Park to come.
Lots of possibilities.
And it's also and of course, let's hope for more Pippin to come.
Of course, the jam and jesters do the entire do it front to back bands do front to back.
All the time.
Now that's yeah.
But do the whole show.
Did Ben Varine ever sit in with the jesters and do Pippin stuff?
I hope he did.
I haven't found the video yet, though.
We'll find out and many more things.
Thanks for listening.
Goodbye.
Bye.