Forever.
Dog.
Howdy folks, welcome to our week long Country Bear thing.
Quick heads up, today's episode features Mule Talk, Goofy getting hit by a car, and Joe Piscopo
on a cruise ship.
Just wanted to warn you, it's Country Bear Jam for week day one on today's podcast, The
Ride.
Howdy folks, welcome to the one and only original podcast, The Ride Country Bear Jamber Week,
a daily podcast series devoted to the Walt Disney World, Tokyo Disneyland, and dearly
departed Disneyland attraction, the Country Bear Jamboree.
We made it, we finally did it.
I'm swinging Scotty Gerdner, joined by big car Albson.
Howdy there, yes, that's my name.
I was going to call you, if I was doing the intro, Scooch or Scooter Gerdner, I think.
That works.
Because I was trying to think of a name.
But anyway.
Anybody else can be swinging.
Yeah.
I have a Jason, if you want.
If you accept it.
I'd love to hear both Jason.
I have one too for Jason, but go ahead.
Well, maybe we landed on the same thing.
Mine was Jason Bonnet Sheridan.
That's good and more clever than mine, but I think I do have to say mine because it ties
into something that I said on the show a while ago.
I was just going to call him Jason Jughead Sheridan.
It's double meaning because Jughead, obviously we like Jughead because of the Archie Comics
character, but also I said many, many years ago at this point that what I wanted is Jason
Sheridan to learn how to play the jug for the Country Bear episode.
And I have a jug with me here.
I feel like he didn't learn it though.
I had a jug.
I didn't.
It's a little water in it because I was, I watched it real quick because I forgot about
it until the last second here, but this is a jug.
I cleaned it.
It's freshly cleaned.
So, when you-
Whoa folks, there's a genuine jug.
I brought a jug with for Jason Jughead Sheridan.
And what was his other name?
Jason Bonnet Sheridan.
Oh, Jason Bonnet Sheridan.
I think you both did a great job.
Jughead Jason Bonnet Sheridan.
Why not all of it?
Why not the longest name?
Yeah, that's good.
Okay.
Let's clear the air.
Let's, okay.
Cause we got a whole week here.
It'd be great if there was improvement by the end of it.
So let's hear just unvarnished Jason Jugheading.
I'm getting a little.
Okay.
So here's the thing.
I watched a couple of YouTube videos of jug instruction.
Of people hooting on a jug.
And here's the thing I didn't know about playing the jug.
Cause I thought it was more like what you're trying to do right now.
It's actually a lot more, you make the noise with your mouth and then it resonates off
the bottom of the jug.
So you're making a-
And put it into the jug.
That's actually good jug.
That's good jugging actually.
That's good jugging?
Yeah.
That's actually good jugging is from what I understand according to YouTube.
This is also a glass jug.
It's not the ceramic brown and white kind of traditional jug.
He says a glass jug might be a little bit tougher, but you can do a couple of these
gentlemen instructed me about this online.
And you can do it in a milk jug, an empty milk jug that's plastic.
You can do the classic, what you're talking about, the ceramic that you've seen, you know,
like everybody drank moonshine out of.
That's the issue is where are we getting one of those?
Where are we getting an old timey jug?
They used to be everywhere.
And now I don't know where I'd go for a jug.
Well maybe by the end of the week we'll have a ceramic jug for Jason, but this is what
I had on hand.
Listeners, point us to like, where do you think is the most authentic jug that we could
get?
Yeah.
So Jason, if we call for it during the episode or anytime this week, if you could just do
a little jugging for us, I would appreciate it.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, I'll do my best.
Okay.
As always with this show, I promise to try my damnedest.
Cause you know, like you're like when Lisa had the jug on the Simpsons and Homer would
ask her to play it to cheer him up.
Yeah.
Well, and so if like somebody's looking up information that they don't have at the ready
or if the cricket comes back, we've had a cricket issue here in the garage.
We need to deal with that.
You're going to need to fill the time.
That's a great little bit of audio color for like a country bear jamboree kind of like,
you know,
Oh, a cricket would be great.
Yeah, I wouldn't care.
Would you're, you're currently holding it's a little, it's like a modern water bottle,
but it looks a little like a drug.
Yeah.
This is, this is a, it's got the wood.
It's slowly the wood slowly fading away.
Cause it's like a couple of years old.
It's like a swell style.
You think you can get anything out of that, out of the swell?
Maybe it's full of water.
No, I'd say that.
I think, yeah.
Can I play the empty burger king cup with ice in it?
Let's see how I can get out of my zone.
I can get out of this.
I got a glass iced tea.
See that's pretty, I'm doing too much of the work there.
A little too much.
Yeah.
That's not genuine.
And there speak of the devil.
There's the cricket.
Wow.
Really?
Where's that cricket?
That cricket sit back.
Wow.
We have some characters here today, including our cricket friend.
Wait, this is the opportunity.
Mike here, Mike hit the wall and Jason cover with the.
All right.
I'm going to hit the wall, hit the wall to try to get the cricket to stop.
Jason go.
Didn't work.
There was a brief pause with the cricket though, when I heard the sound.
Wait, if I can ask what was in this jug beforehand?
I'm getting a little bit of like a citrus flavor.
That's got to be the soap.
Yeah.
That's the soap.
Okay.
Well, we're keeping an ear out for the cricket, but there's a couple of bits of business to
do here at the beginning of this new event series.
It's been a little while excited to be doing, doing it.
It means we have different stuff at play.
We've got a new country fried theme song courtesy of our own Mike Carlson.
Thank you.
Fantastic.
Thank you very much.
It's fun.
Yeah.
You go out to the bar and you whip up that old fashioned garage band and you just see
what happens.
You know, I have my plugins.
I'm using logic filters.
I'm using logic on Apple.
That's just, that's quality.
You help me out with the pro tools here.
Pro tools acting up again.
My midi keyboard is acting up.
My midi ports ain't showing up.
I got no ports.
This is a hee haw sketch.
Pretty good.
Jug modern day jug, but 21st century jug.
Yeah.
And we've got great artwork courtesy of Tonagrassa.
And this I'm excited about.
If you're a long time listener to the show, you might know this art already because a
long time ago he, they did art called the good boy jamboree.
And I think maybe the best fan art probably we've ever received.
It's up there for sure.
As the country bears.
Aaron, my wife often does like the special art for, and the main art for these things.
But in this case she was like, you already got good boy jamboree.
It's gotta be good boy jamboree.
Use that.
Yeah.
Tona helped us out and thanks so much.
And you can check out more of Tona's work at, in the show notes.
Yeah.
Sure.
They'll be there.
Yeah.
It's so good.
So it's, you know, we freshen it up for this week.
Everything's fresh.
Yeah.
And it feels good.
I feel the sheen and the shine, the moonshine where it's, we've turned into a, it's a real
hoot and holler now.
Yeah.
So we're gonna, yeah, we're gonna do a lot.
There's a lot of content coming this week.
And I don't think we're not gonna say everything.
It'll be a fun, fun surprise.
Yeah.
I think so.
Cause you might, yeah, you could make guesses as to how we'll, we'll sort of break everything
down and parse this into different areas and topics.
But I don't know that you could, you could guess all the twists and turns.
I'll say that if you want the full country bear jamber week experience, you should subscribe
to the second gate at hn.com slash podcast, the ride.
But I think most of what we're doing right here on the main feed, uh, for, for our good
old family.
Cause we're one big, we're one big family here.
You're entitled to most of the content in front of the paywall.
We're generous bars.
Yep.
Just a little, but just a little bit.
You gotta pay.
Family's got to chip in.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
You want to hear the two hour episode about buck Owens, his music career.
You got to listen to the patron and pay us a little money.
Oh, that'll get them over there.
Oh yeah.
I see such a spike today.
Um, yeah, this, this I think is exciting.
It's cool to be tackling something to really like do, do a major here, do a thesis.
We're really, this is a thesis project about, about an attraction.
It is.
Yeah.
Um, and I, you know, that deep breath that you just did, Mike, that was a question I
had is I think, I think for you, maybe this is the biggest, um, hill to climb because
this has been looming for a long time.
I recall an instance where I suggested maybe doing the country, Virginia and you said pretty
seriously, I have, you know what?
I got to tell you, I'm not ready.
I'm not, I don't think I can do it yet.
I'm not ready.
Yeah.
So now, now we're here.
Are you ready?
I would say this, uh, I am ready in the sense that I'm always ready, which is, uh, something
that a podcast friend, Matt Cardona uses as a tagline.
So I'm always ready, but am I ready?
No, I'm not ready, but that's look, Saturday night live.
They say, you know, it's the show.
What do they say about it?
It goes on.
It doesn't go on because it's ready.
Exactly.
They say that about studio 60.
Do they say that?
They say that, yeah, the show goes on because it's a Friday night at 11 at a theater resembling
of the palladium, but that isn't the palladium.
Right.
That's studios.
So the hallowed studio 60.
Did you see the thing there in Sorkin said about I love Lucy?
That he, that it's not, if we looked at it today, it's not funny.
Right.
Fuck off.
Are you kidding me?
No, no.
He said that he makes making the Lucy movie anyway.
But no, I'm who we've been trusted with this property.
I am not ready, but I'm ready.
Yeah.
Okay.
Great.
Um, I mean, because like, you know, we're, we're taking our time here and that's, that's
some of what I think is easing us into it that we don't have to get to all of it today.
But the, the notion of today's episode is that this is the country bear jamboree, right?
The primary thing, the big ticket item.
Now I was, I should say at the top, I think that if we stumble into something or we're,
we're at like the distant mo we're at three and a half hours and we haven't even gotten
to big Al, whatever it is, I think we could call for an episode.
Ah, yes.
Break off.
Of course.
We could, we could break off a piece.
I agree with that.
If we need to.
So let's put that option on the table.
Anything yet.
If you want to call for it a full episode during this show, you can about any topic.
Don't, don't summon that spell.
Unless you're ready to cast it.
You gotta be sure.
I'm sure there's enough, there's enough meat there.
But again, but also it's a, you know, it's a, it's a saga or an ordeal or a jam or week.
We've used a lot of words at this point and that's, you know, that, that setup is hopefully
so that, um, these episodes don't all have to be a minimum two and a half hours, but
maybe they all are.
I don't know.
I don't know what the shape of these will be.
I think part of my mental thinking or the way that it's shaping up is we, we just kind
of had this, you know, buckle up and just do it.
Cause we've talked so many different angles on it.
It's like, well, at a certain point you just have to break down and it just becomes something.
Maybe I'm still delaying it, but even talking about process.
I guess we just got to dig in and on this attraction, which I'm glad we're doing it
now because it is the 50th anniversary, just like Walt Disney world.
This was an opening day while Disney world attraction.
So it's celebrating its 50th anniversary.
Still there.
It's made it there.
It was opening day Tokyo and it's still there as well.
And notable for being the very first to open, uh, open at Walt Disney world and then get
cloned for Disneyland.
This is the first time that happened in that order.
Oh yeah.
Most things started at Disneyland and they made us, they shipped the door land out.
Yeah.
And it changed the complexion of Disneyland or I guess the name.
My complexion seems like a lot.
Well, we had keep going.
What do you mean by that?
Well, like bear country then became a thing.
Like that, that area all became bear country because of the country bears.
Yeah.
Well that that's kind of like, um, one thing I find interesting about all this is that
it opened in Florida, seemingly pretty big smash hit there pretty beloved out of the
gate in Florida.
So much so that I think it was pretty hyped coming into Disneyland and California and
maybe too much in a way, because it's a little unassuming in Florida.
Like it's, it's one of, it's one of a bunch of attractions.
This one's new and exclusive to Disney world.
That's cool.
But there wasn't a lot of pressure put on it.
Maybe that helped it take off here in Disney by the time they get it to Disneyland, it
gets an entire land devoted to it, uh, which happens pretty rarely that an attraction is
accompanied by an entire land.
And also they are also e-ticket.
We're still doing the ticket system at that point and they name it an e-ticket attraction,
which I don't think, I don't think people, I don't think we've talked a lot about the
ticket system.
I don't even know what a lot of these older attractions were ticket wise, but today e-ticket
is thrown around mostly for thrill rides.
You'd think that that system was retired, but Indiana Jones or rise of the resistance,
you'd imagine would be e-tickets kind of weird that a theater show, that a sit down show
was considered an e-ticket.
In my heart, it's not weird, but it is weird for the average public.
I think.
Yeah.
So we have a graphic that yesterland preserved from like 72 73 of all the e-tickets at Disneyland.
Okay.
Do you want to guess some of them?
Um, do we have, there's no big thunder yet.
Not yet.
Uh, the haunted mansion pirates.
Correct.
Uh, how many we got here?
Um, two, four, six, eight, somebody else has got a joke while he can't read.
Like 11.
There's 11 on here.
Uh, 11 really?
Then like, is the, uh, at that point in time is like the railroad, an e-ticket.
That's a good question.
Um, the, uh, a mode of transit is.
Monorail?
Monorail is.
Monorail is an e-ticket.
Small world an e-ticket at that point?
Small world is an e-ticket.
Interesting.
Yeah.
Okay.
Matterhorn then?
Uh, Matterhorn is not listed.
What?
What are you talking about?
Small world and not Matterhorn?
Really?
When does Matterhorn open?
Is Matterhorn not open?
No, it's open.
I'm sorry.
Matterhorn is on here.
Oh, thank God.
I'm losing my mind.
This is not the clearest graphic.
Uh, what else we got?
Uh, we have the Monorail, the Jungle Cruise.
Huh?
Uh, the mine train through nature's wonderland.
Oh, interesting.
Um, the submarine voyage.
Hmm.
Pretty good.
Can we list what wasn't an e-ticket at this point?
I mean, the other, the weirdest one to me.
Walking down Main Street e-ticket.
The strangest one to me that not only was it an e-ticket, but it was still here.
Pack mules.
Wow.
Yeah.
Writing a mule.
Pack mule is an e-ticket.
That's right.
Wow.
It's a vaunted phrase that they only, like, that they say in this, let me tell you, this
is going to be a real e-ticket akin to writing a mule that might take a dump or like spit,
it's like just piss all over your shoes.
If you could still ride a mule at Disneyland, you would have to pay for the Lightning Lane
to ride a mule.
Lightning Lane for a mule ride.
You would have to pay $15 for the Lightning Lane to ride a mule at Disneyland.
By the time an entire family has done it and if you're there with a big, you might, some
people travel with bigger families than there are mules.
Yeah, sure.
So what do you do in that case?
They've paid the money, you want to make it work.
Yeah, a family, an angry family reunion and matching t-shirts arguing, like, you've got
to get more mules out here.
And a collective $210.
I mean, if they, if like Bob Chapek or Demaro was on stage at one of these D23 type places
and they're like, we are starting a virtual queue for the mule rides at 7 a.m.
You will wake up and get on your app and get a spot in line for mules during the day and
that will go quickly.
So you have to get up at that time and everyone's writing articles about how to get in the virtual
queue for a mule and just all of us queue for a mule.
Geez.
All the theme park media pleading with them.
Please update the mules are very old.
They are struggling.
Several of them are from the opening of Disneyland.
Several of these are original days.
Let shooter retire.
Shooter to deal with Bob Cummings opening day and now he has to deal with me.
Most of shooters legs are fake.
Let him rest.
I'm going to be the first to say I don't know anything about mules, but I'm going to hazard
a guess that they either live very few years or they're like turtles where it's like, oh,
they live a long time.
Yeah.
The average mule was 300 years old.
It lives to be 300.
Mules are sterile.
Yes.
So they can't sit there.
So when a mules or donkeys, one of them, I think it's difficult to make.
It's difficult to make.
Well, they're sterile.
They're not like, you know, hold on, hold on.
This is important at the top of the country.
We got to do some animal husbandry.
We got to cover a bunch of non country bear mule, just stats about real mules.
Mule.
Okay.
Continue talking while I do this.
Well, at Disneyland, this I thought was interesting when it did come to Disneyland because they
were predicting it being such a hit.
Two theaters.
Florida has one theater.
Tokyo also has two theaters.
Seemingly still a big hit there.
Okay.
I was correct.
They are sterile because they can't make sperm or eggs.
A female horse and a male donkey have a mule.
Got it.
Oh, so once, but then that a mule is an evolutionary dead end.
Basically.
Yes.
Like our country.
It's, it was a dead end.
Bear country, the mule of lands.
Yeah.
Um, I mean, yeah, that's, that is all pretty crazy.
Like it's, it's coming in blockbusters that you got to use the biggest ticket on it.
It's its own land.
It's two theaters.
And I, and I think it like, did all that hurt it in a way?
Did that make it not take off in California ever to the degree that it did in Disney world
and seemingly Tokyo, Mike, I think you can attest or you got to see it there, right?
Was it?
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Um, psyched crowds.
That was like a absolutely hyped audience.
Although lately I've been noticing that in Orlando as well.
I think people, it depends.
Sometimes.
Yes.
I was going to say that, yeah, just it depends.
I've been there where no one gives a shit.
I've watched YouTube videos where no one gives a shit, but then I have been in there with
a crowd that likes it.
Yeah.
And I think it's infectious.
I think if there's a couple people in the country bear crowd who are determined to give
it their all and really cheer for everything and really clap for everything and who laugh
at the things that there are to laugh at, um, then everybody has a better time.
I think in general, the more the audience puts into it, the more they, uh, the more
everybody gets out of it.
It's just like the end of the Abbey road suite.
The love you make is equal to the love you take.
I agree with that completely.
They famously cut the hoedown portion of, there was a right after the big drum solo,
there is a big, uh, jug solo.
Yeah.
They will, they all turn, take turns jugging.
Pretty different jug players take turns jugging like the guitar solos at the end.
When John Lennon was staying at the Polynesian, do you think he saw the country bears?
Whoa.
What a question.
Oh my God.
Can I call for an episode about this?
About this hypothetical?
Well, I don't know how you find, how you verify any of this.
The other thing about that story that I had read on some sort of like long form article,
like ages ago, and I don't know, I don't remember where it was.
I don't remember how well sourced, um, but I think it had kind of a debunking angle of
like, Oh, the papers were presented there, but they realized the lawyers had to tweak
something.
So he was further down.
Uh, he was either Miami or he was somewhere else in Florida when he finally got the final,
final pep.
I have to dissolve the Beatles.
To dissolve the Beatles.
Yeah.
I have seen this correction that he didn't actually dissolve the Beatles in Disney, in
the pollination.
But he got papers that were going, that was going to do that.
But yeah, the final, final ones, I guess happened somewhere else.
Would he have been like, um, would he have enjoyed the country bears?
Would he have been impressed by them?
Like the way he, you know, he likes a Nielsen, like, uh, I respect to my musical peers.
Would it have stressed him out?
Uh, like it feels like work to him to go analyze another great band's music.
They liked, uh, they liked, uh, like American country, Western.
I mean, Ringo covers Buck Owens is act naturally and Buck Owens has a song in the country bears.
Oh, that's an interesting crossover.
I don't think I knew he was the artist of act naturally.
Uh, yes, yes.
So, uh, you know, that song, of course, they're going to put me in the movies.
They're going to make a big star out of me.
Yeah.
I mean, I think a lot of those British invasion bands, I mean, the early, early stone records
are mostly like covers of like a blues and country songs.
Right.
Did any of them do a blood on the saddle?
Well, it's okay.
It's a good question.
I don't know.
I mean, Elton John is in the country bear movie.
Spoiler alert.
I guess I shouldn't have said that, but he has a bunch of old, he is like a bunch of
very country Western tumbleweed connection and stuff, like all these different influences.
So I think that would be right up John Lennon's alley.
It has a question.
You might've appreciated it.
I think he would have loved it.
Yeah.
Unless he was just like high out of his mind and doesn't recall seeing it and it was not
really possible.
It was the, it was, it was with may pang right now with Yoko.
It was a long weekend situation.
I guess so.
Yeah.
In the photo, the Polynesian, it's may pang, right?
I believe so.
Yeah.
And she's also, I think in the, is she the one in the photo of him doing like the Mr.
Nat, he's doing that crazy walk.
I don't know.
I can't remember.
Okay.
I can't remember that photo where he looks like an alien.
I won't tall string being alien.
I won't remember it.
Um, I refused to, sorry, may my eyes are straying.
I've got a new, I might have a new girlfriend.
Her name's swinging Teddy bar.
When it was so high, he like clung to her animatronic as she went into the ceiling.
There's a man trying to ride up into the rafters correction.
That's the most famous man on the planet.
John Lennon had a long weekend with swinging Teddy bear from may pang.
Right.
I'm being told to allow it to happen.
Uh, he's going to, he's going to stay up there.
We don't want any trouble with Apple records.
So, uh, let's not bother him for the weekend folks.
Paul famously had to go and tell John, get back with Yoko leave swinging Teddy bear.
He went to him in California.
Is it funny because it's Trixie was seeing text Ritter at the time and she got him in
the show.
Sure.
Yeah.
Uh, I, so where do, where do you even begin here?
Uh, I mean, we could talk a little bit about where it, where it came from because it, um,
you know, as with a lot of stuff that was put into Disney world originally, like there's
a couple of attractions that were new to Disney world and, uh, Walt had passed away, been
a deceased for five years or so, but a lot of the new attractions in Disney world still
had roots to stuff he was alive and helped think of.
It's like not till further down the road that they finally are willing to try an attraction,
but Walt didn't sort of approve.
Um, but this, yeah, he was around for an iteration of the country bear jamboree because it was
meant for a ski resorts that never got built.
Mineral king.
The mineral king ski resort.
Um, I mean, it starts of course when Walt was the chairman of pageantry for the squaw
valley Olympic games.
Of course.
Uh, I'm going to call my own episode.
Uh, all right, squab out.
Uh, I was looking that up and like you would, you'd think like a, an entire Disney run.
He did not like do like a custom animatronic show.
I don't think he had the lead time to, he didn't make up the Tiki room or have like
an original show about, um, you know, chipmunk skiers and uh, like, uh, vulture shot putters
or what have you.
I don't think anything too interesting was happening there, but, uh, I guess in doing
so he got interested in, in putting together a ski resort.
Um, I don't know the math super well of how all that played out, but that's a property
that's it's now part of Sequoia.
It is, it wasn't at the time it got annexed in the 17th century.
It was the 70s.
Um, but yeah, he wanted to build what would have been the biggest ski resorts in America,
um, and drew up a lot of plans for it.
And in doing so he, it was like, well, what do people do at night?
We have to come up with something once the skiing is over.
And he tasked Mark Davis with coming up with a great imaginary.
We've talked about a lot, really responsible for a lot of the, you know, funnier, zanier
character designs over the year.
These characters where you feel like you get a picture of the whole character just when
you look at his concept or forget about even the robot is concept art says so much just
speaks volumes.
Um, the whole quote I have, uh, Walt commissioned Mark Davis to come up with shows that would
keep those folks and their money right there at mineral King.
Uh, Walt thought maybe we should have a show that had something to do with bears said Mark,
lots and lots of bears.
And he went off and thought of a lot of different bears and a review that they could do.
Um, but here's something interesting.
I discovered in all this that, uh, something Mark Davis said is that the drawings that
he showed Walt had all kinds of bears.
Sure.
There was a country band, but also a jazz band, a circus band, a one bear band and a
red outfit with a bunch of instruments he was playing.
So because if this was supposed to be in Northern California, um, country music is not, you
know, the exclusive dominant music there.
So there's an alternate version of this where it's not the country bear jamboree, just a
bear, the bear show, the bear concert.
Yeah, it's multiple things.
It's like, uh, uh, Andrew Dice Clay used to do a bunch of characters and then he settled
on one of the concepts that became his whole persona.
That's exactly the same thing.
I see.
Hmm.
So like there were a lot of versions that could have been of a bear band.
Um, I guess it's actually kind of like America sings where there were multiple, like they
weren't all sort of a part of one like group on America sings that were different.
Yeah, essentially a bunch of American genres represented in half now canceled.
Right.
Yeah.
When you look at country bear jamboree and then America sings, it does feel because we
were talking about classic rock, like, uh, important rock bands.
It does feel like the trope of, you know, big first hit with country bear jamboree and
uh, kind of doesn't nail it on the sophomore efforts to ambitious, maybe too ambitious
or not focused enough for it's like American idiot and 21st century breakdown, you know,
21st century breakdown is not as good as American, right?
We haven't used this as metafitals fairly new.
We didn't land on this metaphor for half an hour.
We can't, we can't dive in more though.
We have so much to get to.
I was trying to think of like, is there a more current reference at all?
Like I think of it's like, well, that first shins album to that second shins album.
And I'm like, that's the same time period.
What am I talking about?
The first shins album, I think even older than American idiot.
Oh yeah.
Maybe.
Hmm.
I don't know.
I don't remember.
I liked the second shins album.
It's a first shins album.
The one with the garden state songs with caring is creepy.
Is that right?
Pretty well along before garden state.
Uh, but yes, a lot of it.
And then shoots too narrow is the second one.
I'm calling for a separate episode about shoots too narrow.
We got two already separate shins episode and that's going to be in country bear jamboree
week.
Okay.
Great.
Perfect.
If you're a good boy in college, you would order them online on the CDs come to your
dorm room and yeah.
If you're what I say, if you were a good boy, if you were an idiot like me, you didn't know
how to steal music.
Oh, I see.
Oh, you're so you were a good boy.
I was a good boy and I bought the album.
Sure.
Yeah.
So anyway, when they realized this was going to be a Florida specific attraction, that's
when it became country music because country music, country Western was the like, uh, dominant
music genre in Florida.
So I don't think I realized that that if it had started in California, maybe this is not
a country music attraction.
Yeah.
Not a jamboree at all.
I mean, I love the idea that they could have done just different bands for different spots,
different Disney parks, like different types of bear bands.
That's pretty fun.
Uh, so in Europe, is it like a craft works?
Oh, sure.
Oh man.
Oh, why?
Oh jeez.
Craft work.
Uh, just a really art.
Yeah.
With like, you know, we are the 3d components and they're aware that they're robots.
They know that they're robots.
Yeah.
We like, like the craft works on.
We are the robots.
We, we're the bear robots.
We are the bear robots is what you could call it.
Uh, yeah, that would be perfect.
Oh boy.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
You dampen my enthusiasm for the jamboree cause I'm just going to be thinking about
that hypothetical.
Also all of the, if you, if you kept it cause craft workers such like, you know, svelte guys
and then, but it's those kinds of suits, but like, but massive.
Yeah.
Fantastic.
700 pound.
So great.
Yeah.
That would be amazing.
Um, but I don't, the window for that has passed.
Sadly, there's no chance.
I don't think of us ever getting a new animatronic show based on characters that don't have a
TV show or movie.
I don't think maybe anywhere.
I don't think they're, because this kicked off, you know, I think I'm not sure that you
have Chuck E cheese without the country bear jamboree.
I think this is such a, you know, there'd been the Tiki room, uh, you know, there's
Lincoln and hall of presidents, but those aren't, you know, fun and for families, right.
Uh, depending on your view of things.
But, uh, this is, I mean, clearly the, just style wise and just the, you know, how much
you meet people and like, Hey, why don't you play us a two?
It's completely what Chuck E cheese turns out to them.
Yeah, for sure.
It's interesting because like where the Disney regional projects never really took off.
I mean, between mineral King and then there was that St. Louis indoor one Disney quest,
like very famously flamed out and, but Chuck E cheese got off the ground, but Disney couldn't
get their act together.
They tried weird.
Yeah, it is weird to think about it.
They had care, beloved characters that everyone knew, but they didn't figure it out.
I mean, I guess, yeah, Michael Eisner tried it later.
You got the store, but that's not the same.
Yeah.
I mean, how much did you look up in the rafters and wish that all of those characters, I loved
seeing those characters.
Yeah.
I wanted them to do something.
Of course.
Yeah.
But I mean, there were all these like rules.
And then like we talked about the directive DVD sequels and stuff where it's like, there
were just like rules in place.
And I think for awhile, the idea was like, Oh, they should be like just kind of contained
to hear.
But then Michael Eisner had some wild ideas, but then didn't go hard enough with them.
Maybe well, he was still stuck in the confines of the rules.
I mean, the same issues keep arising with that.
They can't get the regional stuff off the ground.
They can't get their act together there.
But also the problem you mentioned of, you know, Walt saying, how do we keep these people
and their money here at night?
That was the same idea with pleasure Island.
It's like they're leaving property.
They're leaving Disney world.
They're going to church street station or they're going elsewhere in Orlando.
We need some sort of nightlife.
Yeah.
Thing.
Um, which I don't look, I think if there's animatronic bear shows all over the country
in the world, everybody's money is going to it.
And that's still today.
I got not, not country bears, but I got like right before I came here, I was rewatching
the country bear jamboree and YouTube suggested it's like, do you want to watch this bear
animatronic show in Brazil?
It was also in England and I was like, what is this?
Like I had never come across this.
We have another episode to add this week.
I think it's worth looking into more, but I don't know anything about it.
Oh, wow.
Yeah.
And this look, this is inspired, this inspired a generation, multiple generations, uh, to
want to make their own animal talking animals show.
Uh, I think also people have written about it.
There is something about talking animals.
Like human beings have been obsessed with talking animals like forever and it is, it
is strange.
Yeah.
Like, but there is something about it that is funny, weird, fascinating.
I don't know.
It works better than human shit, like human animatronics just like sort of end up creepy
or at least did until the recent past where they've kind of cracked a little better.
But these guys can be big and round and fuzzy and don't you just like every country bear,
don't you want to just like grab their face, just like see what that feels like?
Just like, yeah, they're, uh, give their cheeks the shake more than anything.
Yes.
I want to do that.
Uh, the bear it's just, it's like, I mean, it is funny.
Cause obviously like a bear doesn't talk.
So you go in here and you see a bear talking and then singing sad songs or weird songs
and it's funny.
It's really funny.
So I think somewhere in the, I don't know if this was Mark's concept or Walt's concept,
but I think somewhere in the brainstorm was just the idea that, you know, if we're staying
with the mythology of the, this is like, we're in this ski resort, we're near the Sequoias,
uh, you know, you're, it's a regional thing.
So, uh, where we went out and we found some bears and we trained the bears to be musicians,
but not very well.
They are technically trained, but the show is a problem and it's high jinks and falls
away.
And that's like, I kind of never thought of that as the concept of the show, but it's
pretty neat.
And I think it makes you, I think the fact that the show's coming apart at the seams
a little bit in a very Muppet show, you know, what predating the Muppet show, there is no
Muppet show yet.
And I think there's a lot of Muppet show feel to the Country Bear.
Yeah.
Cause it's old, like vaudeville stage stuff and it definitely feels like, yeah, like,
like it's a fun zany show going wrong.
I didn't actually think of that, what you were saying about that.
Cause that is an element of the show is that it goes wrong, but it kind of isn't that bad.
I mean, like big L at the end is interrupting stuff and they argue with each other a little
bit, although they've cut some of the arguing from the recent, the newer show.
The newer version of the show, but in the vacation one, which we'll cover down the road,
there's the, there's the Rufus, the unseen bear who has to go fix problems.
Like you hear him climbing around to settle tech issues and what have you.
So that has a little bit of like coming apart at the scene, but yeah, it's, you know what?
Under that lens, they do a pretty good job.
Yeah.
They're a lot more professional than the Muppets.
Good, good musicians.
They're all, a lot of them are a little goofy.
Some of them are a little horny.
I think we can safely say that.
Well, I also very, yes, the show is horny, which is funny, which is something that, cause
when Lindsay and I went to Disney world, which I hadn't been in like 10 years, we went like
now, I guess 10 years ago that we went and we, I hadn't seen it in a decade or more and
we watched it and we were high.
We thought it was so weird and funny.
Not literally, of course.
Well, no, no, not literally.
No, of course.
Hope not.
But we ran up to somebody.
I'm sure I said this on the show before we ran up to cast members like, Oh, where's all
the, where's the country bear merchandise?
And they were like, we don't have any.
And I was like, we were like, what?
This is unbelievable.
But yes, the bears are horny.
I always thought, I always interpret it that a lot of them are hammered.
Like, like they're like, cause they're goofy.
You're saying goofy, but like they're like weird, like they seem out of it.
And I feel like that's a, you know, thing about country Western music, you know, and
honky tonks and dive bars and stuff.
Is it, they're all hammered?
You get, yeah, you get a little hammered, maybe a paid in drinks, you know?
But they're drinking human alcohol and it has the same effects as it would on a human.
I think, yeah.
If you give a bear moonshine, he's going to get drunk.
Suppose so.
Is that a thing, like other videos of like the bear broke into the, you mean like, like
on a frat party and it's like, let's get the bear drunk, man.
That's a dangerous endeavor for this frat, but, uh, I don't know.
I don't know if there's drunken bear YouTube videos.
It's like a dark part of the internet.
Bear bags in the Boy Scouts.
You'd have to, if anyone's gone camping around bears, you've talked about bear bags on the
show before.
Have I?
Yeah.
I think it's so interesting.
I mean, you, you just put all of your food, essentially, like most of your like dry good
food that you can't like seal in an airtight cooler or something, you put it in a bag and
you tie it with a rope and you hoist it up in the trees.
So the bear can't really get to it.
Yeah.
So you put your moonshine up in the tree so the bear can't get it during the night when
you're sleeping.
Sure.
According to backpacker.com, the answer is a qualified yes.
Like almost all animals, uh, wait a minute.
This is like from the point of view of a bear.
All right.
I'm confused by this.
I don't know how to appeal.
I was starting to read it and it was like, ah, yes, I can.
All right.
Well, I guess, all right.
I am susceptible to the sauce and will experience the effects of alcohol provided I drink a
ton of it.
I see.
Uh, there's got to, what animal wouldn't get drunk if you gave it alcohol?
Oh, here's a, uh, in 2004 federal wildlife agents found a black bear passed down on the
lawn of a resort in Baker Lake, Washington after drinking 36 cans of beer.
Oh my God.
Sure.
So there's one.
How did that happen?
Wait, how do you like 36 cans?
You slash a cube that you slash like a, a crate of though.
I guess so.
But in the slashing doesn't most of the beer come out.
Yeah.
How would the bear get it?
How would it know to like have its mouth by it?
Put your mouth, but you start, you smell it and you start like licking it up, you know,
36 cans though.
Then keep popping it, crushing it on its own head after it completes a can.
Uh, this is another, maybe the, you know, the daily nature of this, we can go off and
do homework.
I can get the full story of the Baker Lake drunk black bear incidents, figure out the
logic of it.
Uh, so John Lennon is homework, black bear is homework, but bears can get drunk.
So you're saying that these are, well, does this bother you?
Does it bother you that these are, uh, inebriated horned up performers?
Uh, it doesn't bother me.
They're not real.
They're, it's a, it's a fun, fun fantasy life for bears are anthropomorphic.
Uh, so no, I am not so bothered by it.
Um, but this is, I was thinking how, you know, because it's almost impossible to unravel
where some of the threads over the years on these podcasts have come from, but I do feel
like country bear jamboree is one of the primary sources in theme park world of Mae West level
sexuality, which has I think been a runner in your comfort level with such sexuality.
Yeah.
Interesting.
Uh, well, Mae West, I'd say all of the female bears, Mae West herself obviously was a big
influx.
She, everybody's been doing the Mae West thing.
I think for Ms. Piggy, everybody, like that's a rich tradition of kind of that vibe that
Mae West vibe.
Um, so yeah, no, I think it would be interesting to know where this thread came from when the
first time I, I wrinkled my nose up at some sort of bodyness and was bought was the first
use of the word body related to the country bears.
I think it was, I misused the word body.
I think that's honestly what it was.
I used it wrong.
I was like an idiot and said body in the wrong way and then now I'm Mr. Body.
I'm bodyness is part of the fabric.
Yes.
Uh, so yeah.
Uh, but no, this is, uh, um, this is the ball.
If a bodyness is funny, I have to give it up to it.
I have to give it up for the body.
It's body is for the sake of bodyness.
Yeah.
If it's, if you're just trying to be body and trying to be shocking, then that's not
something I'm interested in.
But if it's in this, in this service of comedy, in the service of comedy and it's funny little
bears doing it.
And it's safer.
Yes.
Saying like, as soon as I find a ladder, I'll be right up.
You know?
Well, the show would be a lot creepier for humans.
It would be much creepier.
Yeah.
If everything that happened in it was a similarly proportioned human being.
Yes.
It would be one of the most disturbing shows of all time.
The country guys.
If it was older country guys who all look like they're melting.
If it's like a late in life Elvis.
The Knott's Berry farm like mine train.
Oh God.
The log workers.
The lumber workers.
A bunch of like wrinkle.
You look at them and think that they're 68, but they're actually 31.
They just lived a hard life.
Yeah.
The show would not be the same.
You'd be really worried about that one kid one.
Yeah.
As it stands, the kid who sits with the band, he's like part of the family.
But if there's only one child in this seedy world, you could rescue him.
Raise him as your own.
There would be a lot of concern if this was a human based show.
There would be a lot of people you would be worried about.
But yes, again, this is fun.
It's a fantasy.
Yeah.
The bears aren't real.
Uh huh.
So, oh you know who we should, because you guys brought this name to my attention.
Mark Davis isn't the only person to credit with the formation of this.
There's the guy, Al Bertino.
I hadn't heard that name until you brought him up and I needed it explained to me.
I was like, Albertino?
What is that?
No, it's Al, space, Bertino.
And he is the namesake of Big Al, the biggest, saddest country bear.
So we know anything else about Albertino.
Oh, that's about the Imagineer.
Oh, and I don't have anything written down here.
So I'm sure there's a lot about him, but I don't either.
All right.
Well, Al, you're not getting your full due then.
I know that Big Al is, you know, at the Disneyland version of this ride, there used to be like
bear sized dressing room doors.
Yeah.
And I always forget this, but Big Al's full name is technically Big Albert, which is very
funny to me in that it sounds like a thing that John Kerry messed up on the campaign
trail.
Like he was just like, I love the music of Big Albert.
Or like when he would get like when a politician just clumsily like they were prepped with
a local reference and they eat it, like they do something a little wrong.
What did John Kerry say?
Did he have a famous mess up of the?
Well, I mean, his whole vibe, like nothing he said sounds natural, but in Philadelphia,
he got a lot of flack because he went to a cheesesteak place and ordered a cheesesteak
with Swiss cheese, which get the fuck out of here, fancy man.
Like that, you don't do that.
That doesn't fly.
Cost them the election.
Yeah.
Jason voted for Bush that year.
It genuinely could not in his case.
He was, I don't think he came close, but being that Pennsylvania is a swing state, you really
can't mess that one up.
Yeah.
You got to know.
Very densely populated Southeastern PA.
Don't fuck up your sandwiches.
Any future candidates, please.
The future of the world depends on it.
That's true.
Jason's willing to coach you through regional.
I will coach you through.
Rolls and candies and.
Yeah.
Cause cause I think he had Pittsburgh cause Teresa Heinz Carey, you know, that that she
would have Pittsburgh.
She'd be like, okay, some of the places here put french fries and coleslaw on the sandwich.
So don't be confused, John.
Like don't freak out, you know.
Jason, you brought up that room.
I love that room.
I got to be in that room in Japan, the pre show room.
Yes, with essentially nobody in it because there was this horrible rainstorm.
The only one of my Japan trip that cleared out Tokyo Disneyland.
And since we survived it, we had every room to ourselves.
So we're just running around.
I hadn't looked at the pictures in a long time, but we went up to every door because
all of these characters and probably one thing we got to do is sort out these characters
because I didn't know straight till we started thinking about this show more.
But every character has doors that represents their, their height.
It's little, it's short doors for short characters, tall doors for tall characters.
There's doors that like expand out in the seat zone, only the seat zone so they can
make it through a swing and Teddy Barra.
The one who is, is it Barra or Barra?
Am I saying Barra?
I always heard it as Barra.
It's probably Barra.
I might be.
All right.
I'll, I'll, I'll stop it there.
I'm sorry, Teddy Barra, I think there's a little ladder and the door is up in the ceiling.
Oh, so she's going to climb up to get to her spot.
And so much other fun nonsense.
Like there is the song that they, they sing you on the way out the door.
There is musical notation of it that's scratched into wood.
Like Henry, the host like made the music notes, but scratched it with his claw.
I think they also have a record that is screwed that they scratched themselves like a weird
clunky bear scratched vinyl.
A lot of fun details in that opening room.
Yeah, that's really great.
I, I'm trying to remember.
We, we, I end up, I feel like we ended up rushing through that more in Tokyo when we
were there.
But going through back on the YouTube and looking at it, it's like, it is a pro.
Now would you say Scott, this queue is something that you would just skip immediately to go
into the theater.
I'm just saying it sounds pretty great.
I think that there's no version where you, there'd be like a long enough line where you'd
have to, but, but if there was a teleport machine outside of the country bear to teleport
you right into your seat, straight.
Look the answer is yes.
There is no one skippable queue.
There's no such thing.
I stand by this lot.
This is not the episode.
It's not the episode to do it.
We have too much too much to cover.
Sorry.
Too much.
We don't have the time here to discuss the issue that I was correct on in which there
was almost no support for the other side.
Anyway, moving on.
Well, we'll just, we'll discuss it in 2022.
We'll, we'll earmark it for that.
Cause again, I have, I have emails.
We'll talk about these emails.
Yeah.
Oh boy, that morning I thought I was going to open it.
I thought I was going to be so mad at me.
It was just a day of, I'm just laying back in bed.
Ah, another Scott is right.
Why another Scott is right?
So good.
So good to be me.
Well, you know, what it'll be a whole, we'll do two and a half hours.
And we'll bring in many judges.
I think too, there'll be a lot of independent, like independent councils and independent
judiciary bodies to help us litigate this, whatever it takes.
I'm ready for it.
I'm up for it.
Me too.
Folks prepare for it.
Um, anyway, you were the building that you're in is, uh, is grizzly hall.
Hello, grizzly hall.
That's technically where you are.
Um, it's not like anything else before you're just, you're in the place.
Um, you know, it's a, just a great place to see that beautiful Disney wood.
Yeah.
Uh, it's the best thing about frontier land or anything with a similar theme that it's
old and tarnished, but also shiny.
You want to like touch every inch of the room.
Yeah.
It would just looks great, feels great.
Um, and I, uh, yeah, I do, I do love, uh, I do love grizzly hall.
There's the old before they redid like Mrs. Knott's, I got the same vibe.
Even though the country bear lobby is better.
It's like, I still get the same vibe.
Like you're a hundred years back in time, maybe like there's an old vibe there.
Yeah.
I remember I kind of all my memories of country, but I remember are being in this room largely
empty, not just when I went recently in Tokyo, but like usually, and cause I feel like just
my park day trajectory, it would always be, I wouldn't get here till close to closing.
So you're in, and everybody's kind of like, nobody's seeing this thing late.
And I just have fond memories of like Disneyland's getting dim and it's all lantern lit around
frontier land now.
And a lot of, a lot of kids have gone home, but my mom's sticking it out with me or whatever
it is.
And where we got, we got grizzly hall to ourselves.
Um, so yeah, your memory is see, cause I saw this when I was little and I always liked it,
but I was not, I didn't like country music as a little kid.
No, I liked the animal.
I liked the robots, but I obviously didn't get any of the joke.
I didn't get most of the jokes.
So it didn't make a huge impression on me.
It's like, do you have memories of seeing it specific?
You're saying, I guess you do.
I do.
I like, I mean, my whole thing with it, I feel like I find this thing, like, uh, I always
liked it as a kid and I find it so pleasant and fun and I've always dug it, but the characters
have always been muddy in my head.
I don't, I haven't, like, I don't have a lot of like individual beats memory.
It's just a general feeling.
I like those guys on the wall, but I didn't have the names memorized, but where do you,
like, uh, did you get up to speed, Mike, in preparing for Jambor Week or did you have
a lot of this mythology set just from like liking it in the last decade?
No, there's still a lot of stuff I had to refresh.
Like, I know who Wendell is.
I know who Big Al is.
I know the Sunbonnet trio, but there's like, I need Oscar is the little boy you referenced,
I believe.
Baby Oscar, baby Oscar.
Yeah.
I didn't know that.
I couldn't have picked out Zeke and Zeb, like which one is which in the, even though it's
in the song, if you think about it, because he says who's playing what.
And somewhere it's implied that Zeb is the father of baby Oscar.
I believe that's correct.
I have that written down just to make sure.
Yeah, it's Zeb's son, it says.
Yeah.
When I saw this in Florida recently, first off, Pac Theater, everyone into it, clapping
along, but also much of the day, Wendell and Big Al on the roof waving, waving, taking
pictures, mugging.
Really?
Still doing the suits, still the suited characters.
Yeah, there's a lot of cavalcades right now in Florida, a lot of quick character pop-ups
or character, or like Chip and Dale were doing like loops on a raft, on like the rafts over
to Tom Sawyer Island.
They had one of the rafts set aside and they were on the rafts like in cowboy attire, waving,
like doing.
So one everywhere, there was one point where we were standing on that sort of footbridge
shortcut in Frontierland and you could see Chip and Dale doing raft loops.
There was a cavalcade like float coming by with a bunch of characters and then Big Al
and Wendell are on top doing a dance to the music the float is playing.
And so everywhere you look, there was stuff going on.
So that was very exciting.
Wow, wow.
And that's one thing to say that the country bears have maintained as suited characters
and they still show up in Disneyland once in a while, don't they?
Like special events?
Oh yeah, we got our pictures with them I believe when we did Thanksgiving years ago at the
Disneyland Hotel at the buffet.
We had Thanksgiving at the Disneyland Hotel many years ago.
We had photos with them then.
They'll pop up in California Adventure sometime over in the Grizzly Peak area.
Wow, wow.
And then of course I danced with them in Tomorrowland a couple years ago at a dance place.
I walked over and excitedly took some photos with them because they were all dancing to
like a DJ with a bunch of people.
So yeah, they wander around.
Has anybody seen Club Buzz yet?
This is a no, we don't have time to do this, but there's like a light rave happening at
Tomorrowland at night now in Disneyland where Buzz Lightyear stands on the top of the interventions
building while like loud music plays like music and there's a lot of lights.
Oh, interesting because Club Buzz was also the name of the short lived name of the Tomorrowland
stage for a little while.
Yes, I think it's, maybe I'm wrong, maybe I'm misremembering, but I think it's Club Buzz
what they're calling it, but it could be wrong.
Oh, that's fun.
So anyway, that's a different, hopefully the country bears will party there in Tomorrowland
again and I'll get to see them.
Sure.
Hope so.
If they aren't busy.
They can make time.
Yeah, well their home was destroyed so.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Adventures of Winnie the Pooh has so much blood on its hands, Toad Hall, Grizzly the
theater.
Yeah.
It's evicted some of the greats.
Let's keep talking about characters.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let's get everybody straight and give them their due.
And I don't think there's any order we got to go in here, but just like, let's talk about
everybody.
Well, yeah.
Do you want to do the guys on the wall?
Yeah.
Yeah, I guess we are.
That's order, but Melvin Moose.
So yeah, basically they're mounted heads of animals and they're talking in case you haven't
seen the show.
I also, by the way, I know it's an hour in, but maybe you watched the show too, if you
haven't seen it ever.
Yeah.
Yeah, I was thinking that.
To know what the hell we're talking about.
Because you mentioned the show getting shortened and we both went down around 2012, 2011.
And so we like, and it was closed in August of that year to shorten it.
So it's very, very good chance that we saw one of the last showings, the last runs of
like the full.
Maybe.
Unabridged show.
That's interesting.
Yeah, I'm not sure.
You can find the Unabridged show on the record album, which you can get on the iTunes store.
And that has the banter, has the song that was cut and then some other area music kind
of stuff.
Yeah.
The full show is still in Japan.
They still do the full one in Japan.
Oh, okay.
But they've got stuff.
And all the holiday versions.
Oh, yes, the other two versions that they don't do that in Florida.
Geez.
Amazing.
So yeah.
So there's three mounted heads.
Max, Buff and Melvin.
Buff is a buffalo.
Melvin is a moose.
Wait, Melvin's a moose.
Max is a deer.
Yes.
Okay.
And I think that's probably my favorite aspect of it as a kid.
That's like, you know, utilizing the space in an exciting way.
The show is not just in front of you.
It's over here.
It's all around you.
And you get to leave the theater under them and they're still singing.
The show is still going on.
And I didn't know that, or I forgot that the mounted heads were also up in a restaurant
next door to both of the American versions at the mile long bar that you would go and
the heads were there and would, they were moving the entire time.
Once every few minutes there would be a song.
And if there wasn't a song, then they're just like looking around and blinking in a very
Chuck E. Cheese fashion.
It's all very Chuck E. Cheese.
Yeah.
When you read about it.
Um, but yeah, those, I, I, what do, what was the year that closed those places closed?
Do we know?
The nineties sometime.
I don't know.
I don't think I ever went in those.
I didn't have a memory of going in those.
Do you, do you remember that?
All that stuff.
Yeah, a lot of that was closed with, um, the, the, uh, Winnie the Pooh when it shifted from
bear country to credit country.
Even before that, I think I have the faintest childhood memory.
I'd say, and say, wait, and they're out here too.
That's also like, felt funny to me that the hair that they're like, and is it the same
ones or did they move?
Did they, uh, are they alive animals with full bodies and they just walked over to different
holes?
The long bar I read had mirrors at either end so that it wasn't obviously a mile long,
but it would look longer.
The image bounced back and forth and yeah, it looked like it went on into infinity.
Um, yeah.
Uh, that's cool.
Frontier land flavor or whatever bear country flavor.
Um, I, you know, I, I, as often I do, I like going to these Disney dot fandom type, uh,
places or, uh, this might've been on the sea of the society of explorers and engineers
specific Wiki, uh, which, because I think there's in some bizarre way you could say
that Melvin, Buff and Max, the heads are in the sea universe.
And I don't remember why it seemed like a stretch to me, but I'm reading a thing and,
uh, this is a nice way to put what they are.
Um, Melvin, Buff and Max were a moose, buffalo and deer, which at some point in the 19th
century were hunted and turned into taxidermy mounted heads.
However, the three did not die and instead stayed sentient via unknown means.
And we're also able to communicate in English.
I mean, that is correct.
It is true.
I can't argue with the truth of what they're saying.
It's just a bizarre way to put it.
I don't know how you know 19th century.
I don't know that like that they stayed alive.
I just don't look, I don't think of the reality of, isn't it just that magic happens?
I think that when the cast member walks up to the front of the room and starts the show,
he also kind of like, he brings a little pixie dust with him and it turns that, I don't think
these are alive.
And if so, they're not singing.
If these heads are, have been alive for 200 years, um, and feel the pain of when their
body was severed off of them.
You're saying it's a more fun, it's a, it's better to think about it like, oh, just by,
you know, touching the dial, it turns magic on and they're alive again.
And it's a fun little show they put on and then they go back to not existing.
Their consciousness is again gone.
They don't know the pain of having died or being dead.
Or it's magic has to be involved.
It's gotta be a, like a beauty and the beast enchanted objects in the castle situation,
right?
Not some weird, they held on to a glimmer of life.
Just a few alive brain cells.
They live the most tortured existence of any creature.
Yeah.
Okay.
That's less fun.
Um, it is similar.
I'm trying to, I have not read the Oz books and I, I have not read many books cause I'm
a fucking idiot, but, uh, the Oz books, there's a character in return to Oz.
That's a disembodied moose head.
Um, that's like mounted that, that, that kind of flies, helps them fly like whatever kind
of like sleigh that's, I was just looking up the name cause I forgot the name.
The name is the gump, but I do wonder where is like, this is the character.
So I wonder if this was, um, maybe inspired by an old Frank L. Baum character.
Oh, probably.
He had a lot of influence.
So I wonder, yeah, I wonder if, is he the originator of disembodied animal head that's
still alive?
Where's the first part?
Where's the first instance of that in fiction?
I don't know.
Could be.
It's a monster.
He's a monster.
So yeah, condemned these fictional characters to the gump is not as
fun as these three characters.
I will say that a lot more disturbing.
Um, uh, buff my favorite voice in all of theme park world is thorough Ravens.
Croft, the deep voice, the deepest voice guy, sure.
One of the bus, uh, uh, open the fantasy land castle, that guy.
So that's another thing that gives me fun.
Thorough Ravens.
Croft is just a texture in, in similar to like, I dunno, I like Disneyland lanterns
and the way they light up trees and I like the wood and I like the voice of that guy.
That's just like part of enough of the attractions and Africa, the place that it's magical to
me.
Yeah.
I was going to mention Max.
The buck is voiced by Peter Rennaday, who is not also in this show.
He is the voice of Henry, your master of ceremonies has come up before on, on the show because
he is the voice of captain Nemo in the 20,000 leagues attraction of Florida.
He's he's doing the, um, James Mason impression.
I didn't realize this or maybe I had a couple of realizations where it's like, I may have
known this at some point and totally forgot it and relearned it.
He is the voice for years of the, um, tomorrow land transit authority.
When that reopened the people mover, the narration, the narration until 2009 and from like 94,
2000, he's the guy.
Uh, and, and that means he is also my phone ringtone because a portion of that announcement
is my phone ringtone.
Get your phone on.
I'm going to call you.
Yeah.
What do you mean a portion of it?
It's here.
Turn everything off.
I don't know if I've ever played this before.
I don't.
Uh, yeah.
But I heard you get a phone call once a month when I actually get a phone call with a ring
because it's usually on vibrate.
Uh, okay.
Here we go.
I never had my phone on.
Yeah.
All right.
Let's uh, let's see.
Tomorrowland transit authority Metroliner nonstop now departing rocket tower Plaza
station for a round trip.
Whoa.
And, and, and that was a pain in the ass to clip too.
Cause if you try to make a ringtone, uh, in this modern era, it is, um, yeah, it's real
pain in the ass.
There's so much security stuff still on the iPhone.
So you had to rip, I think I had to rip a YouTube video for the audio and then edit
the audio down and then convert it to ringtone file type and then add it to iTunes and then
import that to my phone.
Oh, so this is not, this was not available for you.
You made this custom.
I, yeah, I made this.
You just confessed to a crime.
I did.
I did confess to a crime.
Peter Renned is not getting any residuals.
Oh, for every time you have a phone call, he should get a couple bucks.
Well, he should.
And, and it's a shame he's not in the park because it's like some, Hey, you're right.
And the people move it.
Like it's a different voice.
Oh, is it like a cool skateboarding kid?
It's a cool skateboarding kid since like 2009.
Yeah.
Oh really?
I didn't really, I mean, I've been on it.
I haven't listened to that.
It's really, maybe this should be, maybe this is unfair to put it on.
Well, no, some of it, Jason knows Peter Renned a some money for sure.
But I think at this point, anybody who calls him like myself, unfortunately, I think I
owe Peter Renned a day.
If anyone has Peter Renned days address that voice that you heard, let me know so that
I can send him three cents in the mail.
Okay.
Yeah.
I owe him that much.
Let us know.
Yeah.
I'm going to have to wait a little bit after to see if I could get this to just go off
constantly in the episode, but you've already, I switched it back to do not do not disturb.
Yeah.
What would it sound like if, if you were called and you put the phone next to the jug with
that reverberate?
Oh, Renned a day was laying the jug.
I guess it wouldn't be that good.
Probably wouldn't sound like anything.
Also all this talk, I hope I have that fact right.
Cause I, I saw it and I, cause I was just assumed because it sounds very Jack Wagner
re and I was like, Oh, did they get in to do this?
I looked it up.
Jack Wagner was alive.
He passed away in 95.
So I was like, okay, it was possible.
But then I think you're right.
I'm seeing people saying that, that it was him.
But what do you do?
Do a double check.
I think so.
Well, and the big voice of this guy is splinter.
This is splinter.
He's voices in the country, but Jamboree, the host of the country, but Jamboree.
Uh, any splinter, not just in the cartoon, but in the coming out of their shells life
to he is, he does the spoken word pre before we did all have a set about this on the Patreon
where, uh, there's spoken word, which sounds like old splinter before it shifts over to
sub Brian Adams.
And water nature surrounds, uh, skipping stones, uh, which I was by the way, singing this in
the car and on Lindsay two days ago, I think water surrounds me, which was preceded by
you saying, I have a pitch for our first dance at our wedding.
Oh my God.
You know, it's on the list.
Really, I'm sure, well, I'm sure it's a perfectly normal and romantic song.
Mike, would you feel free to sing it to me?
Well, if I, if you insist, let me get the outfit on first though.
Wait a minute.
I'm also seeing the names BJ ward and Mike Brazel, uh, under transit authority.
So this is going to drive me nuts.
Oh no.
Well, you know what?
With the, the character, some of the characters in the country bears, I know have had two
voices they've been, people have done right now.
BJ ward is now it looks like I think you were completely.
Oh, okay.
BJ ward is the one who's like, he's talking about like, cause when you're writing it,
there was the narrator and then there was announcements and they're very similar in
tone.
The voices.
So your word is now and Mike Bressel is there's no such person.
I think you hallucinated that.
Oh, but it says on Disney.
Oh, okay.
No, no, you made them up.
You're seeing things.
We don't have to deal with Mike Bressel.
There's no Mike Bressel.
So, so he's great and he's Henry.
Henry is the host of the show in his, in his top hats and his dapper.
What is it called when you have just a, like a dicky, the oval?
Yes.
There you go.
He's got, he's got a dicky.
It's what big bird wears when he dresses up.
That's right.
Yeah.
That's as, as dressed up as cartoon characters and puppets are typically required to get.
It's so great.
I, that's another thing I'd love to know who the first like Yogi bear.
It was just wearing a tie.
Like he's wearing a hat too, but like, whoa, the idea that a cartoon character is naked
except for just a little bit of some decoration around their neck is so funny.
Yeah.
Cause he was the first who pioneered it.
Maybe that was Buck Owens.
Did Buck Owens was he naked on stage except for a tie or a dicky?
I don't know.
A lot of these honky tonk type musicians.
They were like red hot chili peppers and in the old days, just penis out.
They didn't even bother to bother them.
Didn't bother them.
Different time.
Or you were, or you did, you could have like a raccoon like blocking your, if you could
get a, if you could get a hide to perfectly hide.
Yeah.
Your junk.
Uh, Henry's the one who has various creatures popping out of his hat.
Yes.
The vacation one, it's a skunk and this one, it's a raccoon cause he's wearing on top of
it.
It's a hat on a hat.
We have a little hat on a hat.
Yeah.
It's the first thing in the wind comedy possible, but it's happening here and it's great.
It's a top hat with a, uh, the Davy Crockett raccoon hat on top of it.
But then face comes out of it and it is a real raccoon who harmonizes with him.
Sammy Sammy.
Sammy is the raccoon.
Yeah.
Kudos to Sammy.
I think Henry is not drunk or just a little buzzed.
Henry seems pretty comfortable.
Yeah.
Um, so, but Henry's a seemingly a nice bear.
He's not, he seems nice, which is good.
Does his job.
Well, he doesn't mess anything up.
I put his professionalism very high.
Well, he gets, you know, he gets yelled at, I think once like Henry helped me out here.
Um, but yeah, basically he's, he's on point.
Yeah.
Uh, and there's a couple of him.
That's one thing I like is that he pops up on the right side of the stage and the left
side of the stage, like he's running all around, you know, like the host of the Oscars might
sometimes they come out of the wings and I'm up in the audience.
That's fun.
Uh, Henry's, Henry's all over.
I think you feel welcome.
Um, one thing I like about this show is the way the is figuring out the mechanics of it.
It's got kind of the cleverness of the carousel of progress where those side stages have to
rotate to allow more acts to come out.
Like, I'm right about this, right?
That like curtains close, Henry might do an introduction curtains close.
And then that entire area has to swivel so that another character can show up.
Trixie shows up there, I believe in the same spot thing.
And then Henry comes back at the end.
Like, cause if you'll notice they all, a lot of them come back for the ending number, but
Trixie does not.
Oh, because Trixie spot is taken.
Trixie is, I think so.
There's only one Trixie robot.
Yeah, there's only one, but like the sunbonnets come up and three like cut out rudely.
Right.
Yeah.
They should make a new rope.
I mean, they should, they should honestly been adding like three bears per year since
this opened.
So there were even on the sides and stuff like there should have been so many more bears
by now, but they're never going to do it.
Obviously.
Well, in different, you know, they were starting to do, we had our Christmas version that they
did a Christmas overlay and they did a summer vacation overlay and then it stops.
They didn't do like, I'm trying to think, cause if these stop happening in the nineties,
what did we miss out on?
They didn't do a Gulf War benefits.
They didn't do a like, let's get our troops home safe.
Yeah.
They didn't do like a warped tour.
They didn't do a warp tour.
Country bears alive aid.
Yeah.
Bear, bear, gelled off, bear, gelled off, doing I what's the boom town rat song Mondays?
I don't like Mondays.
Is that what it's called?
Tell me what it's a Bob Gould song.
Phil, Phil crawlins traveled to both.
There were two.
Oh, the Concord.
Yeah.
I don't know how you, the corn on the Cobb cord.
He took the corn on the Cobb cord so that he could be at the Orlando and the LA ones.
But nobody knew how he did it, but he made it.
What a funny show to do like up on both coasts all the time and then go back and forth with
like live feeds to each coast.
Oh yeah.
And it's real and the camera, they have to be synced up.
This is difficult because this whole hours of operation, they have to open the park early.
Yes.
It always has to be open at the same time.
Or I guess you could do it where it's like when it's not open, it's just like the, it's
not the live feed.
They have just like a placeholder video.
But you know, it's tough to sync them up, which is why it like, like to have a duet
happen from across the world, which is why David Berry and Mick, oh shoot.
What is a Mick Jagger?
What's a Mick Jag Bear?
When in doubt, just make it bear.
David Berry and Mick Jag Bear, when they did their, is dance, does the songs have to change?
Can it still be dancing in the streets?
Oh yeah.
Well, they know they don't have bare versions of these songs.
They're just doing like real songs or songs that were written for the show.
So yeah, I guess it could just be dancing the streets.
Yeah.
Well, that's why they pre-taped it is what I'm saying.
Right.
David Berry and clawing.
Oh wait, David, no, David Berry and Mick Jagger did dancing in the trees.
Okay.
Of course.
Yeah, of course.
Country bear alive, folks.
Did Josh tomorrow announce this at the show, the thing this morning that we're recording?
Totally interactive, completely retro show.
We think it'll blow audiences.
Hey, do you remember Liza?
Their chairs.
We are.
So yes, we are rebuilding the country bear Jamboree and evicting the poo ride so that
we can do country bear live aid.
So we can make a parody of live aid.
Yeah.
Unfortunately, in a couple of years that will get down much like the luxury hotel was downgraded.
The live aid bear version will get downgraded to a very small lawn.
Oh, we can dream.
Well, yeah, they look, they should have kept them going, you know, they'll show about Y2K
paranoia, paranoia.
Yeah.
But we missed out on so much.
I know.
Yeah.
No growl cello.
Oh yeah.
That'd be the way to do it.
Like you do it, all right, the theater's gone, but now you do it open air.
You do put them on a lawn.
Oh yeah.
It doesn't rain that much here.
We can do it Disneyland easy.
The weather's pretty consistent much of the year.
Yeah.
So it's a multi-stage outdoor festival.
Put the stage over at the end like that's by the exit of splash mountain.
That's a dead end there demolish the poo gift shop.
Pretty much.
Just put a big stage there.
Yeah.
And it's a shame to you have to stay for three full days to see.
He used to live there.
Yeah.
For three days because you got to keep the money there.
That's what Walt was was worried about.
Yes.
Bear cello would growl cello would is that what you said?
That's right.
Yeah.
Growl cello would finally achieve Walt's ultimate dream.
Walt would have tried to get into like the concert venue.
Like he would have been like, we should have a Disney three day event.
Like he would have kind of come up with something like that.
I assume.
Yeah.
Because he liked always liked it.
Ladies and gentlemen, Annette Funicello.
This is in 1979.
I think it was like 89.
He submitted a big list of artists and just like, no, no body.
No, no offensive.
No.
When was French?
Whatever weird reason he has.
My Marine Corps band, John Philip Sousa, John Philip Sousa, that band of imagineers who
all wear fire hats.
They're allowed to play the fire, the fireman jazz band.
Yeah.
My theory that like like celebrities are just going to start coming back from the dead once
the technology is there.
Like Walt will be one of the first, I think to come back and then this will happen.
He'll start, then he'll start bringing back who we're talking about from the dead.
Yeah.
So Annette will come back.
For example, Shet will come back.
Yeah.
He fires the full Hollywood records slate.
He fires anyone's song and it's all just everyone is back.
I only want like, I only want neatly dressed girls singing about popcorn.
And I, oh, who are these Avengers?
Can we get Annette in the Avengers?
Well, he sees the money that's coming in and he's like, fine, but can we put some of them
in like some, uh, some red checkered dresses?
Why not the women of the Avengers wear red checkered dresses?
They don't play the ukulele.
What's the tie clip situation with these Avengers?
Tell you what, uh, I like them all.
Keep the, keep the movies the way they are.
But this Robert Downey, I don't care for him, sordid past.
Can we digitally comp Harvey Corman's face on this, on the iron man's body?
All right, get to it.
Well, it's maybe a problem.
I don't want to hear it.
Good luck.
I'm going skiing.
Uh, characters, liver lips, McGrell, sorry about liver lips, McGrell.
Yeah.
He's got a funny outfit on a lot of, yeah, there's a lot of funny outfit.
Like what you were saying earlier with like stuff barely hanging onto the bears being
held up by like one overall strap or one suspender strap.
He's got just the one strap.
Look, I'm looking at a drawing of him.
So now I don't know how much the actual, the reality reflects it, but I bet it does a lot.
He's kind of, he's got hair cover in his eyes.
This is probably Walt's jab at rock stars and how foolish they look.
Well, right.
And in the, in the, in the summer show, he is rock and roll star.
He's Elvis.
So this is the character Elvis essentially.
Basically.
So yeah, that is sort of, you know, um, these old men being like, this is what rock stars
are like these awful.
They don't know how to dress themselves.
Yeah.
There are haircuts or lack thereof, uh, are really a, uh, a vision issue.
Um, I liable to fall off the stage.
Yeah.
I don't know what Mark Davis thought of the Beatles or anything.
I don't know.
Or the Mark Davis might've done those, uh, um, those vultures in the jungle crews who
look like the Beatles.
So he might've been, maybe I'm, I'm, that's a guess.
It's similar looking.
Oh, right.
Right.
But that's kind of, you know, that was one of their only comments on rock and roll at
the time.
And, uh, it was similar.
It was just, they got hair covering their eyes.
I guess, you know, the monkey's uncle is a rock and roll song technically by Disney standards.
Yeah.
The Annette beach boys do it monkeys uncle.
So there was a little bit of it, you know, that again, I've talked about beach, but I've,
I be true to your school is not in the rotation so much monkeys.
Uncle I would say is not in the rotate.
I do not.
I can't say I recreationally listened to monkeys uncle.
What about let's get together from the parent trap?
Uh, no, well, you got no beach boys on that.
So no beach boys specifically.
Oh, beach boys.
You guys blast and let's get together in the car a lot.
Haley mills.
Uh, wedding dance candidate.
Yeah.
I listened to that Sherman Brothers city.
So it's not uncommon that like pineapple princess is playing or something from that album, from
their greatest hits.
Who did, uh, um, who did the music for this?
It's not Sherman Brothers and a lot of the covers.
It's a George Brun, George Brown, bronze, excuse me.
Did a lot of the animated, um, and exitensio.
He wrote the lyrics.
I have, um, hold on, I have in the, in the, there's so many notes here.
I have like the, I have the credits for songs for the show.
Um, so yeah.
Uh, like, like for instance, the, uh, the big band serenade, which is the big thing
where they introduced the five bear rugs who we haven't talked, we've talked a little bit
about, but that one's exitensio and George runs.
Um, they wrote that, that song.
Okay.
Uh, uh, that where they all like was Zip and Zed and that's that.
Yeah.
It's kind of one of the grander, I mean, it's always exciting when the, you know, you got
your side acts, right?
You got your little stages and that's where a lot of the characters appear solo.
They get little solo spotlight numbers, but the most exciting moment in any of the shows
is when the big stage opens up and the full band appears.
Yeah.
And the way it all rolls up is one big, you know, that's like, that's some real concert
theatrics.
That, yeah, the, the, the big moments in the concert.
And I'm trying to think of like other big concert moments in history.
Like, like Teddy bear, I think in this one is a bit, is like the big, it's the, what
you're saying, the big rollout at the start.
And then Teddy bear is the other one.
I think where you go like, wow, look at their bears.
She's coming from the ceiling.
This place is exploding with bears.
It's exploding with bears.
They pop up under my seat and I might go to the restroom.
Yeah.
And they might burst out of the toilet.
But those are, yeah, huge, huge moments in this concert.
But yeah, the five, the bears playing all together, which you like, you never get, although
this is just a side note, I'm thinking like you never get like no bear wears out their
welcome also.
You would think if you were like, well, let's just do a bear show and it is like six bears
and it's 15 minutes.
Yeah.
And that's like, you can have six bears or whatever, but they're in those constant, you're
getting assaulted by bears constantly during the show in a good way.
I'm literally lucky.
No, in a good way.
Yeah.
The bears maintain their distance.
Stay on the stage.
Right.
So they were, they are well trained in that regard.
You don't get attacked by these bears.
No, these are not bears that are going to maul you.
I don't get a bad vibe from any of the bears as far as like violence.
I mean, some of them are singing about violence, but sure.
Well, it's not in, you know, and the ones that the ones that booze are only hurting
themselves.
That's true.
So yeah, yeah.
The five.
Do you think anybody would like, you know, like if I were to take my son in a couple
years and his reality is blurred, he knows where bears are and we're going to see a bear
show.
Is it possible that he thinks, is he scared to go to this because the bears might at any
point drop the instruments, see a delicious kid sitting in the front row.
I dive.
If you're in the front row, I think with a lot of this for me, at least when I was a
kid, proximity is a big deal.
So if you're in the front row, I mean, there's still pretty, there's still pretty big space
between the front row and the stage.
I assume that's for general admission in the front there.
There's a pit maybe if they have like too many people in there.
Get in the pit, girls to the front.
Yeah.
There's a mosh pit going on at the bear show, but I've never seen that.
But I would assume you have proximity wise.
There's a very good chance that your son will yes, think the bears are going to eat him.
Yeah.
At the very least take him and like put him up on stage like the poor Oscar.
Oh yeah.
Oh yes.
He has to live with them.
Now I have to live with them.
Yeah.
Cause that kid isn't even having any fun on stage.
He looks a little shy.
He's there with his dad.
It looks like mom couldn't take him that day or something.
He's kind of the, he's kind of in the, the almost famous scenario.
He's along with the band.
Yeah, yeah.
In the crew, but not, you know, so the, the five bear rugs are still water.
He's the, he's the writer, Henry, I think.
I don't remember the name.
He's Patrick Fuget and the sun bonnet trio, I guess is the, is Penny Lane.
And what are their names?
Oh, this is a sun bonnet trio.
No, no, no.
The names of the, of the, no, this is a tangent.
The names of the almost famous.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Am I not coming up?
I can't.
I haven't seen the movie in forever.
Yeah.
Um, but that's another, you know, obviously they made a film about the country bears,
but that's a movie I might rather see.
There's just something with the almost famous sheen.
Right.
Like dramatic tour.
You know, full of romantic woes and, and ending up with them being on the cover of rolling
stone and that's growling stone.
I would love to see the bear version of Philip Seymour Hoffman's, uh, cause he played a real
life guy.
He's playing the guy from cream magazine.
Lester bang.
Yeah.
He's playing Lester bang.
Lester bears.
Yeah.
Uh, jamboree music is dead, man.
Don't the band aids, the band aids is what I was.
Right, right, right, right.
Um, yeah.
Um, famous groupie Pamela DeBeers.
It's getting real obscure.
It's getting really obscure.
Pretty dark too.
Uh, um, anyway, uh, oh yeah, you know, the country beers are on the cover of, uh, climb
magazine.
That's something that I saw in the lobby in Japan.
Okay.
That's a hard pun to get when it's time magazines, the style of time magazine, but it's climb
magazine.
Okay.
That's pretty good.
Current bear issues.
That's where they go.
That's good.
Uh, do you want the names of the five bear rugs?
Yeah, please.
Zeke who plays the banjo, uh, the fiddle, uh, he's got the little bowler hat on.
He's also playing like the dish pan basically with his feet or wait, no, excuse me.
Zeke is playing the banjo.
Zed is playing the fiddle.
I'm already confused.
Uh, uh, Ted plays the corn jug.
Fred plays the mouth harp and then Tennessee bear is the one that has the base with one
string.
Um, and a lot, I think all of them are hammered.
I think they're all drunk.
These are the, but that's the, you know, it's what, uh, the, you know, Carson and the tonight
show band.
It's always that, uh, these guys are smoking dubs in the parking lot.
This is the, this is what you want out of your 10 year.
Yeah, sure.
Yeah.
I'm getting a little loose.
Well, so they're a unit.
And so if one's a little further gone, the others can carry this.
So many other acts or solo acts except the sunbonnets.
Yeah.
And, and Henry is the one who introduces all of them basically during this song.
They all, they each get called out.
Um, if we know now that it takes 30, at least 36 cans of beer to get a beard, there's five
of them and that's the rider for the country bear show.
The five bear rugs need 180 cans of beer.
Yeah.
But shine can be a lot stronger.
You know, moonshine can be like paint thinner, you know, like rocket fuel.
Yeah.
They just, so they just leave a big trash can of paint thinner out.
All of the bear rugs dip their heads in.
If you smell really hard, especially if you're in the front row, you can, yeah, yeah.
It smells like paint thinner stink.
It smells like cleaner.
It's that's what bleachers on there.
So there's no pupils in their eyes.
A Mountain Dew Mountain Dew originally a mixer for paint for not paint thinner for moonshine
to make moonshine more palatable.
That's what I always heard.
At least in the early days people would mix it.
Really?
That's what it's called Mountain Dew?
Like a mountain.
Yeah.
Like the, like the mountain, like it was, it was a more like country fried product and
not as much like for an outdated idea of what skateboarders are.
Yeah.
No, that was a big pivot when it became like the extreme drink, I think.
Are we really, are we supposed to buy that it is?
Cause when you Google it now, it's just MTN.
This is a branding that no one on the planet uses.
MTN.
Yeah, they just took out some of the, I mean, it's like, it's like a license plate version
of the, it's like Flickr or like, you know, when they, they just take out the valves, you
know, wait, it's MTN and then no D E W.
Look at a bottle when you, when you leave here, if you're getting your traditional post
show Mountain Dew, 7-Eleven, you'll see on the bottle, it's just MTN.
I get it.
It's been this way for a long time.
I just get a super golf.
I go to the, get at the 7-Eleven.
I was going to say, Galeen through the takeout window or the drive-through window at Taco
Bell and like, Hey, can I see the Baja blast pump?
Can I see that?
Can I see the jug of like syrup?
Does it say it on that?
Like, yeah, what is the jug?
What does the canister say?
Yeah.
Um, I was just about to bring up and I really, really shouldn't cause we're still behind
probably.
I would say we're behind, but the, I still like the character, then that character person,
popcorn Sutton.
Have I ever talked about him before?
You've not talked about popcorn Sutton.
Popcorn Sutton was a bootlagger of moonshine in the old days.
And he's, I believe somebody's going to be mad.
I'm going to be, get this a little bit wrong.
He was a part of like, what listener is going to hold your feet to the fire about moonshine
or popcorn Sutton.
Well, he would, he would, he would have a lot of listeners in the holler and they're
going to come for Mike.
Jason knows I've talked about popcorn Sutton before.
They have to hand crank their podcast machines to, uh, for two straight hours to hear our
crazy rigged up cars that they had to outrun the feds in.
Yeah.
But he used to challenge other like bootleggers to races in a circle, which is how NASCAR started.
Yes.
Cause they all had crazy souped up cars to outrun the police.
During bootleg, uh, yeah.
Bootleg times.
Did you learn this in his autobiography?
Me and my liquor spelled also incorrectly like current mountain do L I K K E R.
Uh, I did not.
I have, I learned it.
It was like during college, I was visiting somebody.
We were watching like, like CMT like 2 PM in the afternoon.
It was like popcorn Sutton is one of the popcorn.
That would have stopped me in my trucks.
I would put anything aside.
I'd say to watch a biography of popcorn.
I don't know anything else about him.
I just know that.
Yeah.
He seems like he died in a very dark way.
I am sure.
Look, I don't know anything about him.
If he's canceled, I mean, he's passed away.
I know.
If he's canceled, I'm not saying I celebrate him or anything.
I'm just saying I find it an interesting fact that he was a bootlegger and that's part of
the Genesis of NASCAR.
Uh, this man, uh, had a foot stone prepared in advance for his grave site.
He knew what he wanted it to be and had it made years before he died.
And what it says is popcorn said, fuck you.
Wait, did you say a foot stone?
That's the word that's in this Wiki.
His foot stone.
I've never heard that term before.
I've always heard hate stone.
I've never heard foot stone.
Interesting foot down here.
We got foot stones.
I guess that's also, uh, you can get those socks at the sock market at universal city
walk popcorn says, fuck you.
I had a college professor who worked on a documentary about a similar character named
Jessica white.
Um, and then another documentary came out about him and his family called the wild,
wonderful whites of West Virginia.
But he was like, um, that phrase.
Sure.
He was a maniac like bootlegger and, uh, he was really good at like dancing.
Like it was like a country kind of like tap dancing, uh, sort of thing.
But then sometimes if he got real liquored up, Elvis would come out and a different person
like, Oh, it was Jesse.
Sometimes it'd be Jesse.
And sometimes he'd be Jessica and you don't want to mess with Jessica.
Hmm.
Anyway, since we're just because we're talking about all these characters.
Yeah.
Um, who's the, who's the country bear most likely to have such a profane epitaph who's
got the most.
Oh, that's a good question.
Um, let's see.
Uh, not Henry.
Wendell's got like a mouth on him.
That's what I was going to, that's my first inclination is Wendell.
Wendell seems like he's like sassy.
Wendell said fuck you.
Wendell says Wendell says fuck you.
Um, Gomer seems very nice and quiet.
He's a piano player who doesn't really talk, but what if he's just quietly seething?
Uh, like he has a lot of anger that we don't know about.
And then we get a Gomer said, fuck you.
There's a weird line in the original version that they've cut.
I just got to do, listen to the regular, the original version.
I don't think so.
Or well, maybe.
Um, cause, uh, I forget exactly which pair Jason, I think knows you what, listen to this
where they go, yeah, they're talking about Gomer and they're like, yeah, he's a regular
liberace.
Whoa, no, I didn't hear this.
And then the other, one of the other bears goes, yeah.
And he plays good too.
Which I guess, I, that's what I was trying to figure out.
Is it, is it a gay Joe?
Is it, they're saying he's gay?
I've never, I don't, but I know I'm telling clear cause there's also like, it's also unclear
cause like later on there, there's sometimes they do that thing where it's like not really
a joke.
That's like phrase like a joke where they're like, we wrote these loud.
One of the songs is like, we wrote these lousy lyrics and we also wrote the words.
And it's like, that's not really a joke, but it's like kind of a joke.
Do you know what I mean?
It could just be that they're dumb or Gomer is a pioneering gay piano, Liberace and, uh,
and Elton John.
That's possible too.
That's a possible reading of it.
Yeah.
But they have cut that from the show that is cut from the modern version of the show.
Well they also, you can hear on the album track, Henry says, you know, just refrain
from hybrid date and something, something, and we'll all enjoy the show.
Cause we got a lot to give, which is a reference to Pepsi's slogan.
You've got a lot to live.
Pepsi's got a lot to give, which Pepsi sponsored this attraction for awhile.
So it's possible that that line and then this Liberace line was just cut.
We're just cut because no one knew what the reference was anymore.
Not necessarily because it's pretty obscure Pepsi tagline.
People know who Liberace is, but when you say the name weird, it's tougher to understand,
which I like.
It's funny to say Liberace like Liberace.
Sure.
Yeah.
So, um, should we talk about the, the big thing that they cut the song that they cut?
Oh, which one?
Uh, the but my mama don't whoop little Beaufort.
That's still in the show.
Yeah.
That was a good fractured folk song.
Oh yeah.
Mama don't whoop little Beaufort is still in the show.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
I saw that a couple of weeks ago.
Oh wow.
Fractured folk song where Henry and Wendell duet on that and he, Wendell gives him shit
for coming in late.
Jim Hill has talked about how this is probably, this will get caught.
This is on the chopping block.
Uh, it's a very brief song.
Yes.
And it is a very dark.
It's a joke song, but it's a very dark song.
Yeah.
Um, which is just mama don't whoop little Beaufort.
Mama don't hit something on his head.
Mama don't whoop little Beaufort.
I think you should shoot him instead.
Yeah.
But that sort of shit, I feel like still flies in country music, country music still insanely
popular.
Well, I don't, is there a Kobe key song about shooting a child?
Does he talk about shooting someone in the Applebee's like song?
I don't know.
Oh, what's the guy's name?
What's that song I like about Applebee's on a date night?
Yeah.
We both discovered this.
Scott, you know this song?
I don't know.
By this point, we discovered it late because it was in the commercial.
It was a song and then it became a Tik Tok dance sensation.
And then Applebee's used it in a commercial and the guy was, and it's about like taking
your lady to Applebee's on date night and getting her the bourbon street steak and an
Oreo shake.
If you don't hate this with all your being, I think I'm totally misjudged doing everything.
And they heightened it recently because there's a remix with Kesha doing a verse on it too.
It's called fancy like fancy like the Applebee's commercial.
You know, it's hard for me to hate Toby Keith because I don't come across.
It's not on my desk a lot.
You know, there's another guy.
This is another guy.
Oh, who is this?
This is Walker Hayes.
Okay.
Uh, let's and stay with the Oreo shake and some whipped cream on the top too.
Two straws, one shackle.
I got to get to the chorus first.
I don't know what he's saying enough to get the gist.
Yeah.
You'll have to listen to the home and private.
I don't know what he's saying enough to get the gist.
Yeah.
You'll have to listen to the home and private.
I don't know what he's saying enough to get the gist.
Yeah, you'll have to listen to the home and private.
Well, give me some lyrics though.
What are we fancy like?
Ooh, it's not the chorus yet.
You just, yeah, the chorus already played, but that was a natty natural ice, natural
light, natural ice, squeak squeaking in the truck bed.
So that's a natural light in a cyber from cooler squeaking in the truck bed all the
way home.
Uh, yeah, we fancy like Applebee's on a date night.
Got that bourbon street steak with the Oreo shake.
Uh, I didn't, I would say nothing about this terribly bothers me.
It's look, I think I'd have trouble if I had to hear this music all the time.
If you know, married to someone who made me listen to this all the time, that could be
tough.
But, uh, you know what?
I don't think that I don't think I'm going to run into that song naturally on the street.
If you see the Applebee's commercial though, you'll know what it is.
It's a lot of these songs, like obviously Toby Keith has some just dog shit politics
and opinions.
Um, but I was going to say in terms of violence, there's the, you know, put a boot up your
ass.
It's the American way, but yeah, Osama bin Laden.
This is how a lot of people were feeling about Osama bin Laden.
Yeah.
I mean, obviously I think maybe he, in his mind, he wasn't just saying that about one
person.
I don't know, but likely not.
But impetus certainly.
But, uh, but I will say this red solo cup is a good song.
I have to give it up to the guy with terrible opinions and politics.
This is a thing that Mike, uh, every few years a song comes out.
That's just so technically like a hit, a country, red soil cup, chicken fried.
You've ever heard the song chicken fried and this Applebee's is the newest Zach Brown band.
Yeah.
Okay.
Really you end up like, you've got your like country hit of every two years.
Yeah.
I weighed into that in the past.
We sat around trying to like reverse engineer, like, like if this truck could talk, like
the truck could talk, like how do you mathematically create one of these?
Just like you can do with a lifetime Christmas movie.
Oh yeah.
How do you line up?
Yeah.
It's sort of a mad libs.
Name a restaurant, name a type of pants.
Yeah.
Probably going to be jeans.
Blue jeans type fit.
Yeah.
Well I've done it.
I've done it a little bit with Jimmy Buffett.
I've done, I wrote the song, uh, uh, hiding out in a Pelican's beak and the song, my wife
is a boat.
So those exist.
But I, I haven't, I haven't recorded the country, one of these country versions.
Well don't you think, is your, uh, do you think the country bears have influenced your
taste to go this way?
Is there any correlation between the slightly country air of Jimmy Buffett and your love
of the country bears?
It's a good question.
I do think yes.
I think actually the answer sincerely is yes on some level because I am very fascinated
with old time like, as we've talked on the show, Bob Wills and his Texas Playboys, Roly
Poli like old, like at this point, a hundred year old music, uh, that sounds like it was
recorded in a tiny little can.
And then recently of course, Little Jimmy Dickens, I am fascinated with some of these
and some of these songs I think are legitimately good.
You say of course the, another throwing around of course, like I know what you're talking
about was a little Jimmy Dickens.
Little Jimmy Dickens.
Uh, Little Jimmy Dickens is a-
Oh that helped Jason.
Thank you.
No more questions.
Little Jimmy Dickens, remember we looked him up.
He's a small guy.
He only passed away a few years ago, but he was, uh, remember we looked this up.
He had done a sketch like 10 years ago with Brad Paisley at the country music awards where
he played Justin Bieber.
Okay.
Oh, I kind of remember this thing.
He was like a little Justin Bieber.
Did this come up in America Sings or Reed?
Probably.
I guess so, yeah.
Bullshit again.
Yeah.
And he has a, uh, take, he has a song called take an old cold tater and wait, which is
about how-
The most buffety stuff.
Yeah, yeah.
And he's saying he has a song, uh, and basically the song is just how he was malnourished as
a child and that's why he's so short.
That's the whole, that's the whole point of the song.
Like his mom didn't feed him very well and that's why he's so short.
Uh, and I don't know, this stuff is all fascinating to me and some of it I think is legit, um,
enjoyable.
I think some of these songs in the country bears are legit good.
Mm-hmm.
Um, we, you know, we can keep character jumping around, but also like let's give some songs
some do.
Well, yeah.
In this territory, it seems like I think you like songs, uh, that aren't afraid to be a
little funny.
They aren't afraid to reference things that other songs would, would be embarrassed to
reference and that I think is what the country bears have where you get a sense of, of, of
a character and a guy's way of life and it might be odd, but it's just the way I am.
Yes.
I mean, there's, there's, I mean, uh, every song in it is pretty good.
Uh, some of them are like funny and some of them are not really funny.
Like I'm sure the idea like Trixie is singing that song, uh, what tears would be the chaser
for my wine.
Yes.
Um, but that's a good song.
That's like a, just a legit pretty song.
Like pretty.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Pretty song.
We do a lot of cute here.
Is the tears in my wine song, tears of the chaser for my wine.
Pretty.
I think so.
What would you say?
Pretty little melancholy.
Yeah, it's Mel.
For sure.
Melancholy.
A lot of these are Mel.
Hart, we did all that we could.
Yes.
Teddy bear song.
Uh, a lot of now I really don't know which of these are covers and which of these are
well, I have a bear original.
I think this might be, and I'll save some of this for down the road, but there's, I, I
maybe generally like vacation a little more or some tech cause I think I remember the songs
a little more and I know more of those are original.
Uh, maybe I just, just the one I saw more cause I think just switched over permanently.
Well that's good.
Yeah.
That is more.
So I mean that is, it is on the road again.
It has more.
Oh wait, actually there are a lot of covers.
Yeah, you're right.
There are some covers in that one too.
Um, but this one, yeah, I like, uh, let's see here.
I have a little list of all the songs.
Um, by the way, just, I was like, is there, are there any Google results if I put in Jimmy
Buffett and country bear jamboree?
And there's only a comment that references that this, what Jimmy posted reminded them
of the country bear jamboree.
Does he post a photo of him holding a giant fish fish like as tall as he is.
Uh, and his caption was, um, posted, I believe the month that we saw him live at the Hollywood
bull.
Uh, but I got to stop wishing, got to go fishing, which is very much like the great outdoors
song.
It's like almost, almost the same as a, I think, I think nobody would bat an eyelash
if Jimmy Buffett started putting country bear songs in the set.
No, no, it makes complete sense.
I think I've told this story.
I like no, nothing is almost too absurd for Jimmy Buffett songs.
Like it's on, I wrote this, I literally, I did a thing for a screen junkies at the time,
Jason and I went to go cover the opening of Margaritaville and I wrote a song called hiding
out in a Pelicans beak about a guy who cheats on his wife and hides out in a Pelicans beak
until she's not mad anymore.
And I went in there like playing the song for people live thinking they would like,
think it was absurd.
And they were just like, this is great.
I was like, don't you think Jimmy Buffett would like record this?
And they're like, yes, of course he would.
That's pretty.
That's a pretty song.
No one said pretty, but they were all like hell, they were all drunk and like they had
just seen Jimmy Buffett and they're like, yeah, he would like that song.
I was like, oh yeah, what am I doing here?
This was not the calculate.
I was not correct in my calculation.
Well, I'll tell you what you're not doing is writing a song like that a week, getting
your ass on tour, playing the, there's artists, if you don't know this, who like they're where
they play almost exclusively is in the parking lots of Jimmy Buffett concert.
I know this is like, there's enough of the tailgate culture that you can like, you can
like, yeah, my thing and it like, and they do songs that just reference Jimmy to the
Jimmy show and Fort Worth tonight.
So that's like the parrot head equivalent of Patreon.
I guess you, you, you play the parking lots and you, you build up some degree.
Yeah.
I mean, that's, there's a documentary on, he'd do himself well.
Jimmy should flag.
I wish a copyright that and see if we can get Jimmy to pay us for it.
I'll take some money.
Jimmy, 5% of visa.
15.
I don't know if I was not enough.
Yeah.
That's the parrot heads documentary, right?
You get a lot of that.
TROPROC.
You get a lot of, of that, by the way, are you going on the beach boys cruise in March?
Joe Piscopo is on it.
Oh my God.
COVID-19 is on it.
So let's see here.
Oh, my notes are just, what were you, what were you looking up?
Songs?
Yeah.
Songs.
I think it's called Don't Growl, which I believe is caught Jason.
Can you confirm this?
Cause I've gotten myself all mixed up here.
Uh, yeah.
That, well, that was moved.
No, that's in the show moved to where folk song was.
Right.
So, okay.
And, and then Jason, can you play the jug really quick?
Jason, play the jug real quick.
Yeah.
I'm so scared about shattering this chuck.
Excellent.
I think a little bit.
Great.
Okay.
All right.
So back to Mike's phone.
Where you're like, it's just, this is a crazy song about a guy flirting with a woman, but
he's not allowed to hook up with her because he's married.
So she basically tells him, if you can't bite, don't growl.
I genuinely am lost and don't remember if this is a country bear song or if this is
a, uh, little, little Jimmy Timbers or Zach Brown.
I don't hear, get me back to reality here.
Tommy Collins.
Okay.
This is not an original country.
This is a different, this is a old recording Tommy Collins song that's in the country,
but yes.
Okay.
Got it.
He recorded it and he wrote it as well.
And yeah, it is, uh, who's, and who sings this song in the country bear show?
It is.
I, uh, Ernest, Ernest, uh, in the five bear.
We haven't even talked about Ernest.
Okay.
Wait, no.
Ernest isn't a bear rug.
Is he?
No, he's not.
No, no.
He's with the five bear rugs.
Okay.
He's, they back them up.
So who's Ernest?
Uh, okay.
So Ernest this, I like this energy we have right now.
The fiddle.
He wears the Derby and a polka dot.
I wrote the, my note here says Ernest plays the fiddle.
He is fancy.
Uh, great.
Yes.
He doesn't have a Dickie.
He has like a, well, no, it is a Dickie.
I mean, there's a bow tie in the picture I'm looking at here.
Yes.
Yeah.
But it is a little like collar.
He just had sort of as a white collar and a little like bow tie and bowler hat.
Okay.
I like Ernest a lot.
I do too.
Um, do you, you guys don't have the art in front of you?
I know it's fantastic work.
Um, but I am, am I, who's who in this art?
Who's who's playing the banjo in the show?
Um, that's not, do we have a fiddle player?
I believe that Jason is a bear rug.
I think you were, you, you two are both bear rugs and I, I'm a sleepy looking guy.
Uh, am I Wendell perhaps?
Oh, maybe you're saying golden kind of Brown, golden Brown.
Um, I know.
No, no, I'm dark Brown.
Okay.
Well, one of them did change fur colors, uh, during the refurbishment.
I, I don't have that.
Maybe I am a bear rug.
Um, somebody tell me who I am.
Yeah.
This art, by the way, if you get, and we'll post this so you can look at it high res.
Um, but it's, it's really wonderful in that, um, I'm holding a glass of white wine.
Mike has a moonshine.
One of the X's is crossed off on the, on the X, X, X, and I wonder if that is a nod to
your dislike of body nets.
I think that is a really dry joke on Tony's part.
That's good.
You're not okay with triple X and there is a crazy straw and an umbrella coming out of
the top of the show.
I mean, that's great detail.
And then yours, I, Jason, you're hanging off of the guitar is a parsley eaten donut, a
parsley.
And I want to say churro unless it's a sausage, either would apply.
And then there's a little Mr. Tato up on the top.
Oh yeah.
Truly the finest arts.
Yeah.
Real great.
Check it out.
A new new merch will be available with that art.
Um, yeah.
So, so Tommy Collins, uh, that's a song I like, uh, you know what is a legit legit good song
too.
How long will my baby be gone?
Which is another Buck Owens song in this show.
And who sings that?
Uh, that is, I just want to make sure I know.
Uh, these notes, you guys, you should see these notes.
Uh, it's all on your phone.
Terrence.
Thank you.
There Terrence is also called shaker.
Hmm.
You can have two Terrence, AKA shaker.
Yeah.
I find that confusing.
The, um, one country bear appearance that I like a lot to jump around a little bit is
when they are on the great Disney Disneyland sing along songs video.
Uh, and there is a song they do the great outdoors, which is in the summer.
Vacation version.
Oh, yeah.
Running around.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
She was telling me about this this morning.
She's like, we gotta watch this sing along.
Great, great.
Take great number, great use of the country bear walk around suits and like a kind of
obscure song for the, for a video that otherwise has grim grin and ghosts.
And when you wish upon a star and big ones, this is a seasonal attraction specific song.
And I like that.
But one, that's the main way I had to look up what even, what are they saying?
Cause at the beginning, a big chorus of children all goes, sorry, what are they saying?
Watch it again.
How, how do you shaker?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Um, I don't think there, I don't think you could find 10 children today who all know
shaker.
Yeah.
I don't think that's, yeah, I don't think so.
Probably not.
Um, so yeah, I like that song.
I think that song is good.
Shaker is the, he has kind of a, kind of a quiver.
It's kind of a, sort of not like he's not Elvis.
Shaker is not Elvis.
Liver Lips is Elvis, but he's sort of, he's tall and he sings kind of sad songs.
Yeah.
Um, and it's very, how long am I, baby?
Just a little snippet of it.
Um, but I think that's a nice, a nice song, a pretty song as well.
I would say it's pretty.
There's a real earnestness when you say this about these and there's another, then another
pretty one.
Yeah.
I'm an earnest guy.
What are the, what are the, what else is pretty in this show?
Uh, let me look here.
I mean, like, um, we said Heart, We Did All We Could is pretty.
Uh, I don't think the Five Bear Rugs introductory song.
No, I would say it's not pretty.
No, that's the attempt.
That's not what they're going for though.
Uh, yeah, exactly.
Um, I don't know.
I think that's with the ones I think are pretty.
Is the, is what, uh, Teddy Bear swings swings.
That's what I said.
Heart, We Did All We Could.
Yeah.
That's the pretty.
Which is a Wanda Jackson song.
She sung that.
Okay.
And she is Reese and I say this recently, she did the Jack White album, but that's probably
like eight years ago.
Hmm.
Person who might enjoy the country bears.
Jack White would love a country bear.
Oh, Jack.
Third man records.
Does it have a animatronic show?
Oh man.
It should.
It really should.
Performance space.
Yes.
They put out the like, um, seven inches or the, the singles.
Isn't there like a, yeah, like you make your own vinyl or is that a little booth or something?
You can make your own.
Yeah.
I like the country bears for a residency.
They have nowhere to go.
Yeah.
Um, Disney will be eating their hat if they show up in Nashville.
They have a permit.
Right.
They're all of their, uh, or potentially installed at third man.
I say like, you know, cause Jack White did the Wanda Jackson album, but then before that,
I think he did for sure.
He did the Loretta Lynn album.
So he has an appreciation for the classics.
With Slogin Fitz.
Yeah.
So he should, uh, he should produce the country bears.
That's what I was getting at.
Yeah.
He should produce.
Makes some new.
Yeah.
This is all right.
Like Rick Rubin, Johnny Cash.
Exactly.
New relevant music.
Yeah.
Well, the Johnny Cash went to a little bit of a bummer because to me it's not suggest
they're dying, but uh, I guess he's where he doesn't work with all.
Country bears two country bears three.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, I don't want to, uh, say anything dour, but if the country bears learned, if
any of them learned that they're not long for this world, they gotta make their way
to Nashville.
If big Al did hurt during one of these shows, the roof would go off the building.
Big Al.
I think you could absolutely switch it to that.
Yes.
Yeah.
Would it seem insensitive or something?
I hurt my bear self today.
Well, I think we have more bears talk about, but since we brought up big Al and, and uh,
and I mean, I think a lot of people's favorite, everyone loves big Al people laugh.
People are excited.
Yeah.
Comes out.
Um, big Al's track is unique in that it's pretty much just a Tex Ritter album track.
Yes.
He's like his is not an original, at least the first time around, it was not.
And when I found that interesting that this weird, funny, depressing song he sings that
brings down the room that that is not a Disney invention at all.
That's full text reader.
No.
And it, okay.
A couple of weird things about this.
This is another thing that I think I unlearned, unlearned, relearned in the last week.
Tex Ritter, the father of John Ritter.
Yeah.
From television.
Uh, they seem like that seems like completely different eras and types of pop culture.
It's really weird.
Yeah.
They're linked.
And that his, his, uh, he, I don't believe he wrote blood on the saddle.
Uh, Everett Cheetham is the name I have, uh, as writing, uh, blood on the saddle, but blood
on the saddle, the, uh, Tex Ritter album came out in 1960.
Here is a cover of it.
It's a fun painted cover.
This show opens 1971.
That isn't that long of time.
That is like if they opened a show now and one animatronic towards the end just did chicken
fried or just did red solo.
Right, right, right.
Like that is modern.
Yeah.
Cause you don't, you think of all these songs at the time being like 50 years old, but that's
not the case.
No.
Yeah.
Um, um, blood on the saddle.
I mean, I don't have a clip, but maybe we should just perform it to the best of our
ability.
Yeah.
They're blood on the saddle.
Boom.
Blood all around.
And this is the funniest thing in the show.
I think the sun bonnets is the funniest thing.
Oh, that's fair.
Yeah.
This is almost kind of close.
But it's so funny that he's such a depressed looking bear and he sings just this like the
dark dark song done in the most minimal, the way those notes bend down, which I guess
is the original track.
But what a well chosen track.
It's just very funny that he, um, sticks to his guns.
He, he sees what everyone else does for the jamboree and he says, no, I'm going to bring
a different flavor to this.
I have to be true to myself.
Yeah.
I have to represent myself like any you'd be told to do on American idol or the voice
or anything.
He can't be, he can't do happy songs.
That's not who big Al is.
Yeah.
They're embarrassed by him.
They're embarrassed by the choice.
Well, the show is a kind of self referential, like that song that is not cut about, um,
beating little Buford.
After that, Henry goes, Henry goes, uh, yeah, exactly.
Henry goes like, uh, we only have high class stuff on this show folks.
Uh, but they want big L off the stage.
They want him to stop.
So they're like really just like, this is not what we thought you were going to do.
That's what I, how I read it at least.
Well, I think he does his song and then they go into the ballad of Davy Crockett and then
he brings it back.
He interrupts that and to kind of, uh, overpower him, they go into old, old slew foot, uh,
which I think is a very jaunty song.
Uh, there's a recording by an act called Jim and Jesse from 1976, uh, on a television program
doing it.
I, you know what?
You're right and, but I, for whatever reason, I always, in my mind, I was reading it like
he was, he had to end it early and he wanted to come back to finish it.
Oh, interesting.
But maybe he was just, you didn't give me my time.
Yeah.
Maybe that's not right.
That's for some reason, that's how I interpreted it, but that's probably not right.
You're going to have to shut off the goddamn lights to get me to leave over my dead body.
Al said, fuck you.
I have the text reader version and there are more lyrics after blood on this apple.
Oh yeah.
What keeps happening?
Sure.
Because that's the, we should say blood on the side, even that you're in a theme park,
it strikes me and I think a lot of people in that audience funny every time that you're
hearing a song about blood.
I don't think they would do this from the ground up today.
No, there's no way.
Yeah.
We paid for a new show where people sing about blood.
I mean, I think there, there is, um, there's transgressive stuff that you can get away
with and country music.
And I think that's why it's still like in the park.
Bring it closer.
Yeah.
Is that what's in the show?
Or is this is not an issue?
Like if I'm reading blood, I don't write any Broncos no more.
Oh, the next line is, Oh, pity the cowboy all bloody and red for the Bronco fell on
him and bashed in his head.
Whoa.
There was blood on the saddle and blood all around and a great big puddle of blood on
the ground.
So yeah, it's good.
That's what, yeah.
When we, we saw the show after so many years, I was like, Whoa, this is wild.
Wow.
This is wild.
This still exists here.
That's a good, that gets a little more serious.
It's like it almost, it reads as a comedy song completely.
Right, right, right.
When you get into details of how this guy's head was bashed.
Right.
So dark show sometimes some ways, but you know, these performers live rough and tumble
lives.
Yeah, sure.
Again, Alice speaking his truth.
That's right.
This is something he saw.
This was a bear.
He knew.
Yeah.
Or he's just a really great interpreter of song.
He's really feeling.
Well, he's absolutely that.
Well, yes, you're right.
For sure.
He's that.
I feel like you could give him a, like Adele, you do hello in that style.
I people for one of those nights where you have to pay extra money to go into Disney
world or Disney, I guess Disney world, they should just fucking have him sing Adele and
people will lose their minds.
Yeah.
Go and you want to see, they're going to do Adele and people would pay money for that.
We'll need to sound like off stage.
Dexter at our long dead.
Well, sure.
I know Dexter.
It did not show up at every performance.
Oh, if only, if I sync it up, but like a success again, a successful singer in his own right.
And so did that just put his song?
I mean, they think seems like it's a little deeper, a little gravelier in the show, but
it's so close.
Yeah, they didn't change that at all or barely at all, I should say.
So yeah, he, I would imagine yeah, he's number one.
I'm trying to think because big Al the merchandise in Tokyo, because Tokyo still has country
bear merchandise.
Yeah.
At least was when I was there and they have Henry, they have a stuffed plush of Henry.
They have swinging Teddy bear.
They have the sunbonnets.
But I don't remember.
Did they have big Al or not?
I don't know.
I mean, those are probably the main most popular characters, but there's a very cute trio of
stuffed sunbonnets and we should talk about the sunbonnets and the song they sing.
Well that's maybe, yeah, that I think if you were trying to do a weird trip to Disney world
or to, you know, I guess Tokyo too, if you're trying to like, all right, I know what the
big rides are.
I know what big thunder and space man is and tell it, show me weird stuff.
I think like, you know, your list would include Carousel of Progress with its weird 1994 locked
in time sequence.
Yeah.
And it would certainly include this for Blood on the Saddle and probably, I think maybe
this moment is one of the weirdest things you can see in the Magic Kingdom.
Well, yes, there's a lot of stuff going on.
For one, there's still a slideshow.
There's still a 1970s era slideshow.
Oh yeah, that there's a slideshow at all, I guess, is very much dates it.
But that's, you know, one thing I like about all of these versions is seeing them represent
that in slides, they're still drawings.
They are, they don't look like robots.
Right.
In the different medium of slides, they are drawings.
They're Mark Davissy kind of drawings.
Also I think for the song, All the Guys That Turn Me On Turn Me Down, I feel like Turn
Me On used to be a little more chaste or generic, like turn on.
Yeah.
You're right.
So yeah, that is aged a little bit more aggressively.
Yeah.
Now turn on is full on horny, like ooh, it's a turn on.
I think that is right.
So yeah, when that song was written, it wasn't quite as aggressive as it sounds now.
Turn Me On is like mentally, like make me perk up.
Yeah, I mean, it is a horny song, but it is not meant to be as aggressive as it sounds
in the parlance of our time in the language of now.
And that's what it is.
It's aggressive.
This is aggressive sexuality coming from the Sunbonnet trio.
That's right.
Yeah.
So it's hard.
It's jarring at first and it might take you five, six viewings to not have it feel so
aggressive.
Yeah.
Be prepared.
A nice, like a different tone than Heart We Did All That We Could and Tears Will Be the
Chaser to My Want.
Those are both pretty sad ballads from the female coded bears.
This one's kind of sad too, because they're getting turned down.
I think all the females, nobody's like having a lot of luck in general.
Yeah, I mean, a lot of the bears are singing sad songs.
Even some of the jauntier ones, if you listen to the lyrics, are sadder.
Yeah.
Like how long will my baby be gone?
That's a sad one.
But yeah, yeah.
These are all pretty sad.
And this one, yeah, this is, so in case you don't know, again, listen to this probably
before, like go to YouTube and find this, like look up Sunbonnet Trio and they do a song
called All the Guys That Turn Me On Turn Me Down.
And they're just upset that they can't get one of these gentlemen bears to give them
the time of day.
So they're all missing.
In the original version of this show, there's banter.
Trixie is like flirting with Henry.
Well, no, he still flirts with Henry.
She's still-
Yeah, that thing of if I had a ladder.
Yeah, yeah.
That's the one there.
No, that's Teddy Bearer.
Oh, okay.
Oh, Trixie.
You're right.
Trixie flirts with Henry in the uncut version.
Yes.
And then they're like, well, I'll be up as soon as I can find a ladder.
That's kind of sad because like, although all the mounted heads, that's kind of sad because
she wants him and he wants her.
Because he doesn't have a ladder?
No, no.
I mean, that Trixie wants Henry, but Henry wants Teddy Bearer.
Oh, I see.
Although the mounted moose heads are very taken with Trixie, the moose and the buck
and the other one.
Yeah.
But they don't have bodies.
So what are they going to do?
A kiss.
It's all sad.
Yeah, you can do mouse stuff.
Yeah, you're right.
You could kiss.
We want to give people what they want to see.
Show Trixie the bear kissing all of the mounted heads.
That's for Disney Plus.
That's a Disney Plus show.
There's no story.
It's just kissing.
The Sunbonnet Trio, Bunny, Bubbles and Bula, they are tiny bears and they're wearing bonnets.
They feel young probably from the way that they dress.
From the bonnets and the little blue skirts.
That's what's crazy because they look like babies.
They look like children.
And I've confirmed there's a blurb that was on one of these wikis.
The Sunbonnets are the babies of the country bear Jamboree.
They begin singing in public school in Clint, Texas in Miss Grizzly's class.
We know the town that the Sunbonnet Trio comes from.
From there they appear five weeks running on Major Bears Amateur Hour and were booked
into Walt Disney World.
Backstage they study their lessons.
In their spare time they are knitting a scarf for Big Albert which they hope to have finished
for Christmas three years from now.
Is there this level of detailed backstory for every country bear?
Like if you were to dig?
I think it depends because I honestly I had to look a couple places to find this.
And then this is another thing we've run into where I think even with Haunted Mansion where
you're like it's canon according to like a comic that was written but I don't know if
it's technically like Disney canon.
Like Disney proper I don't know what they consider official.
Yeah because I walked through a gift shop and they had the Disney World game of life.
The board game life.
Oh yeah yeah.
And Big Al is on that and he looks so like happy and very healthy and I'm like was that
canon like he looks like a totally different character.
No it should be canon that he's unhappy.
He should look like shit.
He should be like a little cutesy.
Yeah but yeah so these these like I guess okay bears live to be I look this up 25 years
old.
Okay.
Okay so if they're students I mean what they could be five to ten.
I'm just trying to retcon this to be not so bizarre.
So you know.
I'm sure it's not.
I'm sure they did their this is a public show.
They're not going to do anything that anybody's gonna get in trouble for.
You're right.
These are there of bear age.
Now we don't know what bear age is and I don't want to go saying it.
But this is yes this is just guessing.
This is high school.
This is you know high school feeling of crushes and not being reciprocated.
That's all this is.
Yeah.
But it's funny.
This isn't pornographic folks.
I didn't say that.
I'm just saying this is just.
No what Henry wants to do with that ladder.
That's pornographic.
That's disgusting.
Henry goes like.
Like Henry makes like a like a he's smelling a stew or something.
He makes like that type of a satisfied noise after he goes like I'll be right up.
He goes like a real.
That's aggressive.
They make some growly bear like they all make some grunts and stuff.
Yeah.
He is.
It's a disturbing sound.
It is horny.
Yeah.
That's for sure.
Can I call just to get the sounds of the episode going.
Can we get a quick jug and then I want to hear your that sound in response to the jugging.
Now that's an appropriate use of that kind of sound approval of great jug music.
Yeah.
It's not to be used in lewd settings.
That's good.
That's proper.
That's nice and proper.
So yeah.
This song not not this is not originally there the guys are really on.
Well there you go too.
They don't even know what they're singing about.
That's the other thing.
So they can't be held responsible.
Can't be held responsible.
Somebody I don't know.
Maybe they're not being protected here.
Maybe you know Henry shoved these lyrics in their hands.
They go sure we just want to say we just want to be part of the show.
Right.
And they aren't even aware of the potential you know what you could infer from it.
This was written by Plot and Powell.
Those are the last names of the songwriters.
Is it men?
Not sure actually.
There wasn't.
I'll look into that.
That'll be coming coming up on another episode.
Well is this what I'm worried about is that like you know suggestive lyrics are being
put in front of these young singers and is the sunbonnet trio a Britney situation.
Is it possible that they're yeah are they in some case.
Is Henry in charge of the conservatorship and do they need to be freed from it.
That's a good question.
That's something to look into.
We can look for it.
Well when we go through the hint that Christmas or if we go through the Christmas and summer
show if we can look for clues there as well to see what's going on.
Whatever we can do if we need to start a separate podcast about that to get the sunbonets freed.
Sure.
We'll do what we can.
So here's what it stands let's just read these lyrics.
Every time I meet a guy who gets me shook all I ever get from him is a dirty look.
It's the same way everywhere I've found all the guys that turn me on turn me down.
All the guys that turn me on turn me down.
Nothing works for me I've found the same way everywhere I see nothing ever seems to work
for me.
Doodle doodle do bum bum.
I think this is the three part harmony is very pretty on this.
I'll say it's pretty.
I think it's pretty.
Yeah.
There's a gag in one of the slides where she's like waving a handkerchief at a guy and in
the next one he's like walking on top of the handkerchief which is such a bird.
I don't know if it's a reference that old thing where it's like oh you lay your coat
down in case there's a puddle but it was just like he's just trampling the handkerchief.
Well this is where like I know I don't have that image in front of me I don't have copies
of these slides.
I wish I did but the you know how handsome is that bear.
How good looking is this bear that he can thumb his snoot at all three of the sun bonnets.
Well who I mean yeah I don't know what the standard is for male bear beauty.
Yes Henry the most attractive his big owl his big like he's all set for hibernating.
Is he the most attractive?
Because he's going to survive through the winter.
Well let's we should all make our we again we don't have a meter of bear attractiveness
but just going off of your gut if you get some of the pictures in front of it who do
you think's the most handsome bear?
Which bear can get it?
Which there you go which country bear can get it?
I think that Gomer is kind of quietly handsome like there's nothing you know he doesn't
have like the you know he's well dressed he doesn't have like kind of the goofy smile
or the odd lips.
I think he's just like solid and putting his head down he's an artist and you know I'd
like to I'd like to get in his head learn his you know what makes him tick his piano
theory what made him passionate about music.
He's not a showboat so I'm gonna say Gomer can get it.
Okay Jason do you know?
I mean swinging teddy bear is a knockout you know the confidence alone I think we can all
agree.
I'm just talking male we can cover that territory separately.
I think part of the humor of Libra Lifts McGraw is him going my woman ain't pretty but you
don't swear none and he's like looked like he just got like punched in the face.
He says she ain't pretty but I ain't too.
That's yeah so at least he's in on in on it.
Yeah.
Do we think that he has maybe kind of like a kind of a rock star swag again I was earlier
we were saying it's the scruffy hair I'm sure is there is there anybody this guy looks I
mean is there sort of a Mick Jagger vibe to.
Or like Dylan?
Like Dylan's kind of got a weird.
Oh sure yeah he's a little scraggly.
You know a little rough he's not for your parents you need an entertainer and a nice
suit.
Yeah maybe I mean the rebelliousness to him right.
I think that's yeah I think I can see what you're saying there.
You can say that I think Henry though.
The sleepy eyes a little bit you know do we consider he's an interesting odd looking fellow
but is Steve Buscemi attractive in some notable in some way.
Yeah I think look everyone is attractive on some I think you know everybody has different
tastes you know there's not really one standard of beauty so yeah for Steve Buscemi a real
talented guy I could see it.
You know so.
Kind of looks like Steve Buscemi.
Really we're just talking like who can get it when we say who can get it we're just saying
for us personally.
I mean Henry I think that's probably the easy choice but like you like a leader you like
that confidence.
I like Tennessee Bear a lot.
Yeah I'm a big fan of Tennessee Bear.
Sorry Tennessee is one of the bear rugs.
He's got the one string bass.
Okay okay.
Yeah and he's just he's like he's definitely hammered but he's got like he's got a nice
grin on his face and he seems like he'd be fun to talk to.
There's a by him there's a jug that says do we say this E flat it's a moonshine jug next
to him.
Oh like you can like they have them tuned differently like the way if you play glasses
filled up with different amounts of water that makes different notes so.
Yeah there's one that says B flat here too.
Oh okay.
So there's multiple different jugs that have different notes.
They can perform a different again Jason B flat.
Can we have a quick B flat.
You're lucky to get any letter.
Great as opposed to an E.
Could you give me an E yeah.
I think actually you made an octave up.
I just realized this glass jug looks like the sad up like jug that they they put the
change in that they have to constantly dig into to not take their trip.
Well if he was you know he could look at it half empty and say that's a trip I'll never
get to take with my dead wife or he can look at it half full and say maybe I could start
a jug being career.
That's true.
Yeah.
Get with it Carl.
Here's the thing I want to say.
Do have we talked about maybe we haven't I'm forgetting.
We talked about Disney on parade.
Hmm.
Well I don't know because I don't think I know I fan what it is.
Okay I don't know much more than there at least there's okay.
So I was looking up some bonnets and some bonnets appear as like a trapeze act and something
called Disney on parade.
And this is by far this is not an episode on Jambor week but this is an episode.
This is an hour long live Disney circus from the set in Epcot.
I should know where it was traveling the country thing.
I don't know.
I don't know where I just know there's a special that's recorded.
There's a scene in it where goofy or her be the love bug is trying to run over goofy.
Whoa.
And it is wild and the goofy hits her be on the top of the head and her be like has a
little bump that grows and it is bizarre.
Disco bare necessities happen during it.
Mowgli like dancing like crazy during it's it's I it's wild.
I found it toward the end of today before we had to come here so.
Okay forgive me the the name of the toy that's the red goggles where you flip through and
you see different slides.
View master.
I had a view master of this.
They took stills from this experience or from the special or something.
Right.
Yeah because I like oh Disney stuff that sounds neat and I remember it being so dark and like
not just in the way it was shot because it's like a live theatrical presentation in the
70s that wasn't very well lit.
Right.
Then also like yeah on it her be attacking.
Yeah he hits him.
A real car drives into somebody dressed as goofy.
Yes.
Like hits him in the butt and he flies forward and there's a whole scene.
You know what I'm talking about?
You've seen this?
I think what I was talking about was a different circus themed special called Epcot's Daredevil
Circus Spectacular that is from the later 80s.
Oh interesting.
Where they set up circus acts in the middle of World Showcase.
If you want to talk about hat on a hat.
Wow.
Yeah so that's different than Disney on Parade.
Disney on Parade.
Which is also circus themed.
Circus like country music it was okay.
You could just anyone could use it.
You know anyone could get away with it.
You mean the tropes of a circus or the acts of a circus?
It was like a go to theme for like variety stuff.
It was seen as family friendly and widely popular I feel like.
What was the Disneyland 90s circus thing?
That was.
I forget what that was.
You know what I'm talking about?
Yeah.
Where like it was just like circus acts set up.
On Main Street right?
Everywhere.
Yeah.
Right right.
Something like that.
Like a male married.
Like that was like a come to Jesus moment.
What are we going to do?
Okay circus.
Circus.
But sorry the country bears are part of Disney on Parade.
Yes.
There's just I saw a picture.
I saw honestly because I was scrubbing through it.
I just saw a picture of the sun bonnets like hanging.
They were like a trapeze act and I don't know if there's multiple.
I don't know there's multiple maybe there's multiple Disney on parades.
Maybe it was just one I was watching.
I'm not sure.
So it's people in suits of the sun bonnet trio?
That's well let me I'll find a picture.
Are they thinking because female gymnasts are often very tiny is that the like this
is they can be as small as the sun bonnet trio?
Perhaps that's correct.
Oh here we go.
Let's see here.
It is unclear.
I think these are not people.
I think these are like these are I don't know if you can see this.
These are the country bears suits people in those but then hanging from the ceiling it
looks like it could possibly just be like dummies.
Okay.
You really concern me when you said they aren't people.
I was picturing some like a dog in a suit.
Well or something like you know if you like some country like needed gymnasts so bad that
they like bred a species that are tall smaller and sleeker than a human could ever be so
they could win all the gold medals bred a human with a mule.
They cracked it to get the mule out of its dead end.
Yeah.
So we got to look into this because this is a nightmare.
This whole thing was just scrubbing through it is a nightmare.
It was great.
I remember how much it scared me in view master.
Yeah I'm sure it did.
But I kind of would keep doing it.
It scared me but I like needed to process it.
Yeah yeah it was a good kind of scary kind.
So yeah Disney on parade.
Okay okay.
I well what have we missed?
I mean besides all the other stuff we're going to talk about throughout the week.
I any other moments numbers characters.
Yeah I'm looking through here.
And by the way I yeah I'm looking at the merch display that I saw in Japan and I think there's
no big L representation.
But there's a massive there's so much merch but I think it's Sunbonnets and Henry and
Teddy all in different sizes and a cute little display of them all together.
I'm trying to remember if I got I think I bought Henry I think there's a Henry around
some with the raccoon with Sammy popping out of his hat.
So they're covered on the and good for Tokyo again this is so well positioned in Tokyo
it seems like a perfect crazy thing to be in Japan.
A weird robot show full of darkness and sensuality.
Yeah there's been so many rumors of this thing going away in Disney World.
It has survived up until now but I am more I am still thinking like luckily every like
they're so slow at building anything I think we probably have to at least 10 more years
of it.
Yeah I mean it was very popular the day I was there.
It helps that it's adjacent to Pirates of the Caribbean Splash Mountain Big Thunder
Mountain like there's so much in the area that you likely need to wait for or need to
do something in between or afterwards.
I just want to say real quick the the changes done in 2012 banter cut down fractured folk
song was the big one that was removed.
Pretty Little Devilish Mary right is the name of the other song that was removed and then
if he can't bite don't growl was moved up in the lineup.
Yeah but you can hear the full version of the show and that old record that is is you
can buy digital copies of now.
It's on Spotify too but I think only some of the songs are playable.
It's yeah you can't do the full full.
It's on Apple Music.
You could listen to the whole chunk.
But for some reason that's not on there anymore.
I don't know why you can be a buy it or it's just it's still on YouTube.
Somebody ripped it and put on YouTube.
So listen to it.
Yeah there but I do think I do think this is unless they come up with a TV show or movie
this thing is gone and within within the decade in here.
I think in Tokyo it'll last.
Sure.
Yeah.
But it's in a weird spot like you exit in in Orlando you exit into a rest to a restaurant.
So like they'd have to like shut that down like a pretty busy quick service restaurant
and you don't get I feel like you don't get a lot of room back.
It's kind of in a busy area.
I mean yeah.
Florida.
Yeah but that doesn't mean they're not going to do they wouldn't do that.
I mean the rumor was a couple years ago was it was going to be a toy story they're going
to turn into a toy story show of some kind.
Some like Mary and then round up sort of.
Yeah.
Sounds fun.
Don't get me wrong.
But yeah but like the idea of losing this that we love and enjoy for it like you just
want them both to exist.
Sure.
Yeah.
If possible.
So Disneyland I think the what you're saying about how it's an odd space in Disney World
and how do you really get it out of there and how much space do you really gain from
it.
Again it comes into Disneyland with the two theaters.
Yeah.
It's not filling those two theaters pretty quickly.
I think by the 90s they are discussing how do we get that space back and do something
else with it.
It just never.
And maybe there's something to the music of it too.
Maybe they were right with that calculation that country music's bigger in Florida and
less so in California.
It just was never the blockbuster here that they wanted it to be.
Yeah.
And it's also I can't remember if I heard Tony Baxter say this or somebody else say
this.
So since Disneyland is such a local crowd you don't go to a show that's the same often
as often as tourists would.
Absolutely.
So like if you're there's a lot more tourists in Florida so they're going to they're more
likely to see that show versus like how often would I be seeing the Country Bear show if
it was still here.
I'm sure a couple times a year especially if they were doing the multiple versions but
yeah that's another thing that hurt it especially with two theaters.
Yeah was what you were saying before like one theater didn't change a land around to
make it theme to that.
Maybe it's still there.
Yeah but it's smaller more less of a burden of what it has to support and the amount of
crowd it's supposed to eat up.
So I think and being that it's such a big building they start talking about I think
this building is big enough to get a ride in but there are all of these great animatronics.
Can we do something else with them right leading to a pitch of an attraction called the Critter
Country 500.
Yeah not aware of this before this week.
Yeah.
So great.
A couple photos of this.
So this would have been that the broader name Critter Country 500 because the area got renamed
when Splash Mountain moved in.
But basically this is a little like race and ride.
Like there's they show kids in a car that says Bearcat Racer and it's made of barrels
and wood and it's falling apart and there's a weird stove powering it.
Like great idea for a vehicle.
This all feels very Knott's Berry Farm.
Yeah like wacky Soapbox Racers.
Wacky Soapbox Racers or Berry Tales for sure.
Kind of like Kooky and Psychedelic but it's hard to picture them.
The 90s is like as late as they're going to do something this weird.
They didn't do it then so they didn't do it at all.
Henry is on the radio calling the ESBN.
Yeah.
The Sports Bear Network.
That's really great.
The Sammy the Raccoon's in his hat.
He's waving a flag.
Like crazy contraptions being operated.
What's the thing where all the Hanna Barbera characters race?
Wacky Races?
Yeah yeah.
It seems so much like that.
In the spirit of that this is a vehicle with a pig up front in goggles like protecting
him from the wind.
This is the most like claptrap made out of a train engine.
It's bizarre.
It's being operated by two cranks by one of the bears.
Handsome Gomer is driving.
Gomer who can get it can also get it on the road.
He's kind of like got a Mad Magazine Sergio Argonis vibe to it.
Very much so.
It's like fun chaotic.
A lot of details.
This is is this Liver Lips who's just blowing giant overalls.
He has a big sail made out of overalls.
I hadn't meditated on what's actually happening in these photos.
They're fantastic.
Yeah.
It's being held up by a broom and there's an outhouse that's part of the car.
So I don't know if you're racing against the bears.
You're just kind of it's you're alongside probably and you know they probably let you
win because you're a guest.
You would think.
But this seems like a weird like a kooky proto Radiator Springs racers that reuses the animatronics
puts them in a different light.
I mean this seems like a great unbuilt attraction.
Oh yeah.
What a dream.
But it didn't happen.
Of course they discovered there is a critter who needed representation.
Representation on the merch front.
A bear even a fellow who stabbed other bears in the back.
Alia Kazan affairs named names.
That's right.
A man took yet took bodies.
The the mounted animal heads are in his ride.
That's right.
Yeah kept them.
Yeah.
No they're staying here.
They're my prisoners now.
Winnie the Pooh moved in and if you didn't know all this time we were talking about this
this this show was in the space where the Winnie the Pooh attraction is now in Disneyland.
It's hard for me to hate on Winnie the Pooh at this point.
I love Winnie the Pooh growing up.
I've started to show my son Winnie the Pooh.
Winnie the Pooh is in my heart recently.
I'm excited to take him on that ride maybe in the near future.
But we'll you know we'll talk about that ride down the road.
I like the ride.
Is it worth losing this beloved like theme park IP specific for.
I don't know if it is.
No because it's a little off the shelf when you're also talking about broken dreams of
the Winnie the Pooh ride there is a version of it that was a water ride.
There was like a little like a rapids and a flume ride that was tame that kids could
do where you're in a honey pot and it's floating because you're along the rivers of America.
So there would have been like a little drop off of that hill.
Oh wow.
Down into the river for a second and that sounds like a better ride than what we got
which a little bit of a stock.
I don't think it's anybody's favorite.
It's fine.
It's not as bad as everybody makes it seem but I always come off all smiles on that.
Yeah but it's still like OK but kind of a lateral like I think they thought they had
a hit and maybe short term they did.
But I think now you look back and you look at Mr. Toad and country bears and you look
at poo and it's like you look out wise it's a it's a lateral move and you look at the
Tokyo version and you look at yeah yeah they have a better poo ride and country bears still
intact the dream scenario.
It's the dream realized yeah.
Yeah it's why that I think that Tokyo Park is underrated as a magic kingdom.
It's a strong magic kingdom.
Yeah for sure.
Just for those reasons alone.
And what the Southern California fan base now is of like nostalgia and I feel like the
people really into it if you get them going they'll go like yeah country can't believe
they got rid of country bears you know.
Sure.
Yeah there's been many fan requests or fan whatever you would call it blue sky of like
put the country bears on grizzly river rapids.
Yeah no idea if that was actually an idea they ever talked about.
You say don't know.
The characters show up around there.
They're hanging out around there.
But it's not going to happen now.
Yeah there's probably no way it happens now.
I don't think the robots exist.
I don't think they're all sitting somewhere.
No no no no.
No.
They would indicate if they were sitting.
I saw a thing that the mechanics for swinging teddy bear are used for poo and the hot air
balloon going up and down.
Yes I had no idea of that.
That's a pretty clever reuse.
That's cool.
It's a pretty famous fact as was said but the if you're on the Winnie the Pooh ride
the mounted heads Melvin Buff and Max you can see them.
It's right before the honey room and on the way out of heffalumps and woozles.
Good thing to impress some pseudo impress somebody that you're with.
I can never see them.
I always try.
I always miss it.
I feel like I'm always I'm never sure.
I'm like is this it.
And I think I look out and get it.
It's a little dark.
It's a little tough to see.
I don't know exactly the spot but I like that.
I like that they kept them there.
And it's in the you got to know where that it's a particular angle.
That's a pretty good.
Well a very good Disney Easter egg.
But of course you wish they were around.
Why can't they still be talking in one of those shops next door.
There's no reason they have to be off.
Keep them alive.
But there be a whatever 19th century magic was.
Yeah right.
Drawings in the Hungry Bear restaurant.
OK.
Not a ton of representation there.
Right.
Certainly drawings.
Yeah.
So they have this plan.
We're going to get rid of this.
But the Country Bear Theater turned it into Winnie the Pooh.
Country Bear Jamboree's last day of operation in Disneyland September 9th 2001.
What did they know.
We got to get out of town.
This shit's going to hit the fan in the cities.
We're going to head back to the holler.
That's Bob Iger resigning like a week before Covid started.
That's like if you and that's not a little fishy.
Look it up folks.
It's like a week before everything shuts down Bob Iger's like I'm out.
Hey Zeke and Zeb we still got that underground bomb shelter.
Yeah.
Who?
Calpac Clint Texas.
Hey Tennessee Bear you're getting a call from Langley Virginia.
You know anything about that?
We're not telling.
We know even if we do know something we ain't telling.
Some weird sign ups for flight school I've been reading about.
Bush White House is calling.
You getting a call from the switchboard of Bush White House?
Scooter Libby was one of the bears right?
Yeah Scooter Libby.
George W used to jam with us.
He goes way back.
We haven't seen Big Al in a while but he was muttering about jet fuel not melting steel
beams on the way out.
We didn't know what that meant.
We jammed with John Huntsman and Mike Huckabee too.
We get a whole thing going here.
I'm telling you September 2001 shit's gonna hit the fan.
The twin theaters are gonna go down.
Oh God.
Our two theater we got two theaters for the Jamboree.
It happened.
It did happen.
Also a weird like you think of Disney as like a real corporate synergy like divisions knowing
what others are doing sometimes not knowing what they're doing.
But the movie was they everyone knew the movie was coming in 2002.
You'd think they would have given the theater another year to like.
How does it hurt them to keep it around to plug and this is not now they're trying to
get as much IP out of the parks as they can and there's a billion other ways to promote
things.
But like this is at this point in time the first or second major movie made out of a
theme park attraction.
Do you not want to keep said attraction open with a sign at the end that says if you liked
this maybe you'll like the movie.
Now that would have been a lie.
They probably wouldn't have liked the movie.
We'll find out soon enough.
Yeah.
You would think you would think that would have made sense.
But no.
Yeah I guess I guess no one was paying attention.
I don't know.
So strange and as this movie comes out and just flounders just eats it just did not too
well at all.
Do you not think.
Well you know I have an idea.
There's a place that we own that thousands people go through every day.
Yeah.
Maybe we could keep our living advertisement for this movie there.
Was there anything in Florida.
Do we know.
Was there any sort of ad for I mean well maybe if if we talk about the movie we'll look into
that because I'm wondering is there a flyer outside.
I think it's also interesting just in the sense of I think Country Bears is like Pirates
or Haunted Mansion or Space Mountain where it becomes a shorthand for either Disney World
Disneyland or theme parks at large.
Yeah.
There's a lot of reference in the popular popular consciousness popular culture to this
attraction.
So to like shut it down.
It does feel yeah I think like to a person who doesn't have theme parks memorized to
a John Lennon who probably didn't go terribly often.
Right.
I think your vague sense of like what's Disney World.
Well there's a castle and there's tea cups and there's the country bear jamboree.
It is a thing where a bunch of bears sing songs.
It does oddly feels like a Disney tent pole even if it hasn't been treated as such and
yeah he isn't to a lot of people.
I feel like there was a point in time where it was Mr. Toad's wild ride country bears
pirates.
I even think like phrases that right like to that like jump out at you more.
Nobody would call it the utopia.
Nobody uses the real term man tea party but I think the phrase is Pirates of the Caribbean
and country where jamboree are so weird they like stick with people.
Yeah.
Went even if they don't care.
I would think actually probably if you were pulling people more people would know country
bear jamboree than tea room.
Yeah.
Maybe so.
And yet you know what is weird about it.
I was gonna bring this up.
I don't know that there's like the hit single you know what I mean.
You know the Tiki room.
So I see what you're saying.
No great big beautiful tomorrow.
That's the only song in the fit but like yeah these songs are all good but there isn't
the one.
Well, the Crockett but that was a hit on it.
So that was a huge hit for you.
Yeah.
But there's not like here's the I would maybe say great outdoors maybe but it was only one.
I think that hurts it a little bit too that there isn't the small world.
You probably right.
Yeah worm.
There is something up to that I think.
Songs are all good again but it's not like great I would say but you're right.
It's not it's missing its hit.
I told the families did not come out of the park they like drove in from Arizona and on
their way back home they're all singing.
Yeah that's true.
That's a very good point that I think is right.
When I had not been there in a while then went back around the time you did Mike.
I thought the transition from the Davy Crockett song to old slew foot is pretty smooth.
Like I thought like wait is this a verse of the Davy Crockett song.
Yes I agree.
I thought that too.
Yeah.
Because it's just so so like slick the way those two transition and then blood on the
saddle also still going in the background like pairs pairs with all of those kind of get
meshed together in a big finale.
I also just like to encourage the future use of old slew foot as a nickname for Jason Sheridan.
I did there there is a term I did look up the meaning of that old slew foot.
Oh God.
Someone a someone treat lover who gets exhausted walking through theme parks readily.
Oh yeah.
Having big clumsy or turned out feet.
Well I haven't told my feet like tilt a little like I'm trying to correct that.
Oh sure.
Oh mind you too actually I had cast when I was a child I guess I'm the slew foot.
Oh my sister had cast too and like sad hard saddle shoes with a connected with like a piece
of metal.
I hope there was never blood on the saddle.
Blood all around.
I don't have the saddle shoes.
She kicked me with them.
Yes my blood.
One thing also to say in terms of how the country bears are represented in the parks
to this day Oogie Boogie in Haunted Mansion Holiday is big Al.
He was de skinned.
His organs were removed and he was turned.
He was a large ghost.
On his driver's license though he was a donor so it's okay.
I would love to see Oogie Boogie program to say that puddle like I always love that delivery
of puddle.
Puddle.
Yeah.
Yeah so I would be interested I'm sure there's plenty of like parts because they just sub
out parts of animatronics all the time from my understanding.
So you could have like Zeb's shoulder is somewhere.
In Millard Fillmore.
Yeah.
The whole presidents.
They're like oh shit we need to oh yeah just take it out of Zeb.
Poor Zeb is like half half like not even there half missing.
Really depressing probably.
We were yeah Jane and I were talking about that we were in Florida of like what is preserved
what is safe because I saw pictures from that destination D23 event they did recently and
they had the dream finder like machine.
Yeah.
And and we're always trying to figure out what was demolished what was you know stripped
for parts and what was just you know.
I was thinking about how annoying that actually is to me.
I love seeing that dream finder thing but it's such bullshit that they just bring that
stuff out at conventions.
They're like hey remember this.
Yeah we do this at any time.
Anytime we just put it back in the right one.
We're not we're just going to put it in a fucking showroom.
Enjoy it here.
We know by the way we know you want it.
Like this is the thing with D23 and anytime they trot all this stuff out we know you want
this.
Yeah.
But this is all you're getting.
We know the dream finder is from a park that is mostly construction walls.
Yeah.
But we know that we have gutted his ride to turn it into the worst ride that exists perhaps
on the planet.
We know.
We know it.
But the good news is we are now selling t-shirts that look like the construction walls.
So pretty good.
It's got the stripes.
People are going to be nostalgic for him someday.
They're going to miss the yeah they're going to miss the stripes on the walls.
So yeah they they they know.
That's what it's doing to me that they know.
And that's why yeah look Gomer's foot shouldn't just be turned into Andrew Carnegie's right
elbow in American Adventure.
These are not interchangeable.
These are perfect characters who sing pretty songs, catchy songs, honest songs, songs about
their experiences, about all the blood they've seen and all the moonshine they've drank.
Yes.
This is one of the most honest raw pieces of theme park entertainment that exists.
And if yeah and if look it sucks but like if you need if they to exist they need to
sing fancy like and Red Solo Cup.
That should be the case.
They should do that.
I'm fine with them.
It's on you.
Keep your eyes on the country contemporary charts.
Yes.
I have some goofy voiced guys sing it with an occasionally change words into bear.
Yeah Zeekers somebody or Henry singing like lyrics of Chicken Fried about a cold beer
on a Friday night and the touch of jeans that fit a pair of jeans that fit this right in
the touch of a precious child.
All the things that the character that Zach Brown loves that he says in that song Chicken
Fried.
We definitely spent some time examining like what does he mean the touch of a precious
child.
It's just such an odd for it not in there's anything on toward just that it's like it's
such an odd thing.
I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think I think
ten years ago to my friend's wedding is just I was I was making fun of that song and she's
like I like that so I go but let's let's listen to the lyrics without the words and I said
I just said them to I go doesn't that sound like if you were on a date with a guy and
he was like you know what one of my favorite things is the touch of a precious child you'd
be like oh God.
And she's like yeah you're right.
It's like I do agree that's a weird lyric out of that context extremely creepy.
Okay.
So maybe we don't do that one do fine.
Look I'm just Googling country songs do.
I was on a boat that day by Old Dominion.
Fantastic.
I see the thumbnail on Vivo.
They're all on about this five of them just like the bear rugs.
The parts are already divvied up.
You just have to make one part for a single string bass and turn one guitar into a jug.
Stop being lazy.
The songs you need are there.
They're on the album Time Tequila and Therapy by Old Dominion.
Just get busy bearifying it you lazy imagineers.
Oh yeah.
I want to light up Lake Nona with this call.
Just get him you know you know who's bored and not doing anything is that rockafire creep.
Get him on it.
Wait no don't.
No no.
All right well ask him if he knows a less creepy animatronic guy and yeah steal a phone
number if the rockafire explosion could be reprogrammed so easily for too many music
videos then why not do it with the country bears.
Yeah get one song past the year 1980 into that thing and maybe you'll start packing
the crowds in again.
Well the only thing that we can do is keep the country bears relevant and you know what's
a good way to do that is by having America's hottest theme park podcast.
That's true though right.
Yeah that's right.
We are the hottest.
Well I can't think of anything that would.
That's a pretty specific word.
It's a narrow category so why not put ourselves as kings of that hill.
Podcast the ride is no longer hot.
That's where he lost my vote.
Yeah.
When he called out our podcast.
You can go after grace and Carter whatever the hell his name is all day.
You don't come after us.
Say what you want about that.
Greed and Carter.
Yeah.
We breathe our souls into this very hot theme park podcast and what we're going to do all
week long is keep the country bears relevant and I think after what we do with this week
you know I think it might be a different story.
I think 2022 is going to look very different for these 50 year old bears because if you
didn't get enough out of this what the amount of time episode almost 250 Jesus really.
Yeah.
You know.
Okay.
Well then let's not wrap this thing up forever.
Wow.
Okay.
So if that didn't give you your fill of the country bears then the week certainly will
not done.
We got more.
Can you believe it.
You survived day one of country bear chamber week.
I'm really questioning what are we doing.
Yeah.
I don't know.
It's a little silly.
I'll say that was that.
It's nearly three hours enough.
Hell no.
No.
We got vacation overlays to talk about.
We got feature films to talk about.
There's all kinds of odd manifestations of this attraction and we're going to keep going.
We're going to keep deep diving.
So you survived night one.
Stay tuned.
We haven't said this in a long time.
We'll be back tomorrow.
Oh yeah.
Back tomorrow with more episodes.
Till then follow all the country bear chamber week happenings at podcast the riot on all
the social media.
Merch is available in our T public store for the full country bear chamber week experience.
Check out podcast the ride the second gate at patreon.com slash podcast the riot.
And if you aren't sick of content from us in general I now get to start plugging Saturday
morning all star hits on Netflix.
The new show from Kyle Mooney with a little help from me eight episodes streaming on Netflix
right now at this point with this amount of podcasts and that show going you have no excuse
but to only absorb content from us.
Yeah.
In the next week or so.
This is your whole holiday break folks.
Really.
Unless you're doing it daily.
Yeah.
You could.
But we all say I think we're loading you.
This is how we're ending the year.
So we're loading you up with goodies to take home with you.
Yes.
Yeah.
To your holler.
What are you going to do?
What?
Come on.
Everyone in America already has.
We already all watched it.
Seventy million.
We're all.
We're all embroiled in the tale of Cleopatra's eggs.
Finding Cleopatra's eggs.
The movie which is the most popular movie of the decade is about.
Is that what it is?
Does she lay eggs?
Yeah.
It's about finding.
I don't know.
It's in the trailer.
She lays eggs.
Cleopatra lays eggs in this movie?
Watch the trailer.
The Rock says Cleopatra's eggs.
They've stolen two of Cleopatra's eggs.
Fabricate, like the decorative.
Faberge.
Faberge, that's what I was looking for.
Not her leg.
Eggs from her ovaries.
And also in this movie's universe, Cleopatra lays eggs.
It's a different human.
This movie supposes human beings laid eggs.
It's kind of frozen in previous centuries.
Well, that's how you bring country bears back.
Just in the opening of the show, he's like, well, we got to do a little show for you while
we wait for our eggs to hatch.
And everyone just has questions about, wait, why do the bears lay eggs in this show?
So the premise is they play bluegrass music, but also they lay eggs.
So they're freak bears in multiple regards.
All right.
So again, no excuse.
Only content from us.
We're giving you plenty.
We'll be back tomorrow.
Y'all come on back now, you hear?
This has been a Forever Dog Production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehme, Joe
Sileo, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts,
Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram, at
foreverdogteam, and liking our page on Facebook.