Forever.
Dog.
Stay tuned with the Country Bear Jamboree Week.
We got Guy Selga from the TourPlan's website joining us.
This episode contains California bears, secrets discovered via animatronic nametag,
and the difference between theme park work trips and theme park fun trips.
It's the Country Bear Vacation Hoedown on Podcast the Ride.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride Country Bear Jamboree Week Day 2.
This feels good, right? How long has it been since you just immediately got a new podcast?
I assume having devoured yesterdays, which, you know, despite it being exceedingly long.
Well, wait, I haven't been introduced, I guess.
Oh, yeah, really well, yeah. I'm keeping the names alive, so I'll go through them.
I'm swinging Scotty Gardner, seeking to speak, is big car-owl-son, and yes, go ahead.
Oh, I was just going to say, yeah, like the first episode of this was already longer than the first Get Back.
So we're already winning as far as doing content on very famous bands.
So will this go long? Because I think the second episode of Get Back is actually longer than the first.
So will we go longer than yesterday? That's really my question. And I don't know. I don't know the answer.
It's up to all of us to be a little Peter Jacksons.
We are little Peter Jacksons today.
Little Peter Jacksons, including Jughead J. Sun Bonnet Sheridan. Hi, J. Sun.
The littlest Peter Jackson.
Among little, like three little ones, but you're the littlest.
I do have, sometimes he would do interviews, I feel like, around the Lord of the Rings or The Hobbit,
and his hair was very frizzy and frizzed out, and my hair is very long and Peter Jacksons.
Well, I'll probably get a cut before then. So as we're recording.
Your hair looks like you were ready for senior prom versus what Peter Jacksons looks like during an interview.
His is crazy. His is wild.
He knows cameras are in front of him and he's still like, this is fine.
He's unkempt. You look like you're ready.
I'm picture ready.
You look like you're ready for the Sadie Hawkins dance. You look like you're ready to go.
Yeah. Well, thanks. I'll take it.
Looking sharp, J. Sun.
Anyway, it's day two and today we are covering the vacation hoedown,
the seasonal overlay that they started doing in 86.
There's so many fragments of different shows and pieces of The Country of the Jamboree that we got to get to.
And I know a fan of this particular iteration and The Country of the Jamboree in general is seated over to my left.
He is the Disneyland writer for touring plans and the co-author of the unofficial guide to Disneyland.
It's Guy Selgo. It's going on.
Hey, thanks for having me. Walking in here, I thought we were going to talk about coming out of their shells tour.
Oh, man. But from what I understand, this is this is the showbiz pizza band.
Close. Very close. Yeah. Oh, wait. See how he's all mixed up.
I thought he knew what all the things were. Go with it.
OK. Yeah, sure. Anyway, so Billy Bob, he drinks gasoline or something.
I believe so. OK. Yeah.
There's little guys who pop up out of holes.
I don't remember any of their name. You probably do know more about.
We actually haven't done that. Mizzy Mozzarella. Yeah. Mizzy Mozzarella. OK.
Trying to beat you to the names. Yeah. Bats. You know, the four little shavers.
Wow. Geez. We haven't we done. We probably got to do that one.
That's an episode. Yeah, we got to get what's his name on the show, too.
Just kidding. The inventor of. Yeah, just kidding.
I don't know about that.
Yeah. Guy, thanks. Thanks so much for being here.
Thanks for having me talking about my favorite attraction of all time, specifically the vacation version.
So I'm really happy to be here. Oh, fantastic. Great. Great. Well, OK.
So, yeah, we had heard that you were a Country Bear fan.
I even looked up. I was like, I think I Googled your name and country bear.
I saw that you like this one like, OK, that is perfect. That's great.
So we will leave that to the side in our first episode and narrow in here.
Also kind of funny how you came to be on the show when we were talking about who do we who is a country bear fan, like a super fan.
I mean, yeah, yeah, yeah. Really next level bear fan.
And somehow Jason knew Jason brought up your name when we were discussing people.
And then I was at Disneyland a month ago drinking alone at the Ant Man bar, as is one's right to do.
I've done it a couple of times. It's a pretty good spot. It is a pretty good spot.
I guess I've only been there alone once.
But soon enough, I was not alone because I bumped into Chuck and Sally, who are listeners to the show.
My good friends. That's just what I've heard.
And so I started saying, hey, I think we're going to do this country bear thing.
And they said you got to talk to Guy Selga. He's a fan of this.
And also, he's the person who married. Yeah, I think wedding out in Phoenix.
Yes. Yeah. Yeah. In another state, even.
This is commitment. A good friend, a good, good helper.
So they spoke very highly of you and it was nice to meet them.
So there's a lot of love going around here.
So it was meant to be, I feel like, between all of these these endorsements.
Yeah. It does real quick before we even talk to the Bears.
I want to let the audience doesn't know your job is to be at Disneyland, essentially.
Yeah. Touring plans. We we take the guesswork out of trip planning
and we help you save time and money in Disneyland and Walt Disney World and Disney Cruise Line and that sort of thing.
And we have our day to day itineraries that go where the crowds aren't.
And we have every bit of information you could possibly want to plan a trip.
Right. So it's your job to gather this information essentially on an almost daily basis.
Yeah. And I'm the Disneyland dude.
Keep everything up to date over there and do a lot of blog posts and whatnot.
And yeah, I've been there for about 10 years. So, geez.
So for that amount of time, you've been going to Disneyland. How often a week?
It depends on what the needs of the company are.
Like sometimes I'll be there every day, but you know, sometimes it'll be a couple of times a week.
But wow. Wow. And then what is the divide end up being between like, are you are you having your Disney fun a little bit,
but like observing things doing your work as well?
I'm good at in my brain flipping on the fun mode versus work mode switch when I'm at the parks.
So if like if I'm there with friends, I can just flip it off and enjoy it like and really like Disneyland never gets old.
I mean, we agree with flipping it on and off.
Yeah, like we were there for a couple for the opening of Marvel, the opening of Marvel and the opening of Star Wars.
Like those lands were we're a little stressful.
Like you're about you're about here. Can I finish what your point is?
I think you're going to make is that when we went to the opening of Marvel, you had the work switch switched on. I did.
You are the kid you are. You are.
I've noted a number of times you saying like, well, I'm here for work.
So like the degree of stress was also like very stressful.
I mean, yeah, of course you had to have a reservation, the wait in the line or a reservation for the ride to get in the land.
It was all kinds of chaos. I mean, I'm sure you saw a little of it.
If you were not there, I was there.
The line stretched back to I think like Little Mermaid and it was kind of unorganized.
They said the line is going to cut off. Yeah, it was it was stressful.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I remember I was about to just say I remember seeing aerial pictures.
Oh, yeah. Little Mermaid. I apologize for that.
That word specifically. But yes, I looked really insane.
Have you been there for like a lot of the initial like first Galaxy's Edge first?
Yes. Yeah, everything. We're not big on, you know, being first and getting all the blog posts out and like bragging lies.
We just want to get the data. Yeah.
You're like just your organization is just like just the facts.
Yes, pretty much. It's no frills.
It's like a Bill Moyers PBS style. You know, it's not like a trashy Fox News type place.
Yeah, we don't post rumors or anything.
And you know, like being a Disney blogger is a is a very negative job to have.
I feel like you make fun of. But I like being for turn planes because I can say I'm a writer.
I can say I'm a writer. Right. Right. Sure.
Well, yeah, I mean, being that you're just trying to not like a go nuts with opinions, that definitely puts you in a different category than a lot of these sites who are so full of complaints.
Yeah, weirdness. Well, that yeah. Good for you. I mean, like other stuff just being that you're there so free.
I mean, what like is it? Will it just be like I'm just going to watch how a line works today for a while or if like focus on this attraction, that attraction?
Yeah. So we have a team of data scientists and sometimes all they need is to sit in this on this bench in this walkway in the park and count how many people walk by.
And then other times it's just ride this ride over and over and get the actual wait times because Disney's wait times are reactionary and are and we predict the wait times.
So they're they're posted away if it's 40 minutes. That was the wait 40 minutes ago. And so we predict the way. Right. Right. Gotcha.
Can I ask a question? And maybe this to inside and I'll have to cut this. But since Disney reopened after the pandemic, Disneyland opened, I feel that each way time is double what it actually is.
They say it's like 75 minutes and it'll be half that. Yeah. There's a lot of bloated wait times going on right now for sure. OK, because I have I have thoughts and theories about that.
But I don't we'll talk about that off air. Do we have to? What's the what are you worried about something? I'm not worried. No, I'll talk about it.
I feel the theory is sorry to interrupt. The conspiracy theory is that they're bloating it for lightning lane to make it more.
Yeah. Oh, OK. So because because the Guardians, like it feels like every time I've been out in the last few months, it's like 75 minutes, 80 minutes.
And I'm I breeze through that line. Yeah. And it feels like they're get they're priming people and getting them ready to go.
Oh, 80 minutes. All right. How much? 15. OK. Yeah. Even rise of the resistance.
I've been timing that a lot this this week and last week since they put it on a standby wait. And that's been 30 or 40 or 50 minutes under the post to wait sometimes.
Because I was giving this theory to somebody else. I was ran into some friends and then I told them the theory and they're like, oh, we'll check.
And then two hours later, they were like, yes, you're right. It was half the time. Yeah. I feel like they're yeah, I feel like it's real.
I feel like this is a conspiracy theory that's real. Yeah. Yeah. It was kind of that same way in Florida, too, because I got the Florida and
Cali, Anaheim touring plans apps a month or so ago in anticipation of going down to Florida.
And I did find like touring plants was usually pretty accurate, like usually impossible to predict, like phenomenon of like, OK, they're holding the entire standby line
because there's a full family that doesn't know how to scan their lightning lanes. The cast members over and everyone's overwhelmed.
And it's Disney Plus Day and no one knows what that means.
So weird phenomenon would pop up that like, oh, no app could account for this. Yeah, it's scary accurate sometime.
Can I say something, too, about Disney Plus Day? Yes, I feel like at Disneyland, they had a big blue carpet out covering the entire entrance of the park.
Well, really into the train station and stuff. OK, I feel like that's a future like look at this weird thing that happened at Disneyland 20 years ago.
Disney Plus Day. Remember Disney? Oh, yeah. It's just gigantic blue carpet like one of those like it's tailor made for.
Wasn't there a thing where there was an Olympic size swimming pool on Main Street? Yeah. It's one of these oddities like really?
Or like when Chicken Little was hovering over MGM Studios? Yeah, totally. That's going to be when Disney Plus is dead and gone.
Yeah, the pod. Yeah, the pod. Like whoever is us in the future like that as a theme park, like whatever nano podcast would just be like,
did you know there was a blue carpet out 20 years ago? That's weird.
And it goes it's a nano because it's like nobody needs headphones anymore. It's like little nanotechnology allows it to just be in there.
And then some auction way down the line will sell pieces of the carpet for like $2,000. Oh, yes. Disgusting, stinky pieces of the carpet.
And that, yeah. Well, I mean, we'll all be like go and see it before it's auction and go, oh, it's a carpet. I was alive.
I tell my grown child, you brought me out for this. I mean, I consider there was an eBay auction for some of the inflatable Castle Cake.
Yeah, I remember panels not too long ago. And I was like, I don't know how well verified this is.
And also this might stink like this sort of industrial rubber that was sitting in the Florida sun and humidity for whatever that was.
Yeah, they should really disclose at an auction if something's going to smell, if it's something's going to be smelly, something's going to be smelly.
Good condition, lightly stinky, a little stinky. Is there a guy, do you have like, how often are you doing something that maybe you haven't done?
Is it pretty much like it falls into a couple of categories or like once in a while are they like, we need you to count how many people buy mozzarella sticks at the stage door?
Even though I think I don't think they offer them anymore. It's pretty consistent on what I do for work.
But it just depends on what the stats team needs and any given time. Like right now, for example, rise of the resistance just switched over to standby.
So I've been told to go to the park and rope drop rise of the resistance and time the weights for the first couple hours of every day.
So we can get a solid prediction set up for that for the future. Gotcha. Are there any other people that are doing like your job for a different organization?
I don't think so. I think a lot of them, a lot of the other non Disney wait time apps just scrape Disney's wait times and just be done with it.
So you're the only person that has your job probably in the world as far as I know. Yeah. But then we have our Florida researchers.
We have two researchers for Walt Disney World. Right. Gotcha. I was wondering if there's like a group of like people like they're all doing a different but yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. You ever seen the episode of step by step at Disney World where there's a character named Flash who's trying to break a Russian guy's record of go doing all the rides and Disney well, the rides and shops and restaurants.
And Disney World in four days. I haven't seen that. But that sounds like a TGIF plot point.
Like a thing that wouldn't happen. There wouldn't be a Disney like NASA headquarters with a bunch of people in lab coats.
And I guess does that sound do you think that if you watched that, would it resonate at all with your job or would you just think, oh, this is wildly inaccurate?
Yeah, I probably tear up and it would probably be like the Bible. You know, I'd get really emotional watching it.
Finally feel seen. Yeah. Representation television.
Okay. Well, to bring it to the Bears. Yeah. After several people had said that you're a Bears fan. I think I looked at your Twitter and then indeed you had just posted this this pile of merchandise that you just come across.
Yeah, I mean, I was going to bring this up later, but Japan still really loves the Bears out there. Yeah. Yeah. And they regularly release merchandise.
So recently they released a line of plates and trays and cutlery.
This is new. It looks so like cool and it's brand new like, and so out there they have, you know, the Country Bear Theater where Country Bear Jamboree plays and then they have hungry bear restaurant.
And it's it's all curry. Every dish there is curry. So in this new line of merchandise was a curry bowl and like a curry like a wooden. Yes. I know what you're saying is I look at this.
Their curry is pretty good. That's like it's pretty good to in that. Yeah. We ate there. Yeah. Yeah. They used to have a curry house in in LA here and it was the same company.
I think it was called House Foods. Really? Oh, really? It would be like my little bit of Tokyo Disneyland food here in LA, but they they got bought out by hometown buffet and they they closed all the curry house location.
That's how evil is that? I thought you were in it for a COVID closure somehow, but I didn't expect that even worse. Yeah. How long was it? I'm going to be so upset that I could have gone to that.
And it was it was like a year and a half ago. Yeah. This Japanese curry around. Maybe not that Japanese curry. It exists. That is, of course, there's. Yeah. But that's a little piece of Tokyo.
Right. And our yard. You know, so also sorry, the they they love the bears. They're still releasing stuff. They just announced days ago they are going to sell Country Bear Jamboree branded packets of curry that you can take home.
Really? Wow. I swear. Look it up.
So great curry because I know it universal in Osaka. They have like cup noodle with like Spider-Man. Yeah. It's Spider-Man themed cup noodle that you can take home with you. Yeah.
Wow. So is that I'm trying to think in Tokyo. Is that uncommon where it's like they have I mean, I guess like in the whatever confectionary or whatever they call the bakery or whatever there. But I'm trying to think is there other like food items that's branded with a character there?
Yeah, they'll they'll do they'll do like they're they're moving through the food so fast there. They're coming out with new stuff all the time and retiring old stuff. Like I remember they had a couple a couple trips ago. They had this Chippendale like pastry and it was it looked like a peanut.
And one half of it was sweet and the other half was savory. Wow. And then in universal Japan especially like they they had the it was like a jaws some kind of breading with a hot dog sticking out. Yeah. And then like I saw that back draft.
They had a body bag with like a turkey leg inside.
Wow. Yeah, so good. So good. Yeah, that's kind of the secondary element I think of when I think of factor. Yeah, go to the fire first. Yeah, really think of human human suffering.
The cost of our set of malicious ours. And now you get to enjoy and enjoy it with your taste buds. One more thing about in Tokyo the the hungry bear restaurant in the lobby for country where theater they have a napkin from hungry bear and written on it is the lyrics to the
Bear Band Serenade. So it's like Henry was in hungry bear having a meal and he jotted down the lyrics. It's just it's so good because there's like a little glass case of paraphernalia stuff. That's very get back just you know you said where he doesn't know where inspiration is going to strike.
If it's at a restaurant than it is the napkin dirty. I think I met with is the napkin knew because we ate there but I missed it. I know it's in the lobby of the show the theater. Oh, I missed it there to the year. They also have a cover of climb magazine where they were named.
Yeah, I mentioned climb yesterday and there's something where is this the same thing actually where like there's musical notation scratched out where like he makes the dears. This is E and this is G. Yeah, that's that's so cool. It's a cool lobby.
I mean so well this implies that you see you've seen you've been to Japan you've seen the show in Japan. Oh, yeah. Was it exciting to see it there was the enthusiasm high. That's what I found. So I got I got legit emotional because so let me let me just let me just give a little history here.
Yeah, please. I've had a Disneyland annual pass since 1994 and before that I would go almost every week with my mom because one of her friends dad was like a old time monorail pilot who could get us into the park for free whenever we wanted.
So, growing up country bear jamboree vacation hoedown was my country bear show. Oh sure yes because they just switched over to it permanent right and I didn't see the original show until I went to Disney World in 96 and 2008 those were the only times I saw the original show.
Wow wow okay. So, yeah, it and then it closed on September 10 2001 I think which ended up not being the worst thing to happen that week.
And then, yeah, going back to Japan I think about 15 or 16 years later and seeing the vacation show again it was mind blowing it you know some of the songs were in Japanese and some of them were different like Trixie sings a key breaky heart.
Yeah, it's so weird that one opened later it opened in 94 right they gotta keep it relevant. Yeah, relevant to them. Yeah. Did you know at the time what you were going in for was it like, like, did somehow they say it's going to be this one, or did it just wash over you like oh I haven't seen this in decades.
Yeah, I mean I knew we were going to be there in the summer season so because they still show all three shows there they cycle through all three of them is while they get in there they change those clothes, unbelievable, they put the sandwich and Trixie's hand, the sub.
Yeah, that's that's so cool. Did you find that the audience loved it. Yeah, they're that that show is still very popular, it's in a it's in a really prime location as well.
And it's also right off the parade route and prades are just massive yeah it's like one of the main forms of entertainment there. So it gets a lot of traffic, and yeah people are really into it and if they keep doing the merch obviously like people are buying it and it's popular,
because they, they they also released over the last few years, a line of plushies of all the characters.
And then also for each of the shows, the seasonal variety of the shows so it's like, there's so many of these stuffed bears now and they're like $18 each and me almost a 40 year old man just having a big box of stuffed bears in my closet.
Well I came back from Japan with like it was unreal how many little bags I had because like they always have to give you one and like, like, geez I'm like, like the pile was like 50 deep and I'm in America I'm not a theme park merch buyer at all.
Yes, I was shy just like could not stay away from everything there was crazy. Yeah, yeah, I got my sister the sun bonnets in the bathing suits. Oh yeah, they have of course good stuff.
Do you are you so like, there's so many different, I think we've talked about a little bit on the show. There's like services now to get merchandise from Tokyo Disney, and have it sent here.
Are you generally just buying it when you go there or do you are you in got like something going on. I'm buying it when I go there I mean I haven't been since 2019 now because you know, you know,
Yeah, but yeah I have some friends over there that are able to send me the stuff and I just pay an insane amount for shipping but I don't have to pay like the service charge that a lot of those personal shoppers do.
Geez, yeah, it's a whole industry I've looked into yeah yeah I'm not gonna start doing it. I'm saying, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I bought some I bought that popsicle shirt.
Yeah, I did a free service. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I didn't just like take a picture. Oh yeah you bought that for me. Yeah, yeah. Right.
Yeah, vacation hoedown specific although feel free also any bare stuff. Yeah, yeah, if there's anything that made you fall in love with the franchise, although I guess you were saying, vacation hoedown was was your first.
I mean vacation and Christmas when Christmas would roll around which is also a great show but I'll get I'll stick it to the I'll keep to the vacation version.
I wrote some stuff down. Oh, if you don't mind we just get into it.
So, the original country bar jamboree opened in Disneyland in 1972 it was so popular in Walt Disney World that where it had only one theater that in Disneyland they built two theaters because they're like this is going to be a hit, people are going to love the bears build two theaters.
So that was really all that was back in that corner of the park in bear country.
It was a dead end, and it brought in the people for a couple months. But then it kind of slowed down so they said, we, you know, we need to, we need to do something about this.
So Tony Baxter and his team were thinking about reworking the land but that was going to take several years. And so these two young imagineers came along and they said, why don't we just make a new country bear show that we can get together in six months or a year instead of, you know, 10 years.
So,
David fighting and Michael sprouts were the two imagineers. Okay.
They were big fans of the country bear jamboree and they said quote those bears must get tired of singing the same old songs over and over again.
They said this in the Disney News magazine in an interview.
So they pitched developing new shows to Marty score, and they showed him sketches that showed hey we can take this these existing see stages and bears and we can redress them and write new songs and make a new show.
So, Marty saw the potential and he approved.
So the, the Christmas show was first was the first one to come along. And it was a big hit. And so they pretty much immediately like within months approved a another new show, which ended up being the vacation version.
So they, they, they did that and it opened and it was also a hit but but ultimately it slowed down again because again there was still no attractions back in that corner.
Yeah. And so can I just say to some things I love about the vacation version is that it builds upon the lore of all the bears. I feel like in such in such believable ways, like you can see.
You can see shaker being kind of like a duet artist singing with a little penguin or a little octopus.
You know Henry with his with his old camp t shirt on, you can see him being kind of nostalgic for being back in camp and still hanging on to the shirt. I don't know I just growing it a little bit it's getting dirty.
Yeah, it all makes sense in the character it all makes yeah it's not like they just threw it up in the air and said well who cares about keeping consistent with the narratives that we've, or whatever yeah the character games of these different pairs.
Yeah, I love hearing that I like I did not know any of that that it was done by that it was developed by people who were fans of the original now to measure it because you that makes so much that it's like, it feels like a cool like you know, hey Oakley and Weinstein on the Simpsons like started watching it and then they were now they're running the show.
Right now like what do we want the characters to do what a dream. It was like a mini version of that. It's that's very charming.
I almost brought up the camp grizzly shirt when we were talking about merch because as soon as I saw that I was like, they have to do a camp grizzly like they do all these throwback things.
You are wearing these at the yesteryears. Yeah, this is yesteryears with big Al in his vacation.
Right. So he's flannel shirt and his little minor hat and whatnot. Yeah, his little teddy bear.
Yeah, I have that. So I think that would be a hit if they sold that shirt. Also, if they sold as a half shirt, that would be very funny because yeah, he thinks him.
I mean, I don't know about it. I feel like, you know, two tops half shirts are very in style.
That's true. You're right. X number of years. That's true.
So to open the vacation show they play the great outdoors a song called the great outdoors great song probably one of my favorite Disney songs ever.
Yeah, we were saying I was saying you I don't know if you find this controversial, but yesterday I was saying I like maybe a weakness of the original show is there's not like the hits.
There's not a great grinning goes. Yeah. And I think maybe great outdoors is as close as you come.
Yeah. And the Christmas show has tracks in the snow, which is also a banger opener.
Just a total bop. So I'm such a big fan of great outdoors. I've always have been. I used to watch country bridge and very like multiple times a week at Disneyland.
I just so I a few years back. I was watching the Disneyland fun sing along to. Yeah. Yeah. And they they do their great outdoors on there. Yeah, they they sing it on there.
So I'm watching the credits and I see this name great outdoors by George Wilkins and so I'm like I got to look this guy up. He's a genius. I don't know what else he's done, but he's genius just for the song.
So I write him and I'm like your song changed my life.
So anyway, he's like funny you bring that up because I actually didn't write that song. My colleague, Phil Baron did and I wrote a song called great outdoors for Winnie the Pooh, some Winnie the Pooh project.
So Disney credited it wrong and and then he had Phil also write me and he said that even Disney mixed it up and he they were sending Phil's royalties to George for the song for a little bit.
And once they realized it, they got it all straightened out and I've seen compilation CDs and since then that have credited correctly. So they they obviously did fix it along the way. This is wild lore.
They communicated with these people and found this clerical issue. This is what's often so infuriating like trying to research some of this stuff. It's like, okay, I went to a book. I went to a book by the company. I went to a primary as primary source I could get or even like if you try to reach out to someone and you're like, oh no, the book's wrong.
And it's like, okay, well, I get someone doing like a Geo cities or a blog spot. They get a fact wrong or something, you know, but like when the when stuff like that is wrong or the company's paying the wrong person.
It's just like, oh, well, what do you do that happen with the horizons where like the big mural at the end, I had found like one very old blog that said it's in a cast member building backstage and I couldn't find any one else.
I like emailed every reporter I knew like, do you know where the painting is? I've heard it's preserved and no one email the budget report. I emailed. Yeah, email like Carly and Todd. And I was like, you know where the mural because I couldn't find any other.
And then after that we put that episode out. Someone did tweet at me like, hey, another show just talked about this. This is the cast member building. It's in it is still there, but I couldn't find any other. I hadn't found anything else like after like a week of looking.
You think somebody would have snuck out a picture of it since then? Right, yeah. It's also massive. Yeah, gigantic. Yeah, right. So yeah, so they yeah, I watched that sing along to a lot. I remember as a kid not know. I knew they were the country bears, but I was like, what is this song from?
Because I wasn't even aware of the multiple shows. I had just seen the regular show and it was only like maybe less than 10 years ago, right? I was like, oh, okay. And like I figured out what it was. But yeah, that is yeah. Yeah.
You bring up not seeing the original or only seeing the original show and I'm that's one thing I've never gotten a clear answer on is why they gave up on it so fast at Walt Disney World because I think it only the vacation show I think only lasted there for less than 10 years, maybe five or 10 years.
92 I read 92. So yeah, there you go. Yeah. So what what happened there? Because they still would switch to the Christmas show up until I think 2008. But then they didn't want to pay the what I heard was like 50 grand to switch over shows.
That's what it cost like every time that that's what I read on Jim Hill's some some ancient Jim Hill Geo cities.
But yeah, they gave up on the vacation show so fast over there. Huh? I don't know. I like it's all you're already on vacation. Maybe there's more vacationers there. Don't want to be reminded they're on vacation. Yeah. The stresses of vacation. It's like a double up of it's a hat on a hat.
Or is it just like we don't need to spend money because more of these people are tourists and you're you're seeing more like fresh eyes on the show right? Yeah, then you would on Disney at Disneyland and it's not popular enough like in Tokyo to warrant the price.
Although in Tokyo you get the sense they spend money because it's fun. Right. Which is nice and they don't do that as much in the American parks anymore. Well, if they don't change the ending of a show about progress in the future from an ending scene where they say, boy, the 21st century is going to be great.
Yeah, why would they constantly change outright song of singing bear show? That's a point. Yeah, but virtual reality and voice commands did eventually come back. They thought, you know what, if we just hold out a little longer, the Oculus is going to show up.
They're just waiting for laser discs to come back.
So going back to there being two theaters in Disneyland's version of Country Bridge Ambry. This is what I think ultimately doomed the ride was because it took up so much real estate. Yeah. Yeah. I think if it would have been in Frontierland one theater, it probably would have made sense to keep it around.
Because even by the end of the seventies, they were already thinking of cutting the building in half and re theming half of the show building to something else. What I read was one of the ideas was to make it something called Mark Twain tonight.
So they would have half the building would be Country Bridge Ambry and then the other half they would make a facade on it that would look like a building and then inside would be called Mark Twain tonight, which apparently was a one man show at the time.
Oh, so it existed. Yeah. And this was in 1982. They wanted to make an animatronic version or maybe a live actor, whatever version of this thing called Mark Twain tonight. So that's something. Howell Holbrook? Was that what he was doing?
Yeah. Howell Holbrook, I think. So they're trying, we got to cash in. All the kids are talking about the Howell Holbrook Mark Twain one man show. Playing your local performing arts center. Well before Val Kilmer also did.
Before that the Val Kilmer one. Yeah. Mark, when you say Mark Twain tonight, the first thing I thought of was, oh, it's a talk show parody at late night talk show parody with Mark Twain. That's what I thought too.
Which is by the way, a great idea. Yeah. So and then one of the other ideas was to re-theme Hungry Bear as a hoopty-doo style venue and show, which can you imagine that at Disneyland? How great that would have been? Yeah, I can imagine that. Yeah.
But then that's, but then like, were they still doing Golden Horseshoe then? Is it? Yeah, they were. Yeah. So they're now they maybe have two Western entertainment venues. Maybe that's why they decided not to do it. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It's already covered a little bit.
Wow. That is Mark Twain. You're bringing us some deep stuff here. I will. Yeah. Mark Twain tonight will haunt my dreams. Yeah. Like Mac tonight, Mark Twain tonight. That also feels connected. I don't know. I guess that's the word tonight.
Is if yeah, Mark Twain. So if there's animatronic standups and if Mark Twain likes him, then he gives him the wave over the couch and then yeah, slowly walk over here. Cigar.
And it's like, it's historical figures doing standup. It's like Ben Franklin doing standup or something. Like it's not just a random. Sojourner truth. It's Lincoln. Come on. It's also Lincoln. Yeah. Wow. That's insane. It's also you were sorry. You were just saying it was like there's no rides over there too. So it's like it's a victim of just traffic too. I know they were saying like it's also I've heard maybe Tony Baxter say the same like there's not enough traffic going there. Plus it's more of a
local crowd. So it's more unusual to go to country bears a lot. Right. Like if you're a local because you've seen the show, you don't need to see it, which I was, of course I would disagree. You don't need to see it more than once every couple of months. Yeah. And you know, even in the last few years, the show was open in Disneyland. I can't even recall them running both theaters. Yeah, sure. Sure. Yeah. So you think, well, maybe can you definitively say, I mean, you were only eyeballing it then it was not your job, but you probably know the kind of
like the flow and capacity of Winnie the Pooh. Do you think it makes sense from a strictly numbers standpoint? Like did they make the right call just in the drive? That's impossible. You're you're you're going to say, no, it's got to be bears.
I mean, you know, who is one of the least attended rides in the park just by eyeballing it? I would say it's on a busy day. It's 10 minute wait. I'm sure more people write it than do country bears and the merch, obviously, because they blow out of the water though. It's not like tremendously more people than country bear. I think it is taking the merch into account. It probably that probably right. That's what makes it. Photo ops and states. It becomes like the Pooh corner. Yeah. Where Pooh corner.
Is and where that that's that Pooh store is. That was all country bears stuff as well because they had the mile long bar where they had Max Buffen Melvin on the wall, which are in the Pooh right now. Right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That they're from the mile long bar. And then they had teddy bears swinging arcade, which they stole the sign up for outside of the building. Oh, yes. Yes. Yeah. That's crazy. That's where they had hoof and Henry, which is why this did not come up yesterday somehow despite a very long episode. Yes. Explain hoof and Henry. This is hoof and Henry was, I mean,
in spirit, it's still there as like Woody dancing Woody or something in in in frontier land. Right. OK. But it's this little arcade machine. You put a quarter in, you tap the buttons and you make this little marionette of Woody dance. Or back then it was Henry and it was called the Woody one. I don't think it's in frontier mercantile in in frontier land.
Oh, my God. Things I've never seen in Disneyland. Is it the same one as the Pinocchio one on Main Street? Yeah. Same thing. OK. And you can look at pictures, too, of the Woody. I mean, it's still the country bear stage inside the Woody arcade.
Right. Really? They just modded out the same. Yeah. And they sold hoof and Henry the puppet in one of the auctions a couple of years ago. And he went for like one of those now. Yeah.
One of any auctions. Yeah. Right. They also sold the marquee from the from the attraction. And yeah, we saw that. Right. Was that at the big one where we did the show? Yeah. That was from the that's that's from Disneyland. Yeah.
That's oh yeah. OK. That sounds familiar. And so I found the original guy, the original dude who did the woodworking Raymond. Yeah. Raymond. And I mean, I mean, and I'm just as Raymond.
I'm just everybody loves Raymond. Yeah. And I like, hey, what how much just just just just just a ballpark. Just a quote. Yeah. How much would it make to recreate that?
And he said, like, I will recreate it down to the precise detail for like 10 grand. And I'm like, OK, that's a little out of my price range. But thank you.
He is so it's yeah. Boy, if you win the lottery and I follow him on Facebook or I'm friends with him, I think I'm like following him. I didn't like friend the guy. That would be weird. Right.
I'm following like his page and he does like a lot of I'm assuming you're following this as well. Yeah. He does like a lot of these customs.
So he will like show like he did a poo one or something. And it is just like looks like it belongs to Disneyland. Yeah. He did.
The how I even found out about him was somebody messaged me and was like, look at this. And it was some family commissioned their own country bear marquee.
But it said like the Smith family or something. Wow. Wow. Yeah. That does sound cool. Wait. So what's who's Raymond?
I got to look up his last name. Yeah. I don't call his last name. I have again. I follow him. I'll find it much more dignified than right after it closed.
I found a picture on yesterland of where they just covered the marquee in a seemingly a garbage bag, a garbage bag. Yeah.
God, there's a there should be another picture. It's like a little printout that says like the bears are harboring, harboring or something like that.
Yeah. And they're taking their show on the road. Yeah. There's a new come on back for the new ride. Yeah. OK.
Raymond Kinman and Kinman. Oh, and that's his custom wood pieces.
That's his I mean, that's obviously the picture of it. That's his like whatever you call it. Sure. Photo on Facebook.
Oh, wow. OK. Yeah, it seems like I love my I love my Disney wood.
This is always thing. He's got a web website called Woodcarver. Hold on. Woodcarver guru dot com. That's a good name. Wow.
Yeah. And he's got different pictures like there's like I don't know if you can see this.
Here's like Chip and Dale with like a laugh at Daniels. So whoever the Daniels are had this commission.
Can you see that with the Disney? Yep. Yeah. So so what are you thinking you're going to get?
I think maybe we all know we need wood versions of the three of us as bears. Yeah.
OK. The good boys with us close to the two of G's.
You can get to the Disney. If you're a patron subscriber, if you would change your pledge from five to ten thousand,
appreciate that.
Geez. Wow. This is all crazy stuff.
This is a great outdoors.
I think one of the things that I it's very catchy, obviously, but I think lyrically, I think it stands above the rest
with the fun of like join us bears and suck up some air. Yeah. There's something so weird and brutal about that.
I was going to say this was like to me, it feels like it was almost the start of that 90s Disney like attitude a little bit
where like the ride the ride scripts were like a little sharp, you know, like the dinosaur pre show and the test track pre show and all that kind of thing.
Yes. Like they like Jamboree Vacation Hoedown. It's like it's it's it's really quick. It's quick witted.
It's sharp. It's fast. I feel like a lot of 90s Disney stuff was like that. Yeah.
I think it's funnier maybe. Yeah. The original. I might say some great lines, some great delivery.
Yeah. I laughed too when I realized what the clothes like I was trying to as as you know, I'm watching rewatching it more recently.
And I'm like, OK, yeah, California Bears. That's very funny.
What are the other singing in the rain ghost riders in the sky?
And I was like, oh, what's the closer? And then when I slowly dawned on me, it's thank God I'm a country bear.
I thought that was so funny. So good. Yeah.
To probably a good percentage of our listeners, that's a song by John Denver.
And to those same listeners, he was a singer long ago. This is an old reference and not as old as some of the ones yesterday.
But well, we have been talking about little Jimmy Dickens a lot and that's a much older reference.
Yes. His song was Country Boy, though.
Thank God I'm a country bear. He didn't write about bears. John Denver. More recent than Tex Ritter.
Yeah. Yeah. And Bob Wills. Yeah. Bob Wills. Yeah.
He's like a modern artist compared to those guys. Yeah. I'm also a fan of And If You All Don't Join Us, We'll Chase You Up a Tree.
I love the bite. There's a literal bite in this song.
Also, they for Trixie's song, they really got rid of all the like making fun of her for being a bigger bear.
Like she's just singing about I'm going to eat and everyone's like, hell yeah.
And I do you. Yeah, that's pretty well deserved. Yeah. That's the song.
In this one, it's the song about if. Wait, what is it?
If heartaches were fried chicken, I could buy them by the pound or sell them by the pound.
Yeah, I. And she's got that sandwich. Yeah.
That plastic sandwich, the sub. I.
I just that is like such an appealing.
I know I couldn't eat that, but don't you want to eat that specific this plastic?
Sub. Yeah. Did they ever? They didn't. They didn't sell that a country bear or a hungry bear, did they?
Oh, I wish that would. Yeah, that would be. That's a bit submerged.
There was a video. I was there was a video I was watching that really maybe was the same one of the show where it like really like feels like it features the sub.
Like it feels like I feel like the sub is really picking up like three, four quarters of the frame.
Yeah, there is a shockingly good multi camera.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Recording of this show on YouTube.
They get right up in there like they're walking around right up front.
Like, yeah. Yeah, very watchable. Yeah, absolutely.
You brought up a video. Look up this video. This this this annual pass holder party in 96 was legendary.
OK, was it? There there were several behind the scene ride experiences so you could go underneath star tours and see it.
The the simulator moving. The best thing, though, and the thing I was obsessed with, I think I did it five times.
You could go up on the stage of Country Bear Jamboree and it was when the vacation version was was installed.
And you can look up a video of people walking through it and there's several pictures out there of people posing with the bears.
It's just amazing. That's actually how the Country Bear Jamboree fandom found out.
You know, it's a raccoon. Sammy the raccoon is a or Sammy the Sammy the raccoon is a skunk in the vacation version. Yes, but they never name him.
Oh, so so in in that video and in those pictures, each of the bears, each of the characters have name tags on and the skunk has a name tag, Randy.
So nobody knew it was Randy. No, it was really on the stage to know that was Randy.
And this wasn't even realized until maybe like five years ago in some Country Bear Facebook or something.
Wow. Well, it's not said in the show.
Not said in the show. Yeah. Geez. Well, so you got to do you went on stage with them.
Yeah. On stage and and a little bit of backstage. Yeah. Well, then they weren't moving.
No, not moving. No. So how was it because you were a younger man at that point.
Was that creepy at all? I mean, I was 13.
So I was I was probably like at that age where I should be aging out of country, but I was just more into it than ever.
Right. Yeah. Yeah. So I'm also just interested in this event in general because this feels like this is they'll never do this again.
Yeah. And I don't think they ever really did it again after.
I mean, they had annual pestle their parties. Right. Right. Yeah.
No, no behind the scenes stuff. But you don't get to go to the bowels of a ride anymore.
Yeah. Man, that's cool. Yeah. That seems beyond like it's too cool.
Now they because now the vents are all just like here's a button.
They were a couple of years ago they were doing it where like if you got up at six a.m.
and paid us five hundred dollars, you could eat on the Jungle Cruise.
Is that right? I don't think outside on the bank of the it's not in our boat, but you could pay to do that.
And then there was a Honomanche one right where you could like pay them eight hundred dollars and eat.
Yeah, I think that was a club 33 one. OK. You could eat in the portrait hallway. Yeah.
Oh, OK. OK. Yeah. There's pictures of that one. Yeah. OK.
And Bob Gur was in the graveyard scene. I remember seeing pictures of that. OK.
He was just hanging out. Yeah. Just hanging out.
Lying in a grave. He sat up. Hello.
Gotcha. I've seen that ghost.
Wow. So that's always I did think about like as a kid, I was like,
I would love to sing on the stage with these animals, but they really couldn't make that come true.
I guess that would be logistically too hard.
You know, we didn't talk about yesterday was the opening special.
This might have come up when we talked about the opening special a couple of months ago.
But you get the whole show essentially in the 71 Disney World
opening special and Glenn Campbell gets to be on the stage. Right.
It's to actually perform with live your dream.
Oh, they finally rescued him from the swamp underneath the monorail beams.
He's wandering through the opening. Yeah.
He's just singing verse after verse of a song he's making up on the spot.
Wish I had a flair with me.
All I have is a camera man and a sound guy.
Do you guys know where we're going? Yeah.
On your own, Glenn.
Other songs, obviously, hey, like now, why is it that I like this one more?
Yeah, why? The other one.
We got California Bears.
We got a Beach Boys. I'm a big Beach Boys guy.
I did forget this, though, that I think I have let it like
there's a bunch of odd little Beach Boys Disneyland connections that pop up.
And there's still a picture of the Beach Boys in the Lincoln area.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Like great America.
Like I was there with my friend who was he said, like,
and you know, there's a picture of Edward James almost like, I don't know that.
Really? I like I didn't know that.
That's one of the more obscure corners in general.
Anyway, the Beach Boys are hanging out there and the Beach Boys
have got a song covered by an even better band.
The Sunbonnet.
The Sunbonnet Trio, another family got together, started harmonizing,
you know, just this family fun.
And then it blew up, took off.
And and a great backdrop behind the Sunbonnets as they sing California Bears.
It's all the bears relaxing on the beach. Yes. So good.
So the stuff on the screens is really under underrated,
but so good, like so funny. Yeah.
Like the on the road again stuff is all it feels like.
I feel like there's too much going on. You got to see it a couple of times.
Yeah. Yeah. Oh, the slides. Yeah. They repurpose the slides. Yeah. Right. Yes.
Well, I love how they made Wendell kind of this.
I don't want to say pathetic, but, you know, like the pathetic dad trope
they kind of gave to him in that and the Christmas show. Right. Yes. Yeah.
He's just kind of like a bumbling fool, but but so endearing.
So that's a great joke where an over it sounds like an overhead voice
is yelling at Wendell. No flash photography.
Like, sorry, that is really solid.
I remember that kind of tricking me as a kid.
Like, did something activate some robotic voice
that would play if you did something wrong in a ride?
And then when they say that means you, Wendell, like, oh, OK, it's part of the.
I think I think I bought it.
Well, and after he takes the picture, it shows the picture of the audience on this
on the slides and it's all bears.
So are we are we bears watching the show?
I think we're bears is the idea. Yeah.
There's like a premise to this that we didn't even know
that wasn't even established in the 70s.
Yeah. Similar to you put on the bug goggles and it's tough to be a bug.
Yeah. Or like Avatar or something.
Wow. It's pre dates Avatar and the transformation and the hookup.
That's where I got the idea from. It has to be.
It has to be for them. Yeah, not just the ride, but the films.
James Cameron got the entire universe from this one moment,
from this one bear photograph.
He predicts the design trend that like, yes, you are the star of the ride.
Like you are Spider-Man.
You are helping Spider-Man. You're not just an observer.
Verify yourself on this ride.
You verify yourself.
This is OK.
This is the only thing that could probably be misconstrued
as a bit of criticism for the ride.
And I so apologize for even getting close to that.
It feels a little too new sometimes when I watch the videos.
I like the feeling that the show is going to break down a little bit
or that the puppets are the excuse me, the robots look like they're going to.
The head's going to fall off.
There's something to that.
That is cool.
Do you disagree?
Agree with what I'm saying? The vacation one specifically?
I'm saying the vacation one.
Sometimes I see all the outfits look a little bit too modern for me, for my taste.
The outfits that were put in in 1986 are too modern for you.
A little bit too modern for me.
And I like seeing like the original version of the show on the video,
because I feel like the I keep saying puppets, the robots are like.
You're saying robots, the animatronics.
Yeah, but we say robots all the time.
You're going to hit him for that.
That wasn't that weird.
I'm just teasing because you're going in on yourself.
I'm just joining the fun.
It's a complaint on every episode.
Finally, it's been addressed.
My mom was upset.
You know, my mom was like, why do you keep calling them robots?
I go, because we say animatronics.
Whatever.
But yeah, I like there is something I like about the old one,
because I like imagining that it's been there for 100 years.
That's all I'll say.
That's the closest thing I can say to a criticism.
That said, as a compliment, this show really moves at a quick pace.
Like, yes, it's a nice clip.
It's a great show. I love the show.
Are you at all upset that we are maybe I will say I have definitely landed at
I like vacation hoedown better.
I definitely do.
That used to be a controversial statement.
I feel like with the generation before ours.
But yeah, I am firmly vacation is a better show.
And Christmas is also a very good show.
Crazy.
It's not crazy.
I'm not upset.
I like the original better because I just the older the older it gets,
especially the closer to Bob Wills and little Jimmy Dickens, you get.
I feel like I feel more of a connection to that, like what feels like another
world of like old timey country music, music recorded in a tin can.
Exactly.
And then like, yeah, Bob, oh, like as long as that's in the feels like it's
recorded like, yeah, 200 years ago.
Since you brought up criticism, Mark Davis, who was the designer of the show,
he did not like the vacation or Christmas.
His wife, Alice Davis, also an imaginary also Disney legend,
said, why do they have to change things?
Why can't they just leave it?
So, you know, Jason says that in therapy every week.
Well, yeah, what's everyone else's problem?
Six million people of the world are assholes.
And I'm just there just trying to do my thing.
I'm thinking I'm back for that robot remark.
Zing. Yeah, no, I assume I assume if I sat down with Mark, I would say,
don't these costumes look too new? This is new.
These modern music market.
You're like, yeah, you're right.
Got to go to the old school. This is crazy.
This is when why do things have to change?
This is the this is often where the I'm not we sometime.
We certainly have our things where we don't want them to change.
But I feel like overall, don't you feel like we land in like,
this is the opinion of the like backwards theme part?
I'm not against the show being I love the idea that there's multiple shows.
I'm just saying if I had, I'm just trying to feel out all my thoughts on it.
And that's just a thought I have about the newer shows.
But I like I wish there was a new show every month.
Yeah, I wish the Bears were singing Gangnam Style.
I want so, yeah, a couple of things.
And I say this every time anybody puts a mic in front of me, I say,
Pete Rennaday is still alive.
The voice of Henry Disney.
If you're going to do a new show, do it now.
He's like 95. Wow.
Get get a microphone over there. Do a new show.
Yes. And also, this is also from I think it was Jim Hill posted this rumor
years ago, probably like 10 years ago now.
He said one of the ideas being thrown around for a country bear modernization
was called a barricade idol.
What were the bears with modern songs and the audience would cheer
for which songs they liked or performers?
Oh, my God.
And, you know, who knows, that could have just been somebody's napkin pitch.
Yeah, probably never even got far.
But that's the only modernization of the show that I could find.
Oh, my God.
Baby, you're a firework.
Come on, let your colors grow.
That sounds great. I'm not sure.
That sounds awesome. I would love that.
I do know what I think we like that.
I think I would askew I don't want judges in the audience.
I don't want to big Al is Randy or whatever.
I'll maybe I do as I'm saying it, because I if they had done that
and then it's still locked in place and it's several generations
of American Idol judge ago, like they have not like, no, all I was so long ago.
But I think we maybe we want the modern songs in the jamboree setting.
Maybe that's the ultimate.
Yeah, like a country versions of of modern songs, even to sections in
in a show now where you would have like the younger bears in the show play
like a modern a couple of modern songs for the kids in the audience.
No, baby Oscar finally grows up.
There you go. Oh, he's like, well, he's in his max goof.
He's like he's 15 or so age. Yeah.
He looks he is wearing like a scout uniform and his teddy bear
has a little kerchief in the show. It's very cute.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I have the little plush of that.
Oh, wow.
They just released a plush where Oscar's little teddy actually squeaks too,
which I thought is such a nice. Wow.
That's a great touch. Yeah.
Mike, what you want is like you want to like a boy band going on.
You want you want Bear T.S.
Yeah, I mean, I do want that.
Seven member bear band.
I always forget what's the band that's the band that's
that Mickey special from a few years ago that Mickey breakdances.
I for my favorite clip on YouTube.
Other than other than seeing Mickey drum, it's my favorite thing.
Like Mickey in a suit does.
I love watching Mickey drum, especially in Tokyo at the big.
There's a lot of numbers in NCT 127.
Yeah. Mickey's 90th spectacular.
Mickey breakdances with that band. And I love that.
And you make Lindsey's mom watch it again this Thanksgiving.
No, we had too much Beatles to get through.
But I have made I have made her watch that.
I want the country bears maybe to just watch it again.
Country bears maybe to just recreate.
Can we just program all eight hours, feed the audio of get back into.
And it's just noodley like it's it's as slow as that documentary often is.
Yeah. Yeah.
Just watch the whole bear show with.
But also, can you dub though?
I kind of want the voices to.
Yeah. The acoustics ain't great at Twickenham.
The technology. Can't we go back to Apple?
The technology exists for them to do that right where it just transfers it.
I think some things we haven't said yet.
A lot of stage time for the five bear rugs.
Yes. Yeah. Yeah.
They get featured a little more.
I feel like they get swept under the rug a little bit on the other show,
even though they're in the back.
Did they all sing as opposed to in the previous?
Like, aren't they more instrumental in the first one?
And then they all get little moments and ghost writers in the sky.
Yeah. And and really the opening great outdoors also.
They get like a couple words here and there.
Yeah. Mm hmm.
I think the ghost writers in the sky is very charming and it helped
save that song for me, which has been tainted for a long time
by its inexplicable appearance in Blues Brothers 2000.
Has anyone ever seen that?
I haven't, actually.
Yeah, I somehow haven't.
I don't say inexplicable in the songs in there.
That makes plenty of sense, but it's just this like
long, jokeless.
And then like the sky opens up and there are literal ghost writers.
Yep, it just like how have I watched an awful thing?
How did why did a studio finance?
There was a Nintendo 64 game about Blues Brothers 2000.
I remember reading about a Nintendo power.
Yeah. Do you play as them?
Do you know anything about it?
I don't know anything about it.
Oh, my gosh.
In that level of graphic.
Oh, my God.
Well, we got to go.
Are they on the road?
We're doing in the New Year.
I mean, there's there's been there's a Blues Brothers episode for sure.
That's they performed in theme parks.
There's plenty to talk about.
Well, then we've we also discovered that there are like there are alternate
Blues Brothers touring.
Well, yeah, yeah.
So like they've licensed or whatever, or they have us like,
what would you even call them like?
Like sub Blues Brothers touring.
But then also you can still see Dan Aykroyd and Jim Belushi
touring as the Blues Brothers.
You have to make sure that to check the casino schedule
to see which version of it is, is just like two younger guys
like performing the old stuff or is it Danny and Jimmy?
Well, I saw for Ghostbusters Afterlife, the media tour.
For some reason, Dan Aykroyd just starts singing on so many of those interviews.
And then that's a nice show.
Suffice it to say those have gone around a text chain of ours.
Yeah, yeah.
So he still looks great.
He still got it.
Yeah, I always had it.
Loves a little spook.
This will get the kids into the sea.
Yeah, this movie for babies.
Let's put this old man
swinging his hips up there.
Cool. Screaming.
Very old man doing a gravelly Robert Johnson cover.
Well, Bill Murray tries to remain in the literal shadow.
He like, like, can I just be in the dark and move around?
Am I a supportive enough friend if I do that?
Speaking of things kids would be like,
I know young Jason would have been very excited to see Swing and Teddy
Barrett come out and sing it in the rain.
You know what?
This has been this has been sick of me since yesterday.
I feel like I'm watching performances because we discussed how do you say the name?
Sometimes I'm watching Henry and I'm like, he's kind of saying Swing and Teddy Barrett.
I think it depends on what you're do you have a ruling on this guy?
I mean, I don't have the twang.
I'm a I'm a California boy.
I got the surfer accent, right?
So, you know, you couldn't possibly.
Yeah, that's what I can't tell is if that because you only hear Henry say it
and there's the twang. Yeah.
Yeah, it's confusing to me.
And it's spelled A. It's spelled B-A-R-A.
Probably Barrett. I've Shazam.
No, I'm saying the opposite.
You know, I'm saying it's Barrett.
You're mumbling. It's probably what I think anyway.
No, no, I'm saying I'm I'm Shazam.
Kazam. I'm confused.
I'm convincing myself it's Barrett because she's a bear.
Yeah, it probably is Barrett.
Maybe. Yeah, I know, because it's after because it's because it's Theodore
Barrett, the the old actress. Right.
Which this is I don't know how this I don't know how you didn't bring that one up.
Yeah. How did a Barrett reference?
You had your shot. I know.
Well, one thing's for sure is that the vacation show really hammered home
how horny Henry is for Teddy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. You're right.
You're in a little more so.
And the first one's already a little. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Now I forget how does it go further?
What is the flirtation?
Oh, well, the Christmas one is come up and sign my cast.
And he says, soon as I find a ladder, I'll be there.
The first one, though, that's similar.
There's no ladder in the he says, like, I'll see if I'll get a ladder.
I'll be right up.
He says that in the first one.
And then he makes the noise.
I think I said yesterday he was like,
like, there's some really, really intense noise he makes.
Yeah. Like some grunting, lustful noise.
Peter Rennaday dug deep for that one. Yeah.
That came from the soul.
Yeah, we need to get him desired.
As you were saying, Disney needs to get a microphone in front of him
so he can do that again. Yeah.
We need to get a couple more of those on tape.
Can I say something about a voice actor?
The great Frank Welker. Yes.
In this show, he's Melvin in this and he's Randy the skunk
and Frank Walker.
I'm so obsessed with and impressed by.
He's been Fred and Scooby Doo since 1969.
He's Abu Raja and the Cave of Wonders in Aladdin.
He's the Mars Attacks aliens.
I didn't know that till recently.
Quack, quack.
One of the craziest sounds you ever heard in anything.
None of these things sound like each other.
I feel like I used to only know him as like if the Simpsons needed a monkey
or like he's the best animal guy. Yeah.
But his just rather voices and stuff are so great.
In theme park world,
Zerg in Buzz Lightyear, Mr.
Eggs in Kitchen Cabaret and Megatron in Transformers.
He's Megatron in everything but the movies.
So in the ride as well.
And just when you say putting microphones in front of these luminaries,
I've been plugging in a ton.
I apologize. But the new show Saturday Morning All Star Hits is out.
And we got to work with Frank Walker.
It was a zoom. We couldn't even see him.
I know he looked like but like this was like such a dream to get him.
Would he do it?
And it's not it's although he oh, he did do some animal stuff for us, too,
which ruled. I forgot about that.
Anyway, if you check out the show is up on Netflix, check out episode six.
He plays a character named Ronnie Selfish.
It was a huge deal to get to have him to be a villain and do crazy laughs
and then like bring some of the Megatron.
We're all nerding out a ton.
So I was earnestly thrilled about that.
And you didn't have a chance to ask him about any of the bears.
No, no, no.
I don't think I knew the.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And say it's tough on a zoom.
But I hadn't done my country bear Jamber Week research yet.
I scarcely knew he was Randy or that Randy's name was Randy. Right.
Now we know we know so much.
That's very cool.
Can I bring up a slide that I like?
This slide that shows the Statue of Liberty is a bear.
Oh, yeah. Good stuff.
Yeah. Really good.
Does it imply I mean, we don't have to get too bogged down in this,
but does it imply that it's a bear, a complete bear world?
Like we were saying in the picture.
So like when we enter there, we all become sort of bears and we are.
It's like a window into their universe.
Yeah. Exclusively bear.
But it actually history played out in a similar way.
Obviously, like Bear France gave us that statue.
The French bears gifted it to us.
I have to imagine that history played out in a similar way. Yeah.
Yeah. And it greets bear immigrants coming from the bears from other nations.
Yeah. They seek to be everything of a bear.
A bear. Yes.
So, you know, so yeah, it would seem to imply an alternate timeline
that I'm interested in. Yeah.
Yeah. I want to go there.
Yeah. I also want to just let's stick with the history
and convert all the presidents, the controversies that will always be from now on.
Just make them all bears. What a great idea.
That's right. And you have to think of puns for every.
Yeah. That's true.
Sounds like we could do that, though.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Have to stare at him for a while.
But, you know, of course, when in doubt, it's just Joe Joe Baird and.
And yeah, yeah.
For, you know, well, he's already Teddy.
So he's oh, yeah.
But because it'd be Franklin Roars of Elts if you needed to do.
Yeah. What do you say?
I think of something different.
Take the Teddy away because that's that's too obvious.
You're right. It's already.
Yeah. And you know, when they say Theodore, so it's they use the proper name.
Yeah. That shows they wouldn't even let you get away.
All right. Theodore Roars of Elts. Yeah.
All right. So that's an overlay.
Mark Davis be damned.
That's an overlay.
We're demanding.
What is doodles of the Hall of Presidents were much more whimsical.
They were all it was like
Millard Fillmore was like like putting out a fire with his butt.
Fun little hijinks. Yeah.
More presidents butts were on fire in the Mark Davis version of Hall of Presidents.
Martin Van Buren is trying to like steal a picnic basket.
What other shit?
I mean, those are the songs I noted.
I singing in the rain is a lot of fun.
Yeah, that's a good outfit.
I like that you're right. It's very modern.
It's bright that the like slicker that it's a great outfit.
Again, I don't think outfits are really good.
I'm just saying for my personal taste.
Yes, it is. It feels like a more modern outfit.
I like after there's is it is it like does this
the rainstorm kind of build to a torn and then it goes dark?
And that's maybe when Ghost Riders in the sky happens.
There's just a sequence in it where then it gets very dark
and there's that like night cricket chirping atmosphere
for a little bit that I think that's just a tone that Disney does so well,
that I'm so nostalgic for.
The it's I feel like American Adventure is stuff like that.
And the, you know, the beginning of the Blue Bayou and Pirates.
I just I like my Disney cricket chirps.
They're always great.
We hear Oscar speak for the first time in that in that part,
because they say Oscar, you want to hear a story, a scary story.
Yeah, it's like that's all we need.
Uh huh. Is that all he says in any of them?
Do you think? I think so. Wow.
Huh. One line wonder.
We don't know whose voice is probably not sure.
Probably not documented very well. Yeah. Yeah.
Just like so much about this this version of the show,
it there's nothing out there. Yeah.
I've asked imagineers over the years,
like, do you know anything?
Do you know anyone who worked on this? No, nothing.
Like nobody knows anything about it.
It was just a just a quiet little project.
That's so interesting. Yeah.
You would think. Yeah, I guess.
When when was there a shift even in just like somebody's going to be interested
in rides and the history of it?
Obviously, like there's a lot of stuff from Haunted Mansion Pirates,
but it does feel like that's a switch just in culture in general.
Like we should document everything.
And even back whenever this when these two were made, it's like,
no one's going to ask us about this ever again.
Yeah, I'm curious about what the first thing was also
that kind of got the ball rolling that made Disney realize
people were interested in that sort of thing.
Yeah, I don't know. That's a good question.
I'm going to say I yeah.
I mean, it all feels like mid 90s seems like when all right,
like Comic Cons are getting bigger and yeah, like Star Wars isn't going anywhere.
People are only going to be more interested in this and it's not niche.
It's not just what nerds are into. Yeah.
Yeah. It seems like like from that point, like, yeah, nobody's outgrowing.
All the things are obsessed with that they grew up.
So start start having some stories and keeping track of some stuff.
Oh, I was going to say for the public.
Yeah, I think that that timeline sounds about right.
But I mean, the Disney archives, I mean, that was kind of
they had been saving a lot, although you always hear the stories about that guy.
Is it Dave Smith? Yeah.
Like they were going to just get rid of a bunch of stuff.
And he like saved it from the incinerator.
I mean, his story sounds like quite a story.
And like maybe it'd be interesting to see a movie
where you get to see what a young Dave Smith was like.
I don't know if you know where I'm going with this, Jason,
but there's there was some discussion on our socials
of who looks like a young Dave Smith.
Oh, don't. Oh, man.
The dream. Oh, I'll do it.
Have you seen it like I did? Oh, man.
People at fan you're being you've been fan casted as Disney archivist Dave Smith.
I'll take it. You know, I lost out on Jughead.
I lost out on, I don't know, Pugsley.
There's probably been some Addams Family.
We put a shot at Pugsley.
Like Pugley is an adult Pugsley show coming soon.
I how they I guess they're animated that.
We said, yeah, sure.
And yeah, but yeah, no, I'll do it.
I'll do I'll do.
Yeah, happy, happy to do it.
Look at the photos. It is pretty good.
Yeah, I see it. I'll take it.
I saw there was there was like an hour special in the archives
recently went up on Disney. Yeah, yeah.
I feel like he wasn't his hair wasn't so unkempt, though.
So you might have to trim.
I'll hit up Floyd soon enough.
Give me the Dave Smith, you'll say.
You know, in the photo for the barber.
I got to walk. I got to walk along Alameda.
I got to walk in front of this lot of punch.
You know, we haven't talked about Rufus, the disembodied voice
Rufus that is stomping around and that has to solve problems in the show.
I forget if I said yesterday that that how that feels like one of the more
Muppet show ish elements, just like stuff's going wrong.
And now this huge character's got to go take care of a tech problem.
Rufus is this whole I'm no expert on this
like backstage manager there kind of thing.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, totally.
But isn't this a character who even predated?
I guess no. All right.
Disney bear country only ever existed for the country bear jamboree.
But when you walked into bear country, there were big growls.
And that was this character Rufus, a bear that you didn't see.
Yeah, it was. He wasn't in the show yet.
It was a cave and you could hear a bear snoring.
That's what it snoring. OK, OK.
Which you can still hear on on Splash Mountain that you go by
rare bears, little hut thing and snoring bear.
And that's the same snoring sound.
Oh, I didn't know that. OK, OK. That's cool.
That's an interesting like mythology jumping like was just in the land
ambiently and then ended up in country bear and now is in.
Yeah. Characters don't jump.
You are attractions that you're giving us so many things to annoy people
that will be there with soon.
Oh, yeah. Oh, did you know this is the bear song from what?
Well, OK, yeah.
I don't know if any of you remember the show at all, but that it was a really
convincing sound when when Rufus would roar and moan and complain
because it was it was behind you up in the balcony.
And so it would be like hit the lights, Rufus, and you would hear like stomp,
stomp, stomp from one side of the theater to the other behind you.
Really convincing. And I remember as a little kid,
I would always like look up and behind.
Oh, yeah. You thought you were going to see some.
Yeah. Yeah. It was so convincing.
Like really shook. Yeah. That's so cool.
On good context, because some of these things get lost when you just watch a video.
Yeah. Yeah. Effective, it was in person.
What did anything else you haven't called out?
Like just favorite moments or little things characters do.
Oh, wait. Big one.
Two different worlds.
Yeah. You know what I'll say about two different worlds.
So so that's the shaker Terrence.
He's singing to an octopus.
And we saw that in Japan.
And that's the one that I'm going to make sure I should probably make sure.
But I think it's that's when in Japanese.
Yeah. And the difference is and it's kind of the same with the Christmas show, too.
The octopus has an articulated mouth and sings along with the song.
And right. His version.
Only in Japan. Yeah.
That was it was not that way. Wow. Yeah.
And this one, it was just that sound, which is such a great sound.
That was like, like that kind of thing.
And I'm sure somebody was going to bring this up.
But Dolores, the octopus is in the queue for Mission Breakout.
Oh, yeah. Yes. Yes. Yes.
Crazy. Honestly, I forgot it, but I didn't know that.
I swear to you, I would have passed the light.
I knew that I just was forgot.
And I was going to say, what's the name of the octopus?
Yeah. I was going to say, though, that like even not even know.
I mean, you could tell what the song was about in the Japan version,
but it's so funny and so funny in Japanese, too.
We were just like just the characters and yeah, what's going on?
But yeah, he's you're like, oh, these this octopus and bear are in love.
And as the curtain is closing and the lights going out,
you just hear him say, I thought you were going to help me sing.
So good.
Wow. It's a pretty perfect like, you know, that's like an opening.
Those curtains open and you see that tableau and he sings that line and like,
all right, I know everything I need to know about this.
Yeah. Now I can just sit back and enjoy it.
It's just a perfect like it's all contained in that first line.
And yeah, you most I guess almost all the numbers just because the bears look
funny and it's the music's fun and like they all play probably
really well in any language.
Yeah. You still go, oh, that's funny.
I don't know what they're saying, but less melancholy this show,
except for Jesse. Yeah. Yeah.
That's you know, that achy breaky heart is so funny.
I will try to isolate a clip of that.
Because that's in Japanese.
Like, well, the first half is in Japanese, the second half is in English.
Oh, OK. Vice versa. OK, OK.
Just a funny song to hear any of in Japanese and what a and so it's still that
like in 2021.
Long past Billy Ray's relevant.
I love that though.
One thing I wanted to bring up that I love about the vacation show is that
each bears little section of the stage got dressed
in rather than just being a normal curtain backdrop like shaker
and the octopus are on a little dock by some water.
And Ernest is out with a little campfire and his violin
has a hot dog on the end of it.
And I just love that everybody gets their own background
and it looks really nice and really dynamic.
Yeah, absolutely. Yeah, that's a great detail to point out.
And I it's it just like it's really nice that what these overlays
are spoiled down to is just like playing dress up.
And when they install these, that just a crew gets to come in
and put a scarf on this one and a shirt on this one.
And there's something very like charming and lo fi about it.
Yeah, Gomer's piano has a clam on it. A big clam. Yeah.
Yes. Yeah.
Oh, and he's in like one of those kind of frayed straw hats.
Like it's all the all the pieces are flying all over, I think.
Can I just bring up one?
This is going to be so in the weeds.
Just just so nerdy.
Yes, he is in the American version of the vacation hoedown.
I think it's bunny, you know, their bunny bubbles
and be like in their swimsuits.
Bunny is wearing sunglasses in the American version.
The sunglasses are over her eyes in the Japanese version.
They are above her head.
I have a lot of Japanese followers that I've accumulated over the years.
So I put the question out to them on Twitter one time
and I got a lot of responses.
And somebody said they think it's because in Japan
they associate people who wear sunglasses with the Yakuza.
Oh, wow.
And so in the show, they wanted her to have the sunglasses up.
But then I responded back and I sent a screen cap and I said,
Gomer wears his sunglasses in the Japanese version and the American.
Oh, interesting.
What does Gomer get up to at night?
You don't know.
So he's the he's the quietest one.
Yeah. What's he staying quiet about?
Was it literally like they were like, well, these are these people are too young
to be in the Yakuza, but Gomer, yeah, maybe.
Yeah, he could be. So it's all right.
Like it would it honestly, it was really more of an issue of like
it made it unbelievable.
It wasn't an issue of they were worried about the bears being affiliated
with the Yakuza.
How many bears has Gomer killed?
That's the big question you come out of the show in bear Japan.
I mean, he's got those fast hands to play the piano.
He's probably stabs and shoots pretty well.
And it's also true.
Parts also piano wire.
Yeah. Oh, he's got plenty of it.
Perfect. String that back up.
Wipe your hands of it.
And the police, yeah, they go, oh, why you have all this piano wire here?
And he's like, well, I'm a piano player.
Makes sense to me. Yeah.
Be on your way, sir.
Wow. That's crazy.
That's so funny.
Wow. Wow.
Well, what else?
Anything if we were interested in here, but the
in terms of the show in Japan,
you know, we mentioned like, oh, it'd be interesting to ask Imagineers
about making this.
I would be so curious to hear
the Imagineers who worked on the Tokyo version of like,
how did you decide what songs to swap out?
Is it just these songs are more popular in Japan?
And also, how did you decide?
Because there are chunks of it in English and chunks in Japanese.
All the banters in Japanese.
But some of the verses on the songs are in English.
Yeah. And of the three shows, it's the most changed from the English version.
Yeah. Like it has a whole new ending number.
I forget the name of the singer.
It's an American song called Vacation, V-A-C-A-T-I-O-N.
Like that's the chorus.
Oh, V-A-C-A-T-I-O-N.
Oh, they sing that really?
They sing that in...
Connie Francis?
Yeah, they sing that in Japanese.
Perfect mic question.
Yeah.
Connie Francis?
They sing that in Japanese in the Japanese show.
Oh, OK.
But that's the closing one.
And then the walkout music does like an instrumental of that
instead of the Thank God I'm a Country Bear.
Huh.
This is pretty...
So even so, like within your overlay,
you've like it's already different for all the overlay reasons.
And then Japan is all other set of overlay differences.
This is really...
This is why there should have been camera crews
when they were putting this all together, like in the get back sessions.
Mm hmm.
And now we would watch eight hours.
I mean, we would.
All of us would watch eight hours of like just sitting going like,
which song is it going to be?
Which song should it end with?
Gotta do the Connie Francis number.
Japan loves Connie Francis.
It's a well known fact.
I... well, I...
I'm trying to think like closing thoughts here.
I mean, I do like this thesis that this is maybe the strongest one.
I think it's that there's so much that's funny about it.
I see why you're passionate about this one specifically for sure.
I mean, but you can make an argument for The Christmas Show too.
Also, a lot of the same things can be said.
It's sharp, witty, funny.
Yeah, yeah. Quick.
Anything you want to call our attention to specifically,
I have not done my deep dive on it yet.
Do you have a favorite moment of the Christmas?
Oh, Wendell shooting out the lights and you hear...
This is another thing lost to watching on YouTube.
You hear the bullet bounce around the show.
Ah, OK.
Because Henry calls it out, watch out for that old squirrel gun, Wendell.
Then it goes, and it shoots out the lights.
You hear the lights going out.
And then it's dark and he's just like, sorry.
So he has another one of those moments like the no flash photography thing.
Where you say, sorry.
Yeah, yeah. Oh, that becomes just a great little more of a little character game.
Yeah. Do you have more?
Yeah. Is there like really like, do you have more bearer
fandom even like that we might not know, like digging deep in your fandom of country bears?
Do you know like you're on Facebook groups or something?
Do you know of like, what is the fandom like in general?
Because I actually am not on these groups yet.
Yeah. When I did have Facebook, I was in a Facebook group.
Like one of the members on there has like one of Henry's hats.
And another guy has the banner from when the show premiered.
And it was like, go watch the country bears.
He has that. And but that, like I said, that's where the Randy Sammy thing came from.
But really, there there's not like a website or anything where all the
country bear. Yeah. Yeah.
Just a lot of people on Twitter, you know, will tweet about it.
But yeah, I don't I can't think of any central hub.
OK, I'll investigate. Yeah. Yeah.
And I think not to get off on a whole tangent,
but just quick thoughts being that you're you love the mythology and all the shows.
Any any thoughts on the feature film?
Oh, I can't stand it.
Thank you. I think it's so bad.
OK. Like almost nightmarish.
Well, I can see.
Custom wise. Yes. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. But hey, they tried. Yeah.
Uh huh. People put effort. The hairs were laid on suits.
Yeah. A complicated puppet mechanisms.
So people lost sleep.
Scott, one thing we we neglected to talk about one of the big Al.
Oh, yeah. Right. Big Al song.
Uh huh. And now no longer like you're you're not just doing the text
writer cover, getting our own like new big Al stuff.
Yeah. Do we?
This is what maybe this is one where the other one I would not
because blood on the saddle is so funny.
But what? Yeah. What do you guys think of the big on my way to your heart in
America and then in Japan?
It's I've been working on the railroad. Yeah. Oh, OK.
These are fun. But it's yeah.
I do like the dogs howling in the in his song in the American version.
I think that's funny and kind of spooky.
And he's got the little teddy bear on his backpack.
I think like aesthetically, he he looks better and funnier.
But yeah, I mean, blood.
You can't beat blood. Yeah. Yeah. That's the yeah, for sure.
It's so funny that we we keep going.
We think of this.
Have anybody been like, no, I don't like this bear singing this song.
You know, like a bear singing.
What what what bear singing what song will we go?
No bad.
I guess 90 minutes of it.
Particularly like bear singing.
OK, fair enough.
I see. I see. This show in the previous yesterday show.
OK, OK. I guess I get what you're saying.
Maybe export these bears.
The bears bear.
No. Yeah, you know, the bear, they could sing the phone book.
That's right. You upset.
And they should bring them back.
Let's get them programmable to do whatever we want.
Any whims. But maybe we just make them do this show because it's so charming.
Yeah. Sorry. Real quick.
One thing I wanted to bring up,
there are still remnants of Country Bear Jamboree in Disneyland,
even though the show is long gone.
Yeah. Yeah. Just over 20 years, which is.
And they just added one recently.
When when you get off Splash Mountain, there is a sign that's like
Sammy's recycling corner.
And it's talking about recycling because it's it's the ride sponsored by Ziploc.
Right. Oh, yeah.
So they you get off the ride.
And it's like a painting of Sammy standing there going like recycle everyone.
Wow. And it's new.
Yeah. Like new within the last couple of years.
Wow. Yeah. Well, that's so there.
So there are obviously fans keeping it alive in imaginary.
Yeah. And I want to know who presents yourself.
I just I have so many questions.
Yeah. Make yourself.
Well, yeah, if you're listening or if somebody knows who did it, email us.
Yeah. Yeah.
No. And please, I correspond with them and then come tell us
how it went down, because your correspondences are fantastic.
Your deep facts are fantastic.
Thank you for sharing it all with us.
I saw you survived podcast the ride.
So happy you could do this. Thank you.
Yeah. What a blast.
Let's exit through the gift shop.
Is there anything you'd like to plug?
Touring plans dot com and touring plans on all social media platforms
and my own personal Twitter at guys, Selga, G, U, Y, S, E, L, G, A.
Right on. And you can go there and look at those plates.
Look at those curry bowls and spoons.
I tweet about a lot of dumb stuff.
Sure. That's good.
That's better. Not like our Twitter.
No, that's so different.
It's for work. Yeah, we're working.
Hey, so as for us,
the Country Bear Jamboree Week artist, courtesy of Tona Grasso,
you can find more of Tona's work in the show notes.
The Country Bear Jamboree Week, courtesy of our own Mike Carlson.
Thank you, Mike.
You can find us on the socials at podcast the ride
and keep up with everything going on this week.
Merch is available in our T public store.
And tomorrow, I believe the main feed goes into hibernation.
But the Hootenanny continues over on the second gate,
which is at Patreon.com slash podcast the ride.
So come see where our Country Bear oriented twists and turns
take us down there behind that their paywall.
Remember, change your pledge five to ten thousand.
Or if just a bunch of you change it to, say, a hundred and you all band together.
I want one good benefit.
We want a lot of weight of it.
Yeah, a lot of work.
What if they all do it?
You can donate your plasma, too.
And that's just not just you guys, the listeners, too.
That's right. Yeah.
Give us your plasma.
We say here at podcast the ride.
Thank you for that.
That's right. Yeah.
Tagline. All right. Bye bye.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson,
Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify
or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.