Forever.
Dog.
Yeah, well, here's another one today.
It's a gosh darn team up with Zach Reno and Jess McKenna on the Off Book Podcast crew to
do an improvised Country Bear Jamboree.
We're doing a real show, not just talking about one.
We are Country Bear Jamboree Week Day 5 Podcast The Ride.
Hey guys.
Hey.
Hey, isn't it so nice that Podcast The Ride and Off Book are getting together to see-
It's like we don't hang out enough.
We don't hang out.
We're so busy working, doing podcasts and we don't, we never like, it's so nice to get
to like go out and see a show.
We like have a share a culture between us events and talk about them and not necessarily for
content.
Well, when Mike came to me and was like, do you and Jess, we got, we have five tickets
to go see a Country Bear Jamboree.
And I said, do you mean the Country Bear Jamboree?
And he said, no, a Country Bear Jamboree.
Very hard to get into the, the one.
But there are Country Bear Jamborees happening all over.
You just got to know where to go.
And some of them are great.
The Indy circuit.
I was going to say, I don't know too much about them.
It's there.
They're so I'm excited to see this, but yeah,
overall the bears are safe.
That's what I can tell you.
I don't, you don't, you never know, but you don't really have to be worried about danger.
Oh, okay.
You don't mean like, like real bears or like bears being scary or-
It's definitely not just a room where there's a bunch of loose bears running around.
There's there's kind of a control to it.
And the idea is that they're actually, they're trained and they do music and sing songs about
their life.
I didn't even know there was a theater in this part of the Angeles national forest.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's what the it's see if you're like a city dweller, you know, it's if you're trying
to just stay around the Orpheum or the ACE theater or whatever, you're probably not going
to get a Country Bear Jamboree.
But if you hike, yeah, you'll find it all over.
Can I say thank you for dropping a pin because otherwise I think I would have gotten lost.
And Jessica McKenna and I would not have been able to make it out here to the woods.
Thank you, Zach Reno.
Oh, yeah.
Well, it's no problem.
I actually learned how to get here because Van Morrison played here last week.
Oh, secret shows.
Okay.
Yeah, one of the secret shows.
He's doing the whole album.
When he's topical material.
Yeah.
All his anti-mass stuff.
He's trying to stay off the grid.
So what you can do more easily in a cabin in the woods.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So he's playing to mostly an audience of woodland creatures.
But that's probably good for him just to keep workshopping.
Yeah.
So he's not going to be a witch really, except for the birds.
Except for the birds.
Well, shall we, Mike Carlson?
Yeah, let's go in here.
Let's go get him.
Head on into the theater as well.
Yeah, sure.
Oh, gosh.
This stump is so cozy.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, wait.
We each have it.
There's like a number carved in it.
Yeah.
Did you want to be in four or do you like the aisle?
I like to sit in the stump.
My tickets.
I'm weird.
No, I get that.
We'll scoot down.
Sorry.
No, no.
You can sit between Jessica and I.
Sorry.
No, it's fine.
I don't care.
No.
It's a thing.
No, I get it.
I get it.
Do you guys want any like concessions before we start?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
What do they have?
Oh, grubs.
Yeah, there's grubs mostly.
Popcorn.
Not popcorn.
Yeah.
I'll take a grubs, I think.
Popcorns are too risky.
Like what is it?
What is it actually?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Grubs, at least you know what you're getting.
There's a peppermint bark as well.
Oh.
I wonder if that's what we think it is.
Do you think it's what we think it is or do you think it's probably actual bark?
Actual bark, yeah.
I wouldn't mind that.
They just, some peppermint got stuck to it.
Yeah.
But they don't really blend the best.
Yeah, it's not blended.
Oh, I think it's starting.
Oh, yeah.
Boys.
Wow.
Country bird camp, baby.
How did they get the lights to dim?
Have you found your way into your stump?
Are you all comfortable sitting out there?
Everybody fit?
Your seat ain't too big for your seat.
Or too small for your ego?
Are you all ready to hear some music?
I can't hear you.
Oh, sorry.
Yeah.
I love you, Bears.
Well get ready because what we're about to do has never been attempted before.
Do a show following Van Morrison on the schedule.
We've never done it.
Van Morrison was our opener, that's what I say.
That's what I like to say too.
He hit the road. This is our place in the woods and we're gonna tell you a little bit about what it's like to live here.
Yeah, maybe we should introduce ourselves.
My name's Rudy.
Oh hey Rudy. Oh it's just me, Cur-San-Thum-um-Su.
It's me, Oh Turnip.
Why I'm good old Gumfrey.
And I'm Juniper.
Have you ever seen a bear with another bear singing a song?
A song.
Only if you come out to these flungy woods.
Well, if you do, you might start to think that you could sing along.
Go ahead, try it.
Because we're a bear and we're with another bear singing a song.
Sounds so lovely.
We're a bear group that likes to be safe on stage.
Safe on stage.
You don't have to worry, we're not gonna attack you.
In an angry rage.
We're not gonna say weird stuff.
We're not gonna be offensive, is what I'm saying.
We're not gonna be political.
We're not up on current events.
Have you ever seen a bear with another bear singing a song?
Well how about five bears?
I suppose they have now.
Hey you're right.
You've seen a bear, one or two.
Singing a song, singing just for you.
Now you've seen five bears singing and a singing and a singing a song.
Singing a song.
If you're brave enough we won't attack you if you try to sing along.
I guess we're supposed to sing along.
Okay.
Have you ever seen a bear with another bear singing a song?
Yeah, I'm not mad.
It would be helpful if they put the words up on the screen.
We just heard this the first time.
Hey good job all you fun folks singing along.
That one's Ruby, what's the name?
You're with the bears and you're singing and you're singing a song.
Juniper's cute.
Yeah.
Yeah I like.
Is that Juniper with the jug?
Yeah, Juniper has a jug.
Yeah, Juniper's really cute but Juniper seems like he's falling asleep.
Now I do have to tell you all sometimes I go off and when I am awake you gotta keep your eye on me.
So be forewarned I have covered my legal basis and you signed away and it rots when you bought this ticket.
Whoa, does Juniper have a knife?
Wait, so what happens when he falls asleep?
Well he falls asleep and when he's awake you gotta keep his eye on him.
Okay, yeah, alright.
And we sang a song.
Yeah.
Oh yeah that was great.
Oh boy, it's just so nice to be back in the company of the bears who I love harmonizing the most with.
Oh you know it's just so special to be out here on a moonlit night looking at the faces of my family favorite bears.
Now all you youngins you may not remember this but Van Morrison was here somewhat recently.
That's right.
Yeah, I heard about it.
Boy your memory's going. We talked about this nearly a few minutes ago.
You don't remember when you came in the place, did you?
Don't mind old turnip.
Old turnip, old turnip. We already spoke about Van Morrison and how he was our opening act.
Where did I put my hat? Do I have it?
Oh no.
Oh it's right here on my head.
Old turnip, that's why we keep 25 hats on the ground. See you always got one even if you forget.
These old hats change so much these days.
Oh old turnip.
Well now we've got more hats than I ever seen. Some are blue, some are green, some are wide, some are thin.
Pick a hat and put your hat right in. If you want another hat you want more.
We've got 25 hats right here on the floor. Some are big, some are small, but they're all hats after all.
Now this one's got a feather and I gotta say it looks pretty nice.
But you gotta be careful about every hat cause everyone is covered in lice.
Every hat, oh when you pick a hat oh you might want to switch.
But it doesn't matter which hat you put on your head because it's gonna give you an itch.
This one sure does.
This one's black and this one's white. This one's made out of a rug.
This one's straw and this one's grass. But all of them are covered in bugs.
We gotta stop storing our clothes in a closet full of bugs. That's what I know.
We gotta get those dang bugs out of here before our family can grow. We have to raise a family too.
We're trying to raise a family with all these hats.
Well thank you for reminding me. I was wondering what all these hats were doing out on the floor.
Oh we just told you. We did a dang song about it.
Now be careful when you put these on your head because some of them are covered in bugs.
Oh thanks old turnip.
You're welcome.
It's best to humor remain it.
Old turnip you should do those puzzles with numbers to keep your mind sharp.
The Sudoku?
The Sudoku, yeah.
Why won't you Sudoku?
Now if I remember correctly, y'all were working on a bit of a tune about a Sudoku.
Yeah, oh yeah we were doing that. I was having a problem though figuring out what it was and how it worked again as far as the Sudoku.
But I love the word Sudoku. I love the idea of it.
I just end up with a page with the numbers one through nine scrolled all over it.
Well I think that's a mighty good step Juniper since that's basically the nature of the game.
It's a start. I've been trying to channel my bear-like urges into more productive activities.
I think that's grand Juniper.
Keeping your paws busy. That's what it's about.
That's right.
Because you're the one most likely of us to get a mauling.
That's what the knife is for but I'm trying to wean myself off of it.
Now I knew ever since you were little Juniper that you were dangerous if I didn't keep my eye on you.
Now with Chrysanthemum I ain't never had to worry about that.
No, no you don't have to watch old Chrysanthemum Sue unless you're watching her do a dance.
Now I'll take your eyes on the stage while Chrysanthemum Sue presents part of the Sugar Plum Ballet from the Nutcrackers.
That's right this is our holiday show y'all.
And hit and one two three one two three part of the ray and spin.
And arabesque in second position and you can do it too.
They want us to do it too?
I think they want us to do it too.
That can't be right.
I don't know if I can ballet.
It's ballet that can't be right.
I don't know if he's moo I have not a dent on the top.
Everybody get up and do the dance.
Okay that's fine.
Ever look in on your feet and dance.
Oh he's brandishing his move.
And part of the ray and part of the ray and aeroette and spin.
That's not right.
Arabesque in second position don't make us start it again.
You call that an arabesque?
Where is your turnout we don't want to eat you please try to move from your hips.
They're all getting mad.
That is better and that looks better and give it a cute little dip.
Alright they ain't doing it send security out into the audience to make them do it.
The security bears are much more frightening than the second one.
Security bears are always mad so it's not just me for once and that puts my mind at ease.
Oh my gosh these bears are I mean okay just everyone.
We're far from the worst people here as long as we try we're going to be fine.
And part of the ray and part of the ray and aeroette and spin.
Security bears will eat you alive if you do not come in.
Rough up the one and see three.
Bring them up here bring them up here bring one of them up here on stage.
Make an example of them.
Why me?
Okay just tell me how to do the moves or just grab me gently and I will try to do them.
Alright here you go.
Ouch that's not gentle.
Part of the ray and part of the ray and aeroette and spin.
They're more delicate than your bears.
I could simply crush your body and tear off all of your limbs.
No please don't.
But I won't if you try just give it your all.
Part of the ray now part of the ray will eat you if you fall.
Don't fall Scott.
Don't fall.
But I'm up on only one toe I've never done this.
You've got it.
Oh they're not much for yoga.
Oh my god his joints his joints are manipulated.
Part of the ray and part of the ray and aeroette and spin.
This isn't so bad now that I'm trying it.
Bear ballet is kind of fun.
I'm glad that I've tried but please let me go.
Juniper is that a gun?
It's okay.
Now this is for my protection but I'm just showing you it so you know I have it.
We're not going to get political but that's going to be for protection.
It's for protection.
Now keep up the moves or else we're going to be playing Mumbledy Pagle.
Don't worry about Juniper.
It's just the right for a bear to bear arms.
That's so funny.
Don't hurt me.
Let's give it up for our volunteer.
Now all you have to do is one final move.
Okay.
You're going to run and jump and I'm going to do the dirty dance and lift with you.
That's not the other way.
Do you trust me?
I guess I have no choice.
You trust me.
I trust you.
You're my god today.
Everyone clap.
Scott, Scott, Scott, Scott, Scott.
Here we go.
He has the time of his life.
Bear arm.
Okay.
You only dug your claws into my chest a little bit.
That was kind of invigorating.
You can return to your seat now.
Thank you for, let's give Scott a big hand and remind you that pause can't help but do a little Mumbling.
That's true.
Guys, okay.
You need to stay in line.
I can't say, I wasn't pretending.
I'm so jealous that I didn't get to get, but that was so cool.
It was really, it was like really playing along with how dangerous that was.
Scott, that bear lifted you into the air.
That was amazing.
That was great.
Grace, thy name is Scott.
If they hadn't have confiscated our phones at the door so that we could be in the moment, I totally would have had a great video.
Yeah, me too.
I'm kind of only focusing on the negative.
I guess actually I unlocked kind of a beautiful graceful side of myself.
You're bleeding a little bit, but I feel like it'll be fine.
I can't, I mean, like it seemed like you were playing along with the danger of it as well.
But did you like actually feel, I mean, I thought I could tell they were kidding.
I wasn't like actually scared.
No, I think some of these cuts and scars might be permanent.
I think I have these forever now, but hey, it's nice to have some souvenirs of a visit.
Scott, the security bear is offering you a bandage.
Okay.
Can I put it on myself, please?
No, they're putting it on Scott.
No, they're putting it on and they're mostly using claws.
No, you're making new cuts.
They're cutting him.
Oh, well.
It was a ginger ending.
You know what?
One more might as well.
Oh, you guys, I'm getting a little used to it.
I think I like a country bear.
Just real quick.
There's just for my own sort of identification.
That's Chrysanthemum Sue.
Old turnip.
There's Juniper.
Is that Rodney?
My name's Rudy.
I can hear you.
Yeah, we can all hear you.
The whole damn theater can hear you.
We'll be black.
Hi, y'all.
It's a small house.
It's an intimate affair.
What's that one's name?
Gunther?
Good old Gumfrey, I believe.
Gumfrey is his name, yeah.
That's right.
Know it and fear it.
Yeah.
If you got any other questions, I guess just ask them out loud.
You don't normally do a question and answer part of a country bear jamboree.
Yeah, but I don't know.
I guess we could.
Has anybody got any questions?
Yeah, me too.
I would need anyone to see my hat.
There's 25 hats on the ground.
Oh, well.
Don't turn up and remember they all got bugs.
Well, if it wasn't, if it don't have bugs on it, it's no hat of mine.
Yeah, I'd just like to take this opportunity to remind everyone that we have merchandise
in the lobby and if you want to go out and get it anytime you can.
Me?
Well, you can.
I don't know what's going on.
You could wear your own merchandise, but it's a delicate line.
Yeah.
Yeah, and plus the merchandise is just hats with bugs on it anyway.
So you already got a bunch.
You got 25.
That's a good point.
I don't like it.
But listen, good old Gumfrey's recently divorced, so I'm going to need some souvenir sales for
the Alamoni payments.
I remember your wedding.
It was a beautiful day.
Oh, it was wonderful to have all of you there, except for you, Juniper.
Sorry I didn't invite you.
We were going through a rough patch.
You know how it is.
Bro, you're the right call.
I have a question.
Why are, why, why'd you get a divorce?
Oh, geez.
Well, are you serious?
I don't know.
They said they were opening a Q and A.
Well, you know, if I'm reflecting on it, I guess I, I'd have to say that my, my, my
bare eyes started to stray.
I might've had a, might've been a party to some of this myself.
It's a sad, it's a sad story, but I guess I could try to tell it.
If people's, everybody's hearts are willing to break a bit.
Yeah, we'll make sure that we fill in any sort of details that you leave out.
Okay, sure.
Yeah, we remember all of it.
Oh, well, it was a, it was a few years ago.
I remember it well.
Well, I got married and she was the, the belle of the ball.
Oh, yeah.
And then it just started to seem like she wasn't true love at all.
My eyes started to stray and I decided to take a risk.
I realized I was more in love with all of my tics.
They lived on me and I started to find them appealing.
So when it comes to affairs, I started wheeling and dealing.
There's a little cabin in the woods and I arranged a romantic time.
I made love to all of my tics.
They gave me a disease they call Lyme.
He caught the love bug.
Oh, you know I did.
And it hurt.
Breaking his wife's little heart, he was supposed to be thinking of.
But he caught the love bug.
It happens to everyone.
He caught the love bug.
Oh, well, literally.
Oh, and he was falling in and out of love.
Yeah, well, I remember when he went to the woman and he said,
Hey, I got a, I got a thing I got to ask you.
Is it possible we become poly?
Can we be poly with bugs?
Yeah, that's right.
I said, would there be willingness to open things up?
And she kicked you out.
Is that what, is that what, and chased you around the riverbank.
Yeah.
That's pretty accurate.
She said she didn't want to be in a polycure with you and 300 tics.
And then she came back and said, how do you even make love to a bug?
You're a bear.
Yeah.
She had a lot of logistical questions.
She wanted to see a chart.
Yeah.
She made you draw it.
You got to have rules in those kinds of non-traditional relationships
or else they fall apart.
Even I know that.
Sure.
Well, I bet I decided to describe it a bit.
Lay down here, my love.
I'll show you how this works.
You let them crawl all around your genitals.
You'll see they're tender.
They ain't jerks.
I showed what tender lovers.
Those tics could be.
But she walked on out the door.
She said, you're on your own now, you see.
Oh, what a day.
He got the love bug.
Oh, why don't I know it?
Good day and a sad day, both.
His wife said, no, thank you.
Goodbye, please.
He got the love bug.
300 of them.
Kind of nice, though.
She said, I hope you enjoy life with these fleas.
Love bug.
But now I got 300 alimony.
Oh, no.
300 won if you counted wife number one.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh, life's been rough for good.
What a heartbreaking tale.
You know, I feel a little better getting it off my chest.
And my chest is pretty big.
I needed it off.
It was a good question.
I did not expect.
Yeah, it was an excellent question.
I'm relieved I wasn't eating, but I feel like it unpacked something.
You're speaking of good stories.
Hey, hey, Julip.
Yeah?
Juniper.
Juniper?
Well, they're friends.
You're not talking to Juniper.
Oh, are you talking to Julip, the fast talking possum?
That's right.
Julip on Juniper's head.
Oh, look at it.
No, he came in.
He's up on Juniper's head.
Oh, hi, everyone.
I just got here.
I was running a little late.
Sorry about that.
Hey, Julip.
Yeah?
Now, I was under the impression that you were out acquiring all sorts of nicks and nacks
and wares and tares.
Yeah, you know, I like to go antique and I like to go yard sailing.
I like to go estate sailing.
And I just hit them all up and I got so much old crap in my house.
Why don't you tell me all about your latest haul?
Well, you wake up Saturday morning, show up in a yard, ask to buy their crap and they say
we don't starve for three hours.
And I say, I'm here now.
I'm here now.
I'm here now, yeah.
You go to an estate sale, you ask who died.
They don't really want to talk about it.
They just want to sell that stuff.
You keep asking.
You say, I'm here now.
I'm here now.
And you're really bored of most of that crap anyway.
It was being crossed by like nine quads, you see.
What did you get?
Oh, what did I get?
Now, you see, eventually you go to these estate sales, you can talk them down.
You see, you can talk them down because you get so annoying they just want you to leave.
Okay?
Tell me about it.
So they were like, hey, I'm sorry, but that attache is 75 and I can't go a dollar lower.
That attache, it's dinged up, it's holed up.
That attache is garbage.
And I'm here now.
I got $2.00.
I'll take it off your hands.
Well, all right.
You made a five point.
You go to a church parking lot.
They're trying to sell some goods.
To better do more church, they wanna do more church.
What do you say?
I'm here now.
If you want to do church, we can church, want to church, and the church wants more church,
church wants more church, and the church wants more church, church wants more church,
I know what you're saying.
I'm here now.
I don't care when you open.
What I care about is I'm here now.
I'm here now.
And you're here now, Julep, and we're happy you are.
Julep, you've gotten that tachy for $2?
When it was originally listed at $75?
My, what a deal.
What a deal.
That's right.
Little did they know, I had gotten there many hours
before that and scuffed it up myself.
Oh, Julep.
Oh, you fast talking possum.
What a Swifter you are.
I admire you for it.
I'll tell you what.
Oh, thanks.
That's wonderful.
Yeah.
I just got to say that's a lovely ensemble.
And I've been trying to work on my look too,
and what I'm carrying.
I'm going to say, Rudy, you look mighty fine.
Oh, really?
You think so?
Oh, yeah.
Got like, you part in your hair different ways.
You got highlights and lowlights extensions.
Yeah.
I got a little, I got a dickie on, like an animal.
Yeah, I love that.
Yeah.
Why wear the whole turtleneck?
Just wear the top.
Yeah.
Now, this is a no pants zone.
Y'all may have been aware of that by looking at us.
We like to wear, when it comes to accessorizing,
look in the mirror and then take your pants off.
Oh, yeah.
That's right.
Now, do they mean us too?
Are we?
Because we've kept our pants on.
Take your pants off.
Oh.
Look in the mirror.
Why did I say it out loud?
Take your pants off.
Took them off as soon as I sat down, because I'm the only one.
Jason was going to ask.
I understood the code.
Some people take coats off.
I just, you know.
Yeah, you wear those.
Jason wears those heart boxers, though.
I'm not really worried about this.
I've got a, I don't want to brag,
but I have a lot of Mack Weldon.
Hey, actually, we did ask for Mack Weldon too, you guys.
I think I have a lot of Mack.
Like, we got, like, did they send you stuff?
Yeah, we got sent stuff.
Yeah, you got a code.
Yeah.
You got to redeem the code.
Sometimes you forget.
Oh, yeah, I know about that.
It happens to us too on our podcast.
That's a good point.
We should probably now take a moment for our sponsors.
Firefly Hooch.
Yeah.
When you got to get drunk off of the remains of fireflies
that have been put in a machine, and then they
have been fermented over the course of many weeks.
Read the copy.
What do you mean?
Just riff and read the copy.
Read the copy.
They said, they got must reads.
They highlighted it in yellow.
You got to talk about the natural probiotics
that this booze has in it.
Firefly Hooch.
You said you wanted to do it.
Read the copy.
But it says at the top, make it your own.
All right, let me get another shot at it, all right?
Well, I just want to say that Firefly Hooch,
you can put it in a cup.
And when you get the cup, you're going
to want to put it out on the table first.
And what I like to do is I get ham and eggs.
I get the cup on the table.
And I get a napkin.
And I tuck it into my shirt first.
You have to paint a picture for them.
Yeah, thank you so much.
Yeah.
At least somebody knows what I'm doing here.
You make it sound real natural, or else you're
going to have to do it again.
Yeah, we'll have to do it.
We'll have to do a make good.
We're going to have to do a make good.
Well, I don't want to make good.
But I want to put this in my own words.
All right, well, if you like Firefly Hooch
and you like to have a good time,
let me remind you what I like to do.
Go to the table, get a plate of ham and eggs, get a cup.
It's very important, because do not
pour the Firefly Hooch just on the table,
because it will not stay.
That's good.
That part is highlighted.
You have to read that part.
Yeah.
Make sure they know that you need a cup still.
Yeah, so just pour it there.
Pour it in a cup.
And then crack the paper.
And read the headlines.
Read the news.
Read what's going on and try not to get the blues.
Read the paper.
Read the news.
Read the obituaries and see who dies.
Who dies.
Spend your time reading the obituaries
and crying for people you don't know.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Try to see their names and think of all how they won't grow.
Think of their families.
Think of their friends.
Think of the cost of the funeral.
What are people going through?
Then take a sip of your Hooch.
Firefly Hooch.
Yes, right.
Read the people that died in the news.
Yeah, you've got to learn about all of them.
Firefly Hooch.
That's right.
That's good.
Read the people that died in the news.
And yes, so then what I do, I go on IMDB to find old celebrities.
Internet movie database.
People over 80 don't have long.
Don't have long.
How sad you'll be when all these people pass away.
Won't it be a bummer then you go back to your cup?
Firefly Hooch.
That's right.
Oh, I'm so sad.
Read the names of the people who died in the news.
Hell, yeah.
Firefly Hooch.
Oh, my goodness.
Won't it be sad when the rest of the Mary Town War Show cast us?
There's only a few of them.
There's only a few.
Few.
Promo code bears.
All right, well.
There's no way we're going to make good for that.
No way.
That was 90 seconds right on the down.
Right on the down.
Precisely, you're a pro.
Good enough time for a mid roll if this were fine.
Hey, y'all, I was thinking that since this is a very special
audience, then maybe we should tell them.
What do you think you're saying to them, I'm Sue?
Maybe we should tell them.
What are you thinking, Cassandra, I'm Sue?
I'm about to say it.
Maybe we should tell them.
Maybe we should tell them what, Cassandra, I'm Sue?
Oh, turnip.
Maybe we should tell them about all the special things we do
to get ready for hibernation.
Oh, it's quite a time of the year.
What should we tell them, Cassandra?
Oh, to shut down and just reflect.
All the things we do to get ready for hibernation.
Oh, yeah.
Well, yeah, we gather first.
We put things together.
We party so hard that we're ready to sleep it off.
That's right.
It's a big old bender, that's for sure,
because we know we party hard enough to sleep for three
months after the fact.
You don't want to wake up in the middle.
That's when it's coldest and darkest.
So you didn't make sure you get fucked up.
Yeah, I emptied this jug of the moonshot.
Oh, oh no, Juniper.
Oh, yes.
Yeah, you get the Firefly Hooch and you just drink
till you're fucking sick.
Can you give us a little bit of that jug, Juniper?
Oh, sure.
Yeah, I've been taking a master class from a guy named
Little Jimmy Dickens Jr. and he's been teaching me how to
jug. I've been doing a few master classes.
You got the subscription for all of them.
I got the two I'm learning about.
At the price point, it makes more sense to just get a
subscription to master class.
It does.
Hillary Clinton's teaching me about green.
Play the jug.
Milking.
Oh, wow.
Doesn't that sound so sweet?
Yeah.
Sounds real soulful like.
One thing's for sure, we can hear it real good.
There you go.
I've only watched the first one because I got obsessed with
Bill Gates's one on eating the mors.
Now first of all, Ms. Nomer, I initially thought that when
someone, and you told me this, Rodney, you were essentially
told that when someone is playing the jug, you would
think that the tone is made by blowing air across the top of
it perpendicularly.
Well, what I did, I was looking at YouTube and I learned that
jug playing is sort of, you got to make the noise with your
mouth.
It's more just humming into a jug.
You're thinking it's for the resonance?
OK.
All right.
Someone has watched more than the first master class of
jugs.
Humming into the jug, dude.
He bootlegged him, probably.
He stole him.
So you're not humming, you're just blowing.
Jason, this is great.
Jason, you could learn from this.
We've been trying to teach you how to do well at the jug
all this time.
No, I'm trying.
He seems sick up there.
You actually are better than him, maybe.
You're much better than this.
Yeah, there.
The clear jug on stage, you see it's full of germs now.
It looks really gross.
Yeah, it should probably be destroyed right now.
It's an old bong.
God, it's disgusting.
Yeah, it's like an old bong.
The bear looks lightheaded.
Oh, party's not a party.
Does someone pass us out from blowing on a jug too long?
About that, there's no doubt.
So we'll get tanked.
We'll drink all this Firefly hooch.
And then we'll sleep all night snoozily snoozily snooze.
Snoozily snooze.
I'd offer someone else the jug, but it's covered in my spittle
now, so I guess.
Yeah, the bear's got COVID too.
I guess I'm stuck with it.
Yeah, but didn't you guys hear Grant Van Morrison last week?
That doesn't exist.
It doesn't.
It's not real.
I'm just glad he's gone.
The forest has gotten significantly less cantankerous
somehow.
Somehow a forest of bears is less cantankerous
when Van Morrison leaves.
Oh, that's true.
I can't disagree with you there.
A forest is less cantankerous when Van Morrison leaves.
And you can put that on a stick pillow.
Yeah.
Yeah, there you go.
Oh, I'm hearing it a lot more now.
Yeah, this is perfect.
Oh, he's going to be sleeping for months, no problem.
You're going to miss the entire winter at this rate.
Oh, play that.
Oh.
Yeah!
Sounds so nice.
What a sweet sound.
He's like he's kissing the jug, isn't it?
Oh, he should throw that in there too.
Oh, a party, not a party until someone passes out.
From putting too much air across the jug
and last without a doubt.
So you hear that dulcet tone.
And you know that it's about time for the party
to keep partying on.
So you feel alive.
This guy is turning white.
He's looking such a fright.
I think he'll be asleep in no time.
What should this rhyme be?
It's like he's trying to navigate
the difficulty of blowing air out and also
humming at the same time.
His fur did turn white now.
He looks like a polar bear.
That's what polar bears are.
Polar bears are just brown bears that have been
playing the jug for too long.
Oh my gosh, I didn't know that.
Did you know that?
And then we exile him to the frozen north and south.
We send him out with just one Coca-Cola.
Hey, y'all, if you want a Coca-Cola, you can go get one
and get merch at the same time.
Van Morrison, you take one more step to my honey
and you getting the knife.
Oh, he's back.
Sorry, back.
He's all right.
He's fine.
Not quite polar yet.
But you know, we got to finish the show first.
We can't, you know, we're all going to turn polar
by the end eventually.
But not before we close this thing out strong.
Hey, y'all, why don't we go to the audience
and see what their favorite of our famous songs is?
Yeah, and make sure the pig rat.
If you don't pick right, we're going to eat you.
Oh, they are really looking at us, like really giving us
that eye.
Oh, the security guys.
Oh, they're back.
OK, the security guys.
OK, OK, well, what kind of I mean,
they probably like have to do with like a hoedown.
Well, Danny might be in there.
Like, yeah, but that's right.
I think one of my favorite songs of theirs
is called the tin can pool.
Tin can.
Tin can pool.
Is it like the game or the or like a swimming pool?
I think the swimming pool full of tin cans.
Oh, we like we like.
You know, they were all great.
We loved all of them.
But I think my favorite is wisely.
I think it's got to be tin tin can pool.
Jory.
We were made pausing to make sure you weren't pulling our chain.
You got us on Spotify, our number one track by a long shot of tin can pool.
Y'all are real fans.
That's for sure.
I love to hear that.
Yeah, thank you for being real ones.
This goes out to all you real ones out there on stump.
One for the real ones on stump.
Oh, yes, you all are sitting out there, the real ones on the stumps.
I know you might be thinking, oh, are you talking about a dump?
Is this just a landfill or is it a trash can?
Well, I say no.
Thank you.
You do not understand.
And sometimes all the tin cans, they get taken away.
And so we fill the swimming hole right up with razor blades.
And that's what we got to do sometimes, although it is less cool.
Won't you come and take a dip in this razor bladey pool?
Razor bladey pool.
It cuts deep, but it's cool.
Ouch.
The water ends up pretty hot.
You're going to need a tennis shot.
But sometimes, though it hurts to say, you show up at the swimming hole,
but there's no razor blade.
Oh, no.
What's there instead?
Well, you are in luck.
It's just the headless bodies of a bunch of undead ducks.
Undead ducks.
Necromantic arts of risen ducks.
I'm pretty scared of what's in this pool.
Turns out ducks can be zombies, too.
My baby bear, he tried to learn to swim.
He was having a big problem when ducks were biting him.
He wanted to learn, so I said, stay in there.
You don't get out now.
I paid for these lessons.
You take those bites, or I'm not getting my money back.
Tin can pool.
Yeah.
Oh, hey, everybody.
Thanks for coming to our celebration.
Now we're getting time for a hibernation.
Before I fall asleep, ain't anybody seen my hair, anyway?
It's full of bugs, anyhow.
Tin can pool.
Oh, hey, everybody.
Shake it out, junk man.
Turn one.
Mmm.
Juniper Dunn turned bowler.
Turn and bowler.
Oh, folks, I guess we're heading for the end of it.
Oh, starting to teeter a little bit here.
Oh, god, they're going to stumble off the stand.
Yeah, they might fall on us.
We might be stuck here for three months.
No, no, just get out.
Follow me, follow me, follow me.
OK.
Does anyone want to get their stubs signed?
What?
They're asleep.
Get out of here.
This is our chance right now.
OK.
Maybe ask the possum.
Does anyone see my pants?
My Mac Welpons.
Juniper's wearing your pants.
Jason, grab the jug.
Oh, OK.
Let's cover up with that.
He's asleep.
Let's go.
Is this a trade?
OK.
Yeah, don't.
It's glass, but it's a little foggy.
People won't be able to see you down there.
OK.
It's better than pants.
It's almost as good as pants.
I'm going to hide behind the jug.
OK, you'll be fine.
OK, so quietly.
Don't creak.
OK.
I liked it.
I liked that a lot.
I felt scared more often than I thought I would.
Yeah, they made a point of saying it to be you guys said the bears are safe.
Yeah, I guess that was an assumption I was making.
One of them straight up had two knives and a gun.
And you're still kind of bleeding.
I mean, those security bears gave you sweet kisses, but.
Oh, yeah.
I got a white shirt and it is the red is steadily spreading here.
I guess that's a pretty cool.
It was such a fun hang.
It was good fun.
Such a fun hang.
So nice when podcasts get together.
Yeah.
And I just feel like I'm glad that was just for us, you know?
Does everything have to be content?
Why does everything have to be content?
Why can't you just hang out with your friends and witness like a horror show?
Yeah.
I'll tell you what, I'm adding Tin Cam Pool to my Spotify playlist right now.
I think we all are.
Yeah.
When you go from tin cans to razor blades, I say short.
Then you go to undead ducks.
Well, now I'm a fan for life.
Wow.
Unexpected turns in those songs.
I don't know if it was just them being sleepy that made me sleepy or if it's the blood leaving my chest.
I might just like lay down here outside the cabin.
Scott, how is this white?
No, I think Scott's turning polar.
No, this is me.
No, I think he's bleeding.
I don't get tan.
No, no, he's turning polar.
Let's send it to the North Pole with a Coke.
Oh, just one Coca-Cola.
Yeah.
That sounds really nice.
Those bears in those commercials look so happy.
Good night, Scott.
I love you guys.
Guys, Van Morris is also coming through the woods.
Oh, God.
He's still selling cassettes?
La, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da.
I'm worried about...
I am worried too.
I'm more scared of him.
I don't want to be part of this interaction.
But you know what?
It was a marvelous night for a moon dance.
Remember when Scott danced with a bear?
Yeah.
You did the dirty dancing thing.
That was cute.
He's fine, right?
Yeah.
How do we get our phones out of the bear bag?
They put them...
Those are gone.
I think I saw Julep the possum take off with them.
Oh, because he can climb up to the high tree and get...
Yeah.
Okay.
Shoot.
Well, Apple backups.
I got burners if you need anything.
Oh, Van.
No, we're good.
We're actually good.
We're good.
Thank you.
We're actually good.
La, da, da, da, da, da, da.
He's walked into the woods.
I know that there wasn't a longer Q&A, but I wish I could ask the possum what he's going
to do with an attache.
Oh, I assume resell.
Good point.
Yeah, refurb it.
Yeah, flip it.
Flip that.
Take that thing down to Sunset Vintage.
Yeah, sure.
Do you guys want to keep hanging?
Do you want to maybe hit up Margaritaville?
Yeah, maybe let's record it this time.
Yeah, okay.
That's a good idea.
Yeah, I wouldn't want to hear...
If I was a fan of either of those shows, I wouldn't want to hear that.
I would want to hear us hanging at Margaritaville.
Yeah.
Yeah, I think that's right.
Margaritaville Forest, which is the one over here.
Yeah.
They don't require masks there.
La da da da.
Okay.
All right, man.
Hey, that was Scott Passarello.
Give it up, Scott Passarello is on the keys.
We got Brett Morris on guitar and banjo.
We also had Scott on bass.
We got Dana on percussion.
Dana Williams on bass.
We got Scott on bass.
You can also check off Book, The Improvised Musical Podcast.
Well, the same place that you can check out our friends and extremely recent collaborators,
Podcast The Ride.
Hey.
Thank you guys so much.
You survived Podcast The Ride from the Podcast the Ride side of things.
And I guess I did too non- firstly.
You survived Country Bear Jamboree.
We all survived Country Bear Jamboree together.
I was about to, usually we say,
what would you like to plug?
But you just did, so we're already, you know,
that's covered.
Why's everything got to be content, you know?
And this is confusing being in two podcasts at once.
How does it work?
Yeah, so if you're listening on the off-book side,
we're just completing a Country Bear week of content.
There's no, like, we don't do fun songs.
But we talk about, for hours,
the history of the Disney Country Bear.
Yeah, if you like fun songs,
don't listen to the rest of the week.
Because it was like three hours at a time
of talking about Country Bear Jamborees.
But if that does sound good to you,
yeah, check out podcasts to the right.
And you're listening right now,
if you're learning on our feed,
this is the final main feed of 2021.
And thank you.
You all survived 2021.
You all survived the Country Bear Jamboree week.
There's maybe one little treat coming for you
over on the Grizzly Gate.
But thanks for sticking with us through a crazy year.
And thanks, Zach and Justin, everybody,
for closing us out right here.
Our pleasure.
And if you're listening to this on the podcast,
the right side, that is basically what every episode
of our show is like.
A lot of bears.
Yeah.
It's all Country Bear Jamboree.
Thank you for inviting us into your Country Bear Jamboree week.
Yeah, yeah.
It's an esteemed place to be, I think.
Everyone stay busy out there in those woods.
And if you see Van Morrison coming, turn the other way.
Turn the other way.
Do not buy one of those burners.
Bye.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a Forever Dog Production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Bohm, Joe Silio, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit
ForeverDogPodcasts.com and subscribe to our shows
on Apple Podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news by following us
on Twitter and Instagram, at ForeverDogTeam,
and liking our page on Facebook.