Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to podcast, The Ride, The Second Gate,
where today we will be known as the guys on the rides.
My name is Mike Carlson.
Joining me as always, Jason Sheridan.
Oh, just reach out and exceed at your grasp.
Which is the phrase?
I don't know, it's something.
There's a phrase to describe what I just did.
I don't know if Scott Gardner knows what it is.
Clever, hilarious.
There, thank you, yeah, yeah, that's what it is.
Perfect.
That's what it is.
We're the guys on the rides,
which makes it harder to say.
I was trying to remember,
was there some dumb celebrity trend
where everybody was posting rhymes for themselves,
like what we're doing, Minch on a Bench,
which came after Elf on a Shelf.
Was there some Twitter annoying thing?
I just found something where Harry Connick Jr.,
who hosted a show once,
showed himself as the host on a post.
Is this, am I really getting an item for this?
This was a trend, yeah, this was.
I'm not really remembering any specifics,
but yeah, it was blank on a blank,
and there was some sort of rhyme or tangential connection.
If the show was called Guys, the Guys on the Rides,
and it was just what I say all the time,
is that we were just positive about every ride,
we would be millionaires.
We would be so rich if we didn't criticize anything.
We never made jokes, if we never goofed around.
And we didn't have a name that has confused people
who had to make signs for us and Tony Baxter.
And Tony Baxter was confused,
which is the one that breaks my heart the most, of course.
Yeah, I know, no.
He's all about clarity and purpose.
I don't know if we did, was that in an email somewhere?
No, what it was was we were down at Knott's.
The first time we went to Scary Farm,
Doug Barnes from Season Pass took us,
and he texted a picture of all of us to Tony Baxter.
Because he's been on their show, and he was on our show.
He's been on their show a lot.
So he texted a photo, because we had just done the interview,
like a month or two prior, and Tony said,
oh, it looks like The Ride Guys.
Or like the guys.
He was trying to give us the name you just gave.
He was way out of it.
Yeah.
We should have listened to him.
Pretty close.
So, the guys on The Rides.
He thought we were from a podcast called The Ride.
I think yes, he thought that podcast
was just describing what it was.
And we were called The Ride.
It's too late to junk it.
My favorite is when people cold email us.
I've heard other shows talk about this too,
like cold email.
Like, we'd love to add you to our new podcast app
and directory, The Ride.
Or we'd love to make NFTs out of clips of your show,
The Ride.
Like, oh, you seem like a big, big listener.
I would be interested in doing that.
So forward me that NFT email.
Oh, great.
But.
Sure, yeah.
We'll just start selling Amway and Lilo Roe.
Lilo Roe, whatever we call him.
We should sell candles and Tupperware,
and we should do everything.
So let's ask our guest here
what he thinks about our name change,
potential name change.
You know him from this podcast.
You know him from Doughboys.
That was the request last time is to only be credited.
He's the commissioner from the Doughboys.
I assume that that would remain.
Hey guys.
Hi, Evan Susser.
Evan Susser, hi.
Hi.
I like the name change.
Okay.
Have you considered,
I know sometimes you maybe would talk about
like a Ninja Turtle action figure or something like that.
So you guys could also be the goys on the toys.
Oh wow, that's good.
Yeah.
Bring it on tonight, today's episode.
That's what we're doing today pretty much.
Yeah.
We're talking about a toy.
I've considered toy podcasts for a long time now,
but that's maybe that's it.
That's the way to go.
Maybe that's the way to go.
So yeah, spin off podcasts with that.
Yeah, that's perfect.
Wow.
Well, thank you for being here
and coming back so quickly after your last appearance.
I, now here, I think we have to discuss
you being here in general because,
before this topic, because,
well, how do you recall this coming up?
You talking about the
the mention on the bench. The mention on the bench.
Yeah.
Well, I think that
I was once again in the bathroom of Sesame Place
and then, let's get a long bleep in there.
No, I think that I kind of vaguely remember
texting with Mike about Mensch on a Bench last year,
but you asked if I wanted to discuss Mensch on a Bench
and I didn't remember that at the time,
but then I am familiar with Mensch on a Bench.
I have a Mensch on a Bench.
Right.
Oh, great.
And in fact, I brought with me the Mensch on the Bench book.
The book. The story that comes with the toy.
I remember, like all good religious traditions,
first learning of Mensch on a Bench on Shark Tank.
Right.
All our great culture comes from.
For a Jewish tradition, maybe appropriate,
but I was curious about it
and it's not something I grew up with.
It's not anything that any adult has grown up with
because it's only about five years old.
But I'm basically looking for absolution
that we didn't make up you wanting to do this.
I want to be on every podcast at any time for any reason.
So no, this is not a situation
where you're exploiting my heritage.
Yes, you said what I was worried about.
No, I.
I feel like I remember last year.
If necessary, I would come in a Yarmulke
or whatever you want from me,
I'm happy to do to be here for this
paywall episode of a podcast.
My memory, I think, is that,
because we were playing all pandemic,
we and Anthony Geo and Tim Chang
were playing Grand Theft Auto.
That's right.
And we would play a couple times a week.
And I think maybe the day of we were like,
did you know there were like a whole range of Mensch
on a Bench character?
And you were like, yes, I do know that.
I have one.
And I think that's where we talked about it.
But again, that's that part of the pandemic.
My brain is completely fried.
Right.
And also, you know, that would be, I was playing,
I was on the East Coast for most of the pandemic.
So when we would have these Grand Theft Auto sessions.
Oh, we haven't even told the story.
Well, which one?
Well, they would just usually start for me.
Sometimes, you know, they would,
these guys would want to start playing at like 10 p.m.
Yes, right.
Which would be like 1 a.m. my time.
That's true.
For the child.
And this can't be done.
You know, be playing until like 4 a.m. or something.
The story, you know what I'm talking about?
Yeah.
So Susser and I were playing just the two of us
in one instance.
And I forget exactly how it happened.
But all of a sudden you stopped responding to me.
I was talking to him in the headset and we're playing,
his character stops moving, but he's still in the game.
And he stops responding to me.
And I'm going hello, like over and over again.
And then I like hang up and I call you back
and you're not picking up and you're not picking up.
And I was like, first I was like,
I guess maybe he fell asleep.
But then I have a part of me that goes,
I hope he's not in like some medical distress.
So like for like 20 minutes, 25 minutes,
I'm just trying to get confirmation
because he's still in the game.
He's still, he isn't like.
And this is like 3 a.m. on the East Coast.
Right, of course.
It makes sense.
That's a pretty reasonable conclusion.
Right when Mike is debating
if he's going to call my wife at 3 a.m.
And see if I'm okay playing video games,
I wake up and call him back and say, yeah, sorry, I fell asleep.
And the reason also was we were in the middle of talking.
Yes.
It wasn't like there was a lull for five minutes
and we're just kind of playing whatever.
And then it was, it was like, we were in the middle of talking.
He said something, I said something, nothing, nothing, nothing.
Hmm.
That was like.
Fair.
Yeah.
So, so I was like, hmm, am I going to call?
So Mike's just killing time in the game,
just driving through crowds of civilians for 20 minutes.
Well, I was shooting him over and over and racking up points.
Oh, okay.
Because I might wake him up too with a more gunfire.
Yeah, so, yeah.
So, but at some point in one of those discussions.
We probably had some monumental mess.
Yeah, at 3 a.m.
Because it had come up on an episode we did
at the end of the year, because we were in the episode,
we kind of live discovered,
I think we'd heard that phrase.
Maybe you didn't quite remember the origins of it.
Maybe New Shark Tank had something to do with it.
New Shark Tank didn't know about the extended universe
of characters. That's really,
that's what we got excited about.
What kind of lit us up.
And so I am happy that you were familiar already
and own the product, own the book.
It was given to me as a joke, the product.
It was not butter and a sliver.
Yes, I do own it.
What I was curious,
mensch is a term and a word that you guys know.
Yes.
Is it one you'd ever use?
For me, I don't think I've used it like,
oh, like what that guy is such a menscher.
Yeah, I don't think I've ever used it
in casual conversation.
Okay.
Just checking in with where we're at.
But I would say it.
Yeah, it's not a bad thing.
Yeah, yeah, I like the word.
It's not the M word.
It's an okay word to say.
Yeah.
You're bringing us this context
or we'd be really deep in it already.
I think it might be an age that I feel like
a non-Jewish person could say it if they are in show biz
and are 65 years old.
That is kind of the thing that everyone in show business,
if they're 65, regardless of heritage,
is allowed to just become Jewish.
I don't know what that is.
But everyone there is saying like, mensch.
John Mulaney.
John Mulaney has adopted the voice.
Just slowly put on that thing.
Yeah, I'm trying to think of any even just Jewish,
like I guess oi ve is something that was said a lot
in my house.
My mother is half Jewish,
but not the side that makes her Jewish.
So that's really the closest thing that might,
like I might pop into my.
An oi ve might slip out.
I might say oi ve once in a while or just oi.
Yeah.
Yeah, once in a while, but I don't know,
it might not be so common with me.
So the giving of the mensch on a bench,
I mean, yeah, is that just, is it like on a novelty level?
Was it somebody who you already talked about this thing with
or made fun of it and then you got it or just sort of random?
No, it was given to me by a non-Jew as maybe a hate crime.
No, I think it was just like,
oh, you would find this funny.
And they were right, I did.
But yeah, I mean, it very much,
it's much in the tradition of Hanukkah.
It's just a knockoff Christmas kind of thing.
There's Elf on a Shelf,
which also you guys, I don't know a ton about,
but that is also kind of a thing where someone
just created it to sell a toy.
Yeah, I believe so.
Yeah.
I don't trust that Elf on a Shelf
because he hides and he moves around.
The mansion on the bench is encouraged to move around
so he can rest and see some new parts of your house.
And that's much more reassuring to me
than just this creepy little Elf guy.
Can I just say, I didn't know any of this, the actual,
I knew the phrase, and oh, that's a cute phrase,
but I didn't know the mythology of it where,
what an Elf on a Shelf is, is like Santa's helper
who is the one determining if the kid is naughty or nice.
So parents can say the Elf is watching,
so watch what you do.
Right.
And the moving is to kind of sell the illusion
that they are alive.
No, that's not a toy.
Your other toys don't move every day.
The Elf moves because it's not a toy, it's real.
Manufacturing consent, getting children used
to the surveillance state, you know?
You know?
It's pretty weird.
I think that's why there is the Google auto-fill-in question,
is Elf on a Shelf bad?
And Jason would say yes.
I think not knowing much, I might veer to yes.
Yeah, there's some, much more mild element, I feel like,
on the rules, there are eight rules,
eight rules to dating my mench on a bench.
There is a rule of like, hey, be cooler,
might not get presents at night, you know?
Like be nice, be a good person, you know?
Yeah, but you know,
it very much does mirror Hanukkah,
which I don't know if you guys know how much you know
about Hanukkah, but Hanukkah is not a particularly important
religious holiday, it's a minor religious holiday
that basically only has risen in prominence
because of Christmas.
And I will say, as someone now who has a daughter
who's three and a half, it's a good thing,
because as we're going around the world, you know,
and we're seeing Christmas trees and hearing Christmas music,
she started to ask, hey, why don't we celebrate Christmas?
And we do have a go-to thing,
oh, because we celebrate Hanukkah.
Yes.
If we didn't have that, I mean, what do we do?
She'd be so mad.
Yeah, she'd be furious.
Now, when she doesn't know, Hanukkah much worse
than Christmas, but at least there's something to say.
Yeah.
So, mench on the bench is the same thing where this,
you know, it's a knockoff even of the commercialization
of Christmas, where it's just like, all right,
this other thing exists, we gotta have this mench
on a bench thing, then it's also gonna be not quite as good
and not as thought out.
And like, you know, the elf, it's like, okay,
that's like a part of the Christmas mythology.
Right.
This is just, the mench is just like a Hasidic guy,
like you would see like in the Lower East Side of New York,
you're like, yeah, that guy's a mascot now.
It's crazy.
And you know, the creator of it, this guy, Neil Hoffman,
I don't know a ton about him, but he looks to be kind of
like a secular Jewish guy.
So he was like, okay, yeah, like he's not,
he doesn't look like the mench.
Right.
Oh, I seriously, no, no, no, yeah,
just very average looking guy.
This product has such a narrow audience for it,
because it's not for people who are like orthodox,
observant Jews.
Right.
And it's not for people who like don't care about
being Jewish and just, you know, like whatever.
It's people who are like committed to,
they're gonna do a Jewish identity thing for like eight days,
but also it doesn't really have to be based
in any sort of religion.
Right.
It's weird.
Yeah, it's, well, the guy, I don't know a ton about him
who made it up, but he apparently worked at Hasbro.
Yes.
The toy guy, which I gotta respect.
Hasbro makes good toys still.
And for the Shark Tank investors,
like someone coming out of like toy marketing,
starting a toy startup, like that's a slam,
that seems like someone you wanna be in business.
Sure.
I think, but if you, I don't know if you rewatch the segment.
Yeah, it's just a little touch and go.
It doesn't seem like one that's gonna,
it seems like one of the ones, you know,
they throw the chum into the tank sometimes
is the ones that are a little thin and not thought out
that they can kind of dunk on and make fun of.
But as it goes, I think the rule of thumb with Shark Tank,
if you're not an avid viewer of it, is like,
some successes are like happening
or done within one act, but,
and some failures go into a second act,
but really, if somebody kinda teases something
and then you see the logo and we go into commercial,
oh, now there's something, now there's a negotiation
or the guy screws himself for,
so when I realized this was a two actor
and I knew they meant business,
and it is a very solid,
just it's a solid Shark Tank episode
regardless of the product.
Well, I think where they land it was reasonably fair,
right?
I think, yeah.
Laurie and Robert did a dual deal.
Laurie and Robert.
150,000 for 15% of the company.
Uh-huh.
He won it, so 150,000 for 10%,
so he compromised a little, but not too much.
That's not bad, yeah, yeah.
I think he went in a little too hot
trying to peg down Mr. Wonderful.
Like he seemed like he was really trying to,
like I don't think he can go in
like angling for certain sharks.
That always backfires.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
People are really pushing.
It's a QVC thing.
Yeah, we know you're going for Laurie when she goes out.
You're gonna start to well up with tears.
I thought it was interesting that he said
that they could have the mentions at Mav's Games,
but Cuban didn't really go for that.
Cuban seemed pretty dismissive off the bat, too.
I thought he came in too hot.
Which is he the only two?
Is he?
Or is Robert?
Barbra?
Or are they all Jewish?
I don't know.
That's a good question.
Yeah, I'm not sure.
I don't wanna start guessing.
No, it's good.
I don't know about this.
Barbara is interested for a little while.
I was like, come on, man.
No, no, no.
You're allowed. Jason, but.
You're allowed.
You're not appropriate.
Hey.
Do you, I think, you know, I kind of,
there's a lot of things to talk about.
Do you think,
cause like Santa Claus has been around a long time now,
and Santa is so, in my mind,
could be just completely disconnected from Christianity,
as far as the lore.
But what you're saying, the Mensch on the Bench
feels like it's like,
one of the characters name is Dreidel Dog.
I mean, it's so one to one.
It's so.
Yes, well.
So, Mensch on the Bench,
what is weird about this Mensch on the Bench thing
is the story of Mensch on the Bench,
they attempt to retcon Mensch
into the story of the first ever Hanukkah.
Oh, oh, okay.
Which is not something that Santa,
I don't really, I guess, know the lore of Santa,
but is Santa like,
connected to Jesus in any way?
Only in like weird, specific,
like people trying to carve out a weird religious,
I don't know, am I wrong?
Well, I think it's a European thing, Saint Nicholas,
and like.
Oh, that's right.
Oh, it's biblical in that sense.
Yeah, so it goes back.
But nobody said that Santa Claus
isn't in the Bible or anything.
No.
Maybe like, I guess Saint Nicholas isn't either,
but you know what I mean.
No, I mean, our modern idea of Santa Claus
comes from the Coca-Cola Company, I believe.
Yeah, yeah.
And even the modern version of Christmas,
a lot of that comes from various things over the,
Coca-Cola, various marketing,
oh, the Christmas Carol.
Oh, sure, yeah.
The Dickens book.
But all the songs, I feel,
not all the songs, but a lot of the songs
are from the 50s and 60s.
Yeah.
It's something I kinda like about
Neil Hoffman's opportunism here,
is he's looking at like,
well, we haven't had Rudolph the Red-Nosed Reindeer
for that long.
Right.
And now we don't really remember where it came from
or who thought of it, but somebody had to,
and he's like, down the road,
maybe mention on a bench is just,
what was it?
Maybe that is.
Yes, maybe it does come, but yeah.
So in the story, though,
he tries to take the story of the first Hanukkah,
which, should I tell quickly?
Sure, yeah.
So the religious story is the Jews,
the Maccabees, led by Judah the Maccabee,
defeat the Greeks or something like that,
and then they rescue the temple,
and there's only enough oil for one night,
and then it lasts for eight nights,
and that's why Hanukkah lasts eight nights,
and that's why you like candles for eight nights.
So what they've done with this book is say,
well, while that was all going on,
there was this other guy named Mensch,
who was just hanging out at the temple
and looking at the oil being like, ah, good.
He volunteers to stay up, like, I'll look at it.
He was like, hey, you need someone to look at the lights?
I'll do it, no problem.
I'm a night owl.
You've all fought a war.
I'll just be here looking at it.
Which again, this is not something that's like,
there's no text or anything that supports anything close.
It's just an invented thing,
but it also is so tied to the religious story.
It could have just been like a made up thing.
It was in New York, and there was this Mensch
who saw all the Jewish kids celebrating Hanukkah,
and he dropped off presents, or it could be anything.
They didn't need to go back to the,
and do this kind of, it really is like a Rogue One version
of here's how they got the plan.
They don't know why that was,
and then with all these other extended characters
who they clearly, it's just not a continuity
that he fought out from the beginning,
because none of these other characters come up
in this origin story.
There's not even room for them,
and I don't know if they have their own,
or if they have their own books, or the mythology.
Well, Mitzvah Moose has a story.
There's a video online.
Mitzvah Moose is insane.
That is just like.
Mitzvah Moose is really wild.
Like I looked away for a minute, and I came back.
What's the Mitzvah Moose story?
Mitzvah Moose has the menorah candles on his antlers,
and Moshe has to do different mitzvahs in a day, right?
And as he does them, a new candle lights up.
Yeah.
It's a Rudolph ripoff situation where.
It's the same thing.
It's like Christmas, you got one night, we got eight.
Yeah.
Rudolph, he's got one night.
No, this guy, he's got eight light-up things.
Antlers that don't glow.
He wants the antler.
Why aren't his antlers glowing, says Moshe,
and you might say because antlers never glow.
Right, no, to be fair, neither do noses.
Oh yeah, that's true.
Yeah, you know what?
I keep trying to get Neil here,
and yet he keeps out-foxing me.
Yeah, but so the good deeds make him light up.
Yeah.
Which is also consistent with the toy,
which is with me today.
Wow.
Look who's here.
It's Mitzvah Moose.
Wow, there he is.
And if I press on his hoof,
then you, is it this one?
Yeah, yeah.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
That's awesome.
Yes, you can see why I bought this.
I went to Target, which boy, this speaks to how,
this is one of the great Shark Tank success stories,
that it's in so many big boxes
that there's an entire section
in the middle of a Target aisle,
because I went to buy Moshe, I went to buy the Mitch,
and then as I'm looking at him,
I'm like, this is the cool that lights up.
That is some cool function.
We've been kind of snarky,
but that's some fun functionality.
And one at a time, I think is cool.
There's toys where now it all lights up,
but the fact that you can count them up,
so, mid Hanukkah, as we are currently,
where should we be as we're recording this?
You wanna squeeze that bad boy twice.
Twice, but it'll come out sort of soon, right?
Oh, when it comes out.
Well, I guess we shouldn't tie ourselves to that,
but I probably, three or four, anyway,
it could be two right now.
That's where we are in time.
But, pretty cool, right?
And there is the story with it.
It comes with a book, is not hardcover,
like the one that you were holding for Mitch and a Bench.
And this is, so it's more of like a leaflet,
like kind of a set, like remember, in downtown Disney,
like the stuff you get handed at the little table.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like Latter-day Saints kind of pamphlets.
Or that Target used to be,
I don't know if you remember this,
that Target, you used to,
even if you went in the store for five minutes,
you would come out and find pamphlets
for the Tony Alamo Christian Ministries,
wedged under your windshield wiper.
Yeah.
Oh, you just get flanketed.
That's a whole, that's a real bunch of kooks, that lot.
Oh, I don't know about Tony Alamo.
I think he's long dead, but as he was in-
Next year we'll do an episode about Tony Alamo.
And not for something great, if memory serves.
There's two things to say about the book,
which would also be true of your book, Evan, the font.
You have to deduct points,
well, I would deduct points for the font,
which is the dreaded Papyrus.
Yeah.
Mike might add points because it is the font
of your beloved Avatar franchise.
Avatar Pandora, yeah, yeah.
The mighty Papyrus.
Navi love Papyrus.
That's one of the things we actually-
It's their handwriting.
Yeah.
When a Navi takes like a tentacle
and squeezes ink out of it and writes with it,
they form, that's where the font comes from.
Right, it's like-
Every Navi's natural handwriting.
It's like when you're in Navi school,
like that's learning cursive, is Papyrus.
So yeah, so it's beautiful to me.
You have to have little holes on the side constantly.
Yeah.
Little edge marks.
Oh, I finally watched it.
Oh, it was on Thanksgiving.
Really?
Oh, interesting.
Oh, this is, well, this is probably,
this could be an episode.
Yeah, we can't.
Yeah, that could be an episode.
I, any general-
I thought it was great.
Oh, wow, yeah, there you go.
Wow, unbelievable on board.
Yeah.
So-
Can't wait for the seed bearer in the way of water now.
Very excited.
So, also nothing on the back, that's not so strong.
And then like, just look at the text.
This is some of the strangest-
There's a lot of white space.
Yeah.
And then a few sentences.
The bottom third of the page is just white
and then the tiniest font I've ever seen in any book
for just only two lines.
Can you even see it?
I know, oh my God.
There is text there and you aren't that far away, Jason.
I can barely tell what's going on, yeah.
What happened?
Is this a mistake?
Is this a printing error?
Is this gonna be worth something someday?
Because-
Yeah, possibly.
It's the famous Mids for the Moose
with the tiny papyrus.
Wow.
I mean, I even knew Glass's prescription
to get filled at some point, but it ain't that bad.
No one needs to be able to see this tiny text.
Wow.
Yeah, it's pretty crazy.
Otherwise, it's charming, the drawings are nice,
you get to see Mids for the Moose.
Among the things he does are like recycle.
That's one of his Midsfas.
It is full of like spelling errors and typos,
but then you get to meet, maybe this is a good segue
into some of the other characters
because here is a Midsfa that he does
as he hopes give a bath to another
Extended Universe character, the Dreidel Dalmatian,
who is a dog with spots, but all of the spots
are in the shape of Dreidels.
Right.
And even though we're making fun of it,
it is like, you know, Mench does come from ancient Greece
where both Dalmatians and Mooses were native,
so it makes sense that these characters exist.
Uh-huh, of course.
And most importantly, they're very cute.
So does he, is there any interactions
with other characters besides Dreidel Dalmatian?
Oh, in the book here, I should skim, let's see.
Didn't do the full read.
Well, some kids.
Oh yeah, you know, I think a lot of them,
this might be like a later edition.
Yeah, they try to get everybody in.
Yeah, because you've also got.
You got Papa?
I'm not sure.
Hannah, the Hanukkah hero?
Yeah, I think maybe the pronunciation
is supposed to be Hanna, the Hanukkah hero.
I saw a video where he described it,
even though it's spelled Hannah,
but it's like trying to be the same sentence, Hanukkah.
Right.
Who's also, you got another issue.
Hannah, the Hanukkah hero, you ran into the same thing.
Your issue with tying it to the original Hanukkah story,
it's also weird because now the Moshe is just in modern times.
Yes, he's an immortal.
Yeah, I guess like Santa, again.
Yeah, yeah.
There's always analogs to these things,
but like Santa's not really tied to, you know,
here's something that happened in 1692.
It's not so specifically dated.
So yeah, Santa's like James Bond,
can kind of just happen in any time period
and no one really asks questions.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It resets, we accept that it resets.
But this would be the equivalent if like,
Santa was one of the three wise men,
is basically what they've tried to do.
Oh, that's good, yeah.
Right.
Would you, as a writer, you're a creative person,
have you thought about, well, what would I have done?
Of course.
Okay.
Okay, good.
Open.
Oh, yes.
No, I think that if I'm gonna be honest,
should I give like a serious answer?
Sure.
I think that as Mench on a Bench is so much tied
to America Judaism that Mench should be
an American Jewish creation.
And maybe I think that you would do it
like kind of New York Ellis Island-y kind of times,
and you would like tell a story about like a Jewish family
living in like Brooklyn and the Mench on the Bench
that like took care of them
when they like first came to America to flee.
During like a tough winter or something.
Yeah, a tough winter to flee the Nazis.
Maybe you don't get into Nazis for a children's story.
But on the other hand- But that's the influence, maybe.
Yeah, it's kind of like in the background.
Right.
I think that setting it in America
would be a better origin story for the Mench on the Bench.
That would be my punch up.
I do like the extended characters too,
and I wish if they had had the thought too
that that's where they were going,
that there had been little teases
in the origin story of Mench.
Right, because it feels a little bit like,
oh, this is like a cash cow or something.
Let's cash in.
Shove some more in there.
Right.
Yeah, because now, because it's why we're talking about it now
is that we never thought about doing
a Mench on a Bench episode.
It's the universe that kind of is the appeal now.
I like these animals.
I like a dreidel- The Bench universe, yeah.
Spotted deletion.
Right.
It's good that there's an extended universe.
And it's also funny that one of them is Papa.
Right.
Which is like, that is so not different.
It's like an older Jewish man.
It's like, they have this big extended universe,
and two of the characters are basically the same.
Now, the toy, I understand from the toy purposes,
they wanted to design a toy that you could squeeze,
and I think it says something.
Right.
It's my understanding of what that does,
so that's why they wanted a different one.
Because Mench doesn't do it.
That might be important to note.
Mench doesn't do anything.
He doesn't do anything.
Which is why I didn't buy him.
Right, that's why I went for Mitzvah Moose here.
But, and they went with Bubbe,
but they didn't go with Zadie?
Well, again, if they went with Zadie-
Yeah, I know, they went with Papa for some reason.
Right, they could have, Bubbe and Zadie, they could,
which is, that was probably like, oh, that's a good one,
because then you have the grandparents to buy that.
Oh, right, right.
So that's probably what they were going for.
Mm-hmm.
Bubbe Dances, that's the thing, I think,
from my Target experience earlier,
although the toy didn't seem to work too well in the,
but I think-
And are they related to Mench?
I really, I couldn't find.
Also, this is, the Target,
in the sign that this is going really well,
the Target displays that they have all of them,
which is a great branding thing,
just like, it must be successful,
there's a whole universe of these things.
Right, right.
In the not so successful, no Wikipedia page
for Mench on a Bench.
Oh.
Not true, if anybody actually cared about this mythology,
yeah, somebody would have taken the time.
You would think that it would have a Wikipedia page.
Yeah.
We're beating them, people have written the mythology
of the Sector Keeper, the important,
which was certainly not tossed off.
Is there a Sector Keeper Wikipedia page?
Not, well, on the, well, not, look,
on the podcast, the Ride Wiki,
I am I cheating by saying,
because we have a Wiki,
but there's no Mench Wiki.
No, there's not a Mench Wiki.
I know that with Big Dog, Wikipedia is the ultimate game.
Uh-huh.
I don't remember if we have one of those,
but do they not, does Mench not even have that?
They don't have a-
It's gotta have a main one, right?
No, it's not on the main Wikipedia.
Hmm.
It's a section on Elf on a Shelf.
Are we not either?
I feel like I'm throwing stones.
Yeah, I gotta check this out now.
Mench on a Bench Wiki.
Do you devote it solely to your commissioner duties?
No mention of the films.
Yeah, there's not.
There is not, it just goes right to
just defining what a mench is,
and then define it in an Elf on a Shelf Wikipedia.
So it says in the Elf on a Shelf
that there's a Jewish counterpart to Elf on a Shelf.
Yes.
Yeah, it's not its own.
Oh, okay.
Well, I think it, well, I mean, isn't this really
because it has stopped at the toys and the books
that mainly you get with the toys?
There's no product here, and wouldn't we,
not no, those are products, obviously.
I mean a, you know what I'm saying,
a film, a TV show, even like animated shorts.
Right.
There's gonna be a YouTube channel that's all like,
it's all the creator going on local news in Orlando.
Like I was trying to, in frantically coming over here,
trying to prepare, I was like, okay,
they probably have made even at least
a cheap animated thing, or maybe on Spotify
I was gonna be able to find someone reading a Mench
on the Bench book or something,
and you really couldn't find that.
I really think that someone,
and I'm gonna say now as I'm thinking about me,
they've gotta get in touch,
and there's gotta be like an animated thing for this.
Well there's some, I don't know, we'll get to,
I thought there's some YouTube videos,
I don't know if you came across the same ones,
but I think is the official channel.
Did you see any of this?
I saw, I just saw a lot of stuff that was with the creator
and the shark tank and like that story,
but was there stuff about like?
I'll, let me get to this.
I just, I also wanna say this real quick.
There is not an official podcast to write on the Wikipedia,
but there is a Scott Gardner Wikipedia page
that mentions podcasts in the Wikipedia page,
but you don't have a link to our main Wikipedia page.
So I'm the elf on the shelf.
So Scott is the elf on the shelf
and Mench on the bench.
All of us together.
I found that too, but you're the second result.
The first result under podcast,
and it's just searching the words individually,
the first result was, did you mean Red Scare podcast?
No, we didn't mean Red Scare, absolutely not.
I did not mean that, no thank you.
Guiding you to Red Scare what?
I think it just had podcast and ride somewhere in the entry.
Cause then there was like another net,
some network I'd ever had,
and it was just seemingly like the terms
were used throughout the entry.
We gotta get the Red Scare podcast guys on.
Yeah.
Oh, I assure you we don't.
What if it's just, do we know what it is?
Yep.
Oh, okay.
All right, nevermind.
It was like a history, historical analysis.
I'll explain, we'll explain later.
Uh oh, okay.
I don't know what it is either.
So I think this is the official Mench on a bench YouTube,
which has 82 subscribers.
Okay.
And there are 82 subscribers.
I thought you were saying 82,000 or like.
82 subscribers.
This video I'm about to play was posted 11 months ago.
It has 191 views.
And it is a song, there is music on the page.
I don't know if you saw this.
And again, it could be a fan page.
I don't know, I guess, but this is Saul the snow mench,
which is a character I don't think we've talked about yet.
Oh no.
And as you know, we're talking about,
it's just the Christmas version.
This is.
A little song we whipped up in honor of the newest member
of the mench family.
Saul is the snow mench.
He's a very menchy soul.
With a cool black hat and toilet wrapped
around him to keep cold.
Saul is the snow mench and he'll sing a song for you.
Just touch his arm and you'll be charmed
to listen to his tunes.
He's painted.
That's an ad for the toy.
That's not, that's just an ad for the toy.
I don't know if the actual character also plays music
if you touch his arm.
But then I think they also talk about his origin,
which is like he was just the mench made a snowman, I think.
I think it's a lie.
Or Moshe.
In his yard he was very, very proud.
Oh, Saul is the snow mench with a fuzzy beard of felt.
And he cannot hold any candles or he would surely melt.
So that's, I guess an ad for the new,
I guess maybe the snow mench was new as of last year.
The story is that a man made a snowman.
Yeah, it does have a lot.
It does seem very influenced by Frosty the Snowman.
Yeah, I think, you know, I think you might be right.
That's what I was trying to place it.
Yeah, I was also.
I wasn't coming up with it.
I don't criticize anyone's process,
but yeah, I can see that, I can see that.
Yeah, so that's on there.
And there are, that's not the only music that's on.
Okay, what else do we have?
Okay, so imagine, you won't be able to see the video,
but here is like, imagine, you know, Jib Jab,
we all know Jib Jab.
Imagine the characters from Jib Jab,
but with the like felt heads
of the mench on a bench characters.
Can you see this?
A little bit.
Okay.
That'd be a deal.
It's some characters and.
So yeah, they're like dancing,
but then they're like human bodies.
They're wearing sort of blue, like velvet.
Are they gonna say off to do some campaigning?
Well, here, here we go.
This is only a minute long.
A little dreidel, I made it out of clay.
And when it's crying ready, a dreidel I shall play.
24 karat magic mixed with dreidel.
And then it's.
Oh, I don't know, I don't know.
Night on the note of let's have a party.
We'll all gather around the table and give out a treat.
See people that play with it.
I just turn around.
Dreidel is so lovely.
Relax, just trying to say.
Auto tune on this.
It's so tired.
It drops and then I'm here.
Oh, dreidel, dreidel, dreidel.
Now probably dubstep.
Dubstep kind of beat there.
So yeah, I don't know if you can see
they're like kind of dancing.
So I don't know this.
This is different.
Like this is weird.
Cause like they have human bodies
and they're like break dancing during it.
Yeah, very strange.
This isn't like the rest.
Right.
This feels like off tone, off game.
Yeah, they really need some help here.
Yeah, they need to, you know, streamline.
So I think that they gotta get this mythology nailed down
a little bit better and have it be a little more compelling.
Sure. That's one.
Two, I think there needs to be some original content
that is created besides just the books.
Right, yeah. Whether that's songs
that are maybe a little better
or it really feels like some animation thing
should really be within grasp.
Yeah, it is. Easy.
The level of like dog shit, you know,
like what kids YouTube animation,
which is made by bots and frightening.
But if we're really going for it,
they need like a voice, a celebrity voice.
Yeah, sure.
Who are the top picks in this?
Larry David.
Larry David's good.
Do you think Mensch for Larry David?
Oh, well.
But if he's sort of...
He plays the opposite, you might say.
Yeah, but he's so fun to like, he seems like,
if he's just not saying something mean,
I think you would hear his voice
and maybe not think he was angry.
Like he would be like such a nice guy.
I don't think it's that hard.
I got one.
Evan Susser.
I mean, that's a good idea.
I wasn't gonna say it, but now that I hear it, I like it.
Yeah. No, I'm serious.
Larry David's a good one.
I think old is, I mean Sandler just for moving,
getting people excited is obvious,
but he's maybe a little young still.
Maybe older.
But doing a silly older voice.
Yeah, doing a silly older voice could be really good.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, it's a tough...
It's kind of narrow, I guess.
Older and loveable.
William Shatner.
You know, not as a...
Even though he is Jewish,
I feel like doesn't have that same sort of Jewish...
Yeah, I don't think I know who it is.
It's in the Hanukkah song, that's how I know.
That's true.
Mark Cuban.
Maybe.
I know he didn't go in on it, but maybe he'd do a voice.
And then I think for singing the song,
they really should reach out to the Maccabeats.
How familiar...
No, I don't know what that is.
I don't know what the Maccabeats are.
The Maccabeats are an Orthodox Jewish singing sensation,
acapella group.
That I believe started...
I don't wanna say...
I'm not in college or somewhere,
but then have gone on to be a bigger thing.
And every year, for all the Jewish holidays,
they come out with parodies of existing songs
and really do have a pretty big following.
And I'm gonna play a sample of one of their songs
to give you guys a sense.
Great.
Oh.
How does a hazmer need a sun?
Oh no, no.
Raised in a village with his four brothers
in a Judeo-Prophet's river.
He sets high a kiss of the pressure
to grow up to be a hero in command.
When the king came around,
his son said, I'll be my piece of sing.
Yeah, that's good.
You know, my favorite genres of music, I'd say,
is Hamilton parody.
Spotify, it's all they give me.
It's in me.
Calling you to Maccabeats.
All right.
Wow.
That's great.
So, you know, I think if you get those guys in.
Yeah.
So, and that, I think, they really do have a pretty big,
also, Orthodox Jewish audience.
So you get them in.
Right.
Then you get in the secular Jewish celebrity.
And you put up some, you know,
good original animated material.
I think this thing could, again, not really take off
because there's only so much of an audience for it.
Now, wait a minute.
I think, wait, what you were playing was just,
that was like variants on the dreidel song, correct?
Yes.
I think that the snowmench,
when you press the snowmench,
I think what he plays is variants on the dreidel song
done by the Maccabeats.
They already are in the partnership?
I think that they have made the connection, yeah.
Well, you know what?
I'm pretty sure.
I took my hat because that was.
Yeah.
That's a pretty good connection.
They're fix up.
They're like, they're slightly on top of it.
I do remember like in elementary school,
like music class,
that we would do a little Christmas concert.
And at least one, if not two years, we sang Ohanica.
And looking back, I think maybe the teacher,
our music teacher was Jewish
because we sang that song
and we learned the story of Hanica.
There were no Jewish kids in my elementary school classes,
but I did learn the story.
The story then cemented in my mind
by an issue of a Marvel holiday special.
Like what's the annual holiday issues?
I can't remember who was the thing or Kitty Pride,
the two most prominent Jewish members
of the Marvel universe telling the story.
But yeah, looking back, I'm like,
it must have been the teacher
because I don't remember any other.
I don't think I met a person of the Jewish faith
until high school, otherwise,
until like a teacher in high school.
And she had converted when she got married.
Interesting.
You know what, also real quick a thought
just to do some music,
who wrote an original Hanica song,
Mr. Stephen Page of the Bare Naked Ladies.
Wow.
From the Bare Naked Ladies Christmas album.
That would be great.
Cause they do cover a few traditional songs,
but then he also wrote an original Hanica song.
So I think he's got to get out there.
We streamed a Stephen Page concert
during the pandemic as well.
We did, like the second week.
The second week, and he really had a lot of tech.
He had a lot of tech problems.
When he was currently live, do you know?
Yeah, yeah.
I don't know if you-
It was, was it maybe just in Zoom?
I think it was just on a Zoom.
They were doing, yeah, that was happening a lot
where you would have to like,
we paid like $10 or something.
Kind of made less of an impact
than everyone's seeing in Imagine two weeks in.
Yeah, that's true.
Cohen Brothers World guy.
Like, you know who's so good on the Monica Lewinsky
American Crime Story is Fred Melamed.
Yeah. Oh yeah.
Get Melamed as a bench on the bench.
Oh yeah.
You know what?
That's for the live action version.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh.
You know, that's pretty good.
Or maybe that's just because of his thing.
Right.
Like that's, you know.
Playing a live action in a big-
Just send this podcast to some executives.
Yes.
Yeah, kind of genuinely.
And then you're telling the story on,
well, I was actually just,
I was riffing on a podcast.
And then now, but I realized I had the take and the actor.
Yeah.
And he's here right here with me.
Ladies and gentlemen.
And doing the music, Mr. Steven Page.
Yeah, perfect.
Here he is.
Well, thank you guys for helping me fix this.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We also even have,
we have to talk too about like,
what you would do with the theme park land.
The theme park of Mentsch on the bench.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Man, that's a tough one.
Well, you, I think, Mike,
you were just telling me that there was a Christmas themed
theme park that you grew up.
Oh, see, yeah, yeah.
Growing up, there was something, what place called,
there's many Santa's villages around the country
and world probably.
But yeah, there was one very close
that also had an ice skating arena or like rink,
the big one, my sister took lessons.
And it was closed.
And you asked, you were surprised that Santa's village
was closed in the winter.
Yes.
Which, yes, it was.
It was only open, the ice skating was open in the winter.
So I think, so what are you doing for the theme park?
That's the real question.
What's kind of like.
Well, or is it a land?
Or is it a land somewhere else?
Can it just, can it be a Moshe's village?
Do we just start with that?
Yeah, well, there's a story,
there's just a story where the Mentsch on the bench
goes to Africa.
Which is a book you can buy.
Well, it seems, it kind of seems like it's alluding,
like he's going there to convert people.
The Mentsch? A little bit.
You know, it's strange,
cause Judaism is not a prophylatizing religion.
Right.
So I'm kind of surprised to hear that.
I mean, I don't think, I don't know,
maybe I'm reading too much into it.
You know, but that's sort of.
I think that honestly the path
for Mentsch on the bench getting a theme park
is connecting with one of these
nut job, far right, fundamentalist Christian theme parks.
Because a lot of those guys
really do have a fondness for the Jews.
Because it's like in the prophecy
that the Jews will still exist and be in Israel.
And that's why you get all of these
fundamentalist extremists who are very pro-Israel.
Right.
So maybe you just, you know,
do a partnership with one of these museums
that has dinosaurs walking with cavemen or something.
Yes.
Strange Red Fellows for startup capital
is what you're saying.
And then there's a little,
Moishas village where people just tucked away.
Tucked away.
Look.
Behind the ark.
You don't even see it when you drive up.
And then, you know, food,
like there could be a lot of great food.
Sure.
Yeah.
You know, they could have the potato latkes.
Sure.
They're around.
They could have the chocolate gelt.
They could have a Souf Gonyot.
I've not had that.
I haven't had that.
Well, you might know it by its more common English name,
jelly donuts.
Wow.
Which is also a tradition of Hanukkah
because it also requires oil.
And as you gentlemen may have noticed with me,
I brought a pink box.
You got the famous pink box.
Wow.
Of jelly donuts to you guys.
Geez.
So, the second night of Hanukkah.
Well, since you've given us permission,
I would say that this makes you a real mensch.
Ah, it feels good to try.
It felt weird when you said it, Scott.
I didn't want to.
I don't want to do it again.
The box closed after you said it, Scott.
No, no, I don't get one now.
A serious man.
No, no, that was nice.
Yeah, so I guess, I think that it really, at this point,
it's definitely much more of a land
where there could be the bench.
He could take pictures on the bench.
Is that the ride vehicle?
Oh, you're on, you sit on a bench.
You sit on the bench and you're going,
and they each, you know what, in eight nights,
that works out really well for each stages of a ride.
So you could have things happening inside of a house.
I think, again, we want to get away from not the temple
that was destroyed, you know?
Come up with more American house or something
where there's some story going on
and you're on the bench with Mensch
and you're seeing scenes kind of happen.
That's pretty good.
And you're seeing all these other characters too.
Yeah. Yeah.
Because if you hit religious Judaism and cultural Judaism,
you'll reach a much bigger audience.
That's what I'm thinking.
Yeah.
Oh yeah, you could just have it,
one is like you're meeting Mitzvah Moose.
Yes, you're meeting Mitzvah Moose.
That's like a stage.
And then you're all together at the end celebrating.
Like, Mensch on the bench has to collect all of his friends
for the big Hanukkah, for the eighth night of Hanukkah.
Right.
And then it's like, you know, getting to him,
it's like, oh, Moose, you gotta come.
Uh-huh.
And you like, you gotta come.
Kind of the Hanukkah hero.
It's like a big party,
like you have secret lives of pets.
Yes.
Yeah.
That's pretty good.
Yeah, what Dreidel dog is like biting something.
So he does whatever they're planning to pull him away.
So that's a whole, that's like a little development.
It's like, we gotta make more latkes.
And it's the first ever ride that has like a latke smell.
Yes.
Which they've never done on a ride as far as I know.
I think.
Is it not space mountain doesn't do that?
All right, I guess maybe no ride does it.
Yeah.
Mitzvah Moose has too many Mitzvahs to do.
Right.
Trying to do so many kind things all at once.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, like reading to orphans over here,
but then with their foot.
And then of course you're being chased by the Greeks.
Who wanna kill you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
For being Jewish.
That's like a little minimized.
So it's like the Ursula scene on Little Sons of Sam.
Right, exactly.
The mermaid ride.
There's one scene.
You kind of like, it's just can't say that.
Just in the background, there's a bunch of Greek people
going like, ah.
We were defeated.
There's just one scene of a Greek guard inspecting genitals
to see who's Jewish.
Just one.
Just one scene of that.
We're not talking lots of scenes of that.
That'd be weird.
Right.
I think that's pretty good.
Wow.
Yeah.
And then at the end, they're all hanging out
on a bench together.
His bench was empty at the beginning,
but now it's full of friends.
It's full of friends.
And at the end, for some reason,
all the characters have human bodies
and they're break dancing.
Yes.
That's also part of it.
That's part of it.
That's part of the party.
I mean, we're probably winding down,
but I will say there is a place that this could go,
were it to be a land.
There is a potential,
I think they'd happily have it,
because I was just curious,
well, is there,
I just Googled Jewish theme park in general.
Is there anything that's made a point
of having a consistent ride or land?
And I came across something called Plame Park.
Plame?
Plame.
You know what I mean?
I watched a video,
and I think I'm saying it right.
I guess it, I don't know,
it translates to where they also call it
the Park of Wonders.
It was planned for the Demona Israel.
This place never got off the ground.
And I think I know why.
So this was to be a park that celebrated
and was rooted in Jewish tradition and heritage.
And I looked at what,
this is being proposed like three, four years ago,
and I looked at what was supposed to be there.
One of the proposed rides is based on Splash Mountain
with the theme modified to show six work days,
then a calm zone after a drop
that signifies the day of rest.
Okay.
All right.
A bloom ride,
but that shows you that's about how the week is hectic.
But then you get to-
So the splash is like Shabbos?
Well, what is, yeah, what is-
Or the other-
Or the book of Genesis?
Thursday.
The seventh day he rested?
I have a little bit of information and in fact a video.
So-
And do they insist on the song
of the South characters being in it too?
It wouldn't be a bloom ride without our pals, the Brayers.
This is a video that was made five years ago.
So this is, the beginning of it is a wise grandpa
and then like an iPad stuck kid are having an argument
about whether Jewish heritage is boring or not.
I will say that this argument is boring.
So I won't show you that part, maybe 0.1 for a kid.
But then some magical stuff starts to happen
and I'll let the video take it from here
and it'll show you a little bit
of what's going on at Plame Park.
History's awakening.
Wow.
What's that?
I don't know.
It looks like something from the future.
A weird iPhone kind of thing landed.
Sliding up.
Grandpa, press on that.
Step inside the Jewish wonderland, Park Plame,
where thousands of years of Jewish values and heritage
is brought to life right before your eyes.
At the very center of the park is its heart,
towering above all the Jacobs Ladder.
Whoa, Jacobs Ladder is the weenie?
Yeah, it looks, sorry, I was not really good.
It looks like a big DNA strand.
And then there's one of those SeaWorld Magic Mountain
kind of like the tower with the big observation deck
that goes up in the top.
Yeah, the weenie is Jacobs Ladder is wrapping around it.
The weenie is like the castle you know.
Yeah, this is all CGI, like what it might look like
that we're looking at.
Yeah, Jacobs Ladder.
Then, head in the north and then spurge on to the physical.
The entire park can be seen from the top of this ride.
Wow, Grandpa, we have to go there.
Behold, the people of the roller coaster,
the high-speed twirling ride that traverses pages
and books of the Jewish people.
Oh my God, oh my God, okay.
Yeah, yeah, that's really good.
That's really good.
Wow.
Yeah, yeah, we're looking at a roller coaster
that is pouring out of a big set of like old mahogany books.
That is so good.
What do they call it?
The book of the.
I didn't, I couldn't, yeah, which holy book did they say?
Yeah, let me see, sorry.
Well, they ran into an issue
because they wanted to be the Torah,
but then that would have to be the scrolls
and that was probably an architectural nightmare.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So then it's like,
oh, it's a hard cover for Talmud or something.
The people of the book roller coaster was the name of it.
How insane is this video, this proposal,
these fully rendered rides?
Yeah.
I was like more than I expected to find
in Googling Jewish theme park.
Wow.
And then, but then here's a little more explanation
of the flume that I described.
Wow.
So much.
Thanks.
It's not free really.
And what's that?
The Shabbat attraction lets the visitor experience
the contrast between the craziness of modern life
and the tranquility of Shabbat.
Shabbat is the time for loved ones,
personal reflection and a connection to the almighty.
Wow.
So what's going on here?
It's like you're in like a busy subway station.
Yeah.
So bustle of modern life.
It's basically, if people are familiar
with the Jurassic park ride,
you're going on a ride and instead of,
well, what's the name now?
It's not the T-Rex anymore.
The Indominus.
Instead of that popping up, it's just the word Friday.
And it looks like a freeway sign.
Freeway sign.
Because you're always, you're on the subway
or the freeway. and then you just go down.
Yeah, it kind of looks like a subway tunnel.
And then it's a Shabbos.
In like glowing gold, kind of like reminiscent of,
you know, like the first Superman movie font,
like is light rays shooting out of.
And then you're surrounded by video screens
of like a Jewish mom bringing food to a table.
Right.
A bunch of children patiently listening
to their father give a speech before they're allowed to sit.
It's just a video of that.
Yeah. It's like, it's a, look, it is part screen ride.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Unfortunately.
But what's on the screen is inspiring and important.
Yeah, that's true.
A little girl lighting a candle full of wonder.
So, I mean, I love it.
Yeah. It would be better with robots, but.
Yeah, sure.
But he used to say they aren't somewhere in that attraction.
Right.
A guy saying, I want those papers on my desk
by the end of Friday night.
Hi, wow.
Man.
That is crazy.
I'm wondering, are there proposals
for like all world religion kind of theme?
Like float by the Bodhi tree
as the Buddha sits under it contemplating.
Yeah, good pitch.
Pretty good.
Yeah, Buddha.
Rub his belly.
Wow.
It's soft.
Does it say it's coming like soon at the end of it?
I believe so. Yes.
This is, yeah, this was from 2016
and there are almost no Google results for this
besides the initial story about it,
despite them saying that this idea represents a cultural
and educational game changer relating to millennials
in a language relevant to them.
Millennials were like, I'm not so sold on this religion
until I rode a roller coaster through some books.
And then I'm on board.
This park will unite Jews everywhere around the world
with a common vision and values.
It'll like, this is gonna have like an incredible effect
on harmony within the religion, within all people, I guess.
No, it says only Jews.
All people are welcome at this park.
I would love to go through the books for sure.
They ask to see your, you have to do a 23 and me
before you go in.
Wow.
Anyway, and so this is proposed by a rabbi
as opposed to Mensh on a bench.
Okay.
Right, that is interesting.
It seems like it's much even more religiously rooted
than Mensh on the bench.
So maybe Mensh on the bench is not like orthodox enough
for this park?
No, I think this guy seems willing to make a deal.
Is it like sacrilegious to like be like,
yeah, and the roller coaster goes through the books?
I don't know.
I would be curious to get some opinions
from some rabbis on this.
Any more or less sacrilegious than Mitzvah Moose?
The moose with a menorah for handlers?
Well, that's what I meant.
I just want to know what the level is here.
Yeah, I mean, you know, you want to engage people.
I don't think there's anything
specifically forbidden about this.
Right.
I don't know.
It's a good question.
You put a hole in the holy books?
Right, yeah.
Are you kidding?
Well, they're not real though.
Yeah, cause they're like generic books.
They're not, yeah.
So as long as you can prove to a rabbi
that there is no sacred text in the fake book,
you can run as many coaster cars through it as you want.
Yeah, but it's the thrill.
It's trying to make you like associate like thrills
with the religion.
The thrill of learning.
The thrill of learning, yeah.
Yeah.
Okay, all right.
So if this gets off the ground in Israel,
then maybe there is a place for the mention of the bench.
Israel has kind of adopted a mention on the bench.
The baseball team in Israel,
like uses mention on the bench as a mascot, one of them.
Oh, whoa.
That's something that they've.
Right.
Huh.
Oh, that's priming it.
Then the characters around for photo ops and hugs.
Well, yeah, there's a walk around mentions
cause there was one at a Red Sox game
for Jewish heritage night.
There was a walk around motion wearing a Red Sox cap.
Yeah, there's a guy we know who played baseball,
my only baseball.
And there's a picture of him on the website of mention
on a bench next to at a press conference
with a big mensch character.
Oh yeah.
Cody Decker, you know, you remember him.
Oh yeah, he's on the Israeli team.
Oh, oh, there you go.
He was the one who was behind this whole adopting it thing.
Wow, really?
I didn't know that.
That's correct.
So that's why he's on the website.
Which is the thing I do want to talk about real quick too.
But politics in the state of Israel.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
All right, gentlemen, let's hunker down.
The website, there's like a hall of fame
for the mensch on a bench.
Did you see this?
No, I didn't see this.
So it's basically like, at first I was thinking like,
you know, it's like all Jewish celebrities,
but like, I don't think it is like David Krumholz is on,
on there's a picture of him holding,
but then like Whoopi Goldberg,
Jason Alexander is holding a mensch
and then Cody's on there too.
And I was like, can we get us on
or just at least you on there?
Yeah, I mean.
I feel like it's the mensch wall of fame.
And like, I don't know.
We're talking about wikis and caring about wikis.
This is what you're after.
The website says Neil reads all tweets and emails himself.
So.
You know what?
I believe it.
I mean, he can't listen to the episode probably.
He's probably gonna listen to this episode.
We've been a little too negative.
Oh, yeah.
Isn't it?
Oh, man.
It's paywall though.
All right.
I like the zebra from Zaraon.
Okay.
Why we do it?
If we say, because we're worried Jimmy Fallon might hear it
or that Neil Hoffman might hear it.
Right.
No, I really, now that I'm thinking
that he's listening to it,
I commend him for trying to get this off the ground.
It's, I mean, certainly look,
when I was a kid and the Hanukkah song
by Adam Simmler came out,
it was the greatest thing that ever happened in my life.
Sure.
When you are, you were so starved.
There's so much Christmas stuff
and there is so little Hanukkah stuff.
Right.
And so the idea, even if it could use some improvement,
the fact that there is anything to get
that's like a Hanukkah thing,
it's a good thing.
Now, is there room for improvement?
Yeah.
But.
But that's what, it's productive and forward thinking
that you're saying any of this.
This is not a doom thing.
We're not even remotely.
We've been punching up Mention on the Bench.
We haven't said, just throw the whole thing out.
You just create a whole new thing.
Absolutely not.
So he's got something.
He's got something.
The Christmas could evolve and grow.
And when there's the theme park land
and the animated shorts and you on the website,
then they'll really be cooking with gas.
Yeah.
I do, the last thing I'd like to say
is that there's an article from last year
that the headline is,
Hanukkah's Mention on a Bench is safe from COVID.
That's good.
Says creator, Boston native, Neil Hoffman.
And it's been.
And he said, we're very thankful that like his friends
of the magical variety,
we have found that elves and Santa and Menches are immune
because Dr. Fauci said that Santa was immune.
Anthony Fauci, the nation's leading infectious disease
expert confirmed that Santa is immune to COVID last week.
That happened.
I guess it did.
NORAD also said it will continue its tradition
of tracking Santa this year as he travels across the globe.
Despite being immune, Mention on a Bench
is being an example to non-magical children
by practicing safe guidelines.
So I just want to make everyone aware that in canon,
Mention cannot contract COVID.
That's canon according to the creator.
Incredibly powerful.
So he has some power.
That does make me want to see a line of people with COVID
all cough in his face and him just sit there with a smile.
That's, yeah.
Doesn't affect me.
I'm fine.
I'm a little skeptical of this claim
because in some of the ultra orthodox communities,
they've been resistant to vaccines.
You weren't the most co-operative
with the social distancing and many of the guidelines.
So I'm a little worried that he's just going around
till I'll never find him.
He's immune.
Maybe this hasn't been 100%.
It's a what's his name?
Not a wild about-
Situation.
Aaron Rodgers.
Aaron Rodgers, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, I'm immunized to it.
Don't worry about it.
We said non-magical children, but I am a magical child.
I always have been, so I'm fine.
Right, right.
Wow.
All right, well, thank you so much for doing this deep dive.
May you remain magically immune yourself.
Thank you.
And thanks for the donuts.
You survived podcast the ride, Evan Susser.
Thank you so much.
Exit to the gift shop.
Anything you'd like to plug?
When does this come out?
Soon.
Still within the, there's only a few more lights to go
on the antlers.
For any listeners who also get the Doughboyz Patreon
on December 7th, my investigation of a hot dog transgression
between two friends, it's called Man Bites Dog,
where one friend ate another friend's hot dog,
it was brought to the attention to the Doughboyz,
and I've done a deep dive investigation,
and it comes out December 7th on the Doughboyz Patreon,
and then I will be available later for everyone.
Yeah, you described this to me a couple of weeks ago,
and it sounds like you did a ton of work.
It's quite the ordeal.
It is quite the ordeal.
You said the phrase hot dog transgression,
and Mike looked right at me.
I don't know anything about, I am not involved in this.
No, I know, I just wanted to see what you're like,
if your face lit up, or you like fell out of your chair.
I'm intrigued, certainly.
Yeah.
Well, hey, that's great, yeah,
go subscribe to the Doughboyz Patreon,
and maybe they need your help more than ever
in this holiday season.
Maybe stick around there through the month of December,
you might hear some other familiar voices.
That's right, that's right.
Something to plug in.
Oh!
What's that?
Oh, you guys.
Yeah.
No, I don't know, I just did it a few weeks ago.
It's Scott and I, is that a rune, can we rune it?
I think that's fine, yeah.
Yeah, I think it's okay.
Did we tell you that, Jason?
Are we telling you this now?
We did it together, because you had just done it,
apparently, like that was, I guess.
They were very explicit.
This sectioning off is only because Jason has just done it.
I have, I had just done it, yes,
but I didn't realize you guys, I mean, that's good.
We're catching up with your Doughboyz numbers.
Yeah, sure.
But maybe everybody's on together.
Well, look, this is great,
everybody's crisscrossing Patreons all month long,
and keep it tuned to this one that you're already on,
Podcast the Ride the Second Gate
for three bonus episodes every month.
Hey, happy Hanukkah, everybody.
Happy Hanukkah.
Merry Christmas.
Most important.
All right, thanks guys, yay.