Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast contains company issued khaki shorts, regal but imposing owls,
and madcap animal bra hijinks.
It's Universal's Animal Actors on Podcast The Ride.
Hey everybody, welcome to Podcast The Ride.
My name is Scott and I am a podcaster trainer here at the podcast.
Now you might not know that a lot of our podcasters are actually rescue podcasters.
They were brought to a shelter and we put them to work reading ads for online therapy
and bitcoin exchanges.
You want to meet a couple of our podcasters right now?
All right everybody, give it up.
Let's meet a few of our stars.
Say hello to Jason and Mike everyone.
It's Jason and Mike.
That's right.
All our podcasters today were aimless comedy loafs who were rescued from their aimlessness
and given a microphone to talk into and all sorts of Ponzi scheme-esque startups to advertise
for and aimless conversations to have for hours on end.
See look at that.
Jason's doing incredible.
He's speaking at a very advanced level, an advanced amount of cynicism which is what
we look for in our podcasters is what we try to breed.
Right and Scott's slipping me a fun-sized Mr. Goodbar because I did a good job.
Very good.
Here you go boy and let's see how Mike does.
If he gets a treat.
Mike can we say our name?
Can we say hello?
Yeah my name is Mike.
I'm a rescue.
We are trying to work the McGruff out of him.
Many podcasters start with a base McGruff voice and we see if we can kind of massage
that away.
Can you try saying your name in a regular way?
Hello Michael.
This is Michael.
Very good.
Thank you.
That is very good.
That's very listenable, very normal and for that we give you a treat which for you is
a foot high Ninja Turtles plastic figurine.
Wow its head is the same size as my head so I can kiss it in a realistic way.
Wow.
Thank you.
It does have tongue.
You can go all the way with it.
Right and the tongue is warm.
That's what's really nice about it.
Well how about that.
We are off to the races.
We have the energy that you find in every edition of Universal's Animal Actors Show.
A stalwart attraction.
I don't know how long it's been running in Hollywood.
They don't chart these things as well in Hollywood.
Universal Hollywood stuff just was one day.
It just evolved.
It sprung up out of the ground like a plant.
In Florida they track these things and this is an opening day attraction.
In Florida the show where you go see your favorite animal stars of stage and screen.
Yeah it may as well have been like it may as well have opened with the studio before
the theme park I feel like where they were just you would like wander in and somebody
would be like hey you want to see a hawk?
You want to see what the hawk just did in the sound stage?
And like that's where like it's almost like a Mrs. Knott chicken like a roadside attraction
first.
It was there before the park.
I saw the date of 1970.
Oh okay.
So I'm not 100% sure.
I saw this on the page for Animal Planet Live which was the short lived name for these shows
for a brief period of time.
They classified as Animal Planet Live just by that not having been the name.
I regard it as like an unpleasant era.
You get those 2000s fonts going which I'm usually persnickety about.
Yes.
There's this show is going by a number of Animal Actors stage, Animal Actors on location,
Animal Planet Live.
Yeah.
All very similar shows.
Like I'm kind of an annoying pedant sometimes with this stuff of like well this is different
than this.
I was like well even I have to even I will condense this one down to Animal Actors, Universal's
Animal Actors.
That's enough.
That sort of says it.
Yes.
The current name explains what all of them are.
That's what we're focusing on today which I'd like to say at the top here.
So this is the first main feed episode of December.
And December we sort of usually wind things down right?
We're getting to the end of the year.
We always take a little Christmas break, a little winter slumber.
So you know I feel a little sleepy, a little lazy.
Me too.
Because we're getting down to there's only a few more episodes left.
We're just going to sort of like sleepwalk through those and then we'll get the podcast
done for the year.
Completely phone it just a few.
Wrong.
Incorrect.
What?
We guys, we are, I have an idea.
I'm having it right now.
What if we didn't just do a few.
What if we did too many?
What if we went out for the year with an unnecessary amount of effort?
Isn't that the podcast the right way?
You're suggesting we hit the big red button and make ourselves even stupider.
Like you're suggesting we give ourselves a little obstacle course like a dog running
through a little tunnel and a child you know as a you know.
We're barely ducking weave through cones.
That's how we're going to go out this year.
We're barely making it through December.
I almost dropped my phone cracking the zoom recorder destroying all the files on it.
Yeah we all we came in with so many maladies.
So many energy.
I was yelling before.
Stan Anilman's throwing us off.
But we got to fight through.
We got to muscle through because I think it's time in the last episodes of the year of 2021
to make good on a promise made in the first episode of 2020.
It is finally time for Country Bear Jambor Week.
Let's go out with Country Bear Jambor Week guys.
Are we in?
Are we going to do it?
We're in.
I thought you were about to say let's review Captain Kidd's buffet and I was going to
have to tell you something really tragic.
But Country Bears is good too.
Yes.
I thought it was interesting that that got.
Why did that suddenly end up in our feed as if we didn't know it?
I think the fate of Captain Kidd's was very clear.
Yeah.
It was confirmed this odd bad I assume buffet right outside the gates of Disneyland.
Very poorly reviewed and now it's gone forever.
I think it boomeranged a little.
I think people saw that it was closed.
Everyone talked about it for a day and then like the boomerang went out and then it came
back and someone else went, hey, wait a minute, it's closed.
And then there was a second day of it.
It got a second.
This happens every now and then on the internet.
Like something comes back.
For some reason.
Right.
It gets more of a swell this time.
So we pay our respect.
I mean, that's our that's in our in memoriam.
Twenty twenty one montage.
That's really remember what we used to do.
Like it's the start of the year.
Here's the things coming to the theme park world this year.
I think now maybe we have to switch the tradition to the in memory of everything we lost in
2020.
Glendale's creative.
Oh, yeah.
Something unpredictable.
No, it'll still be just not as I will play it over.
I'll play the Green Day song live when we do it to several times, multiple times and
then Green Day songs.
Yeah.
Most of the play, most of their discography over the course of the episode.
No, but look, yeah, we could mourn our losses for the year or we can go out on a fun note,
a celebration note, a jamber, a jamboree, a jamber week.
And that's what we're going to do.
So the last week of new shows for December will be Country Bear Jamber Week.
We're just we're excited to announce it.
To it. If we don't say it on the podcast, then maybe we don't finish it.
This is a we have at this point in time recorded some of it.
And I so far would say this in the other episodes before the end of the year, if Get
Back hasn't whetted your appetite for extremely long content, we're going to we're going to
blow get back out of the water in terms of our count.
Yeah. So get ready.
You got a lot to binge before December's through.
I had like an hour to kill the other day between like things I had to do.
And I was like, oh, what's the first episode of Get Back?
Because I thought it was a for each other.
I thought it went, oh, no.
I mean, I love it.
I'm a big fan of it.
And I'm sort of like I'm really stretching it out.
I'm like seeing if I can get a meal and two leftover meals out of every episode.
Like, can I split it into three nights?
Because I want to keep hanging out with my friends, the Beatles.
I'm done with it.
We did it. We did it the first three days.
Wow. Wow. Yeah.
Well, we got there's a lot of talking off air ice because I thought that maybe some
listeners don't like the constant classic rock talk.
There is maybe that strain in in the Disney plus.
We do the plus us up.
Yeah. So it's not. Yeah.
It's I was telling my very just that is we could do plus us up.
Get back in the new year.
It's you know, I was telling Mike Mitchell about how they have a Marvel characters,
like the new Marvel characters from Disney plus shows come in.
And he goes, oh, you mean like characters from Get Back?
And I said, yeah, like Mal Evans and Michael Lindsay Hogg are walking around
Avengers campus. Oh, they get they count.
They get to well.
Mitch opened up a good idea.
Linda Eastman. That's right.
And it wouldn't be it can't be Linda McCartney.
That wouldn't be time accurate.
Exactly. Timeline in the Beatles cinematic universe.
She's Linda Eastman. That's right.
And she's got the daughter from the first marriage or first really.
I forget which relationship she was married before, I think.
Yeah. So, yeah, it's they're all they're up for grabs because they're now in there.
So the Apple scruffs, the Apple scruffs, of course, the girls hanging out outside
of Apple Studios. I have to credit my friend Charles Ingram for really.
I think I let Apple scruffs come and go without really noticing.
And he well, he sent a voice memo in a text chain of Joe Biden talking about
the Apple scruffs.
Apple scruffs. We got to get good jobs.
Real jobs. My mother worked as an Apple scruff.
Bring back Apple scruff industry.
Thanks, Charles.
We were listening to All Things Must Pass on the way back from coming from San Diego.
And George Harrison on All Things Must Pass is a song called Apple Scruffs.
What? Really? Yeah.
Oh, that's why that phrase. That's what that song is.
Yeah. Oh, geez.
Yeah. Clearly, I'm no expert in that album. Interesting.
Yeah. OK. But all right.
So we've heard you listeners who don't like that.
What was just done?
You like us to talk about theme park things and we're going to.
We're going to talk about the country, bear jamboree incessantly.
It'll be the get back of the country, bear jamboree.
We'll cover all of the the ins and outs, the breakups,
when things got awkward,
when when Zeke almost walked out, like quit the right with the bear rugs,
but came back triumphantly.
It's all in. It's all in.
So, yeah. So get excited.
Yeah.
Are you ready? Are you ready?
You are already get ready.
You left a good pause there for people to yell.
That's what it was for.
Yes. Yeah. We don't have the luxury of an applause button like a show would.
You just have to assume if there's a little pause that that's what you're.
Yeah. Yeah. That's right.
Are you excited, cricket?
Well, we're here in the cricket again.
No, I was just saying.
I could cue it.
Cricket.
I guess the cricket doesn't know its name is cricket.
Were you doing that because of the animal actors?
No, no, I don't have a little cricket clicker or like a cricket feed.
Or have they ever had a cricket in the animal actor show?
Well, I could like do it's cricket noise on command.
It's funny you say that because there is a bit of internet that doesn't apply
anymore when it was Animal Planet Live.
There was an animal live website
that had like live cams on like tanks of bugs.
And the the wiki wiki entry for that said, like,
and that website is still active.
That website is, of course, not still active.
I don't know.
No one has updated the Animal Planet Live Wikipedia entry in some time.
No, no.
And there's no animal actor entry.
I was shocked to see that.
There's not. The thing that we're talking about today
doesn't have its own.
No, it's got a very slight fandom page.
OK, OK. The universal.
Similar to Mention on a Bench, which was just discussed.
Right. Second gate.
You can check that out.
But wow.
We well, you know, we're doing deep cuts.
We're doing our Yoko freak out style.
The non album stuff, because if we're talking about things
that don't even have Wikipedia pages, you know, we're in good territory.
Where do you start?
Where do you begin with the research?
If you don't have the Wikipedia page to begin with,
I guess where you dive in is watch the show.
The show. Yeah.
Which, you know, this show is I watched
pretty recent editions, 2020 or 2021 editions of this
Universal Animal Actors Show and
discover that it is exactly the same as the first time I saw it,
which would have been in 1991.
That is really the big takeaway of the show for me is that there's those gags
that have never changed one.
I know it is. They found a formula that works.
It makes the kids laugh. It makes the moms laugh.
And it's a funny thing to see an animal do.
And they it's that forever.
Yeah. And it always seems to hit.
The crowds always like it.
I feel like this is my family.
I always stop and see the show.
I'm trying to remember if I saw it when we were down.
I may have gone the day I just went to Universal.
Yeah. Before I flew out.
But I always like this show.
Yeah. The audience, I think I watched one from four or five years ago.
And the audience reacts like with honest to God shock
almost after every thing, after every trick.
Like it really worked.
These are like time tested tricks that work and like elicit a response
because we've all been to theme park shows where the audience is dead.
The audience is no response or like, I did.
I performed a lot of short solo.
I did a lot of bombed one man shows on wheels and my trip to work.
Yeah. But it seems like this one is always a hit.
Always a hit.
Yeah. The bird, you know, the smaller bird
flying to an audience member to take their dollar.
And then the animal handler pockets the dollar and then says,
is anyone over here? I have a 50 kills every time.
It's like there's so little evergreen comedy.
This always works.
The one I the one I watched, she said she said 20 20.
OK, I think so.
A little wiggle room. Yeah.
Fifty and 20 are both pretty funny. Yeah. Pretty funny.
Depending on how the economy is going, like it's it's scary to lose a 20.
I mean, you know, in boom times,
you have to go to 50, but right.
Everybody's going to make every 20 count depending on what year it is. Right.
So like if you go into work in the morning,
you check the newspaper to see how the stock market did that day.
The dollar. Oh, yeah. The dollar index.
If the dollar index is down, then you go for 20.
But if everything's doing well and the economy is surging, then you go 50.
Yeah, that's in the rule book, I assume.
This is the difficulty of being the host of this show
beyond that you have to work with animals,
beyond that you have to wear slightly embarrassing khaki shorts.
This is where in my universal years, I
I send my respects and condolences to the people in the show
who have to wear awkward khaki shorts, as I did.
This is the universal uniform for a number of things, I guess.
Were they you had to purchase your own?
They're not like universal administered shorts.
No, no, no. They give them out.
Oh, they do. Yeah, yeah. No.
Oh, OK. So it's not just check in and get my uniform every day from a,
you know, big dry cleaner, like complicated system.
They scan a code.
So you can't just bring your own khaki shorts.
They have they might know they aren't code khaki shorts.
Yeah, they're kind of uniform.
Interesting. That's actually I didn't even think about this,
because like when I used to work at the container store,
you'd have to wear like khakis and a polo.
And the polo was container store polo.
But you could bring in like as long as they looked about right
as far as the color of pant.
Oh, similar. That's like a that's kind of the level of school uniform I had was.
Right. Doesn't have to be this specific kind of like in this range.
Wow. So you all got your little khaki shorts
in the morning, as I'm sure I've said before, with the awkward
like crotch puff, just you would it would sound men and women.
It would you would sit in such a way where you just get this huge tent
and you're looking at this room of in the little lounge,
this 15 people sitting around all with the worst crotch puffs.
It's like the least glamorous anybody could look just like the founder.
Oh, God, who's the the universal guy that they're like?
And then back in 1916, so and so Carl Lemley,
Carl Lemley, almost said Irving Thalberg, but that's MGM.
They used to talk about and I was thinking you said founder.
And all I could think was Ray.
Yeah, that's what I was thinking, too.
I was like, oh, Ray Kroc, Jason.
Ray Kroc and the McDonagh brothers.
Yes. But no, that yeah.
What's his name?
I already forgot the name.
You said what's Carl Lemley was the one who wanted the Lemley theaters
that have nothing to do with universal.
He was the one who instituted the crotch puff.
He was the one who wanted that at Universal.
That was a tradition.
It was in style in the 30s.
Yeah. And they started things like Jodd Hoppers and the big Scott and stuff.
It was a sign that's the same puff.
No one can imagine what else is under there.
It was a sign of wealth, too.
Yes. Well, that's what it was really.
You could afford excess fabric.
Right. It's like that.
Well, I look at that rich gentleman over there with his large crotch puff.
He was people were very tight pants. Right.
Yeah. Less less fabric.
It's all I could afford.
Well, that's yeah.
So the tradition cares carried on at Universal Studios.
I like that as the general.
I mean, I think it's a style you see also at SeaWorld or any zoo.
Like I don't know at what point in time
khakis became synonymous with handling animals.
Right.
Like which is also how like your Joan Embree's dress, your your your
Erwin's. Yeah.
Yeah. The Irwin's. Absolutely.
Jack. All of them have like khaki shorts or pants.
I feel like shirts, too.
Sometimes shirts.
Is it to blend in?
Is it like a nature color?
My back is green. Safari.
Safari. I mean, it's usually lighter cotton.
It's usually flexible, but sturdy.
Yeah. No.
I mean, I'm sure the answer is like obvious and people know.
And they'll be like, you should have known this is why khakis were worn
by these animal handlers.
But it might be something about like dullness of like a muted color.
Like you wouldn't want to wear,
you know, bright zebra stripes in front of an actual zebra.
It might upset them.
They they might charge. Right.
Some animals you can probably wear their like fur pattern and they like it.
And then some they don't.
I think khaki chinos came.
That was a fashion design that started with the military,
British military,
and slowly got into civilian life.
Oh, hmm.
I don't have any.
I am khaki less for maybe the first time in a long time.
I don't have any khaki pants that I wear.
The only khaki pants I have still are the the ones I was issued as a tour guide.
Oh, well, were you supposed to give them back khaki for things like as I've
which has only been in sketches,
like a sketch on stage where I played a universal guy.
Right. For some reason, in my Michael McDonald Halloween video,
I'm in those khakis.
Wow. Really? Not sure why.
He must have been a khaki wearer.
Now, I don't remember why I picked the pants.
Why were you asked for oral history?
Were you supposed to give them back when you left?
Yeah, absolutely. Yeah. Wow.
And I kept the I kept the uniform and I will use it as wardrobe every once in a while.
Wow. So you are committing to a crime here.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Universal. I own.
I don't own. Obviously, I the opposite of own.
I have probably thirty dollars worth of universal property.
Yeah. Give up. Like, let's do a ransom note here.
Let's tell Universal what they have to do to get that clothes.
Those clothes back. Let me do a tour one more time and fill the tram
with podcast, the ride listeners. OK, great.
And you'll strip nude at the end of the tram tour and give it back
to the current president of Universal.
Oh, we're finally branching out into performance art.
Yeah. Yeah. So exciting.
The early days of UCB, man.
Downtown scene, man.
Hell, yeah. Like Yoko.
That's true. Yoko's territory.
Oh, yes. Yeah, yeah. Yeah, true.
Yeah, absolutely. Yeah. All right.
So, yeah, you have to let me fill up a tram with only listeners to the show
and to say whatever I want.
And then I get to show my penis and then you'll do the two lovers.
Yoko, John picture with the president of Universal
of the theme park or of the movie studio, which president?
Well, we'll have to negotiate.
Terry, figure that out.
Do you ever see an interview with a guy named Terry Koo?
I have. Yeah.
Theory, go it not.
It's really I don't know.
I mean, that's how it's spelled.
But I think it might be pronounced in a weird, you know, not outspelled way.
Recently, going around because at the IAPA conference
in Orlando, they asked what his biggest career regret was.
And he said, not telling management not to build Fast and Furious supercharged.
Wow. Like he admits to that.
Really? Currently in charge.
Room lost it like the room loved it.
Yeah. Geez.
So he's cool. Yeah, he is.
So he would take the photo with you naked.
Yeah. So he probably likes the Beatles, too.
Yeah. I appreciate the nod.
Yeah. Mm hmm.
So I'm am I Yoko?
Am I like I have to cling to him essentially?
No, Yoko was clothed.
John was John was clinging.
Oh, John was nude.
Yoko had clothes on and John was clinging to.
Oh, so Terry gets to keep his clothes on. Easy.
Yeah, that's why.
Just let me a naked man. Yeah.
Yeah. Blowing any universe.
We're going to get quietly removed from the press email.
Oh, they're cool. The social media tweeted us. Remember?
Oh, that's right. They acknowledged the the city.
So the sector keeper is universal cannon.
They probably own it now.
Whatever. By doing that.
Yeah. All right.
Well, that's another you have to give us the sector keeper back and let me do.
I've got a lot of ransom now.
It's all building up.
This is the point where an animal handler would have a spray bottle of water.
And they go like the comedy.
The comedy guys are trying to find reasons to get naked on a stage.
No, no, no, no.
Dad, yeah, doesn't work as well anymore.
Might have flown in 2005 for the CBA today.
At that that that to bring back to the animal actors, you know, you were saying,
regardless of your feelings on khaki pants, I always liked.
I thought they had a cool little utility belt and a walkie talkie.
Like I was like, oh, they got a little utility belt.
I've like clickers and treats and stuff.
Mm hmm. Clickers and clickers and treats. Yeah.
Well, do we know what the treats are?
Is there is just like little meat treats.
I'm sure it's a little meat packer kibble or something. Yeah.
Yeah. Probably. They don't say, though, I don't think in the show.
It's just a little I don't know.
No, there's training treats. Right.
Like, yeah, yeah, those little like circles or little little balls.
Sure. Well, Fanny full of treats. Mm hmm.
I guess like, you know, I think the show is is a lot of fun
and we should talk about our fair little moments in it.
I think are you guys what percentage of you is is uneasy
with just the animal training nature of it?
Like, does that put you off a little bit?
Do you feel weird about these animals having to do this stuff?
I mean, like, obviously, there, if they had free will,
they wouldn't be performing 15 shows a day or whatever.
It wouldn't be flipping signs to
signs that say ban bacon. Yeah.
Kind of thing. Ethically, that is an interesting question,
because like with with SeaWorld, like Shamu, whatever Shamu,
like they shouldn't be in tanks. Mm hmm.
Like it's a lot more of a like, well, this is not where
this is not a comfortable environment for. Yeah.
These the sea life.
But this is a I don't know. It's different.
It's a little different here, but still like, I don't know.
It's a good question.
Like, do I feel that the dog is having a good time?
Like getting applause.
You know, it's where I think that the the dogs,
I think dogs enjoy it because dogs like doing like little tricks
and getting applause that seems like in the nature of dogs.
I maybe I brought it up because I was I'm looking at cats doing tricks.
And I'm like, this is I ain't never met a cat who wanted to do
anything that anyone asked.
Yeah, I there's I think there's a reason there's only one or two cat.
There's like a limited number of cat moments in this show.
Yeah, yeah. I the one of the first things where we hung out, Mike,
was that that sketch that you were in at Conan, the cat controlled.
Yes, Shubhaka piloted decoyed Shubhaka.
Right. A video about that Andre Dubashe wrote, where if you don't want to go
to a Halloween party, you get a Shubhaka costume and put a bunch of cats in it.
Pilot it like a spaceship and they go to the party and your girlfriend
thinks you're in the suit. Right.
And you can look this up.
Mike is the star of it. And I directed it.
And it involved having to have a bunch of cats in the part you weren't in.
The whole morning was like, OK, so we'll shoot out the cats.
We'll do the cat part.
And there's a bunch of cats and little like little like spaceship units
inside this Chewbacca costume.
And I just remember like, oh, God, I've never hated a shoot more.
Yeah. Being around cat wranglers, which is a fake thing.
Cats cannot be wrangled.
Yeah. It's just click city.
Just click, clack, click, clack.
All the treats everywhere are disgusting.
Like we're little cat food plops.
So it smells bad.
And you see it on the props and like I and then like, you know,
somebody like waved their arm too big or something.
And then the cat trainer went like, hey, there's a dog creature.
You do not do that.
You do not dare. They are scared.
You understand we're all getting screamed at.
Yeah. Cat trainers.
It was just like, boy, do I never want to be in this scenario again.
Funny you bring that up because Jason Sheridan and I worked with cats last year.
Yes.
Hmm. On a Nickelodeon show.
You did both of you.
It's a real brief little thing.
Shot in and out in like less than an hour and stuff.
Yeah. Well, we were security guards.
Yeah. The cats could not have.
What the hell is this?
Have we not talked about this? No.
Well, there's like, we'll find it.
We'll find it and rip it.
It's a real quick.
But I had a similar observation because there were cats.
And I was like, these cats barely listen to what they're told to do.
Like they had like plans for the cats and the cats were not interested in the plans.
And I was like, this can't be good.
Like, and it's just like, and it was like, all right, here's what they're going to do.
And then it was like take six, seven.
Their cats are not doing this.
OK, well, what are we going to do?
We're shooting here. Blah, blah, blah.
So why does anyone even let the cat
trainers show up on the set and stay mum about that?
They know there's going to be five unusable take no matter what they're shooting.
At least that many. Yeah.
And they know it and they're letting it happen.
All right. So how long before the jig is up?
Because I won't get hired anymore if they figure out cats can't be trained.
Yes, the whole thing is done the whole job.
But yeah, I don't know.
I think they should just use cat puppet.
Like they should use the Tunesys, the driving cat puppet.
Anytime now they need a cat. Yeah.
That's a really old reference now that I'm realizing I'm saying it.
It's from 30 years ago.
Mm hmm.
But yeah, it was a puppet.
So, yeah, as far as animals, I also think we're in a weird
transitionary time of thinking about ethical treatment of animal.
Like I'm I will still eat meat.
I'm trying to eat less of it still.
But I feel like in who knows, 20, 50, 70 years, you look back and go,
we were making animals do what at Universal Studios every day.
Right. What? Yeah.
There's a lot of that with animals, I think that'll still evolve.
There's so many dogs in rescues.
I kind of understand that when you start getting into birds of prey
and pigs and stuff, I mean, I guess there's pigs in rescues, too,
or farms or whatever. Mm hmm.
Yeah, it gets a little confusing.
And then the other thing to consider is like, I've heard stories
from anyone who has worked at any theme park or any chain.
You hear stories about corners being cut or like, oh, we didn't have enough staff.
And just hoping to God that is not the case with the animals.
Oh, that everybody's taken care of.
Yeah, I think there's a lot of state and federal regulation with working with animals.
So I think that you kind of have to follow the rules a little more strictly.
Yeah. I mean, there are like just seeing animals personalities
like Edwin, our dog Edwin would not be pleased to have to do this.
And you can imagine like, you know, there's certain dogs
that are the friendliest dogs, they love running around, they love doing so.
So I'm sure it depends.
I'm sure it varies from animal to animal.
Exactly what the enjoyment level is.
So Edwin will not be appearing in a live show if we're the next time.
When live show he well, if it's live via satellite and he can like sit in the sun,
because that's maybe his favorite thing to do is find a window
and sit in like a hard sun, like a sunbeam. Yes.
So are you agreeing that's your favorite thing, too?
I don't mind.
I mean, Garfield loves to sit outside in the sun.
Yeah, he gets very energetic and we've trained.
Like he can do he loves to play and we can.
I think we've trained him to go like up up and like jump, jump,
you know, standing on his back legs and like put his front legs on us.
But then he needs he also likes to like sleep for a good two thirds of the day.
It seems like so we're on and off two thirds of the day.
Have a big burst energy and then sleep for like two hours. Right.
You know, like you doing the podcast.
Yeah, basically like doing the podcast.
Hey, I'm feeling great.
I'm so happy to hear us all talk about having the December wind down,
you know, crutch crutch feelings going on, because I was like,
well, this makes me feel less insane. So you like the fake out part
where I say we're just going to settle into the end of the year.
I did. I did get on his nightcap like like an animal trainer
standing behind an actor holding a treat up. I got fooled.
I got fooled. You got me to do what I wanted.
What? Huh? I'm looking this way.
What do I get it because I'm looking this way?
Yeah. So, I mean, all that being said, we have no we don't know anything about
the what's involved in the show, and they certainly present a good face of that.
Yeah, they do push the rescue animal situation.
Right. They work with dogs and shelters and they push that at the end of the show.
As you're leaving, they say, you know, if you're looking to adopt
those sheltered messages seem very good.
Heather, it's very, yeah, really gentle.
And my point I was trying to make earlier was it's not the same situation
where like the dog is being exclusively kept in a
like a four by four cage for most of its life.
I assume I'm just saying, I think we really don't know.
We really don't know. You're right.
I guess we really don't know.
But I think it's at least a little bit different than the like sea world situation.
If you get into that line of work at this point, like you have to be
passionate about animals and they come in from you would think so, because it is.
And now I did. I don't know in the 1940s.
Maybe I do know. I bet.
Oh, you know, yeah. Film was quite awful.
There's an Earl.
I think I've even said this on the show before.
There's a I guess it's like an old Errol Flynn Robin Hood movie
where there's a stunt where somebody jumps out of a fake tree onto a horse.
And it's like 10 feet in the air.
That doesn't feel good for the horse.
I mean, it doesn't feel good for the human, but the human knew what he was doing.
At least the horse just has like a fucking weight
to fall from 10 feet in the air on it.
Like, that's not good for the horse.
Sure. So, yeah, no, we do know what it was like, especially in the old days.
Yeah. The one thing associated with there
should kind of tangentially is associated with Grinchmas is happening at Universal now.
And they always have a Max.
Well, they always have Max. Yes.
Few Max's. And then they always say these these will all be adopted
at the end of the throughout the season or at the end of the season.
I met Max. Yes.
Remember my exclusive interview with Grinch a couple of years ago?
I have not been invited back for some weird reason.
You won't be now after I guess that I want to get naked
next to the head of Universal Creative.
I don't even I'm not even sure who it is.
There's so many shifting someone left, someone took over people moving around a lot.
Well, whoever it is, I'm getting naked on them over at Imagineering.
You're going to two virgins that guy.
That's right. Hey, pal, I'm going to two virgins you.
OK, I was warning you.
Shump up on him.
All right. Please escort that man out of city.
Well, take his shirt and away.
He said enough.
I already did the 19 part series about everything in city.
He's definitely had enough.
This guy doesn't need to be here again.
That's like that's like a horror movie.
They'd be like, well, is he a universal fan?
He's done 19 episodes about the shopping mall.
And they'd be like, oh, my God, like, let's get a restraining order,
which is really what they should say about all three of us.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, definitely. Yeah.
Let's you know, we're working our way through.
We've done so many universal attractions.
It's like, yeah, we're almost getting down to the end with with Hollywood stuff.
But there's plenty in Florida for sure.
The only thing to do is to do them all again.
Art to every single thing. Part two.
The guy who started the show, who like put it in place
and is a big pioneer in animal training in general for movies is named Ray Berwick.
He's a pioneer in using positive reinforcement to get animals to perform.
He created shows for the San Diego Wild Animal Park,
and he he produced this show initially in the 70s,
which seems like, you know, he and he was working in film in the city.
So he worked on I think first was Birdman of Alcatraz
with Bert Lancaster and then the birds for Hitchcock in 63.
And a quote from this guy in my work, I've trained more than 25000 animals
and I've only lost one in an accident.
And you go, oh, that's nice.
Those are pretty good numbers.
Then he keeps going.
One of the birds for the birds was crushed by a wagon.
OK, well, you know, the first part was the stat might have been nice.
I know about the bird and the birds.
But that being said, like you'd think just like naturally,
just crew members would be stepping on them.
It's the birds. There are so many birds in the birds.
Yes, there are a lot of birds.
So only one is that that ain't bad, especially in the old days.
Yeah, I'm sure the birds had been filmed in 1911.
Then birds would have made it out.
The stat 25000 and he's only lost one.
They would have lost 25000 birds.
Yeah, I feel like film sets back then are just the whole ground is just cigarette.
But right.
Yeah, they can't shoot the ground in old movies
because they're all cigarette.
But one clean footstep.
Anywhere the birds land, they get singed. Yeah.
No, but Berwick made sure that things were comfortable here.
And if this thing did start in the 70s, then that might
it might make sense why the show still feels like the comedy of the 1970s.
Yeah, I think in a bad way.
No, it's fine.
It's age is very old sitcom or even like the tale
and like memories of broad broad vaudeville, like old guy.
It kind of like that.
You know, the kid.
This is the one the dollar trick I always remember.
And then I always remember they bring a kid on stage
and they're like this.
Think of a clothing item.
This dog is going to go fetch it. Yeah.
And sometimes they go like, oh, did you think of a hat?
Yeah, he got the hat. Good job.
Think of another one.
And then it's inevitably like bathing suit top or bra or something.
And then dogs are pervert.
Yeah. Or the boys are pervert.
I guess pervert and then an orangutan in a towel or a little dog hopping out
on it in a towel.
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
A lot of great public domain like comedy music cues.
Yeah. Yeah. Stock library cues.
But also like the the
what's the what's it called? The peewee like,
didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't.
It's nice to hear that.
Well, a bunch of animal hijinks go on.
Yeah. That sequence.
Yes, a classic.
I think that while I don't remember, maybe I guess I think it was always a dog
in that main role and then yes, an orangutan who would go
who would come out in shower gear and shower cap.
I think that's the big change in terms of,
you know, animal equities, whatever you want, safety, whatever you want to call it,
is they stopped in both parks.
Universal stopped working with primates in 2014.
So because that's really the way I remember the show,
is that like multiple monkey appearances and they stopped doing that.
PETA, I think, got them to stop.
There was like a swinging, a rotating like jungle gym kind of thing
that a monkey wouldn't implement and they were like,
you would see if we could swing all the way around and they get cheered on.
And it's yeah, it was I was surprised to learn that they
that they stopped working primates because I that's those are a lot of my
strongest memories and probably the most clear memory of the show is like the
it's the physical comedy routine between the monkey and the the trainer,
where there's like smacks on the back and like sounds like like,
what do you mean?
Hey, how could you do that?
The crowd to be nice to the people.
And and then the impressions, the impressions is the big thing.
And this is what they can't do with another.
They can plug and play other species for some of these gigs, but they can't
push the monkey's lips out and say, look, everybody Mick Jagger.
Right.
Well, for sure, the main thing I remember.
Yeah, that's the big one.
Yeah.
And I think I've only seen this show in person, I think once.
And I do remember that because I think it was before they got
they stopped doing the the monkeys or primates.
I think in Florida, it's in a good spot.
If you are going like you want to break from rides
where like it's kind of between Simpsons and ET.
So like where if you're having a slow start today, you do ET, you do
Animal Actor, you know, as you like complete the loop, you know,
you're saying it's a good spot to rule.
You're saying it's something in the layout.
It's a good spot for it.
I think it's a good spot.
It's also good if it's just like everything's crowded or you just need to sit down.
We're like, you know, we're like everyone in your party is like,
can we sit for a while?
Can we do this? Because it's it's outdoors, but it's pretty shady.
You know, it's covered and all.
Little amphitheater amphitheater of both these spaces, though,
since we bring in the amphitheaters, huge plots of land.
Yeah, a little surprising these shows are still going.
I mean, the the they the play into the movie,
how the movies are made element of the Universal parks.
But man, they take up a lot of real.
It's a little surprising they haven't been pulled in.
Yeah, yeah, really. In Florida, it's mainly just I guess
just that they have the room in the second park.
Yeah, they don't super need to.
Yeah, Hollywood where it's a little more cramps,
but maybe they can't fit a full ride in there necessarily.
So although they got they they made a lot of that
secret life of pets.
Yeah, I was going to say, and that's two stories.
So, yeah, I'm sure there's something.
Yeah, maybe they'll do it when Mick Jagger dies, when they when there's no longer
the when the the point when the impression isn't relevant right anymore.
I guess they can't do it because the they're they're gone.
So but they probably thought about it.
They probably thought about just get ending it when that joke got cut.
Yeah. Yeah. Why even do the show anymore?
Right. That's what we're here for, isn't it?
This lips thing.
And there's no other celebrities to do this with.
Who else? Right.
Are there? Oh, I think there was maybe a time where they switched it to Angelina
Jolie. Oh, really? OK.
Who else has big lips?
Because I think they tried to play.
Smith. That was a very top of reference for a while.
And you know, 20 years ago, that was good. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah.
I think they just lucked out that they picked somebody who remained relevant
and around for so many decades, because that had been type.
If it was a big lips celebrity who passed in 1973, then what do you do?
Right. So screwed.
Everyone, it's the lips from the opening of the Rocky Horror Picture Show.
The disembodied lips, you know.
Yeah, that would have again.
That would have been great 40 years ago.
I don't know. It may have remained popular and it's been showing way.
They do the animal actor show at midnight at Halloween Horror Night.
All the animals are very tired.
Or it's creepier animal.
It's like nocturnal animals.
Oh, yeah. Sure.
And they don't shoe the like the the little poodle in the bra way immediately.
Like, that's the whole that's the beginning of the show.
All the animals are in human underwear.
Yeah. Yeah.
That's a that's a sultry show.
They just unleash raccoons into the audience.
The Rube Goldberg esque opening where like one hits and one lever and one does this is all.
Yeah. Ends with a barrage of raccoons aimed directly at the audience.
Somewhere in the Rube Goldberg, a bunch of like there's a confetti,
but you don't realize that the confetti is pepperoni and it's like a spice.
Pepperoni and it's like a sprayed all over the audience.
And like right when you realize it, when you pick one up, hey, is this oh, God.
And then raccoons are coming at you.
Yeah. Too late to do anything about it.
Too late.
So, yeah, they're not be careful of the midnight show, folks.
It feels like these are going to be here for long.
Like it feels like there's so much momentum.
Why would they get rid of these shows?
Yeah, I think so.
And they, you know, like like you said,
people still laugh at this stuff.
There's always new movies they can cross promote with.
We shove clips of Secret Life of Pets into it or, you know,
they actually have the animals from recent movies.
Now, this is I've always had this question about it.
When they say it's Lassie, when they say it's Beethoven,
whatever they were doing at the time, is this just the I certainly took it on faith as a kid,
that that is the real sitting Lassie.
I knew it wasn't the one from the 50s opening that I'd see on syndicated TV,
but it's the current owner of the Lassie throne.
Yeah.
But like, is it just we're just talking the same breed, right?
There's no especially in Florida.
They're not flying Lassie down.
I would think so.
I mean, the one I watched the one from a couple of years ago,
and they said this was the bird from Ace Ventura.
But that's not.
And I was like, is that?
Yeah.
And then they also that the hawk from 310 to Yuma.
The hawk from 310 to Yuma is a great.
Yeah.
Let's talk about some of these credits.
So yeah, we're just I'm just trying to figure out.
Yeah.
Are they just saying it's the same type of animal and they're just lying to us?
Oh, I see what you're saying.
Well, I think some birds can live very long.
Sure.
Yes, that's true.
So maybe it is.
Yeah.
But there was one.
Oh, another one was the pug, Rick the Pug from Men in Black.
Right.
Men in Black 2 is what they say specifically.
They they isn't that character in more than one or maybe?
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, it gets an expanded.
All of them into all of them.
Yeah.
So but that can't that's a that's from 2002.
There's no way that there's no way that it would be the same.
But there's no way that in 2021, the walkout music would still be nod your head.
Black suits coming.
And yet what is the walkout to but nod your head?
Black suits is coming.
That's great.
Jason getting pumped up.
I love it.
I watch one of them where the pug first off, if you stick a little bit black suit on any pug,
it's going to look like Frank from Men in Black.
And I think that's what I saw.
Like they did kind of the mad cap ending where like the animals are crisscrossing the stage
and the trainer comes out with just a pug in a black suit running by her who jumps up on
the one platform.
She goes, thanks for coming and just doesn't really acknowledge him.
And he just like hops up and sort of like smiles at the crowd.
I don't know why I'm here.
Yeah.
But are you happy?
I ran from backstage to my little mark here.
Very impressive.
Some of these dogs hitting their marks.
Very good.
Better than some actors I've met better than me.
Honestly, just hire Jason to do a dialogue scene, but don't make him run into it.
You're going to shoot right past that camera.
They'll put a piece of tape down and then take it away if they do a wide shot.
And I don't know if I'm supposed to go back.
Yeah.
If the tape is gone, how do you know where to go?
I don't think, you know, communication.
Well, if you're going to put, then if you put Jason in something, do it like in this show
where like there's a little stack of rocks and that's where you.
Little stack of rocks, pepperoni behind the camera or to the side of the camera.
So I don't look at the camera.
Pepperoni and a dollar bill.
That's all Jason needs to work.
They tried to do a 20, but it kept fading from excitement.
The swelling salts.
When you see the 20, you see the 20 again and you pass out.
Lost our sunlight.
Shit.
Lower money this next time.
Real quick, can I just shout out some of my favorite animal actors?
Please.
Yeah, great.
Crystal the monkey who was in Dr. Doolittle and Night at the Museum.
Do you remember that?
And all the other roles.
Well, community.
This is what I like.
I like animal actors that have multiple roles.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know what I mean?
Like Bart the bear.
Yes, exactly.
Bear from the edge.
Moose was the dog on Frasier, but also in My Dog Skip.
Oh really?
These weren't necessarily in the show.
You're saying these are just.
No, these are just in general.
I just, this is just a fun.
Esteemed animal actor who some of which could have been in the show.
I feel like they got prominent.
Right.
What else are they going to do?
I didn't realize this.
And again, they could be lying to me and who knows.
The dog common on Full House was also Air Bud.
What?
Wow.
That makes sense.
Yeah.
Wow.
That really blew my mind.
Geez, that's a major, major talent.
Bart the bear is your, you just said Bart, right?
Yeah.
Was in White Fang and The Edge.
Wow.
And a movie called The Bear.
I don't even know what that is.
But there was Bart.
If it was that bear in the, have I ever talked about the Boy Meets World episode I love where they
there's escalating pranks happening between the gang.
I don't think so.
And then like there's, you know, there's one that's a little crazy, but then
I believe it's Corrie and Topanga and maybe Sean.
And they realize that they're stuck to their chairs in a college lecture hall.
And like, okay, so they glued us to our chairs, some prank.
And then suddenly a bear shows up at the door and they launch out of their chair.
Oh, they get, they get honey dripped on them as well.
Okay.
So they know that bears come in right form.
So they, they jump out of their chairs.
Some of their clothes rip off and they dive out the window.
And then there's a little sitcom spin around transition and it cuts to Mr.
Feeny and extreme closeup.
And he says, a bear.
It's my favorite moment of him, William Daniels.
Uh-huh.
But then I'm running the math of like.
Is it Bart?
I don't, it could have, I don't know.
It could have been Bart.
I just mainly am like, these college students,
like got the college to agree to have a bear walking through the hall for a prank.
Yeah.
That's pretty intense.
They meant, they meant business with that prank.
You got to find out who, which bear that was.
But I wanted to also reveal here, there was also Bart the bear too.
Whoa.
Like Gallagher.
Yeah, Gallagher.
Yeah. His brother that stole his name and worked as well.
Fooling people.
He was in game of Thrones.
He was in, we bought a zoo.
Wow.
Into the wild.
Yeah.
So, so we bought a zoo would have been a big, because universal gets these kind of like,
when they get a big multi-animal movie and they can plug it in this show, you can tell.
Right.
It's a ground swell of excitement.
It's new blood into the animal actor show.
They would have like freaked out if that was their movie, but I don't think it was.
They're still banging the drum for Evan Almighty.
Yes.
So many of these.
Yes, a lot of them.
Evan Almighty.
I know it was a Noah's Ark story, but man, those birds, they got a lot of the Evan Almighty birds.
You know, it's, it's hard, you know, when you're working actor and it's like,
you know, my last credit was over 10 years ago.
So you're just like, you're hanging your hat on like, yeah, I was in Evan Almighty.
Like.
This bird doesn't even look like their head shot anymore.
Some reason.
Bailey was, Bailey, the dog was in a dog's purpose.
Oh, wow.
It's really weird that they mentioned a dog's purpose.
Cause that was on the universal lot that they got in trouble for making a dog.
Swim.
Yeah.
I don't remember the specifics of it.
I can't remember exactly on the lot, but there was a thing where the dog was fine,
but it was like, oh, you did a lot of takes in a row of that dog swimming.
Like, are you, that dog was in that water.
For two.
There was like a damning video.
I think.
Yeah.
So yeah, I don't, I feel like maybe you leave a dog's purpose out
or people that excited about a dog's purpose anyway.
I don't know.
Does America still have a dog's purpose fever?
Was there a sequel?
Like, wasn't there a second one in the series?
Was that the one where even though was that the Clint Eastwood racing movie?
What was it?
Clint Eastwood.
You know what I'm talking about?
Where the dog was like, I love to race.
And I know it was Kevin Costner.
Oh, what movie was that?
We talked about it on the show before.
Was it?
Kevin Costner is a dog who loves to race.
That's all I know about it.
I think he's the dog.
Voice Costner.
I'm Googling Kevin Costner racing dog movie and seeing what pops up here.
Is that one weird talking cat?
The art nine lives.
Nine lives is the space.
That's the space.
So yeah, yeah, screwed that.
We said his name.
He's going to appear.
The art of racing in the rain is the movie I'm thinking of.
And Kevin Costner is the voice of the dog Enzo.
And I don't think this is related to a dog's purpose, but in my mind it is.
The art of raising the rain is Kevin Costner talking, you know.
Similar.
Dog era movie.
Would you consider, let me ask this real quick question.
Would you consider Montecore of Ziegfried and Roy fame an animal actor?
Yes, right?
Absolutely.
Yeah, Montecore was the troublemaker.
Yeah, I think so.
Yeah.
But all the tigers in the show were actors, like they were doing.
It's kind of an animal actor.
Ziegfried and Roy is kind of an animal actor's thing.
It's just a different context for the animals performing.
Yeah.
So they were jumping through little hoops and stuff and fire.
I don't know, fire?
I've never seen the show.
I have an answer.
A dog's purpose 2017.
A dog's journey 2019.
Ah, okay.
There you go.
Sequel.
These are based on very successful books, by the way.
Right.
That's why they happen.
We're going to GAD in one of them, right?
Oh, you got GAD.
Dennis Quaid, Mark Helgenberger.
Betty Gilpin, you know?
That's a name I said on the tram a lot because we passed by the CSI stages.
So I remember when I was kind of getting warmed up and doing my very enunciative tour guide
voice that a good way to make sure that the pipes were polished was early in the tour.
You get to say, and Marg Helgenberger.
I always knew, do I have it or not?
How much gusto can I put into this?
Helgenberger.
Did you ever really like, what would you remember ever toying with
the lowest energy you could be?
Just to see what would happen?
Oh, not even as an experiment.
You just had to some days.
Oh, okay, sure.
If it was hot as hell.
Yeah, no, I knew how minimal I could do.
How can I do it with almost all clips, saying almost nothing,
acknowledging the crowd very little?
I wonder if I ever, did I ever read a book while I was doing it?
Certainly texts, dude.
Probably, but I bet everybody texts.
You could have booted up the Kindle app.
It might have been too early on for that technology.
I should have, I could read people part of a story.
I'd switch things up.
Sure.
You don't expect to hear chapter 13 of a Franzen book.
Yeah.
When you're out looking at the Spartacus square.
Right.
Uh-oh, stay in your seats, folks.
It's one of his famous uncomfortable sex scenes coming up.
I'm glad you knew something about Franzen.
I have no more to say.
As if there's no further that reference could go with me.
I know they're very thick and I somehow acquired a copy of the Corrections years ago,
and it is sat in a box.
But I know a lot of facts about his weird dealings and stuff.
Oh man, there's some sort of crazy first person essay written by, I believe, his partner.
I don't know if it's his long-time girlfriend or wife.
And I don't know if they're still together, but she doesn't need,
names her journey as a writer, and then she meets someone who's a little more successful
and very slowly through it.
I didn't know who it was about and I was like, oh my God, is it Franzen?
And very quickly, like, oh my God, it's Franzen.
Whoa, whoa.
It's a thrilling.
A little secret, like the primary colors of, you know who it's about.
Well, just the timing and the like, and then his book was selected for Oprah's Book Club,
but he didn't want that.
And it's like, oh no.
What am I saying?
Why am I going with primary colors such an old reference?
It's really the, it's the all too well.
This is the Taylor Swift.
We know who all too well is about.
Rat bastard.
We know.
We don't have to say it, but we know.
I won't even, I won't say his name.
I won't do it.
I have everybody did it.
Taylor.
Yeah.
Yeah, the Hawk from 310 to Yuma is a great credit.
Obviously the Evan Almighty credit comes up a number of times.
Dog's purpose.
Lady Hawk.
Do we very much miss Lady Hawk?
That's a old movie.
I'm like, I guess I know what Lady Hawk is.
Oh, Safari.
The one Hawk Safari from the Mummy Returns.
So Hawks must live a long time.
I guess.
Yeah.
How let me look up Hawk lifespan.
Wingspan.
What are all spans?
Hawk life.
The average Hawk's average lifespan is in the wild.
In the wild is 20 years.
So that's not crazy.
That's not that long.
Yeah.
But Mummy Returns is too old.
2002.
Yeah.
To still be working in a 2019.
Elderly Hawk is being forced to work.
Maybe I'm reconsidering what we were talking about earlier.
Let them retire.
Enjoy its autumn years.
Elderly animal actors really should be the name of the show if that's accurate.
Dex from a Blue Buffalo commercial.
When they name the commercials, that's very funny.
Iris and Olympus the Owls who were in Harry Potter, Bones, CSI, and a Geico commercial.
Oh, yes.
Yeah.
It's a big sequence in it now.
The last time I saw it in person where they take these giant owls around and just sort of like,
they don't really do tricks.
You just get to see them.
You feel the Harry Potter nature of them, the majestic nature of them,
and the music is very magical.
And they just are sort of walked up and down the aisles.
Yes, they're very regal looking owls.
Yeah.
Is this maybe a good time to tell the story of my most recent visits to this show?
Please.
It involves the hawks and the owls.
The story really is not just about seeing the show.
It's about taking my son to Universal for the first time.
So I had him solo.
Mom was away.
So I wanted to like, let's fill up the morning.
Let's do something big and fun.
I've been wanting to take him up there and we did it.
Pretty successful in general.
Now I've done it, but this was I think back in August.
And now I've done it a number of times.
He really likes it.
He loves all the big Universal attractions like the hundred empty chairs that he can push around.
Unthemed umbrellas that he can point at.
The unthemed stanchions in the corner of Harry Potter land
that don't even like look like an owl or something.
It's just regular like line separators that he just pushes around.
I could not tear him away from those.
He's just ignoring like,
like look, it's like snowcapped.
So there's a train over that doesn't care shaking the line dividers around.
I've really enjoyed.
I've liked taking him up there due to the lack of pressure.
I like Universal, but it's not like Disney where like, all right, now son, this is important.
This is Walt's.
This is you must appreciate this.
There's the universal.
All better off.
Yes.
Yeah.
All right.
Look at the lamp.
Look at the, I know you don't know the word lamp,
but you're going to stare at that thing because that represents the soul of the finest man.
Whoever was right.
Exactly.
So anyways, yeah, you could, you know, it's a little sillier.
I've, I've had a lot of fun.
And so I'm feeling really good.
Like I, all right, this is a successful just dad and son trip up to a theme park.
We're having a blast.
I got to, I got to get lunch in him soon, but not yet.
Well, you know what's starting.
Look what I'm passing by right now is the, is the animal actor show.
And at this point in time, one of his favorite activities was pointing at a bird and saying,
but so I figured, well, this is a great opportunity to point at birds and say, but this happens.
There's a number of opportunities in the show.
So I'm like, well, this is a little riskier because at this point in time, he's 16 months old,
I think.
And just any parents out there picture your current 16 month old or what your child is
like at 16 month old.
These sitting still abilities are probably not the greatest, but I think, you know what?
Any amount of this that he gets through is great.
It's, it's, it's fine.
And we'll just go in the back so that we can leave quietly and it won't be a problem
because you sort of like enter through like under the bleachers basically,
but we can just run out the back and it'll be fine.
So we sit in the very back row.
He's having fun.
He's dancing around.
He's ready for the show.
And then the show is about to begin and a universal employee very kindly points down
to the bottom, just like down there.
And I'm like, oh yeah, wait, I guess so.
There are a lot of much closer seats.
I shouldn't make him be in the back.
He should be up where the action is.
That's great.
So we get down there.
I take all my stuff.
I get him down there.
And then I realized, well, I have lost the escape ability, but that's okay.
This should still be fine.
I think he's probably in a great mood.
This is going to go fine.
Then there is an announcement like the show is about to begin announcement
where they say for the safety and comfort of our performers and our animals,
please remain seated at all times.
Uh-oh.
And I think, well, it shouldn't be a problem.
He's excited to be here.
I can't imagine that he will start acting up at the precise second that the big
dangerous birds start flying right over the audience.
He took him.
The hawk took him.
That's the story.
I know I've told recent stories about my son, but they're all made up.
He's been in the land of the hawks for God knows how long.
He took the hawk, took him.
Then you stood up and another hawk took you to follow and chase after him.
Get him.
That's why you want to do.
You know where he lives.
You bastards work together.
Take me to the mother nest.
So after a thrilling sky adventure, uh, no, it's just, you know, hey, look, I think I just
spoiled what the story is.
He's enjoying the basic things.
Those little animal hijinks, you know, the animals are getting ready for the show.
That's all great.
He kind of points at stuff.
But then bird stuff starts happening.
And of course, for the first time ever, he doesn't care about birds at the precise moment
that there are exciting birds in front of him.
He's chosen now to not give a shit.
He is much more interested in the bleachers and the bleachers that are next to me that
are the aisle.
And he's really starts running around reaching for other people's bags, yelling, blah, blah,
blah.
I'm very lucky, by the way, that when he freaks out, it's not like whiny, but like he's really
cute even in that.
But this is still the wrong thing to be doing.
And then I haven't seen the show recently, so I don't know about the owl parade.
I don't know.
Oh, yeah, the Harry Potter.
He's in the aisles and then they're about to do a march.
Oh, yeah.
Precession where they, by the way, are wearing the like falconers gloves.
Right.
So you know that these birds mean business if they have the gloves that you can't get
through because the talons could do some damage.
So I'm like, I gotta yank him out of the aisles in time for the owl parade.
And still he's just making a big fuss.
I'm like, this is not good for the owls.
This is not good for him or me or for the audience or the host up there.
This is going to start getting real bad.
I got to get out of here.
It's time to get out of here.
So I grab my bag and kind of like yank him.
And then I run down the nearest aisle that I can see and I immediately see a big rope.
And then right after that, the employee who kindly pointed to my new seat in the front
goes, no, no, no, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Don't stop.
And I'm just frozen and like, oh, okay.
And am I going to start getting the attention of the rest of the audience?
Hopefully not.
And I'm just like, what do I do?
Do I go back to my seat?
Just I'm just pointing frantically.
Where can I go then?
And then she's like with a deep annoyed breath.
Under, okay, go.
And somebody lifts the rope for me and I kind of barrel out of there.
I'm like, so now I'm moving with a pace because I'm stressed out.
Because we've gotten attention.
He's going a little crazy.
So I'm like going fast.
And then another person stops me.
So now we're like under where the bleachers and where the audience enters.
And with the speed that I'm moving, somebody puts out their hand.
No, stop.
And I freeze in my tracks.
And then like I'm given just hand signals that are like calm.
We have to be calm.
And that is because I am now in this little confined dark space under the bleachers that are
my baby and me and the Universal employee and the owls.
We are now right in front of the owls.
It is only us.
So we are staring right at the owls.
Now he cares about the owls because they're very close to him.
Now he's pointing.
Yes, very good.
Those are owls.
I am also noticing because I'm holding him and the owls are also kind of being held on the arms that
with their relatively similar heights, the owls are much bigger than my son.
Oh, man.
It's like way more.
And there's two of them.
This fight does not go well.
Oh, my God.
If a fight goes down.
So everybody just tries to convey calm.
And it's this little like, you know, they're waiting for another animal thing to happen
and keep the owls calm so that they can be returned to the wherever the owls go.
So keep them calm.
Babies should not be charging right into the owls.
But everybody gets on the same page.
We're all looking at each other.
I apologize profusely as much as I can, as quietly as I can.
And we're all just waiting.
Tension.
Please, owls, don't hurt my son.
Okay, you may go.
The owls go.
And now I sprint the hell out of there.
Oh, my God.
I don't want to be seen at the animal actor stage again.
And dad's trip to the theme park, which is supposed to be triumphant, now almost ended
in an owl turf war.
Wow.
I got a couple of things.
First off, when your son is older, he is at like 12 or 13 going to go like, hey, I had
a dream last.
Did I meet an owl when I was younger?
Not that it will be negative.
It'll just resurface like the image of like waving to a couple owls.
Did I do a seven minutes in heaven with two owls bigger than me?
That's nice.
As long as it's not like a Val Kilmer Batman Forever deleted scene with a giant bat and
he's got like a giant owl in his mind.
And then he decides to take on the form of the owl to fight crime.
Oh, jeez.
This is his origin story to become owl man.
Yeah.
We're perfectly set up.
All right.
So if all right listeners, if you're hearing this in the year, well, he's got to be old
enough to, you know, so in the 2030s sometime, probably a suited owl guy running through
the shadows could be my son.
Yeah.
The other thing is that this must be what they have hit upon as like this is the best
option to take the owls up the aisles back here for a second and then back to do they
live in a rookery?
Is that where else I, but confidence makes me think yes.
So it, uh, cause you can't be the first parent who's like, I gotta get, I gotta get this
one out of here.
Yeah.
I think this must happen every show, right?
Every show.
And I feel like there, there should be an announcement of like, okay, there's one moment.
Okay.
Don't move during this one part.
The other times the door is here.
If you have to scoot away, the door is here and just watch for flying birds.
That's a, I mean, it happens in theaters where it's easy, like in whatever Muppet Vision or,
or anything like a fill our magic, whether they say, or the captain, you know,
theater where they're like, yeah, this is where you leave.
Yeah.
If some, if you need to leave before the show's over.
And obviously that's a simple, that's a smaller place, but yeah, they really should,
if there's a chance that you're going to run headfirst into owls, you should know.
Well, boy, do I appreciate you putting any of the blame, not on me
for this situation where suddenly my son is face to face with owls that could demolish.
You didn't run on stage.
No, and you didn't get caught in the moment where the audience gets like
buzzed by like a flock of birds fly still probably like six feet, 10 feet above the audience.
Oh, that's right.
Yeah.
You get that little surprise.
They all fly out of that little door.
Yeah.
I'm just like, you know, it, I felt very like
Homer taking care of Maggie for the weekend, loses Maggie, his Maggie under the house.
I just very happy to like have mom return home and the son was not reclaimed by,
taken by owls in the one day that I had him.
How was your day, Scott?
No owls.
No owls, Aaron.
Oh, fine.
Owl-less.
Is how the day went for me.
What did you say?
Alice?
Yes.
Alice.
Normal owl business.
Oh, he's questions.
Who, who, why are you keep saying who stops?
Stop grilling me.
What is this?
Is this what, what band is this?
Owl City?
You never listened to Owl City.
Three licks, but the world may never know.
When can we do this?
When can we do this again?
This guy, why are you doing this again?
Who wants to know?
I've always liked this band.
What are you talking about?
Pick out any bet.
Fireflies.
Always eat Tootsie Pops and listen to Owl City.
So I made it.
Narrow escape.
You know, I, will I go to the show again?
Sure.
But today of a more appropriate age.
Yeah.
Right.
Wow.
I'm still fond of it.
I'm fond of the gay.
I, if we missed anything in terms of like the little, the little fun moments.
Yeah.
I mean, we, I mean, we talked a little bit about it.
There's a whole long, like kind of sort of ramp up to the show where they're doing a lot of.
Like a show busy things, like so and so to the set or.
Oh yeah.
Get in a wardrobe.
Yeah.
Like all the Hollywood stuff you would imagine you hear on a set.
And then it's like, oh, someone sows mocha latte.
And then it's like an animal walks around and that's like a fun little bit they do.
They're not, you're not going to see a dog or a cat with like a latte in their hand.
But yeah, there's a whole, it feels long also.
It feels like it's three to five minutes.
Maybe it's not.
Well, a it's a very long time to be listening to a techno remix of the pink panther theme.
That's also a good point as well.
Makes time stretch.
Is that the same?
Is that always been the case?
I don't know.
I.
The five year ago one was the pink panther theme.
Yeah.
Oh really?
I saw that a year ago.
So I don't know at least it.
When did techno get popular early 90s?
The universe probably adopted it circa 2007.
Yeah.
But yeah, that makes it last a while.
And then also this is true of the Jason, you described the sort of like everything goes haywire
at the end.
I think in any video you pull up, you end up with the awkward moment where the animals not quite
doing the thing.
And maybe they like, I was watching a little dog try to like grab a little
sign connector rope with its mouth.
Yeah.
I think like seven attempts were made.
Still stays eager, keeps trying.
I'm going to get it.
Audience starts to cheer him up.
But I like what that does for the pace where you're just like, boy, this is,
this is basically a sequence that has five actions.
Yeah.
It is taking seven minutes.
And I have seen it work.
I have seen every work, every, you know, every animal hit their mark perfectly.
But yes, a lot of recording ones by chance are the ones where it's like, oh, he missed.
The handlers are you see an arm like, no, go back.
Do it again.
It's okay.
Yeah.
It's it's not the most precise thing.
I was going to say this is really where like it would be, it would benefit them to have
puppets and stuff.
I guess maybe I'm getting ahead of myself here is that I really just want all the animals
replaced by puppets and like robots.
I don't want real animals anymore.
But you know, if we're going to do the bit with Hollywood and animals and stuff, I want
like a puppet drinking a latte and a cat puppet drinking a latte.
I think that's better for me, at least as a viewer.
I'll go back to that show a lot more if it's a puppet drinking coffee.
A realistic puppet.
Not even realistic.
Oh, really?
Okay.
It could be.
Oh, geez.
And this is really easy for them.
Yeah.
But I get it why an average person might want to see this.
But yeah, that's that's my personal preference.
But yeah, the start of the show is there's a lot of fun showbiz nonsense.
But yes.
What do you think the hit rate is?
50 percent perform performing like well or performing the task at hand?
Oh, I think a little higher.
I mean, 75 shows a day.
Yeah, maybe 75.
Yeah.
Okay.
But it's but they boy time has done a number to that.
See like a little Hollywood in jokes because, you know, you end up with like like, all right.
Where's the where's a champ?
Mr. Ratner's waiting for you.
Your costar, Mr. Spacey, has been on set for 15 minutes.
There are moments I mentioned evergreen moments earlier.
The the one bit where they bring out two dogs and the one does the obstacle course again,
hit rate not 100 percent pretty high 75 80.
But then the other dog is trained to make it look like he's peeing on the kid volunteer.
Right.
That always gets a big laugh.
Oh, yeah.
Right.
Yes.
But the dog doesn't pee.
He doesn't pee.
No, he is trained to lift a leg.
The universal symbol.
That has to have gone wrong once.
Surely.
The leg is up.
Like the dog is going to want to do its favorite once in a while.
If it's got a full bladder.
Also, the one who completes the obstacle course surely has at times gotten so excited.
It just starts peeing.
You never know with dogs.
Sometimes they're scared.
Sometimes they're cold.
Sometimes they have to go.
And sometimes they're just excited and don't know what else to do.
There's 300 people looking at me.
I got to show them something.
Check this out, gang.
Look what I can do.
I have one talent.
Yeah, that's again, that's where puppets would come in handy.
Then the pee blast could be purposefully.
Massive.
And not pee.
Something safe.
Water.
It can be that wine that the beetles drink and get back, which looks like urine.
Yes, that's true.
It either looks really urinary or really bright green.
I'm always like, what is this?
Beetle wine.
Yeah, the beetle wine I do.
Yeah, it looks gross.
I mean, they're drinking just 24-7, smoking 24-7 from morning to night.
I feel very validated as a white wine aficionado that white wine
fuels some of the finest work of the century.
Right.
So yeah, no.
What's grosser, beetle wine or dog piss?
Dog piss.
So yeah, you could blast off, get a full hose of that wine and.
Beetle.
Shoot it at a kid.
Yeah, so yeah, there's got to be videos of the dog peeing at the animal actor show.
Yeah.
If anyone knows of a video of this show going awry in a fun, safe way.
Oh, well, there was video from a couple of years ago where one of the dogs in kind of a mad,
real mad cap way, one of the dogs got out.
Oh, got it.
Yeah, yeah.
It was running around by the horror makeup show and they were like, come here, come here.
And like guests are trying to help and it looks very cute.
I mean, it looks very harmless.
That's fun for everyone.
Oh, you know, here's a little like dog hijinks thing.
We were talking about this a while back, but the, you know, the bit where they bring up a kid,
will you whisper an item of clothing to the dog?
He'll go get it.
And it ends up in the in the bra and the towel and all that.
Now there's like, I'm going to learn this when I was a tour guide, because I think there was,
there was a day where like, well, go do everything at Universal.
And I think along, we saw the show and then people were asking like, well, how does this
thing work? Because the aim is that the dog, the first time I'm going to ruin the magic trick,
by the way, magic exposed, the dog goes and gets a hat no matter what the kid says.
And sometimes now they, if they can play it off as a mistake, if the dog doesn't get the hat,
but the aim is that the kid does say hat.
And then the dog goes and gets a hat and everybody's like, wow, he actually, this works.
Like the dog understood and got a hat and somebody asked, well, how does, how do they do that?
And like, well, it's a little like, it's, it's a cue.
If you listen closely, they say hat.
It's like the last thing that said so that the kid thinks a little kid training situation.
Oh, right.
So they say hat because they've heard hat.
And I was curious how this worked in practice.
And in the video that I watched of a recent show, the trainer is explaining all this like,
okay, we've got our dog here and you can say any item of clothing, hats, shirts,
shoes, pants, hats, anything. Hats is twice.
That's a real Dale Carnegie, how to make friends and influence people like mind trick.
Like you got your brain.
If you want to show someone you're listening, you repeat like a handful of the words they
just said to you.
Like you, if they ask a question, you put a bunch of the question in your answer.
And then they go like, oh, wow, he really took the initiative.
Like he's just said words back at me.
Yeah.
But that's why if a, if they, if a trainer worked there and really needed to make it work,
then they could just like anything you want, hat, shirt, hat, hoodie, hat, glasses, hat,
watch, hat, hat, hat, hat, shoe, hat, any item of clothing.
If you run with that, the audience is going to laugh.
If you say a nut hat enough times.
Oh, that's true.
That's a good joke.
Maybe that's what I would do if I was there.
That's how I feel like I had my tour guide jokes.
I was trying to like let you in a little bit.
Like, you know, like I'm all exposed to the artifice, but not too much.
It's still too much because the show, the outline of the show has a lot of madcap stuff.
They have stuff going wrong.
They've built themselves some wiggle room of like, well, if the animal really does like lie down
and just want to go to sleep.
I mean, there's play dead.
There's a, there's a big play dead sequence sometimes.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
Is it that the trainer keeps like looking up?
Like do they, they're pretending they think the animal actually died,
but then it's like the animal keeps moving right when like in panting and they're like,
no lie down when the person, oh, okay.
Okay.
Yeah.
That's cute.
This is pretty cute.
This is one of the cuter things I think in a theme park setting.
Yeah.
It's a little bit, bits that work for everybody except for 16 month olds.
This is what I'm.
Yeah.
Well, you could have when he's, when he's older, you could actually have him sabotage it.
You can get them up there and tell them like, don't say hat.
Whatever they say, say like shoes.
Say brah.
Oh, that would be the way.
Yes.
You ruin the show.
You'd wreck the show.
The whole thing would get shut down.
They'd like shut the thing down immediately.
And don't, and you have to yell it because if it's just a whisper, then the audience won't know.
But like, maybe even don't even let the question get out.
Just get up there and scream the word brah as soon as you get on stage.
All right.
Well, we'll have fun.
This is a future father, son, fun outing.
But I don't know what else about this thing.
I mean, it's, it's, it's a bless.
It's a lot of fun.
We haven't mentioned the, when it was used,
it was a real working production studio location.
Yes.
That's right.
So the Florida one, you know, the set's a little nondescript in Hollywood.
It's like kind of, you know, beige and flats and soundstage walls.
And they, I really like how this, this to me was always like, oh, this is
a way that they've, they've plused up everything.
Like they've gone more epic in Orlando.
That the set still is this amazing jungle ruins environment.
And so these big statues and a lagoon and a water slide that animals could go down.
But I assume you're talking about that.
This was the set for several years worth of the ABC show, animal or animals, animals,
funniest America's funniest people.
Yes.
Correct.
Which I remember very excitedly watching.
I feel like before Sunday night was Simpson's night for me to watch.
I loved America's funniest home videos.
And then when you have a spin-off America's funniest people
hosted by fellow full house star, Dave Cool.
Yay.
Another full house or yes.
As a little kid, I had been to universal Florida, saw the show.
So when he would stand in there, I was like, that's the animal actor.
Stay like, I definitely, I was looking at the time.
Once upon a time in Hollywood, Jif.
I was like, did I see the show and then got excited when I went to see the theme park?
And I was like, oh no, the timing would have worked out that I definitely would have been
to the theme park first and then saw the seasons where they shot on this stage.
Cause they switched it later.
It was the second half.
It was the Tawny Cotain era.
Cause there was another host, another coast first.
They let go and then like, we're coming back big for season three or whatever.
It's Orlando and it's Tawny.
All new.
This is all new America's funniest people.
Yeah.
And I, I mean, I bought all hook line and sinker as a kid that like Orlando,
some stuff was filmed in Hollywood, but a lot of stuff is filmed in Orlando.
You know, our studios, Florida and MGM studios, you know?
Yeah.
They really needed to create the impression in the early 90s.
A lot's happening here.
You're going to want it as if, if you're in the business, you're going to want to come shoot
here and if you're not, you're going to want to come see how we shoot stuff.
Yeah.
It worked on children and it drove a production member,
production managers and second assistant directors out of their minds.
Cause they're like, we have to stop shooting.
Monsoon like rains have come in.
Oh yeah.
Right.
Yeah.
That's not, it doesn't work for many months of the year.
Weird show.
I'm shocked that you liked the show.
The show is like such a faint memory.
Did you watch this Mike?
The Cool Yet?
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
I was pretty famous than I remember.
I mean, obviously it was.
I have a pretty strong memory of it.
Yeah.
I would watch it a lot and I liked that it was, I may have liked it better than
America's Funny Stomped videos.
Oh really?
Cause the idea of you don't know was like, it's still hosts doing a lot of like
little, little pantry bits and then like, uh, watch this and then, and then it's not home videos,
but rather like it's not people falling down or getting hurt or whatever.
It's people like purposefully being funny, doing a weird, like making a weird face.
Or, uh, uh, talent that they're a butt has or something.
Right.
When you describe it like that, it sounds worse than the original and it probably is
cause it, you do, I used to feel like, I feel like maybe it was my mom or some parent who was like,
I don't like the videos where they're trying.
I like the accidents.
That's a smart distinction to make.
Not that it was like accidents, like somebody got really hurt, but oh, you know, a funny thing.
You slipped a little bit or whatever and not the like on purpose videos seem always seemed less funny
than the accidents.
Um, but my memory, maybe it was just cause I liked Coolie.
I was into Dave Coolie at the time.
It helps.
He gets to do his voices.
Yeah.
Little in little bits.
He's the voice of the Jackalope.
Of course.
We're Jackalope with his stars in a lot of odd little short films.
Um, I guess I liked this, but it's an ultimate like, boy, do we like this cause it was on
or did we?
Well, how many things did we just like cause it was on?
Yeah, of course.
Maybe all.
So many things.
Is the answer.
Yeah.
But I, you know, I found an episode of it and just the sweeping shot of Universal Florida,
helicopter shots, searchlights are going, the original gate.
I think I liked the original gate more than the current one.
Oh, right.
A little more beige.
I like the severe white one.
Yeah.
Ernie Anderson, Paul Thomas Anderson's dad, the voice of ABC and the announcer of the show.
It's just like.
Goularty.
Yeah.
Kids horror shows, the host Goularty or local, maybe not kids, local.
Local.
Yeah.
That's magic.
That's that park overheads of that park.
It's there is a standup special that I found in some obscure streaming service,
a standup special of Michael Winslow, the voiceover or the voice effects guy from police academy.
Yeah.
That is shot maybe with the same footage, helicopter footage,
and it's still it gets to me every time I'm like, boy, oh, they're taking me to the.
Yeah.
Ultimate place, the ultimate destination for fun.
I wonder if you could, there's no way to ever really do a study.
Oh, I guess you could do with kids, like show them a clip of like that type of like marketing
and then show them like whatever how universal markets now and see,
because it does feel like there's something extra exciting about that era of marketing,
but also I was sick seven.
So it's impossible to really know if it landed harder.
This is the most dynamic way you could market a theme park to people,
or it just felt like that at the time.
Yeah.
I mean, I, if I flip over to Nickelodeon nowadays, some of the marketing is still pretty similar.
Some of the aesthetics, some of the marketing.
Sure.
Pretty commercials are kids.
Commercials are very similar.
His commercials are shockingly.
Yeah. And cereal commercials and.
Yeah.
Yeah. So I don't know.
I can't unsee the universal, the promo that was on the bag to the future three VHS,
where it's just the word universal going by slowly.
And in every letter, there's a different universal ride.
Yes.
It's still like, like I have, I get like a pit in my stomach when I see it, like,
yeah, I'm afraid of what's down there, but I know I have to go tackle it.
Um, does that make sense?
Like, I don't know.
It was that, it just felt like, are you up for the challenge?
Can you, this is this, it's the Jetsons in the letter a, can you,
you think you can handle being there in person?
This is like, you're going to be wise brave how going like, I have to rise to the challenge.
I got to get that kid.
I got to scoop up that weekly little kid.
He ever comes back here.
I'm remembering this face as opposed to any other 16 month olds face because I will eat the face.
This is, I was just going to say, this is a, this is you in the retirement home,
like kind of your brain is just slowly going, but like they just have like a loop,
this tape on a loop to calm me down.
When you get started getting riled up and they're like, just wheel, Mr.
Gardner into the room and play him the universal tape from 1991.
That is what I want.
Yeah. I'll get my wishes out right now.
I want that slow universal word going by and then the logo forming.
And I want the general cinemas space candy opening.
Yeah.
Just those, those things over and over again.
I'll be a very happy, mentally collapsing man.
He's freaking out.
In a couple of years.
So I don't know.
I thought you were going a much darker direction where the, the orderly would like the Irishman
would be like, all those rides are gone.
Scott, no one cares.
No one's going to hurt you.
It's all gone.
Yeah. No, that's like Coco.
There's a, like, there's a land of the dead for rides.
And as soon as the last person doesn't remember the ride anymore,
but you can still go all of them and they're all made of bones,
but they, as soon as the last person remembers the ride, they all go to dust.
They're like, they're like force ghosts of the rides.
So like you see like a blue outline of the back to the future ride.
You're like wave at it.
He waived all the rides and logos and like fonts,
the fonts that are gone that are now in blue force ghost form.
Oh, he's waving to the ghosts again.
Mr. Gardner is waving to the ghosts again.
He thinks he sees the battle for galactica attraction that was in the
spot that the bags of the future had was built in.
He's calm now though.
Let him go.
Let him believe last person on earth who knows.
People know what it is.
He's the last person who cares.
That's the rules of the bone of bone universal studios.
Well, it's peaceful though.
Yeah.
But that's what, you know, we help people remember with this podcast.
We collect these memories.
We tell you about them so that we make you as crazy as us.
Dave Cool Yay was there Tony contained something called a jackalope.
You're doing an impression of anybody describing an episode of this podcast to their significant
other who doesn't listen to the podcast.
There's a lot of get back stuff.
Yeah.
A lot of get back.
The Irishman came up at the very remember the Irishman.
Are you on episode two of get back?
I'm in the middle of two.
Okay.
So you've got the camp.
You've seen the cameo already.
Oh yes.
Yeah.
Is that a spoiler?
Maybe.
This thing that happened in 1969.
That's similar to yeah, that's similar to like Nick Fury showing up or something in
the middle of a Marvel movie at this point.
Yeah.
But if Nick Fury showed up, looked around the room and was like, I don't think I want to.
I don't think I'm on the same wavelength as these Avengers.
Wait, are you wait, are we talking about the same cameo?
There's many cameos and get back.
I'm talking about the actor who wants.
No, no, I'm talking about the musician.
Um, I don't maybe I don't know.
Oh, well, I don't know.
I don't want to ruin it.
Okay.
A lot of work to hide the identity of like a member of the wrecking crew or Harry Nielsen
or something.
You don't just mean Billy Preston, do you?
No, no.
Okay.
Well, I mean, I don't know.
Yeah.
I don't know who's coming.
Oh, wow.
Okay.
Are they okay?
All right, folks.
Well, in that case, check out get back on Disney Plus.
If you want to know who walks into the room, uh, the cigarette and wine laden room.
Uh, but as for us, you survived podcast, the ride.
Um, and that was a blast.
Nice memories of decades old jokes.
Um, if you are a fan of Dave Coulier, you might want to return next week, uh, for next
week's episode.
Yeah, right.
It might factor in again.
Uh, you can find us on the socials at podcast, the ride, uh, merch is available in our tea
public store.
Jason, what'd you want to say about the merch?
You got to order if you're already for Christmas.
Well, they're shipping delays everywhere.
We already got like a message from tea public.
Biden is the crates.
He's not letting the shirts out.
Our shirts are all on the crates.
All on the crates.
They're all on the crates.
Ever given and, and Biden's, he just won't stop talking about how his dad knew how to
drive a car, but it's like, you got to dock the ship, Joe.
We need those shirts.
Yeah.
We're trying to get them out.
Podcasts, the ride shirts.
They're all in the shipping, but we got to move them.
We got to get them into the mainland.
Folks for Christmas.
They need to be there for Christmas.
Under the tree.
We've got to give him Santa room to land.
Get the planes out of the sky.
Give him Santa.
We're landing all the planes.
Give Santa free air.
Drop the shirt from the plane and the chimney.
The shirts need to go on the chimney.
Drop a launch queen and a no launch queen.
You don't know who lives there.
Get both shirts.
Put on the chimney from the plane.
Every type of shirt.
Santa's going to throw the shirts in the chimney.
Folks.
Our friends around the world.
The European vacation shirts.
Remember the good saga.
It was another saga.
So many great sagas.
Shorter though.
Another shorter.
Shorter saga.
They're doing Jamba Week, folks.
We're going to talk about Zeke and Zeb.
Tennessee and Corn Pop.
All the country bears.
Driving a car.
They drove too.
They drove cars.
And for three bonus episodes every month,
check out Podcast the Ride, the second day,
to patreon.com slash podcast the ride,
where we just discussed the Minch on a Benchiverse
with our friend, Adam Susser.
That's a really fun one.
Check it out.
Patreon.
That makes a great last minute.
That you can do day off.
That you can do on Christmas.
On the last night of Hanukkah.
Jason's going full QVC now.
Yeah, really.
And for the low price of $5 a month.
Those, yeah, you can't,
there's no Patreon subscription stuck at a port.
That's right.
Yes.
Yeah.
When it's in the cloud, no,
there's nothing.
Can stop.
Yeah, the cloud is fine.
There's no nothing holding the cloud back.
That's right.
Yeah.
Give a gift.
Give your loved one a gift from the cloud.
Reach into the cloud and grab a handful of us.
We got to move the stuff from the water into the cloud.
Why aren't we using the water more?
When we put it up in the cloud.
The cloud should be over getting our goods and services.
What's that do, folks?
Omicron don't stop the cloud.
It can't be done.
Omicron can't reach up that high.
Folks, the Lakitu.
We need help from the Lakitu.
All right.
Okay.
Bye.
This has been a Forever Dog Production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson,
Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner,
Brett Bohm,
Joe Silio,
and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts,
please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple Podcasts,
Spotify,
or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news
by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at Forever Dog Team
and liking our page on Facebook.