Forever.
Dog.
Previously on Podcast The Ride.
We've been invited to do an episode about the TGIF shows that filmed at Walt Disney World.
Mind if I tag along?
Kyle.
We are not sharing a microphone.
Wow, I can't believe we're doing our show underwater.
This is a shark!
Me?
Podcast Prince of the Day?
Oh no, the repopulating podcastulator blew a fuse.
You can find yourself a new guest.
I'm outta here.
Kyle, wave!
And now the conclusion of Podcast The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, a theme park podcast with hosts who are such dorks, no transformation
chamber would be powerful enough to make them cool.
I am one of said dorks, Scott Gardner, among the others, Mike Carlson.
Hi.
Hi, yes, if I got into that transformation chamber, it would either break or I would
somehow get less cool.
It would just not even know what to do with me.
Arrows on it would just spin around, steam shoots out, thing collapses.
It would meet its match in you.
Jason Sheridan, how would you fare in the transformation chamber?
I'm gonna go even one step farther from Mike and say I would simultaneously come out dehydrated
but also clammy.
It's unclear how I'm both at the same time, but I just am.
Okay, so yeah, it would just affect you physically.
It would almost be like you went to space but no transformation actually happened.
Yeah, it would probably just suck the moisture out of my body and just put it all on my forehead.
So somebody expecting, some babe expecting a suave version of you, Jason Sheridan.
Sorry, madam, I got worse.
Aged a bit, several decades, it's okay, we can go out.
You've heard of glow ups, this is the first glow down in history.
Folks, we today are, I'm thrilled.
I hope there are some audience members who've been anticipating this one for a while.
I certainly have been as a host to talk about some of the greatest narrative content ever made.
That being the episodes from ABC's early 90s TGIF lineup where the entire cast of the show
went and visited the Walt Disney World Resort.
These are spectacular, a half hour, two part, really hours of television.
And we're going to tackle a few of them today.
And excited to be doing it with, I think, an aficionado of the genre joining us for the first time in a while.
He is a cast member of Saturday Night Live and the co-creator and star of the new show
Saturday Morning All-Star Hits, which premieres on Netflix today.
You can check it out right now.
Press pause on this, go watch it, come back, however you want to do it, up to you.
It's Kyle Mooney, ladies and gentlemen.
Hey.
So excited to be here. Thank you.
I get, I get nervous.
Like I was thinking about it yesterday.
I do really love TGIF and this genre, we'll call it a television.
But even you calling me an aficionado makes me very nervous because just why I feel like I need to be
continually watching it to know, to be able to pick from everything, if that makes any sense.
But at the same time, it's so ingrained in me that it feels a part of my essence.
I was nervous picking the word.
I didn't, I made a point of not saying expert, perhaps anticipating not wanting to put too much on you.
I appreciate that.
Yeah, it's definitely like influenced me spiritually in some way.
Like I couldn't, I don't know that I could like name off episode synopsis like in a moment's notice,
but I feel like it's kind of changed who I am structurally.
Yeah, you're not. It's not that you would win a TGIF trivia contest, but that's not what it's about.
I feel, yeah, it's tonal.
It's what these shows are, which I can see.
And it's affected your work.
I don't know if you feel like it's affected, I mean, seemingly that it's affected you as a person.
I mean, yes, undoubtedly it's affected my work and my sense of humor.
And therefore, like my sense of humor is part of who I am.
And so I think you could say it has affected me on a human level.
Yeah, I mean, it's definitely part of the all these shows are part of the fiber of my being as well.
And I know my younger sister would just parrot things Stephanie said and Michelle said.
These would just be around in the house for decades, for far too long.
She's still saying how rude and that kind of stuff.
I grew up in a Full House family a little bit, less people.
But you could underscore a lot of moments of the Gertner upbringing with the heartfelt music
as the heart to heart and the moral are conveyed to little Scott.
Full House was like on in the was on in the right time in like the morning when we'd be getting ready for school.
So it did feel like I was learning just as many things from the show as my parents, maybe more so.
My dad worked nights was not awake in the morning.
So I definitely like in the morning it was the three men of Full House giving me like fatherly advice.
I didn't realize that that you like ascribed some those are your your morning dads.
I just thought of it now, honest to God.
My dad worked nights, so he'd be sleeping in the morning.
So my father in the morning, my father's in the morning were Joey, Jesse and Danny.
But I am not I'm not a I don't know this stuff like I know certain comic books,
but it's in the same way with like just probably it's more influence on me than I realize.
That's something I was thinking about was real.
Because when you guys go off on Marvel tears, I wonder why is this lacking for me?
Why don't I have this pop culture avenue?
Why didn't I? Because we grew up with so much of the same stuff and not that you guys didn't grow up with these shows.
But I do feel like maybe this is my Marvel, like the TGIF shows.
They are again, I doubt my ability to like really spit out a bunch of information.
But I was thinking how I can definitely like an episode starts and like based on the
the picture quality or the age of the kids, I can go, OK, so now we're in the era where like
Mrs. Carruthers would be in it or Joey's doing the Ranger Joe show where he has the the Woodchuck puppet.
Or like there's certain things I could sort of, you know, spit out on site about these shows.
You're probably I'm trying to think if there's a bigger Urkel fan I know than you, I feel like.
And I don't even. Is that accurate? Really? I don't know.
I think you made this observation before.
I thought about it, but I feel like maybe it's just because we're doing the show and we are referencing things from our childhood a lot.
But I feel like you love Urkel and I feel like you talk about Urkel more than any other adult I know.
Huh, huh. Well, I think because I don't feel like I'm talking about Urkel a ton.
I almost feel like this is this is that other people aren't talking about Urkel enough.
I think everybody else needs to bring up their their Urkel quota. Yeah.
Kyle, how do you fall in terms of how much does Urkel come up in your day to day?
Well, also, I do want to this is a slight clarification.
I want to make that maybe it's neither here nor there.
Full House started as TGIF, but it did move to Tuesdays.
And I bet that this episode likely aired on a Tuesday.
Is that right? Really? So it was not started.
If maybe when season five, I think I was reading that it was it had moved.
Yeah. One of the reoccurring things with these shows is that like when they hit season five or six,
like it's going to have the Disneyland two parter.
Oh, yeah. All of these shows, it did it in season five and six.
The other thing that was interesting to me is all of these shows are on HBO Max now.
That's how I watch them, because I guess Warner Brothers was the production company.
It was definitely the distributor.
But somehow the ownership has now ended up with Warner Brothers of these shows.
Yeah, all filmed on the Warner lot.
Warner Brothers logo at the end, now on HBO Max, even though these episodes aired on ABC
and are giant commercials for Disney World and in two cases have a lengthy Indiana Jones
sequence, which at the time was paramount.
So there's a real like car wreck of corporate ownership going on with these.
You can also really see in all of these like what
Disney World is pushing or what is new at the time because it gets like prime placement.
Yes, absolutely. Yeah.
You could like within the different episodes, for sure.
I mean, you know, Tower of Terror comes up a couple of times.
I always I feel a number of these episodes.
You can feel Disney saying, I know, I know you just want to do Castle stuff,
but we've got Epcot, so do Epcot, too.
Like eat your vegetables, make sure there's some Epcot in there.
Cover everything.
Yeah. And it definitely feels like they like they were going over.
There was some planning.
Obviously, Indiana Jones, they were pushing hard with a stunt show,
but it definitely feels like, all right, they all shouldn't be at the same hotel.
Like we need to make sure we spread it out a little bit.
People need to have a variety of the things they see, a variety of things they can do here.
The fact that they get like the big family shows to to go to Disney
allows them to cover a lot of bases of like four to five stories
going on at once, which can send everybody off to every park.
Everybody can cover a lot of ground.
I do like Urkel, by the way.
I didn't get I didn't get to
formally state that I was.
Thanks for that.
I don't know. I feel like just to speak briefly about my history,
if with this with the block, if anyone, I don't know, but yes, please. Yeah. Yeah.
This this was an event on Friday night.
I was not going out to hang out with cool people or anything like that.
So from like the age of, let's say, you know, eight years old till about
I would imagine 15 or something like that.
I consistently spent my Friday nights watching TGIF.
And and I think it also probably formulated like
kind of how I perceived what like high school was like or dating was like
in the same way, like Say By The Bell kind of had a similar
um, influence on me.
But Family Matters, I like I always had my favorite.
Family Matters was not my favorite at the time.
But then, like I would say in my mid 20s, I went back and watched it all.
And the way that it sort of evolved into almost like a sci fi fantasy show
and that they were like like fighting pirates and stuff like that at some point,
like I really was able to appreciate it on a new level.
And like, yes, the introduction of the chamber and Stefan
like just took the show to a to a new to a new place.
Yeah, yeah, it's I definitely I think all of us probably agree
that we would like prime time television to have more like chambers
that would transform the main characters into alternate versions.
Well, we discovered that Honey, I Shrunk the Kids show
and that that's full of chamber kind of bullshit and emotions all the time.
And it's like you can tell, you know, that critics at this time
must have been so judgmental of shows like this.
And like this is American trash and this is what, you know,
whatever L.A.
law is saving us from smart television.
I don't know what was being held up as the opposite.
But yeah, I think in retrospect, yeah, we would love if it was this kind of thing,
all that, especially the chamber.
The chamber is just the most fun.
If you started an episode and you realize that's where it was going,
because there's like how many like a dozen that end up involving the chamber
or Urkel's suave alter ego, Stefan or Kel.
Well, it's it's nice that I know I don't know what episode we're starting out with,
but it's nice that, yes, we got Stefan.
And like you're saying, I don't even know how many episodes Stefan is in.
But that's like a specific trope that we got used to.
That was always fun to see.
But I feel like in the full house special, we got to see
Jesse perform at the piano and with the Rippers.
And like that felt like a very fun.
I hadn't watched that episode in a while and thought for sure
when he was trying to convince Becky to
to forgive him for missing their date at the piano,
he was going to start playing forever. It just felt like.
Yeah, that's why I think I might have assumed that.
I know my wife, Aaron, thought that also at some point it like
you feel like that's what it's supposed to be for listeners who don't know.
The Beach Boys loom very large in full house.
They appear multiple times.
They lend a song to John Stamos, his character, Jesse,
and his band, Jesse and the Rippers, which is the one of the top tier
bands in the world in the universe of full house,
despite them not having any original songs.
They're like cover bands that is just outstandingly popular.
And having so much money, they don't move out of the.
Jesse still doesn't move out of the house.
And he is also a morning radio co-host at the time.
He's got like two different jobs.
Yeah, both of which come into play in the episode.
He's doing both.
I mean, that's a good era that he's it's rush hour Renegades
and Jesse and the Rippers.
He hasn't been kicked out yet and replaced with Barry Williams
from the Brady Bunch.
We turned it into Barry and the Rippers forever.
Just to say that is a you know, if I'm like doing the map of what is Beach Boys
that I kind of kitschy, ironically enjoy and then what's Beach Boys I truly love
forever, the original version from the 70s by Dennis Wilson is like deep
into what I truly love, just like wonderful, lush, beautiful little ballad.
And then for some reason, the Beach Boys elected to give
the only the biggest song by a deceased member
to the show Full House.
We are like he is this guy's been dead for 10 years
and we're going to like power ballad Brian Adams.
If I this song, I was just so as a kid, I was so confused by all of this.
I didn't say it out loud.
I wasn't asking questions out loud, but I was like this music video.
Is this supposed to be good?
Like, am I supposed to like this?
Because it's very like, you know, soft lens.
That's an insane music.
That's so silly.
Like like the many candles as he's in, like a no, no shirt underneath Vest.
Yeah. Despite the rest of the show being a sitcom,
you were supposed to watch that music video and think it is really cool.
And that Jesse is cool and Stamos is cool.
Yes. And that you want to buy the Beach Boys Summer in Paradise album.
The only place you could find on me as a child.
I didn't know that.
I didn't know. So I like Jesse at the time.
I thought he was cool, but I definitely was like, this video is funny, though.
He's like, looks funny.
And I'm laughing.
His twins are filmed in front of like on top of like in a cloudscape,
like and then he like tenderly kisses them and get his portrait.
Oh, yeah. It's really, really in get his. Yes. Yeah.
I don't think I was processing the music video element.
I think I probably just went, this is something for adults.
Like, this is something for my parents.
But I did know something from my parents.
Yeah, I don't know this.
I don't I guess this is a thing adults do.
I don't know what this is, but I knew only my parents,
the only people on earth who like this for my parents.
Yeah. And my aunts and uncles.
I knew Kokomo because that was always played at like weddings and stuff.
That was always played at like reception.
I feel like that was in the mix. Yeah. Yeah.
Kokomo with John Stamos in the video filmed at the Grand Floridian Hotel
in Disney World. Yeah. Yeah. I didn't realize that.
Mm hmm. Mm hmm.
History. Yeah. Not the Coronado Hotel in San Diego, you might think.
But let me clear. Let me get that on the record.
That's great.
I guess we're sort of full housing it a little bit here.
What year did this air? 90?
This is May of 1993.
93. The first one of these three days.
Yeah, I was going to propose chronological order.
By the way. And also just really quick, I think we're going to
we're going to try to just cover three of these.
The big family episodes, which are all two parters.
I was saying to Kyle, like they're all like roughly the same episode, kind of
like a lot of the same things happen structurally. They're the same.
You know, technically we should maybe be covering Boy Meets World
and Sabrina the Teenage Witch, but those are going to have to wait.
Not to say they're off the table forever, but apologies to
fans or stans of those shows anyway.
That's that's the plan.
Proceed later. TGIF later. Later on.
I was just going to bring up
Jesse and the Rippers doing the hippie hippie shake in 1993.
I know it's interesting now as an adult to watch it and go,
that song was 30 plus years old at the time.
It's like, but these are pretty sure that song is heavily utilized
in the Angels in the Outfield soundtrack as well.
So it got some some mileage, circa 93 to 97.
Just yeah, just throwing it out there.
It's interesting, though, because I think as a kid,
I actually didn't even realize it was that old.
Like it didn't register, but now it is just an interesting choice.
Well, and it's how they open the gate.
Like so the impetus of the show and of the Tanner family
going to Disney World is Jesse and the Rippers booking a gig at Disney World.
And you don't really know the specifics of the gig.
But then when it starts, it is in front of Cinderella Castle.
They've shut down Magic Kingdom.
It is all for Jesse and the Rippers.
I think the way it plays in the episode is ladies and gentlemen,
Jesse and the Rippers for goodness sake, I got the hippie hip.
They are straight into the middle of the song.
And one general question in all of these, I'm curious
if any of you have insight into this, like,
are these actual park goers or are these background actors in these
in some of these like like in that spot?
It's a good question, because you see you do see when you go on Disney
on certain days at Disney, they'll have a sign up that says we're filming.
And basically by being in the park, you agree that we won't sue us
if you're on camera for any reason.
So I wonder if it's a mix.
I wonder if it's like people that extras like right around the main actors
when there's like closeups of them in crowds.
But then like there's possibilities that they just got stray people
far in the background and.
Yeah, I don't know.
When we were watching, Jane was like, look at that crowd.
They're like rubberneck.
They're like really staring at the action going on in the front of the shot.
Yeah, it's it's pretty crazy crowd acting specifically
in the in the family matters proposal scene.
If you if you really stare at people in that one,
when a a big grand proposal is happening between non famous people,
this isn't like Jesse and the Rippers.
Nobody knows who Stefan and Laura are.
And yet they're up on the stage with Cinderella and a crowd is gathered
that goes all the way back to the front of Main Street.
It feels right. All of me.
What is this event?
Is this a thing that occurs?
I mean, that's something you can ask about a lot of what happens in the right.
So that I think is another strong point of all of the is that they all
it contain things that do not, did not, never will happen in Disney World.
But I didn't know that as a kid, I thought all of these things were on the table.
Yeah, possibly.
I definitely thought the Michelle, what is she, the princess for a day?
I thought that might be possible.
Yeah. Now, in in my memory, and I don't know, this is another
show at Disneyland or Disney World.
I had thought that Michelle pulled the sword and the stone sword.
So I don't know if that plays in Blossom or something else.
Or I just totally imagined like imagined that.
But that's kind of always how I remember her becoming princess for a day.
So it's fun to see it change up.
That makes more sense.
That's what's that's what's there.
That is a thing where like only one kid does it.
I almost wonder if that was what was written.
And then Disney noted it and said, we're pushing Aladdin really hard right now.
Can we make this some sort of made up Aladdin thing?
Because if you haven't seen the episodes and again, HBO Max, look them up.
If you want to know what we're talking about.
As soon as the family enters the Magic Kingdom, there is the setup in Main Street.
Mind you, in the Victorian era, Main Street,
there is just this little Aladdin world set up
with a big, like loud vizier kind of guy.
And this announcing that there's you people can come up and rub the lamp
and there will be a princess for the day chosen.
Can I just add, I wrote down this quote and I don't know if this is directly
what it was. And I've not seen I've not seen Aladdin in a minute.
So you guys can correct me if like this is actually a major character, but
someone in the group is like, Whoa, look, all the guys from Aladdin,
the lamp seller, Jasmine.
I read that.
I knew it. All the guys.
Just like, yeah, it's everyone.
The lamp seller.
That's what teen girls are obsessed with.
It's the lamp seller.
So there's the ceremony that's going to happen.
Stephanie, the the middle child, Jodie Sweden.
It's supposed to be her turn, but then she offers it to Michelle.
I forget why it becomes Michelle.
But it's like rightfully her turn to rub the lamp.
But she gives it up or gets distracted or something.
And Michelle does it.
And she is chosen as princess for the day, which there's like
a bunch of magic, a big puff of smoke.
All of the all of the daughters together say, oh, baby.
And then suddenly a big inflatable genie is there,
which Storks knows from that Aladdin's Royal Caravan parade,
which was in Disney MGM Studios.
And what's it doing in in Magic Kingdom?
Makes no sense.
See it later on going down Hollywood Boulevard in MGM Studios.
The other inflatables, you know, that were used a lot in the parades at the time.
You know, Minnie with the fruit on her head and Jester Roger Rabbit.
Those, of course, come into play at the end of the episode.
But that's a different stream.
Yeah. Nice to see them.
Really good to see.
I'll add plot wise.
I mean, just because we maybe pass
and went past it a little bit, but like when Jesse gets these
when it gets asked to perform with his band at Disney World,
there's also this whole thing of him having celebrating his anniversary
with with Becky and like and you'll see this when we get to step by step.
But there's this whole thing of like,
I guess, couples like trying to have sex while at the parks
or like trying to make love.
Yeah, it seems to be a driving narrative saying that's all of them.
Yeah. Every episode, every episode of every show is about a horny.
Almost every character is oddly enough.
These episodes are not pushing Disney's very robust babysitting services
and kids clubs, which they were really pushing in the 90s.
I was like, hey, parents, if you want to get the hell away from your goddamn kids,
leave them at the hotel.
We've got people.
You know, there should have been one that one at least that showcased that service.
Yeah, you think.
I don't know. Is this an uncomfortable area?
Maybe for why? I don't know what you were heading for, Mike, but I'm just
I'm curious now.
Is there anything accurate about this depiction of like Disney
World as an especially romantic place in that regard?
Well, here's what I'll say about this.
When you're a certain age and this is not
people think this is out of character for me, but when you're a certain age
and go anywhere, especially when you're with your parents
and maybe you're in your mid to late teens,
there is an idea that like maybe I will just lock eyes and fall in love with someone.
There's a lot of that on vacations all the time.
And, you know, stemming from like Kyle and like my worldview kind of coming
from shows like this.
And people are always like, you know, finding the love of their
especially on trips.
Any show goes to Hawaii or something.
They instantly somebody meets the love of their life and like
maybe gets engaged within three days.
I always thought that was in the cards for me.
In Disney World or anywhere. Yes. Right.
Yeah. I also it isn't until you're much older that you realize like all these
shows are written by weird by like weirdos who had like big old nerd
childhoods and they're writing what they wanted to have or like
didn't happen to them on vacations.
Yeah, I think the shows made me gave me the wrong idea.
Like that it would literally just be like a look at someone.
They would look at me and then they go, oh, OK, great.
Now we're in love.
And really, I would bypass the need to like
I would have to show my personality at all.
Like I would have to demonstrate I wasn't a crazy person.
Like all that stuff felt like, you know, basic stuff.
But maybe because I watched these shows and they made stuff like that,
seems simple.
It warped my brain and kept me
not having kissed a girl for extra a few years there.
A little more than the average.
Yeah, a little bit more. Yeah.
It might be true across the board.
To the requirements and structure of like we have to get this done
in a certain number of shooting days and also like it has to be two
or three acts or whatever.
Yeah. Influence the way you thought about love.
Yeah. Oh, we all did.
Yeah, yeah. Just you.
I don't mean to put it on you to stay on full house for a little bit.
Yeah. So that's kind of the kind of the biggest story, I guess,
is Michelle becoming princess for the day, because now she truly does have
royal reign over specifically the Magic Kingdom, mostly.
Although I guess they go to other places.
One thing that I like is the way
characters are around all the time, like Disney suited characters
and face characters like Snow White.
You know, they're pushing the Grand Floridian in this one.
That's where the tanners stay.
And just like as the show goes on, Snow White follows them back to the hotel.
Like she leaves the gates of the the Magic Kingdom.
That's how she in general is like kind of solving the family crises
and getting real mixed up in their interpersonal politics.
Besides that, people are just like having little sidebars
with the characters, Chip and Dale are roasting, roasting on Becky.
And yeah, being very rude in the wake of her being ghosted by by her.
Jesse. Yeah, that's not fair.
What would they be saying about her now? For God's sake.
Yeah, but she's turned to a life of white collar crime. Yeah.
What would pantomime insults would they have today?
Yeah. Anyway, this is another like way that these shows
incorrectly calibrated my expectations, where I thought that you
you go to Disney World and you become friends with the characters.
They hang out with you.
They follow you around.
If you're bringing some personal strife to the parks, they're helping you solve it.
Yeah, no, that is what struck me here.
And I do think that gave me unrealistic expectations.
We've talked many times on the show.
I think I think I think my initial expectation was that Goofy
would just be working there, that the characters were so much more active
at the park, I guess, in my way, doing like manual labor.
But this is a different version of it where they're just very engaged
and they have like free rein to go anywhere.
So it is a little bit.
It is a it is a little bit more fun to see kind of what I maybe expected.
By rewatching all this stuff.
Characters more involved in your personal like.
I want them involved in my personal life.
I want them all to know what's going on with me personally.
Well, it's you know, you recently engaged, Mike, and it's like it's a bummer.
I just, you know, I know the timeline and I know that you weren't
going to the parks a lot in the lead up to this because it was pandemic.
And I'd like to think that you like took a trip to Disney World,
wanted to ask Lindsey, couldn't find the right moment.
We're side barring with Captain Hook and
I take her about.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Of course. Yeah.
And all all ways of love, you want Peter Pan's thoughts on it.
But then ultimately culminating in an extremely ornate
fireworks display like the most complicated fireworks display in history.
Well, I reunited my band second level from high school
in front of Disneyland's Castle, and I played the song
I played in high school called Rock the House.
Yeah, you know about second level.
I've heard. Yeah.
Yes. And I've heard it mentioned.
I've heard the song mentioned specifically, and I feel like you've
sung the chorus maybe before.
Has it has it? Have we heard have you played it yet?
Has it been circulated or?
I haven't played the original recording of it, but I played a little bit of it
on guitar. It wasn't a very good re it wasn't great.
Didn't sound. Yeah, we made you play it.
Yeah. Yeah.
But there's also a live performance from a variety show, too, in high school.
Oh, wow. That's great.
And I want to say congratulations again on all the rock the house stuff.
Oh, yeah. Thank you. Yeah.
It was it was a big
the audience loved it at the time, I'll say that.
I'm sure it sounds awesome.
Yeah, yeah.
How much mileage like this is like a year of your life
where you get where you're getting mileage out of rock the house or how how
how long was this a hit for?
It's a good question.
I was probably there's probably a period in like two.
There's probably a couple of months there in 2001.
And then it was like sort of dormant.
And ever since I brought it back up on the podcast now,
I'm getting a little more again. Oh, sure, sure.
So it's been a 20 year gap.
It's beautiful. That's like a song like an album kind of bombing.
And then you're discovering that it has a big following in Japan or something,
which happened to Jesse and the Rippers, by the way.
Yeah. Rock the house gave you the confidence to do well on the SATs.
And then it came back around, gave you the confidence to get engaged.
Right.
So it was rock the house that did it.
Well, it's rock the house that did it.
But help.
I got help from Peter Pan and Hook and everybody.
Yeah. Anyway, I mean, that's the way I think they can sort of,
you know, make a richer, like more interactive,
augmented reality kind of experience is that the characters are around
giving you advice and stuff.
Yeah, that's a yeah.
Bob Chapek should really work, get focused on that with Disney Genie, at least.
Yeah. Yeah.
Just have your phone, like listen to all your phone calls and read
all your texts for a while. Right.
So that when you get there,
Pinocchio is really versed in what's up with you.
Yeah. Yeah. Setting you the very least.
Genie's Jack Nicholson impression has some advice about how to deal
with your family when you open your phone.
You know, trouble your mom again.
You know, the shows, since you mentioned dealing with your families,
these shows do present one way that I often am a big proponent
of on these kinds of vacations, which is like split up sometimes
and everyone do their own thing.
Although these shows really hit the because they need to do
ABC stories like multiple stories.
I mean, they really split up a lot.
Like you think Danny would want to do some of this stuff with his children.
We want to see this smiles on their faces.
Oh, yeah. And it even occurred to me that, you know, when he he gets a
so he's having a romantic meal at the Coral Reef restaurant,
which gets ruined.
He's trying to do a wedding proposal, gets ruined by Jesse and Joey
trying to go do their the first underwater radio broadcast ever
with the Rush Hour Renegades.
But then he then it gets interrupted again
because he gets an urgent phone call saying that his daughter is missing.
And I realize when that happened, he's he hasn't been around for any of it.
He's not even aware that Michelle is Princess for the day.
Like his daughter has taken part in an unprecedented
Disney World program never to be done again.
And he did. He missed it 100 percent.
Yeah, that is shockingly negligent.
And I understand he has something else on his mind,
but that also seems way out of character for him in general on the show.
He's very micromanaging. Yes.
So how does he let entire children's stories get away from them?
I mean, let's be honest, if this was I mean, I've seen there's some YouTube
videos reviewing like Full House Disney World episode now.
But if this were like YouTube era and in the time that this came out,
there would be so many like cinema, cinema sins or honest, whatever's
about like what the problems and the inconsistencies are on these shows.
Like there would be like, what do you think?
This is not how Danny would act.
Are you kidding me?
There would be like the the Red Letter Media
90 minute to our like Star Wars prequel reviews of these
just to show the inconsistencies in the characters.
Is that is that what those
outlets do, because I see those phrases every now and then.
And I was like, what is what are you talking about?
I don't know what these are.
It's always people are mad that things aren't honest, that trailers aren't honest.
And if like, yeah, if if this
news report or episode of a show were honest,
I thank these YouTubers for taking media to task about honesty.
Yeah. OK, OK, got it.
So there's yeah, if it's an honest portrayal of Danny Tanner's,
you know, character, he would actually have seen some of Michelle's reign.
Yeah, and he never would have done this.
They've completely betrayed the Danny Tanner character.
Oh, OK.
So you just throw aside suspending disbelief.
OK, got it. Thank you. Yeah.
One of the other side plots, I don't think we've mentioned yet is a DJ.
Candice Cameron's character is DJ.
Oh, yeah, absolutely.
She is constantly seeing her boyfriend, Steve, everywhere.
Yeah, she's hallucinating. Yeah.
Hallucinating. And then he does show up.
But one of the early hallucinations, she imagines him on the float
dressed as Aladdin, which is an inside baseball joke
because he is the voice of Aladdin, that actor.
Yep. Yeah.
Scott Wanger.
This is the type of little fact as a little boy that made me feel so smart.
I was so self-satisfied by knowing this
and like just a little chuckle, like the most obnoxious, like nine year old.
Like, I know what this is.
There's a lot of kids watching this,
but not all of them are privy to this information.
Like, yeah, I was exactly the same way.
Snooty kid.
I also I remember thinking that because at that time,
Scott Wanger, pretty big part, like pretty major scene
stealer on Full House in this era.
Also, the voice of Aladdin, the biggest kids movie at the time.
Didn't you think that Scott Wanger was going to be like a Chris Pratt level
star for the rest of your life?
Like based on that beginning, based on 93,
I thought we'd be like just knee deep and winger our whole lives.
I agree. Yeah. Charming, handsome.
I don't know. I don't want to put it.
I mean, he's worked. He works.
But yeah, yeah, as a kid, like this was like this was a big star to me.
I was going to say at a very basic level, just thinking about these episodes.
I don't know if we're going to touch upon it, but like
the way we're used to Full House presented, like as a multi cam,
we're now seeing like a totally different version of it.
And like, I guess, single cam, I imagine.
But there's something that's allowed in in these episodes
that I feel like you don't get in the typical episodes of Full House, which is like
there's all of a sudden like space for ad lib at like the beginning
and ending of scenes sometimes.
So like you'll get the sort of like, yeah, then we'll go on a haunted mansion.
And then, oh, and then like they'll do their real line.
I don't know if you caught any of these moments, but there are a handful of them
in all the three episodes we watched.
But there's just something so disorienting about seeing the show
look different than what you've you've come to expect.
Sort of like Scott, remember the the Saved by the Bell,
the wedding, the one where like Zach and Kelly get married.
It's like all of a sudden they've neglected the way we've like
seen the show presented and it feels alien.
The whole the whole thing feels alien to some degree to me.
I don't know if you all felt that.
It's weird. It's them out of their elements.
Yeah, you're totally right.
Like, yeah, rhythms are different.
They give characters stuff.
Now, I don't think I have it written down.
Whatever DJ and Kimi say when they're coming down the stairs in the Grand Floridian.
I posted an Instagram of this like truly like years ago.
But yeah, it's like then we'll go.
But it's some ad lib about like roller coasters.
And then, yeah, they spot Steve like checking in the hotel.
Like, oh, yeah, so scary.
Yeah, that's pretty much what it is.
And then it was going up so high and I didn't think we could make it.
I oh, look, yeah, staged interruption.
That was really fun.
I like Splash Mountain with the like the.
That was a lot of fun.
I thought it was really cool, too.
Oh, my gosh.
I must be really losing it.
Yeah, just out of just out of the tone is so weird.
I step by step is the one that felt the weirdest to me.
This feels like a weird handheld verite
step by step going on.
And that's like, I don't know what to like.
This doesn't. And I was never a big step by step watcher, but I was like,
this really felt kind of unnerving.
What's that one?
I mean, you know, I think we could jump around.
There's yeah, there's the one scene in.
They're in the hotel room.
It's when the the the country group has been formed.
They rehearse once briefly and then break up immediately.
That scene, the audio is so wretched.
It's really weird, which you never see on a sitcom of this nature.
For any criticism you might have of it, they're always
very solidly made.
They're always extremely clean.
So, yeah, it's weird to hear.
Yeah. What is also probably a very when Stefan is transformed
back to Oracle at the ending of the Family Matters saga,
there is so much coat rub on the lav mic consistently for like
a handful of lines that it's pretty awesome.
Like, I didn't know if like I was getting some HBO Max
special edition of the episode, like unaltered.
I was like, this couldn't have aired.
Maybe, though, they didn't know this was uncharted territory for all these shows.
They didn't travel. They didn't know how to do this.
It does feel like in the old days, you know, you watch movies,
not even that old movies sometimes.
And you go, oh, this whole scene seems like it's 80 yard,
which means that they had to redo like the sound.
I mean, they always redo sound effects, but they read the dialogue
and you can see it's like doesn't quite match the mouths.
That was an option to do here.
And they said, you know what? Fuck it. Yeah.
Who gives? No kids doesn't give them good shit.
Yeah, that is weird. It isn't super 80 yard.
Yeah, for sure. Yeah.
Was there just too much
in inventions like actual
attraction noise in the background for them to have like a backup boom
mic recording the dialogue?
It's just too many say, no, we tried.
We did have that audio track for everyone talking on a boom,
but there was too much Sega Genesis click clacking in the background.
Let us close the Sonic games now.
Yeah, we could not close the vector man displays.
Kidding. I guess we're going to if we're going to move from Full House,
the only thing I want to mention that I had fully forgotten and is special
is the is Joey at the animation studios and seeing the boy
animated Joey come to life, which is who's doing the voice
for the cartoon Joe because
Joey does voices, but it doesn't sound like him. Am I wrong?
Is it? I think it might be him.
OK, OK. It's just a it's odd.
Choice. He's definitely like suddenly he's
super Brooklyny out of nowhere.
He's a little like Brooklyn Pipsqueak kid who.
Yeah, just to set the scene, you know, they used to have the animation tour
at Disney, MGM Studios and kind of without explanation,
Joey is just like walking and talking on the floor
with an animator who he's like good friends with.
Seemingly, I think it's one of the major ones. His name is Mark.
I think that's Mark Finn who did Jasmine.
But don't quote me on that.
Mark Henney is what I read. Oh, that's that might be right.
Yeah, that sounds right.
Anyways, he offers him some coffee.
Joey asked if he could get some crazy cartoon stuff.
The guy says, I think coffee will do.
And then he's left alone to start doodling.
He draws a cartoon version of himself, which comes to life,
is drawn in like simple pencil drawn form.
And then you get the hijinks of Joey, like adding new parts to him
and embedding and squishing and squashing.
It's yeah. And this is a show
that doesn't full house doesn't have magic otherwise.
Doesn't get surreal. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, no, it's maybe the first time ever.
So to see some Disney magic sprinkled into full house is a lot of fun.
And that specific stuff that he's that a cartoon,
Joey is saying like, hey, down here, you're you're new at this, right?
Now that you mention it, could you draw me a couple of aspirin?
I didn't catch that.
I had not to reference the thing that people have not seen yet,
but I was certainly it's it's very little Bruce, is it not?
Sure, sure, sure. Yeah.
A tease for the show.
I kind of wish in hindsight, they could have just taken this little character
and just made him like Joey's great
Gazoo going forward, where he was like a character over Joey's shoulder.
The rest of the like the rest of the episodes are running.
You know, it's remembering and I don't know.
I feel like Scott, we might have brought this up when we were working on
the show Saturday, Saturday morning.
All started. Sorry to plug the full title, but these straight to video
cassettes McGee and me, do you do you all are you aware of those?
I don't know those there.
They're Christian, as I recall.
And it's it's a similar set up, I believe, where like it's a cartoon character
who's like maybe first drawn and then pops out of the page
and becomes like this kid's best friend.
But the characteristics match this Joey thing.
So could be something to do a side by side if anybody has any time.
I don't know. I'm just just coming to me right now.
Sure. Yeah.
Paracontrast of young Joey, your cartoon, Joey and McGee and me. Yeah.
I totally agree, though, that, yeah, there's like
because he doesn't have a kid of his own and I think he continues to not
on Fuller House.
So if he if his child essentially is the little Joey that he drew one day
and he cares for and he stays that age always, he never grows up
like other kids, like just like Joey himself never grows up.
Well, with this cartoon voices and all.
I think they can.
The little guy can feud with the puppet.
You know, Mr. Woodchuck.
Yeah. Oh, the Woodchuck puppet. Yeah, sure. Yeah.
What was his name? Who was the who was the Woodchuck?
Mr. Was it Mr. Woodchuck?
It was just Mr. Woodchuck. Oh, yeah, I think so.
Woodchuck. Yeah. Yes. Yeah. OK.
Yeah. Ranger Joe and Mr. Woodchuck.
And then, of course, there is the jackalope on America's Funniest People.
Well, that's a whole other.
No, no, no, no, no, that's this.
I was.
Recording out of order, I'll I'll.
Confusingly, the episode will come up before this.
I'm planning on bringing up the jackalope.
I hadn't thought about the jackal. Oh, wow.
You're the jackal. It was weird, right?
That's a this is this other Dave Coulier show that was kind of his
America's Funniest Home videos.
Erin called it out.
She's like, this is basically this is like they're trying to do
Caddyshack and the gopher. Oh, yeah.
I've not watched a jackalope segment in probably two decades.
So I'll have to.
I'll have to get on that.
Forest animal terrorizing.
This show was strange.
This is a show that aired for three seasons and yet no one recalls.
Do you remember the America's Funniest People?
Funniest people. Yeah.
It would be on Sunday nights with America's Funniest Home.
And it was Dave Coulier and Tawny Cattain.
Yeah, correct.
You know, we're taking care of it now.
We can just maybe we don't have to do it a week ago.
I'm so confused by the time we'll do it anyway.
All right. Apologies for more America's.
I was I was just, you know, the jackalope's back in my life
and I'm happy to be talking about him again.
Full house. Real quick, I'll just say this is going back to the
Jesse and the Rippers thing real quick.
Like and this is no put down of what I'll say that they should be doing,
but Jesse and the Rippers should be playing at like the stage outside of Earl of Sandwich.
That would have been a much more realistic place.
And again, I'm not putting I've just great bands that play there.
But that would have been more realistic for him going to Becky.
Like we have a great gig.
We're paying we're playing seven times a night
out by the Earl of Sandwich in downtown Disney.
That is where cover bands actually play.
Right. 20 minute sets.
And that's what they should have had.
The whole climax of the episode happened there, not in front of the castle.
But that concert is like unbelievable, right?
I mean, with the white piano, like it it has the vibe of like
like a it's a it's a live aid or like a, you know,
one of the last Freddie Mercury concerts or something like this is like
this is an unbelievable show that they're putting on that culminates in fireworks.
I really love that little like mumbled
this is this is a song for all the dreamers out there.
Or he does.
But it's not when you wish upon a star.
It's a dream is a wish your heart makes.
Yeah, right. Right.
A very breathy version of a dream.
You're a wish your heart is.
Jesse's hot.
He's so sexy.
He has to he can't.
There's no way to do a not sultry version of something.
No, he uses sultriness.
And again, that fireworks display,
that is like, how does it work?
Like so again, like Danny Tanner has been trying to propose
to his fiance at all time, struggling to find a way.
And it seemingly within the course of several hours
communicates with the Disney company and allows for the
creation of like the most complex
block of firework text ever made that isn't flashing on and off.
It like appears once, but it's not attached to wires or a framework or anything.
It's just the floating words.
Vicky, will you marry me?
That just stay in the sky unbroken for seven seconds or so.
Yeah, I do think this and I think I'm being serious.
I do think this made me think you could do this in real life.
And yet you didn't do it for your own marriage proposal.
Well, I inquired inquired.
And such an iconic just the setup of the guy
constantly trying to to ask the question and get interrupted.
I feel like we need a supercut of the like, would you
like to go clogging with it?
I don't know what I don't know what happens
in the German area, but
it's pretty it's actually pretty infuriating that he can't just say it.
Yeah, yeah.
By context clues, she should understand like it's an important question
that he's tried several times to ask.
I was impressed by her performance,
because I didn't recall how this concluded.
And she kind of plays it like can go either way for a second.
I think she played the drama of that scene very well.
So congrats.
Do we know that actor's name offhand who played?
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know. Offhand.
And I always felt bad that it didn't work out like I was rooting for him.
I liked Vicky a lot.
And it kind of deflates this whole episode to know that it didn't.
Yes, it does.
And that he spent all that money, you know, getting close to six figures,
I would think, to make that display.
And he didn't get a bride out of it.
And all those itineraries he made, there was a line earlier
where he made everyone itinerary.
That wasn't cool.
Everybody threw away the itineraries immediately.
Yeah, they wanted to do their own thing.
Now, granted, most of the adults are wearing business casuals.
So like they're not going to go to nuts that day. Yeah.
Joey's wardrobe in that, by the way, very bizarre.
It's like, oh, yeah, collared shirt with wacky pattern,
but then blazer and shorts shorts shorts.
Yeah. Yeah.
Sport coat and shorts, which is really I mean, I didn't even pick up
on that outfit until his kind of emotional sit down with Stephanie,
where he's like hyper serious in that it's like
he's like a clown that's trying to dress up essentially.
Yeah, like a real it's it's very sincere as and then just whenever it cuts
to the two shot, just like big old man leg up on that bench.
When we were talking about like how this
the sensibility of these TGIF shows influenced my work, our work, whatever.
Like, I don't even know what I how I can articulate what this is
or what this type of joke is or why it resonates with me.
But the in the midst of
a moment when DJ claims to see Steve and
he's not actually there.
I believe Stephanie says something to the effect of like up next,
women who hallucinate and theme parks on the next Oprah.
I don't know why.
I guess I just like that it's like this feels like it's like
a daring joke for them to some degree. You know what I mean?
They're like making a comment on TV culture.
It's like contemporary and hip to some degree, even though I don't know
that like Oprah is necessarily known for that, like kind of Maury Povich,
Jerry Springer style, like.
You know that she would bring that up, like that would be a subject of an episode,
but maybe it was in like 1993.
But I guess these are these kids are like cool and clever
and versed in television and they're able to to like
riff to and reference to like a Dennis Miller degree,
even though they're only 16.
That's how TV brained.
You're right. And I love and I can't in step in the step by step episode.
And I can't even think of the references that are that are are are thrown out
there, even though I might have my notes.
But this mix of one thing that I've always been obsessed with, like
I want to say Flash when we get to I mean, I'm very excited to talk about Flash.
Oh, yes. Yeah.
But I really episode Flash is making some
he's making some reference about like what is America because he wants to win,
set this regain the record for America anyway.
He's like Americans like our mom, Americans like the but master,
which is as I saw it is like clearly an analog
for the thigh master, which Suzanne Summers was a
spokesperson for. Yeah.
And this is what I like.
Why is it that Oprah exists, but the thigh master doesn't?
And this is something that I that I picked up on, say, by the bell as a child.
Like in on these shows that I I really am obsessed with.
Like when do we get to choose the real thing and when not?
You know what I mean?
The inconsistency of what exists and what doesn't exist in this world.
I mean, you're your your favorite one.
I have to pimp you out to say the the band on Saved by the Bell.
That's the greatest.
Yes. On on I think it's what is the Zack attack episode when
they have a band, the band is playing in the garage.
The manager of the Beach Buddies runs past them,
hears them playing and essentially like says he wants to, you know,
I don't know, sign, give them a record contract or everybody's like,
they're like, oh, you're you manage the Beach Buddies.
He's like, oh, yeah, but the Beach Buddies aren't buddies anymore.
But the point, but the thing is, like
the Beach Boys have been referenced in this universe,
and yet they're kind of presenting the Beach Buddies as the Beach Boys.
It's like in another show that thought about any of this would go,
well, do we have a Madonna or not?
Or do we have to make up a Madonna equivalent?
Like they make these choices, but these shows are done so slapdash that like,
does it matter? We've already mentioned the Beach Boys.
No, there can be the Beach Buddies.
So and we can make a joke about how they aren't buddies.
We can make a joke playing on their name that we made up.
We're subverting a thing that doesn't exist.
Yes, no one cared at a certain time, you know, but now
there's a line in Step by Step where it's like, oh, if this was made now,
there'd be so many minders on set because one of the characters go like,
we should go check out the haunted house.
And like, you know, if that was shot now,
there would be a Disney rep going like, you need her to say that line again
so she can say Haunted Mansion properly. Thank you so much.
I yeah, there's another one that's about like the jungle boat ride.
This is never happening today.
I we're asking what are second gates that we should do.
And loud and clear one that was said was Disney fairy tale weddings,
the wedding show that's available on Disney+.
So I was I was prepping for this one in advance.
I was starting to watch some of the and there's a couple
that is the first couple ever to get married in Pandora.
And so this is a Pandoran wedding.
But I go to CIVACO indeed.
But they it's just funny hearing this couple, these very like regular
people have to say, and we are so excited to be the first couple
to get married in Pandora, the world of Avatar.
When no one even the biggest, the biggest Pandora fan.
By that, I mean, Mike is not regularly saying Pandora, the world of Avatar.
No, but I will from now on if that's what they want me to.
Sure, make sure you do.
I'll call you on it if you don't say it.
Can I maybe I miss under misheard, but I just just did a double check.
Suzanne Summers had the Thighmaster and the Buttmaster.
They were both. Oh, OK.
So I was misinformed. OK, so the Buttmaster is a real thing.
Yeah, I'm looking at it right now because I it's weird to bring it up
because it's less OK. Yeah, there you have it.
OK, yeah, I fully I feel bad about that.
I'm sorry. I didn't sound it.
This isn't gotcha journalism on my part.
I just I was just trying to remember what it was.
But it does sound like a fan.
And your point still stands that this was happening all the time
where it was like, why not just say that?
No, you know, Mike, no, it doesn't stand.
Yeah, did I feel bad?
Oh, man, I shouldn't have told you about the.
So sorry. No, I know.
You're right. The Buttmaster does sound it does sound like a 90s joke, like.
Right. For sure. That's right.
And it's less famous than the Thighmaster.
So they shouldn't have said something that wasn't going to read immediately.
They can't count on everybody looking it up on on a website after the fact.
Right. That was also love you sharing your screen, Mike,
and then seeing your your previously on eBay,
just that there were recently looked at turtles.
Oh, yeah. And large turtles, too. Expensive. Oh, they're big.
Yeah, they were one sixth or one quarter scale, actually, which is pretty big.
She's yeah, that is unusually big.
Bigger than my son.
I just you can buy a third scale of the Joaquin Phoenix Joker, which is huge.
You know, it looks exactly it looks so accurate.
He's like a man.
Like, why wouldn't you?
I could see wanting that for, you know,
Winnie the Pooh for something like cute or
an animal. Why would you want a guy?
You're asking a good question, but they obviously think there's a market for it.
So it's you're considering that one.
It's about a grand.
You can buy it. Jesus.
Well, it's a good thing to have if you want to like give anyone
you're thinking about dating a major red flag as soon as they come in your apartment.
That's a good point.
There's one more of those little like sentence interrupters, Kyle, where you.
OK, so one thing to mention,
you watch the entire Indiana Jones stunt spectacular fold out like
not the entire show, I guess, but the full boulder sequence happens
over the course of five minutes.
And that's another great thing about these episodes for these shows.
We can kill a bunch of time.
Let's just show all of Indiana Jones in the boulder.
Let's show a big concert like we're going to burn through these two episodes
in no time.
In this case, DJ's hallucinations are continuing.
She believes that she is seeing her boyfriend, Steve, as Indiana Jones.
Then when the stunt happens and he gets run over by the boulder,
and I'm sure I referenced this in our episode about this stunt show,
the entire audience gasps because they buy the gag 100 percent.
And DJ stands up and says, Steve, no silence.
One believes you're actually here.
Awesome. Love it.
Love these. This this mechanism of.
Try having to save the sentence.
This is only in sitcoms and movies, but I think we should all.
Yeah, I also caught how it was fascinating because, like, you're right,
the stunt had concluded, essentially.
He pops up and then you would expect the audience to applaud.
She gets the Steve comment out,
but there's still like an awkward silence until there's a sound cue
that's like, do do do do.
And then the audience applaud.
I just don't believe that everybody is going to be fully silent for DJ
to to question where Steve is to say that entire thing.
I don't think that the show was timed out to have just like a six second.
Like it is Indiana Jones dead
where there is no music cue accompanying it.
I'm sure you we all know.
I mean, this almost exact sequence, it feels like,
was repeated for step by step, like moment by moment.
Yeah. Full thing again, entire.
We got to go through the spikes.
We got it.
We I like that they play the tension of the trading out the idol
for the bag of sand or whatever, like they do.
Indiana Jones is tension as if it's the character Flash or Steve's tension.
But like it is like it's a fake stunt show.
He doesn't need to make the trade out as much as Indiana Jones does.
It was fun, though, seen like kind of from an an act early place,
like kind of, you know, where kind of Steve and Flash's versions of Indy.
I think they both both of theirs deserve merit.
I might actually take Flash over, Steve, I hate to say it.
Yeah, good. Flash is really good.
Flash has a purpose.
He has more of a reason for being there.
He's got the energy.
Flash is a little more energy as far as that performance, I guess, too.
I love Flash so much.
I think maybe we go out with Flash.
I think maybe Flash concludes the episode.
I think it's the peak of narrative content at Disney World.
So let's let's shift over to Family Matters, the episode
We're Going to Disney World, the two parter that began on April 28th, 1995.
Overall, this might be my favorite, and maybe this is just
my love of Urkel that Mike has pointed out,
poking through.
I know. I think it's not only my love of Urkel.
It's my love of Karl Winslow and Reginald Vel Johnson.
I think Reginald Vel Johnson is the strongest performer on any of these shows.
I think that's the reason why it's easier maybe to watch a Family Matters
than some of these other shows.
He's just so charming and fun.
When he's happy or happy, when he's mad,
you're scared.
I love I'm just in for whatever Karl Winslow is going through.
I completely agree.
I wrote the note down that like Karl is also the most happy to be here
of all the characters and all the episodes we watched as well, which is fun to see.
Karl's the most excited.
So it's like it is fun to like live through the Karl's enthusiasm.
The actors playing his wife and mother are also very good.
Like I rewatching it, I was like,
Oh, the grandmother's really funny on this show.
I forgot about that.
Yes. Rosetta Lenoir, I believe, is so funny.
And maybe another thing to say, but I think all of the way that I say
that all of these episodes are the same, they all start with like a scene or two
back in the regular set just to acquaint you.
And there's you have to figure out how to get the characters to Disney World.
Usually it starts with just two of them are going to do it.
And then everybody gloms on or it's a good thing.
Wherever that where I'm inviting everybody in this case,
the impetus is that Urkel has been invited to participate
in an inventor competition at Epcot Center.
And he is inviting everybody in that not his family to go with him.
Well, he's inviting all of his neighbors, but not his girlfriend.
Right. Oh, yeah. Wait, my.
Yeah, why isn't Myra?
And that is strange.
That was I mean, like how how many plus ones does one get in that one of these
in in innoventions contest?
Because that's how many people that was like seven, eight.
I don't even know how many.
It's it's not like the Oscars where you maybe only get a date.
It's more like the Miss America pageant
where you want to bring an entire fan section for yourself.
Mm hmm.
This is like Rock and Roll Hall of Fame where you get like a table,
but you have to pay for the table, maybe.
Oh, yeah. Those guys, they're mad every year.
Steve Miller took him to task. That's right.
This isn't the Rock Hall podcast.
Yeah, sorry, sorry.
No, I would just start doing the Rock Hall.
Yeah, everybody's excited, except for Carl,
who is too addicted to his police work to cut off and relax for a little bit.
And then his mom tells a very sad story
about how on his deathbed, Carl's dad,
he his last words were, I never got to take little Carl to Disney World.
And then he died.
And that is moving enough that Carl realizes that he needs to do
the family trip to put work to the side.
And then she, the mom quietly admits that that was a made up story
and that that never happened. That rascal.
In addition to the Inventors contest,
the justification for getting them to Disney World in this show
involves lying about a dying man's last words.
So, Brad, it's a pretty funny dark joke.
Like they say, like he died years before Disney World opened.
Oh, yeah. Oh, I love that flippant way that like he died
way before that place was ever built.
There is so much lying going on on all these shows, like week to week.
The amount of lies characters tell each other and not little stuff, big stuff.
Weekly is always impressive to me going back to watch.
That's true. That's kind of the that is sort of the like central mechanism
of a lot of sitcoms is people like keeping up ruses.
Huge thinking that they can't. Yeah.
Yeah. They require them to like play parts and pull in people in their lives.
Now, you have to be this part.
You got to pretend to be my cousin or my wife or whatever.
Even though like every scam unravels, they just keep doing it and doing it.
Yeah, I was I mean, like, I don't know if this falls into that same category,
but I was really disappointed in Laura for for messing with the chamber.
Like that. Yeah.
No, that felt like very wrong to me as it was happening.
Like this felt like such a big deal for for Steve.
And yeah, that's incredibly selfish.
Incredibly. That's like a like relationship ender for like,
oh, you did something that will prevent me from going back to who my normal self.
Like that's a crazy thing.
I'm trying to think of like a real world equivalent.
Yeah. I say you were on a trip and you like had a car and somebody like I
cut all the tires on your car so you would stay here longer.
You'd be like, what the fuck are you talking about?
Why would you do that?
Like I get like that's sweet that you want me here.
But obviously, like something's wrong.
Like that's a misery situation. Yeah.
Yeah. That's like a fatal attraction. Yeah.
There's also like some weird dynamics in this of like the psychosexual politics
of like Stefan and Laura and the Myron Steve.
And it's like, well, if he changes his DNA, if it is another person,
but an only person exists occasionally, like it's like, oh, bizarre, bizarre.
Do you wrap?
Try to step back and wrap your head around this thing that no one was
probably really thinking about that much in the writers.
No. As Kyle was saying, with the logic of pop culture references,
I just love that these shows in there, who cares?
Let's get it done. We got to go to lunch.
And like give us these riddles that we've been unpacking since we were 10 years old.
Maybe I still do feel bad about the butt master stuff. OK.
I'm sorry. I'll cut it out.
I'll cut it out. No, no, you don't have to.
But immediately I'm like, I'm living the fantasy of like somebody listening to me
talk like go off on the butt master, like, whoa, no, this is not right.
And the kind of thank God moment that like Mike, I am thankful that you looked that up.
No, I'm sorry. I feel now I feel bad because I didn't want to butt.
Like I don't want to make no every the world might not know about the butt master.
And, you know, I need to tell them it was too good to be true.
The idea that that flash would make up an apparatus called the butt
master in terms of like all that makes America great.
That's a stand in for the real invention that is hawked by the star of the show.
Really go either way.
But it is also worth mentioning that it's like oddly,
an oddly patriotic sea story to stick into that.
That's that common.
Right. Yeah.
Look, Kyle, the degree of knowledge and accuracy
and getting stuff right on this podcast is exceedingly high, almost never.
I've never.
So we will forgive you in this this instance, but we're trying to.
I appreciate it.
I'm glad I'm glad that you that that you checked me on that.
And we didn't have to have like
ongoing sitcom hijinks where we created a world where we're pretending that that
was, oh, yeah, I know.
For years, I don't want to be talking about like.
And then there's the episode where he says, but master.
So I follow you around.
I was going to YouTube comment.
I was Car the Dracula for the longest time, and then I was shamed for it.
And, you know, well, it's best if we can be our own regulators
and do the shaming for each other.
We are our own ombudsman.
Yeah. Mm hmm.
I also thought maybe I'd say but master, it's real.
And then there would be a rift or two.
You know, I was thinking maybe, you know, so I wasn't even maybe
totally incorrect. I wasn't even thinking correctional wise.
I was just thinking, oh, did that exist?
You know, but.
Well, was it familiar?
Was it familiar to you?
Did it make did you remember it all or was it like, I just want to look up.
But I'm asked vaguely familiar, vaguely familiar.
And I was like, I wonder that does sound because there were so many
those 90s at home things you would like your mom would buy.
I don't know my mom in a book.
She has like my mom still has like this weird like saucer thing
she exercises on that she bought from like late night TV.
And I'm like, I think she'd be upset that you were even like bringing up
the possibility that she had the but master.
Mm hmm.
I don't think so, but you never know.
I'll say that. I don't think so.
That's why all the whole but master thread will get pulled from the episode,
not the accuracy issue.
But yeah, it's like I run into an issue.
Yeah, the but master does exist, folks.
It was real and you can buy it on eBay.
It was real. It does.
I mean, in the way that it does sound like a cheap sitcom toss off joke, it does
very clearly sound like the thymaster was a hit.
And they're like, well, we need something else.
We need someone else. What else you got?
Yeah. You know, and they really quickly rushed it out.
Right. Work. You can't like put one of those things between your butt cheeks, right?
That's not what it is.
It's not a little bit.
Shreer, Scott, you can.
And you will.
And here's a demonstration.
The thing goes in. Yeah, that little ball goes in your anus.
And then the great.
Yeah. My issue with my blood is that the cheeks aren't spread wide enough.
I wish an implement could help me.
Exactly. OK, let's let's explain the transformation chamber thing.
Just the math of it to be to be very clear.
And again, I just think that we were so lucky with all these episodes.
All the shows are in their primes.
Jesse has the band.
Urkel has the transformation chamber.
He has invented a machine that we know just to be clear.
Step by step is not and we are post prime for step by step.
Yeah. Step by step.
It have a prime. Characters at this point.
I don't I lost track of who was what, whose kid.
But I kept going like, where is the older one?
And it's just like, oh, he was kind of written out at the end of the season.
The nephew like. Oh, well, that's a whole yeah.
Well, that's why there is a flash.
Urkel, a nerd has invented a machine that you can walk into
that changes you from a nerd into not a nerd anymore.
And in his case, it turns him into the very suave
Stefan Urkel, who I I just want to say,
I really like the specific mold of cool guy that Stefan Urkel is.
It reminds it's like boys to men and baby face and like
the vibe of the movie Boomerang.
I haven't seen Boomerang, but I feel like that's kind of that's just like
the type of like gentleman that that Stefan is.
And it's, you know, look, Jaleel with his multi character abilities.
I think he really nails it.
You love Urkel and then like, could there be somebody you love more?
And I think I don't know.
I love Stefan. I love every time Stefan.
And you got you.
You have to give props to Laura is so infatuated with Stefan
in a fun, in a fun, almost cartoonish way, like when whenever Stefan enter,
like whenever he's mentioned, she's just so ready for it.
Is that's the the deepest love there ever was.
It's like, yeah, it's like the Chase Meridian Batman.
Or she's just like, oh, my God, I can't even imagine.
Like, I can't even hear the name or else I go nuts.
One one Stefan thing that I noticed that maybe again is maybe
maybe it's not that peculiar and like maybe there's more information necessary.
But there was a scene and I don't know what's happening, but he's
with Laura and he pulls out a wad of cash.
Do you guys recall this?
Oh, it's for it's when he's paying for the
the artist who's who's doing their like their portraits, their
oh, like in the in France and yes, exactly.
And like he pulls out a lot of money, which got me think like,
is Stefan rich? Is he like richer than Urkel?
Did Urkel have that money on him?
But he's just so suave.
Yeah. Where does that money come from?
Are like are random women just giving him money for no reason?
Just to say thanks for giving me something to look at?
Because his clothes are different.
Yeah. And is that part of the transformation chamber?
Yeah, it feels like it's some sort of like dimensional reality
altering thing.
It's not just making the human body different or the brain different.
It feels like it's actually altering reality.
So my I'm just this is off the top of my head.
I think the money is created by the machine
because a cool guy like that would have more money than a non-cool.
And those are that's probably like, yes, those suits are not inexpensive.
That's probably like Italian made like.
Yeah. So I think that the yeah, the machine,
they don't explain it on the show, but it alters reality in some way.
So then it takes it away to like when he gets back in the chamber
and becomes Urkel again, right.
However much money Stefan had in his wallet is eliminated
and decreases.
Yeah, if it's if it's on him, but if it's left in the other world,
I think like like Stefan could leave his sack of money outside of the machine,
get into the machine and Urkel could change back and Urkel could take the money
because Urkel still knows he's Stefan.
He has memories of Stefan.
And where does Urkel go when he's Stefan?
Like, where is Urkel's soul?
Well, like there's a there's a you know, this is a comic book reference,
but there's a thing place called the negative zone.
The fantastic it's kind of like
it's almost like we're like a containment unit and Ghostbusters.
You know, what is this like sort of not real play?
It exists on some sort of other plane and it's like a limbo of sorts.
Is Urkel stuck in limbo with unbaptized babies?
You know,
it's possible they're there all the time.
Yeah. Well, with the Urkel Stefan dichotomy,
Laura's lie isn't just
breaking the machine so that he stays Stefan and doesn't turn back into nerd
Urkel. You know, sure, it messes up the results of this inventor contest,
but then the further ramification that like a soul will be gone.
Like Urkel is no more.
Urkel just lives in oblivion now, which by all what, you know,
you always make a lot out of how Family Matters started as a very grounded show
and then became about inventions and time travel and stuff.
But this is one of the headiest.
This is just like a regular family police officer with a bunch of kids.
And now his daughter is dealing with a scenario where a soul is in limbo
because of a DNA machine.
The father and that could affect their lives for 80 years.
That's like that's a major part of being a Winslow now. Right. Yeah.
Also, how old is Laura supposed to be?
She like 20 at this point.
It's like a few seasons in.
Not sure.
I think that was my guess, but I don't know. Yeah.
They in step by step, the the two, the one kid and friend are like,
we're saving for an apartment.
And I'm like, you look like children.
How old are these characters?
Laura breaks the fibrillating
rebobulator, which causes this live inventor
contest that's happening on the floor of interventions to be delayed for three days.
That's how long it'll take to.
Well, I don't because nobody's working on the machine.
Really arbitrary.
I was sort of bothered by
how quickly they allowed
Urkel, Stefan
this opportunity, like in what is seemingly a very organized sort of contest.
And it's similar to in step by step when
Karen's in this country,
find a star contest where she just leaves the stage
and then she's allowed to just come back and they're like, now I'm ready.
And then she's back in the contest.
Similarly, like, all right, we'll give you a few days to figure this out.
That just doesn't.
I don't know if I if I believe that that reality that whatever this
not that I know anything about this inventing contest, but they're so quick
to be on Urkel's side to prove whatever this DNA things that he has to prove.
But famously, you choked in your SNL audition, ran away in tears.
Now I'm ready back and said, can I get an extra two days?
Then you went and had a bunch of New York adventures
came back better than ever.
Yeah, it's it is completely it feels like a Florida recount
in the pocket for the Republicans, like which maybe, you know,
what happens with those things are these people like hobnob at a party and now like,
all right, well, I'll remember you when the time comes.
And in this case, Urkel did in the hotel lobby meet
Martin Fisher, publisher of Inventors Weekly,
who all ahead of the competition, who then is the emcee of it.
So I don't think that should have been allowed.
Like you shouldn't get to meet the judge.
You shouldn't be able to do Pratt fault nerd pratfalls.
The second nerd pratfalls in like a five minute span
with the supposed authority of this contest, because they're both nerds
and they both bonding.
I think even though they're not like actively bonding, they're both bonding
while they trip over each other.
Yeah. Speak an unwritten language, you know, a secret language.
Right. Dropping things.
There's really good, by the way, physical comedy, I think, in the lobby of,
in this case, the wilderness lodge.
That's the hotel that's being placed.
Placement for the wilderness lodge and interventions
and Tower of Terror, all of which would have been fairly new at the time of the show.
Those are good things to push.
I like I think a couple of these, they make the characters for no reason,
kind of run past the sign of the new Tomorrowland at the time.
I like seeing that sign.
That's another great thing about these shows.
They all like preserve the parks and the hotels in their mid
90s, pristine new peak Eisner vibe.
Yeah. Is that do we know what?
I assume it's a pleasure island club.
Now, this spoiler alert later on in the step by step,
they are at the neon armadillo.
Correct. Which is a big deal for us.
You pleasure island heads out there.
But do we know are they at Manicure?
Do we know if they're at the club in this?
Like on a pleasure island, do we know where like that contest is being?
Oh, no, the contest is interventions.
Oh, wait, I'm getting confused.
Yeah, that's step by step is the OK.
Yes. But they're they are at a place.
Some are at a nightclub at one.
That's what I'm thinking. Oh, yes.
Oh, my God. You're right. That part is incredible.
I didn't realize when when they're
Stefan and Laura have nothing but time to go date and explore Disney World.
Oh, my God. That's so epic when it zooms in on that
dance floor with the light up screens that spell out is that Stefan Hart, Laura.
I mean, that looks like the best nightclub I've ever seen.
And I would know I know nightclubs.
And according to that pleasure island Facebook group, I read Mannequins was the best.
Maybe that was Mannequins.
I don't know.
People know offhand big light up screens
that you could have made, say, Stefan Hart, Laura, just watching them date is great.
I believe that montage is set to a cool version of Kiss the Girl.
That's another throughout these.
I didn't say in full house, so you get to hear like the full house
kind of like jamming, I love playing When You Wish Upon a Star.
Yeah, that's great.
Now, well, yeah, I would mark that down because I love those
uh, sitcom musical interludes.
Yeah, exactly.
Exactly. Yeah. And to hear the Disney five versions.
But there was also earlier in this they do kiss the girl.
But there's a song that plays earlier.
I think maybe it's for a Carl montage.
And I wrote down, yes, that song is Every Day Sunshine.
Yes. Is that a Disney song?
What is I guess I didn't know what that was.
I should have looked it up before.
Isn't it by a fishbone?
I was going to say, oh, gotcha.
Those nineties Lauren B type. Yeah. Yeah.
That part, that sequence is the best.
That's the kind of thing I love where like it's not drama and stakes
and characters lying to each other.
The point of this sequence is Carl has decided he's going to have fun
in Disney World and put his troubles to the side.
And then he just has a moment with every character.
He and Donald rub their seats around.
They have a lot of fun.
Then all the characters gather in a big tableau and the whole audience cheers.
There's just a huge hooray.
It's Carl and the characters.
There's no stakes or drama.
It's just you just get to see Carl Winslow having a blast.
Mm hmm. That's really fun.
I can't find a good picture of this mannequin stage, but it's possible.
I think it could be it, though.
I think it's possible because they do have like a big light.
Oh, oh, oh, whoa, whoa.
Whoa, let me let me see.
Let me take your guys's temperature on this.
Do you think this is that's a big light screen?
Yeah, it looks like it might be it. Right.
Damn. I think there's a decent chance somebody correct us if please.
I'll be corrected in the comments if this is wrong and it was not mannequins.
But I have information about pinettas when we get to that.
Oh, I want to know all Jason and pinettas.
I'm so excited. Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I'm all about.
Also, here's that Joker statue I was talking about.
Oh, wow. Oh, that's worth thirteen hundred dollars.
That's two hundred dollar nonrefundable deposit, too.
Is that like is this like a FBI snaring situation
they think are they running a sting by the product that doesn't exist?
I'll take him. Look, if I buy it and I'll take him to court for entrapment.
So anyways, yeah, Stefan and Laura
go on a bunch of dates to go to the sci fi dine in theater.
I like seeing that.
And then there's this massive
engagement ceremony.
Love, Stefan. There you are.
The sun, the rain is this.
Oh, how much he puts into the rain.
I'm in love with them. I'm in love with Stefan.
I'd say yes.
Stefan asks Carl for Laura's hand,
and he's maybe more primed to say yes, because he's having such a fun time.
He's he's having such a fun time.
And this is might be relatable for, you know, certainly Mike and Jason,
maybe me, maybe Kyle, I don't know, the feeling of being in Disney World,
having so much fun that maybe you think, should I live in Orlando?
Should I move here forever?
That's what Carl's grappling with.
Yeah, I can relate to that.
It's a conversation we all have a couple of times a week
in our heads.
But yeah,
I'm pulled the trigger.
Not yet. We're all cowards.
Not yet. We're all cowardly up until Jason is one day,
texts us and goes, I did it.
And I'm here with like keys in his hand.
He's in a trailer outside on the ground so he can vote.
So we can vote in the local election.
Here's another one of those repeat situations.
Long sequence where the stakes of the episode,
a little scene happens in front of the elevator doors of the Tower of Terror.
Then they go in and sit.
The elevator goes up. They get the view.
There's a creepy elevator guy who says, enjoy your ride.
And then the drop and it's scary.
And the same promotional footage is used of the elevator.
All the same stuff happens in step by step.
They do every beat of this, the same direction, the same staging.
And is it the same guy?
Yeah, the same guy, too. Yes.
I say this in dignity or something like it's a problem.
I guess why is it?
I like the scene.
I was seeing my friends go on the ride.
And the elevator operator, I'm wondering, like,
and I'm sure we can figure this out very quickly.
This is an actor, right?
This is not where we're assuming not a Disney park employee
who actually is an elevator operator.
Or what are the odds of that? Do you think?
There might have been a guy who was really good at it.
A little. Yeah, some people play it up a little if they're working in the parks.
But this guy seems pretty picture perfect, you know?
So you think he was this actor was hired on two separate occasions
to play the elevator operator?
Or do you think this is a one and do you think they may have shot
step by step around the same time?
I think they were shot for far enough from each other
that that wouldn't be the case, I think.
But maybe they had the I don't know.
Family Matters was April of 95.
Step by step is February of 96.
So it could just be the same local actor they hired for both.
Or a guy who worked on the ride.
And they're like, we we need you to come back.
You do get people sometimes on rides where they do.
You know how you like, you know, you would spot a star
at Schwab's drugstore or something like you do have people.
You go to a ride and you go, well, that person on Haunted Mansion
is like 10 times better than everyone.
Everyone is good.
But it does happen where you go.
I saw like there was a guy who was doing the old Tower of Terror
a couple of years ago where he was like so good and scaring everybody
and scaring like little kids in a fun way.
It was something they talked up a lot doing the Universal Tour.
Like when I was doing the training of it, they said,
and for the aspiring actors out there, think about where you're working.
You're on Hollywood's doorstep.
You're trying to get discovered.
There's producers on that tram every day.
Well, what?
I believe the times this actually worked out for anyone was zero, I think.
But I could be wrong.
People are quiet about their tour guide pass.
Was the whole and step by step was was the Tower of Terror
was in the second episode, right?
That was in part two. Yeah.
That's another same thing.
If we're talking about the Venn diagram, the Family Matters episodes are called
We're going to Disney World.
The step by step episodes are called We're going to Disney World.
Yes. Started getting a little lazy with the and all of it
basically cribbing the format of what Full House laid out.
So really, you got to give them the credit for cracking the formula.
Full House called the House Meets the Mouse. Is that right?
More inventive title.
Yeah, more inventive title.
I by the time they get to step by step.
Yeah, they're repeating a lot of the attractions and stuff.
From Family Matters.
The the big difference is in step by step.
They appear to be staying at the Old Key West Resort, the Vacation Club Resort,
because they also you would know which one it's clearly a vacation club.
Yeah, because they also they get dropped off in an old timey car,
which are parked in front of some of the hotels.
But Jane caught that the car door had the vacation club logo very small on it.
And I was like, I think that's Key West,
because it looks like there's a golf course outside the door.
They had to push that the with by getting a vacation club condo.
There's plenty of room for your giant family to all travel the Disney World together.
But they never mention it in this one.
I feel like the other ones, they either name or at least have a big shot.
Yeah, yeah. They lay on the promotion a lot thicker.
What else about about Family Matters before we move on?
Other than that, like I just enjoy this one quite a bit.
Well, I guess we're plot wise.
We have, yeah, Carl deciding he's he wants to live in Orlando.
He's going to give up the police force.
And then we also have Waldo and Eddie
struggling to make their way to Orlando and hanging out with India.
The con artist. Yeah. Yeah.
There's a lot of that's that's that's not taking place in Disney.
That's on the road to Disney World, and it lasts both episodes.
Kind of green screeny. Yeah. Yeah.
That's another great look.
I love Jaleel. I love Reginald.
And I don't know his name offhand, but the actor who plays Eddie's
dumb friend, Waldo Geraldo Faldo, I think that's a really solid.
He had he was entering such a tradition.
Like I almost kind of follow Urkel as this as the silly scene stealer on that show.
Totally. And like I and I'm sure this is my own
immaturity in some way.
And maybe you you all caught it.
But like his joke, which is like a hundred miles away from a little town
called Kenyatta, I wasn't ready for the punch line.
I didn't do the math.
And so it played for me when the reveal was that he was referring to Canada.
So some of the writing is hitting in the right way.
Yeah, I love that.
Like the fake deathbed story and then Kenyatta and all of that.
Like Urkel, it goes behind like he well, he crashes into luggage carts
outside the hotel when he's driving.
And that's definitely I feel like one of the big case explode.
Big laughs. Yeah.
Genuine laughs in all of this.
There's a weird line where Myra calls the hotel
and they can't get Urkel on the phone.
And she says, what kind of Mickey Mouse place are you running?
And that is an old phrase.
That's a very funny phrase to like have a shot like a young person in 1995.
Say like what young person is using that
describing a hotel as a Mickey Mouse kind of place?
Well, what young hip band is playing the hippie hippie shake?
That's true. Yeah.
All right, guys.
You know, there was big 60s revival, nostalgic revival in the 90s.
So, you know, we have to think about what the coolest band
in the world would be playing in this year, 1992.
I just make it hippie hippie shake and then we can go to lunch.
Sounds good. Great. Great work again, gentlemen.
That's something I was going to say about Stefan and the whole like,
well, does Urkel become Stefan forever?
I feel like we talked about this for a while.
I think there was a point where Stefan split off,
like I think with the atom so that Stefan could exist.
I feel like that's the final season, the CBS season.
I could be wrong. Maybe it's also the season prior.
But yes, they both exist.
And then I believe the finale is like Laura choosing between
the series finale between Stefan and Urkel and she chooses Urkel.
Am I wrong that the very final episode of the show is about like Urkel
going to space and then it's not clear if he's going to make it back or not?
And that maybe they left it on.
Oh, that's familiar. But I don't know.
Are you? Well, I'm the guy who claims that the butt master is a made up
thing.
Keep beating yourself up.
That's what we wanted. That's what we asked for.
I would go back in time.
Urkel could build a time machine.
I go back in time and prevent myself.
There would be like a thing that would come through and I would like grab
the microphone out of my hand.
It's the D butt masterizer.
He might have made it back from space.
Are you thinking of the elf?
Are you thinking of the elf season series finale?
We'll find out.
I think I think so in the like unresolved nature of where
else gets like gets kidnapped by the FBI.
And then that's this they thought there would be another season.
And that was just the end of the show was elf in custody.
Well, it's called Lost in Space.
Part two is the final episode.
So, hmm.
Um, oh, no, it's not.
But master part two.
Ah, yeah, I'm really sorry.
I hope you're not actually offended by that.
Is there a plot synopsis of the second episode?
It does seem like I think he promises not to go to outer space again.
And then I think they do.
Urkel and Laura kiss.
So I think Laura does end up with Urkel ultimately.
So Myra is out of the picture completely.
But in this case.
And there's no Stefan.
Interesting. It looks like he gets stuck in space.
He left Stefan. That's what happened.
Yes, Stefan was just fired into space because they didn't want to deal
with the moral quandary anymore.
Some clarity on the Stefan stuff.
The permanent Stefan made several more appearances throughout the series
and proposed to Laura again before the series finale.
After Wayne, Wayne, her choices in the flashback episode pop goes the question.
Laura chooses chose Steve over Stefan.
So it's not I'm incorrect that it was the finale where that that choice made.
So Stefan banished to limbo, banished to the Phantom Zone.
To suffer, you know, he was never asked to be born, honestly.
You know, yeah, that's a raw deal.
You know, it's crazy.
It's a person who starts their life at 23 or whatever.
Like he had no childhood.
Right. Bizarre existence that Stefan Erkel lives.
Yeah, he just woke up one day.
He just was. He just was.
And he just was fine.
Urkel played God.
Urkel was playing God, let's be honest.
And we're better to do it than Epcot Center.
Celebrating invention in the great minds.
Ray Bradbury, this Stephen Urkel.
He they so Laura admits what she did in an emotional scene
with heavy music in a United Kingdom gazebo.
Look, I sabotage the chamber, she has to say, and sell through.
And Urkel agrees that the ultimately agrees that the machine is a more a moral,
I believe, in sort of a back to the future three kind of
destroying the DeLorean situation.
Or if it's the contest.
Oh, that's what that's why he says that. Right. Right.
OK, yeah. And he he doesn't win and neither does David Lander,
the uppity guy with a suitcase car.
It goes to the woman with the food processor.
Which it was an impressive invention.
Yeah, she dumps a bunch of raw food into it, dropped a rock chicken
and carrots in there and then came out as a arranged and nicely.
Yeah, yeah.
And I mean, that's kind of that episode.
Any other Family Matters observations?
It's just a fun one. I like it.
It doesn't. Yeah, that one lacks maybe in some of like more the epic
like set pieces, I would say.
But I like the I like the intervention.
I like interventions as being a big part of it because it's so locked in time.
Oh, and everybody's in the crazy uniforms, like the imagination
Institute.
Yeah, it's that kooky 90s Bill Nye, that new Epcot era.
It's fun to see it preserved.
Yeah, interesting that it's the only one where like they think about like,
oh, what if we just had a character whose whole thing was they're going to have
a lot of fun at Disney World?
That's their whole story arc.
Like you'd think they would have a moment like that in all of them.
Well, that's sort of in a way they they with the thin
plot device that is given to Flash.
That's almost what is happening.
Like he it's a guy who has a like a moral imperative
to have the most fun in Disney World that he can have.
That's true.
It was a little hard to track step by step because at this point
and even before this step by step, there's too many goddamn characters.
And a lot of them are very similar.
Yes. Yeah, yeah.
I still I this is the one that I watch the most now, by the way, like in the.
Yeah, the one I've seen the most recently myself,
even though probably it was like still eight years ago.
But yes.
Is there a way to to just quickly
capture what is the step by step magic that I think you and I have bonded over?
It's some of this stuff.
I think it's a relationship with pop culture.
Yeah, totally.
And I've never attempted to articulate it.
So I forgive me that that I might not.
But it's like Cody, for instance, I think
who's not in this episode, Cody, the Sasa.
Sasha Mitchell has been let go from the show at this point.
He was kind of the goofy scene stealer, the attempt at the Urkel on this show.
Yeah. Sort of a like fifth generation Bill and Ted Wayne and Go.
And that's why I think, yes, he represents his connection to like what
I think the writers or ABC or whomever like kind of
what they're trying to project as like 90s cool.
He is he is that.
And I think that's one of the main things I love about the show.
And a la JT and Cody JT's world, like their version of Wayne's world.
It's like they're trying as a kid, as a let's say, 10 year old.
And my older brother was actually like watching Saturday Night Live
and like love the Wayne's World movies.
This felt like, OK, I'm getting something cool, too.
This is just as cool as that.
Oh, I was a way to like kid of five.
What teens are into late night, a little bit cracking into TGIF.
And like similarly, like I remember this quote that stuck with me
with Boy Meets World, also a TGIF show where it's like
Corey is like, we're the MTV generation.
We listen to alternative rock and watch Beavis and Butt-Head.
And it like gets a massive applause or or or laugh from the audience.
But just I feel like Step by Step has that thing where like
it almost felt cool in a way that like Family Matters
certainly with the introduction of Stefan, that felt very cool.
And there once we like started to see like Urkel play basketball super well.
That was really cool.
And Eddie was cool.
But like Step by Step felt like the most relatable and
and a good a good thing going in terms of that.
Well, and that like sort of that early 90s definition of cool
that like Michelangelo was like everything kind of decided for us.
A like doofy surfer guy is the ultimate what what cool is. Right.
It's also but I think it's then it's like the most fun to watch now
because it it like almost worked really great then and much less so now.
Like Family Matters, just by being solid,
probably seems like the highest quality show today.
But Step by Step you watch and just has these like jaw dropping choices,
these bizarre things.
Like you were saying, this thing that we love where they just had characters
who were Beavis and Butt-Head, they just kind of stole Beavis and Butt-Head
and put them on the show just to kids show up and go, hey, hey, cool.
But then they reference being aware that that Beavis and Butt-Head exists, too.
It's just the weirdest thing ever that they like stole Wayne's World.
It's so weird.
I think what makes this episode so significant and interesting is this
this this primary plot surrounding the kid Flash.
We get to Disney World, everybody's anticipating what they're going to do.
There's some somebody's looking at a trivia book
and learns that the person who did the most rides and shops
and restaurants that covered all of it in Disney World
was a guy from Russia.
And this character Flash hears this, who's a friend of the family, right?
He's not in the family.
He's just joining them.
And he hears this and he's indignant.
I think he even says a Russian holds the record.
That's a disgrace.
Yeah, he does.
And the wall fell years before this.
This is 1996.
I mean, children still mad about Russia.
We had to keep them mad.
They're mad. We had to stay mad.
We're mad at them still.
They say you hacked the election.
This is even like
Flash has been introduced in the episode at this point
after we kind of learn in Orlando that like it's not just going to be
the fan. It's there.
There are a few extensions joining the family like
Jason Marsden and Flash.
And I don't recall like seeing Flash on TV when the show
show aired. I can't until I rewatched the show years ago.
But he was definitely a replacement for Cody and his
introduction is so awesome to me.
I don't know what he's like.
Hey, you forgot your hammer.
Like it's so cartoonish.
And like you're just like catapulted into this into this universe
where Flash exists and you're kind of like, what is happening?
This all comes in with very Michael J.
Fox ripoff energy.
He traveled across the country to give the main character,
Frank Patrick Duffy, his hammerback.
And then suddenly the episode is just about him and about him
trying to regain the the ride record for America.
And like not having the show memorized years later, I'm like, OK,
so I guess at some point they gave it over to this guy, Flash.
They got rid of Cody because the actors like did some awful stuff.
So they had to just bail on him midseason. He's gone.
So we need a goofy guy. It's Flash. We're going to bring Flash in.
And I think I assume like so they must have planted the seeds of Flash
slowly throughout the season to give him this big spot.
His first episode was the episode before this.
Wow. This is the Disney World episode is the second episode ever of Flash.
And this actor only has one credit before all this,
which is one episode of Full House.
So his third and fourth episodes of television ever
are a massive plot using all of the rides and facilities of Disney World
devoted to him.
His fourth episode of television he's ever done is him in an American flag
jacket, waving an American flag in front, like with all of Main Street
cheering him on. This is never he's brand new.
And I wanted to and I again, like I know we spoke briefly about who are these
are we seeing background actors?
Are we seeing park park goers in these background scenes like this,
like him running down Main Street?
And I couldn't help but think like the idea of like, if you are a park goer
in 1996 or 1995 or whatever, and like you find out that they're
shooting step by step and you're like, oh, yeah, I want to be a part of that.
That sounds awesome.
And you're you're told to basically just like you're going to you're going to be here.
You're going to root one of the main characters from step by step,
running along the end.
It turns out it's Flash and you just have no idea
what you're seeing or interacting with.
Really responded to that.
Right. Yeah. You're like, if you have a huge crush on Brandon
Cole, like ultimate heartthrob Brandon Cole, and then all you only get to see him
super far away up by the castle and you're like, who's this guy?
Judea, I've heard of Jeff Judea.
I I misremembered, by the way, I had always thought it was that the nephew
that it was Cody who did the like, I'm trying to ride everything
and that it was him who did the Indiana Jones.
I remember there was a character.
So it was probably him who did the Indiana Jones show
because a kid wanted to see it, but he's got to get to the airport soon,
which it's also like kid, don't save your favorite thing for last.
Are you crazy? Do it first.
What if it breaks? Like, what are you thinking, kid? Yeah.
Yeah. So then in theory, he like Flash
speaks to whoever whoever is in charge and is able to like
costume change into the indie role and then do that upcoming show.
But later on, they say that he claims that they're slowed down
in terms of this record breaking run because of what happened
at the indie stunt show.
But it seems like it actually moved on time, if this makes any sense,
because he kind of probably took that.
I'm sorry to be if this is a convoluted point I'm making, but it's like,
he did that upcoming show.
He spent the same amount of time performing it that he would have
spent watching it. Is that accurate? Right.
Yes. Yeah. If part of his duty was to watch every single show,
then that's the exact same amount of time, regardless of whether it's an actor
indie or him himself doing the dangerous stunts with no vetting or rehearsal.
Yeah, it's really weird.
This one, I think, takes some of the biggest swings in terms of stuff
that could never happen.
I mean, this entire scenario that he sets out to get this record
and it's just an indie enterprise initially that the character Mark,
the nerdy son is helping him with.
But then all of the resources of Disney World get behind Flash
and his trying to bring the record back to America.
And his pro-America agenda, yeah.
Yeah. All of the people in lab coats in a place called Ride Central.
Right. We're not going to let a child back there.
Yeah, we're going to have to.
I'll go talk to Disney Ride Central.
And then suddenly he just is.
You don't see a scene of him talking his way in or seeing if that exists.
He's just there.
And then there's like an Apollo 13 type crew
all tensely watching every move.
And there's cameras everywhere.
This is like Kristoff and the Truman show.
Like we've got all every possible eye on everywhere that Flash could be.
And it's all, you know, it is a lot of fun because now you get to see a guy
just having fun on all the rides, but with the sort of like
the ticking clock of he's running out of the China pavilion.
He just had a blast at the Circle Vision movie.
And then the kid who never has anything to do on the show
has a churro right there waiting for him.
You know, it's got like it's got a pace to it.
There's a clock on it.
You know, I one line I wrote down just maybe which
falls in line with this whatever I was getting at in terms of this
being representative of like a cooler, like our
kind of watered down Wayne's world or whatever is he does
coming off the teacups, Flash says something to the effect of like
the G forces have my stomach set to hurl on her.
The G forces of the teacups.
Like Hurl, I think it's just the perfect kind of encapsulation of like,
oh, as a 10 year old, like, OK, this show is actually cool.
They're saying the word hurl.
They're talking about gross stuff, stuff we all do.
They're willing to address it on TV.
They talk like my friends and I talk.
I this relates to me as an adult.
He drops so hard because he basically does like a trust fall,
like he's passing out and goofy catches him.
And he gets so low to the ground before goofy catches him.
I was so impressed with that.
Like he thought he like Chris Farley style, like physical,
like threw his body down and he really trusted that goofy to catch him.
And goofy did. But I would wonder if there was like another take where
he like cracked his head on the cement.
Flash trying to make a good first impression, you know, he's given it
his all, he's on his second or third gig, you know.
Yeah, it's pretty he does really carry it for having not really been on TV before.
He's the star of this episode and big locations.
He's he's really got to sell all this stuff.
And yeah, is he I mean, like you get the idea that he works for
Patrick Duffy in that first scene, right?
I mean, like, I guess like if you showed this
to somebody who's never seen the show, like, yeah, he passes it off like.
There's no question this could be the star of the show.
He seems like he's always been there.
Yeah, even though he just showed up in like a construction
hijinks episode, the prior episode to all this.
He can he sells some great topical jokes.
This could be the the if we don't get this back, it'll be the worst thing
that happened to America since Roseanne sung the national anthem.
Yeah, that was very tiny tunes like they're trying to like
everybody's pushing Roseanne is weird.
When did Roseanne sing the national anthem?
What 90?
Is that a joke? Five years at five year old joke already?
I think so. But but again, that's as like up to date as you're getting on
what ABC program anger.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, because the rest of the show,
I feel like all these shows are just really littered with like
Chia Pett and the Clapper, right?
It's all that sort of switches, I guess, is vaguely recent.
But the master and but and let's say it, but master
and to shift things over to Suzanne Summers, to Carol,
we were talking about this, about their this is the they get the horniest
plot in this episode.
Frank and Carol Duffy and Summers are trying to, you know,
basically they were trying to take a an anniversary trip
and then it got ruined because his mom showed up and said, I'm dying soon.
I want to take everyone to Disney World.
Horrible thing to happen.
So they're just like so pent up and horny this entire.
But she's trying to.
Suzanne Summers is trying to find ways for them to break off and have a little fun.
Like when they, you know, they somebody brings up Peter Pan.
Oh, that's a kiddie ride.
Oh, I don't know. A slow moving fantasy ride in the dark.
We all know this, the sexiest ride
could ever if there is a place where you were going to
go with the show, say, do the nasty that that might be too much.
I'm sorry. I feel like we feel like
Cody may have done like
I've never I've never done the sideways monkey dance.
The horizontal mom, though I will say I did make note that like
I was kind of taken aback that in the beginning of the episode,
JT, in reference to his parents flirting, says something to the effect of like
you guys are too old to have sex anyway.
And just hearing the word sex was off putting, I thought.
Yeah. Nine thirty, the gloves come off.
Yeah, I guess so. Yeah.
I yeah, you would think there would have been a euphemism there.
Yeah, at least they would.
The daughter is the oldest daughter would say like, I have sex, mom.
OK, I have sex.
Do you have a problem with that?
I don't know. I guess that was like the maybe that was the core idea of the show.
We are going to write.
We're going to address stuff and be
a sort of uncomfortable throughout.
The boys trying to lose their virginity, that's alluded to that.
This is the night they're going to.
They are going to run this con where JT pretends that he's JT Disney.
And this will this will be the path to them both losing their virginity.
Yeah. Together your everybody's dream with their best friend.
Of course. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Like that scene in Fargo.
Yeah. They go to I alluded to this earlier, Panetta's.
They pay the bill at this very expensive restaurant.
No restaurant ever existed at Disney World called Panetta's.
That was a fake sign made.
This is fake. The building is it was called the Portobello Yacht Club.
Now it's called Terra Lina at what is now Disney Springs.
But yeah, here's here's the back to the but master point.
Nine Dragons is referenced.
And that's a real up a real up caught restaurant in in in the World
Showcase and Panetta's is not.
So again, they're inconsistent logic in this episode where it's like, right.
Not just you. Thank you for that.
Real real places.
Why is that where a Disney person jumped in and go like, don't
don't go around talking about things being too expensive for people at Disney World.
That was probably their logic is because they have to say it is expensive.
But they could. That's why I looked it up.
The girl is really whiny about it.
Like we want to go to Panetta's, but it's way too expensive.
And I was like, that can't be they would never allow that.
Yeah, I said about a real restaurant.
I will say I fancy I am impressed by
this hustle like claiming yourself to be JT Disney is funny.
That's like a cool whole idea. Yes.
Yeah, that's funny.
Yeah, like, did he had to think on his feet about like, what is the relation?
Is he the grandson?
Did he have to like spit out facts about him or like what he made in the will
or like what his shares are at this point?
Yeah. How would you prove that other than with like a limo, a local Orlando?
Yeah. In 1996 would be much harder to prove.
And like the Disney kids and cousins, like there's a lot of them.
There's a lot of grandkids and cousins.
Well, what he could have like, you know, he's like sign his name like Walt.
Yeah. The.
See, that's how I sign.
That's the thing. We all do it.
We all do it.
Also, like, I mean, I'm assuming you guys made this connection,
maybe not as deep or as interesting as
Steve is to Aladdin, the cartoon.
But Jason Marsden is a heavy Disney voice actor and was to.
I don't know if he had done Max Goof at this point, but
maybe maybe that might have come out or was like about to or the same year.
Yeah, I'm not sure when Goofy Movie came out.
He had a really funny moment.
I didn't even write it down that like felt like it could be improvised.
It could have been scripted, but I thought was like, oh, that's funny.
I think it's like he walks past Captain Hook maybe.
And he's like, love your movies, by the way.
Yeah. Which like he definitely performed it in an off the cuff way.
And I was like, OK, he's he's got some chops. He's funny.
Yeah, he's just very pro.
He's just a very Broadway pro.
Well, he can hit his mark.
Every movement has purpose.
Just this is really good.
It's a really good Marsden, Scott.
Yeah, Marsden. I got a Marsden in the pocket.
Because I thought my use of that, I think nobody had nobody had anything to say.
Oh, my. Here's your hammer back.
I'm so I'm sorry we didn't say it before.
It's a great judge.
You got it. Yes.
I do Marsden, you do.
Jude, we covered the gamut.
If anybody wants to grab a Christopher Castile,
it's the balls in your court.
I'll workshop it up at the laugh factory.
I don't know. Yeah, what's open?
Panetta's go to Panetta's does a stand up night.
Go a big thing we've not gotten to speak too much about
that I thought was really fun was, well, Karen's whole plot
and in the song Girls with Guitars, I thought was, oh, boy, something of no.
Mom's worry.
Yeah, that was a good time.
Now, do you think this does this pre date like the Dixie Chicks, do you think?
Or is this at the same time?
Because like it felt like that's what not popularized, I think.
But maybe they were like quiet on the rise, but they certainly hadn't hit yet.
Before Natalie, I know they were around before Natalie Mains joined the band,
which is sort of the part that made like skyrocketed them.
But apparently they were around since 89, the original.
The other two. Oh, I gotcha.
Yeah, this song is great.
So the all the girls are hanging out together at Pleasure Island,
which it's great to see Pleasure Island, that is prime.
The Jessica Rabbit way in the back on a sign.
So many clashy styles of buildings.
It's just awesome to see
Karen, one of the daughters, who is has pursued country music before,
gets a flyer, which she reads in a very like Marsha Brady stilted
country music competition this Friday.
Top prize gets five hundred dollars.
Music scouts in audience.
Guys, we have to do this.
Maybe also like a like a live band accompaniment.
There is like some phrase in it.
It's provided.
Exactly. Give chord changes if you can.
Only do one verse chorus and bridge.
Guys, we have to do this.
Every every competitor allowed to walk off and disgrace once and then come back.
That's to be fair.
That's how I read the rules of the coffin challenge to Anthony Geo
at Six Flags Fright Fest.
It's been three days in a coffin and you can't stand up except for peeing breaks.
We have to do this.
Top prize is six hundred dollars.
Anthony, what are we waiting for?
Yeah, she they work up a little country act.
They rehearse this song Girls with Guitars, which is a Winona Judd song.
Oh, OK.
Is it a song that exists?
It is. I looked it up.
Yeah, Girls with Guitars exists.
Girls with guitars.
It will be in my head forever having watched this.
They do a scene with horrible sound back in the hotel room.
The band breaks up immediately.
But then they join her ultimately for the big show with the neon armadillo.
She really eat shit on try one and then crushes it on try two.
How do you as all of you perform to some degree, how do you deal with
with scenes in television film like this with the like
the person getting on stage and in this case, her vision,
we we get her perspective and her vision blurs and like she just can't get.
Oh, yeah. It's hard for step by step. Yeah. Yeah.
Do you get I'm just having yeah, what you're like psychological,
if it just doesn't bother you or it does bother you as a performer on that level.
I don't know. I feel like any time I've seen that usually it's before someone
takes the stage or like I feel like usually just adrenaline kicks in.
Like even if you're nervous, you know, I've never watched anyone
like run off stage and then come back and do it again.
You know? Yeah. Yeah.
Even in like you're like one on one improv, like class performance, nobody.
Like I've never seen anyone flip out like this.
Usually just somebody says something dumb like.
Yeah. You're saying like that it is it is maybe kind of like the trope is
that they'll just be like a full minute of silence and people glaring.
And yeah, fuzziness.
Less I was commenting on like the reality
versus what we're seeing, like, I guess I'm just as somebody who goes,
I get nervous when I see these.
Well, I may be like I'm fearful.
I guess I'm just wondering if it stresses you guys out.
It was kind of what I was getting.
I see. I do have nightmares like this.
Like I don't I feel a little nervous before I go on stage,
but not to this level, but I do have dreams where I'm on stage
and don't know my my lines or don't know what to do.
Yeah. Yeah. Not being prepared. Yeah, for sure.
I don't know that they're like seeing this now without something I'm nervous
about that's in the arena doesn't stress me out necessarily.
You weren't nervous.
OK, because I like I guess it made me put too much of my own
mental and like an investment into the performance of girls with guitars.
And like I did really want it to go well.
Yeah, I guess I guess as a kid, for sure, stuff like this would stress me out.
I mean, I think I've said this before on the show.
One of my favorite movies seeing in the theaters as a kid was the Lassie movie,
like from 1993 or four was because there's literally no conflict at the end.
There's no like stressful thing.
So I can relate, even especially being a kid.
Anything like this would really stress me out
to like feel like the character is having sort of a breakdown.
I also had an anxiety attack in real life a couple of weeks ago.
So I really I guess it's I guess if now that you're pointing it out
and if I were to rewatch it, I might actually feel a little more stressed out by it.
I didn't mean I don't want to do that to you.
No, no. But it's an interesting question, because
it is something I don't think about in the context of performing
until I had like an audition or I'm doing a show.
Are we saying that Girls with Guitars
is a chillingly accurate representation of the performer spotlight?
Is it like the most gripping what it is like to be in that position?
Well, it's no it's really not any different from
B Rabbit choking an eight mile.
It's like almost the exact same thing.
So if that has a ton of merit or did when that came out,
I don't see why we shouldn't maybe get that.
He does get a second chance, right?
He comes back and kills it.
If I'm remembering just like Karen, just like Karen.
Yeah, she comes back and she feels great.
I mean, like she's immediately you see her confidence on stage
when she comes back the second time.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. It's not even a ramp up.
It goes great.
It cuts around to everyone in the family and a bunch of like
weirdos there for a country music new star night.
Yeah, the grandmother's French side piece like a stranger she met.
Oh, yeah. Speaking of Lassie, Lassie's June Lockhart.
Lassie's June Lockhart. God bless you.
I guess she was on Lost in Space as well, right?
Oh, that's right. Yeah.
Who ultimately solves the problem of that solves Frank
and Carol's main problem of that they can't find anywhere to have sex
because she offers up her condo, which is so it works out great.
They get to sneak away on the last night to his mother's
Kissimmee condo and have sex in her bed.
Well, she because she's hooking up with a French guy
at his place, presumably.
I think the sound I like the sound of Jason Sheridan's Kissimmee condo, don't you?
Sounds pretty good if you say it out loud.
Yeah. Well, maybe one thing to mention also, just like the rush
to do everything at Disney World within four days.
Sounds like a job for Mike Carlson.
Do you think you could get the record? Absolutely, I do.
I absolutely was thinking about this because there's going to be
we're upcoming episode whenever Disney Genie launches
and I'm going to compete against the app to do the most stuff in a day.
It's like, what's the what's the chess program?
Oh, the deep blue Gary Casper.
I'm going to be deep blue, basically.
And planning. But yes, I was watching this going, I bet I could do this
and I bet I could do this quicker and I could like bring home
a bigger victory for America for a character who people have spent
a lot more hours with.
Flash was coming up on his finishing up his third half hour.
We've done more than that in this episode alone.
A lot more. Yes.
A good point.
The fictional character, Mike Carlson, is more beloved.
OK, faith, like Carlson.
Yeah. And Flash, the character put the hours in and that's who should it.
The Russia wasn't the disgrace.
It was given it to a guy with barely any screen time like Flash.
I will say, I do feel like Flash maybe had a big advantage
from what I could tell in that, like concession persons
and souvenir persons were truly just handing him things.
There was no money exchange I saw.
I felt like he just grabbed stuff and that was accomplishing his feet there.
Yeah, at nine dragons, they just hand him the little thing of a Chinese.
Shrimp, lo mein. Yeah, yeah.
So you'd have to.
Yeah, I think it's maybe impossible to do this without the Disney apparatus
helping you. I think if you explained I'm trying to beat Flash's record,
the character from step by step, they might help you out.
If we can figure out if somebody can actually like a real like figure out
exactly what Flash did, let's like write it down on a list and see
what day by day, how much time it would take us.
This is complicated because there was no animal kingdom yet.
So how does that factor in?
Comes out if it's just you're trying to beat Flash.
I think it has to be what existed, what they had in 1996.
And then it'll be tricky, though, of course, because they don't have
quite the same, you know, a lot of stuff.
That's right.
Lots of stuff to full strength down there operation wise.
So you'll yeah, you'll have to figure out like what substitutes rides
if there's a different ride that exists.
This is really complicated.
Well, and it's complicated because you just are going to have to
skip all the lines and not stop and appreciate them.
Well, it will be it'll be tough, but I will keep remembering
what a victory I'm bringing home for the red, white and blue.
So there's a greater good.
It's for our country, which was which is hurting so much more so than back then.
Ninety six. Those are prime times.
America needs a victory now and you could be that victory.
Yeah. How about we do this?
Is there a way to just look up?
Is there a Russian record for most Disney World stuff done in four days?
And whatever in real world that exists, if there is a record like that
specifically done by somebody from Russia, then I will try to beat that.
And that's a cleaner way to do it.
See, that's going to be hard.
We're going to have to find like a really neutral source, though,
because our propaganda apparatus would underplay the
what they did in four days and their propaganda apparatus would would upgrade it.
Right. OK. Yeah.
Well, we'll get in the Mueller report.
Does he get into any of the Russia's Russians doing Disney
World challenges or I didn't read the whole thing.
You know, I'm not really sure. I'm so busy saluting him.
Might be deep in there. They address flash.
They address the Disney World issue.
Got it. OK. Yeah. Yeah.
Well, we'll get you going on this.
Yeah. Bring bring the record back home to real people
and not fictional characters who barely appeared on the show. Exactly.
Flash did not come back, by the way, in the next season.
He was replaced by. Yeah.
By a Frenchman by Jean-Luc played by Bronson Pinchot.
Drafted in there.
Cousin Oliver.
Right. Our first cousin, Oliver didn't work out this kid.
Flash, we got a second cousin Oliver coming.
We should start winding it down.
The anything else we want to say about these or Kyle having revisited these
is just any like specific memories or does it just like
is it flash you bet these like are these your favorite episodes
of some of these shows?
I mean, I do.
I know you were saying you think Family Matters is your favorite
and the best of these three.
Yeah. I think I had I definitely had the most fun watching step by step.
And Flash is iconic.
Yeah. Well, I texted you before that before before we got into this.
I was like, we were like, what do we do?
And you said, well, we got to do Family Matters and Full House like,
oh, we should do step by step.
It's with the fast guy.
Yes. Yeah.
I mean, the fast guy.
What other episodes have something as short and iconic as that?
What an idea.
Yeah, no, they're they're also fun.
And like I said, I love like we were talking about those moments
where these characters are forced to sort of be off the cuff.
And like kind of riffing on rides.
I think there's probably like more moments that if I went through all
all three of these, we could find little times where they're like kind of
ad libbing, like you were saying, not even correctly referencing rides.
But I don't know any of these things.
It's fun when you see your favorite characters
like taken somewhere entirely new.
So I had a great time watching.
Interesting that they're all two partners.
Yeah, which I think makes them fit together nicely.
We left out Boy Meets World really quickly.
A big thing that happened then later is that Dana from Step by Step
shows up in the Boy Meets World episode.
Like they were there.
They kept Dana in Disney World in time.
And she went and visited Corey and Boy Meets World on the same night of TGIF.
Wow. But it's sort of, you know, it's a different format.
It's not the two parter.
They don't spend as much time in Disney World.
I figured it makes sense to leave it out. Right.
Focus on these focus.
And I saw also there was outside of TGIF, there was a Blossom
and a Roseanne around the same time that also do.
Yeah.
Boston to Disneyland, Roseanne to Disney World,
and then later Modern Family and Blackish.
But when I haven't seen those, I don't know what they did, but it's tough to top
Jesse and the Rippers on the white piano, the transformation chamber, the fast guy,
his American flag jacket triumphant on the the Cinderella Castle stage.
I mean, these are all these are all wonderful moments.
And it's it's awesome to go back into them and awesome to just remember
and meditate for a little bit on the but master.
So thank you for bringing that to our attention.
Yeah, I really feel bad about the master stuff.
I feel bad, too, now.
It's just I feel bad for it.
I actually to me, I almost I actually almost this was a scenario
I almost forgot about.
I forgot about the but master for a while.
And now it's now it's back.
I've done a little.
I brought back a dark memory.
It's now like but mass, but Master Gate is like the scandal
now on.
So but yeah, I feel bad.
I'm going to feel bad all the rest of the day.
We know you please don't, Mike.
I'm so thankful that you call me out on that.
And I'm also thankful that you were able to reaffirm the argument
I was trying to make wherein we don't know what what in our universe exists
and what it's it's a it's a consistent, cohesive logic
in pointing out things that are, yeah, invented based on the information
we had at the time, the but master was relevant.
It being a real thing is relevant.
I'm glad we know about it.
Thank you, Kyle, but master Mooney for her.
Bring it to the table.
You survived podcast the ride.
Your car, that's a that's a nickname to be comfortable with, right?
You feel you feel fine about that?
Yeah, about the but master stuff.
We'll leave it. All right.
We're leaving it behind. It stays in this episode.
Let's exit through the gift shop.
I know that you have something to plug, but we've been talking about
this is a block of 90s television with an acronym
meant to air on a specific day of the week, which is applicable to your new show.
Saturday morning, all star hits.
Let's talk about that.
Yes, our our new show, Scott.
Well, I mean, like, I feel like people have made it this far
past all the but master and flash stuff.
They skipped to the end for the promotion.
They only want to hear the promotion.
Yeah, no, this is super relevant in the sense that like TGIF was something
we were thinking about when Ben Jones and I, who co-created the show
with myself.
When we first started talking about
this seed of an idea, like I was definitely talking about TGIF
and the idea of doing that condensed experience in a half hour in our show.
We tried to do that essentially for the Saturday morning cartoon experience.
So it's called Saturday morning, all star hits.
The acronym is Smash.
And Scott was a big part of bringing it to life.
And yeah, we tried to essentially replicate
that Saturday morning TV viewing experience.
So like we have kind of our own versions of
late 80s, early 90s cartoons all condensed into a 30 minute block.
But then the show evolves and it was really fun.
And I think we did a pretty good job of sort of replicating
the experience of of TV of the era.
I don't know. What do you think, Scott?
I think so. Thank you for the credit on it.
I'm like I'm thrilled and proud to be part of it.
It's surreal to even be actually talking about it as a tangible thing.
And within the podcast, the ride setting.
And it does feel like excited to be doing this relevant to to what I imagine
your listeners are into.
And like there's almost like some like
certainly Disney afternoon parallels, I would say.
So for sure, that's what I was like.
It's that kind of like the show is like it's a bunch of blocks of TV
taped off of TV like you're watching it on a VHS later.
And if listeners watch the Disney afternoon where shows would come in and out
like now, there's gummy bears, but gummy bears is retired
and Goof Troops coming in.
That's kind of what happens within the single season of Saturday morning.
All star hits like, you know, there's entire mini shows.
And then the show ends and a new one comes in.
But there's also this this through line with the hosts of the show,
the live action hosts, both played by Kyle, Skip and Treyboar,
who are kind of it's it really is the Urkel ization or the Cody effect.
I was almost I'm 99 percent sure, like in the pitching of this show,
we had like Skip and Treble or, you know, like think
Bill and Ted Dan Cortez, Cody from Step by Step.
Like I think Cody was may have been the reason why Netflix
decided to make this TV show. I don't know.
But I think so.
I mean, yeah, knowing that you could have a new Cody on your hands.
Yes. What that times to your cash flow.
Well, and on my end, Kyle, that you you set up a scenario
where beyond like the dream team of people to work with you,
Ben Jones, animation and art genius, Dave McCarrie,
your your awesome friend and director,
besides working with all you guys and and getting to write so much fun stuff,
truly like kind of realizing that and like, oh, I'm like,
I'm like getting to write stuff for Cody, basically.
This is as close as I can come to writing for Step by Step in 1994.
So for that, I really got to thank you most.
Well, when we were taught, we were.
Yes, subs are a running theme in our show.
And I don't know when some sandwiches are like occupy the place of pizza
within this, like what pizza was to the turtles subs are in this world.
And certainly when I was like, when we were talking about Cody
and maybe what makes him cool or the idea of him being cool,
like that image came in my head of like somebody eating a sub sandwich
on one of these shows always felt like a very cool thing.
Well, Carl Winslow, like I, you know, that that's his dream day is like
he's settling down for a sub until Urkel making a massive super tall sub.
Is this a Jason dream to potentially build?
Like it should be, if you haven't, is just like building the ultimate
too big to eat in one day sandwich.
You know, I try to leave that to the professionals.
I like to sandwich artists, if you will.
Yeah. I'd like to see you try.
Look, if you like, if you like subs, if you like cartoons,
if you like TGIF or the Disney afternoon, if you like classic Vio people,
we have so many amazing Maurice LaMarche and Frank Welker
and Eric Bowser and Chris Summer and all those people.
Like amazing voice talent as part of this thing.
And if you like Kyle Mooney, if you like your old pal Scott,
I think listeners, you will really enjoy Saturday morning All-Star hits.
I enjoyed working on it more than almost anything I've ever been a part of.
So thank you, Kyle. Sincerely.
And look, not not to be too sincere, not to make things awkward, but no,
I really appreciate it.
And like, you know, this is truly the beginning of my
of my press and support for for the show.
And I'm just really sorry about the but master stuff.
Do you think you'll bring any but master oriented material to any?
I think this is that you I think I'm going on Seth's show.
And it's like you have podcasts the other day.
You know, the but master is a real thing.
They brought it. I thought it was like a joke on a sitcom.
They actually made this thing.
We have a picture, if you want to come to that.
I don't think it'll get you.
I don't know what's going to do any gotcha journalism on you.
Hopefully I'm going to be the only one who will have done it during this press tour.
It's right. And I think that's why we ran you through the ringer,
because we know that you have you got big shows to do.
We want you to kill it on there.
And now now I think you will.
Well, I always have a great time with you guys and it's good to see you.
And I'm sorry I couldn't be there in person.
Yeah. Yeah, no.
Thanks for making time in New York. A lot of time.
I'm again embarrassed by the runtime.
This happens. It happened with you before Star Tours was very long.
Look, this is how we do.
Check out Saturday morning.
I'll start it on Netflix.
Eight episodes all available today.
I guess. Yeah. And stick with the show.
It's fun all the way through. So stick with it.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. There's like I think there's an evolution and changes and surprises
and, you know, a lot in store as it as it evolves. Absolutely.
So Saturday morning, I'll start it on Netflix right now.
For us, you can find us on the socials at podcast, the ride
merch is available in our public store and for three bonus episodes every month.
Check out podcast, the ride, the second gate at Patreon dot com slash podcast,
the ride next week, Country Bear Jamber Week.
And we've already started recording it.
So we know these aren't short either.
So load up for the winter.
You've got a lot to hibernate with. What's that?
We've been doing so well with like the I runtime reasonable.
I feel like and then all of a sudden in the last week and a half,
it was like the Springsteen concert length are back
as well as the quality.
I think everyone would agree.
You know what were the stamina, the vigor we're bringing to the table.
You lay look with that.
Check out Country Bear Jamber Week next week.
Thanks for listening, everybody.
See you next week in a flash. Bye.
This has been a forever dog production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner,
Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts dot com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify
or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter
and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.