Well, all good things must come to an end, even Jamba Weeks.
But first, we rustled up a yule-tied tree, featuring conspiracy theorist Santa
and the most unusual bear you ever did see.
It's the Country Bear Christmas Special on Podcast The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, The Grizzly Gate, the one and only original Podcast
The Ride Country Bear Jamba Week. Coming to a close here on day six, I'm swinging
Scotty Gertner, joined by Big Car Alson and Jughead Jason Bonnet Sheridan.
Oh, I will miss these clunky, these endless names. We bid them a do as we do so many
aspects of this week. We're at the end, fellas.
Yeah, I think I am. I can't help but think that my half idea of just, like, if I was
doing the intro to call you like Scooch, would have been so much simpler, saved us
so much time, and we would have, these episodes would have been a lot more brisk.
Just by virtue of there being much less of a name than suddenly it all tightens.
Yeah, like, you're Scooch, Jason's like, let's call him like J, and I'm...
J?
Just call him J, yeah, because his first name starts with a J.
And I'm like, call me like Lean and Lean or something.
Lean and Lean.
Just call me Lean, I think.
Oh, okay, I thought you were saying Lean and Lean and Lean. It was like a big and rich
kind of situation, but the same word repeats.
Well, for my country, my new country band, maybe I will call it Lean and Lean and I'll
find another taller gentleman to do it with. But yeah, for the, for brisks, for the sake
of brevity, Lean, I guess.
By even discussing this, we've made it all longer.
So brevity's been out the window.
It's been, you know, it hasn't been brief. We've done a lot here, but I've enjoyed
everything. You think about what we've accomplished this week. We've covered every
iteration of the show. We improvised a jamboree with Zach and Jess from Off Book, and we
had fun with Guy and Doug, and we unanimously agreed on the pristine quality of a fine
overlooked film.
That's right, I remember.
We all got on board with a new American classic.
I remember.
It's been a blast.
Writers, get the think pieces ready and just make sure to cite your source. That's all
I have to say.
Vulture AV Club, sharpen your pencils.
That's right.
Just get ahead of the 20th anniversary. Yeah, yeah, please.
You know who to credit. And that is Scooch, Jay, and Lean and Lean.
My big question before we dive into the Christmas show, which we close out as we head into the
Christmas season. I think we did this for you, Mike. This is for you, Mike. You love
the show. There was no way, you know, we couldn't just do a basic episode about it.
I think we had to explore every nook and cranny and experiment and really see our way
around the Country Bear Jamboree. And I just want to know now, how do you feel?
Do you feel good about everything?
Yeah, I do feel good about it. When I initially thought of it, I didn't think of it as a big
event, but I'm glad we did it like this. I'm glad we got to hoot and holler to sort of
experience what it would be like to do a Jamboree. I don't know. It's like, it feels like,
are we ever going to do a Country Bear related episode again? I hope so, but I don't know
where it's going to come from. So maybe it's a bit bittersweet on my end as well, because
it's like, well, you know, we climbed that hill and doing six episodes about it, it's
like, well, what else is there to say? Like, there's other episodes, you know, of big popular
rides we've done where I feel like, yeah, we could probably do another episode on it.
But like, the bears, we completely exhaust bears. So I feel a little, I feel good, but
also sad.
Bittersweet. Well, can we run a quick checklist? Is there anything that we didn't cover?
I mean, we talked about these bathrooms. We haven't, I don't know that we talked about,
I think I came back from Japan with crushed pennies or whatever coin they're called in
Japan with the carry, and we didn't really talk about those. So there's maybe a crushed
coin episode in the future.
As Guy alluded, there's a lot of merch, especially once you factor in Tokyo Disney's bear
offerings. And we only kind of touched on like what bear country used to be, you know,
the Mile Long Bar, the bath houses.
And then there's Disney on Parade, which I found in the first episode. And we have to
go back to that because supposedly there's the Sunbonnet Trio are like doing a trapeze
act in it. So yeah, I guess you're right. I guess there's more bears. So I shouldn't
be sad. I should be hopeful and optimistic about the future of bear talk on this podcast.
Yeah. The plush episode, the coins episode, the bath house episode. There's country. You
would think that Country Bird Jambor Week one would exhaust all the big stuff being
that we're doing the shows. But isn't that a little passe? I think now it's really going
to free us up in Country Bird Jambor Week two to cover what people really want to hear
about. Yeah. Yeah. Plush three hours on plush. When I am kept up at night that it's like
it wasn't five episodes. It wasn't seven episodes. It was six. It wasn't a full week and it
wasn't a work week either. Just tossing and turning. Do we need to think of one more then
to make it? One more. It could be a minute long. We could just like clip something from
this episode. Just like snip it out and call that its own thing. Tracks in the snow is
especially good. It's the first one sentence episode. If I guess the right. There's no
intros. Talk about brevity. It's like a tweet of an episode. That's less of a mile long
bar. More of a ruler long bar. You know what it is? It's the, when the chicken, if they
ever bring back that gosh darn sandwich. The fried tomatoes. Fried green tomatoes. The fried green
tomato sandwich at Hungry Bear. That's its own episode. Then we finally do Hungry Bear
Restaurant. And we can talk about bears there. There it is. It's the Bear Restaurant. Yep.
But we won't do it until they bring that sandwich back. For now I think this has worked out
very nicely that we are ending the year with this because we get to close out with the
Christmas iteration of the Country Bridge Embry. Which there's not that many. I feel like
every year it's like what is our Christmas episode? And there's not that much stuff. Like
we talk about holiday overlays. But there aren't really a ton of those in theme park
history. So this is sort of a bigger one in that regard. Yeah. This was the first. I guess
so. This was the first overlay they said. It's before Haunted Mansion. It's before It's a
Small World. Before Jingle Cruise. Yeah. Before Avatar. Before Flight of Holiday Passage.
Flight of Holiday Passage. Or you throw presents to the Navi. We've got to get to the Navi
Mall. The Hallelujah Mall. Hard times have fallen on the Hallelujah Mall. It's only one
third occupied. I hope there's a mall in one of these upcoming Avatar movies. I would like to
know where do they get their loincloths? Show us James. Show us. I'd like a size 102 please
they say because they are very large. Right of course. And lean. Yeah. Yeah. So here we are
doing one of the bigger Christmas things. And I think it's very nice and charming. And
almost weird that they don't do this more often with more things. Especially with these show
situations where why not? All the robots are there. Just put sweaters on them. Make them do the
standards and you're done. It's easy. Yeah. It is. It is. It does seem to me. I mean they did a little
of that with the Jingle Cruise and I think the first year at Disneyland at least it was a little
underwhelming. But I think they added some more stuff to it. But it's such just even calling
anything like the holiday edition and putting a Santa hat on does go a long way. Like C3PO and
Star Tour. Well I guess it's Life Day. And they did Life Day. They did like one day Life Day a couple
weeks ago at Galaxy's Edge. But they didn't barely do anything. They just had a couple food
offerings. And some merch. A little bit of merch. And a little bit of merch. You want to see the
whole land decked out. And it's like it's you know it looks like our holiday decorations but it's a
little slightly different. So yeah. And plus Life Day season just starts earlier and earlier every
year. So you can really stretch it out and you can really go to a three moons day which is an
early January. Of course. It's just getting so commercialized. That's right. Oh terribly. Yeah.
Used to be about the life. And now it's about the credits. But so. Oh yeah go ahead. Oh I was just
going to say the basic facts of the Country Bears Christmas special. Yeah. You know started in
Disneyland and Disney World in November of 1984 and then opened in Tokyo Disney in November of
1988. Of course still running. Still going strong in Tokyo Disneyland. Yeah. Ended at the Magic
Kingdom only in 2005. I was surprised to find out about that. That it kept going for so long. And
Disneyland the last one was 2000. The ride closed in September 2001. Yeah this is and this is of
course the only one now that I haven't seen in person. The only version. Oh is that right. Because I
saw the vacation one in Japan and then seen the regular in Florida. So it seems what Guy told us is
that the big thing you'd be missing out on by just watching a video is how fully rendered it is when
Wendell shoots the lights out. Wendell who is lovingly holding a gun in the show and he blows the
lights out and you could really feel it. The sound was very good and it really felt like glass was
shattering. Squirrel cone. Yeah. He says it's not even loaded. Yeah. And Wendell is so sad in this show.
Can I just say that? He bums me out so much and I'm a big Wendell guy. But I feel like I will say
overall I think the show half fully like is kind of sad too. There's a lot of sadness in this version.
Yeah. You were talking about over the doughboys that we did that might people might have heard earlier
this week on their page if I could play a different oh yeah. You have some like holiday melancholy I feel
like a lot of it. Maybe you're bringing that to the table here. That's true but isn't he's Wendell. Yeah
that's absolutely true that I feel very I get like December the sad sads I get them in December. And
I got the sads again. So yeah. So some of this Christmas songs make you like kind of wistful and you know
but I think also like Wendell is like stuck out in the cold like he can't get home. It's like so sad. Yeah
he's like he's really like upset and bummed out like it's not so it's not just on time with with some of
the songs it's like not just the melancholy Christmas it's like something bad has happened to this
character and Trixie Trixie can't catch a break in all of these shows. I mean she sings a song called
the Hibernating Blues about how she was supposed to go ice skating with someone and he was busy sleeping
he was busy snoozing and she's introduced as a girl who was sure to break the ice at any skating party
which I guess has two meanings. Well yeah yeah it's a little it's mean to Trixie for sure they they're
we have to take them on there we have to take Henry at his word that he only means the one that is about
conversation. Do we trust Henry enough to think that this isn't a double entendre? I don't know I mean
Henry's got you know Henry's got his eyes set on swinging Teddy bear up Aura but he seems like he's mean
to Trixie. I don't know I don't trust this Henry especially in the show I'll say that. It seems like an
arbitrary picking of favorites because also like if we're being honest if you look at silhouettes of the two
of them they look the same. Why is he so hard on one and so in love with the other? Yes I did have that
same thought where you're like yeah what are we even doing here like what is this these are just bears
there's different sized bears what they're both like similarly sized I feel like. Is it confidence?
Is swinging Teddy Barra just more confident? I think you're probably you might be onto something there we're just
saying that then the shots he's taking at her are uncalled for if he's being selective I don't know he's
blinded yes maybe what you're saying he's blinded by Teddy Barra's confidence. Yeah in the process he
might hurt Trixie's confidence he might cause the confidence. Of course he is he rejects Trixie she asks to make
out with him and he says oh maybe then the bears save him so yes this poor Trixie is just getting like the
shaft again. The heads on the wall are all in the Trixie. That's true they're kind of my favorite characters
so I mean if you're gonna get admired by anybody doesn't it make it all the better then that Trixie as portrayed
in the film gets this full makeover and is presented as the sexiest bear on earth. That's true I mean I think in bear
logistics you would want your mate to be bigger come hibernating season at least because then they're more likely to
survive until the spring. That's true a lean bear would struggle might not make it through the end. If I was a bear I would
struggle. If you were a bear with your current body yeah you'd be like an alarmingly skinny bear. Yeah that's probably true. I think though if you
bearify any of us as Tona bearified us in the work is very confusing not verified bearified. Bearified yeah. In the artwork for the show I mean
like we all gain a lot of pounds because we're I think by virtue of like if you become a bear you're just you're not just
yourself but with fur I think you also there's 50 pounds minimum. Yeah no that's probably true too so yeah Trixie sad Wendell sad
there's another one too would I have written down. Big Al's pretty sad. Oh Big Al's so sad it's sadder than the other one. Big Al's so sad. Yes. In the American version very funny
dressed as baby New Year. Yes very fun I mean it's that's the funniest thing for sure but it is also like he's really like depressed. It's like one of the big finale things
of the show is how depressed Big Al is. And then Shaker has turned white and is freezing and he's like like chattering. He turned polar. He turned polar as the bears that we went to
visit. That's right. And then Teddy has been in a ski accident. She's hurt. Yeah. Is that why she has the cast on? Yeah she's hurt. I missed it. She is hurt because he says he says like a very easy
like as soon as I find a pen I'll be up to sign your cast you know. Yeah she does want to come up and sign my cast. Yeah but in watching the videos a little odd you weren't really like set up to notice the
cast. Like it kind of creeps up the longer you're watching it. One of the performers is injured. I mean God bless her for continuing on. Yeah she's like when Dave Grohl broke his leg on stage and you know he just they put him in like a little throne and he continued the
tour. You know that's right and by the way here's some there's a type of comment I've noticed lately because I suddenly got in an episode recently I got a little self-conscious about you and I's classic rock talk and yes I do
consider Dave Grohl classic rock at this point in time and I just want to say recent feedback has taught me that people are on board with the classic rock talk. All I needed to hear was two people say it so guess what? We're back. Okay. Guess who's getting referenced? The bad finger and the raspberries. You're all in. You're all in again. You're welcome on this theme park podcast. They're all back. Those listeners who were into it would say they're back.
They would say it's a little bit of a reach but they would say it yeah. Yeah okay. They'd see Mike or I and say there goes my hero. That's right. And express that they don't want to be a monkey wrench. Does anything defy this Christmas depression that we're all suddenly feeling from the show? Is anything, does anything
brighten it? Sleigh Ride by the Sunbonnets is pretty lively. All three shows the Sunbonnets have such great up tempo like jaunty songs. I think the Five Bear Rug songs, some of them in this tracks in the snow I think is really good and Hungry as a Bear is fun too. When they say if Santa Claus is if he comes down the chimney he might get it. I think that's a good one.
If he comes down the chimney he might get it. Like they rhyme, they stretch the pronunciation of eat to like if I get it and I just thought that was so funny. You know what's a great thing about the show? The Sunbonnet trio is finally decent. They're bundled up. That's right. They're covered up to an appropriate level for their age. No more of these skimpy bikinis. This is finally a modest show.
Non body show. Big like Mrs. Claus style like velvet hoods and outfits. Yes for sure that is true. My awakening was Mrs. Claus. That's my definition of a woman. That's why you found the bonnet outfits too much. Those scandalous bonnets.
Yes I want velvet head to toe. Scott is a Mrs. Claus fetish. Alright took four years of the podcast to get it out of me. That's right. She gets the tough end of the stick. That old Helen test situation. How do you think she feels? She doesn't even have a first name. It probably is Helen.
I don't think so. I guess you're right. Probably named in some Hallmark movie or something but those don't count. There's no official word on this. There's McCarpenter as Mrs. Claus and she was like Janine Claus or something.
There's like three movies with the Lori Loughlin. Yes right. Mrs. Claus. Hold on I gotta find out if she has a first name. Mrs. Claus. I'm on Wikipedia. Mrs. Claus also known as Mrs. Santa Claus. Is the legendary wife of Santa Claus.
What's the female version of Santa? Santina? Oh maybe. A gender swapped Santa. That's what the movie executives would say. That's like in a saucy 1960 mad magazine spread. Santa is hot now.
And tempting presidential candidate Richard Nixon. Does Mrs. Claus have a first name? Arthur Christmas. What is Arthur Christmas? Is that a new thing? That was in the last 10 years I think. 2011.
What's her name? Margaret. Pretty close to Helen. It's gotta be older though for it to be canon in my opinion. It's a pretty nullified name a little bit. She's gotten a raw deal. We could name her now. We could have our own Mrs. Claus first name.
What's an appealing name? Rebecca? Rebecca Claus. Gertrude? Scarlet Claus. Scarlet Claus is cool. Great. It's an S. By the way you just launched a franchise too. Scarlet Claus.
Scarlet Claus seems like she's gonna be out for revenge. Yeah she is. I wonder why. Did somebody shoot a reindeer in front of her? Yep that's it. Reindeer was gunned down in front of her. Oh it's just a John Wick scenario. Yeah I'm thinking I'm Mary.
There is a reindeer in the show. They added the red nose to one character and I'm blanking on the name. To Max. Max is the Rudolph nose and Melvin has the Christmas lights and his antlers which is very cute. I just wish that was done on more rides.
I guess they would argue it would cost 10 grand to put the red nose on Melvin or Max every year. They would explain to me you might think it's fun but do you understand how much money that costs?
Power? We gotta pay somebody to get up there and do it? That's a ladder that we have to have around? Ladders aren't free. Yeah and I would say make the red nose on Cosmo in the Guardians of the Galaxy queue. On the dog or something. And they would be like that's 15,000. You don't understand that. We have to get a specialized person to open the glass. A glass opener. And then we have to make the nose. And then yeah it's a team of three people.
Haunted Mansion Holiday must cost a fortune. Because you have to cover or remove or hide the original stuff. Then you have to put in the Nightmare Before Christmas stuff and then you have to do it all again a few months later.
Yeah. I mean the numbers for this thing are like Haunted Mansion Holiday costs like $100,000 to do the transformation every year. Something like that. Or more. It is major. It is major. So yeah I get it. But it is just so fun to see little tweaks to existing characters to make them fit into whatever the holiday or whatever the event is.
We got Monsters After Dark. Is there a good... I feel like they could easily do a Christmas overlay of Guardians.
Oh and they have that holiday special coming. Oh that's a very good point. To Disney Plus with the whole cast and stuff.
Yeah. What if it's that maybe Santa is trapped in the tower. They're glad he's trapped because he's been hoarding presents. He's been keeping presents away from Rocket and the Guardians. He's determined that they're naughty and not nice.
So we gotta go up there and steal Santa's presents. I mean that's a great idea. And leave him up there in the tower to rot.
I would have said yeah like it's Evil Santa or like Planet of the Evil Santas or something. And there's like Santa's Unleashed. You could call it Santa's Unleashed. And it's just like alien Santas.
On every floor? A different giant Santa? Oh yeah. Yeah different like grotesque Santas. And then have the same... I mean you could call it Santa's After Dark I guess. Just like Santa's After Dark.
And then use the same basic song. It'll be just as fun. We thought we found a real Santa. It turns out it was a Chitauri disguised as one. Right? Is that the aliens from Avengers? That's the aliens. Yeah.
We're gonna find him. We're gonna rescue real Santa. We just gotta get through all these alien ones. Yeah. I mean it's done. Done. There's no notes needed for that. Perfect.
Take this Santa punch. Just take the audio of Jason doing Rocket there and don't even call Bradley Cooper about it. Wolverine Santa. Just kidding. He's not here yet. Sorry. Perfect. Yeah perfect. Again perfect.
And also like on Web Slingers they could like have it just be snowing. Oh you're talking even less. I love that. Yeah. Why are we... yeah you don't even have to redo the entire... Yeah absolutely. Yeah.
The Spiderbots took his gift to MJ. To Mary Jane. He's gotta get back. I mean that's good too but that's a little more work. Oh okay. You gotta get another Tom Holland. I'm just saying like don't even mention it just like it's snow. There's snow going on.
You're just adding another layer in a video editing software of snow in front of the existing like final footage. No you don't need to get Tom Holland. He doesn't have to re-explain and thing. He's working on his dancing. He's gonna be Fred Astaire. I saw that he's gonna be Fred Astaire.
I also saw somewhere in like Fred Astaire like put in it as Will like never make a movie about me. Oh Will Schmills. People can write whatever they want. Doesn't mean anything.
I'm sure he'll do it. I've got a holiday overlay idea. What if the Little Mermaid ride starts and you start trying to go underwater but then you just like hit solid. Yeah. But then like you hear a drill sound. Like there's actually a secret drill in the back of the clams.
So now you're burrowing through ice and all the characters don't move anymore because they're all frozen. And then they also just turn the air conditioning way fucking crazy. So you're freezing. Yeah. Extremely unpleasant. It's bitterly cold.
And by the way I think I described science where I have it right where all lakes and rivers and bodies of water are all frozen all the way down to the bottom. Yeah. Yeah. I thought so. My science understanding is solid. Yeah.
Scott that reminds me of an interesting I think an interesting detail about their show at least the frozen penguin that is one of the differences between the American and Japanese versions of this show.
Terrence sings Blue Christmas with a penguin and in a mirror in Disneyland Disney World it was frozen in a block of ice and shakes like jingle bells. But in Japan it's a full ass like animatronic who has a conversation with him.
Oh wow. Oh geez. Well again I was with so many things they did more and better in Japan. That's incredible. It is funny watching the Japanese version too. I was it struck me how much the big Alan is.
How much the big Alan animatronic moved like it just looked so smooth and right right detailed. I like Gomer is Gomer's outfit a lot. He's like what's Gomer wearing remind me. He's got like a like a silver coat on and he's like got like I would say like he's got like a tinsel kind of like wreath around his neck as well.
And then he has sunglasses on. He looks like he's definitely the coolest dressed I think of the of the bears during this holiday one. He's got like a little tree I think I think it's on his piano unless the angles wrong but he's got like a tiny tree on the piano and then a stocking hung on the front.
Like he just has a great looking setup as per usual. I figured this out in the first one. I think I think Gomer is handsome. I think Gomer can get it doesn't wear out as welcome stays quiet while the other ones blabber on and on. And that's why he gets the gentleman's lair.
If you were to have to go really like to like make compared to another like a rock and roll icon or something I'm trying to think.
I think Brian Ferry. I guess he sings I just think of him as being like a dapper. Yeah. It's a good question. I actually I don't I didn't have one I was just thinking because now that we're full steam ahead back on classic rock talk.
Those two commenters. Hey be careful what you wish for. That's all we needed to hear.
We'll we'll say names session musicians besides we just heard. Boy you're in for a treat. Here's so much Lee Rittenour talk from now on.
Twenty twenty two is a whole new ballgame. The differences between Wilco drummer Ken Coomer and Wilco drummer Glenn Cochie.
Get ready. I guess that's class. It's newer but still that's 20 years old at this point. Baby Oscar is cute a little looks a little concerned in this one looks a little more scared and sad.
It's a weird sad winter. It's the sad alarming revolution different. Oh what a pout. Oh this guy. Did you find this sad. Now are you just realizing it now Scott. Jason you thought it thought there was a lot of sadness here right.
I noticed I mean a lot of Christmas songs can be very melancholy. I'll be home for Christmas you know. Yeah. Song in the trenches of World War One and have yourself a merry little Christmas.
Also pretty sad. I mean all the it's so funny all these are so recent but yeah I mean sleigh ride is very up. I love the conclusion of the show. Let it snow into Rudolph the Red Nosed Reindeer into winter wonderland in America and then in Japan.
Yeah yeah there's difference. I love a music where Q where like one person is singing and then the next line everyone on stage is singing in like joins in with the Bears. You just hear so many voices in that conclusion.
There are yeah there's a big yeah they're both I think I don't know what I want to say this is like the best big finale of all the shows but it is it's up it's up there of the three I guess.
Yeah always you know when that big stage rolls out when the five bear rugs move forward and all the little stages open up and all the bears are singing in harmony. I don't care which of the three it's always such a delight.
Yeah like and everybody's just lit up and clapping. It's I think one of in any of the shows in any of the parks I think it's like one of the more joyous vistas that you get to see in anything.
Just everybody's so happy. Out of the context of this podcast calling the country bears singing a joyous Vista is just fantastic.
Most people would say like seeing like a national park is a joyous Vista.
No these bear robots in Christmas sweaters is one of the seven wonders of the world does.
In Japan Big Al sings Auld Lang Syne.
The show in Japan too a mix of song song sung in Japanese some in English. Yeah it's interesting the ones that they chose to do that way.
Yeah Santa Claus is Coming to Town is in Japan.
They still have Rudolph and Winter Wonderland it just instead of Let It Snow it's Santa Claus is Coming to Town.
I don't understand any of these are all the side steps to me.
Yeah it's a good question I mean I don't know if there's anything just like there's a cultural difference or something or that song is more popular in Japan than it is.
There probably is something like that. I think Guy was even talking about like for some reason there's not the extensive history of why Let It Snow is playing in America and Santa Claus is Coming to Town.
For some reason that's not an easily gettable fact on the internet.
It's not people begging for this information.
People aren't dying to know what the difference is but it is look I'm interested I'm very interested.
That would be the most interesting thing I would learn all day if somebody would tell me I bet.
I could be wrong but I bet there's something interesting along the lines of like this song is more popular in this country.
But Santa Claus is Coming to Town is popular in America too.
Covered by Mr. Classic Rock Bruce Springsteen of course.
One of the best rock and roll Christmas songs of all time if we're going to go there which we will.
I love the Billy Corgan Smashing Pumpkins like Christmas Time has come that's kind of creepy.
That's what I'm talking about.
I don't.
Maybe now I don't like that we've let the cat out of the bag on the classic rock.
Because now we're going rock and roll Christmas.
I love simply having a wonderful Christmas time.
Well of course.
I feel like people say or like or the Mariah Carey people are like oh I'm hearing it again.
It's like yeah these songs are great.
Well I think I think everyone's in support of Mariah but you hear some weird feelings about wonderful Christmas time.
Boy do you and it's not fuddling to me.
You can say maybe the songs are like a little too long.
That's the closest thing I would accept as a criticism.
Madness. The ding ding dongs can go on as long as they want.
That's what I feel too.
I like long versions of every song that I like.
So I don't want the country where it's done wonderful Christmas time.
That's that's that's a plus up.
The Sun but our tricks.
Someone should have done Christmas rapping by the waitresses.
That's a fun.
There's a lot of different.
As a kid as a kid my favorite Christmas song I think was rocking around the Christmas tree which I guess is a little bit like do what be.
I don't know.
I don't want you guys to get mad at me here but I think it is a little bit of a boom boom boom like Brian Susser.
I'm sure does a version of rocking around the Christmas tree.
No I bet he does.
Oh I bet it reinvents the wheel.
He brings so many new ideas to these songs.
And what if I did it but like the same.
Oh yeah.
Another good one Brian.
The whole orchestra cheers them on.
I found about this show I found a newsprint a framed newsprint ad that someone was selling I believe on eBay and it's advertising bear season starts November 23rd.
The show is new at the time but you can also see in this ad with other musical acts at the bottom.
Wow.
Oh baby.
Yeah.
New edition.
Hey there's one.
My favorite Christmas song songs album the new edition Christmas EP.
Everybody look it up on Spotify.
By far my favorite Christmas rock or R&B adjacent music.
They did a whole it's six songs that are original super synthy.
They don't even really feel that Christmasy.
It's just like they it's almost like they had demos or something.
It's just like they it's almost like they had demos ready to go for regular songs and they just made the lyrics Christmas and they rule weird little monologues like I want to spend Christmas with two girls.
My mom and of course my candy girl.
That's great.
Oh that's adorable little speeches.
Check that one.
That's that's my recommendation.
Also playing around this time I feel like we've namecheck these groups before crash and Papa do run run.
Yeah probably when we talked about Tomorrowland bands.
Yeah I'd imagine.
Yeah.
Papa do run run like a Beach Boys cover but like people who played with them.
What's the best.
How many Beach Boys Christmas songs are there.
There's a lot because there is a 60s one and I love that album obviously but then there was a rejected 70s one which is a little lazy talking about just Christmasifying song.
They had a like not that great song called loop de loop flying in an airplane and they just like all right let's knock out a Christmas album fast loop de loop Santa's got an airplane.
Not even Santa's got a sleigh Santa's got an airplane.
They kept airplane they were committed to airplane.
Kind of interesting so why doesn't Santa have an airplane.
It's less magical but probably get more done.
Here's my DC 10 I fill it with presents.
You can fit more cargo space.
Why not.
Thanks cool.
Great idea.
Thanks cool pilot John Travolta uses less magic a lot more diesel fuel.
My gift to the air and your lungs.
How would we use solar what happens when it's cloudy.
Oh no Santa Santa's on one Santa's got theories.
The earth is flat anyway.
Oh geez wheeze.
I what I would not be who else among you who among you travels around the entire earth.
I've seen it.
It's flat.
I'm telling you who are you to believe me or your lying eyes.
How much time have you spent in the sky.
I am into the polls really I live at one.
Here's a photo of me almost falling off the edge.
I did it look at see one leg is teetering I'm making a face.
Oh I'm saying right into space I could have gone.
Here's the ice walls and if you squint you can see the UN soldiers guarding the edge.
I've been read and green pill.
I'm going to the conference next year.
I'm not going to wear Santa clothes.
I'm just going to be playing because I don't want to distract.
I don't want my celebrity to distract from the theories of what the flat earthers have to say.
The truth.
I'm going to shave.
You won't even know it's me.
It'll grow back by Christmas.
That Jim Brewer's really something.
Oh ho ho I say to his comedy.
I was excited to learn because theme park great Thurl Ravenscroft credit it in this show as one of the voices on the wall passed away in 2005.
I learned was doing Tony the Tiger until 2004.
Wow.
They pick him up in a limo and take him to recording.
Oh that's wonderful.
Oh geez.
That's so cool to hear.
And even commercials after that have apparently used occasionally used archive audio.
They still use him as they should.
There's a new voice.
There is a new voice.
But I guess every now and then they would use him.
Oh I almost forgot one of my favorite parts of this show.
Henry at the beginning says the line and coming from the kitchen is the sweet smell of turkey and yeah yeah.
Like he says yams in such an odd way it is up there with puddle in the original.
What?
Don't recall this at all.
I don't know it either.
Yeah.
Yes.
That's it.
Yeah.
Like it's kind of a Yaya.
Yums.
I was I was think I was writing something down and I had the video playing and I had to go back.
Hold on.
I got to hear that again.
It just hit my ear in such a way.
This is a sequel to Ham in the House.
Yams in the House.
It's a given that there's ham in the house but this Christmas Jason wants yams in the
house.
Yeah.
We usually do have yams with the little marshmallows on top and the ham.
So you're a yam guy.
I'm a yam guy.
Oh I love a yam.
Sweet potato or yam.
Yeah.
I guess I like them.
I can't tell the difference unless they were both prepared and I eat them back to back.
Well it sounds like something to do in the new year.
Hey.
And it's something to do an episode about.
You're not wrong.
The difference between sweet potatoes and yams.
Yeah.
Well if we don't have anything else I think this might be we might actually be heading
to the the end of this episode and therefore the end of Country Bird Jambor Week.
Geez I think I think we made it.
This is this is one thing though really quick.
This is this is rare.
This might be neither here nor there.
But just funny that we've been doing all this bear talk and then right outside my house
like on my doorstep I found this little this little bear this little stuffed bear just
coincidentally which is not it's not my son's I don't know where it came from and I don't
think anybody's given it to I don't really know the story with it but like it was just
outside my house.
It's sort of like the little bear that the kid bear in the show holds right like Oscar
Oscar Oscar.
Yeah.
Like he's holding a little teddy bear and it looks it's kind of similar.
I you know I guess there's just bear spirit in the air.
I don't I don't know what it's about exactly but just you know just sort of fun sign of
the week I guess.
Yeah that's really nice.
It's pretty cute right.
Do we think it's.
Yeah I think it's very cute.
Yeah.
Is it.
No.
Something.
Is it moving.
Yeah it looks like it's moving.
Looks like it's moving a little.
Huh.
What.
It's like moving on its own.
Is that are you manipulating it with your fingers.
I mean I'm sort of shaking here.
Maybe I'll just put it on the ground and see if it.
Oh my god.
Oh yeah.
Look at that.
Oh my god.
Wait it's moving without me.
Boys boys.
What.
It's speaking.
What was that.
I mean I.
Good tidings to you.
Good tidings to you and all of your friends.
It's the sector keeper.
Oh my god.
Boys.
Yes it's me.
I Trojan.
Bared you Scott.
Wow a Trojan.
You fell for it.
You brought the bear in.
You have a child and you brought the bear in your house.
Jeez.
Oh were you trying to teach him a lesson.
I'm trying to teach all of you a lesson.
Boys.
You've been bad.
What.
We have.
How.
What do you mean.
You did a full week without me.
Oh are you saying because I mean we haven't done like a daily thing since the downturn
did like the ones that we've done with you.
Yeah so we did a day we did an episode every day.
But it but I didn't think.
I mean why would you want to be on it.
Why would you want to be on this.
It's about country bears.
What do you have to do.
You're like a mall guy.
Like we're friends.
Yeah but I I like bears.
Chicago bears.
Coca Cola bears.
Those type of bears aren't in this show.
They're there.
They don't.
The Chicago Bears aren't singing on stage at Disney World.
Bear naked lady.
Those aren't even bears.
I mean they come up all the time but that's a different spelling of bear.
It's not.
Look I'm glad you're trying to like free associate and attach to the topic but honestly we just
didn't we just I don't mean to like typecast you but it seems like your thing is shopping
centers next to theme parks.
I just didn't think you cared about this show.
I just thought you guys were just kind of like hanging out without me and I don't know
like you didn't want to be friends anymore.
No that's not what I know.
I've been tweeting.
I've been tweeting a lot.
Yeah I've been tweeting a lot about the work stoppage at Cricket Wireless.
I know like I've been busy too and.
Is there like a like sort of a union situation.
There's a lot of this in here lately.
We're trying to become the first cricket wireless to organize and.
Did they turn off your complimentary like cell phone plan.
Is that why you had to possess a stuffed bear.
You couldn't just call Scott on your cricket wireless.
They cut my prepaid minutes and we're pushing for just like so we could go home at night
just like pretty basic worker rights.
They're not letting they weren't letting you go home at night.
Fuck you in the store.
No they have a clock in policy.
What is that.
What does a clock in policy mean.
You can't clock out.
It's a one way.
A one way policy.
You can only clock in.
Oh my gosh.
Like a haunted mansion or so.
This is awful.
Yeah.
So anyway I thought maybe because I was working a lot you guys just left me out or something.
It doesn't mean just because something happens without you doesn't mean that we're you're
you're not in the crew.
You're always in the crew.
All right.
It just doesn't feel that way and I think you guys would take it pretty hard if I ran
away or something.
Oh my god.
We wouldn't want to run away.
You want me to pack up my snacks.
Is that what you want.
You want me to pack up my snacks in my backpack and run away.
No no of course not.
Of course not.
No we want to be.
Granola bar.
Gushers.
Ring pop.
Twinkies.
Well like we'll have you back on sometime when there's like a mall or something like
when the thing you know about one of your areas of expertise.
Did you know that.
It doesn't seem like this is enough.
Maybe we need to Mike.
Maybe we need to put our money where our mouth is.
What if I don't want you to feel this way and would it help ease some of these feelings
if we promise you that in 2022 next year we will do a new daily adventure with you our
old friend the sector keeper.
Really.
I say yes.
Yes.
I haven't talked about this before but the last thing we would want is to betray your
friendship and have you run away.
So we're willing to make that promise for next year.
Can Jason come.
I mean I hope so.
He'd never miss it.
He wouldn't miss it for the world.
He loves it.
Can Mike come.
Yes I can come too.
But is there anyone else you're curious about coming.
Can.
Can Edwin come.
Hang on hang on.
You're listing.
I'm putting out this offer to you and then you're ignoring me.
Can Scotty come.
OK.
Well assuming that means me then yes of course I'll be there.
Oh you're just pulling my chain.
Classic sector keeper.
Well look hey are you in.
Does that make you feel better about what happened this week.
Yeah if we can accomplish something.
But you know I'm going to be a little icy until then.
I don't know maybe I'll still run away and maybe me running away will set up some sort
of hijinks in premise for a future date.
And perhaps all of this will be postponed to 2023 because Western countries keep hoarding
the vaccine.
Well it's up to it's up to America to decide then I guess if we do another saga.
It's not in our hands anymore.
This is another benefit of a vaccine patent waiver is that it makes daily podcast series
that much smoother to do.
Right.
That's right.
But in the meantime I only clocked in so I got to get going.
Oh yeah.
Geez.
OK OK.
Yeah we'll go go go make your shift.
By all means we don't want you to be late.
I guess we'll see you next year it seems like.
Yes we'll see you next year.
My heart's still broken and we've got to mend it and you know there's still some beef and
stuff and surely we'll remember all of this stuff a year from now.
I absolutely will.
With that you survived podcast the ride country bird jammer week and podcast the ride for
2021.
Thank you for listening all year.
Hit the road go remain clocked in and we'll talk to you soon.
See you soon.
Bye.
Happy holidays y'all.