Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast may contain
dystopian cookie nightmares,
forced removal of elephant innards,
and toxic ass foam.
2022 takes flight with Dumbo the Flying Elephant
on podcast The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the podcast that turns 90-second rides into 90-minute episodes.
I'm Scott Gardner, back in person with Jason Sheridan, hi.
Hi, that's right.
Yeah, it's been a month to the day since the last Improved.
We've done a couple, but over Zoom.
So here we are, changes everything.
Worth bringing up, obviously, Mike Carlson.
Oh my gosh, worth bringing up.
Don't people love the ins and outs of the podcasting game?
Yeah, we are here.
It is the longest maybe break between a main feed
that we've ever taken, is that correct?
Yeah, maybe.
Yeah.
And if the world was better, it would have maybe felt like a nice break, wouldn't it?
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, well, you brought it up.
It's, you know, you want to come in with some positive energy in 2022,
and that's, you know, for any new year, you want to do that.
You want to do it this year, but it's really hard to do, I'd say,
under the shadow of everything that's going on.
And I don't need to say it, but I'll say it.
That is, of course, the closure this week of Shrek 4D Universal Studios Florida.
It's like, how do we even...
I think we should be lauded for even doing an episode at all,
considering the circumstances, but...
And I'm sorry if this is too painful for you to bring up,
because it's closer to home, but the soon upon us closer of Sugarboo and Co.
Yeah.
At downtown Disney.
No, I know. It's a rough one.
Yeah, I think the dates are set.
I mean, what, like...
I don't want to vocalize this where we end the podcast,
but I know we've at least all thought it.
I think there'd be a relief to saying, like, how do we even go on,
given all of these closures on both coasts? I feel trapped.
Yeah, but you know, here's the thing, like, you're right.
And I felt like we should end the podcast after Sugarboo announced it was closing.
But...
No one would have blamed us. Not one person would have blamed us.
Right, because our spirits were so low.
In case you know what we're talking about, this is a store at downtown Disney
that sells wooden signs with sayings on it.
But I went into the Sugarboo and there was a sign that said,
My heart will go on.
And it was one hundred and fifty dollars.
And I said, you know what? The podcast must go on.
That's right. So right.
And if they weren't reducing that price, even though it was one of their final days
of operation, if they're going to be true to who they are right up to the end,
then so do we need to be.
Is there a liquidation sale going on at Sugarboo?
Should we? I haven't really been going a lot of places lately,
but should we go down and see if there's any good sales?
Well, I mean, you also got to go down and check out the new stores,
Pele Soccer and Love Pop, a store that sells mostly pop up greeting cards.
Pop up like so like a picture book, like a pop up book.
Yeah, a child's pop up book like paper flower, pop up paper flower.
There is now now in 2022.
In like as we heading into year two of pandemic.
Now there is a Disney store that is all pop up cards.
Well, the third party, they do have some Disney themed cards.
And then the Pele Soccer, of course, has Pele stuff
and also soccer memorabilia and jerseys and everything.
And it's his brand of it's great.
Pele, it's the corporate entity Pele.
It's the whatever you want to call it, Pele.
I think this is that was the most rosy theme park news I'd seen in a while.
Like, oh, very odd, very specific stores returning to downtown Disney.
Maybe nature is healing.
Yeah, I guess so. Yeah.
Like micro targeted, oddly, like more specific
than would be at a regular mall or shopping center. Yeah.
Like who would ever it does?
The pop up card place harkens back to like an all wind up toy store
at City Walk or the you know, it's not gone, but the sock store.
I feel like sometimes when I see a Sephora,
I feel like they have lost their mission of stores that you
would assume don't exist, which shouldn't exist.
And why would they? Yeah.
I want fridge magnets and bottle openers and nothing else.
I just like I would I wish Pele was involved in more of the stores
down at downtown Disney.
Oh, Pele's Jamba. Yeah.
Why not? Pele's I'm glad to see that.
Pele is the man Pele we're talking about, right?
The soccer player. Yeah.
So I'd like to see him get out there with more like endorsements and more.
I don't know. Got to get his brand up.
Does he have let me ask this question, a celebrity liquor.
Does Pele have a celebrity liquor?
I don't know. Offhand.
OK, he might be a clean living athlete who does not
who thinks that liquor would get in the way of great soccer skills.
OK, well, we'll look it up and maybe we'll suggest it to him on his website
if he has a, you know, suggestions email.
I appreciate that you're striving for more, but you know, that Pele
has finally come to downtown Disney and then you're just like, you're right.
Pele, you're right.
You got to appreciate Pele land. I'm greedy.
I wish Scottie Pippen would come to downtown Disney
because he has a celebrity liquor.
He has a celebrity endorsed popcorn.
And I wish he would come down and do something with Disney.
But I don't know what it is. I'm not sure.
But we can talk about that later.
I feel like it'd be a good
zone for him. Just yeah.
Well, he's really ramped it up in the last couple of years.
So I feel like restaurant stores is next for him and for the brand.
So to play on the ultimate stage, to play in the ultimate arena,
I guess you would say that I would say downtown Disney.
That is the ultimate arena. Yes, I would say that.
And of course, I still have a bottle of digits.
His bourbon I have not opened yet.
It's going to be saved for a special occasion.
So I've transitioned out of liking
Casamigos to exclusively liking digits, despite having not
tried it. Yeah, exactly. Yeah, exactly.
The mere notion of digits.
Yeah. Bye bye, Randy. Hello, Scotty.
That's the way I feel.
Hey, no complaints for me. Yeah, I'm I'm loving.
Well, now I've never felt better about 2020.
22 is different. There's a lot of different.
I mean, if everyone wants to declare how they're going to be different
going forward in this year, I think this is the time to do it
before we dive into Dumbo.
Jason, what do you think? Oh, I don't know.
I hadn't really given that much thought.
OK, so you're going to be the same.
Got it, Scott. Yeah, exactly the same.
Perfect. No, no, it's
let me see. I I don't know.
I say this and I think I might immediately take it back.
But like, I don't do I need to be more
open minded to
generic radio music of the 90s and 2000s.
This is what I feel like is it's it's come up a lot.
I don't know if it's becoming a wedge.
You know, I I I I slap these things down the green days
and the Brian Setzer's and am I missing
many musical marvels by not pursuing these discographies
of things that are played at supermarkets all the time?
I don't know. I mean, you have to answer that question for yourself.
It is it funny to me now that Brian Setzer is a villain on this podcast.
It's hilarious to me. I love it.
I love that you hate Brian Setzer.
And this was a second gate development, potentially, if you missed this.
I think about it every other day.
I go, Scott hates Brian Setzer and I giggle like it makes me laugh so much.
I didn't want to add to the episode that we just did on the second gate,
which was about an Incredibles ice show, if you didn't hear it.
And we also met a new friend named not the opposite of an enemy,
a new hero on the podcast named J.
Bigga, of course.
So check that out at Patreon.com slash podcast.
Right. But over there recently, yeah, there was some Brian Setzer discussion
because he was in the Country Bears movie.
And I didn't want to bring it up, but I was the thing that inspired
that Incredibles ice show episode.
There was a the 2005 very Merry Christmas parade features Brian Setzer
at the beginning. They open it.
I didn't want to open that can of worms.
But since we've opened the sets are kind of worms now.
He he he say he opens up the parade.
I'm in the whole orchestra, of course.
He does jingle bells and the change lyrics to be,
oh, what fun it is to ride in a 57 Chevrolet.
And here I am saying I was going to be more open minded.
But I did when I heard that, when I watched the video of that
and then like his whole horn section go like, hey, I was like,
Mike, Jason, tell me this is good.
Look me in the eye and tell me that you like that.
I have to watch the video. I have to see it.
Yes, I've already tainted the description of it. Yeah.
I don't know. Offhand, though.
I mean, you laughed. But is that a mocking laugh?
Is it a or is it a laugh of you?
If you were at the concert, would you go, ha ha?
Well, Brian, you're encouraged.
It's so tainted by now, though.
This is a problem because you've tainted it with with this disgust.
So I feel like I wouldn't even maybe I would have been like, oh,
it's kind of annoying or that's stupid or whatever.
But now when I see it, I can't help but think of the anger toward it.
So I don't think I'll ever be able to completely assess it because it was
I never owned a Brian Setzer album.
I've never like all I said was I do like the song he does in the Country Bear movie.
That's really all I've actually said.
I liked what the single he had. What was it?
I don't like the Stray Cats one as much as the 90s single that he had with the orchestra.
What am I? Jump driving.
Thank you. I did like it at the time.
I don't listen to it now.
So so it's never going to be possible for me not to watch it and laugh.
So now it's actually you made it better for me.
You've made all these performances better.
I know. I knew this is where it was.
Go that like what now would have because I've registered my dislike
now to Mike and Jason going full force on Brian Setzer out of nowhere.
As a spite listen.
This is a situation.
Yeah, I will be I mean, I'm full disclosure, like depending on what you're shitting.
There are the green day.
I did have like a lot of affection for and I do when I say I mean, I know it's
how it makes more sense to talk about it.
And they're in there in my reconciliatory twenty twenty two.
I get it. I get it. It's not for me.
But Setzer, yeah, I don't have much affection for or disdain for.
But yes, if it comes up on the show, it is 100 percent an attempt to get a rise out of you.
Yes. Yes. Yeah.
There's no way around it. Yeah.
Understood. Jason, you've been awfully silent on this matter.
Well, where's the in terms of what I would like to hear and what I I like.
I think I liked Brian Setzer Orchestra when they were leaning more towards
the like Dorsey Brothers than the Rockabilly stuff.
What are you talking about?
I didn't really more towards the Dorsey Brothers.
The actual like big band.
Like I thought about like you reference something I have no reference for.
Basie's orchestra. Yeah.
Yeah. Like I saw them.
I first learned about them from Cone.
The Brian Setzer Orchestra was on Conan and they all had like tuxedos on or white
chat dinner jackets on and they were doing like in the mood, you know, just a straight cover.
Mm hmm. I don't know.
I don't know what song you're talking about.
And I just like that.
I just like old music.
I played in the mood in eighth grade.
I'm in the mood. What's in the mood?
Now that I know that title and I just liked old music because it was I liked old movies.
So like I I and that's where I got to it and I would find the CDs and like you record stores.
So you had this.
I had one or two of the like Setzer Orchestra CDs.
So when Jason's brings it up, it's not necessarily 100 percent troll.
Yeah, no.
But like anytime anyone has like a very visceral reaction to anything on the show,
the others like jump on.
Well, yeah, there is a potential episode topic floating around the other day where you're like,
guys, this one's real bad.
And you gave a specific and I'm like, you are making me want to watch it so much more.
Oh, you are making me know the other.
Yes. Everyone else becomes a vulture all of a sudden.
No, I smell blood.
That's good podcasting is sadly the problem is the problem is that.
And then I started getting marketing material for your consideration.
And I'm like, well, if I'm already considering it as well, I guess it is well.
That to the movie you're thinking about, I just heard Jim Hill talk about it.
Really? I was just listening to Jim Hill talk about the same.
Well, if he's talking about it, we got to America's talking about it.
Yeah. So, OK, well, I just wanted to know like where the traps might be and where this could potentially be going.
And if you end up suddenly all nine albums deep into you're always playing Brian Setzer in the car.
Lindsay and Jane are like, what's happening?
Why is the song? I'm going to have to listen to a few.
It's nothing but Big Band with you for now.
Look, it's a whole thing. It started with it started as a spiked thing with Scott.
But now I look what can I say? I love the BSO.
They remind me of the Dorsey's BSO.
If I get into Big Band revival music in twenty twenty two, it's not out of the question.
I mean, possible. I have actual like Big Band compilations like in my eye.
So like when my Bluetooth, my car connects to my phone.
Usually when I drive, I listen to podcasts.
But if it this is auto defaults to music and sometimes it will just default to whatever is in the eye.
And then a live.
Yeah. Jason said, oh, I guess we're listening today.
Folks, we're listening to Bunny Bear again while we drive to In-N-Out Burger.
Oh, man, we got to do an old timey Big Band.
Yes. By the end of twenty twenty two, I think maybe not spurred not just by Scott's spite,
but also by being hopefully by then excited to be in bigger groups of people.
I think it's the Mike Carlson and Jason Sheridan orchestra.
I think you guys started orchestra. OK.
I think you can have one without being a master of one of the instruments yourself.
Well, I play trumpet, so I am.
Yeah. So you'll take a trumpet solo and I'll just do banter.
Uh huh. I'll have like a lazy conductor's one and I'll turn around a lot and mug to the audience.
And in between songs like, well, that was a real humdinger.
Oh, wow. We got another ditty coming up for you folks.
Well, there's more big band to come.
More. Let's just start building the stands.
Start building the what?
M.C. J.S.O.
So just like even though like, I don't know, maybe it's Carp Over the Horse,
but I say start building them even before you get the musicians,
because you got to get those looking nice and polished.
So, right.
Find a carpenter or start building them yourselves.
And before you know it, you'll be doing shows.
God, that sounds good. Yeah. Yeah.
Coming soon.
The all different world at the end of the year.
What's this episode about again?
About Dumbo the Flying Elephant.
The beloved attraction, the beloved attraction, which I saw
referenced as the only one at all six castle parks
or one of the few other websites saying one of the few attractions at all.
It's on every property.
It's on every theme park property. Yes. Yeah. Yeah.
It's a it's a it's a basic.
It's a tenant. It's a tent pole.
The most iconic ride.
Maybe. Yeah, that's what I think you got to.
You got to ask those kind of questions because and if we took our time
getting to it at the beginning, some of it might be at the end of the day,
it's a ride that just goes round and round. Right.
The ride itself is that. Yeah.
However, I think there's bigger stuff here.
I think it's it is. Yeah. It functions as a symbol.
I think it's it's important in the history and the the legacy.
Yeah. Bigger than itself.
Oh, my God. It is bigger than itself.
Yeah, I think it's one of the ones like Space Mountain or Haunted Mansion,
where it is shorthand for like theme parks, certainly shorthand for like Disney parks,
but shorthand for theme parks at large and also
copied everywhere.
Like, yeah, duplicated at traveling carnivals at regional amusement parks,
at fairs, you know.
Yeah. You sit in like sitting in a.
You know, Jason is something's wrong, but I want to imagine it.
Oh, I'm fine. I'm just
coffee repeating on me. Oh, yeah.
I was hoping you were crying about Dumbo
because that's a good also also good podcasting so we can get one of us to cry.
I mean, Dumbo, the movie, by the way, is a well,
there's another thing that's involved far beyond beyond the movie.
The sad kind of nightmarish animated film.
Yeah, which will come up later.
That there is more movie stuff tied into one version of this ride.
Right. Yeah, I did a rewatch of the movie and prep for this,
partially because it is short.
I think I can. All right. I can handle a 65 minute.
You know, sometimes you get the question.
I'm sure you guys do or, you know, as people are trying to figure out,
what is this theme park interest that these people I know have?
Or does that mean so you are you into the Disney movies?
Is that part of this?
And I will tend to say no, that would have been my answer in a soft way before.
But having reflected on movies like Peter Pan, Pinocchio and now Dumbo,
I might say specifically, I don't like the movies or at least these movies.
Right. Like Dumbo is just unrelenting.
I feel maybe you guys haven't done it in a little bit.
Well, it's for my. Yeah, I haven't done it real recently.
But the sadness and the bleakness of Dumbo, like why?
As a kid, I didn't like I liked Dumbo the character,
but I was I don't think I was ever begging to watch Dumbo over and over again.
It's like almost what you want is a Dumbo two, which maybe
I don't think they did that in straight to video times.
I think there were maybe plans in Walt era of another Dumbo that didn't happen.
Right. But what you want is like that to be the miserable backstory.
Yeah, that all is a prequel that you can ignore if you don't want to be upset.
And now you go on a brand new adventure with Dumbo that is 90 percent flying,
zero percent crows, zero percent scary clowns,
making him die from a thousand feet in the air.
Let's get let's strip all that out.
And it's just our friend flying around.
It's it's what you want is a movie that's like the ride.
I feel yes, you do.
100 percent flying and you want Dumbo quest for the magic feather.
Yeah, the feather, the feather gets lost.
Jason, could you make the title a little longer?
Dumbo returns colon
quest for the magic feather.
It can be longer. It could be longer in feather land.
Maybe in the journey, the journey to the rescue of that.
That is right. That's the journey to the rescue of the
phantom rescue of the mists of the magic feather.
Dumbo and Timothy in that.
OK, that's good.
Dumbo and Timothy in the quest for the whatever.
Yes. Yeah, I am.
I will give them credit.
That song, Baby Mine, is
I think a very beautiful song, but also maybe the saddest song ever made.
Yeah, yeah.
I discovered that during
well, I want to say peak pandemic, but who knows at this point
during pandemic one point, oh, when Disney was doing all these specials
that were like sing along from home that Katy Perry sang Baby Mine
in full Dumbo wardrobe with her little dog who was also in Dumbo.
Oh, wardrobe.
But not to a baby, not she had just had a baby and did it.
I don't believe so.
In this case, no, I think this was a dog.
A little doll is a little dress elephant.
By the way, did you guys have you guys seen any clips?
She's doing residency in Las Vegas.
OK, all right. I'll save it.
Never mind. Never mind.
Wait, can I spoiler alert a little bit of it?
Is it? It's got to be the one.
It's got to be the thing.
Are you OK? Yeah, I'm OK.
She's doing California Girls and there's a giant toilet with a talking shit.
Yes, she rises out and then a turd rises out.
She climbs up on some toilet paper.
She like twerks at the audience and then she climbs up on the top of the toilet
paper and then she's singing with this giant turd.
And I'm like, wow, how fast can I get to this?
Wow. I saw I saw her in Vegas.
It was a tour, not a Vegas residency.
But there was a long was this the song was Swish Swish,
which had kind of a basketball veneer.
And she just did a long basketball shooting contest with a dad from the audience
as the music just kind of do.
Uh huh. Just like simmered for a while.
And then I swear, like 15 minutes, it took forever to get the results
of the dunks or the shots in.
But it was great. It felt like now we're watching double their live.
Well, that's fun. Yeah.
Katy Perry's maybe a little a little theme parky.
If she gets silly from the pictures of this nonsense show, it seems like
the set is amazing.
Yeah, the sets are made like changes a lot, too.
I sent both of you guys a link.
We just had to talk about Babymine.
And if you want to talk covers of Babymine, there's nothing better.
And I hate to go to classic rock again, because I guess it's classic at this point.
But nothing is more terrifying than the image of this man singing Babymine,
I think holding his own son on stage.
I don't have it yet.
Jason, you have it.
Professional wrestling promoter Billy Corrigan.
He's doing a baby of mine at the Wells Fargo Center of Philadelphia.
And he's wearing a circus like circus ringmaster jacket.
He's got black makeup on his eyes.
He's holding a baby.
And then he sings Babymine.
I mean, it's so sinister.
Jimmy Chamberlain playing the mandolin.
I do like classified smashing pumpkins as classic rock, because Billy Corrigan
is what, 88 years old?
Well, you got to like throw the Foo Fighters and Smashing Pumpkins at this point,
because it's like 25 years at least at this point.
It is classic rock.
The Pearl Jam, I've heard Pearl Jam and like classic rock stations at this point.
Yeah, sadly.
So the song resonates beyond that.
You could you could pull out of it, but otherwise, maybe we want to bail on
the majority. I want to bail on the majority.
Dumbo. Yeah, I kind of forgot that there was such a clown element to it, too.
I'm never happy about that.
I forgot that that's why Dumbo has the hat, right?
It's that it's initially part of a clown costume as they make him perform
terribly dangerous stunts, diving off a building on fire.
Geez. Yeah.
And then you've got the horrible element of Dumbo also where the
clowns are apparently because at one point the clowns say,
hey, we got to go threaten to strike.
Let's go get a raise from the boss or else we're going to strike.
And apparently that was Disney himself taking a jab and striking animators.
Had to get it in.
A specific clown who there is a silhouette of is a specific animator.
I don't know who. I can tell you who.
Oh, is it the guy who animated Goofy?
Like he was he was one of the big union leaders, I believe,
and was always butting heads with him.
Oh, OK. Hmm.
What a fool. Yeah.
Didn't he got his?
Dumbo. Yeah.
Really stuck it to that little guy.
Literal clown. Great job, Walt.
This the movie itself, I realize now holds like it's in the same spot
of my eye to follow that bird is because of a similar the similar
things that happen to the characters.
Sad makeup trapped in pages.
Yeah, it's like a movie that's all the sad bird, the blue bird part.
Mm hmm. Yeah.
So yeah, Dumbo was not in heavy rotation, but Pan was as a child.
Mm hmm. Sure. I loved Pan as a kid.
I think now that I think the issue with all of these, I think,
I was OK with them being around when I was a kid
because there weren't that many movies.
That is true. More movies.
We don't need to do these anymore.
I'm starting this. I got a kid.
He's not going to see any of these.
Well, not Disney. Not going on.
Could you do you should really show your own Disney?
Like, what do they call the collection from the vault?
Like the diamond?
What are they are they calling it anything anymore?
They used to call the diamond collection, but you have to pair it down
to what you like in the diamond collection.
So you should say this is out. This is in.
This is out and see how many last seem how many are left. Sure.
Well, I don't know if it's mainly if it's got a the primary thing,
if it has a little boy who wants to be a little boy forever
and my little boy doesn't get to see it.
I don't want you learning this perversity.
Well, so what about I mean, it seems like in the boss baby sequel,
he's an adult who has to return to being a baby again.
That's what the trailers have led me to believe.
The only boss baby content I've really consumed, by the way,
is Jane got me the boss baby cameo for Christmas
where the boss baby wishes you a holiday,
where it's like woosh.
It's like the birthday boy sketch woosh, where it's like a video.
I would like to put down the rules for the Scott Diamond
Disney collection that you can put boss baby into it,
even though it's not a Disney movie.
You can add movies to Disney's diamond collection, despite them not being.
They are. OK, OK. I could still pull them into it.
Yeah, because you're the one who's on it going through this.
Now with the child where you are going to see these movies and decide
so you can get to curate your own. Yeah.
I think I'm more less concerned with what's in the vault
and more concerned with the vault itself and making sure that it's unopenable.
OK, it is that you have to get retina scanned and provide a drop of blood.
Like there's got to be so many layers to make sure that you never see.
You're describing a nuclear waste site where like they put up those signs
that are meant to last a thousand years that say like,
this is not a place of honor.
This is do not go here.
What if it's like a movie day and it's like you didn't catch
when that they were going to show a Peter Pan Disney?
Are you going to like picket the school afterward?
Yeah, I think I think I'm throwing a fit as if they were like whatever
whatever people do that is reacting to whatever they think critical race theory is.
Right. That's what I I don't want critical pan theory taught in schools.
OK, this is my biggest issue as a parent.
You'll be at a school board meetings
like crying your eyes out like don't show the children pan.
You know what it does to them like little green unitards
destroy little brains.
Boys shouldn't be lost like shouldn't be lost.
Chicago mayor Lori Lightfoot, you will be going.
We will not relent on this,
which is great when you find yourself saying to teachers, we will not relent.
You're the good guy.
You're definitely the hero of the story.
Yeah, always. Yeah.
Yeah. Famously villainous teachers. Yeah.
The man overpaid. Yeah.
They've always have been.
OK, yeah, look, it's all out.
These are these are out.
But what what Dumbo did succeed in doing, I think, like
I think in the history of of the animation studio, it is
it was a success for its budget.
It didn't have the issues that Fantasia had in the band.
I think Pinocchio, like budget overruns it.
It worked. And I think set up Disney for success,
even though then after Dumbo, they made all this weird like war compilation
movies that were not exactly cruising in terms of like quality movies.
Yes. But interesting fact about Dumbo, six weeks later, Pearl Harbor is bombed.
That is the timeline.
Like I you know, in the way the history just gets so condensed.
It didn't occur to me that like, oh, I was supposed to go see Dumbo today,
but I'm waiting here with the president has to say about
the Japanese attack on the Pearl Harbor base.
Well, pulled off of the time cover.
That's the fact about that.
The Dumbo is supposed to be on the cover of time and then there
and then Pearl Harbor happened and Wow, replaced by General MacArthur.
Wow, wow, wow. Mm hmm. Yeah.
What a time.
I guess I guess history can't be worse
and weirder than it is now.
So, yeah, well, anyway, point is big popular character.
When they start conceiving Disneyland, we have to have big popular characters
front and center. And and this is a big one.
So it's not an opening day attraction because although well,
now I've seen several things about this.
It is credited as opening a month later,
August 1955, because
there were issues with the elephants being too heavy.
Yeah. Construction issues.
I saw that too.
At all the other parks, it is an opening day attraction at Disney World,
Tokyo Disneyland, Euro Disneyland, Hong Kong Disneyland and Shanghai.
Yeah. Disneyland.
Yeah. Always like a big major opening day thing.
I think it was supposed to be for Disneyland.
I read a little bit of stuff that if you watch the opening day special
and I went and checked on this when when the kids are all running
and almost injuring themselves and everyone around them
to get to the Fantasyland rides in that special, apparently Dumbo's in it.
There was a Dumbo, one of the most terrifying original costumes.
Like a freak of nature.
If you look at that black and white photo, Dumbo apparently runs up
like into the direction of the Dumbo ride, but the camera stopped short.
They don't show it yet because they were still having trouble.
Now, I've also seen that they did attempt to run it on opening day
and that it resulted in the ride stopping really quickly
and people having to be rescued with ladders.
Step ladders come out and it was just a rough month
until the thing could actually get going.
Some of the issue of what happened here.
And I never knew this till doing all research that the ears were supposed to flap.
Yes, that's a weird thing.
And apparently for a decade or so before they did a switch out,
the ears still were on a little swivel point.
Like it was like if they had figured it out and gotten the mechanism working,
the ears could be flapping.
But then around the mid 60s, they said, screw it, that's never happening.
And then they just replaced him with unflappable ears.
Right. And there was no time when it would like the ears were like twitching
oddly or anything or like they weren't flapping.
They were just it seemed like something was wrong with them.
I got a thing. I mean, Dumbo, it's funny because I feel like every generation.
It's it's so iconic.
It's kind of glued in every generation, but it's changed so many times.
It's moved locations.
They've changed the mechanisms.
They've painted the elephants like they've done all of these changes.
They've doubled it.
Yeah, there's a lot of different things.
Probably a lot of changes, you know, considering the simplicity of it.
So once they they got rid of the mechanism that made the ears flap,
which took the vehicles down from 800 to 700 pounds.
So that was a little easier to get them up in the air.
Still a little dicey, apparently the beginning.
And still there was a problem that lasted for the first
couple of years of running it.
This is from the Disney History Institute.
That goes into that company, Aero, that built a lot of those early rides.
Yeah, this was an issue that they had when starting to run this thing
on the advice of a NASA engineer.
The Aero team used a combination of oil and nitrogen
in the hydraulic system for this ride for added power.
When they asked Ed Morgan, one of the owners of Aero, about this process,
he explained that oil and nitrogen combined
helped the ride run and gave it the power that it needed.
But it also created a weird foam, like a foam would bubble up
from the center of the ride or under the elephants.
I'm not exactly sure where the foam anyway, it would run.
And in front of guests, there would be a weird foam.
And so just again, there's a photo you can look up, I think, of this guy,
one of these classic, you know, Fred Mertz kind of guys.
Short, short, short. All right.
Eddie had to go remove the foam many times per day,
sometimes as often as between every ride cycle.
Dumbo's down.
Got to go take this weird foam at this nature.
Wipe the foam off of this elephant.
And the Aero people called this process milking Dumbo.
That was just part of the reality of Dumbo.
As you had to milk.
So so it seems like that would suggest it's on his undercarriage somewhere.
Yeah, possibly. Yeah.
If it's him, which is very nice.
I mean, if it's not at that center point, if it's somewhere in the like,
if every single Dumbo is sprouting weird foam
and does the foam ever because the rides up in the air and it's with spray,
it ever. Yeah. Is it ever like a Dumbo foam party going on?
Yeah. Oh, that's fun.
If it was out of his trunk, it would be awesome.
Oh, sure. Yeah.
That would have been a happy accident.
And they would have just I mean, of that going, is the foam
toxic? Yes. But right.
Yeah. The idea of it is oil.
All the parents standing around, if they're not riding, just smoking cigarettes.
Hell, some probably smoking cigarettes on the ride.
It's just like foam, just like little mini fireworks
is placed from airborne foam, catching fire from like long lucky strikes.
Long Virginia.
Bill. Yeah.
Cruella DeVille. Penguin style.
Hunter Thompson kind of cigarette holders just causing fires.
So, yeah, I mean, obviously coming out of the trunk.
That's that would be good.
Obviously anywhere else, probably a little a little weird.
My mouth. Dumbo's rabid.
Not good. Yeah. Yeah.
Dumbo's shitting foam. Not good.
Just confusing.
Yeah. Upsetting that anything's coming out of his butt.
But also what makes you foam at the butt?
Not something that you want to happen to you.
Some sort of new
some new disease from something that'll happen in a few years, I think.
Probably. That's well, Delta Cron, unfortunately, the combo.
It makes you foam out of your. Yeah.
But home out of your ass. Yeah.
That's otherwise fine.
You can see you actually don't have to social distance anymore.
You just might have to apologize for all the foam coming.
Excuse me. Have to excuse myself to the bathroom.
I'm extra. I'm foamy today.
It's a little foamy.
I'm going to go milk myself.
The weirdest fact about the early days of Dumbo I saw was that
because, you know, there's that kind of Disney rule that like,
well, you can't have five Mickey's or 10 Mickey's in one room.
Like there's one Mickey.
Hmm. But the origin.
So that idea applied to the original Dumbo.
There's only one one Dumbo.
So it was going to be elephants like everyone would ride in.
You know, now 16 was 10.
And we're painted pink like the hallucination
elephants from Dumbo's drunken revelry.
Yeah, yeah.
And because there's many pink elephants.
Yeah. In the pink elephants on parade sequence, so that they had to justify that.
There's again, when these they're making up these rules.
So you have these rides where Snow White can't be in the Snow White ride
because you're Snow White.
All these things that nobody they had to learn that nobody's thinking about them.
Yeah. And they're thinking too hard. Right.
But it makes it an extremely different ride if you if it is part of the
the psychedelic sequence that, by the way, comes from
champagne mixed with water.
Yeah. Slightly champagney water causes Dumbo to trip
and the mouse to write.
Yeah. Both in on it.
Very much a gag of its time.
But like as a theme park ride that would last forever,
like they're like we are essentially like we're condoning like kids
and get a little older.
You're going to see the pink elephants, you know.
The pink elephants are more fun than like Pleasure Island.
The pink elephant. Yeah, they are.
Yeah, they are more fun.
But that I think I'd probably mention on the Pinocchio episode
that hide it all DD and actors like for me, I think that is actually what
well thought of act like you're frivolous.
Well, except for your for Russell's implicit and that
the special six. Yeah.
The special six.
They were their own team. Yeah. Yeah.
Fred McMurray. Right.
He was in one of them.
Harvey Korman. No fool.
The rest fools. Yeah. Yeah.
Mm hmm.
The ride was even going to be called 10 10 pink elephants on parade.
That was the actual title.
And I didn't know that they were so committed to this that in the lead up
to Disneyland opening, I actually didn't know any of this before
that they were starting to do the promotional blitz, making people aware.
It's funny just that there was ever a time now they'll promote a new ride.
But it's funny that at one point they had to promote Disneyland entirely.
Hey, everyone, Disneyland is coming. Yeah.
And there was a Thanksgiving parade in Detroit, Michigan.
And then the Rose Parade in Pasadena in in January
1955, that both of these parades had floats involving
pink elephants spinning around.
That was and that was the only ride that they depicted.
So this was the main way they were putting their foot forward.
Come to Disneyland, where there is a spinning ride based on the pink elephants.
And then like a trailer that has a scene that then is not in the film.
Got there and there were no pink elephants.
It's almost like a curse.
Like I feel like when they were promoting Star Wars Galaxy's Edge,
they're like, we have a groundbreaking brand new ride, nothing like it.
And it's like, if you come out with that ride out front,
like that ride is getting delayed.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Just can't or all those, you know, any that the Harry Anderson special
where he promotes all of those things that the higher I don't think one of them
is just like the thing after thing after thing.
Yeah, I feel like Universal actually made these days have it right
where they just like start building and everyone like pretty much knows what it is.
But they don't even say it.
And then like six months before maybe or less, they go, oh, by the way,
it is that thing you thought it was.
Mm hmm. I mean, they keep doing that.
Velocicoaster and and Mario, they just sort of don't acknowledge.
Yeah, they they kind of I think it to Hollywood of a kind of acknowledged.
Yeah, there's a Mario now construction wall.
They're on the and it's like coming.
Yeah, but like for a year or something, it was like being built without confirmation.
This is what I do in my life to possibly a crazy degree.
I try to not. Oh, yeah. But anything.
It's like I told as few people as I could about the baby.
Well, yeah, sure. It happens. Sure.
No, yeah. You have to manage expectations for everything
because life is full of disappointment and pain.
Yeah. That's just the reality.
I do think Universal is I haven't watched it yet,
but there's that making a velocity coaster that they uploaded to Peacock.
Yeah. And it's like that is smart because I feel like Disney has scaled back
on those kinds of specials.
Oh, it's and throw it on.
You will really enjoy it.
It is like wonderfully flat.
I say this as a compliment that it is not.
I think Disney now would try to dress it up and do like sketches
and a bunch of crap you don't need and musical numbers.
It is just like, you know, just people talking.
And then we did that.
Mike Mario Lopez being inoffensive.
I yeah, that's great.
A lot of parks.
Universal did it with, I think, last coaster, maybe Hagrid's.
But I think it was Holiday World when we were talking about some of the Sally
Dark rides, more parks to have started on their YouTube channels,
like strapping a GoPro and a ride vehicle and recording the whole ride
and putting it up on their own YouTube channel.
And I'm like, oh, yeah, absolutely.
Do that, please. Yeah, yeah.
There's no reason to not like spoil.
Like, I guess I think the only rides you wouldn't want to spoil
is if there really is a thing at the end where you don't want to reveal
how it's done or there's anticipation on that first ride.
But if it's a, you know, if it's a roller coaster or especially roller
coaster, yeah, yeah.
Yeah. Spoilers don't necessarily factor.
Are you guys Mario Kart fresh? Are you fresh still?
I have not watched. I don't know.
I'm not seeing a single frame of video.
I've seen like a photo accidentally, but I have not watched the video.
I have a word I've seen the queue, seen that big Bowser.
But yeah, I don't really know.
And I imagine you can't capture it very well anyway.
Right. Given the goggles.
Yeah. But this is, I think, a big thing about Dumbo and saying that they
figured out maybe with this ride more than any is
what you're saying about, let's just show the whole ride
and post a nice video of it.
I think the promotion abilities of
just like I think with Dumbo, they created something
Instagrammable before Instagram. Yeah.
You know what I mean? Like, it's probably the thing that people came back
from Disneyland with is a picture of me on the on.
It's me sitting in Dumbo or my kids sitting in Dumbo or my friends
sitting in Dumbo. And then there's, you know, pictures of notable people
through the years on it.
I think like I feel like maybe Dumbo did a lot of heavy lifting for sure.
I mean, it's obviously and then there's some practical reasons for it
just because it's like it's easy to take a photo of somebody in the ride vehicle
when you're outside of it. That's part of it.
Yeah. Yes. Like you would maybe consider the teacups equally iconic,
a silly thing. You get to sit in a big teacup, right?
To sit in an elephant, but harder to take photos of.
Yes. You feel more rushed when you're getting on that thing,
like it's going to start moving. So I better strap in.
And then everyone can go on it. Yeah, everyone can go on it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And even your biggest scaredy cats
can go on it and not make it go up that high.
Yeah, yeah.
Let's talk about that aspect of it, because I don't know.
I don't know this if other rides of this nature, which, by the way,
like my temptation would be to call it a spinner ride.
Yes, there's some things similarly a spinner ride.
But apparently the term is aerial carousel.
Right. A term I will not ever use because it's clunky.
And I don't think even aerial carousel.
I what I want to throw out is the term is round and round.
It's a round and round. Oh, that's nice. Oh, that's cute.
Aerial carousel is strangely beautiful, but it feels like the aerial carousel.
Very elegant. It feels like too much.
Too beautiful. Too beautiful.
Yeah, like baby, baby.
I don't hear it all the time. It's a fragile phrase.
Yeah, we all got a little wistful just hearing those words.
Aerial carousel. Let's not do that to ourselves.
It's it's a round and round.
What was my point?
Oh, the the ability to control the vehicle.
I don't know if Disney did that first or if that was an ability
that other rides like this had already.
But I think that's key to its success.
The feeling that for a kid, especially, that they can control it.
They can do it to their liking.
And it's not an interactive ride to the degree that other things
have been interactive rides.
But it does. Yeah, it does guarantee that you can have a slightly
different experience every time you do it.
Yeah, I'm trying to remember.
I mean, it was a local park.
I'm trying to remember what the first one of what my first round
and around was.
But I definitely had the same element of controlling it.
And that, yeah, as a kid, especially, you're like, wow, like this
because you can't drive a car yet.
You know, there's a talk of Tony Baxter always has a transformational
experience of blah, blah, blah.
I made it look so stupid there.
That's not what I meant.
But like driving on the Autopia or something, but like controlling
a vehicle and movement is a big deal as a kid
because you see adults doing it.
So it always felt like I have such power now.
Yeah, like the power.
I was also scared of it and would often not go very high
because I was initially pretty freaked out by this and still kind of
a little unnerved going on it, to be honest.
OK. Oh, interesting. Yeah.
Oh, yeah. I guess.
Well, yeah, our relationship with it today is maybe a question.
Yeah. How often do you go on Dumbo?
Not very often. No, no.
Jason. Yeah.
A once in a blue moon.
Maybe every couple of years.
Every year.
I, of course, went all the way up like TJ Collett.
I went all the way up as a kid.
Like I wanted to be a high up.
You're the height.
And I also wanted to be the movement of going up and down.
I want to go high up and then I want to go back down and then up.
So I'm like.
I hate to completely derail you on this real quick, but I just had a thought
that something I thought of over our last few weeks.
If I have a bachelor party in Las Vegas,
will you jump off the stratosphere?
Oh, that's a good.
That's a good question.
I mean, I think we have to judge what the other activities will be.
You know, like what else are we doing?
You know, because we're going to have a big meal right beforehand.
I probably would.
But it's going to require some planning.
Yeah, yeah. But you're open to the idea of it.
I am open to the idea.
I'm not opposed to the idea.
OK, great.
That's all I have to figure out how many times we're going to watch.
I lost my M in Vegas, the 3D movie at the.
Yeah. M&M store.
When will you so like what?
Making sure that we slot, you know, minimum three viewings of that.
Right. Right. And if we have time to.
I know I didn't see it last time.
I was staying across the street and I considered it.
You have to see it frequently because to see how much it is faded.
Yeah. Dark. The projector is right.
If you if you only see it once every five years, it'll be so jarring
how much it has gotten dark and blurry.
Well, and down the block now, there's an actual thing.
There's the fly vague.
I forget what it's called.
There's a flying theater attraction.
Like a soaring. Yeah, like a story.
Oh, I'm like a different shows in there now, like in between a target
underneath an olive garden.
Next to weird. Yeah.
It's the block where it's like, well, the bottom floor of this is a Marshalls
and the top floor of this is a hard rock cafe.
Like it. Yeah.
I kind of love it. Little.
Yeah, it's very confusing, but I kind of love it.
OK. Well, good. Thank you for confirming that.
So it depends. You got to carve it out, though.
Yeah, that's fine.
Obviously, like that would be the highlight of the thing.
If Jason jumped off the stratosphere.
Well, but it's your thing.
Like, I mean, you're doing that for me.
That's what I want. Yeah.
Yeah. Nothing would make Mike happier.
Yeah. You doing this.
I would need to get trial contacts as I want to be able to have crystal clear
vision for it.
So you have a writer, huh?
You have a writer for.
Well, I'm just talking about the prep.
I had to do.
You know, I don't think either way you'll be up there and wind is just flapping
like crazy or like visions going to be tough.
No matter if you think it's I don't want to take time.
I want to talk you out of it.
Yeah, I don't know.
I mean, I would definitely pay the upcharge for the like
we're going to strap a camera to you. Wow.
And so you get the video.
Oh, we need that for them.
We need that. 100.
Can we do a live show at the top?
Maybe it's not for the bachelor party.
Maybe it's like a live show at the top of the stratosphere.
And then the end of it is you jump off.
There's all see.
I think you're you're getting hat on a hat territory.
Yeah, I think I would need I would need time to prepare.
There is, though, is a hat on a hat.
It is true. Right on top of a hat like shape.
There's also all those rides up there.
That's true. Yeah. Yeah.
OK. Well, we'll talk about it. Yeah.
But you were a kid who who cranked the thing up as a child.
Oh, yeah. And there was also like multiple
like knockoffs at the Jersey. Sure.
Either elephants or spaceships or whatever.
And so, like, yeah, I think I was maybe and maybe continue to be a
up and down, like probably primary.
I make my round and round and up and down.
I I don't think I want to just go straight to the top and stay there.
I think like the back and forth is fun, but maybe you don't go all the way down.
It takes a little bit.
And it's 90 seconds.
The only every every second counts.
So I don't want to waste time all the way on the bottom.
And then you got to consider I think Dumbo is pretty smooth.
But other rides of this nature, you could get kind of stuck.
Like if the mechanism is great, like on the weird Elmo one, I went to.
Oh, yeah. Sea World.
If it's not that responsive,
maybe you do just want to stay all the way up at the top.
Yeah, there would be.
That's that's interesting because they do have memory.
And I don't know where it's from again of like where you would try to push it up
and it would take about five seconds for it to respond.
And then that would like really throw me as far as because like if I got too scared,
then it would take a couple of seconds to come down.
And that felt like the longest ride possible.
A big problem I think I have and even when I say I'm a nerves by now,
I'm not like that unnerved by it, but it's on an angle.
And there's still part of me.
And maybe it's because I'm kind of tall.
That makes me feel like since it's on an angle, a little bump because it's bumpy.
It's not the most smooth ride still.
Like I feel like I could fly out of it a little bit.
There's still a feeling of being a little prone, like a little bit.
You know, there's a seatbelt on it.
But especially when you're up the highest, you're kind of tilted toward the ground.
So if you're on the inside of Dumbo, it's like I'm leaning.
You can feel your like gravity taking your body a little bit.
So that's the only reason I say sometimes I feel a little bit unnerved being in it.
And maybe that's why I don't go on it all the time.
Also, I don't. It's mostly for children. Sure.
There are incidents of like, you know, the arms cracking or like stuff cry.
Everyone just kind of scrapes and bruises and, you know, checked out
and then went about their business.
You know, well, but that not with the new that's like that's why they replaced it
entirely. Yeah.
Is that there were two incidents in a short amount of time.
So it was I think the same one from 55 to 83 when they redid all of Fantasyland,
then same one from 83 to 89.
And then there was an accident and then another accident in 90,
which was the arm snap and clean off.
Yeah. That's an accident you don't really come back from. Right.
And so they figured maybe we need to have a new Dumbo entirely.
And in a very rare circumstance, I can't imagine when this would ever happen again.
They had a spare. They literally.
They had a beautiful, more innate spare. A better one.
A better one built for Euro Disney.
But that was going way ahead of time.
Way ahead of time. Yeah. Yeah.
They were so early on that.
So it was just sitting around.
So they just patched in this new Dumbo and made a second one for Euro.
Yeah. And they water water features have been added over the years.
For a long time, the Magic Kingdom did not have the water,
you know, fountains didn't have the water effects
because the utility doors were underneath so they couldn't run pipes.
And then when they moved Dumbo in the early 2010s,
they were able to match it to all the others.
They had that part of moving.
It was to be in a spot where you could have water.
I well, I think and of course, they duplicated it in Florida.
Yeah. So Florida, there's a little more to do.
They'll say this just before getting to the Florida one.
I think some of what stops me from going on
the Disneyland version is very long line without a lot going on.
Now they put some shade in.
It's a little better than it was, but still it's like a great thing
to do with no line, which is why the last time I did it was in horrible rain.
When the park was clearing out at night, it was ended up being awful.
I got so soaked, so soaked waiting for it.
And then it's building up water inside.
It was pretty crazy. I wouldn't recommend it.
But it's one of those I kind of only do with no with no.
Yes, that's yes.
Though I'm trying to think the last thing the last time we went on was
midnight, walked by it.
Hey, yeah, that's a good.
That's how you do it.
That's like that Dumbo as a childless adult.
You go on Dumbo when you walk by and you go, hey, no line.
Yeah, that's like the only time you do it.
Yeah, because you know what it is.
You're not going to nothing about this experience is going to surprise you.
Yeah. And then you can get upwards of half an hour.
Wait on this thing.
I would be way more depending on the day. Right.
So that's the big obstacle for me getting on it and probably for other people,
which is why in Florida, they've re thought how lines work.
Like, was this the first example of a virtual queue or at least one
that the first one is?
Yeah, modern day Disney virtual queue.
Well, this this was in 2012.
It opened as part of their, you know, fantasy land redo.
So right around the time of the rise of like interactive queues,
which only lasted a few years before they're like, all right,
then everyone's got a phone to distract, put stuff on their phones.
I was down there in the summer of 2012 and didn't fully know what they had done.
I knew they moved it and doubled it.
But then, like, was very impressed and shocked by like the play area
and the the Chili's beeper. Oh, yeah.
Which is what it is.
A the actual thing is a it's like a ticket.
And like you've been invited to see Dumbo's performance.
He's about to go on.
And it is a ticket.
Am I correct that Timothy the Mouse talks to you
well from the beeper or is it just a beep?
I think it just vibrates when you're like like when your table's ready.
I think it's a video where it's like maybe they have not kept this up.
But where I think that they're I think the intent was that there's a little
Timothy. Oh, maybe they don't.
Maybe they just they bought excess from the Cheesecake Factory.
Yeah. My my memory that it vibrates.
But there was an announcement.
So there's this big and this is where I was referring to.
Like the circus stuff comes into play because there was a massive indoor play area
and there was an announcement there in a video I watched where he's like,
Hello, Circus Performers.
And it's like, wait, we're performers now.
OK, OK. The children are.
This is the idea. OK.
Like you're not necessarily you if you're crawling around in the in the nets,
if you're going up and doing little aerial tricks, I think that is meant to be.
Well, so you're like the parents are the are like along the wall,
maybe having a sit.
But the kids are the acrobats, I think is the notion.
Wow. That's now I say this.
Had I watched a video about it, you went there in person and their subtext
was maybe not conveyed, which is a frequent issue.
I think it was like 1030 at night and it was reasonably empty.
So I was just kind of like, oh, this is smart.
Kids love play areas.
And watching the video back, I was like, are there kids who are just like,
I don't really care about riding the ride again.
I just want to go back to that play area and climb around.
Yeah, probably. Probably. Yeah.
It seems like a good one.
There's that building on fire, which I don't like in the context
of it's going to hurt Dumbo.
Yeah, but I like it in the context of a thing for kids to do.
There's clown firefighters.
Uh huh. There's Dumbo spinning around the ceiling, flying around the ceiling.
Yeah, it seems nice.
It seems like they did a good job without like a mega budget, I bet.
And and the idea like creating a little experience that you get to have.
That's fun and fills up the time instead of you're just doing back and forth
and back and forth and seeing nothing. Yeah.
And then there's two Dumbo. I think that's pretty cool.
Why would there only need to be one?
I feel like if there were not an issue of space in Disneyland or all of them,
you know, they should do it in all of them.
It's it's trying to. Yeah.
And they successfully did it in other because they have room in Disney World
to do it out here.
They've changed the queue recently to make it a little nicer.
There's no room to do something major with it. Right.
They demolish all of Mickey's Toontown Fair.
That's where a lot of this is on top of now.
Right. Yes. Right. Right. In Florida. Yes.
But yeah, there's not a lot of room unless they were to move Dumbo to like Toontown.
But that's a construction war zone right now. Yeah.
Which probably doesn't make sense to do it either.
But I guess they were trying.
They probably I'm trying to think like they all the other like iconic Disney rides,
I guess, other than teacups, have a lot more themed of a line
of a themed experience feeling like you're walking through it versus,
yeah, what you're saying, Dumbo is just like switch back,
switch back and can be very long. Yeah.
And sucks a little of the magic out of it, probably waiting.
Well, Alice is like that, too.
But a very satisfying ride at the end. Yeah, that's true.
Yeah, that's true.
Yeah. Oh, yeah. You got nothing there.
The other ones that you at least have a little indoor.
You get to write, like, you know, peaks of the dungeon.
You go in their little house kind of first before.
Yeah, that kind of keeps you in it. Motivated.
Yeah, right. You need to be motivated.
Al is probably one of the best classic Disney movies.
Holds up as a movie.
Beautiful. Yeah.
I have no problem with that.
Yeah. We did the episode.
I was like, oh, I loved Alice in Wonderland as a kid.
Like, I completely forgot how much I liked it or loved it.
I think it's part of why you could maybe just bail on Dumbo entirely,
because I think there's better like psychedelic trippy animation
in Alice and Heffalumps and Woozles.
I will say I'm a big Heffalumps and Woozles fan.
What about like a Disney movie that sort of retcons out the original version?
So it was like Dumbo teams up with Peter Pan teams up.
Like any of the movies you don't like, you take the character out
and you combine them into like a team up movie where it's just fun.
As I said, I like Dumbo.
So, yeah, I mean, Dumbo, like I think, look, Peter Pan needs a wardrobe change.
OK, fine. He needs to happen.
He needs an attitude change.
What do you dress Peter Pan up in this version, this hypothetical version?
What's he wearing?
Just a suit. OK, all right.
He can wear that's my problem with Hook is that I think he had it right to begin with.
He shouldn't have missed his kids baseball games and everything,
but he was dressed appropriately for his age.
I don't want to see Robin in the in the unitard.
Y'all in banger rank.
I think he he he should have combined aspects of his adult life
with his former free spirit.
So, yeah, dress Peter Pan should be dressed like banning.
Oh, you got your wish, but it's one of those suits they wear in Hawaii
where the pants are very short, where it's a little shorts.
Goes with a blazer, a blue blazer compromise.
You have to. Yeah, you got it.
That's a good compromise.
I guess I can manage that.
I have to see it on paper.
But like Magnapie's friend, who was always wearing the suits, I feel like.
I like that. Yes. Yeah.
Why? Why am I more like I'm more OK with it on a 70 year old man than on a child?
Well, as on this podcast, we're more comfortable with anything on a 70 year old man.
Yeah, that's just the more comfortable when talking about 70. Yes.
I where were we besides the most expendables?
I don't I don't want to just be cynical for the sake of being cynical,
but I was like racking my brain of like, why didn't they do more
cues like this for like kids rides and stuff where it's like
you wait in a play area and they call you when it's your turn.
And I was like come up with was like, well, it was probably a little expensive.
And then also they couldn't figure out a way to monetize it.
You know, they couldn't scale it to like, what can we add on to this?
You know, like the answer obviously is to do what restaurants do
and have the buzzers feature ads for local real estate agents.
The way things are going at Disney right now, I wouldn't
put it in some lady in a blazer with houses and Lama Rada.
They they've they've been cutting some corners on things.
A little bit. Yeah.
If old Bobby can get a couple more dollars space here.
Yeah. Now, there's something I knew about none of this.
I don't know if you guys did it all.
This what has happened where there's the it's called the Storybook Circus area.
Yes. The new that the little Dumbo zone in Florida now.
There was talk in the mid 70s
of a Dumbo specific area
that was the plan of Tony Baxter.
Do you guys know about this?
I think we maybe I don't say to keep going.
Dumbo's Circus land was was the notion here.
And as part of his, the whole big reroute that he wanted to do with Discovery Bay,
he I'm trying to think of the he basically like
Tony was so up on all of the expansion pads.
I feel like he, you know, he wanted to do stuff in what became Galaxy's Edge.
And that's that's what Discovery Bay would have been.
And he also was trying to do this little Dumbo area
in what became Videopolis and then Fantasyland Theater and a little bit of Toontown.
Basically, the idea here was that
Fantasyland is where the cartoon characters live, the classic cartoons.
But shouldn't those mostly be regal?
Doesn't it make the most sense when that space is devoted to
princesses and King Arthur and all that?
So what if we separate the Fantasyland ideas
and kind of all the random characters who don't make sense in in a kingdom?
Now they just, you know, now they've just said fuck all with all that.
And Winnie the Pooh is just in Fantasyland Magic Kingdom.
That doesn't match at all.
But Tony, with his wanting to make everything themed, of course,
he was going to build this little area, kind of.
It's as I said, like Videopolis, small world.
And it would have been a circus where so they would have moved Dumbo.
That's part of it. Right. And then a what was the ride called?
I'm looking at Circus Disney.
Is the name of it.
And it would have been a ride where all kind of all of the characters,
they aren't using are part of the circus.
So suddenly like Baloo, Baloo is not really anywhere in the parks, particularly.
So he's in this all the bears bongo, all these things that we don't really
they aren't trying to service bongo.
So this is like Toontown before Toontown, essentially.
All the whimsical Toon characters are in one spot hanging out.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And yeah. And to that end, another thing would have been a Mickey attraction
that would have been black and white and the vibe of the old slapstick
mayhem kind of silent peony,
like a ride that is taking you into the early Mickey movies.
And that would have been a wild mouse in the dark, save for clips of the old movies.
So it's like a crazy hijinks, you know,
like the little stunts that Mickey's doing in the early days,
but where you wouldn't have known where any drop is coming.
Right. All of Space Mountain called Mickey's madhouse.
Whoa. Yeah, that's pretty good.
It is good. They've essentially done this with the Joker.
We've come across in terms of Batman rides.
The Joker, a person who makes sense to have a madhouse or be stuck in one.
Right, though.
I mean, I had to change the name of that, I think, at this point.
But it's a fun sounding thing.
Yeah, no, it sounds yeah, it sounds like it.
And that also sounds like kind of like Runaway Railway.
It's like all this stuff is sort of precursor ideas.
They ended up with like now there is a circus tent thing.
It's just not this full circus ride.
But that notion of separating the circus and having a circus zone, they did
a crazy early Mickey vibe attraction.
They did. One thing they didn't do, though, they were basically like.
So he Tony also wanted a way to
you could walk around the corner and get to that area, or
he wanted there to be a way to the ties together Discovery Bay
with its inventors and Jules Verne and all that with the circus area.
So he wanted to do something called Professor Professor Marvel's Balloon Descent.
And this was a little hotter balloon ride.
That's a ride in and of itself.
But it's also like a second skyway, basically, that takes you up over a hill
and gets you into this circus zone.
But Professor Marvel is a Wizard of Oz thing.
One of these Tony, you know, I feel like he was pushing for something Oz related.
And then there's the James Franco movie.
And maybe this is the chance. And there's still no Oz.
Anyway, there's like this kind of famous photo of Tony working on the model
of Discovery Bay, you might recognize this picture.
And where his hands are and what he's working on is this.
I just don't know how I missed this for so long, but there you see balloons
and you see a new location of Dumbo and Circus Tent.
It's a little modest zone.
And I miss this. This picture looks familiar.
But yeah, I didn't realize that's what this is.
There's also I'm looking at it.
It says there was an unnamed Pinocchio attraction,
which was a predecessor during Journey that would have included
Stromboli's Theater in the Queue, where guests could watch puppet
performances while waiting to board.
And who doesn't love that?
Yes. Yes. Malicious puppet performances where there's a vibe.
There's something something off about this.
Why does this puppet theater smell?
Why do I hear people screaming in the back?
Mm hmm. Tony said they were pumping in secondhand smoke the whole time, too.
That was going to make it more authentic to the film.
But yeah, there's a lot of these interesting photos here. Mm hmm.
They all look very cool.
I am I am imagining modern day
height of summer holiday crowds trying to navigate some of these pathways.
Oh, you wanted to think about the scale of some of these. Yeah. Yeah.
It wouldn't have been an easy way to do it.
But as a kid, I would always feel you'd always get an extra thrill
when you would see a character that was newer or more.
Yeah, I guess just newer or fresher from a movie immediately.
So it would be nice to have something and not that this would be it.
But like Circus Disney or something where you're like,
all the characters are here that aren't in other rides,
because I want to see all of them.
And that's what Marvel that's what you got to give Marvel
credit for for their land is because like they got like weird
like Loki comes out like a day after the show premieres.
Loki in multiple outfits, multiple outfits, multiple versions of Loki,
the one in the jumpsuit, the regular one.
Yeah. Like as a kid, that would be so thrilling.
Shang-Chi, the Eternals Hawkeye, like everyone.
Yes, it seems like that's so so just having a spot in Disney
to like park people without rides would like still they still need to kind of do
that, obviously, like walk around characters is the easiest way.
But sure. A ride, a permanent ride.
Do you like if Robin Hood was in the park, we want to see Robin Hood.
Yeah, you know, we did.
Robin would have he would have ended up in this.
Yes, exactly. Yeah.
Oh, yeah, we we met Robin Hood in the whole gang back in the Big Thunder Ranch area.
But they're not these brag.
Well, have you ever seen Robin Hood?
It's very exciting.
Yeah, I don't send.
And you had a Hawkeye.
You had, oh, yeah, a Target shirt on David Hawkeye.
Yes, logo years before the years before it inspired the show.
The comic and they were doing like gags of like shooting out like
like Target, we're going to shoot an arrow and that was confused at their bit
because they were like pointing at like Robin was going to shoot me.
And I was like, oh, wait, what?
And then he like grabbed me and like was positioning me.
And I was like, what is he talking?
And I went, oh, I have a target on my shirt.
Yeah. Oh, very hot.
When you were wearing, I forgot what I was wearing.
And yes, we all do.
So Robin Hood was going to shoot you.
He's going to kill me. Yeah.
Robin Hood was threatening to kill me.
And I loved it.
But I can't send him out.
Yeah, I guess that's true.
The arrow people.
So, yeah, that's that's a cool.
Never. Yeah, that.
Yeah, I never knew about that zone.
I would love to see like all the artwork that exists.
If that area was around, it might be feel a little out of date now.
Or maybe they would have done something to it.
But I like we look at those balloons.
It would have felt so 70s.
It would have felt like 70s knots, which is a compliment to me.
There's a vibe to 70s knots.
That is what it's attractive.
I think at Disneyland specifically, it would have been changed already,
I'm guessing, to not have that vibe.
Yeah. Disney World, who all bets are off.
But Disneyland, I think, would have been changed.
I love you said Tony Baxter is always up on the plots of land.
And he still obviously was when we interviewed him two years ago.
Implied all these zones.
And was was he implying the weird stuff they're thinking about now?
That's what I have every parcel of land.
Yeah. Parking lot.
Did we talk about that already?
Probably we did. But we might have made that connection.
There's the expansion loose plans that we don't even know what the status of that.
Well, I got to know Disneyland forward.
I signed up for every possible email, like update on it.
That anyone could do.
But they were like mainly eyeing like Anaheim residents.
And there was like update on Disneyland forward.
We have an exciting presentation.
I was like, oh, yeah, here we go.
And it was just that we're going to do a digital screening of the first episode
of a show we call the Imagineering story.
And I'm like, are you kidding me?
Like you just like log into this like
zoom or this live chat to watch the first episode of a show
that you have on your streaming service and probably upload it to YouTube
for free or something like what?
What is this?
They all Anaheim hasn't voted out real quick.
The Disneyland forward thing is they put out this big like hypothetical map
of a major expansion of both Disneyland and California venture.
But basically, they were just putting it together to tell Anaheim,
just give us blanket approval to make whatever we want on the land we own.
So it can be a hotel, it can be a ride, it can be whatever we want.
Yeah, like they they own the land.
They can kind of do whatever they want, but they need to get the zoning tweaked.
Yes, exactly, because they don't have necessarily this parts
next to the hotel aren't zoned for a theme park yet.
So they just want to sign off on all of it.
But they haven't even voted on that, right?
I don't think so.
And it also like those were real blue sky plan because like it's a little insane
where it's like, OK, so it were both parks would now wrap around the Disneyland hotel.
There'd be bridges going over the roads.
And like here there was little doodles if you squint like,
it's like, is that Avatar? Is that Wakanda?
Yeah, I love it. Rides everywhere.
I love it, too. Using Mishmash.
Why is that hotel sticking out of the middle of the theme park?
Yeah, so it's certainly
for it's new.
I've never considered like this, but it's also like, OK.
Are you saying you don't think it's going to happen?
Well, no, it's going to happen in some form.
But if they build, if they did everything in that concept art, it's like,
this is the most densely.
Well, didn't they say it was like, we'll complete all this by like 2050 or something.
Wasn't it like some crazy long timeline?
It was probably like at least a 10 or 20 year plan, because there was also like,
we're going to build Disney Springs on top of parking lot.
Right. And we really we got very excited.
The idea of Gideon's being built. Oh, sure.
Yeah. Jock Lindsay's and yeah, everything.
So now you're you're excited about possibly a bakery
that along line closer to where you live, but still still a big drive
where then you go and wait in a two hour line.
That's right. Perhaps longer.
Thrilled in like 18 years at like at least.
When I'm in my late 60s, I I'm going to be so excited to wait in a line.
It's what I what I will be at a point where they're like,
you really should not be eating these cookies.
Your body does not agree with this.
Mr. Sheridan, you cannot go to this Gideon's one more time.
Your doctor Gideon's will kill you.
Your doctor is calling you over and over again.
I know where you are. I heard about where you are.
There's a surveillance thing now.
We're doctors. Yeah, someone.
Someone is scanning the line daily now.
There's like a like a futuristic helicopter trying to get Jason to
like doctor has sent like a retrieval helicopter to get him from
to get him from the Gideon's line.
Jason has our laser gun shooting at it.
It's the far future, folks.
So far future shooting at the doctor's helicopter.
Now you have to get you get deployed as in a Seinfeld esque manner.
Kramer can't go to the.
Oh, right, right. The grocery store anymore.
Well, right, because they're not.
Yeah. So it's like in the future, you have to have a certain like
blood glucose level or like blood pressure to be able to purchase cookies.
That's how the future is.
So Jason's is off the charts.
Mine is still a little more manageable at the time.
That's the future. Michelle Obama wants.
Exactly. I will not eat your healthy snacks.
And don't you teach my kids that. Right.
So so I have to go purchase them.
Now, generally, the future they monitor you eating.
You have to when you purchase it, it makes it like ties it to your social
security number and then the sort of implants you have in your stomach.
It registers to make sure that's the food you're eating.
But Jason, I have to figure some way out.
I have to like regurgitate the cookie into his mouth.
Taking a very blade runner.
William Gibson has this is a cyber universe.
Cyber to our future.
This is when Disney is completed their Disneyland forward.
So Mike's 300 page graphic novel, Gideon's 2062,
that ends with me throwing up some cookies into Jason's mouth
in her older age.
Yeah, it's like beautiful.
It is like people are reading the graphic novel thing.
Like, I don't know where this is going, but the artwork is so good.
This could be the next dune.
This looks fantastic.
And then they get to the last page and it's
this about two older men
exchanging ground up.
Look, this is the this is what Joe Rogan is a warning is against.
That's all I'm saying.
This is what he's daily warning.
Yeah. Cookie regurgitation scenario.
Anything anything left?
I have just a little like I think maybe one one thing to mention about Dumbo is the
as we talked about, we did an episode about the Skyway a while back and
the Skyway buckets being among the most desirable auction.
I guess. Yeah.
And probably maybe maybe number one again could be,
you know, could be neck and neck with Mad Tea Party having a teacup.
But I don't know. Probably is Dumbo.
I would think the one that you'd most want to own.
I think so.
Yeah. So thirty thousand dollars mentioned for.
I mean, a long time ago.
Yeah. This long time ago.
I looked up the the most recent that I'm aware of.
Big public sale of a of a Dumbo, which is that the that's from Disneyland
Gallery, where we did a show with with old Richard Kraft, who we know.
Richard Kraft, I think in the early 90s,
before his agent career had taken off.
So he did not have the money to do this.
He had to like he was at an auction knowing what his cap was.
It went way past the cap.
Bought it. Bought a Dumbo for thirty five thousand dollars.
Kept going higher and higher and higher with a bidder on a phone
who was rumored to possibly be Michael Jackson.
Kraft stuck it out. He got it.
Years later, does the gallery in the abandoned sports authority
sets the price at 150 K, ends up going for four hundred and eighty three K.
Geez, we from a thirty five thousand dollar
lord, and that is one item that was sold at that.
Do we know who bought it?
I don't think we don't know.
No, no, no. Tree buyer Michael Jackson from beyond the grave.
Maybe it was Michael Jackson.
Yeah, he celebrated by doing the thriller dance.
We do know that John Stamos owns one.
The other major Disney collector.
There's this was this is I think also from the those specials
that they were doing. Yeah.
Well, in early Zoom years, years.
I think that's correct.
Yes. Early in early early pandemic Zoom years.
So big celebrities would make a point, I think, of like,
let me choose the most plain room in my house to do this thing
and pretend that I'm a normal human being.
John Stamos is on a Disney special.
He's like, I'm going to show the elephant.
I got to show up.
An elephant. And if you had an elephant, why wouldn't you?
Yeah, I wonder how much could you get like like a Nick Offerman
to build that for you or something like maybe not even a non-sola.
Like how much could you actually just have somebody fabricate one?
Hmm. Ten grand fiberglass.
Yeah, I don't know. That's a tough thing.
Twenty grand. I think.
Yeah, maybe that's too tough. Pretty specialized.
But then don't it isn't some of the appeal that, oh, of course, that money.
Well, then it was they like this was in the park.
Yeah, for sure it is.
I'm just saying, like, if you wanted to at least have the vibe.
Yeah, maybe. Yeah.
You could still get it for a normal crazy amount of money,
not an insane, crazy amount of money.
Mm hmm. You're a fiberglass artisan.
Yeah. Big scale.
Let us know if you do giant fiberglass sculpture.
How many fiberglass artisans are there in the audience?
Because maybe they're so are there podcasts for you?
Are there podcasts that are all about sculpting fiberglass?
Oh, there's got to be. There are.
That's interesting.
That's a piece of an interesting thing, because we've talked about,
like, what piece we would want to own from the parks.
But if the option was just have somebody build one for us,
that would be a hell of a lot cheaper.
And it's like if you could have somebody build you an original Rex.
Yeah. Like that would cost one 20th of the.
I guess I don't need to know that it was actually from the park. Yeah.
But it'd have to be so good, though.
Right. I think I worry you'd be able to tell it's got to be just perfectly.
Yeah. I mean, we met on the end.
The last that 80s night, Lindsay and I went to, we got to take a photo
up close with Rex. Mm hmm.
Very exciting. Bragging again.
Yeah. So sorry.
Sometimes I have to drop the names.
I have a couple of things as we wrap up.
The one big historical anecdote I kept saying about this ride
was that Harry Truman, when visiting the park, refused to ride this ride
as the elephant is a symbol of the Republican Party.
He was a Democrat, took a stand, would not ride the elephant ride,
dropped two atomic bombs on Japan, but he took a stand on this one.
That could sully his whole legacy.
Could as well as a legacy of the man who bombed
in a horrific way.
There was also the Disney Parks blog, which used to update a lot more
in the 2010s, had like an anniversary post about Dumbo.
And I just saw this very funny comments on it.
Dumbo ride is certainly a favorite.
We are Disneyland regulars.
After 15, about 15 years ago, my then three year old nephew
was so excited to choose his Dumbo that he didn't see another child
run into him accidentally bumping him into the water of the ride.
Fortunately, a good Samaritan jumped the fence.
And fished Martin out by his collar.
Thanks go out to that man and everyone else who saved the day.
Every time we pass the Dumbo ride now, we recall how nice everyone was that day.
Oh, now a couple of things going on there.
One, that's about a foot of water under that ride.
And two, man, if you're going to hop the fence, get in the water.
Why are you fishing them out like a stray cat?
Where are you picking them up with the collar?
Yeah, you can grab them.
Just grabbing the kid like, come here.
You like grab them by the scruff.
I'm going fishing.
Yeah. Wow.
I've never seen anything like that happen.
No, that's that's pretty that's pretty dramatic.
Did I say on the podcast that I saw a kid lose a tooth on the Incredicoaster?
I don't think so. This is very dramatic.
I was there solo a couple of months ago and I was in the single rider lines.
I was on like the other side and not where you normally load from.
But so I'm watching people get off and there is a kid just like screaming
bloody murder and and like clearly bleeding from the mouth.
It was really like, what happened here?
Oh, my God. And then it turned out it was a tooth miss.
And watching a dad go and scramble and like, stop, stop.
And like they wouldn't let them let the train go because like,
we have to find the tooth.
Wait, OK. So you were waiting to launch.
I wasn't on the ride yet.
OK, I was. Yeah, I was waiting to be called up to go on the elevator and and go around.
And I'm watching this very dramatic situation.
Oh, wow. I watched the mother be called.
It's like, oh, no.
It was like, boy, there was a height for five minutes.
This is one of the craziest.
They're the only thing I've ever seen.
You know, that's there are little plays that happen all during the day,
especially when you're an older gentleman going alone.
Mm hmm. Nothing to do but watch when you don't have to watch your own.
I did almost the exact same solo Disney Day
last year back when things were a little better, where I think I went to I went
to California Adventure.
I drank a beer. I went on a credit coaster.
I did some work on my computer and went back to the Marvel area.
Drank a beer as well, went to Guardians and went home.
Just shut it, chilled out and did a little work.
But I saw the craziest child crying
and their parents trying to force them to go on Tower of Terror,
the Guardians Tower. No.
And I've seen this happen a couple of times, but never this dramatic.
And what you're saying, like, this was just a scene.
And it was the same thing where you were like this.
What am I watching here?
This child is going to lose their mind.
And these parents are not allowing this child to get out of this.
And an employee had to come up and tell them like, you can just switch.
You can do a child switch, basically.
And they had to be talked into it.
They were and that was not they know we need you.
I couldn't believe this.
This child was melting down.
And as a child who didn't melt down, but wanted to, is it like,
you know, and melted down recently in a in a escape room situation.
I felt felt for the kid.
But like it happens a lot when you're especially with not with anyone
where you're just noticing like this something scary playing out basically.
This is crazy. Yeah.
Dairy. They should be taken away.
Disney should have taken the kid away.
Well, I felt like being like you should get as the property of the Disney company.
You want to get out here?
I'm not to live with me. I'm just saying I'll help.
I'll help with the situation because these parents are being assholes.
I also can't what I can't like, look, I'm I'm I'm new to this
and I'm new to tantrum.
Tantrum is very new for for my kid in the last month or so.
We're heading to the two year old point.
It's just they make it so unpleasant when they you're trying to get them
to do something that they don't want to do that.
So far, it has been like, oh, come on, you want to.
OK, I'd screw it here.
Give them the give them the thing.
Yeah, right. Take them out here.
I mean, we have about like it's a it's a one exchange.
We got about five seconds in us before we just relent.
Yeah, I it's hard for me to imagine you are going to go up.
You're getting in the tower that lightning is hitting.
That's full of ghosts and screams.
Yeah, it's like like or Pat Bennett hit me with your best shot.
It's going to play loudly. Yeah.
And try to write that.
Yeah, it's a less scary one, but that doesn't make it.
You're going to go up into this tower and appreciate some loud classic rock.
Yeah, well, it is now.
Look, I can get behind that logic, but
yeah, if it was like Pinocchio or something, OK, yes.
I go look, oh, the kid probably won't be so scared.
Maybe and you know, this is a kid who gets a little scared
and then like is OK on the ride.
That's a phenomenon.
But that was not the case with this child.
Yeah, this child was crying
at 100 from the time we got loaded into the numbers.
And I was like, no, what are we going to do?
Please. And like employees negotiating with the parents.
And maybe they didn't understand what they were talking about.
I don't know. But it was like and they had like two.
There were two parents. There were a couple of kids.
So it was like one of the parents cannot go on it.
I hate being I hate being that per like adult being like,
you don't need to go on this. You're an adult.
And then be like, well, what's your problem, pal?
Who are you with? I'm alone.
Yeah, just doing some work down here.
Yeah, it's a little hard to like pull a child screaming that much.
It's like, all right, let's do the halt method.
You know, are you hungry, angry, lonely or tired?
Which is it, pal?
You know, the kid could talk also.
It was not like a two year old.
No, but I mean, Scott, you can take some comfort in the fact
that they call it the terrific twos, right?
Oh, yeah. Oh, boy.
That's the universal term applied.
They call it. That's true.
Yeah, I can't wait. Yeah.
From recent implications, it'll be a terrific year.
Anything else before we go out?
I've got a little I've just got some photos of some
some dignitaries who've been on the trash.
But Mike, were you heading?
So I was just going to say, did it did it ever?
And I think it did a little bit bother me as a kid.
Did you ever think about it that you're inside the animal and on top of it?
Ah, hmm.
Yeah. So what happened here?
Was he like a big chunk was carved out of him?
Yeah, I'm not saying it was like, oh, I was so preoccupied with it as a kid.
I was not. But it was a little bit like, oh, we should be on top of Dumbo,
not inside Dumbo.
Well, the ride doesn't necessarily hold up under a narrative.
No. That might be true.
No. And I guess it should be like they should have built something on top of Dumbo
for you to sit in. But that would have made it a bit heavier.
So I understand why we're just like sitting in a hollowed out carcass of Dumbo.
Dumbo and his six his 15 brothers have all been strapped to poles
and scraped of their organs, but not their brains.
So they can still understand what's happening to them anyway.
Get inside him.
There's future technology that has condensed their entire body
into a tiny little ball, and it can be held in their neck now.
So Dumbo is alive. OK, because this is the future.
Everything he needs is packed into his.
Exactly. This is the future.
They've condensed it. And now he can still be happy.
He loves it. But he is connected to a big rod.
And you can sit inside where his organs used to be.
But he likes it. He loves it.
He's got a big smile on his face.
Don't you see? Yeah.
Now, and but depending on where you're going on this ride,
his mouse friend is holding a whip.
In some places, it's not a whip anymore.
It became a feather. But if there is a whip, don't worry.
The mouse is small and the whip is smaller.
So and their friend, their friend, he's probably not going to use it.
Yeah. It's just there as a reminder.
So not pleasurable.
It's, you know, you expect.
Yes, it's a symbol of like, oh, animals and circus.
It's not practical, though, but it needs to communicate something.
It's either it's soft or he'll use it softly.
I assume he just like drapes it and rubs it.
Don't worry about Dumbo and his clones.
Yes, it's the future and he's copping cloned.
This is a dark, dark ride.
It is a dark really, really quick.
Just I was like, this is going to be fun pictures of people you wouldn't expect.
Oh, right. Going on Dumbo.
Here's the the most most interesting ones I've found.
Here's here's old Kevin Costner.
And this is kind of where, you know, again, you're you're a sitting duck
when you're on that ride.
Others, the celebrities can sneak in and out of Disney rides.
But there people are going to see.
I mean, some of these are posed photos. Right.
But that's I also read that some of the appeal of I think Walt
talked to a carnival person, a guy who did a park called Kittyland.
That used to be where the the Beverly Center is now.
And his thing was the rides should
the rides should advertise themselves, you know, like you like.
If you if you have a ride where there's people on display
having a good time, that's going to make people want to go have a good time.
And so, again, just the photo op in the tableau, I think, is important with this ride.
So look, Costner's having a great time.
Christian Bale's having a good time.
I see him at Disneyland, right?
Like he's a cameo machine.
It's nice to see him out of it.
But was, you know, has been part of the Disney family before.
And Newsy, yes, indeed.
He's coming back. He's in the new Thor.
Oh, I didn't know that.
Tim Tebow was Tebow.
I had there's a Chicago mayor, Richard Daley.
What's the deal with Richard Daley?
Is he good? They're all like corrupt.
Oh, yeah, sure. Yeah.
It's a it's a mixed bag here in the early 80s.
Michael Jackson on the Dumbo attraction.
And then some 30 years later, Dr.
Conrad Murray, the man.
What?
Right. Ultimately involved in death.
Oh, I don't know.
I think this is this might have been it's credited to some.
This might have been a paparazzi situation.
I don't think that Conrad Murray proudly like
brought a private photographer.
Well, I think he was getting out his like last couple of jollies
because six months later, he was like, OK, so it's after the thing.
There was I think it was between trials going on.
He would he would be in jail within six months of this photograph.
That's really bizarre.
Isn't that a real that's a you know, time goes round and round.
I was wondering, like, which who does Scott have in here?
Because he's going to have a really good one that I don't know.
Is it like and that really I would like stars from Kevin?
I would start a Conrad Murray.
I would not have bet that.
Well, Kissinger and Ted Kaczynski in the same car.
Who would have thought the same element?
So look around you the next time you're on Dumbo.
You never know if you'll spot
one of the greatest pop stars of all time or a man who will be responsible for
the demise of one of the greatest pop stars.
She was one of the Dumbo.
Yeah. So hey, after on the note of Dr.
Conrad Murray, it's a weird photo to like, I don't know.
How can it not be a weird photo? Yeah.
What is a normal photograph of this doctor convicted of manslaughter?
Well, hey, on that note, you survived the first podcast, the ride of 2022.
More fun to come.
More criminally convicted doctors to come, probably.
That's what we're OK. Yeah.
More Conrad Murray talk, more Brian Setzer talk.
How can we get you salivating for what else is to come this year?
Yeah. Oh, I want to say that I bought a bought a package of hot dogs, Jason.
Nice. First time.
First time in other than when we tried to make the Ronto wraps.
I didn't buy hot dog. There was like a sausage.
But I just I thought of Jason.
I went, you know what?
This is my every couple of years I go.
I buy hot dogs as often as I go on Dumbo.
Wow. And I did buy.
They were like boars head.
Oh, they're in the hot dog game.
That's a name you get.
Yeah, they're in the hot dog game.
So I did do that.
Anything particularly inspire you?
It was one of those situations where I was hungry.
And for some reason, I was doing stuff I just don't normally do.
I don't normally buy ice cream.
I bought ice cream.
Maybe it's because of maybe the world.
I don't know what's affecting me exactly.
But I was like this big break we've had.
You're the big break. You're craving Jason.
That might be it. You're buying Jason's ice cream.
I got I got hot dogs.
Maybe I haven't.
Yeah, I haven't heard Jason talk in a while.
So that's it. Oh, I missed you, too.
I was I went back east to see family and immediately put on five pounds eating,
eating immediately.
Yeah. Like the first day of the holidays. Yeah.
Yeah. Jason missed Mike so much he bought 20 expensive Ninja Turtles and ate them.
There's your pounds right there.
It is I have been racking my brain for the last few days because they're Marvel has a deal right now
where they're unlimited per the Marvel Unlimited, where you get digital access to that shadow.
Can you figure you get a welcome kit?
And I was like, OK, it's marked down to 70 for the year subscription.
And you get this welcome kit.
Could I I did a very Mike math of like, if I get it, could I flip the welcome kit for 70 dollars?
You get this. The answer is yes, you can.
Probably. Yeah. Answers.
Yeah, probably. But it is a cool kiddie pride.
It is cool. But I have some complaints.
But we'll see.
Well, there is there's a more traditional kiddie pride from Excalibur toy that just came out that I do have.
Oh, I like that.
She's got the more blue outfit, not the kind of normal X-Men outfit.
Yeah. OK, if you want to stay up to speed on all of our probably less me, but in collective wheeze
purchases of Marvel figures and hot dogs, then follow us on the socials at podcast.
The ride merch is available on our T public store and for three bonus episodes every month.
Check out podcast, the ride, the second gate at Patreon dot com slash podcast.
The ride again, most pressing.
Go there now. Meet our new friend, Jay Bigga.
I really say if you were not on the second gate, I would hate to miss out.
Yeah, the audience. Yeah.
For five dollars a month, you can get three extra episodes and the whole back catalog.
I don't usually give the hard sell on it, but I would say that the audience seemed like
they really enjoyed the last patron episode with a big reveal at the end.
So if you ever thinking about trying it out, you can try it out and you get the new ones
and you get the old whole years, multi year worth back.
If the tease of a horny white rapper from 2004 does anything for you.
Yeah, just like my bow tie spun.
If you want to see my bow tie and our bow ties spin from content, explicit content,
please go there. And of course, Mike's extra detailed,
amazing quality graphic novel, Gideon's, when he 62
hitting bookshelves, lots to look forward to.
Yeah. See you in the future.
Goodbye. Bye.
Following us on Twitter and Instagram at Forever Dog Team and liking our page on Facebook.