Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the second gate, the show where, you know, this is a crazy weekend
time and place to be doing this intro. I mean, the three of us were all just accused on national
radio of being members of the Communist Party. It's been a week, but we're going to try,
you know, we're going to try to get through it because we're professionals. We have vision
and clarity about what we're doing in the entertainment industry. Damn it. I'm Scott
Gardner, joined by Mike Carlson.
Yeah, I'm here and it's my dad believed in work of rights. Okay. So just, I guess tell
them I marked the box. I tell them it was an accident. I forget exactly what happened.
There's not a one of us that wouldn't have passed 2021, like moral judgment tests in
1953. We're all on the up and up by any, any internet spectrum. That goes for Jason Sheridan
too.
Yeah. I mean, you know, I think we're going to be okay when the head of the FBI and or
company saves us because we're making too much money for the latter.
Yeah, I guess that is what it boils down to. Yes.
If okay, say, let's just say, okay, we're first of all, we real quick, we're talking
about the Lucy movie that Aaron Sorkin made, but okay, that's neither here nor there. This
is all references to that. But if we were in the fifties, we would be on radio. And
I just like, what would be the podcast to ride like radio show in 1950? Like there was
no talk radio really back then. So I guess we would be doing like high jink humor about
like Ferris wheels and stuff. What'd you think?
Like a little radio plays. Right. Having like sock boy, I guess that would have worked.
Yeah. Like set at a carnival. Are we carnies?
Well, I think we may be different characters every week. I'm just saying, we probably have
to be narrative. We probably wouldn't be able to talk about like Coney Island's newest attraction
or whatever.
So we're, so we're kind of a bumbling carnival workers. Yeah, probably narrative podcast
with kind of with a live orchestra.
Yep. The three doofuses.
Three doofuses. Yeah, they work at a carnival. They're like the three stooges, but not as
good. That's where we would have been a poor man's rip off of the three.
Yeah, but they're confined to working in a carnival. I assume there were many three
stooges shorts where they had were at a carnival. I'm not the biggest stooge had I know some
comedy fans are. But I assume they they fucked up something in a carnival once.
Yeah. And maybe, you know, the head of a network was like, we noticed you guys kind of move
your faces a little when you're talking about the midway and we got a TV station we're
starting up. We're looking for people who can move their faces a little.
And you and especially with Jason, they would be like, you are the perfect man to advertise
our cigarettes. And we would really like it if you were the face of sort of our new
initiative to get people smoking more. Yeah. So I don't know. I'm just imagining it.
I'm just thinking about it. I think we get our theme park info out via the little the little scene.
OK, that's good. Now, fellas, we got to take care of this here. Mr. Ferris's wheel.
This was only invented 35 years ago. And there's only three in these contiguous United States.
I want a stuffed stuffed bear for my gal. I think it's cute. What do you two think?
Is the stuffed bear cute? Very cute is what I would say. Very cute. Yeah.
It makes me want to throw my guts up into a brine jar.
Cute at all. As long as that bear is stuffed with asbestos, fully approved by the American
Asbestos Council. Our sponsor, our sponsor, American Asbestos Academy, apparently is what
they're called. A lot of the terminology would be fine. You know, I fell on my seat again.
Yeah, we already again, the way that we pass all of the litmus tests of any era, we would
get a lot of many of our episodes could be just aired on the radio in 1951. Exactly. Except for
the J Bigga one. Yeah. Yeah. Everything else. Until 2022. Yeah. Perfectly moral and on the
up and up. Yeah, this is an episode about being the Ricardo's the film that is on Amazon Prime,
if you wish to follow along with us. And which will start, you know, we can issue like the soft
spoiler warning, because this will be from the perspective of people who've seen the movie. But
also this is, you know, I mean, like, Lucy and Desi don't die in a train crash or something. Like
there's only so much how how spoilery do you have to be when it's sort of based on real events?
Yeah, sort of. I looked up one or two anecdotes that I was like, Am I remembering this right
about I love Lucy? And I got so many results of like actual publications and zerg net kind of like
listicle publications all saying the same like, and Ricky gave him three strikes. And if he hits
all these drugs, all Wikipedia information I said on our I love Lucy episode, and I feel like
Sorkin just looked through it and was like, Oh, yeah, yeah, he told William Frawley, he can't be
drunk on set. And he like, yeah, so it's like all that that's all sprinkled throughout. Yeah, that's
a just if you if you haven't seen this movie and don't intend on seeing this movie. I mean, that's
one big thing that struck me about it is that it's, you know, dramatic scenes lit dramatically,
but where it'll suddenly go into like, do you know what Desi has done for this show? Do you know that
he invented the multi camera system that allows us to shoot and not interrupt the viewing experience
for the studio audience? That's how much he cares. It really is just like, how can we leisurely drop
these little let's just like the three doofuses we want to get our info in there. Yeah, also like
all the hits from I love Lucy, like toss offline about vitamin A, Vegemin.
We're Lucy, the same week she was investigated by the House on American Activities Committee was
like, by the way, everyone, while we've got your ears, I'm having a baby. And Ricky's here to tell
you we're going to play it into that we're going to work it in the show. Yeah, of course, the same
week, it must have been the same week. And of course, stomping the grapes. You see Lucy, Lucy
does like the Seize the Matrix, Seize the Matrix Code, takes the Limitless Pill when she thinks
of a good idea for a bit. Yes, that's that's true. He's he's condensed like all the greatest hits
of Lucy in front of the camera and behind the camera into one movie one week, essentially.
It's not the like whole life story type by a pick. It's more like his Steve Jobs movie. Right. Like
yeah, condense a bunch of stuff into one, you know, hot, hot, hot boiled. We have like, I don't know
what term I'm trying to use. Hot, hot, hot boiled week is a boiler pressure. Right. What's the term?
Have you ever hot boiled anything? I guess that means boiling. Yeah, it has to be hot. So yeah,
yeah. What hot dogs say? I'm no wordsmith. Pressure cooker pressure. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Like when
you're getting hot boiled in a pressure getting hot boiled in a pressure cooker like the cast of
Isla Lucy and the writers. Yeah, this kid, you know, boy, this was a week. Yep. I'd say I remember
that week. No problem. Yeah, I read so much of that. Then there was there was here's this let's
issue the hard spoiler alert. There was no week. This didn't there's not this week. Yeah, no
happened. And I don't know why. I don't have a problem with this formula being used for place.
It's something about being like there. Like it's like there. It's it's you're there. You're present.
We've got real this is happening in real time. But in movies like yeah, I the week, the condensed
week in this movie, this very eventful week is is it's definitely a choice. And there it makes a
lot of choice. It probably makes too many choices. I guess that's what I'll say about the movie. Like
I let out the biggest groan when I heard like the synopsis was like the House on American Activities
Committee like that's not even that in it that much. No, it's not the bigger groan worthy thing
is the documentary interview framing device about the importance of television.
On top of it, there's so many hats on hats on hat. There's so much going on in this week. Yeah,
don't forget. It's all a documentary, but not all of it. Some of it, the beginning and the end are
a documentary. It's a documentary, but they're not. It's not real documentary. It's not a real
documentary. And the the the people in the documentary scenes seem so much more scripted
than the people in the other scenes that aren't supposed to be like it is. It's the stiffest.
Just yes. And I understand is what you have to understand is I'm assuming they're being
interviewed for one of the dozens of TV is important documentaries that CNN pumps out.
But it doesn't because you look at the people in there and this is what I really quick in case
anyone's listening to this and has no clue what the hell and why we're doing this. It's because
we did an episode about Lucy attribute. That was a long one. It was a controversial episode because
I got some facts wrong and I was taken to task by that last year on a patron episode called gripes.
And this is just a natural extension of all that because we love Lucy and we wanted to see
what they were doing as far as keeping the Lucy legacy alive. That's right. Yeah. Well,
and being that it's sort of a late shifty movie, you know, way a little bit like less recent events,
but you know, extremely dramatic tellings of comedy tales. I think it's something that appeals to us
and I love Lucy's been in the air. And frankly, when we heard that there was a two hour product
that was full of I love Lucy misinformation, we were like, Hey, that's our territory.
Yeah, I, man, the Sorkin, I think about half hour in, I was just like, God damn, this dude cannot
help himself. There's so many Sorkin that for one thing, I'll say the biggest thing. And I'm going
to give the maybe the first compliment of this movie so far. I like a lot of the actors in this
movie and I do like a number of the performances. Yeah. Yes. I agree with that. Yeah. I think that's
maybe something you could say about many Aaron Sorkin products that it's all elevated by that.
It's always great perform. Maybe not always, but usually very good performers. Yeah. It kind of
helps you see, I think it, it makes the, it like they're, they're all watchable probably for that
reason. Um, again, maybe not all watchable. I've never tried the newsroom. I feel like I probably
should. I feel like I might love the newsroom and I, and I, and love is in imagine a number of quotes
around love. Yes. Yeah. I mean, I, my dad and I, we would every week we'd watch the West Wing when
I was like in high school. I think the West Wing is probably the thing people look, look on most
fondly. It's unnerving when actual politicians reference the rest swing. And it's like, folks,
this is, this is Superman and Batman politics. This is make believe this is, this ain't real.
When this guy was writing the show, he was out of his mind on any number of drugs.
This and sports night sports night, a lot of great performers in that too. Sports night aimed a little
lower. I think it made it. Yeah. Like, yeah, cause I kind of like sports night too. And it was just
trying to be like a fun watchable. It was not like we're going to save democracy or going to
save the planet. Yeah. And we're going to make, make sure everyone knows the power of entertainment.
Right. Yes. But how much it can change minds and hearts. I think the importance of television,
probably the, maybe one of the least offensive surkinisms in this, the most glaring one is,
the men are all heroes and the women are heels. They make Desi, Javier Bardem is very good actor,
I think. And he's very charming as Desi, but very early on, I feel like they say Desi Arnaz is the
most charming man in Hollywood. And then on top of that, Mr. William Frawley, Fred Mertz himself
is the voice of reason. And Lucy and Ethel are very anxious and neurotic and complaining a lot
of the movie. I, that's a valid take. I will say that I saw another thing in it, which is kind of a,
I felt like I was being scolded by a big invisible finger throughout the movie as if like
and the scold, the, the, the, the message of the scold is now Lucy was the architect
of all of these sequences. Do you understand? Do you get that? And they would write these things,
but she was the one who made them better. And she would question the logic and she'd be right. And
she would redo the staging and she was a master of her art. Do you understand that? And the finger
is wagging so hard at me. And I'm like, no, I get it. I know I never look, I swear you can look at
you could read a transcript of everything I've ever said in my life. I've never said that Lucy
LePaul isn't a genius. Why are you so mad at me? It's all of you. You don't, you don't get it.
You don't give her the credit. And look, here's the writers. The female writer was the good writer
and her partner, the other male writer, he was a dope dweeb. He's the dope from white lotus.
You should see him and think dope. And you'd be right. Cause this writer,
I don't know. Am I crazy to feel, I felt like I was like the, this, this was being like, I was
being argued at and I'd never said anything to the argument.
Well, they definitely go back to that, that like plot point. She's like trying to perfect things.
And I definitely, it's like, it's definitely to prove, like to show you all Lucy was in
control here, but it's also like, I think to set up the last thing when she doesn't even go with
her idea at the end. Oh, sure. You know what I mean? So I, I, I agree with what you're saying
cause I definitely felt like we're doing this scene again. We're like, I go, yeah, we know
she was good at really good at what she was doing. Let's run it again. It's four in the
morning, but we're running it again. Damn it. Yeah. So I think both of you, your points are right.
Yeah. I mean, we were all being yelled at by this movie from various, from all perspectives.
Directions. Yeah. I mean, that's a big sorkinism though, that the hyper competent people,
best people are big pains in the asses and they-
Like, I wonder why.
The person writing the characters.
I wonder.
And I think that, and that is he, he's, he wrote so many men that way. I think that's his idea of
like, aha, and now a woman is hyper competent and look, look at this.
Yeah. I wonder what it is. Cause it's like, Lucy doesn't get it. I look, I wasn't there as much as
I wish I was on set with the whole cast. I wasn't there. So I don't know if Desi was just a fun,
loving philanderer and Lucy was just a giant nag the whole time. I assume not. I assume that like
anybody, they have their, everybody has their moments, but it does feel like, and I don't know
if it's, it's a combination of direction script and even performance, I guess, where, yeah, like
you only get like a fun vibe from Desi and kind of even Frawley, but not that much.
He's not, he's, he's like kind of a grumpy guy, but yeah, he is like the wise old Frawley that you go
to, which I'm like, is that, was it, was that right? Was that, I'm sure he had some insight
being an old showbiz veteran, but yeah, Desi is the only one who gets to seem seemingly have any
fun smiles during the making of this comedy show. Well, if you could, now we've, we've alluded to
this on the show before, but like, can the listener imagine, would you be shocked to learn that I am a
big studio 60 fan, love studio 60. So, and I don't know how you guys feel about it. If you've had the
pleasure, but I just, I think I enjoyed this movie on that level, like, oh, we're back here. Oh yeah.
We're back to the making of comedy, which is a miserable slog. It is worse than almost any job
on the planet you could do. Everyone is, everyone's giving each other the cold shoulder and glaring
and it's little like back and forth repartee and little like every conversation is a little
chess match until you get knocked off the board. So, so much misery. It sucks. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
My, my studio 60 story is that that was the, when it premiered, I was here in LA for college. I was
doing the semester in LA and are, I had like a Monday night class and I think it was entertainment
law and everyone in the communication school knew like, Oh, take that required class in LA.
Cause it's really easy in LA. And this was cartoonishly like he would let us out halfway
through the clay. He's like, all right, let's call it there. And especially the, the week studio 60
was premiering. He's like, I know we all want to go watch studio 60. And so we're all thinking about
it. Everyone in this room. I think I, I watched the first few weeks as it aired before I tapped
out. If you'll recall what was going on at the time, everyone's like, Oh, I feel so bad for Tina
Faye, her behind the scenes comedy sketch comedy is mid season and studio 60 is going to beat them
to the punch. And it's the West Wing guy. I mean, it's going to be a slam dunk. Yeah. No way. The
little scrappy comedy one wins the big dog, which is insane too. It was also because everyone was
trying to intern on that show. Cause we were down the street from the set. They built this massive
set for studio 60 at Warner brothers. Okay. And they did not take any interns. Uh, uh, they, yeah.
So you could have, Oh my God. So you could have walked the spiral staircase. You could have seen
the NFL style giant board that just counts down to when the show comes out here. He's office. Oh,
to be in, Oh, to see all the cards to wow. Crazy Christians. It's really up there.
The Holly hunter talk show. I am, I had never worked for, I was in college when I watched this.
I had never worked in any capacity in show business at all, but one episode in you went, Oh, this is
awful. Like I know this is wrong. How does he not know this is wrong? Has he never been,
I know this is wrong. Like I know how to, his show was like that. Maybe I guess, yeah, this was the
way, or at least it's what the West wing was in his head. Yeah. Which is, which would add up because
like, uh, Matt and Danny, the creators of this fake SNL, if you don't know what we're talking about on
this, on this dramatic show about a comedy show, they are, they are kind of like guru gods who
people just like try to bask in their presence for a minute and follow them down the hallway,
but then get called off to some regular person crap. But Matt and Danny, they're just spitting
wisdom. And, uh, and that's, I think that it probably is a window into like, this is what
he thought was happening while he was making the last one. Yeah, I'm, yeah, I'm, but Matt is half
of me and Danny is the other half. And this is what the head of the show would be like.
I'm going to make it more realistic by saying that it was two people. Yeah. People won't buy
that it was one. Of course it was one. There was only one. I did it all. Cause the one is written
out in the pilot. Cause he goes full network. Judd Hirsch goes full network. Oh yes, there was,
there was a Lorne initially to studio 60. Yes. And he, uh, he breaks under the pressure. Yeah.
He gives a speech cause I'll watch that speech every once in a while. And he says like,
there's a show on television where people compete to see who can be the most like Donald Trump.
You know, starting goes back and thinks about it. Yeah. Yeah. I called it. I called it. Also, uh,
probably seemingly didn't talk to his own cast. Cause if you'll recall some of the players,
Hughley coming off a very successful sitcom, the Seahawks, uh, uh, Nate Cordray coming off
of the daily show. Like these are different types of comedy that like, I'm sure they all, they have
stories, uh, Sarah Paulson. Oh, you thought like he was going to ask anyone like, Hey, was it like
the writer's room? What was going on? You know, like I think he's ever asked an actor. No,
I know. Well, someone's experience and perspective. Uh, no, well,
kind of, well, cause Sarah Paulson is who plays, uh, one of the leads, right? One of the stars.
Yeah. I believe it's based on Christian Shanaway. Yeah. Who's working. Dated. Yeah. Yeah. Um, yeah.
So the fully rounded view he has of an actress who he dated, who doesn't get to be around and say her
thoughts on the matter. Yeah. Um, that's also like, it's something we just thinking about the
Sorkin body work and it counts this too. He really captures the way that comedy is miserable to make
and flirting and relationships are mean and bitter and horrible. Like, you know, the way they
lay it back and forth between like a hundred percent lust and a hundred percent pure hatred.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yes. The way all of us, we all have significant others, listeners who have
significant as you all, it all began for all of us and all of you, I'm sure. But with like the most,
the most vicious verbal sparring that has ever happened to you in your life. And then all of a
sudden, like, are you as hot as I am right now? Yeah. And then you, and then you started, uh,
furiously kissing at work. Yeah. It's always how relationships begin. Like, they don't ever really
get friendlier. You stay mean the whole time. Also this, these are, uh, by the way, uh, perks
for when he writes tech weirdos because, uh, especially social network, which I think is a
great movie. Uh, and then the jobs one, I think it's a very particular take. Like I think it's
very particular choice, but, um, if you want to talk about the ego maniacs, we want to talk about
like insane relationships. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Absolutely. Yes. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
The better palette for maybe, or canvas rather for what he's his sensibilities. Yeah. You want
to hear a crazy quote that I found in an interview, which we can, there's maybe another applicable
quote about this movie, but, um, he was talking about, um, low expectations being maybe a benefit
to a project. And in this case it was in referencing that people were maybe skeptical of the trailer
and Nicole Kidman being Lucy, people were maybe not feeling, uh, initially. And so he was, they
were asking about, I think the Hollywood reporter was asking about, um, just, you know, what do you
feel about the reaction? And he said, I've found that you can really leverage low expectations.
I learned that with the social network, people assumed it was going to be a romantic comedy where
like Paul Rudd friends drew Barrymore and they fall in love. And I just thought, great, they're
not expecting what they're about to see. Who thought that? You don't go into a movie and think
that it's different stars and a different genre than it is who like, unless you like were on the
way to the theater and tripped and hurt your head and then you're like dizzy and maybe you catch a
glimpse of a Drew Barrymore poster and a Paul Rudd poster combined. Who on earth thought that's
what the social network is going to be? Also the social network, if I recall, had a very clear
tonal like a trailer, like a trailer that was very dark and very importantly featured that
three word phrase, a four word phrase directed by David Fincher. And I feel like that gives you
an idea of what you're going to see. Yeah, yeah, absolutely.
That's just a point. That is a little wild. I don't think we've all maybe landed
our, these strong sorkin feelings. This is what I was hoping we were all going to come in. Oh yeah.
But, well, he just seems so out of it anytime he says anything.
Yes. Like, yeah. Well, including, I mean, so here's why I found it. And we, this was mentioned briefly
on the show, but let me say the actual quote about this movie. So, but as word got out that
I was making this film, what I discovered is that there are people who are really passionate about
I Love Lucy. For me, it's nostalgic. I remember watching I Love Lucy reruns from when I was sick,
homesick from school. It's not a show that if we took a fresh look at today, we'd think was funny.
Wrong. Wrong, wrong, wrong. Yeah, of course. I mean, there's obviously, there's some like politics
to it or there's some, you know, gender roles or stuff that they even bring up in the movie,
but it's like slapstick vaudeville shit. It's people falling over. I think generations pass.
That's probably the only thing from era in a way that people pass down and yeah, it's, uh,
uninsidious. Doesn't that just reveal that like, yeah, for me, it was just like, I don't know,
like watching a commercial for a soup can. I was staring at the TV and then that'd be on. And then
I Love Lucy was on. I don't care. So then I started doing my research and I saw people care
about this show. Huh? Why would you do the project? I'm not sure. What universe would you
do the pro like, why would you make spend? That's a lot of time to spend something. You don't.
For some of you think does not hold up at all. Yeah. It's not even, uh, I think it is definitive.
It's not a show that if we took a fresh look at today, you mean what you're doing, a fresh look,
what thing you're doing is going to not show that the show is funny. You know, it's all serious
movie about somebody like, yes, beautiful minding how comedy works and that like, like, you know,
Lucy goes into some like forbidden zone. She has her or the dead zone or whatever she has, like
she's, it goes into a trance state and then comes out of it and goes, uh, Fred, you need to be in
a chair in this. He goes, all right, right. Again, loose. Uh, I, I'll give it a credit. Uh, again,
I'll give say something else positive. So the, the kitchen or not the kitchen, the dining room
scene, this is kind of a running thread. They're trying to get the gags right in this dining room
scene. Um, when they, they're, so they do it on set at like 2 AM Lucy summons all the actors and
walks them through it at 2 AM. Um, that did to a certain extent rang true to me having been involved
with directing live comedy and like putting up producing live comedy for a number of years,
that sort of like walking around and you're just kind of like everyone's muttering to themselves
and like, what if you go there? The big thing was missing was everyone going, I'm sorry. Uh,
Hey, I'm so sorry. I'm sorry. This is taking so long. I'm sorry. I'm being a massive pain in the
ass. Like the constant apologizing is not in this movie. Just really appreciate you. Yeah, thanks,
man. I really appreciate it. I know we just need that one joke and then we're done.
Yeah. Do you think, I mean, I don't know, was Lucy not an apologizer? I mean, she does apologize
once in this movie and that says she doesn't be this maybe the first time she's done it
to the Tony Hale character. Yeah, that's true. Well, I mean, even if, well, I mean, she was the very,
one of the most famous people in America, maybe one of the most powerful people in America.
I could see her and Desi maybe not being apologizers, but the fact that those writers
aren't constantly like downing themselves and apologizing.
Well, they're all maybe with all those, the whole, that whole writing team is all just,
uh, Sorkin's split into like five or how many, four, how many writers? Three. Three. Is it only
three? Three in a writer's assistant. I think you're right. That's another good carry over from
Studio 60, a almost non-existent writing staff. I don't know why he insists on this, that all
shows are written by a couple. Yeah. Uh, so you think this is a quibi show? Shows have budgets
usually. Yeah. Besides PB. I mean, if it was like six PBC show, but they're doing like 24
seasons, like written by 23 people. Yeah. This is insane. Yeah. So he hates I Love Lucy. He
sees no value in it whatsoever anymore. Hates two of the writers. All right. The Alia Shotcat
character comes off very well. Yes. But the other way he does, he does not have good feelings about
Jess Oppenheimer. Yes. Really underlined. He's not the funniest guy in the, and when he kind of has
an edict, he's like wrong or, uh, Lucy and Desi have to go shut up. No, we're, we're taking over
even though let's go into some factual inaccuracies among the, the myriad of things adding to the, uh,
what was my phrase? The, the fat burner, the oil cooker, um, that's the correct phrase.
What I said, yeah. The many things in their hot boiler, uh, um, uh, is that, uh, Lucy is,
is pregnant with her second child. The first time this happened on the show, they covered it up.
They don't want to do that again. They want to incorporate it into the show and they demand,
they start saying, we are going to address this. This is, I mean, they, this had not happened
on a major TV show before somebody getting pregnant in real life and addressing it.
So there was a lot of need to dance around the subject and are people ready for that. And of
course they were, and that's all an extremely popular story. Um, but in the movie it's portrayed
as if they were the only ones who believed in it. Especially this, the Tony kale guy, Oppenheimer
was like over my dead, but no, they'll never go for it. Yeah. Apparently the real story is he
immediately was like, yeah, great. Let's do it. Yeah. So like, what is the need to make it for
else? Some people have to be naysayers and unpleasant in order to, yeah, it's like,
I'm trying to think there's, there's definitely a good reason example that doesn't do this of,
of a movie or TV show, but it's like one of those where you're like,
making TV is like, it's a job and it's not like soaring epic music 24 seven of an important
moment that happens. I understand he's like packed all what he thinks are important things
and is extra dramatize them. But like sometimes it's interesting to see everybody like sitting
around goofing around and like making jokes, like how a TV show would be made in real life,
unless it was some insane kind of production. Oh, sure. Yeah. So like he, he, he needs everything
to be conflict. He needs everything to feel like it's a, the most epic moments at all times.
Yeah. I mean, and to that point, when Lucy starts telling the cast and crew that she's pregnant,
everyone seems pissed. Like, like, like the writers are all like, fuck man. Like,
and eventually they have to go like, sorry, sorry. That was weird. I, I, congratulations,
I guess. Like what, what are you talking about? Like also probably that was probably enough. Like
if you want to play up the actual historical, the, the HUAC thing is so intense. I feel like
the, we're going to do that. We're having a baby and we're going to show it on TV. Like,
isn't that enough of like a drive, a dramatic device for a movie, like a 90 minute biopic?
Well, but you know that, I mean, for sure I was watching this and to Mike's question, why are you
making this if you don't like the show? And the answer obviously is this communist scare
house in American activity. That's completely why. And like I was thinking it while watching it,
obviously, like this is, this is such sorkin porn. This is exactly what he loves the most. And then
the same interview or the article says like, yeah, one of the things that captured his attention is
the fact that Lucy O'Balla had been accused of being a communist. Like, of course that's where
canceling in that one. Oh, there's a little bit of cancel stuff. Yeah. Lucy was going to be
canceled and I did go, Oh, okay. Got it. He was like, Lucy was going to be canceled. So I'm going
to use the Lucy movie. I don't know what to say that like we shouldn't cancel Joss Whedon. I don't
know what he, who he wants not canceled. I'm not sure. I'm just saying like that's, that is
definitely his hook. Yeah. But I think like that it can be that it's about like, you know, good
versus evil and witch hunts and the power of entertainment to overturn evil politics. This is
just right. Salivates over. Yeah. But he's, I, but I think, I think it is more about canceling,
like celebrities for stuff versus actual politics this time around. I could be wrong. That's an
interesting. I did write that down about an hour in of like, is, is he talking about culture? But
then also they're talking about how dangerous the house, not American activities, like accusations
are this movie is aggressively anti-communist. Yeah, no, that's what I'm saying. So like if it's,
if Lucy's the hero of the piece and she's still like, they, they don't make her a full like evil
character, but why would Sorkin want to do it? Do a movie like this unless, cause he is a politics
are very centrist Democrat pie in the sky. Definitely seems like the guy who spent the last like five
or six years talking about like the respectable Republicans must have, there must be compromise
on them for them to behave in such a way. That is true. He's definitely probably like P tape guy.
Now we all wanted the P tape to be real. We all wanted to be P tape guys. Yeah. We wanted to be
that. Well, J big as a P guy where P tape guys for sure. Um, but he was definitely like Mr. Muller,
he had a Mueller calendar probably. And like took 365, took the days off of him and was like,
and this will this be the day Mr. Mueller? He was like planning a Mueller by a pick with like the
most like, you know, like upstanding trust where it's going to be like Josh Brolin or somebody has
like, you know, and he's like a, like the young gun Mueller, uh, you know, on the rise to eventually
like bring down a presidency. And then once like Mueller actually talked and kind of sounded
not cool and didn't do anything to help anybody. And then he's like, Oh no. All right. So I'll
crumple up my information Mueller biopic. So America's finest hero, hero of our times, the
Mueller story. Did he, uh, did he insert some more anti-communist lines into the movie after that
week last summer where everyone's like, we gotta help Cuba. And it's like, Oh, well that lasted
three days and we never heard anything about it again. It was very organic and normal and not at
all suspicious. But I, I, all to my point is I feel he's like, he's less interested in completely
going hard against communism and all that stuff in this movie. And he's more interested in the
witch hunt aspect. And when I saw cancel in the article, he said Lucy being canceled. Then I said,
ah, I think I know why he actually wants to do this movie is because of what he feels are, I
don't know, famous people being canceled or Tim Allen says something dumb and 40 people subtweet
him or on Twitter. I don't know. I don't know exactly what it is, but that's my guess. I don't
know for sure. Yeah. And then at the same time, he makes a hero out of the American weirdo media
who probably canceled the most actual people. Oh, Edgar Hoover. Sure. Yeah. Yeah. Um, let's talk
about this. So this ending, this ending. Yeah, this is something. So that just to explain this
at the beginning of the film, uh, of course, at the moment when Lucy and Desi are madly making love
off camera so that we have not yet revealed that the actors don't really look like them so much,
like how long can we get into this movie without this show or radio for a while? And then maybe
you'll like be so ready to see somebody in this movie that you won't mind that they don't look
that way. Yeah. Um, but then on the radio, it said that, uh, it's been dug up that Lucy said she was
a member of the communist party and, uh, and this has to be like undone throughout the movie, like
the, I'm still not even clear on where this lands, that she checked the wrong box or it was
for her grandfather. It's unclear in the movie kind of even still like he doesn't even go that
hard on Lucy explaining. So yeah, uh, Desi adamant against it though. Like you can't say any fleet
communism and you, you know, we can't be sick because this is like, uh, this is like getting
canceled back then. Exactly. This is what imagine a pre-cancellation time. This is what would get
you there. And as they say many times in the movie, this would be the death for the show.
People are like saying goodbye to each other. Essentially. Like Lucy said, like if this doesn't
pan out correctly, she sort of says goodbye to, uh, Fred and Ethel. Like it has been a pleasure
doing business with you, sirs. Um, but anyway, it all culminates like we have to undo this. And even
though she'd been cleared by the committee, this is not true. She's not currently a member of the
communist party. There was still, it was going to come up in the media. There's going to be a big
store with red. They got the red ink out to say Lucy's a red. And, uh, uh, so we, we got to use
this bomb just like her hair. Yes. Uh, um, it's a Ricky or he said a thing in real life. I think
that is not in the movie. He said something in real life. Yeah. Yeah. He said, he said the only
thing right about Lucy's or hair, I think was the line he said in real life. Doesn't say this in the
movie though. Not in the movie. That seems so ready to go. I was, yeah. Cause I was looking at
stuff while I'm watching the movie and I go, okay, he's going to say this in the end. And then no,
that's not. Yeah. Um, anyway, uh, so it is this witch hunt going on and they have to defuse the
bomb. How do we do it? Well, during the pre show warmup where Desi Arnaz would usually play Babalu
and get the crowd hyped as we all would be watching Babalu. Uh, instead he's got to address the
serious matter and say that this isn't true and get ahead of the story. And he ultimately does it
by putting a phone up to his microphone at a live studio audience to say, now was this,
do you test, do you swear that Lucy was, uh, has been cleared of all wrongdoing?
Yes, that is true. And now can I ask your name, sir? This I, my name is Jay Edgar Hoover,
head of the FBI. And it's really now, you know, of course scoff and everything, but it does
really show the lengths that, uh, that Desi would go to to protect Lucy and to protect the show.
And it's a very stirring climax, uh, uh, you know, after all the pressure of the film.
And I, it's, I think it's a really cool moment and it's only undone. I'd say a little bit by the
fact that it's bullshit. This did not happen. Then he did not get on the phone. This is like
the entire, the climax of the movie is a totally made up thing. And just immediately, this is the,
the, the benefit of getting to watch movies at home and not in the theater. You can just immediately
like, wait a minute. Like that, I don't know. You can, there's dramatic license. And then there's
Jay Edgar Hoover called the audience bullshit Santa Claus came down the chimney and said, hello,
uh, Lucy is not a communist. She's been nice this year. Not an anti-communist.
Oh, yeah.
Also that is ending number one of three because that's okay. Big dramatic conclusion, big happy
ending. That's, that's how you want to, you know, uh, wrap it up. No, right after this Lucy confronts
Ricky backstage, which she's been doing every 10 minutes in the movie about a news story of him
running around on her and running around and having an affair. And, um, you know, he brushed
it off of like, they use the wrong picture. That was from a charity thing. We were there together
and I was buying, I was like, oh, this is nothing, but he is doing that again, an Aaron Sorkin thing
where a character will obsess about a thing. And then at the very end of the episode or the movie,
they'll go like, okay, you're right. All right, fine. Here's the truth. Like that, that is a
Sorkin ism and that happens in this movie because she catches him with a different, with like a
handkerchief with lipstick on it was hers. And then she found another handkerchief with other
lipstick on it. And his defense is like, they were just called girls. They were just hookers. I don't
know. And it's like, I looked into that the hooker stuff. All true. Yeah, that's true.
Scotty Bowers, if we know Scotty, do you know what I'm talking about? No Scotty Bowers is a guy who
like worked at a, like a Phillips station. And he basically was a male prostitute slash pimp.
So he had sex with like Spencer Tracy according to this book, by the way, this is in his book.
This character is another Ryan Murphy is in the Ryan Murphy thing. What's it called?
Hollywood. I think it's just called Hollywood. Yeah, whatever that that was. So he has like all
these stories of very famous people and him procuring prostitutes for them. Oh, okay.
Desi being one of them. And he said, Desi would tip very well, which is nice. And Lucy said,
one time Lucy saw Scotty at a party and came in and slapped him and said, like, don't you pimp
women for Desi or something? Wow. Wow. So yeah, that stuff. Yeah, good tipper invented the three
camera system. Yeah, Desi tips his prostitutes well. You should know that about him. There's
something that's related to Scotty that I kind of have to say. I'm so sorry about this, but
there's just something that I'm going to have to say. Well, I'm going to have to say a word
and I apologize if anyone has young children around here. I'm going to have to say some dirty
stuff here. The second gate episode of completely there in Sorkin complaints. Yeah. Great entertainment.
It's about Spencer Tracy. Okay. So I'm just going to read these two paragraphs. And again,
I really apologize, but there's some terminology in here that I just have to read out loud.
Scotty Bowers said that Spencer Tracy, like many male celebrities of the 40s and 50s, used to pay
him for sex. As Bowers remembers it, he would go over to Tracy's house and Tracy would start
drowning himself for hours in scotch. Then Bowers would collapse into bed with the actor and the two
would fool around. Sometimes Tracy got so trashed that he would get up in the middle of the night
and urinate in the closet. A couple times, Bowers said he pee peed on me thinking it was the bathroom.
That's part of it. That's how drunk you fool around. I'm scandalized already. Okay. So now here
is a worse word here. Okay. Tracy had other vices too. He would not suck your cock. Bowers says during
a colorful interview at a Santa Monica hotel, he would chew your cock. That's not nice. It would
hurt. So I, again, I apologize for the language, but that is a crazy way. That is a crazy sentence
I read earlier and I had to say it out loud to make other people hear it because I'm just imagining
the, uh, the Mickey's trailer, the corn on the cob with the typewriter. A long way.
Look, Spencer Trace. I don't know. I apologize to the estate of Spencer Tracy.
Chew. Chew is so. He called that Adam's rib. That's a great old movie joke, folks.
For any, any greatest generation members out there. Yeah. So I, uh, chewing your, is that just a virtue?
He's, he's so confused and closeted. He's and drunk. He's like, is this what you do? I don't,
you do when you're gay. I have no, I can't even begin to do a psychological assessment
in this situation. I just thought the, what you'd say, you say, um, uh, yeah, that's what I said. I
didn't say ouch. It was, uh, I said, that's good. It was such an awful, so much me more with your
teeth. It was such an awful sentence. I had to make other people hear it. I'm so sorry.
Cause sometimes you read something like that and you just like, I have others and must know the
sentence exists. The listeners need to bear this burden for you and all of us. Wow. That's incredible.
So that whole, I, by the way, by the way, this is going to be shocking. I have this book in the
apartment and I have not read it. Jeez. When it has that. Cause I took it from my mother.
Oh, my dad, you know, she's read it. She has read it. My dad bought it. My dad bought it for him.
She's like, what is this? And then she read it cover to cover. Uh, yeah, it's like a Hollywood
Babylon kind of like gossipy. Yeah. Yeah. It's just like, you know, he's talking about getting
hookers for Katherine Hepburn and stuff. So sure. But your mom read those words. Yeah, that's true.
That's true. Try to like, whoop. No, no, no. Didn't see that. Next page, please. Yeah. Yeah.
Probably. So, uh, that book exists. That gentleman has passed away a couple of years ago. He was
like nineties, nineties, but he had been around forever. So full service. I think I've talked to
Ryan Perez about this book. Pretty sure. Um, so. Was buried. Never to be chewed on.
So Jason's trying to recover. He's trying to stay face. I don't know. I do so much. So again,
I'm so sorry. This is like, I will call that ending to the Lucy confronts. That's a during
an ending to is when Lucy, uh, says to Desi, don't gaslight me. And I looked up the, the movie that
that term, you know, kind of comes from released in 1944 based on the play for 1938. So those were
in the ether. The term, the terminology of gaslighting, like don't gaslight, like to a
said to a person that is the most anachronistic thing. And that is more anachronistic than the
documentary Trump era. Yeah. It's like, it's like if Jess Oppenheimer walked in and was like, Lucy,
you're a girl boss. Like, what are you, what are you doing? Yeah. Gaslight. Yeah. That's,
that's very recent. What? And the last two modern, yeah. If they had had someone in the
documentary portion, say that would have made more sense. Sure. Like, and especially if Lucy's like
at the height of like her anger, but then also in a weird spot. Cause she's like, I got to pull it
together. We have to do tape and episodes. Like I understand people being very conflicted in that
moment and very weird in that moment. The third ending is like the text on cards of like the show
ended. Then they got divorced and then there's a little more documentary people at the end.
After all this, thank God, as much of that. Yeah. He kind of shows those cards, those modern cards
a little bit there really early on. There's a, there's a seriously. Yeah. There's a good,
not say that in there. Yeah. And there is definitely like, he is, he is writing dialogue
for like Desi Arnaz to quip. Like he's walking through the oval office or the whole, like you
can definitely sometimes you could, I mean, he's obviously like, that's his forte. He's good at it.
So like sometimes you didn't even pay them, but then sometimes you go, oh yeah. He's like writing
quippy. Oh, for Desi Arnaz and William Frawley, like as if they were on one of his old TV shows.
I mean, they really make them look good. I mean, like they were certainly very good entertainers,
but also their reputations are that they were massive assholes and they are heroes.
Frawley, especially Frawley. I think that's, you know, that's probably something that people
made people suggest that we do this episode. Yeah, right. There's a lot of love for
old William Frawley, Fred Mertz and I, I don't have a lot of Frawley material from this. I think that,
I mean, my, my main note is that JK Simmons doesn't look shitty enough. Well, I wrote down here,
jacked Bill Frawley. That's right. He's open real good shape. If you've seen the pictures,
we've all seen the pictures of JK Simmons, right? At the gym. Yes. No. Scott, can you Google,
are you on the internet? Can you just Google like, is he jacked in the tomorrow war? Yeah. Yeah.
He's pretty jacked. Jacked. Let's see if it's Jack. JK Simmons comes up. Okay. Yeah. But yeah,
look at him. He's like 66 years old or 65 years old. Look at those arms. My God. They,
Bill Frawley did not have those arms. No, and I don't, I don't have a problem. I mean, a lot of
the actors I think made the right choice of like, well, I'm going to do my interpretation
of this, this character. I mean, you know, the, the four stars of the show, you know, everyone
has an image of that. I don't know that a lot of people, you know, would know what like, oh, this
is what Jess Oppenheimer was like in real life. I did, I did think kind of casting against type Tony
Hale being a little more aggressive in roles he's often given. And I liked him as that character.
Yeah. I'd say my problems are rarely with the actors in this movie. Yeah. Almost, almost never.
I think that Cole Kidman, who was awarded a golden globe for this role from an undisclosed
location, wherever they gave out the golden globes this year. The trail of breadcrumb, whatever the
witch's house were, they hid the golden globes. I think the, I think she's great as doing like Lucy
behind the scenes. I don't know that anyone is well served with the show recreation, the black
and white show recreatives decides that one gag where Fred and Ethel elbow each other at the same
time. I think JK Simmons and Nina, I want to say Arianda is that Arianda Arianda. I thought they
did that bit really good. I kind of, well, I don't completely, I don't just completely disagree with
that, but I think that Nicole Kimmins voice is good when she's doing like performance Lucy.
I feel like it's real accurate when she's doing like radio play Lucy. And then when she's like
shouting and talking to the audience, like, but then sort of like, she goes in and out of sounding
like Lucy to me when she's doing like regular scenes. But that's a hard line. It's a very hard
line going between what Australian and, and it's, and, and yeah, right. Right. First voice to like
script cigarette. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. But then it's like also like my memories during watching this
are betraying me because I have watched, I have just mainlined hours of sick of seventies and
eighties talk show appearance, Lucy appearances where she's just tired and seemingly depressed
and her voice is so shot from cigarettes. So I was like, Oh, maybe I'm misremembering exactly
all Lucy's maybe spoke back during the making of this. Like the, the old Lucy is so, so much
stronger than yes. That's cause that's what you take it over your brain. When I think casual Lucy,
I think of that Lucy, a little bit more, uh, stone pillow era Lucy, which we've talked about before,
which might be future second gate. I never watched it. Yeah. Yeah. I haven't watched it.
Stone pillow. Stone pillow is a made for TV movie where Lucy is homeless.
Looks so like she's looks so broad and physical comedy despite having to be a serious,
like a red skeleton, like, uh, so yeah. So I always think of that, um, more so yeah, I'm not,
I would have to go back and see what Lucy sounded like exactly, but yeah, sometimes I feel like,
Oh yeah, she's actually doing a pretty good job with the voice. Um, and then sometimes I'm like,
yeah, she's a little lost in the woods on this. You know what I, I mainly, maybe I was rooting
for Nicole Kidman and wanted to enjoy Nicole Kidman in it in a way, because like,
you know, all that Twitter shit about like, how could it be Nicole? It's gotta be Deborah Messick,
Deborah Messick, damn it. Like, what do you imagine be okay. So by the time they are,
anyone tweeting about that is responding to the news of casting that is done. You're not
going to petition your way. You're not going to like make Sorkin. Although if anybody was dramatic
enough to do that, that he is like faxed the results of a Twitter poll. Yeah. Well, right.
America has spoken. We must do what we must do. But like so strange. Why and why are you fighting
so hard to overturn? I don't people like Nicole Kidman and then like Deborah Messing. I have
nothing against Deborah Messing, but like not really a movie star, right? Like a major television
star, one of the most major television stars. So why, and like, I know that there was an episode
of something where she dressed up like there's a Dharma and Greg episode because it's not the
Will and Grace is the Dharma. Dharma is Jenna Elfman. I'm so sorry. I'll just say Jenna Elfman.
No, like there's already, you have your photo of her like she's red hair, Lucy red, Deborah red,
she's red now today. She is, but in all fairness, I'm a little surprised that Sorkin didn't cast her
because she's the same kind of pudding brained milk toast Democrat. Like I'm sure they shared
a table at like $10,000 a plate at like some like, like Gillibrand for president,
like some awful fundraiser, you know? She's the one who tweeted like so and so was even maybe
like Steve Bannon was like wanted a 50% tax on like, like multimillionaires. And she was like,
this is out of control or something. Oh my God. There was something really embarrassing. People
goofing on her where you were like, this isn't that unbelievable. I forgot that aspect. But look,
I'm actually surprised that this phenomenon is much older than the internet actually.
Like, I don't know if another thing I watch copious amounts of our old Batman press from 1989
and Michael Keaton on all the talk shows. Oh boy, Mike. And well, you show me your YouTube
history. Yeah, yeah, yeah, you're right. We'll compare YouTube history. She was wasting more time.
Uh, but, but there was like a big uproar with Michael Keaton playing Batman. Oh, that's right.
Oh, that was like a comedian. Yeah. Like going to be a goof event again. Yeah. Adam. What? You mean
the very good Adam was thing. And then also like, how do you know that's not going to be that? What
are you? Yeah. Right. And it's not like there's much precedent even either. It wasn't like, oh,
there were like 10 like prestige Batman movies already. And they were, they were upset that
like, I don't know, like where did that come from? People were just like, people have always been
upset at like a famous character being played. I mean, he fledged every, you know, it happens all
the time. And I got, hopefully it'll happen with the character of Lucille Ball over and over again,
when many people portray her over the years. Um, and Bill, when Jason plays Bill Frawley,
in a couple of years, and he sings some of the old ones, there, there is like, as I was reading
about, there's a number of books about the making of, I love Jess Oppenheimer and his son, I think
wrote a book together. I think there's other, there might just be a book just about Frawley
and Vivian Vance. Oh, I wouldn't, I wouldn't agree with that. But like, I think there's very specific
and seemingly not a ton of it, not a ton of these source materials used for this.
In the same interview, Sorkin says there's a number of books about I love Lucy, but
they're not any good. They're written for the fans. And, uh,
this is written by not a fan at all who doesn't know very much other than just the greatest hits.
Well, the greatest hits and this communist thing that I am convinced now, look, I don't know,
I don't know what happened. I'm no expert on this subject, but my guess is my hunch is that this,
uh, the house on American activities, communist thing with them. I don't think this is like one
of the top 400 memories in Lucy or Desi's lives. I think they were on their deathbeds and this
didn't occur to them at all. No, I think this is a interesting anecdote. Sorkin was like,
ding, ding, ding, ding, ding Sorkin vision attack. This is the whole story is this.
That's what their lives were about. Two pages in LA confidential magazine or like, uh, three
sentences and a head of hopper, you know, uh, column, but like, yeah, I don't, there's so many
stories and then they do like, he's got this dismissive attitude in the press about it,
but then they do have all these facts of like, yeah, it's 60 million people or 30 million people.
Well, he has to respect the numbers. The respect and the department stores that you stay open late
on Mondays, but then Lucy, they had to change the day. Yeah. I, I, yeah, he obviously,
when you're doing anything like this, that's like, if you were a dad, if any of us were adapting
this, we would have to pick like what we find the most interesting. And you're, you're right, Scott,
that this is just the most interesting thing to him about a gigantic TV star that has transcended
many generations syndication still to this day, people know who she is, laugh at her.
And the, the, the racial stuff and the mixed marriage there, it's in there, but it's not the
primary, it's like about as interesting as this one brush with J. Edgar Hoover that didn't happen.
Yeah. His number one thing is, uh, canceling celebrities getting canceled and using this
Lucy movie to make a point about it, that it was silly. I don't know. That's the, that's the,
the core of the story. And the also on that J. Edgar Hoover note. So the reality of that is that
he did like write a letter to the show and like, boy, I have to say this, like some stiff, like
the comedy on the program was some of the best executed comedy that I have witnessed in my,
in this week. And then, uh, a little subtext to their like, like a very end of this article,
I'm reading, uh, J. Edgar Hoover did keep a file on Lucy ball for the rest of her life.
Of course. So he's presented as that like, yes, thank you for the call.
Desi, anytime you need the FBI, I am here. Also, I will be following both of you forever.
I think he followed everyone. I think anyone, anyone got some publicity in America is like,
all right, time to open a file. Like I think the, I haven't watched the Leonardo DiCaprio,
J. Edgar Hoover. I think it is, uh, not well reviewed, but I believe, um, one of the things
it seemed to get right is that J. Edgar Hoover wasn't insane, man. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I just
wanted to look and see if J. Edgar Hoover lived long enough to see stone pillow and he did not.
Oh, geez. Going too soon. Out of the file. Yeah. Haven't got another angel. He died in,
he died in 72 and stone pillow was 85. Um, so. Cause he probably, probably could have gotten
that late in life, like juice from Nixon from like second Nixon administration. Yeah. I think
that's probably right. But, um, no, he bowed out before. If he knew stone pillow was coming a
mere 13 years later, he may have hung on just a little longer, Jay. Yeah.
Can I, if I remember, we used to write it down, but I just, what, one quick thing that,
that struck me too. I don't know if you guys, if this registered at all, that there's a lot of
several times in this movie, the name, uh, Damon Runyon is said. Oh yeah. Yeah. Um, that like,
you know, she has been Lucy's film career. She's going to do a movie. It's, it's written by,
well, I'm doing a Damon Runyon. Jesse, it's Damon Runyon. Um, I've never heard the name
Damon Runyon in my life. Again, I am not super educated. I don't know who this is. And I,
I'm so like, oh, this is the most. So I just Googled Damon Runyon, Aaron Sorkin. And if the
first thing I find is an interview where he says, well, William Frawley, you know, was kind of a
Damon Runyon character. Like you fucking, God, again, it Lou that Lucy met Damon Runyon is a
writer he admires. That's more important that we don't need to see the chocolate. We don't need to
write, right? No, but the family, like none of that matter. Damon Runyon needs the time.
Am I crazy? Is Damon Runyon the most famous? I don't, I, I think that, no, that I feel like
I've heard that name as a name. Like when I looked up Gaslight, I was like, oh, directed by
George Cukor. Yeah. It was George Cukor movie. Like he just wanted a journeyman, like kind of
writer, director. There were so many journeymen and like, you know, some would break out or some
would, you know, have a second, a second wind in like the kind of a tour era of Hollywood or, or
you re-examine them like a few decades later and stuff. But like, no, I don't
blanking on Damon Runyon's contributions. And he goes way out of his way to get Edward R.
Murrow's name in there too. Oh, you gotta. That guy from CBS, one of the actors has one of my
favorite voices I've ever heard. He's like, has a real like voice like this. And I love it. I can't,
I should have, I've totally blanked on looking his name up. I really should do that. Cause I was like,
I kept being like, this guy's voice is great. I love this. Again, the character, the people,
the actors who fill out the smaller roles or fill out the support staff of I Love Lucy,
great cast. Yeah, sure. Really good actors. Honestly, I would love to watch just an I Love Lucy
behind the scenes of just the writers and J.K. Simmons and the woman who played Vivian Vance.
Well, yeah, Vivian Vance, I feel like she gets, she just seems like she's just mad all the time.
And I assume she was mad about the things she's mad about in the movie, but she was friends with
Lucy. She hated William Frawley, supposedly, but she was friends with Lucy. So like there should
be a scene where they're like, she's not like just mad, you know, like there had to be times when they
were like happy, like, you know, there should have been a more of a get back. There should have been
a nine hours of seeing behind the scenes of I Love Lucy and, you know, seeing the good times
and the bad. Not just. Sorkin must be furious at get back. Oh, I bet he is. They showed that they
had fun together. That can't be right. Right. And also he's probably says, you know, if we really
look back at it, the Beatles music doesn't hold up. It's just, it's outdated. I think today,
if you took a second look at it, nobody would tap their toes to it. Right. It's not like the
Gilbert and Sullivan songs. It doesn't hold up like those do. I'm listening to a Beatles song.
I'm not laughing uproariously at all. Now Gilbert and Sullivan on the other hand,
I'm going to pause the tape every 10 seconds. I assume we know most of those songs, mostly from
the Sideshow Bob Cape Fear episode. Oh, yes. Absolutely. I know the names. Yep. Information
animal, vegetable, mineral, the very model of the modern age. That's all I know. Any other thoughts
on this on this film? Funny to watch an interesting watch. Yeah, an interesting watch. Spirit discussion.
It's a little long, but I mean, it's pretty, you know, it goes, it's not boring. It's interesting.
I was just going to say, yeah, not boring. Um, I, I don't know how you feel about being the
Ricardo's as a title. I have some alternate titles. I want to go ahead. Uh, Lucy, you've got some
explaining to do. I love the fellows. Uh, television is important. And finally women. Am I right?
Can you combine the last two, the last two, your titles combined? Oh, television important,
comma women. Am I right? Yeah, there you go. Yeah. Oh, maybe some parentheses in there. Yeah.
This really is, I was watching it the whole time. I just kept saying like, I want more movies that
dramatize Lucy's life, but I would like some movies about her time with her second husband,
Gary Morton, who I'm also obsessed with watching interviews. Gary Morton is like kind of sleepy,
older comedian. Oh, actually he was younger than Lucy, but sleepy comedian who like when they're
doing interviews together, I'm like, Oh, this is Lucy. Really like this guy. Like, um, so if he
casts, so if Javier Bardem ends up being Desi, then who's, who's Gary, who's Gary Morton, the guy who
plays, uh, Jerry on parks and rec, what's that guy's name? Give that guy like maybe like a beard.
I forget his name. I knew at one point. Yeah. He's very funny on that show. Uh, what about a movie
where Desi is trying to decide between Gail Gordon and William Frawley for the role of Fred? Oh, but
sure. I mean, just that decision. I think, I think the decision was made because I think Gail was
unavailable because I believe this story. I, I read something where he was like really pushing for,
because Lucy was good. Yeah. Guys be careful. I know the gripes, the gripe makers are watching.
I know, I know. I was trying to have my bets there. This is Hollywood Babylon. This is all
rumor mongering. Who knows? Gail Gordon and Lucy got plenty of time to work together. Yeah. Yes.
And then Lucy, of course. So I just see, I would love a behind the scenes about every Lucy project,
I guess really also that existed. Sure. The Lucy show. Here's Lucy. What's that? She's in Mame. Oh,
Mame. Sure. Yeah. And then, um, of course life with Lucy, the last sitcom she did. Oh, that,
yeah. The kids, the kids that produce her credits, her kids, you know, her kids on this movie. I
learned her daughter is married to the guy who played like Spock's brother in Star Trek five.
And I got real excited about that. Sibak, I believe is the character's name and it's Star
Trek five. It's the worst Star Trek movie. It's the one Shatner directed. Uh, and it's the one,
have you ever seen this scene in Star Trek five, Scott, where they're all in central, like,
no, not like a national park and they like fall off a cliff and it's like Shatner, Nimoy, DeForest,
Kelly. You should see it because they're like Spock has like rocket boots and the effect is really
bad. And he like goes up and he like kept, you got it. Yeah. That was a story going around recently.
Who knows how true, you know, it is as like, you know, when you can fit it in an image to go on
Twitter or Instagram of like Lucy in the Desi Lu capacity was really pushing for CVCBS to make
this pilot called Star Trek. Yes, Lucy. Very. Yes. Lucy was a big part of Star Trek. Yeah. Um,
and yeah, they, they look, there are a lot of facts they should have crammed in to this. You
know, Lucy is going to make a show called Star Trek or she's going to be responsible because she
didn't make it, but there's like a whole, there's a convoluted way in which she has something to do
with Star Trek getting on the air. She's a star. Do you understand? There's going to be actresses
dressed up like her at theme parks, whatever those are. Yeah. Years in the future in the way that like
Ben and, Ben and Matt were like, you know, Kevin Smith kind of saved Goodwill Hunting. Well, Kevin
Smith and Francis, Francis for Coppola and Robin, they all kind of helped save it. Almost didn't get
made. Yeah. Um, I'm realizing now I have to make issue a correction. Uh, it's going to take care of
it now. The gentleman, uh, Lawrence Luckin Bill is, uh, married to Lucy's daughter still,
and he played Spock's half brother, Sibuk. So before anyone emails and is mad, yes, half brother,
not full brother of Spock. So that should take care of that. I think what I would like to see
Sorkin wise and we should be so lucky to get this. This is just, this is almost like if Sorkin cloned
himself in the 10th clone could do Sorkin's dream that there'd be that many Sorkin's walking around,
but like Sorkin, uh, doing a dramatic depiction of anything that's happened to us in the podcast,
the ride, you know, that moment right there that like, all right, thanks for listening everybody.
Half brother, are you kidding me? You know, if you're going to come in to these episodes and get
facts wrong, you make all of us look like fools. You understand that Michael, you're played by a
much shorter actor. That guy doesn't look like Mike at all. And our characters have sex.
We're too riled up. Uh, frankly, I've found many inaccuracies in some of the things you said. Are
you as hot as I am right now? Uh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Mike, can I chew your cock?
I don't know where to go from there. I don't know. I don't know either.
They condense, uh, uh, Mike getting, getting, uh, sunscreen in his eye and Scott getting a, um,
bug infested, Nimgaloo and me accidentally using my dad's, um, uh, Lowry rewards.
Oh yeah. That all happened in one long weekend.
Oh wow. Yeah. That's such a great deal. Oh, I remember that week. Oh, sure. I do.
The entire podcast took place in one week. This is what I, that voice I just did is an,
is a older actress playing Aaron years in the future. That's right.
Just a few years before I divorced Scott, things were, there was a lot of pressure in our marriage
plus the whole Lowry's card thing. Yeah, it was a week.
I'll say. And he just admitted his desire to chew on Mike's cock.
It also sounds like Chuck E. Cheese doing the voice.
Yeah. Or what's the other, the like, yes, it sure does. What? He's not only has so many voices.
Who was it? Barbera or Hannah? I have both of them. Yeah. Um, hey, you survived podcast.
The second gate. Um, I mean, if this is, this is a guy in a way, a good ad for the movie. Yeah.
As fired up as you like Lucy at all or lover or just like this. Maybe, maybe.
Primarily, I guess, if you have never had interest in Lucy until you learned that there was something
involving Senator Joe McCarthy in her life. Yeah, that's good. Yeah. Most ideal. That's red. Yeah.
People are going to be salivating to see this now. Look, it's award season and, uh, you know, the, um,
uh, Oscars will be broadcast from area 51 this year. Totally secure environment.
Uh-huh. Hosted by the Brent Spiner character from independence day. Sure.
With a tentacle around his neck. I assume that's better than most of the jokes I've seen online of
like, who's the host of the Oscars in 2021? It's always like, don't you mean Deborah messing?
Hey folks, keep it tuned here to podcast the ride. The second gate, uh, where we've always
got plenty of cocks to chew on. I mean episodes to listen to. Ah, geez, we better wrap this up.
Yeah. I have nothing to say unless Jason wants to say that. Well, no, it's just if he, if it's not
too much work, if you put the typewriter corn eating sound effect. Yeah, just great. I do.
Anytime you talk. No, just at the end of the day, on the way. Okay. I'll see you. Or you
send me the file and I'll see what I can find. All right. And I'll edit it.