Five, four, three, two, one.
Westward ho everyone.
The fry wagon is pulled up here to the second gate.
I'm Scott Gardiner, Jason Sheridan's here, hi.
Hi.
And Mike Carlson as well.
Yes, I'm here.
If the Oregon Trail would have been a much lovelier time if there was a fry wagon that
followed the group, don't you think?
Oh, fried potatoes, yeah.
On demand, sure.
Oh yeah, what a lifted spirits for sure.
And solved the, they would have had food as well.
Assuming if they could get, it wouldn't have been spirit lifter if there weren't any potatoes
to put in it.
Okay, that's true.
But the wagon itself wouldn't have helped anything.
So if you were playing the game, the Oregon Trail, then it would have been like the McDonald's
fry wagon has run out of potatoes.
And then you'd have to go find the potatoes or you'd have to like kill some.
Powdered beef seasoning, it's run out of powdered beef seasoning.
Run out of plastic Happy Meal toys.
So you will not be able to distribute toys to the children anymore.
So they'll rebel, start hitting you, you're weak already, like you're weak at the knees,
the kids hit your knees and you would keel over and die.
You have to invent cheaper plastic in order to make whatever IP they had during the Oregon Trail,
which it was what?
I don't know.
What stories were they telling?
Oh yeah, Paul Bunyan.
I guess it's a lot of it's like, oh, it's Paul Bunyan again.
Oh, it's Andy Oakley again.
They had three stories back then.
Yeah.
So I don't know, that would still be exciting to get if it was different versions of Paul and his different clothing.
That's true.
Yeah, all those different outfits.
Babe, babe, the blue ox comes at different colors.
Oh yeah, maybe there's like Yoshi.
Yeah, like Yoshi.
Babe is like Yoshi.
Babe, the red ox.
Babe, the yellow ox.
Yeah.
Like them all.
Geez.
Well, kids had a lot to look forward to.
Yeah.
In this fictional, all you got to do is combine McDonald's with the Oregon Trail or anything, really.
Right.
And look how much better it makes it.
I agree.
Always.
McDonald's always improves any situation.
We're talking about a wagon that sold fries in Frontierland.
A dusty old wagon that sold McDonald's fries that people love.
Yeah.
There's a lot of fondness for this, I feel.
A lot of affection, I feel, like I found online.
Now, I never got to experience this because I believe it was, was it gone by the time?
No, I don't think so.
We might have gotten the tail end of it when we moved out here.
I don't think I did it, though.
I think I might have seen it, but I didn't experience it.
Yeah.
On the map, the official name of this place was Conestoga Fries, although on the top of
the Conestoga wagon building itself, it said Westward Ho in big letters.
So that's confusing.
Yeah.
Which was a callback to the, when Tizzyland actually had Conestoga wagons that you could
ride in that said Westward Ho on them.
You know this is a bad ride if we've never even heard of it.
Westward Ho wagons.
Conestoga wagons.
We've kind of, we know that there were mules and we know nature's wonderland.
The wagons must have really stink.
All the practical stuff in Frontierland back in the day is just kind of like a blank slate
because it was 30 years before I was born.
So.
Yeah, yeah.
But it's also just like a big, you know, there's a dirt lot.
Like there's one area of the park that we don't have to make not a dirt lot.
That's going to save us so much work.
But it really was, what is easier?
They had a dirt lot and they were like, just throw a wagon over there and just throw the
people in the wagon and just roll, go around in a circle.
Yeah.
And then people didn't get to go in a wagon every day.
They had no expectations for what this theme park was.
So the wagon worked.
And they'd all been tricked into liking Western shit by Walt over the year of watching the
show.
Wow, that was just like Davy Crockett.
I was, it was exact recreation of what they told me the West was.
Well, three months ago.
Also all popular culture, like Westerns were the Marvel movies of their time.
Yes.
The Len test of the sixties, like getting guest surveys after the wagons.
Everyone, everyone's saying we love the wagon.
It's the highest rated thing.
It's just like the television shows.
So, yeah, I don't, I, it wouldn't be like they do a wagon in knots still, right?
You can still get in a wagon.
Maybe the horse, I believe who wants to do, why would you choose to do this now?
The wagon.
That's a good question.
Jason, would you go in the way you would go in the wagon?
I think I may be a little claustrophobic right now, but if given the option, yeah, I'd probably
try it.
Yeah.
I'm sure I've ridden a wagon horse-drawn wagon at some point in the past.
I've been in a wagon.
I've been in a big wagon and I can't, I think maybe like at a pumpkin farm.
But the fact that you don't remember means it probably wasn't that good.
But I think I'm anti-wagon.
My wagon opportunities have been slim, I think.
I don't think I've been offered a wagon very often.
So that's why my memory might not be so strong, but I'm pretty sure as a kid, I mean, there's
a haunted hayride out here that's kind of wagon-esque.
Yeah, that's a look.
If it's showing you something, it depends, I guess, on what this wagon's taken me to
see.
Yeah.
If it's just like going in a loop around things I can walk up to, which is what I think the
Disneyland one was.
Yeah.
So yeah, I guess Fry Wagon that stays in one place is an upgrade to wagon you get to go
in that just goes in a circle.
Does something.
Listen to, wow, this is how it was, this is from the site Yesterland.
Here's what Conestoga Wagons did.
Your Conestoga wagon is pulled by two strong horses.
Good for them.
I'm very impressed.
They're strong.
We didn't hire weak ones, so don't go accusing us of that.
Taking you on a genuine dirt path along the rivers of America through the genuine dirt.
So the horses are strong and the dirt is genuine.
It's not fake dirt.
There's rocks around, but the dirt is real.
Dirt is not insincere.
I mean, I like the horse-drawn trolley on Main Street.
Yes.
You love being dragged by a horse somewhere.
Well, that is a lot more violent.
No, you don't want to say dragged.
Not like.
And pulled.
Yeah, you wouldn't want to be on a rope on the hitting pavement.
What if you were on like a sled or something and you just had a rope tied around your one
ankle and then you like, so you weren't getting like cut up on the ground, but the horse was
just pulling you.
That'd be awesome.
It would be dangerous.
Somebody would have to stop the horse eventually, but the ride up until that point would be
fun, I think.
Sure.
Yeah.
Wait, what are you on?
Are we one leg?
Legs?
This is really painful.
I think it's simulating getting thrown off an old time before.
There's an old clip of the Undertaker wrapping Hulk Hogan's legs in chains and then dragging
him through the hallway on a motorcycle, through a motor, like he's on the ground and then the
Undertaker is tied him to his motorcycle and takes off and then they drag Hogan through
the hallway.
And this is sort of what I'm thinking, but with a horse, but with something where you're
like kind of on a sled.
So imagine you're on a sled and then you have maybe both legs tied with a horse or
excuse me, a rope and the rope is then tied to the horse and the horse takes off and you're
on a sled on the ground.
Well, the more you say that, I'm realizing like how many roots and rocks and just things
are in the ground.
That's true.
You never stop to notice how much is on the ground until you're being dragged by a horse.
Being dragged by a horse.
Because you're describing a scenario where it's like a clean set, but you still don't
know where that horse is going to do.
And the word drag is in there.
That's the key.
Fine.
Daredevil Mike wants to get dragged by a horse because he saw it happen to Hulk.
But if you, it's got to be the most sanitized version of this or else.
Okay.
I think you just need to massage the language.
Like Conestoga fries sign, eat hearty, round them up, you know, make those McDonald's fries
sound exciting and eat hearty, round them up.
Western-y.
Yeah.
So they did this, which it's funny because this is a stretch.
I feel like this would be, I'm sure there were people that were upset at the time of
like, this doesn't really make a lot of sense.
There definitely were more on that in a minute.
Okay, good.
You found something that's good.
Because yeah, what I, on the reddits and stuff, people were just like, I loved this.
Yeah.
I'm mainly very positive today.
And I, yeah, I'm trying to remember.
I think I probably was on the side.
I was on the dorky side at the time of like, but this is a thing from the outside world.
And I, and now that now just when we talked about doing an episode, like I've none of
that, none of those shackles are binding me down now.
I, this seems pretty great to me.
And I also like, I really, I started explaining this to Erin.
What episode are you doing?
We're doing one.
There was like a wagon that sold them and she was like Westward.
Oh, she was so positive about it, which I may have.
Maybe a lot of people will be.
I think so.
Actually, I think we'll, I think we'll see.
We'll do a litmus test.
I mean, I, I'm a few of a few minds about it.
Cause nowadays I'm like, well, McDonald's fries are miles ahead of most Disneyland fries.
Most Disney park fries.
Yeah.
It's not a very good area for them.
No, as a kid, I don't think it offended me.
I just thought it was kind of fun.
Like I was like, well, I don't need this.
We have McDonald's at home.
We eat McDonald's a lot.
And I was also like, well, they only have fries and soda.
Like it's like, well, I don't, I don't need that.
Like, what am I going to do?
There's no burgers.
Sure.
That's a good point that it's not a full on, but this was, I think them trying to navigate
this middle between the people who are like this, it's the outside world.
How dare you, even though there's been brands in Disneyland from, right?
David, you was probably in 1955 was way worse.
There's so many in an Aunt Jemima thing.
And just some guy we found out named Don DeFour has a restaurant.
It's me, Don DeFour.
Are you a Disney character?
No, I'm not a man.
Maxwell House, Coffee House, Carnation Ice Cream Parlor.
Like there was so much.
But I guess maybe the caveat is and has been that you don't just do, it's not universal.
You don't just put a Panda Express in and it's a regular Panda Express, but more expensive.
You got to do something in the way Carnation did.
And maybe that was the idea here is that it's a special McDonald's experience.
And their definition of special in this case was doing less.
Only the most minute fraction of what they typically do.
Yeah.
And it's like, I guess if I'm thinking about it, what is there like future fries in Tomorrowland?
What would be a better way to do it?
I mean, I guess we should do that at the end.
We should think of like if we were in modern days, like how to apply.
We are tasked with incorporate McDonald's in the park.
Like a ton of new McDonald's in the park.
So maybe we do that at the end.
But yeah, so I guess all right, fries, whatever.
It's old west, they had potatoes.
Okay, that's good enough.
It's a basic thing.
Well, is the tie together?
I mean, this isn't why they thought of it, but they sure try to make it all work together with the phrase.
There's gold in them.
There are fries.
I mean, that's pretty good.
I think that's what makes it.
I think it does.
Were you if you're you're going like McDonald's in the West?
Why doesn't make you see that phrase?
Oh, got it.
That's all I got to do.
Great. Thank you.
Because the goal there, the McDonald's is the golden arches.
The fries are golden.
Yep.
So gold is the gold rush from the olden days.
Yep. Yeah.
Done. Yeah.
I like the hash marks that say forty nine served.
Yes, that is a sign with.
Yeah, they're like counting them up and not that many people have done it yet.
But I'm just only now seeing at the bottom, it says I'll feed you all, which sounds like a threat.
It's that that Wu Tang torture sketch.
I'm like, it's going to keep going and like they plug up your butt or something.
I mean, a problem.
You're getting fed so much.
Yeah.
The signs are doing a lot of work here.
I think the signs are great.
But you're you're right.
Just to back it up, that the combo is really funny.
McDonald's in the Old West.
Why?
Yes, it does.
And there's nothing in here.
And again, they tied it together.
Great. But it's I don't know.
It's pretty good.
Now I'm now I say, why not?
I agree.
Why not?
I'm not mad about this in the least bit.
Yeah.
I'm burger invasion is worse to me than this.
This is why we said some bad things about burger invasion.
Maybe we should back it up even further and talk about the general McDonald's Disney partnership,
because that's that's what happened here is that even today you kind of mentally tie together Disney and McDonald's because it even though they aren't always tied together.
I do think of a Happy Meal toy and it's of Disney stuff.
And it has been recently in this garage there.
Mike, you gave me a 50th anniversary Disney World thing that was at McDonald's.
But the partnership went in and out.
Right. Yes.
And actually in the classic era, like when we were kids and we were going to McDonald's the most.
And I remember having disappointment about this.
That the like the big four movies Little Mermaid, Beating the Beast, Aladdin, Blanking, the toys were not at McDonald's.
Right.
The most severed the relationship was was like 89 to 97.
There's a good.
Yeah.
If you watch the defunct land McDonald's Disney video, it's really it goes into detail and all the all of this and when it stopped.
And yes, it was missing for the majority of the movies.
I'm trying to think of.
Yeah.
Was Little Mermaid even didn't have one?
I know the others didn't.
I know we had a Christmas ornament of Bernard from the Rescuers that came from McDonald's.
I know for a fact that came from McDonald's.
Yeah.
And I had a little.
The little it was a little is that what you're saying?
Camera thing.
I had a little camera ref from rescuers from a little camera for sure.
But no, this was just Bernard in a little cute little Christmas sweater.
I was wrong.
I had that too.
So they were doing stuff.
Little Mermaid is was McDonald's.
Oh, OK.
OK.
But yes, I have that too.
I have that Christmas sweater and they have I have Oliver and company.
I still have.
Yeah.
Christmas stuff for sure.
So they have been doing stuff back then.
And then, yeah, they had like a falling out.
The big agreement went 1997 to 2007, which multiple places online pointed out that that
meant McDonald's was legally obligated to promote Treasure Planet home on the range
and other less successful Brother Bear, other less successful slide into there.
Do we got chicken little yet?
Oh, yeah, probably.
Yeah.
Either way, it's a yeah, that's kind of right when things are getting rough, I'd say.
Unfortunately, this is all from Kevin and Defunct land.
But there was also the relationship apparently got strained because of a Splash Mountain
promotion that McDonald's was doing where they had like a huge like was like splash
for cash or some some weird thing.
I don't know.
I forget exactly the name of it, but it was some sort of promotion with prizes.
And then so like a bunch of people went to Disney with free tickets.
They won from McDonald's.
Everyone was excited.
And then Splash Mountain was horribly delayed.
And apparently McDonald's now pleased.
Oh, timing of this really as well.
Gotcha.
Yeah.
Again, watch this McDonald's.
Yeah, I'm not like super prepared to talk about the relationship in general.
And Jason, as you and I discuss, there's probably like five McDonald's episodes you can pull
out.
We have not even searched the surface of McDonald's.
So that's why I'm not, you know, don't quote me on any of this, but there is that.
And this you guys might have stumbled upon this in research.
The connection really goes back to the war.
Right.
Walt Disney and the founder himself, Mr. Michael later played by Michael Keaton, really a real
man, Ray Kroc, the man that I found her.
I mean, stealer of the idea of McDonald's that they weirdly were in World War One together.
They didn't fight, but they were like, yeah, yeah, they were in some what?
Infantry.
Yeah.
No, they met.
They knew each other.
Yeah.
And yet still then they like wrote each other letters and tried to partner up in some way.
And Kroc was like, no, doesn't meet my qualifications.
No.
Like he was like, I think they were fond enough of each other.
But what are the odds that those two guys are together?
It's pretty wild.
Yeah.
So yeah, it goes back.
It goes back to it goes back very far and then continues to this day in some capacity.
On and off.
I don't understand the why it's exclusive or not, but it was exclusive for they were exclusive.
They were boyfriend girlfriend for 10 years and which started with there was a lot of
pomp and circumstance over this announced in May 96.
Michael Eisner stoked.
I'm sure you've run across.
Oh yeah.
Well, this is the most ambitious promotional effort ever developed between two of the world's
best known family friendly brands.
The agreement we announced today is a true McDisney production.
Wonderful.
I can shed some light on a very specific memory I have of when they got away from doing Happy
Meal Toys Disney characters at Happy Meal Toys is during the I don't know looking back
what the when it began and when it technically ended, but the obesity epidemic, if you remember
the scares of the obesity epidemic and subway was like hot damn we are marginally more healthy
for you than a big Mac.
Big Mac.
Than like non food is.
And so I think Disney showed up at Subway for a little while because Disney was getting
away from like, oh, we can't be associated with like feeding kids all this fat and sugar
and we need to be associated with this guy Jared.
Yeah, we're a family friendly brand and this guy seems very family friendly as much as
we can when you look at this face.
Think of Disney.
They went in there and they were like this Jared guy good.
This tuna real.
This tuna is good and real and healthy and then they looked up and down and they were
like all of this.
All this bread.
A foot of bread.
Good.
This yoga mat bread.
Cheese bread.
Good.
Oh yeah right.
Yeah.
People still do Subway ever.
I kind of.
I love Subway tuna.
I absolutely love it.
Uh oh.
I haven't had it in a while in months but Subway tuna it was revealed I guess that it
was like they couldn't identify what fish it was.
They couldn't tell if it was actually tuna.
I'm not exactly.
I haven't really read too much into it and I didn't even almost didn't phase me.
I went well it's good so I don't know.
It's got to be some fish.
I guess it could be mayonnaise.
You just want that tuna that's tuna-y like really fishy right?
I don't want this at all.
I can't relate to this at all.
I have never liked that variety that sort of tuna so I don't that phrase is a foreign
language to me.
Well.
I don't want that one.
I mean my mom always bought the chunk white tuna which is a little flakier a little nicer.
Yeah.
Even the fact that you can say chunk white.
We're talking about like.
Chunk white versus chunk white.
Yeah.
They were even saying chunk.
Chunk white.
Like that's going to make it more epic that you don't like.
Are you.
You want to gag a little bit when you're talking about chunks.
Are you anti-tuna in general or just certain types of tuna?
I don't like canned we're runny.
I'm like you know.
Any fish like salmon in a can.
Oh yeah.
Not really.
No no no.
I like fish none of that.
Indication crab meat.
Yeah that's okay on a fish roll.
Subway tuna is just like a big scooper and it's already like been like wetted down with
mayo and other stuff as well.
Yikes.
And it's not like it doesn't resemble canned tuna.
It's just it's like a I'm trying to think it's almost like ice cream or something like
it's.
Yeah.
It's easy.
Like a deli.
Like all deli's that's how they scoop out the tuna.
Like tuna salad or something.
Yeah.
I don't do that though.
I'd say the salad genre for me is a no.
I love.
Chicken.
Tuna melts.
Oh don't do it.
Oh I like a tuna melt.
Yeah sure.
I love a tuna melt.
So the fact that there was the also talking about old Disneyland stuff that there was
the chicken of the sea that there was a tuna ship.
It sounds awful.
And in like early Disneyland where everything's like it's hot as hell.
There's no trees yet.
Everything's baking.
So you just got hot tuna.
What about frying up.
What about like spicy tuna on a you know what I'm saying a bowl one of those bowls.
A poke bowl.
Yeah I'm down with that.
But I feel like I need to see real I need pieces.
I don't want to mush.
I don't want to mush or a mayo.
I want a solid solid ground.
All right.
Now one of the things about the fry cart in Disneyland at least Frontierland fries was
the name of the cart in the Magic Kingdom.
But in Disneyland it became so popular they're like we need another one of these.
So they converted the Harbor Galley which was serving like quote unquote healthier fare
which seemed to mostly be tuna salad.
They converted it to.
Yeah no it was it did it said in the what yesterlain article it was like they sold tuna
there tuna and like fruit salad.
And so and then they they turned it into the French fries and then they turned it back
to serving like I would call it because I've eaten there once or twice.
I would call it like a hospital cafeteria level see.
Yeah it's what you want.
It's like the worst lobster roll you've ever had.
I was wondering I'm like I've never heard I've never been to that.
I didn't know there were lobster rolls at Disneyland.
I've never heard anyone talk about it like this can't be good.
You can get a chowder there can't you?
Clam chowder and a bread ball is fine if you if you want to commit to eating.
And you can get that much.
You can get like a hospital salad there.
Yeah yeah yeah.
But like a chowder is okay I feel like I've had once.
I think yeah I think the chowder is okay.
I mean you end up eating like a loaf of bread or like half a loaf of bread.
Yes that's true.
Depending on how much of the bread you're going to eat.
This is also what's so fun I guess we're I'm getting ahead of myself but like what's so
funny about them going like we got to get the McDonald's out of the park as if all the
food was elevated immediately.
Right like as if they were like well we got to get rid of french fries in our park.
Their french fries are probably just as bad.
But they didn't get rid of french fries.
It's not worse I don't know.
But it's a PR thing because there's no stink on their specific french fries.
Nobody made a documentary about those.
Exactly.
Amazing how much damage that documentary did.
Like probably not really to their bottom line.
But in terms of it just probably at McDonald's caused a lot of like okay we got to figure
out apple slices now god damn it.
A tiny little thing of fries and a plastic thing of apple slices.
Yeah.
And let's I want to be clear those apple slices are disgusting.
Skinless vacuum sealed plastic bag apple like.
Yeah.
I only had them for the first time really because I donated to a documentary on Kickstarter
that I'm excited about which is the non-standard McDonald's documentary that I believe Kevin
Perger and Defunctland are involved in.
So I'm excited to see where this thing goes.
But if you don't follow that on Twitter.
Yeah.
They may have addressed some of these things.
I know they've talked about burger invasion.
It's a Twitter account that tracks weird McDonald's that are not the standard boxes
which are you know a dying species.
Unfortunately they have the one way they like to do them that's so boring.
But the reward and this really this was a very enticing reward to donate to the Kickstarter
was you'll get the the non-standard meal.
They will.
They're going to curate McDonald's meal for you.
It's going to show up at your house because you don't know.
I'm like wow that's crazy.
And then I was so interested in what it was going to be.
And then it was like it was just very bizarre.
They basically took what technically was a regular hamburger but did every possible
add on which is like three times salt three to like as much lead it to where that you could probably
anyone who donated to this at all these McDonald's everywhere people are getting this customization
order that's like OK they roll up their sleeves like the poor people at the like they had to
put it in a Big Mac box.
It didn't fit no anymore in the little and then mixed with like I think there were two
giant coffees with it.
It was so bizarre on every level.
So every add on on to what is technically still a plain hamburger and then yes little apple slices
with like to add to the unpleasantness.
I was very thankful for it.
Once I scraped a ton of stuff off became a very good little McDonald's meal.
What was the sandwich just a regular hamburger OK but with extra salt.
I think they just went through the list every add on and did three times that a mess.
So so much cheese so much lead so much onions so much salt.
That was the most offensive thing to add a ton of salt isn't I like getting extra everything on it.
But salt is not one of the things I added more.
This is a delightful experience though and I just I want to say I'm my support of the film is only grown.
What a fun thing.
Yeah that was a trick I heard growing up of like well if you want really fresh McDonald's french fries you ask for a light salt and then they have to make that batch fresh.
And I'm like what do you talk what like what do you mean.
I'm like it's going to be cold by the time we get to the booth like it's going to be.
Yeah they don't they don't stay particularly warm these customizations.
I don't know but you know what I just did it in and out a couple of weeks ago.
I don't go to I don't think I went to Internet through the entire pandemic.
I've been a little off fast food in general not making a point of it.
It just has is not in my general day to day.
So I think I'm I often find that I am not used to what I am about to get like my body has trouble processing sure and fill in the blanks of what that means.
Yeah it's always my body's always like huh what I'm freaking out here.
But I asked for the well done fries because you got about in and out a lot of not in L.A.
That like the fries are all soggy asked for them well done.
I did it. They were very well done.
I took over. It's like I guess so.
I don't know. I wish I just had the regular still ate all of them and the burger the next day.
I had so much sodium coat on my throat to where it was like I felt like I needed to cough.
I was like having it hurt to talk and things being the way they are.
I was like what if this isn't from the sodium of the fries.
Is this a sign of Omicron.
Do I have Omicron and I determined that I did not.
But the salt from the fucking fries was so bad.
So bad. I'm just so not like coded and ready for it.
Genuinely the fries made me think that I had the fucking virus.
You're worried. Yeah.
Yeah. I got to be prepared for an in and out meal.
I feel like you'll understand. I love in and out burger but I got like three different meals I can get there.
Depending on how much food I've had that day how I'm feeling like.
Yeah you eliminate a lot of things.
I can't do the sauce. I can't add like less cheese.
There's just a lot of my body is not to do anymore.
You need to Scott you need to buy fries and just have a couple every day to keep your body producing enzymes that can break this stuff down.
OK. So just like a couple of day.
We'll love to hear your stomach gut balance.
I don't even mean to sound like some pretentious food.
I have tater tots so often but they're at home and they're just treated differently.
It's not from the fry. I assure you that I eat terribly.
You have the enzyme for tater tots but not the in and out fries.
I get well done fries with the cheese on it.
Yeah I was going to say the well done fries are really good at holding like animal style toppings or cheese or whatever.
You thicken them up so the softening that happens.
You get a piece of cheese on it and it melts and that's what I do and then you go in with a fork which is fun.
One of the best hacks ever a little bug told me McDonald's you get a double cheeseburger but with the Mac sauce on it.
Yeah but you can't do that if you mobile order.
No if you have to ask for it there.
That is a good deal.
You have to vocalize what you want.
It's not like it's not even an app hack.
That's an out loud hack only.
McDonald's app is not as flexible as a Taco Bell app.
Taco Bell app lets you play God and do almost anything you could possibly dream of.
McDonald's app there are limitations on it and that's that's the only failing of it is that it doesn't like Taco Bell.
Taco Bell you can any sauce they have you can put on anything McDonald's doesn't like you have to request the Mac sauce on a double cheeseburger.
Yeah Taco Bell and in and out both in separate ways have embraced the like customize our shit.
You know no crazy sink.
We only have so many things to do whatever you want with the yeah the 20 things something.
Something interesting a little bug told me also about McDonald's.
Go ahead.
This is a weird thing the because he was watching the classic Paul Reiser film Bye Bye Love which he never seen and was a surprise to everyone to realize this like a half hour of that movie set in a McDonald's.
Really is the it's the perfect McDonald's it's the McDonald's you know from commercials it's the McDonald's from Mac and me the weird McDonald's sponsored movie I'm sure listeners know about Mac and me but it's the way that's not just some McDonald's.
That's like a giant sprawling like idyllic garden sun twinkling in from the wind from the giant window.
There's a party going on so like you're like wow this it feels so much like the commercials.
Bye Bye Love is Mac and me is the commercials.
He looked up filming locations city of industry.
What is this place?
There is this McDonald's that is only for commercials in an industrial park in the city of industry.
Less than a mile away from the back to the future mall the point that Hills where time travel is first made possible or I end up there every once in a while just to pay my respects.
But yes so you could you'll be walking down like kind of like a cruddy industrial row and then see a McDonald's sign that's facing the street because they go film on the street a lot.
So anyway there's many people there might even be a listener who's like worked on a commercial or even been in a commercial.
Have you guys been in a mix?
I feel like we know somebody who's been in a McDonald's commercial.
I have not or filmed one or something.
I just if anyone has any more information about the camera only city of industry McDonald's.
This was fascinating to me.
I really want to go if I could get a tour.
Be exhilarated.
I've done chilies.
I've done Taco Bell.
I've done Wendy's.
Wow.
And the Wendy's they just built half a Wendy's in a parking lot somewhere.
Whoa.
And it was open.
So it was open.
So like the other side like at the universal back lot literally like cut a Wendy's in half like a full Synecdoche New York.
Like you're seeing yes half of the building.
The chilies the chilies they built the chilies inside on the Sony lot.
Wow.
Interesting.
We were just in a big sound stage and they built part of a chilies in there.
So that's what we shot in there.
The Taco Bell one I was just in a bowling alley and then the Wendy's.
Yeah they built a Wendy's.
Wow.
And then we shot another exterior part outside of a real Wendy's that was closed for the day.
OK.
So sometimes this is I'm interested in this approach and why yes have one around or not.
The McDonald's one apparently came from that they would ask locations.
Can we use this?
It was initially like a cool thing.
Oh and then mine will be in the ad but then you're losing all that business.
Yeah.
So when Ray Kroc was still around if you've seen the founder you know that he is about he doesn't want to lose a cent.
It is efficiency.
It is the speedy system.
Of course.
This has to run like clockwork.
So they had to figure out we just need a campus we can go to so we're never interrupting business whatsoever.
And then I was reading this article about all this from decades ago and they say how you don't.
The only thing is that this doesn't work for like more like urban locations.
This doesn't look like a city McDonald's.
Turns out now they have one of those.
There's two McDonald's on this property.
This is like this is like a theme park.
This is great.
It's like a literal McDonald's land where the attractions are simulations of McDonald's.
Do they have like a play place on that?
I bet or like it's probably like detachable.
You could probably go in and out with that.
Like if you don't want it you don't have to have it.
Could we like rent that for a party?
Oh my God.
Yeah.
God they're missing out on opportunities.
It's probably just sitting around a lot of the time.
Exactly.
You can't be making that many commercials.
There has to be a day a couple days a week where you could go in and have some adult fun.
Oh man.
With your friends.
Not sexual.
Adult fun in the sense that we're adults in McDonald's.
Yeah just pleasant yeah small talk conversation.
That's right.
That sort of thing.
No let's do stuff in it.
Let's orgy in it.
We got it.
We're going to want it.
It's going to happen naturally.
I'm just going to hose it out anyway.
I would like to orgy an officer Big Mac's mouth.
In the play place.
You'd climb the ladder?
Yeah.
Yeah okay.
Oddly that you know what's funny here I threw out the word orgy but something about that
was a little offensive to me.
I'm like I think that's too sacrosanct.
That's like so from our childhood.
That's so from being three years old.
I should be all for it but I feel like I have to admit that it's like.
You are uncomfortable by it.
That's like coming into my childhood bedroom having sex on the floor.
That's what I wanted to be my bedroom when I was a child.
Oh wow.
So yeah you wanted to sleep in officer Big Mac's mouth.
Oh my god.
Maybe I still do.
And again not.
My rules are clear.
I want to have an orgy in the fake McDonald's but the officer head is off limits.
That's all.
We looked.
We looked this up on the Chuck E. Cheese episode with Jamie Loftus because we found that somebody
was selling all of the McDonald land like play place stuff.
Like a full playgrounds where.
Yeah so you could have bought all of that stuff for.
I feel like it wasn't it was very expensive but not as expensive as I might imagine.
So still I mean there's a house here Scott.
I don't know why you don't have it yet.
Yeah I don't know either.
Look I'm as embarrassed about it as you are.
I'm going to look it up again.
The fake McDonald's sets to simulate real McDonald's.
Like there there is a weird connection there.
There's a weird unease of like Disneyland used to have real covered wetlands.
They had real covered wagons.
Now they have the simulation of a covered wagon that they sell french fries out of that they sell like only a cart.
There's only for only a cart and there's items a fisherman's shed a dock fisherman's shed at the end of the dock which no longer sells French sells seafood.
It no longer sells catch of the day.
It sells french fries and to sunny water or french fries and coffee.
That was the thing about Harbor Galley is that they sold french fries.
They did a bottle of water and then they sold coffee and hot cocoa.
Yeah but no soda.
Weird weird.
Yeah.
I was in coffee.
I don't know.
Yeah.
This happened in my nonstandard meal and like I don't know.
Do people do this.
They don't.
I don't know.
I guess that's not so bizarre but yeah I think you can.
Like if you get a value meal you can select coffee as an option.
I just find like coffee is like with a with a burger and fries like that.
That feels very like this is what an old person would do.
That would be their order at McDonald's to go along with their cigarettes.
You know you could smoke inside and do you have the McDonald's with the little tin foil ashtrays or the gold or ceramic ashtrays.
If I had to be up at all night and then take a lunch at 1 a.m.
Then burger and fries and coffee sounds great.
But I think like not in the middle of the day.
It's only if I have some weird you know all night existence there.
I'm like what's that Scorsese movie where the guys run around.
After hours.
Yeah yeah yeah.
If I'm in an after hours experience then yes I would love to stop for fries and coffee.
Yeah.
I'm having a try.
I can't find a for sale officer Big Mac.
So we missed our opportunity.
I think for now we missed our opportunity but maybe there'll be a sale.
Maybe it'll come back.
It'll come back around.
Yeah well we'll achieve this.
We'll have our own McDonald's one day.
Some of the McDonald's offerings like in Orlando every park had their McDonald's outposts and some of them just had fries and soda.
But like restaurantasaurus next to the dinosaur ride had like it's a dinosaur size like big big burgers.
They had the hot dog the source and that would come with McDonald's fries like a rare McDonald's hot dog weird which I feel like they do test every now and then or they have tested in the past.
Yeah they would test that places like Woodfield Mall.
Sure.
The pizza in there they would test a hot dog in there.
Yeah.
Wow.
The rare the pizza was there.
Yep.
Geez.
Did I have it.
I don't think I did.
The dream I remember being excited to hear they had it.
Unbelievable.
The hot dog a source.
I don't know.
Did you ever see a picture of a hot dog source.
I haven't seen a picture.
No.
I mean I still say that like there are times in California Adventure where it's you know the counter service burgers also kind of hit and miss like we would get one every now and then in Florida at Cosmic Rays because they had the big toppings bar.
But like I'd love to just have a Big Mac in California Adventure have a beer and a Big Mac or like a McFlurry walking around eating McFlurry.
That does sound nice.
You know what you're getting a little more.
But now you got that now you got to pop at you pop at the Denton Disney and you get a burger at you know what's the crazy shake.
Oh Black Tap.
You can get decent but you got but there's no way in between it's either like the crappiest burger or elevated expensive burger.
If tomorrow and that tomorrow and Terrace just had like McDonald's food it would just be so much better.
And I don't think it's because like we've been like slowly like group not groomed by McDonald's to like love that food.
I think it is better tasting than all the food at Tomorrowland Terrace.
Yeah I mean I think one of the things about the Disney McDonald's relationship is like yeah it was a fun special treat when we were younger and they had to play places and the toys were good.
And then there was a point where like McDonald's was going downhill and like I don't know as I was getting older I was like I don't want to eat that crap anymore.
And then like I got older McDonald's like I don't know that they up the quality at all.
I think it just became very consistent like I find it very consistent.
Because there's like Burger King is still wild with their consistency.
McDonald's is consistent.
McDonald's is kind of consistent everywhere.
That's 100% correct.
McDonald's that's their biggest that's their ace in the hole I feel.
Is that like yeah Burger King.
There's a Burger King on Sunset by the old the now shuttered UCB Sunset that I feel like it's in like a little strip mall but you can still drive through it that I don't think I feel like I had like the burger was chilled when I got it once.
Like I touched the whopper and it was like cold like it had been in a freezer.
It's distinctly possible.
Yeah.
Right.
And so like there's some Burger Kings where you're like I don't know what's going on here.
And I'm not I also am not picky.
That's a hard job to do.
As long as you give me like kind of a money amount of food I ordered.
I don't care.
You can get an order way wrong.
It's fine.
Yeah.
But if I touch it and it's like an ice cube or something.
You go.
That's disturbing.
What's going on here?
Because they're keeping maybe McDonald's is keeping Ray's spirit alive.
I think that is maybe what's happening.
Yeah.
They finally remembered their core values.
A great phrase that you hear on undercover boss and such their core values and the spirit of like Disney is better when they remember the spirit of Walton McDonald's is better than the spirit of Ray Ray of weird shyster Ray.
I read and I don't know if this wasn't backed up by any fact but it makes sense that like the reason I think people like these fries in this specific cart was because it was such a small place that there was constant traffic constantly.
Everything had to be made fresh.
Turn everything.
That's turnover.
People would get that.
There was no way you wouldn't get the freshest possible fries and every all the stock coming in was like because they had to continually move it in because it was not much room back there.
And that's all they do.
Maybe something about limiting the stuff means that we do one thing and we get it right.
Yes.
Yeah.
That's that's I'm most curious of that because I have to admit I didn't eat at the fry wagon ever but I'd be curious for respond wherever you respond to us.
If you if you remember this being especially this good it's not just that you think the thing is funny that the food was actually superior.
I'm curious.
That's what I propose is a micro like hyper specific item in places in Disney.
That's what I like.
I like the idea of when we talk at the end here about what we would do now.
I think we should focus on where would you put just chicken nugget chicken McNuggets.
That's interesting.
I mean one thing because this is because the deconstructed McDonald's is an interesting premise.
Yeah.
That's what I think.
Which they could go further with.
OK.
This is great.
Well let's let's hit everything we can about the wagon itself.
Is there anything we haven't read off of the signs because it is.
They're also like OK.
So the other thing with this the partnership there was like the audience was not and people were like OK with McDonald's coming into the parks but we don't want it to be good.
What you don't want is the Golden Arches huge in the theme park and it's why the California Adventure Burger Invasion seemed a little like grosser because it was space ships that look like hamburgers.
Yeah.
The static aside looked at it again today.
So on plea like this.
Yeah.
Pretty pretty indefensible.
Some funny kitschy 2000s is works and this I would say it looks awful.
Yeah.
So that's why one little detail when you look at that that menu that the Golden Arches are just little and tilted next to the word that the word McDonald the term McDonald's french fries is in the middle of the sign.
It's not the first thing up top.
The first thing up top is potato food which is also a great like what we're really like breaking down.
Yeah.
It's all very deconstructed and strange.
But potato food original look here eat hearty round them up seven days a week in that and they captured the way that old fonts and like I'm sorry old posters and old movie trailers was just like how many fonts can we cycle it.
How do we get people's attention with like seven different fonts in a row all with odd declarations but then right in the middle grub and then the Golden Arches but small that now that's not the race spirit I feel is the Golden Arches but small.
So it's it's kind of airing of Disney to recontextualize like that.
Yeah, I'm sure that was a common that was, I'm sure that went back and forth between lawyers for approval on the can we do this with the arch, so you don't want to.
They're still trying to make the sign look somewhat period appropriate, even though they have the logos for all the first right and the other side is very much like a traveling like, you know, medicine man like snake oil salesman.
Prize are always good hungry folks treats manly enough for his hunger and delicate enough for her taste that's weird very weird.
Oh, hurry in for in town for a limited time, which they were right about that eventually they would turn out of here.
It'll give you super strength. Yeah, but it's very much like yeah, but the spark back in the love life.
Vitamin A Benjamin.
Eat the fries in your bed. You'll know why you did you'll be because you're you're gonna want to be there about 20 minutes later.
They really should have added a character to like step right up step right up. Oh my god, that would have been really good. Yeah, it's genuine McDonald's fries right here. It's good for what else you sir what are you worried about.
Daniel Blaine view style Huckster. Yeah, Mac Mac D.
Arnold's the name and he's got a he looks like Mac tonight. He's like Mac tonight but in kind of an older outfit like an older steam punk Mac tonight.
Yeah, Mac tonight. Whoa. So with a top hat over so you can't be he hides his pointy part on top of his head with a top hat with a gear on it.
Brass goggles you sir you and your wife still making love on a regular basis. No.
It sounds like you're not having your recommended daily dose of canola oil or peanut oil, whatever they fry this crap in. Yeah, should have in trouble conceiving well the canola oil might be the key to that too.
Powdered beef supplements. How to deliver in the old bloodstream.
Fried potatoes. Old timer. What's your problem? I'm having problems walking. Well, come right up here. This will put the spring back in your step.
Guy eats fries immediately is able to do a big complicated dance and then conspicuously walks away back into the back of the fry wagon. Yeah, right.
Now we've never met before in our entire lives. Is that correct? Why? Yes, that is correct.
Well funny that we talk similar but otherwise total stranger to me anyway. He looks just like Mr. Six.
Kind of like his suspicious looking face. Is that really a little too old? I'd say.
I think one of the things why people, you know, the Disneyland of Disney is Disneyland is sacred kind of credit defense league was like a McDonald's in Disneyland.
That was just for a long time and probably still is like cultural criticism like a lazy cultural criticism of like, oh, McDonald's like I don't have a television, you know, that sort of like exhausting nonsense.
But at Disneyland, you need to walk like six feet to get a Coca Cola place in your hand. So I don't. Yeah, it seems like it's a lateral move.
Yeah. If like Disney was just serving like high quality like fruits and vegetables and they had all this like classy food and there were no sponsors anywhere.
And it was a it was a nonprofit park. Like, OK, McDonald's rolls in and you go, well, this doesn't make any sense. But the most commercial shit ever. Yeah.
Always has been. Well, and people are like in this era, people are like this. This ruins the immersive theming of the park.
Like the recent incredible Indiana Jones adventure where you walk out and there's like a AT&T ad right after I forget what the ad was for invasive sponsor.
Uh huh. Yeah. Everything had annoying sponsorship and, you know, Kodak was around everywhere.
There's a sprite droid now in the Galaxy's Edge, which I love. I think people really like.
There's no problem there. Now, let me admit this and we can cover the animal kingdom because the animal restaurants were the first burger invasion that happened in the.
That's where they started doing McDonald's in the place. I will admit that it did make that park seem like cheaper and more unpleasant to me that there was so so much McDonald's.
And we talked about like I don't have the best feelings about dinosaur, the ride or the or the baby, a lot of it and the weird.
Remember we talked about the pipes are supposed to be ketchup and mustard and I don't like any of this.
I gotta say, well, Dino Land USA, which has been just changed over the that's also in the perjurer video.
We're entirely sponsored by McDonald's. I think so, but also like that used to be even like worse. I know kids like that and bad.
It would be if you went there with your kid, we fun, but like compared to the rest of animal kingdom, you go, what is this? Yeah, this doesn't fit at all.
Yeah. Um, and the heights of animal kingdom are and have always been like high, like very, very high as with it with Avatar and, um, and the theming and immersiveness has always been great.
But then like when something's bad in animal kingdom and so bad. Yeah, it's in hindsight, it's it's it's kind of shocking that they got animal kingdom through the animal kingdom really feels like if we start comparing things to like albums, music albums, it does feel like a experimental Joe roadie piece.
Mm hmm. That slowly has gotten more like commercially, you know, Everest is a thrill ride and like Avatar and stuff. But yeah, especially early on, it's like this weird. I'm trying to think of a good example of like what's a whatever albums after American Idiot.
I was saying it's been deployed in a fucking metaphor. I said if I was going to do a 21st century breakdown would have already come out of my mouth. There it is. White album like compared to like.
Well, I just mean like it's a little bit less like a structured thing. It's a little more like somebody's put out like a experimental jazz album.
Mm hmm. And they normally don't. They normally have like pop songs or something. Yeah, that's sort of what I'm getting at. And then like all of Prince's crappy jazz. Oh yeah, there you go.
All those crappy jazz albums that we overlook now because we like them anytime. I don't like to think about it. Yeah, that's not like Herbie Hancock got a lot more experimental as time went on or Miles Davis even.
Sure, you know, but those are even I would say like they didn't. I guess they had some songs that are a little more pop. Yeah, they were always jazzed though. But like for Disney to do it like it, you would go and you would be like this feels like a classy animal kingdom.
It's like so authentic in places and and all about conservation, right? Environment and then all and McDonald's. You're the main things you're going to pull out of it, protect the environment and enjoy delicious McDonald's. Yeah, that doesn't make any sense. Yeah.
So I do get why somebody would be like, well, what the hell? McDonald aggressive McDonald's presence in the preachiest park is funny. I've kind of never thought about it. Yes, it is. And I wonder, we got to get roadie now that he's going. We got to get really easy.
Yeah, this might be busy making us preparing for us. He's busy preparing like the pre show for space flight. He's late. Sorry, I can't do the fake space hotel you're working on. I am doing space. I'm doing the space hotel. He brought. What's that gentleman's name in the Avatar pre show?
Dr. Stevens, Wallace Langham, Wallace. Yeah, or an avatar. Oh, wait, oh, Dr. Yeah, whatever. The waiver arms around David Dan, for his real name. Yeah, well, yeah, I think it's Stevens and that's a real. Yeah. But yeah, you're gonna have to waver. I'm around waiting for like a real shuttle space shuttle. Oh, then he's going to be the genuine procedure. That's what I'm wondering. Yeah. Like you'll have to go in a room. They'll have to scan you for bugs. They'll have to scan you for like, like, like a
way of, you know, of when you're locked in a space capsule with people, because he's not the only one they picked up, right. There's multiple. Imagine you're people that I think he worked with. Wow. So yeah, he's creating stuff like that. Like, I think that is part of what he's doing. He is like, he is making sure all the little things around the actual experience, yes, are even like, you know, as long as you're in a room. Yeah. Yeah. We're going to try to figure out some way to work with people to do a space capsule. Yeah, I know. I love it. You got to be able to imagine yourself. And that's what you're going to do. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You're going to have to figure out a way to work with people to be able to work with people to be able to work with people to be able to work with people to be able to work with
pumped up in a way that like Disney has a pre show and waiting for Virgin, correct? I believe. Yeah. Yeah. I liked those planes. I miss. I miss Richard Branson. Come on. Sold it to Alaska. And he's the least hateful of the hateful billionaires. Now he's still bad, but you know what I'm saying? He had good taste in like purple light. I was gonna say he had purple lighting, so I can't hate him completely. Therefore I forgive. But he's not, you know, he's he's annoying and that he'd like go be I'm on 30
rock today. Ha, he's not as annoying as you on on Twitter. I will say Google Richard Branson picking up women and there's just he's holding. He's holding women like he's holding them like you're escaping a burning building. He's like, looks like he just like has a compulsion to like a pick a woman up. There's like a very strange find over 20 photos of different women. He's picking up in like press events and stuff. Okay. He likes to pick up a woman. Literally literally pick up a woman. I'll say this. His company, I think, affected further airline
choices because I was on an American flight recently and I dozed off and when I woke up like there was red lights everywhere and I was like, oh no, what the fuck is happening? And then when I looked, there was white light and then on the other aisle there was blue light. And I was like, are you out of your fucking minds? You had to do red, white and blue lighting. Did you not? You know, red lighting means bad. Like, why would you make this decision? No, I thought you were in a notice dive.
I thought you were having, you were about to have a very important decision to make red or white go to hell or go to heaven.
Pick a side. The devil had like a big thing of fries though. And he's like, Jason, no, they'd split the lighting with like white, blue and red. I was like, guys, don't skip the red. Okay. Blue and white. Like that's enough. Or like just make it blue.
Oh, American Airlines. I, I, it would be so cathartic for me to like an empty American Airlines flight to just take like a sledgehammer to the, I hate American Airlines flights so much. So many bad flights with them.
That's where, oh my my, they're, they're the main airline that serves LA to Philadelphia.
I hate it. We took them back. We took them back from Tokyo and they may as well, but she put me in a trunk. They stuffed me in a trunk for 12 hours. I was assuming on a flight, like a flight, that international flight, that there would be a little bit more leg room in the regular cabin.
No, no, not crammed for 12 hours. Most miserable on the way there. We took Tokyo, LA, oh, delightful. I'm repeating myself. Delightful. Everyone worked there was nice. We got like a great meals.
American Airlines on the way back, the American staff were hostile. They were upset to be on the flight too.
US Airways, this didn't happen. They bought US Airways and US Airways was always a much more pleasant experience.
Yeah.
I feel like.
Oh, it sucks.
Started yelling about them on Twitter. That's the best thing. You know, you got more followers now because of the pod and people love when somebody that you, somebody you're a fan of on your Twitter feed starts yelling at an airline.
Yes.
What a happy day. The people's champion is standing up.
Everyone like finally speaking. Can you hear the people singing? Complaining about airlines on Twitter.
Yes, that's true. So let me do it right now. Several years ago. Your leg room left something to be desired.
Yeah, um, fry wagon. So I, well, I guess I think I brought up animal kingdom to say like, I guess I, you know, I'm not, I'm not entirely, I'm not all for blatant McDonald's and any brand all over the park, but I think this was fun.
Yes.
I think that I think the wagon was fun. Seeing a big Westward hoe was fun. The idea that we're only going to do a single thing is fun. So fun that they did it in Disney worlds. Did that come up already? I don't remember.
I mentioned it in passing, but yeah, each park had some sort of McDonald's thing like Epcot's refreshment port had McNuggets and fries.
Okay. Okay.
Fairfax fries at MGM studios had the fries and soda.
Yeah. Oh, gotcha. Right. Right. Um, they did, but they did the same thing in Magic Kingdom. It's old West and it wasn't a wagon. The thing's not nearly as cool, but at least they stuck with the theming and they stuck with the best. They went even bigger. The phrase is much bigger now.
There's gold in them. Their fries. Uh, it's a great, I love it. Uh, a perfect melding, a true McDisney production.
Beautiful. Yeah. Um, but if I could say maybe this is the place to say that not everybody was so happy. As you were saying, this is going to puncture the perfect little oasis that is never punctured by anything that is Disneyland.
And this was in the late nineties, Paul Pressler era, which was a bummer era. They were cutting a lot of corners. Things were getting grosser. There was a lot more focus on the merchandise and less on rides. It was not, not a lot of attractions we all love came from that era.
And this also coincidentally was the internet era and websites were not what they are. And there was not Twitter yet, but there were news groups and there was something called alt.disney.disneyland.
Place where you could go and yell and complain and be very unhappy, including a 13 year old me. I did this posted on this place. Um, so I have memories of this time and I probably would have been this kind of thing did inform me. What is it?
Disney fans supposed to do is supposed to hate stuff like this. So I don't quite remember this controversy and it actually took a Reddit user who I want to credit named Max Mouse who said, Hey, does anyone remember this thing that happened? And let me consolidate the thing that happened.
So he, he reminded just, there was a thread about the fry wagon. Mostly people like, yeah, that was great. The fries were awesome. But he said, boy, people were not happy on this message board. People would post stuff like quote, is there anything that reminds you of the chaotic world we live in more than McDonald's? Something we see on nearly every corner to which I say person posting that in 1998 buckle up with your chaotic world.
Yeah, re mad about then the president got a blowjob and there's a McDonald's and then things will never get worse than this.
Yeah, but anyways, uh, so people are mad about it. And this one guy is like, Hey, if you're mad, why don't you do something about it? And this was a user on this site named Ebola man.
Uh, man was a poster and he started getting mad about this. Like, Hey, I hear your anger about this cart and Ebola man was already known because he was kind of a little Disneyland rebel rouser, right? He had a site called Disneyland underground intelligence or DUI.
And on the site, he would do bad boy things like how you could not wear a seatbelt on star tours. I'm sure which now you couldn't do because they check and there's a little light. Yeah, but you know, you try to surf it basically. Like, can you ride it like a surfboard?
Uh, or he snuck in, uh, he snuck backstage at Adventureland and stole a phantasmic cast member jacket. This guy's the ultimate thief and villain.
Wow.
So he was already known. People were already like tiske tiske Ebola man. This I don't approve of this. This is merry pranksterism. But this thing was the last straw and he's posting crazy stuff like I swear if they build that cart, I will burn it down.
Or if I'm too pussy to do that, I'll commit suicide in front of the car.
Geez, Louise, man.
This is some Limp Bizkit break stuff energy.
If not that, then I'll break into it when it's closed and ransack spelled bizarrely the insides or I'll tip it over into the rivers of America. Any other ideas? And nobody responded because that's not mostly this is like 13 year olds like me or angry 60 year old.
Uh, people who would never do such a thing, but he eventually posted in October 98 and he said, God, you guys are lame. Oh no, stop it. Stop it. This McDonald's. I'm so upset. Well, hello. There's gallons. Okay. The door to the construction site is never locked. There's gallons of paint in there. Do what I did. Open up one of the paint buckets, stand in the middle and spin as fast as you can.
Seriously, guys, go look at the McDonald's construction site and go in it. You will see a big splatter of black paint and a few more buckets that were spilled. Thanks to yours truly and and jizz M monk who I assume was some compatriot of of a bowl of man.
Anyways, I'm going to post pics soon and blah.
Um, so he went in and defiled the McDonald's fry cart when it was just being prepared. He went in, spun around with a paint can and then apparently several days later posted photos of it and people were grumbling about this. This is not Disneyland behavior. We don't like this.
And it went all the way up to the top. The guy who was responsible, I guess the mod you would say of the message board. Do you know the name of the mod of the message board? It's a name you might know from Disneyland.
Internet lore. I actually think I know. Is it six letters? Al Lutz is the name of the person who was supervising all of this. And he said, not only is this not good behavior for this message board or for Disneyland, but for the world, I am calling the Anaheim police because he left evidence. He took photos of what he did of defiling the fry cart. And soon enough, this guy was taken into police custody.
And this was written about in the OC register and the LA Times. This actually made it a little far. And upon his arrest, what was determined is that he was 16 years old.
That's sent the 16 year old to jail.
Al Lutz ratted out a 16 year old and then was quoted in the article.
He after his little victory, he said the fact that he would show the stuff that he stole. This might be a different thing. He also stole stuff. He would show the stuff that he stole was stupidity incarnate. It was just insane. But I guess he's just a kid.
So this is this Disneyland Internet legend, narked out 16 year old Ebola man because he splashed brown paint on the McDonald's fry. I mean, everyone kind of sucks in this story.
There's no winner. Yeah, there's no winners because it's like, well, man, that paint like workers like regular worker like people have to clean that shit up. But also they're probably like, yeah, okay, whatever. I guess some paint's building. I guess we'll just paint over it.
Like, but then it's just like, oh, yes, you're narking out. It's just ban them from the message board. That would probably annoy him more.
Yeah, yeah. And well, and just like, you lose your D platform. That's what happens to the process here. And then but then you can really create a monster because then though, you know, your weird little YouTube channel, suddenly we might be getting our election conspiracy news from DUI Disneyland Internet.
I accept that apparently in the wake of this, his parents shut down the website because I tried to find that on archive.org and I couldn't do it. No DUIs. But anyway, wild story. Shame on you. Ebola man. Oh, he also like story. He found blueprints. He stole blueprints of it. I think he thought like now they can't build it.
There's no plan. It can't get done. I think he really thought he was going to bring the thing down, which again, I'm not on Ebola man's side, but I admire the spirit that these other people are just complaining and Walt would never run blah. And this guy did something. He snuck in somewhere. He stole the plants.
Yeah.
I don't know. Yeah, I follow a couple of accounts like a couple of accounts that repost screen grab like bad comics takes or cringy theme park. And but like, and it's funny to laugh at most of them. And then every now and then there's one where it's like, okay, this person might be a spree killer one day.
Like it's like you shouldn't be getting this mad about like professional wrestling or like television shows. Like I don't I don't think this is worth this effort. So someone should watch this guy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. The level of rage about a thing that does not deserve rage. Yeah. I mean, it depends though, as the age gets older and the anger still there. That's I think even more. I think is the thing. Yeah. Like, 16 year olds. Yeah.
Dream for a 16 year old what you're describing. But yeah, if it was like a 37 year old, I would say that's more alarming to me. Sure. Well, then let's all kid the next time we're mad about something. Let's all be civil. I like that you can just create that you can just grab paint and twirl.
I like the plan he gave us. He prescribed a little plan. Just take an open paint can spin around. It's a little Bart Simpson hygiene. It's not that bad really. But you're right that ultimately it's not like, you know, Eisner didn't have to go clean it up. Right? Some guy did.
Like I just painted, oh, God, I'm making like $10 an hour. Yeah. And but it did delay the opening of the fry cart and the Fry Car ultimately was taken away because the official McDisney partnership ended. So there was a finite amount of time that that car was going to be open. And he did Rob precious weeks of that time. Yeah. Press weeks, although it stuck around. I it's stuck around till like 2008. I don't know that was still serving McDonald's food. Oh, seven and oh, wait, okay. But it was still serving McDonald's food.
Was there's nothing there now. It's kind of like if we haven't said it was sort of like around the exit of Big Thunder and people would say when you got off the ride around that time, like, oh, I just had a great time on Big Thunder and now I can smell the sweet aroma of golden them their fries walking through the air. Yeah, look, I mean, if you're at a theme park for a day and you're having fun, you're cutting loose. What are French fries and a Coca Cola? That's not a bad like little treat. You know, I get it. You're cutting cut loose.
I would be much more likely to cut loose with some fries than the big pretzel. I like the big pretzel once in a while, but I would be much more likely to cut loose that way with the fries. Well, if we want to cut loose again, if we want to find ways to make McDonald's organically in a classy manner, fit back in the
fries. How about fortune fries? Fortune teller kind of a booth, very small that like is you could make it a machine maybe with an animatronic that probably seems more difficult, but just make it look like a fortune teller booth over in the New Orleans square area. And it just sells fries and you get a fortune on the box on the low. Yes. Yeah, yeah, yeah. So good. And then you that encourages you to keep going back because you get a different thing every time you can get collect all the boxes or there's a new.
Or they're just handwritten scrolls every morning. A bunch of people just write like somebody's got to go custom right. I will do well and an upcoming test of your moral character and we can go anywhere in the anywhere. It doesn't have to be Disneyland. We can think of we can think of. Go ahead and go ahead.
How about this Star Wars long time ago, Galaxy far, far away, far, far away fries. You know, you make the box look stuffed up a little dinged up. You know, what's the where do you get it though? That's sort of like, yeah, so just make it look. That's that's what I think we should focus on is like making it seamlessly blend into the scenery. Well, is it the quarter Porsche? Is it on car plots is on car?
I mean, you could switch out some of those stalls in the suck in the marketplace in Galaxy's Edge. If they want to. Oh, I'm so sorry. I got so excited. It's not a quarter portion. It's a quarter pound with cheese. Oh, our plot is going to sell you. He just has quarter pounders with cheese.
One quarter pounder. Yeah, but it's a good thing. Yes, it's a poor reward for Ray for finalized junk, but that's like you found a lot of great junk if you're getting quarter pounder for it. Quarter pound. Wow. Wow. Yeah, that's pretty great.
Where else do you want to like?
I mean, fantasy land I'm trying to think of. I mean, I would it would it's not practical, but if there was a drive through in the Autopia, suddenly I feel a lot more excited. You get stalled at the end. Yeah, there's like a land that you dedicate a lane to that. You if you go, you pay it's an add on. You pay a little more. But you do get you get frightened. You pull up to a tiny McDonald's.
That now you're that's a dream. Yeah, yeah, it gets the chance to like they like they pay or they then your your kids like I got you, Dad. Thanks, son. I bet you probably have to pay before you pay for the special lane. That's that's could be a lightning lane. Yeah. And then yeah, kid gets to pick up the lunch lane. Wow.
They should add more lanes to the new genie app. Yeah, a lot more lanes. How about this? Laning lane and lunch lane. They're they're redoing to town. Yeah. So I remember you getting a very sad hot dog back there once. And I think they they will need some sort of food thing back there. You got Mickey's house. Maybe there should be a little dinery like 50s looking diner. You got a classic movie theater look to the facade that's coming down.
To Mickey Mickey's Runaway Railway. And you get a box. You get the big you get a Big Mac. But the box is not a regular Big Mac box. It looks like Mickey's gloved hand grabbing it. Well, and they call it the Big Mac. Wow. You're gonna have to massage relations with the Irish community. But I think though, I think you let it slide. How did they do the partnership and not do the Big Mac? Yeah, big. Yeah, that's good.
You could have the signage say like Mickey D's. Oh, that's good. Oh, yeah, it's been Mickey. All this Mickey D's. They were that was the nickname. Yeah. Donald's. I don't know if people say it as much anymore. Wow. But it's not Mickey D's. It's Mickey D's. Yeah. Mickey's. Mickey's. Mickey's. Shout down on Mickey's D. But then you could have Mickey's flurries. What? The McFlurry Mickey's Flurry.
Oh, so anything. Well, Mickey's nuggets. I guess I don't like Mickey's nuggets.
Mickey's nuggets. Grab two of Mickey's nuggets.
Fit them between your cheeks.
It's been 30 years so far. It has. The month has been real. Yeah. All of it. Somebody pointed that out the other day. I'm like, it is true. I don't know what's going on.
The well, speaking of McNuggets, yeah, because if we're piecing off elements, I mean, maybe we haven't cracked like space exactly. Yeah. Why not? Why wasn't why weren't fries in space?
I final fry tier front fry. No, that doesn't.
They don't have Star Trek yet.
I wish. I'm so upset that no one's doing most Star Trek. Yeah, that's yeah. Space has to have something. Is it fries? What's the most space like food at McDonald's?
This one. Well, like fries are I mean, no nuggets kind of look like meteors like you're in a meteor. I mean, I did meteor showers. Right. Burger invasion.
A McGriddle to me is a very spacey like futuristic item to eat because McGriddle has the syrup infused into the pancake, which is the bun essentially on a sausage and bacon cheese sandwich.
Was that their last big innovation? Like scientific, like food wise?
That was the biggest breakthrough as far as science is concerned is the McGriddle. I think if I don't think there was anybody they've had new chicken sandwiches. They've had like tiny Big Macs. Remember they had the three sizes.
I well, yeah, the mini the what were they called? The Big Mac, the King Mac, something like that. The regular Big Mac was the middle size. I love the small Big Mac. Yeah. The mini Mac, I think it was what we're called.
Well, then the you know, Tomorrowland used to have demonstrations, the Hall of Chemistry and all that kind of thing. So it's and it's they're always trying to keep that relevant.
I feel like there's still empty space in Tomorrowland. So it's that you do kind of the 50s, 60s kind of exhibits, but it's a but it's the McGriddle lab. It's a McGriddle.
Watch the creation of a McGriddle. Yeah, it's it's and it's in that sourdough bakery kind of thing where there's people in lab coats. It's not it's not treated like a food preparation place. These are our brightest scientific minds.
It's like the baby raptors at the Jurassic Park. Oh, yeah.
Center and Islands of Adventure, the fake hatchlings. Yeah. But they're making McGriddles. And then you pick one like a lobster. That one's mine. Oh, that's good, too. I was going to say do it like inner space and have it be you start with a big pancake and then they shrink it down and you see it go through like a like a like some sort of a machine. And then that's when you eat it.
You could do it like that. Like they have to get it. They have to start to be able to inject the syrup properly. Starts picking. There's a giant like a giant robot has to pour like syrup on a pancake and then he puts it in a machine and it shrinks it down.
Is there anyone we haven't talked about characters in the McDonald and characters never really been in the parks? Is there something where that's either like a a fight or a team up or even a Daffy Donald style dueling piano?
Is there a Disney character who would pair well with a grimace or a birdie? I feel like I'm not I'm not coming up with it. I feel like Eeyore and Grimace are buddies. Oh, sure. Two depressed characters.
What if they believe it's that implies that you'd be back in in the critter country where Winnie the Pooh is and that's where the our beloved country bears were in Big Al. Let's get him back too.
And it's like a really depressing. It's like a like one of those like jazz piano bars. That's the blue note where it's all dimly lit and like the blue part of an American Airlines plane and big boy season all year round.
Get yourself a big boy.
Yeah, like a really seedy sad jazz club where you go here. Standards depressing standards by Eeyore, Grimace and Big Al.
That's good.
Can you put like Mack tonight with Sonny Eclipse?
Oh my God. Yes, dueling piano. Yeah, right. Oh my God. That's the way to make both of them relevant. Right. Take both of their crumbling kitsch appeal and shove them together. There's an image. There's a at least a long time ago. There was a non functioning Mack tonight.
Not playing a piano in a crazy McDonald's in a non standard McDonald's in Orlando. If that guy is still rotten away, replace his hands, make him go again and they duel piano of an alien and a moon. They'd be they'd have so much to talk about and so many puns to say that really it's like Godzilla versus Kong where it's like rising tide lifts all ships. You're you're bringing you're making both these guys look good.
You know, broken franchises a little bit, but you combine their might and now they're bigger and better than ever. Yeah. And cosmic rays is awful. The food. Yes. So change it to best improvement. Change it to full McDonald's.
All right. Wait there was that topping bar does so much for you. The toppings bar is frozen. I just had chicken fingers and fries because I had not had like, aren't they the same as like Tomorrowland fries? Like there's something that special about them.
No, they're not that. Yeah, they weren't that special. I mean, my dad and brother like they had burgers. They like them. You're gonna tell me you've had it recently and you think it's like better than McDonald's.
Uh, well, I think the chicken that there sometimes you want a chicken finger. Sometimes you want a chicken nugget. And I know you know what I'm talking about, Scott. I don't know that you know what I know. But I know what you're talking about, but I've never had a good meal.
The place right. I don't really know you've you're more than you have a chicken sandwich there and it was fine. I didn't throw it up, but it wasn't better than the McDonald's chicken sandwich. Yeah, I think I think people really like that topics more though. So you talk about it.
So I think it's doing all the work. The topics are free in a Disney park. You're taking the tongs and you're taking another piece of lettuce. You're thinking like it's an extra couple cents and you're taking an extra. You're like thinking of the value. You're gaining your sense back now. See that. And they used to sell for years and years. They had cheese steaks there that were pretty good. And that was better than a standard fraud. You're not signing off on cosmic
rays becoming McDonald's. Well, I don't see. But then they're not going to give your not eclipse. They're not going to give sunny eclipse. But if they shine tonight with him. Yeah, that's part of the day. That's step one of the deal. Okay, that's the priority. Step two is all right. Maybe we get your McDonald's food in there if we can. I if you're going to do that, I think you have to then have the hits. You have to have Big Mac's McFlurries. You have to add the and I stand by. I think the regular McDonald's cheeseburgers better than the quarter pounder.
But I think you need both of them in there. You get a more you get more of the ketchup on a regular cheeseburger. Yeah, I think the texture is better, too. But I honestly I think the double the double cheeseburger, though, is different. I think if you get the right double cheeseburger, especially with the Mac sauce, I think that might be the ultimate taste.
I think you might be right. I don't like that quarter pounder meat. That fresh quarter quarter frozen meat, double cheeseburger meat, I think is different than the quarter pounder meat. And I but I think it is. I think in the Big Mac meat is different. Is it like different meat? Really? It is. I don't know if it's just a preparation. I'm not exactly sure what it is, but there is how much raccoon is in it. Yes. Is it 80% or 95% is really I think the big Mac patties are just the cheeseburger patties.
So you like those patties? I like those patties. You're getting Yeah, they're thinner patties. Yes. And I think the thicker ones are better. I can think of the double cheeseburger ones are better. They feel like more meat to me. Okay, they feel more real. This is too testy in here. You guys are both going to go do some shootings or something. This is these are bowl of mans waiting to happen. Yeah, when you the hot the only way we're gonna relieve the tension is driving through McDonald's right now.
Which I have eaten McDonald's a number of times in my car outside of your house. Oh, I love waiting. Really? Well, I'm listening to my my stories listening to my podcast.
Wait out front and eat McDonald's. I want to listen to my show. I've done it. Yeah. I've done it too. I'll see the Dorsey Brothers.
I eat an impossible burro big whopper a couple weeks ago out in front here. Jeez. Yeah. Yeah. You can come in though. I love you. I know you like I know it's I love eating fast food in the car. Yeah, I
That's kind of part of it. Yeah, part of it for me. So there is something fun about it. I don't know what it is. But is it better or worse than eating fast food that came from a wagon and probably you don't have like a table to sit at.
As might be a deficiency of it. But knowing that your fries came from a wagon has to be the best way to get fries that there. I bet that's true. And I'm sad that I missed it. Yeah, I'm sad that I didn't do it. I mean, I do. I had no excuse. There's that's one of the many things like the Star Trek experience in Vegas where I was like right there. I think I think you're right.
We didn't do it. And I regret it. I stayed at the hotel when it was open and I didn't do it. We were fools. We're all fools for so many years, but we're no fools now because we get together and we talk about these things. We talk about the fry cart for a while. You survive.
I guess the ride that makes sense. That adds up that if you if you delivered that it'd be interesting to predict the times before we do them. 90 seems right. Yeah. McDonald's wise, we really haven't even though we talk about McDonald's all the time, we haven't done enough and we haven't gotten close to the real juice.
The characters, the 70s versions versus 90s. We just learned about Burger King knockoff. Some of these knockoff characters. Yeah, on the George Lucas talk show, which in the in the plug pile, if you didn't see us on there, that was a ton of fun. And that's up on their YouTube. But yeah, so much McDonald's to come and so much restaurant stuff to come. Maybe McDonald's might eat in there. I'm not totally sure. We will see. But this is maybe we could do a slightly bigger one.
So here's your plug here for what's coming up next week. Might bear mentioning. Look at your calendars. What is it next week? Well, that's the start of February. But it's not just that. It's so much more than that. February is celebrity podcast. The rides celebrity restaurant month.
This is something we have been talking about for a while. We've delayed a bunch. I feel like we delayed it because we kept the parks are back open and we got to talk about that and diseases and blah. But it landed exactly where it needed to land because celebrity and February go together like fries and wagons.
What I am saying is that we are back on the theme bus. We are doing an entire theme month that is both main feed and second gate where we are covering the many great restaurants owned by various celebrities, themed restaurants owned by celebrities. Would you say? Well, not always. This is kind of an interesting thing to part. I think a lot of the time. Yes, I'd say. But I don't really know some of these that we're going to learn about. I don't know how heavy they are.
I don't know how heavy the theming was, but I think a celebrity in and of themselves lends some theming to it, especially because they're bringing like their persona and what you know him from from their show or movie or whatever it is. I mean, there's there's restaurants owned by all manner of celebrities and we're going to talk about a ton of it. There's some I think big exciting topics that we're heading for. How you guys are you excited about celebrity? I am excited about it. This actually probably great warm up.
I'm excited for it. Great food based warm up and I don't think we even consciously made that choice. It flows. I think very, very well. So stay hungry. We got a regular main feed. That's a lot of fun that is not.
Well, there's a little food in there, but but then and and again, you know, hey, look, we're not stepping on the doughboys territory. These are not exactly restaurant reviews. I'd say we're so much more about the theming and the culture surrounding the places.
And, you know, and most of which probably weren't chains. Some of them, I don't know. You could I the listener could maybe guess some of these, but I can't imagine all of them.
Yeah, some of these, especially on the second gate, will show up in your inbox and you'll go, I guess so. But I swear. But buckle up, because I there's not one thing that's in the in discussion for us talking about it that I'm not pleased about.
Yeah, some of them are very bizarre and then some of them are theme park adjacent, both figuratively and literally.
So, yes, absolutely. Yeah. And some are close to almost nothing on this or some are a real real journey to get to. I think you know what I'm talking about. I don't want to spoil anything.
It's all man. There's so much in here and but we'll get into it. That'll that'll take over the main feed next week, the first one of February.
And then you can keep listening to those on the second gate as well. That's where we really go deep on these.
The wonderful world of celebrity restaurants. So get excited, everybody. I am. So keep it tuned here, I guess, is the main instruction, because all your favorite stars will be popping up.
Favorite doing some heavy lifting.
Yeah, knowing what we know about who it is, especially on the second gate.
I mean, I'd love to meet the people who would describe these people as their favorite stars. It might be you. It might be the listener.
I hope it is. Like I said to my dad, describing him some of the restaurant of source menu, I was like that manor in orange Chinese chicken salad doing some heavy lifting on that menu board in terms of actual food.
Mm hmm. Yeah, well, heavy hitters doing heavy lifting all month long. Keep it tuned here and to the main feed. It's going to be a hell of a month. So long.