Forever!
Dog!
Hey folks, we're here at Podcast the Ride's celebratory event where the brightest stars
in Hollywood sky are out for the Planet Hollywood episode featuring restaurant maven and self
proclaimed sicko Robert Earl, chicken tendies covered in Captain Crunch, and a disconnected
New York telephone number.
Pat Castles joins Mike, Scott and Jason here on Podcast the Ride.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride Presents Celebruary, a month long celebration of celebrity owned
restaurants.
I'm Scott Gardner and I just want to let you guys know right away, I feel like maybe there
is some kind of celebratory curse that has befallen myself, that has previously befallen
you guys because for once I am the one who is dealing with big stomach issues.
I don't know what happened to me and I think maybe, I think it could be because of what
we're doing because we're talking about so many insane bad restaurants.
So, this is maybe prime among them.
For further thoughts, let me go to last episode stomach issue have Jason Sheridan.
Scott, I am on the exact opposite footing now.
I feel great.
I have since had Taco Bell again and felt perfect, felt fine, and I could not be more
excited for today's topic.
One of my rider dies and I know I'm going to be alone in that respect.
Oh, hang on.
Well, now let me, now I'm referring to the food only, but I'll take that.
I'm going to go to bat for some of that too.
To the food too, no kidding.
Not all of it, but some of it.
I'm excited to hear, but let me second you in the ride or die for this topic.
I am thrilled.
I'm not sure I've had so many tabs to pull open.
We'll see how many we'll get through, but let me check in on excitement level and stomach
health level with Mike Carlson.
Hi, I'm here and yes, my stomach is fine.
I feel like it's been better.
I feel like I needed a lot more sleep yesterday.
I played tennis yesterday and as an old man.
It's still tennis in 2022.
I'm back to playing.
I took a couple of months off because of my Achilles tendons, but it was a feel, but now
my shins seem to be sore, but I feel like the tiredness is affecting my whole body.
My stomach, I would say is medium.
It's fine.
It's not bad, but it's not like, it was a little gurgly after I had some lunch, so it's
not perfect.
But yeah, I would think after looking at pictures of all these menus, I'm a big psychosomatic
illness.
I believe that happens a lot with people.
So Scott, I think if you're seeing all of these pictures of blue drinks, like I know
you don't you specifically like blue drinks, I feel like makes your stomach turn.
So I feel like perhaps it's now been sort of like your brain is now playing tricks on
you as if it's digesting one of these delicious sugary alcoholic beverages and you're almost
going through, you're having a phantom digestion.
I think that might be it.
Yeah, yeah.
And which could have something to do with looking at the exteriors or interiors of these
restaurants.
Now, again, I'm not, these are not bad things necessarily.
Again, I'm thrilled to be talking about all of it because today is Planet Hollywood.
It's the big dog.
It's the, in a month of celebrity owned restaurants, it is the biggest restaurant owned by the
most celebrities, sort of, I guess, to varying percentage degrees.
And we've got a great guest joining us from a city that is home to one of the few remaining
planet Hollywoods in the world slash the country.
You're very lucky.
So we need to know what that's like.
I'm talking about New York City and the guest I'm talking about is a Emmy winning writer
for Full Frontal with Samantha Bee and a before that a longtime writer performer for College
Humor.
Hi, Pat.
Hello.
Thanks for having me.
Absolutely.
So thrilled to be here.
Until you told me.
I didn't realize that.
I did not know there were so few lefts on the planets, on our planets.
And I want to break the bad news to everyone that there is recently, seemingly one less
left that very Times Square location.
What?
Yeah, I did.
Yeah.
Wait, wait.
So I'm wrong.
So there isn't one in New York?
It's temporarily closed.
Is it closed?
It's temporarily closed, but the phone is also disconnected.
I called.
You called them?
I called because I had heard a podcast.
I had heard on the podcast what a time to be alive.
They casually mentioned the Times Square planet Hollywood being closed.
And then there was a massive article about planet Hollywood from not too long ago in
Esquire where they're talking about planet Hollywood during the pandemic in New York
doing takeout.
But it's seemingly not open now.
And it's not on the website at the moment.
It's not on the official website.
It's off the planet Hollywood website.
Oh, oh, that's good.
I man, I was there.
I went there pretty close to like beginning of pandemic, weirdly enough, just like it's
probably like one of the last restaurants I went to before March 2020.
So you could have been one of the last ever.
You might have been one of the final diners.
Maybe.
I don't know.
Well, it was open then.
Yeah.
Google says temporarily closed, but I don't know.
Maybe it's it certainly doesn't seem Times Square seems like a lot of turnover happens
there.
Yeah.
And being that it's all like the property values there have to be crazy.
And I feel like even I think during pandemic, like the whatever the landlord was sued this
location for.
That's right.
Okay.
Sure.
It's one of those.
Just a casual five million dollars in back rent.
That's going to be a frequently said stat, I think, throughout this month.
There's a lot of that.
I well, then, well, why don't why don't we start there?
I mean, we can dive into your feelings about the place and any history you have, Pat.
But like, what's give me the latest?
What was it like as close to the pandemic and possibly the closing as it could have
been?
Well, we I normally go to those restaurants in Times Square.
Anytime I see I don't see that many theatrical plays or musicals, nor do I go to MSG that
much.
So when I do, though, I always try and pair it with a outing to some kind of Times Square
restaurant just because it's like, I'm here.
I'll never be here.
You know, I'm here once a year, Times Square.
And so I think we were seeing.
No, we were seeing Beetlejuice the musical.
Oh, great.
What an either juice musical.
And we were like, let's just go here.
It was it was pretty empty.
It was quite empty.
There was a dude there working like on a laptop, like in the corner, which is kind of a bad
sign for like a fun restaurants and like a family fun.
Like it's supposed to be every table's crawling with birthdays and celebrations.
Yeah, it was definitely not at its best.
It was like definitely not full.
But I'm not sure when the last time it was full ever.
I'm not really sure.
Yeah, maybe opening night.
And that was it.
Well, they had mostly celebrities are there.
They had 14 different Hollywood stars there.
Right. Yes. Yeah.
These. Well, I think they all started strong and then it's a slow diminishing this already.
That location, the New York one currently or maybe not currently is like a downsize
already. That isn't the original one.
The original New York restaurant was the first planet Hollywood ever.
And it moved to a smaller one still in Times Square.
But that's kind of like a like a duplex, a sublet.
I don't know what you want to call it with Bucatubeppo.
Like you enter this weird little alleyway and then you go one direction, I think, for Bucatubeppo
and the other way for planet Hollywood.
So it's already sharing the space and we're like cramming the props together much more.
You don't know which way it's going.
It's kind of like a mystery.
Like it's a it's a it's a it's a coin toss.
They keep it deliberately confusing.
I was on the like as empty as it was, though, it's still like
all the props that were there when they stopped being popular are still there.
So it still has that.
I you were saying earlier, the ambiance is like food, notwithstanding the ambiance rules.
And like if you're like I am, I assume you guys are like a really big fan of like mid
90s Hollywood. It's like the perfect museum.
I'm sure we'll get into all this and like what's actually there and stuff like that.
But it was. Yeah.
So for me, it was just like a great museum to walk around and be like,
oh, it's this, it's that, it's whatever.
Yeah. Yeah. Did it?
Did anything stand out?
Do you recall anything from from the real big one was we were eating on
like literally we looked at we were eating lots of, you know, like probably
17 terminator things is like the first thing you say.
And then we realized halfway through we were eating under
there's a lot of ceiling stuff.
If you look up, there's a lot of like the bus from speed is like
literally hanging above you.
But it was my favorite thing was Dorothy from Twister.
You know, Dorothy.
Oh, the like the machine with the machine.
Yes. Wow.
Geez. The Dorothy.
The full Dorothy, you're saying, because Dorothy.
OK, remind me, Dorothy is the machine, but there has the little like balls.
That was exactly what I'm not sure the balls were in there, though.
OK, because I really the balls for me would be the big draw.
That's killer. Yeah. As far as Dorothy's concerned.
And if you're in the mall, the little professor, right.
Right. Yeah.
They would spin inside the to this.
I can't confirm the presence of the little individual things in there.
OK, well, Jason, we'll get on the phone again, hopefully if they reopen.
I mean, I kept trying.
I kept looking.
There weren't a lot of reviews recently.
You know, then lots of information about the Malta one on the website.
The newest, the newest one opened in 2015.
Malta. Malta. Yes.
The small island of Malta. Yeah.
New that before that, the Los Angeles International Terminal at LAX.
Mm hmm. But these the thing with these is it's not the it's not the trash.
It's not the like the like the room with too much going on
and props exploding off of every wall and like big
kooky sunglasses in the bathroom and that kind of thing.
I think like the the new vibe is like the vibe of everything in the in the 2000s
and 2010 is very sleepy and just kind of sleek.
And like like the Vegas one was another move where it was a big, crazy, trashy one.
And now it's like a much smaller.
It does feel like an airport restaurant.
So I don't like this. That's happened to the brand.
Yeah, I remember being at Caesars in college and going like,
oh, my God, there's a planet Hollywood and watching them watching like in the middle
of all these expensive shops as they just dropped a planet Hollywood
and then watching the walk through like in the opening.
It's like, oh, my God, it's across from a Brookstone and down the way
from a Warner Brothers store.
This is the most 90s time capsule footage I've ever seen.
Yeah, the new ones have like legitimate Hollywood props in them
like the way the old ones do.
Not yet. Not a lot.
I mean, I excitedly texted my girlfriend like there's still one in Vegas,
the one in Caesars. It moved. It's still there.
It's at the top of the spiral escalator at the forum shops.
And it seems like they have a few, but the one in LAX does not appear
to be decorated at all.
Yeah, it's just like primary colors.
It's really boy looks like a weird like an office lobby.
It's it's it's so I thought you meant the 90s movie primary.
Now, Scott, that would be a big get if they had some primary colors.
I'm sure one of them has like, you know, John Travolta's Blazer or
from the way the way he is where the white wig.
I just I assume he died his hair.
Maybe he was died. Probably a real hair.
Yeah, yeah. I don't know much about that.
That's the perfect kind of my favorite props there are like not the Terminator
skeleton. It's like the really random forgotten movies.
There's a there's a great I think it was on air.
Jason, you probably heard the story a million times.
There's an unaired UCB show sketch
that Walsh and Besser did
where they did a prank and it was at a planet Hollywood.
And basically what the gist of it was is they made a giant fake glove
that looked like maybe like a Mad Max, like Spikes Road Warrior.
And they they snuck it into the restaurant.
And all of a sudden, like when they made sure no waiter was looking,
they just dropped it on the table and pretended one.
It fell on one of them.
And like, I forget if there was fake blood or not, but like,
it's like Walsh or Besser was like, oh, this fell.
So like all of a sudden, people were freaking out, like running over to them,
like worried about like, you know, getting sued or whatever.
And they I forget if Besser and Walsh was like, we kept asking over
and over again, oh, what movie is this from?
What movie is this?
I don't even know what movie this is from.
But then I guess somebody found out and they could never
they never got the rights to air the the prank or anything.
I mean, like to go there, it is a very ceiling.
The ceiling is just filled with stuff in that place.
It's like everything's hanging from
another thing that the New York one was the independent,
all the little miniatures from Independence Day, like the spaceships and stuff are there.
Wow. Yeah.
It seems like a high, high probability of of a prop falling on you.
A nude, semi nude is it was it Stallone?
Like a mannequin, like a body double of a mannequin of like Stallone
and a speedo from I don't know if it was Demolition Man or something.
He's naked in Demolition Man because he's in the when he gets frozen, he's naked.
He gets frozen.
It's a cryogenic tube.
I think he in the movie, I assume he's just naked.
But they in the restaurants, they had to put in like black fabric
to cover up the crotch zone.
And one thing this was one where I was I kept thinking, like,
I feel like I've seen that at every one of them.
And I was looking around other comments, places that said, yeah,
I've seen this at every one.
I think this is one of the mass produced.
Every single planet Hollywood had the naked, which you could eat.
A family could eat directly under
a tube with Stallone naked and been weird fluid.
And I have.
I have. Maybe more than once.
Wow. Are you saying, am I naive?
Are you saying like they reproduce the stuff?
Some of them, because I also I remember always thinking.
That's OK. It's a little heartbreaking. That's fine.
I mean, I don't think all of it.
But at least that one feels like it was everywhere.
And don't you guys feel like, I don't know, we can get into which planet
Hollywood's people have been to.
But I feel like even as a kid, I was like, boy, there was a lot of
a lot of Terminator robots.
Seems like there are enough to go around.
I get Judge Dredd to I would say I feel like there were a ton of Judge Dredd
suits. They may have needed him for the movie.
But that yeah, that naked Stallone tub.
I don't I don't have a good feeling about that.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
I think this is just in case.
Yeah, I have a photo of it here.
I'm assuming this is the one you guys are talking about.
Oh, that's a worse photo than I had seen.
That's a particularly odd.
He's like, maybe he's really straining.
Yeah. Yeah. So he's I just want to sketch this out for the listener.
Imagine like a slightly taller baby pool that is clear and you can see through
the sides and it is no water in it.
And there is a really realistic wax figure of a naked Sylvester Stallone
with just like maybe a sock covering his penis.
A black, it looks like half of a thong.
Yeah, he looks like he was maybe like there was some sort of like he was killed
in the middle of a pose somehow, like he got shot by like a death ray
and it froze him in this position.
Yeah. And he's like, yeah, like this.
You're seeing the last moment of his life as he was like panicked,
naked with a sock covering his genitals.
I also believe he's in this plexiglass like bowl.
You can actually if you pay enough, they will fill that with liquor
and you can drink it like a scorpion bowl.
It's the most expensive thing you can get at Planet Hollywood.
Yeah, Bachelorette parties can can get it.
It's a big package, part of the package, and they can.
Yeah, they can actually get in the pool with him.
Drink it out. Yeah, yeah. Drink it out off of his butt.
Bachelor parties can pay
and they don't get a drink, they just get to borrow the casual slacks
from the hangover, which I saw the New York location.
There's a there was a video walkthrough from a few years ago, and it's like,
wow, they have all the casual wear from the hangover, like all the main guys,
all their polos and Oxford shirts and khaki slacks.
Wow. OK.
Now, does that include the baby Bjorn that Alan has or?
It just seemed like they had the busy graphic tea he wore.
I was hard to tell.
I don't think it had the baby Bjorn.
Are you there? I love the least.
So the only actual notable piece of wardrobe from that movie
they don't have.
Just like, yeah, just the business casual clothes.
But they have those.
That's true. They do have the clothes.
They have at Helms's Polo.
The plain shoes they wore, the old all the notable wardrobe.
I there's going to be a lot of screen sharing happening here.
And I I would like to share a little because I I got to go to the New York
location a little bit
a little further in time, which was for my this was in May 2019.
And my wife and I were celebrating our fifth wedding anniversary
and we did so in New York City.
I don't look it would be kind of on brand to say that we did
the dinner at Planet Hollywood, but I'm not that bad of a husband.
We were on our way to the good dinner that we got.
And it went like walking towards it like, yeah, but we should do.
Oh, yes. Yeah.
So I might if we go the other way on the stairs real quick.
No, it seemed so like, oh, what a good way to kick it off
would be with with champagne from the Planet Hollywood bar.
So really quick, here's
do I have too many tabs open where I can't even showing me the the eye photo?
Yeah, possibly.
Well, here we go.
It was minimized.
So here's some some memories.
My wife and I am like super thrilled to be there.
Yeah. And strolling behind you was the the like Walk of Fame, but on the wall.
Oh, yes, that's not because the other the way there's a thing to point out
decor wise is that they've always had hands and cement
all the Chinese theater in Hollywood, but they put them up.
They put them up on the wall and they and they kind of put them diagonal.
And that's their their twist.
But in this case, though, like to get it super current and or futuristic,
they're like LED.
What do you do?
They're they're like not even hologram.
Those aren't as cool as hologram.
I don't know. But technically, yeah, it's celebrity handprints back there.
I don't know who of who this point at this point, like, do they really
does anyone know Planet Hollywood favors today?
I forget. I mean, we took a photo and my friends and I last time we were there,
we took a photo in front of that thing and I can't remember.
I mean, it's probably like, you know, it's the usual suspects of like
Schwarzenegger, Stallone, Willis, Julie Roberts, maybe.
Yeah. Yeah. Melanie Griffith.
Yeah, exactly right.
I try to get who's like a who was a rising star then that is no law.
Like, I don't know.
I think I'm in Terry Casper Vandeen.
Casper Vandeen. Yeah.
Lori Petty, Tank Girl, John Claude Van Damme and a lot of the opening.
Lori Petty, Roseanne and Sinbad
at the TV special for the Beverly Hills Planet Hollywood Comes Home.
Oh, yes, of course.
A fine, fine piece of primetime programming.
So so here's here's some other favorites.
Here's us strolling the not the red carpet.
It's kind of red carpets, the red zebra carpet.
And it's also the red, the dirty red zebra carpets.
This is pretty ghastly.
The entire staircase up is done in this pattern.
And boy, is it walked on.
Boy, is it movie theater style?
But that's what you want, right?
That's the actual carpet from Monkey Bone.
Sorry, I'm not sure it was a zigzaggy like.
Wow. The kind of carpet that Chris Katana or whoever would have in their house.
It's the dirty carpet from Monkey Bone.
Well, then I shouldn't have walked on it at all.
I wish they told me how to put a sidestep.
Yes, the carpet.
Thanks for your service, carpet.
But then props.
What was stuff that I liked?
I'm going to go in order of impressiveness.
I'm of course, of course, wonderful to see a gray sports
almanac from my favorite movie Back to the Future 2.
Who knows how many of those there are?
Say these are the time it does.
And they're there. They're a dime a dozen.
But I'm hoping I can I can trust him on it.
We got Foxy Cleopatra's wardrobe from Goldmember.
Roster Powers 3.
I mean, that's pretty cool. That is great.
That kind of gives you a sense of like when they stopped updating.
Like that feels current in Planet Hollywood.
World is 2003 or so.
So like the only place in the world that's like we have Beyonce's wardrobe.
No, not from over concerts from Goldmember from Goldmember.
Well, it was it's an important movie from New York because the summer of 2002,
we were finally able to laugh again.
Yeah, Jason, 911 Context sure.
Thanks to Mike Myers and his beloved character, Goldmember.
It's almost like the guy from Planet High was like, wait, she's a musician, too.
Someone told the hard rock.
So what else we got?
I mean, this this also feels current in this is seeing a big 98 Godzilla.
Yeah. And elsewhere from the Emmerich Devlin universe.
I think I see some of those Independence Day things back there.
But you were mentioning, oh, yeah, you're right.
You have no. Sorry. I need to jump on that. Sorry. No, no, no.
We got a we got a tool time hammer. Oh, wow.
And tool time hammer.
That hammer touched by a grap.
This is like, you know, Thor has a hammer and Richard Karn.
This is Richard Karn's hammer magic hammer. Right.
And it's more important to me than Thor's hammer.
Yeah. And when everyone cheered, when Tim Allen got to pick up the hammer,
that's right. That was a big remember that like Captain America. Yeah.
I didn't realize they had TV memorabilia.
I thought it was just movies.
It's a little bit. Yeah.
Primarily movie. I'm trying to think if there's any other.
Well, you know what I know they used to have.
And I think this might this might actually now this might have moved in
and now is in the studio or the office where they make the show.
But I know that when I was a kid, I was a gog
because they had the original weekend update sign from Saturday Night Live,
like the Chevy Chase.
It was up. What was up on the wall behind?
I think maybe now that's now back in the offices, but that's a legit cool one.
And for a little comedy dork, me at 13.
Oh, my God. The Chevy Chase sign.
Yeah, that's I I will say I did go to Planet Hollywood as a child,
but I don't really remember anything and feel like I wasn't like
they didn't have anything Batman in there that was going to impress me.
And whatever the year was, did they not?
That feels like a given that Batman returns.
I wonder. Yeah.
Well, but did you come across a fact, Mike, that they hired
the production designer from the Tim Burton Batman?
No, I didn't. To design the Times Square.
And that's why there's all seemingly why there's all these girders
and bent metal and stuff.
And as I always was like, this is like Gotham.
There's a little bit of Batman in this design
in between the multicolored zebra prints and the giant collages
and circular screens, which is more like Batman villain, I guess.
Like it's it's a clash of hero and villain within the restaurant.
Spices carpet in Batman forever.
Debbie Mays are spice character.
Oh, of course. Right.
That's the two face had two girlfriends.
Yes. To Barrymore with sugar and Debbie Mays are with spice.
And yeah, she would have had like a animal print carpet.
I imagine it does seem like Planet Hollywood is the only place in the world
that specifically like it's not into it's kind of.
It was too early for the Chris Nolan Batman's
and it was too late for like the Tim Burton Batman.
So it kind of only likes those like Joel Schumacher Batman's.
Right. And do they have like the old Batman?
Do they have like Keaton's Batman suit there?
They've got to have some remnants of that.
I just see that like 95 96 is that Schumacher era where they were
when, you know, Planet Hollywood could get whatever they wanted.
That's perfect timing. Yes.
Well, there are no aesthetically so much like the Schumacher,
like the like so busy and multiple levels and lights flashing.
And that's what Joel Schumacher's brain looks like.
Yes, you should have.
Joel Schumacher should have been a day one Planet Hollywood guy.
Oh, yeah, he should have gotten some some Ponzi scheme shares.
Yes. So I have a quote.
The name is Anton First.
He was a set designer behind Tim Burton's Batman.
And the quote from him in the Esquire article, his mandate
first told Esquire in 1991 was to quit, was great.
A fun place for the Jeans Brigade, not upmarket or smart.
Huh? The Jeans Brigade.
I think that's like, you know, the hoy polo, you know, the the the common man.
Oh, wow. Interesting.
So that's because they wear blue jeans.
I guess that's what I had never heard the phrase Jeans Brigade
to refer to, like the middle class.
Wow. Interesting.
This guy, this guy only did the first Batman.
Yes, because it's a very sad story because he like got weird issues,
prevented him from working on returns and that bummed him out.
And then he tried to he was going to direct a nightmarish sounding
Michael Jackson movie called Midnight with a K and no one.
Where's the K?
I guess before the end.
It's not hiding somewhere you wouldn't expect.
Who knows? I first said it's actually instead of the eye.
It's a K. Makes no sense.
Bidden to big neck height is an experimental title.
No. So he like I think he took this planet Hollywood job
because his like other projects weren't taken off.
And then he did it and was like battling some crazy demons.
And a month after the opening of the first planet Hollywood,
he threw himself off of a building and killed himself.
It's really crazy and a bummer to bring up.
And I don't want to be disrespectful to this this death that occurred.
But what I found this is this, I think where I really got fascinated
with planet Hollywood as an adult was I was on my way.
I knew I was going to see one at at Disneyland Paris, where there still is one.
And I was reading old articles like, that's crazy.
They still have a really locked in time planet Hollywood.
And this article that I read from Los Angeles magazine almost implied
that the decor was so bizarre and depressing that it like
that he like it like
impacted the person getting depressed and committing suicide.
That seems like impossible.
That seems like a major jump for the writer of this article.
Because conversely, like the
Orlando and Vegas ones would go on to become
the highest grossing restaurants in the country.
Like it was very successful, insanely popular and like filled
with celebrities for a long time before they, I guess, overexpand it.
And then their revenue dropped like an insane amount.
It went from like 12 million in one year to four million
the next like fiscal quarter.
Like it was an insane drop.
I agree. I guess the only way it could even it's depressing is that
it is kind of like a Norma Desmond house where it's just like literally
you're reliving your old Hollywood memories, like
it's a museum of like Hollywood's faded past.
Yeah.
Trumbling remains of what we now know is like a business
that's like in peril in certain ways.
But I think Jason's right there.
I mean, it seems like back then it certainly would have been.
I mean, I'm sure we'll get into this, but like
it seems like for at least a week, it was like the coolest place in the world.
I my my memories of it is my family was like all in.
If we we went to the Orlando one a number of times,
if we went to a city, we and there was a plane of Hollywood near where we were.
We were probably going to eat.
I ate at the Washington, D.C. one.
I've been to Times Square twice.
And we always had a nice time.
It was very fun.
We were all very fond of the Captain Crunch chicken.
Which I let's let's let's stop here.
Let's pause here for a minute.
I guess it's going to make Scott's stomach worse.
Yeah, I don't want to get ahead because I'm saying so I'm saying let's stop here
because I have to go to the bathroom.
Everybody hold tight for 20 minutes.
Sure.
I'm going to vomit because of that chicken description.
Just the hearing the the title of it.
So, yeah, food wise, I was trying to remember what even they had.
And it seems like it's kind of generic.
Burger sandwiches, pastas, kind of whatever.
And I don't know that a lot of the food jumped out and was like even the reason to go.
But I do I do remember it being a little notorious from articles and press at the time
that they had chicken that was fried and coated in a batter that was comprised of Captain Crunch.
Jason had it.
Anybody else have it?
No, I did not. But I had other.
I've had like some other places I've had like versions of it.
And it never it's never satisfying to me.
Cornflake chicken, I think, is a lot more common.
Yeah, sure. It sounds all right.
That makes sense.
How is the how is the Captain Crunch chicken?
I mean, I was a kid and I liked anything sweet.
And so I think we're all very amused by the novelty of it.
I think they also lost the license to say Captain Crunch pretty quickly,
because eventually it just became like sweet crunch chicken.
It's still on the menu.
It was so bad.
It was like the flavor of this smirches.
The good name of Captain Crunch.
Yeah. Now they have an appetizer sampler that is served on a little metal wire
ferris wheel.
OK, that was like bring this up.
Yeah. What I thought I was delighted by that.
It's like a vertical lazy Susan. Yeah.
Whoa. I'm picturing this.
What do you Google to find to like
explain it to us or find a photo?
Yeah, let me find a photo.
Yeah, keep talking.
I'll find it.
It's like a circular thing and they would put it like so.
I just don't know. It was like a ferris wheel.
It was like a little like they put on the table.
It had like seven or eight baskets in like around the wheel.
Oh, I got it.
Each one had a different appetizer.
So it was just to expand the amount of space a table could have,
because I think so.
And also, like if you and like a lazy Susan, it's oh.
There we go.
The appetizer wheel, the appetizer wheel.
OK, I love this.
Yeah, this is pretty good.
I can't do it on this. Yeah.
I'm so I'm so happy that this is like proprietary to Planet Hollywood,
because I thought you guys would have already encountered these before.
Yeah, I don't know.
I'm trying to think of the I've had big.
I've had a three tiered like appetizer platter before,
and I'm trying to remember where that was, but I don't ever think it's come
in the form of a theme park ride.
Like my appetizers have never come on a ride.
That's a big deal.
Well, yeah, a ride mechanism that is a bunch of dumb appetizer.
This is pretty this is way up really film reel.
Is that possible?
Hmm. Oh, potentially.
Yeah, very. Yes.
If not, that's a waste of opportunity.
Definitely. Yeah, maybe.
But it's I think I feel like they could have done a better job
of making the outside look like a film canister.
Yeah, I think I'm wrong. I'm just guessing.
I don't know that you're wrong, though.
I just think maybe they were like, well, here's the deal.
All of these existed before and we can just buy up a bunch of them.
We don't need to make a bunch of film.
Like it's possible they cheaped out on an idea.
So I'm not totally discounting what you're saying.
Wonder how they describe it in the menu.
That would be the way to get good.
It's called a I think it's called a high roller sampler.
Yeah, I am also seeing the phrase high roller sampler. Correct.
Yes. OK. It's not film. It's not film.
It's like just a different theme, like Vegas.
Like, why are they going in a different direction?
Like not even trying to make it sound like Hollywood.
Did it debut at one of the places that has a casino nearby?
It well, I saw it also.
I saw it a second place because this is OK.
This is a confusing thing about Planet Hollywood's presence
in modern day Las Vegas.
The Planet Hollywood restaurant is in Caesars.
The Planet Hollywood Casino has a restaurant called Cafe Hollywood
that also has the Ferris wheel sampler
and a little bit of the similar theming.
But I don't think they could call it Planet Hollywood
because there's one of those in Caesars and they didn't want to cannibalize
their own business.
Cafe Hollywood is not Planet Hollywood.
No, but it was in Planet Hollywood.
It was the original name.
It was a name they were batting around before they hit on Planet Hollywood.
The high roller.
Yeah, this is I'm really it's I'm stuck on this boy.
It's an amazing wheel, but it's called the high roller
and it's served at a restaurant that's Hollywood themed.
I just I guess I guess Hollywood people are high roller.
I'm sure I rollers these guys have gambling problems, so maybe it makes sense.
That's true. Yeah.
The Ferris wheel in Las Vegas, the big observation wheel
in the middle of the Las Vegas strip is also called the high roller.
OK, all right. So there you go.
Yeah, I guess is a roll.
I guess it roll.
It doesn't really roll a Ferris wheel, though, doesn't really roll.
Rolling indicates that that the thing would have to actually
spin around spinning bins.
So the roll would be bad for bro is an accident
and it's come off of its axis and it's crushing people. Yeah.
Do you mean are you trying to are you all trying to tell me that
Planet Hollywood may not have thought something through?
Well, I guess I well, if we're talking about food,
are we now talking about actual food now or now?
I can tell you. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah.
Well, I guess my question is off this.
You guys have probably done more research than I have.
Is are any of the dishes like Hollywood theme like
or is there like the Schwarzenegger burger or like the Joe Piscopo fries or something?
You know, that's where one of the breakdowns seem to happen,
because reading about the development of the place,
Bruce Willis was all about the cocktail menu.
Sylvester Stallone kept making comments about wishing the food could just be in pill
form because he just cares about getting protein and working out.
Well, he doesn't like eating. He gets tired of chewing.
He gets tired. He wishes all food was pill.
That's that's his pitch for the world is that food is all he's coming out demolition
and like Taco Bell is nothing but like goo on a plate.
That's right. Yeah. Really made him think.
Schwarzenegger really wanted.
I believe it was his mother or his grandmother's strudel.
And that seems easy to make in both.
So I but I don't remember any of that.
You want that. Who wants strudel at this Jason place?
Probably. Yeah, I do. I absolutely would like that.
That's a pretty easy dessert. That's a pretty easy.
So did he not get his way in his mom's strudel was not at Planet Hollywood?
He said that's a shocker.
Yeah, you get that done.
I don't think he remembered saying that.
I don't know that any of them remembered saying any of this.
Well, the pill form I saw I saw an interview
where Sylvester Stallone would made it made a joke like I don't like to eat.
I don't like eat it.
I don't I don't I never liked it to trade a lot.
I just wanted food to be the pill, which is an odd thing to say
when you're promoting your restaurant.
Yeah, you don't want to hear that.
You hate to hear that from the restaurant tour.
I hate to. Yeah, that's right.
Yeah. Why did you open this place then?
The interviewer actually asked him that.
And it's like it's like it's an English, like a very snooty,
like English interviewer. And he's like, is it greed?
And so, oh, yeah, yeah, whatever.
No, it's fun to do.
You know, you're like half asses.
So my answer, a gotcha moment was attempted.
Take him to task.
Here's what I know that they have.
I think that we find ourselves,
Pat, often let down by not just what we're covering this month,
but other things where like the other theme restaurants
where they don't go the extra mile with naming the things.
This happens all the time.
There's only one thing on the menu where they bother.
And it's so insulting.
Like, why not?
If you're going to do a theme to something, why not go full tilt
and have and have fun?
Because there's so much like there is so much fun to be had with naming.
I did find I think the drink menu is where they really did it.
And this is very pixely what I'll show you.
So it's going to be a little hard.
Yeah, Bruce is the only one who tried.
He gave a damn.
And that's why his movies.
This was in an era where he still was.
He was down to try like two more things.
And I love my harmonica in support of as a sort of like thank you, Bruce.
Oh, yes. For the first summoning of Bruce.
Yes. Please play the harmonica you brought to the record.
I just I'm going to blow.
I can't actually play it.
That's all right.
It's neither can he.
That's great. That was beautiful.
Well, here's if you really want to be him, then like just yell like
you don't have to know the tune of the song, but just just go like long,
tall Sally and then do whatever you want on the harmonica. Yeah.
Have you seen is a secret seven ads from like the 80s?
That is that's that's like in the era where he like he was famous for that.
For me, that's the Bruno kind of like.
Bruno era. Yeah, I'm not super familiar with with these,
but they were like exceedingly popular, right?
But it feels like I think so.
But it was like that he had an actual album that came out where him playing harmonica.
This is like a future proto.
Yeah. Planet Hollywood, Bruce, because I feel like he was famous for playing
harmonica at Planet Hollywood openings.
Am I crazy? His his one of his contributions was always like,
and of course, I can play the opening.
I can help out. I can play the opening.
With the accelerators.
You know, like I think I just have this visual of him with a suede
planet Hollywood jacket, like pointing at the back of it, like that perfect, like
like a letterman jacket.
He goes and puffy as many colors as can be on those sleeves.
Yeah, that are like shirtless.
I feel like he was just shirtless at these openings a lot and and and bald too.
And maybe wearing some goofy hat.
That's what I found in a lot of these. He has a song.
It is shocking.
We haven't done a full Bruno episode because I'm a big fan of the concert.
I know a lot of the songs.
He has a song called Down in Hollywood, which would be what?
Yeah, believe it or not, would be perfect for the opening.
So yeah, I wish there should be a video of him.
I don't I haven't seen him perform those songs.
I've heard I've seen him do it.
Scott's saying like long tall Sally at like a sort of outdoor festival.
And we're in covers.
You could ever.
It's so fascinating that like he he was already the coolest guy in the world.
But in his brain.
He's like, I can be cooler with a harmonica.
I think he saw I just can't wrap my head around that.
I think he saw Billy Joel and I think he goes, I can do that.
Like when you see when you watch Return of Bruno
and one of my favorite songs, my probably my favorite song is called Fun Time
that he does. We we we've been in an episode playing this one.
Yeah, we have talked. What's that?
Sorry, Pat.
Do the lyrics go, this is where the fun starts.
He goes, oh, yes, it's fun time.
Fun time like break time, break time.
Everyone be happy.
It's fun time.
And it's all like, I think I'm thinking of a of a of a Seagram's wine cooler
commercial. OK, maybe that's a different.
Yeah, we have multiple songs about fun.
Bruce that loves to have.
That's right.
I love your artist.
I think you're right.
I think we have played fun time.
I feel like we ended an episode for some reason playing Fun Time.
And forgive me if I've if I've said this fact already,
but it's a it's a fact that stuck in my brain for a long time
and since the accelerators have come up.
I am a massive Beck fan, really love Beck.
And I love all the amazing musicians he's played with over the years, especially.
And his primary guitar player since Odell era,
this amazing guitarist named Smokey Hormel has been on tour of them.
He played all the awesome guitar on C Change and Mutations and all the like.
Lush, pretty stuff.
He was asked to join Beck's band in like 94, 95.
And it was he was heartbroken to have to turn it down
because he had already accepted a purely for money gig.
Touring planet Hollywood's with Bruce Willis and the Accelerators.
He almost and then playing with Beck became like a decades long.
And he is Beck's guy.
And he almost missed it entirely so that he could go right.
Salah right.
I think this is something we should mention
the that a lot of the openings,
especially for younger listeners, a lot of these openings,
they would just be filled with celebrities, like even in the smaller cities.
That definitely fell off at a certain point.
But there is a very funny story of Tom Arnold saying, I went to all of them
and him and his him and his then wife, which I don't think was Roseanne
because Roseanne started getting really into the plan Hollywood stuff.
I don't think he was there.
I think he was there in Roseanne era and post Roseanne era and post Roseanne era.
So he always took them up on the free trips, the free flight,
the free hotel and everything.
You just got gobs of merch.
And he's like, my wife was like next to sitting next to George Clooney
on the plane when he got a phone call and he hung up and he went, well, I'm Batman.
But he got the call.
It all comes back to Batman.
It was the Schumacher era.
She was Batman. Yeah.
Let me I mean, like we'll get into celebrities and stuff just while it's open.
Let me like point out some of these these drinks, because these are good.
I can't read the descriptions too well.
But I love the like degree of selection of movies that we got here.
We got the Jurassic Park.
We got the Steel Magnolia.
We got the cliffhanger, the legends of the fall.
Sometimes they pluralize, not always
indecent proposal and ghost.
I like that it's a it's a mix of like silly movies and then kind of like
austere adult circle of friends is circle of friends goes under shooters.
You can get shooters that are themed after this.
Like, I don't really know what that movie is, but can we can we get around the back
drafts? Can we get around the back draft for the table?
I'm like, I think in Legend of the Fall, Brad Pitt's character, like,
is like a hopeless alcoholic.
So like having a specialty drink named after him is in poor taste.
I'd like to get hammered off of a bunch of terms of endearment shots, please.
What's the terms? I can't.
Can you read the ingredients? There's a two tall.
Oh, God, I wonder if I can find a better one.
The other term. Wait, wait, is there cancer?
Right. It was nice.
Is that a joke? Did I make that up or did you say it?
Wait, no, I don't see terms of endearment.
They made that up. I think I think I assumed it was on here somewhere.
Steel Magnolias is on here.
And I want to get the listener in a little peak.
I said, OK, let's say Carlson, you're a funny guy.
Here's what you're going to do.
You're going to think of a movie they haven't said that seems like a serious movie.
I said it out loud.
No one seemed to laugh at it.
And then all of a sudden, everyone thought it was actually something you said.
It seemed plausible.
Yeah, I commend you for realism because it's like so close to Steel Magnolia.
Why? Yeah, we're all just immediately like, oh, I don't see terms of it.
It's notable they have an entire market like they specialize in martinis.
Yeah. Yeah. Ghost 12 Monkeys, which, you know, 12 monkeys
as they have some bullshit banana ingredients and fakey awful
Sabrina, that real Rat Pack swinging movie, 12 Monkeys.
They're all just a bunch of 12 monkeys.
Can't be licensed. They don't. Yeah.
They have the.
But they are.
A lot of the stuff like Cliffhanger is to loan terminal velocity is Willis.
Right. No, that's
Charlie Sheen, I think, or that drop zone or terminal
Charlie Sheen is either in drops down or terminal velocity.
Charlie Sheen shows up in one of the openings.
She was around. Yeah, she was around.
They picked him up.
It seemed to go in tears like they gave.
They started with the big three, which turned into the big four with Demi Moore.
And then it started expanding.
You know who else was early in fall?
Like often it is like more like, oh, like party guy kind of celebrities.
And Tom Arnold makes sense.
But then like John Hughes early on, John Hughes, not the most like public man.
And I think he he was genuinely interested, I think, in like having a place
he could go with a private booth.
And I think the Chicago location had a space that had to be reserved
for John in case he he came in.
Wow, that's crazy.
That was the Chicago location was in Gurney Mills, which is right by Six Flags.
Oh, wow.
What a zone, Mike.
Yeah, minutes from Six Flags.
One of the ones listed, I believe Gurney, Illinois, stuck out to me of like
in the 1999 news stories about Planet Hollywood to close
upwards of a dozen locations.
And it just I was like, where is why is there one in Gurney, Illinois?
Because of the Six Flags that I'm sure that's why Gurney Mills was a pretty big
mall. It's still a mall.
They forget if its name has changed.
Home alone, maybe home alone.
The massive success of home alone put Illinois on the map for for a minute.
That's possible. That's true. Yeah.
I I went to a couple of times the Atlantic City one,
which was on the boardwalk at Caesars.
I know I have a shirt somewhere.
I have a number of Planet Hollywood T-shirts,
I believe, because my family had the Planet Hollywood credit card for a while.
So we had a lot of points. What?
What? I read a comment somewhere,
might have even been in our Facebook or somebody talking about like they're like
that the waiter was pushing the credit card the whole time.
And it was like, well, it really makes sense because, you know,
if you're going to eat here and you're going to buy merch.
So your parents had a Planet Hollywood.
What does it get you?
Well, I I should say I should ask him if this was a coincidence
or whether it happened at the same time, because my dad, a proud Sheridan heirloom
has the denim jacket, the Planet Hollywood denim jacket
with the patch on the back in good shape.
And I have not stolen it yet.
But we cashed it like he I think they were getting rid of it.
They were they were getting rid of the card and my parents were getting rid of the card.
And we did cash in.
And my brother and I got a few shirts.
They were very clear that like you don't get to pick which city the shirts are from.
We're just going to send you shirts.
But I also got this fine
watch that I would wear to school dances and
family weddings and stuff.
Jane with like the shitty 90s logo with like the very like that's like
latter day style laughing from the other room.
This watch, of course, the battery would go on to die
and the band would very quickly disintegrate.
It's the cute. What did you say?
I what did you say?
Yeah, I wore it to formal offense.
I love you.
I'm responding to the same thing I'm responding to.
I love it.
It's the cutest thing I can possibly think of is that you're like,
I'm getting dressed up.
And to finish off this look for my dressed up dance
look is the Planet Hollywood, the finest piece of jewelry I own.
That's because people would come back from vacations with the shirts
or the bomber jackets. It was the thing.
I love it. It was a thing.
And I know I still have it sitting at my mom's.
And now it's now it's like, OK, do I try to find it and repair it?
Like get a new battery, get a new band or do I just buy it again?
Because that's insane.
I mean, I guess I'd like you to do it.
I think I just like Islands of Adventure watch
like some old Italian watch fixer and like who's normally fixing like
stock stopwatches and old like now this one.
It's like a little hot.
Yeah, it's like a little cottage somewhere up
like in like some of the hills.
I'm impressed that the case, I guess,
if you can't see the photo, like it comes
in a case that looks as if it's the most valuable thing in the world.
Yes, it does. Yeah, it looks like it's like that.
I mean, the case tells you, I guess, especially if you were a kid,
you're like, this is expensive.
This is an important watch.
Yeah, there it is.
Yeah. Well, look, it felt more fitting with a suit
because my other watch looked like, you know, it's just whatever
like Timex expedition that my mom had just bought for stocking stuffers or whatever.
We got to figure out how we can restore this watch
and how you can wear it maybe every day.
There's one guy like the last planet Hollywood who can fix it.
The watchmaker is there.
Did any of those guys star in a movie about a watchmaker?
I mean, I have a watch guy.
I I don't. Oh, I think I know what guy.
Yeah, a watch guy.
How often do you go to your watch guy?
If I need a new battery or the band is worn out
and I need a new band.
OK, because you know the back is the watch is the battery.
Yeah, you pop the back out. Yeah. Wow. Interesting.
I was given you got to take this in.
If you have a guy, we don't have a guy.
But that's the thing.
I don't know where the original one is, but there are plenty of versions of it
online and there are numerous other played out of what not for not very much money.
All right. Well, did you ever go out of your way at a dance to like
were you dancing in such a way to try to like show those wrists around?
Hands up, everyone.
No, no, Scott, I was too busy dealing with the flop sweat and nerves.
So I don't think I ever mentioned it
because at least I had the sense of like.
Can you play a time is on my side just so I can do this when they say time
and sees my watch?
Or are you really a prom song?
You went up to like a strobe light and tried like reflecting
the strobe off of your watch to like.
I do. I mean, that watch, it is actually until you see the planet
Hollywood logo, it looks like a pretty tasteful watch.
Yeah, it is surprisingly reserved by Planet Hollywood standards.
And a girl would have to get really close to you to be able to see
that detail of the logo.
So I think you're showing that off basically in success.
And I don't know what level of success you were feeling the deal. Yeah.
I like Jason guy, but did you see his fucking watch?
Holy crap. Nothing was special about like do anything like Hollywood, right?
Oh, man, I wish.
No, I mean, I think it had a date on it, but, you know,
I thought maybe I had to watch a Star Wars, a Star Trek watch
that would play the theme song when you pressed it.
So I thought maybe like you press a button and play like
array for Hollywood or something.
I Robert Earl just thanks you for the thank you for patronizing my restaurant.
I love you real quick, just because we're talking about the jacket
and the watch here.
I don't know. You guys probably saw this, but there's a shirt here
that Schwarzenegger is wearing.
And I want to know if Jason remembers this because he was I think it's safe
to say he was the biggest planet Hollywood fan of of the four of us.
Right. As a kid, I Jason, it sounds. Yeah, I guess so.
I know. I thought maybe I'm more of a fan post your adult years.
2010s. Yeah, I think so.
Just about era of Hollywood in general.
Like right, right.
But not that restaurant specifically.
I heard it referred to as like the 90s was the last really fun time for Hollywood
because there was a limited number of cameras.
There were beepers and early cell phones,
but like you weren't constantly tracked every hour of the day. Yeah.
So Schwarzenegger is wearing a shirt that looks like
like like a
carpeting at a bowling alley, kind of, but also like it's a Hawaiian shirt.
It's got the big gaudy planet Hollywood logo.
It's got rocket ships.
It almost looks like the Space Jam logo, like the Space Jam logo is
is the planet Hollywood logo.
It's very, very colorful, very gaudy.
But the thing I found the most on eBay are vest versions.
Oh, my God.
And this vest. Yeah.
And we talked about last on the dive episode, there's a denim vest
you can get with a big dive logo.
But these are cheap. These are how planet Hollywood vests.
We can get this for under 20 bucks.
And Jason, I think if you would let me,
I would love to purchase one of these vests for you.
If you wear it, I, I,
I will I would happily wear this like at one of our shows.
We all we all three of us wear these rainbow vests
without shirts on underneath that like immediately.
We'll leave and ask for their money back.
Like, listen, if that doesn't work out, you can all just become
professional billiard players and wear at the billiard games.
Yeah. So, I mean, I guess we'll do it off off, Mike.
But I do think the only thing that concerns me about these vests is like
there's a lot of very like generically kind of designs
that the planet Hollywood logos don't seem big enough to me.
I see what you're saying. You know what I mean?
Where it's like cut off.
I mean, look at in the back here.
That one looks better. Yeah. OK.
OK. So I think you could find it. I think it's it depends.
Maybe each one is very unique because look at this.
This is really a front. That one's good. Yeah, that was.
Yeah. So I think it was like, you know, each one is a unique snowflake.
It's like Lula Rowe. Right.
You also have to wear it.
The only thing acceptable to wear under these vests is a button down,
a colorless button down.
Oh, yes, sure. Like all the way. Yeah. Yeah.
Well, I thought either that or like a white t shirt.
Like a like a too shiny Macy's white t shirt.
Yeah. I think that's very Bruce Willis.
He too, like very 90s Bruce Willis.
Well, yeah, it reminds me of like a full house Stamos look.
Yeah. Oh, big time.
I would think cool. Yeah.
Well, hmm.
With the zany colors.
Yeah, it's the gaudiness of the of the uncle of the Joey character,
not only of the Joey character and the like cool sexiness of the of the.
Yeah. Uncle Jesse character.
Jesse's wearing it without anything underneath.
Joey's wearing it with a like tritone long sleeve shirt
and jean shorts, and it's all tucked in.
The vest is tucked into. Right.
That's can I share some of the the current celebs
that they're like pushing on the Planet Hollywood home page?
I cannot imagine who. Yes.
Some of which some of which are promoting the merchandise.
It's exactly who you think it is.
You got Reese Witherspoon, you got Josh Gatton, a little hat.
Gwen Stefani is doing a residency.
And of course, who would be wearing the clothing?
Why is Jacob Sartorius himself?
What? Who's Jacob Sartorius?
Why is Jacob Sartorius the young online influencer who is like
what came of I think was very popular like years ago and is now 20.
But I have never come across this name.
Why that was Jason before?
I did know who Jacob Sartorius was.
I don't know what he's known for.
Jason is out, hip to us again.
I don't think I don't think Jason Sartorius is hip.
I'm going to call Jacob.
I'm not a man.
Are you calling Jason Sartorius?
Do I could say Jason Sartorius?
Well, that's what he wishes he was, is Jason Sartorius.
Pretty cool name.
It's a cool name. Sure.
Yeah. Sartorius is a first name I would really love.
That's that's the thing.
I just thought it was a very weird crop and a very weird like,
yeah, check out check out this 12 year old wearing wearing this sweatshirt.
Like what?
I mean, you can still mail order.
You can still buy all the sweatshirts and stuff.
They have a very big store at the Orlando location, although I think
Chicken Guy has taken over a chunk of it.
This is modern.
I'm showing a photo now of modern merch and I kind of like these sweatshirts.
They're very like modern.
They have the Planet Hollywood logo, but they're kind of like faded,
faded, monocolor type.
Yeah. And I like I like this is cool, but this isn't exactly
what I want from the brand.
You know, I want the airline one, that top gun looking one.
Yeah, like there's some that they really look like Planet Hollywood
is like a gym or a high school or something, which like get out.
I don't understand.
Why would anyone what would possess someone to buy a shirt
from Planet Hollywood that is almost impossible to tell it's from there?
Exactly.
Yeah.
Yeah. What is that insecurity about your shitty brand?
I guess.
Well, they also got some real American like I'm like over
over designed red, white, blue eagle crap.
Yeah. It's just founded in 1991.
Yeah. This is looks like Patriot gear.
And if you squint, you go, oh, it's a Planet Hollywood shirt. OK.
And then like as far as jackets, like look at this.
I mean, again, I'm not mad at this jacket, but it's not.
The colorful sleeves thick,
like Steven Spielberg bomber jacket with nine colors and only one color.
It's one color. There's a little low.
It's black. It's very form fitting.
And it's got a Planet Hollywood logo on the left shoulder.
Yeah. It's like it's a small again.
It's small. It's like you'd have to you'd have to be like a woman
would have to be slow dancing with you at a high school dance
to read the logo because she'd be kind of looking at your arm that close.
Yeah. You have not taken your motorcycle jacket off.
Yeah. Now they do have here they have one varsity jacket.
And it's that's the OG.
That's the that's the thing. Yeah.
Yeah. And that's one hundred and ninety dollars.
Do you guys watch just do you guys watch the righteous gemstones on HBO?
Yeah. Caught up.
But yeah, there was an episode recently that was set in the 90s
when they were like doing a Christmas special and
Baby Billy, who's Walton Goggins, kind of like ridiculous brother character,
is a rock and a not.
He said in the 90s rock and a Planet Hollywood vest.
And it was right before we take this. I was very excited to know.
No kidding. Oh, I wish I made it up to that.
What a great character to be perfect.
Planet Hollywood fan.
That makes sense. Wow.
You know, merchandise with the logo isn't the only thing
that Planet Hollywood is selling, because I don't know if the question
has occurred to any of you what happened to all of the merchandise.
And I discovered that what happened to at least some of it
is that they are just selling it on Amazon.
There is a store called the Planet Hollywood Collectibles store.
And I'm going to share screen here.
Again, maybe I've overloaded with too many windows.
Let me let me drop a few.
But yeah, you can.
There is a store you can find.
That is just like random props and you could just buy it now.
It's not an auction.
You can just go straight to it.
Is it eBay or Amazon? Amazon, weirdly.
OK, because then yeah, wouldn't be an auction on Amazon.
Oh, so when you say merchandise, you don't you don't mean like the jackets and stuff.
You mean like the props?
I mean, the props. Yeah.
And none of them are I mean, well, you'll see.
There's a few that I might describe as a little exciting
and some that are more of the hangover regular shirt nature.
You guys seeing this?
I mean, we have here Rain Man's shoes,
which are going for 700 Raymond Babbitt's shoes.
And it's twenty five dollars shipping, which I don't know.
Do you get Amazon Prime free shipping for any of these?
I guess not. I don't think the I don't think that applies.
I don't think they have that deal.
I mean, I would never buy these, but it doesn't seem like the worst.
Like that is a best picture winning movie.
Yeah. Yeah.
An iconic character.
Yeah. It's like more prominent than what you would expect to find on the planet.
Hollywood. Exactly.
Like the Amazon store.
Well, don't worry, we get a little deeper
for the film buffs out there.
What with Danny Aiello's Dosmo Pizzo ensemble
from Two Days in the Valley.
Oh, wow.
Which is four hundred dollars for a bowling shirt, a white T-shirt, like slacks,
big boots, which those are crazy.
Lowest dress.
Oh, it's socks. OK.
I was going to say. Right. All right.
It looked like stockings or something.
And then like, do you get his boxers to whatever we talk?
What does it look like?
Traditional white boxers. Yeah.
We're Danny. We're boxer.
We're underwear. Danny Aiello.
That looks like you that looks like you could wear that to a Brian Setzer concert.
Well, you maybe I should.
One of you guys rocks one of the vests.
Yeah. Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Or a vest. Yeah. Vest underneath this, too.
And if it's like you get too hot when you're swing dancing, you get too hot.
Take it off and use a vest.
Hey, this guy looks like Dosmo Pizzo over here.
You're the coolest boy.
Watch out. This guy jump drives in Wales.
You think you're Danny Aiello because you're not.
There could only be one.
Here is Rob Schneider's costume as the character Fergie.
It's like a it's a prison jumpsuit from Judge Dredd
that you can buy right now.
Listeners for the 17,
$1700 or $1750.
I was a thousand dollars more than the like the rain man rain man.
Rain man's I guess because it's more stuff.
And then I guess maybe who cares about rain man about his shoes.
But the shoes kind of tell you something.
They're kind of like they they're sort of like Gump's shoes. Right.
These are simple.
Also, for whatever reason, I think as you I think you mentioned this earlier, Scott, like
Planet Hollywood places a premium on anything Judge Dredd related.
That might be part of it. Yes, that's maintained.
And they feel like with the reboot, whenever that was three years ago,
12 years ago, I couldn't tell you, but it's Dredd mania again.
They keep pumping life into it.
Well, it seems like there's still an informal relationship,
at least a few years ago, that the that Esquire reporter
could not get anyone on the record to say they still were involved.
But the premieres for the 2008 Rambo and the Expendables
were held at the Planet Hollywood Casino and Hotel in Las Vegas.
Huh? Yeah.
So slides kind of in the fold, a little kind of in the fold,
but still gave a no comment of like, do you still own shares?
Because they declared bankruptcy twice, right?
They declared it in 99.
And then in 2001, they they chalked it out to the tourism downturn.
Sure. That's a lot of other.
Isn't there a lot of I think I sent Scott an article back when we
I told him I wanted to.
I mentioned that I am interested in doing this like the guy who one of the guys died.
One of the guys died recently, right?
This one. Yeah.
I mean, there's you guys probably there's some I guess there's so much
financial intrigue with this place that I feel like
I don't only know the surface of.
There's a bunch of stuff.
Yeah, I can explain the characters involved.
That's a funny character.
What are your favorite guys?
You know, I've been dying to talk, but I'll I'll weave the whole whole tale.
And I know you're there really quickly.
Just while it's up, we got a Jessica Lang's cape from Rob Roy
for a thousand dollars.
We got a smashing pumpkins shirt worn by Elijah Wood and Flipper.
Wow. And Flipper.
That's 450.
That's not bad. If you were for some reason in a lot of this,
somebody's I'm like, it was like a two hundred dollars less.
Maybe a little and maybe they'll get there.
They they, you know, they might not be committed to the and these
might have all been up for like years at this point.
So maybe we'll we'll get a little downturn.
This one's pretty genuinely crazy.
It's a John Candy life mask.
That's how they made his his face to be barf and space balls.
So it's a weird, creepy, looks like a closed eye.
It's John Candy's real face.
But with us, with a little like black painted for his snout.
That's like, wow.
I don't know if you were into space balls.
That's not so bad.
People who would like hanging this on their wall for sure.
But for sure. Yeah. Yeah.
That creepily mounted like you like you killed him.
You hunted and killed barf.
It's terrifying. But yeah.
This is a piece of wood that Harrison Ford
has Jack Ryan touched in clear and present danger.
He's in a room with lots of logs.
And he touched his log scene or something.
I looked it up.
I did find a still of him like looking confused in a room full of logs.
I don't know why that happens.
Maybe he beats someone like this.
I mean, kill a guy maybe with a lot.
I don't know. Oh, wow.
It does seem like a scam at this point.
Yeah. If he heard him, if Harrison Ford heard himself on the log,
I think the price would skyrocket.
Yeah. I don't know.
Harrison Ford injuries are a dime a dozen.
They have an impossible to authenticate this like, yeah, it's a log.
He touched a log.
What do you say? He doesn't log. Yeah.
Yeah. I don't.
How can they possibly and how did we know it's the one that he touched?
And how does that like Harrison Ford touches an item and it goes from
worth two dollars to three hundred fifty.
He is he is like Christ.
It's magic powers that way.
We have some actual silk stockings from silk stocking.
Wow. The silk stockings from silk stocking.
I don't know if it's these silk stockings.
They may have had a lot of.
And by the way, silk stockings, you have to keep in mind, is spelled
like stocking, like following somebody.
So in a way with the double play.
But they are stockings and they're only one hundred dollars.
And then where am I heading?
Oh, some leather pants that John Lithgow wore on Third Rock from the Sun.
This is what this is one of the weirdest, like of all the things on Amazon,
you know, like one click and you can buy this.
I think it's really weird that any listener right now could,
if they ponied up two thousand dollars by a Jack Benny violin.
Well, now, now, real gas for me.
Yeah, Jason and I may need to pull our money and do like a like the Simpsons.
One of the first season with the comic book situations.
No, with you'll kill your you'll kill each other with the violin.
Benny's signature violin and bow was he was the violin part of his jam.
I guess that's yeah.
Yeah. I don't know. I don't know my Jack Benny that well.
I'm sorry. I thought he would do it sometimes in a bit.
Yeah. The bit was like, yeah, no one wanted to hear him play it really.
Oh, so this one. Yeah, this one seems more famous than like John Lithgow's pants.
Yeah, it's pretty.
All the respects to Lithgow.
Yeah, yeah, of course. Yeah, I just don't remember the pants
or why he was wearing leather.
Well, clearly, I mean, obviously, like they're there.
If he wore those pants on episode, that's the point of the episode.
Those are those are load bearing.
I remember the pants episode.
I think I do remember the pants.
I watched it recently.
We've been rewatching it.
And yeah, there's it's kind of like a hook, an important outfit in that episode.
So you recognize when I brought up the pants, of course, the pants.
I just saw the pants. Yeah. Yeah.
We're all laughing, but I can't wait for this us to stop recording.
We all just go into a bidding war immediately over all this stuff.
Excuse me a sec.
And I'll just
oh, and then have to do the rest of the episode through gritted teeth
because we're really mad.
Damn it. I'm one of those stockings.
Pat sniped me on the stockings.
The silk stockings.
I mean, the one I genuinely have thought of and I'm still thinking about buying
is a flip phone used by Michael Douglas in disclosure, which is
you talk like mid 90s insanity.
I love disclosure.
But this prop is not in very good condition.
And frankly, I don't understand why a flip phone had to be made out of foam
rubber to begin with.
So I don't know that I want to pony up four hundred fifty dollars for this.
Oh, 450 for that. Yeah.
But I'm tempted. I really I thought about I gave it like five solid minutes.
The thought of it's kind of like the it's kind of like the consolation.
But like you can't get the I'm sure like his cell phone from
Wall Street is like in the Smithsonian now.
Oh, yes. The closest thing you get.
Yeah, there is a much more prominent Douglas cell phone. That is true.
You know, Scott, while we're on the subject of props, could we hear from
certified Hollywood celeb and Planet Hollywood shareholder herself
about Planet Hollywood's?
Of course. I don't know to whom you refer.
I'm I'm on pins and needles.
Well, I'm referring to Miss Demi Moore herself.
Now I'm going to play this clip and kind of gives an image
of Hollywood at its time.
What I really want to focus on is a few seconds in.
But I figured I'd I'd have this set up too.
So hold on one second. Here it goes.
One of the things Planet Hollywood has become famous for
is its collection of movie memorabilia.
Each Planet Hollywood location is like a museum within a funhouse.
And as you might expect, the Planet Hollywood in Beverly Hills
has to be the champion of them all.
So let's get down to the heavy stuff. Hardware, guns.
Now, what would be without?
She's at a restaurant booth holding up a big guy.
Huge gun. That's right.
What would movies be without guns?
A phrase we're all constantly saying still to this day in 2022.
If you'll notice, she also had what appears to be the golden idol
for a Raiders of the Lost Ark binder.
Just not even in a case.
Just sitting around, just sitting behind her in her giant gun.
Somebody could spill a steel magnolia drink on that.
Wow, that's insane.
That frame of you got to post at least the whole clip.
But I'll just clip that part. Oh, my God.
Yeah. Her holding on the gun and bragging about like after
kind of a dull montage of like, look, it's the outfit from the mask.
It's the outfit from this thing.
And then she's like, and of course, where would be without guns?
Wow. Chilling, chilling.
Well, do you want to get into history a little bit?
Or have we missed anything about like personal experiences we've had
or fun, specific memories or food?
Just like, like, you know, the grab bag of what makes Planet Hollywood,
Planet Hollywood?
Yeah, I have a request for listeners.
One of the best meals I ever ate was at a Planet Hollywood.
It was seared scallops over linguine with a lime cream sauce.
And capers.
And I've never had anything like it.
If anyone has a recipe like that, because I went to a Planet Hollywood once,
went back a few years later.
And of course, the menu had totally changed because they were constantly
changing the menu to little luck of improving it.
But so you're calling for the listeners to just give you a recipe.
That sounds like the thing to recreate your magical meal.
One of the best meals you've ever had, which was like Seymour Skinner himself.
I've never been able to recreate.
The stew. The stew.
I well, I mean, I it seems like anyone in the world can find out
the executive chef at that time.
It'd be you guys.
It's true. It's probably a way of harnessing the power of your fans.
Yeah, yeah. Maybe, yeah.
Maybe the man himself or woman could make you the recipe themselves.
It's like a little bit.
I it'll make me come off as really irritating.
So just preface it with that.
OK, well, you were deep in.
People are enjoying you already.
So I thought for them, so right now,
but I think was probably one of the last times I was there.
But I'm actually I went there before we saw the Beatles musical
and we just got drinks and maybe appetizers by the bar.
And the irritating thing is that I have to reference that.
Like I got recognized by the waitress
because she knew from the college she was called.
She knew college humor stuff.
Oh, well, at the time, I got recognized from time to time.
That's the irritating part. Sorry.
No, this is an episode about celebrities.
This was your your sly moment.
I mean, I was like, you know, we were just my friend was laughing his ass off
because he just thought it was embarrassing or whatever.
But I was like, I did ask her, I was like, I was like, oh, thanks for watching.
That's cool. You know, and but I was like, just like out of curiosity,
this is Planet Hollywood.
Like, you get a lot of celebrities here anymore.
Like in this is like twenty seventeen, eighteen.
And she was like, ah, you know who was here recently?
I was like, who? She was Kelly and Conway.
Yeah.
I was like, OK, well, that's me and her, I guess.
What a company to be in.
So Kelly and Conway has been to the Planet Hollywood, New York.
Wow. That's that's good.
That's good to show that wasn't it wasn't like a just a predator suit
that was in the lobby.
You try to steal everything.
I mean, it's like I have to like name drop or like whatever.
It's boastful.
But then also the it makes it like apparently in this woman's mind, I'm
like Kelly and Conway
neck and neck with.
Yeah. The Kelly and Conway of
2010's Internet comedy.
If you need to use that quote on a book or something.
So yeah, what an honor.
One waitress one time at a point.
Jason, you've been to the planet Hollywood inside the Caesars Casino
in Atlantic City.
I know in Atlantic City.
Oh, yeah. OK.
And multiple times.
I think so. Yeah, I definitely have a T-shirt from there.
OK, because I'm reading here that the actual
grandpa from the Munsters, Dracula hung in this planet Hollywood.
What? Grandpa Al Lewis.
Grandpa Al Lewis. Yes.
The location is the planet pictures of there's a, you know,
a website called Munster coached out, of course, talks about the Munster cars.
We know which can now let's get specific here because we've run into
trouble with this before. Which car are we talking?
We're talking about the Dracula grandpa's car, which is a coffin car,
basically like a drag race.
That's the distinction that grandpa's car is the Dracula, but it's not.
You wouldn't call it the Munsters car.
The Munster car and it's called the Munsters coach.
And that's the bigger car that you're more you usually see them in.
The Dracula is from a specific episode where grandpa races.
OK. Yeah. But but it says it's hanging.
There's pictures of it here.
Let me show you, Jason, just in case this jogs any memories for you.
I don't know. And we should say this location long gone.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. It looks familiar. Yeah.
Whoa. Wow. This is a major piece of.
Yeah. Recent PTR.
Things have been very Munster heavy recently.
So that's amazing. That's where this was. Wow.
And then the motion of the Dorothy was kind of a rare exception of like a non
car, like most of the like the speed bus
speed car is so crazy real estate or the prime attractions that these places
had room for a bus to be hung from the ceiling.
Well, I'm not sure how they did it, but it was like it's I'm sure you can Google it.
But like it was bursting through the wall.
Like I think was only like the front of the bus.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, I think I remember a lot of cars at the
the Disney World one, which we haven't super focused on.
But like that thing was but ma'am, that restaurant was so crazy
and went up so high for like a four tiered restaurant and all in a big dome.
And I think this is a picture of the Disney World one.
I could be wrong, but the it or maybe it isn't.
I don't know. But this is the way his world car. Right.
The Murth Mobile Murth Mobile.
Yeah. Big with another demolition man, naked sly next to him.
At least if this isn't Disney World, then that could have been the one
because that had the Herbie the love bug.
That's what I'd rather I'd like to know what happened.
All these cars. That's so crazy.
They had room for all this.
I thought it was like this whole other like museum just for cars for of these kinds.
I'm surprised that isn't it like some very famous museum
just has all like the Batmobile and there's a bunch of that because I think a number of them are made.
Like there is there is a small car museum at this massive chain of dealerships
in Van Nuys, California, and they have a bunch of the cars.
And you used to be able to just walk through Berris Custom Auto had a small museum.
They did a lot of the they did the Batmobile. They did the Monsters car.
But I have a story about the Disney World one that Jane told me her like
she hadn't been there, but her sister was she doesn't like things hanging above her.
So avoid it. She would have a restaurant.
So they her sister would try to scare her by saying there's a massive
Woody from Toy Story in this plane on Hollywood hanging above you.
There's a massive Woody from Toy Story.
And we thought it was like, oh, how big could it be?
How big could it be?
And so we found video online and we looked it up and it turns out.
Yeah, he's pretty big.
Jesus. Yeah, he's that's that's not what Woody's like.
That's so scary.
Yeah, he is like the size of the Home Depot 12 foot skeleton
hanging over like a tunnel with that sort of bent girder design.
This is Batman.
This is not like a props movie.
This is like some custom built thing, right?
Yeah, they didn't.
Yeah, they did.
Like early on was the technology that such that you had to build a
giant two story model of a toy to get it in the computer and scan it.
I think it was it was just a yeah, because it was at Disney.
They had that when we were down in Florida in 2019, I walked through the gift shop
and I was the only one doing that and they had a lot of stuff on sale.
So I don't know how long for the world that gift shop was,
especially when Chicken Guy was so popular and they needed the seating.
The yeah, the Disney World one.
I don't know if you ever went, Pat, or have seen photos of it, but it's like.
I thought I had.
I'm sorry.
You go ahead.
Oh, no, no, no, go ahead.
I thought I was trying to do my like little mental inventory.
I've been to the New York one at least three times.
And then I had this very distinct memory of going to my dad in Orlando because we
a couple of years ago.
My dad's an engineer and he wanted to see the last space shuttle launch.
So we drove down.
We flew down there to see it.
But like we just stayed in Orlando proper.
No Disney World, though, but I can't.
It's in Disney World, right?
It's like in actual Disney World.
It is.
Yeah, it's at the what used to be pleasure.
Right.
They're like weird novelty.
You know, you know, like Orlando, not like there's a lot of themed restaurant.
They have their own little Times Square in Orlando.
Say different.
Yeah, but it's in.
You might have been there.
It's in Disney Springs, which is like this free shopping area.
You could just go to it.
What I mean is there was a restaurant that looked like it looked at the entire building
was upside down from the outside.
Does that ring a bell?
Oh, that is something else.
Yeah, that's like is that a believe it or not.
I feel like that's that's a thing Ripley's does.
Well, we near that area.
So that's not the right.
Sorry, there's a dead end.
I don't know why.
No, no, no, that might be like I drive like I get there is a
lot of touristy crap and dinner theaters and big giant free standing restaurants.
Dracula coach.
And I just like conflated that with like Hollywood or something.
Be that's no, I've never been to, but I've not been to I've been to Disney World a long
time ago, but I've not been to the as far as I know, the Planet Hollywood down there.
The one out there.
It's like, I mean, this it like so captured my imagination at nine, 10 years old.
Whenever it opened, I remember I remember seeing it off of the freeway on the approach.
This is my second Disney World trip ever.
And just like, oh, my God, like I like seeing it rise up over the trees, this mammoth globe
type building, which then not just that in Orlando, you got the globe at Universal,
the globe and Planet Hollywood, like really globe heavy.
What does that mean?
It's like it's some sort of like world conquering theme.
I don't know.
It's not it's creepy.
But they I just like and walking up to that, like stick, it only got stranger and stranger.
It felt like the peak 1994.
It got so strange as time went on and it never changed.
And it's not only this huge blue marble building, but then also a UFO crashed into it.
And also there's a big like alligator or dinosaur or something wearing a Planet Hollywood T-shirt.
And then outside of it, they parked not there's not just the vehicles inside,
but outside there was the fishing boat, Jenny from Forrest Gump.
Confusingly not at a Bubba Gump.
You would think they'd want to reserve that for like the biggest Bubba Gump,
but they lost control of it.
I don't know.
Is there a Bubba Gump in Orlando?
That's a universal.
Yes.
If you could draw the corporate lines.
Yes, they are aligned with Universal.
Was the UFO crashing into the building?
Was it like a UFO from like Mars attacks or something?
Or was it just kind of generic UFO?
I think just generic UFO.
It just like serves as an awning.
See, I don't like that.
I'm like why that's that's breaking the theme of the whole place to me.
Yeah, that's true.
It should be like make it the Independence Day ship or make it like a
Doc Brown's DeLorean or whatever they got.
I don't know whether wherever they have access to.
Or a flight of the Navigator.
Sure.
I mean, yeah, that's right.
Yeah, something Disney.
Yeah, I don't know why they didn't get it.
And why is it some generic dinosaur and not 98 Godzilla?
That obviously would be iconic.
That was living in the New York one, you know?
Yeah, yeah, of course.
All the pieces of the Godzilla were living in New York.
Anyway, I just like stylistically that location, I find it so funny that they
basically the whole area that it's in used to be really like bright, colorful,
gaudy 90s and it like only got stranger as time went on.
I remember like looking outside there as the paint is fading
and the little like lagoon next to it just gets dirtier and dirtier.
It felt like there was malaria in that water.
It was just so seedy, if you guys recall.
And then they're like, we got to refresh this thing.
They kind of like beige-ified this entire shopping center.
But they're like, how the hell do we change this big globe build?
How do we like make this not abhorrent and kind of like, in my opinion, blandify it?
Which is why now it's the Observatory at Planet Hollywood, correct?
Correct, yes.
So this is how this is a redressed big blue marble, which looks cool sort of, but.
A little more restrained.
It's that new logo.
It's that, yeah, it's that Vegas logo too.
Lowercase, that's classy.
Jason's watch style sort of.
Jason's watch style.
Classy Jason watch style.
That water still looks weird, right?
They didn't clean the water.
Probably far too late they have the crazy milkshake trend.
They hopped on that trend.
Yeah.
That's disgusting.
I mean, it's like just caked on.
That building is entirely different looking than it used to be.
Yeah, yeah.
They managed to figure out something else to do with a big weird round.
As opposed to like all the other ones that are like that, like Myrtle Beach,
they just demolished.
Do you have that?
Okay, that's mid construction.
This is the original.
Oh, okay, okay.
Wow, you're right.
That's like an entirely, but you're totally right.
That's so different.
Yeah, yeah.
And the most 90s ever, which is I guess really why I'm in love with the place.
Ultimately, you feel the 94.
100% in its genes.
Yeah, yeah.
But anyway, I mean, is now the time to talk about the rise and fall a little bit.
And bring my favorite character into my favorite character in restaurant fiction,
Robert Earl into the scene.
Pat, are you familiar with the name Robert Earl?
Was this the guy who I sent you his obituary when he died?
It is not.
It is not that guy.
So here, so if we're explaining the whole backstreet, we'll go in order of how this thing
Yeah, no, go nuts.
The original guy, Jason, you probably read some of this in that Esquire article,
which is really great.
Kate Story is the writer on it.
So I'm pulling from that a lot.
But there was, okay, so there's a producer named Keith Barish.
He is the producer of Sophie's Choice.
And in his, of course, and in his, he had an actor, I don't know if it was his assistant
or just an actor who was around, was reading the script of the Flintstones movie
in this producer's office.
And it involved name checking a place called Holly Rock.
And this guy, Brian Kestner, was reading and he said out loud to the producer,
that should be a real place.
There should be a restaurant called Holly Rock.
And that is how Planet Hollywood got started somehow.
Wow.
From those odd beginnings.
And I guess the idea started spinning out of, oh, a restaurant where you could sit
next to the Ruby slippers or whatever from Wizard of Oz.
So that intrigued this producer who went and talked to the person
who's obituary found Bobby Zerum, who was a major Hollywood publicist.
And who seems to have all these colorful stories from the 70s and weird things about,
if you don't promote this movie, if you don't write an article about this movie,
I'm going to kill myself.
Like he's saying that on the phone.
So this is like a weird Hollywood crazy story guy.
This producer-
Is he a valley super in a liquor's pizza?
Oh yeah, I think so.
I think a very 70s level of Hollywood crazy.
This producer doesn't know anything about the restaurant business.
He talks to this guy, Bobby Zerum, and is there anybody you can introduce me to?
And he said, why, yes, Robert Earl.
Robert Earl is a guy I know who is part of the Hard Rock Cafe.
He might've been running it at this point.
He is a theme restaurant, I mean, entrepreneur, big wig, whatever you want to call it.
My little thesis for this zone that I wanted to describe is that Robert,
I think that Robert Earl is a theme restaurant addict.
I think that is what we're dealing with here.
And that kind of explains the rise and fall.
And there's a nice little button to that theory that I have.
But God bless his addiction because we've all gotten so much out of it.
So Keith Barish is introduced.
This guy introduces Keith and Robert Earl.
It should be noted also that this is the same guy, Bobby Zerum,
who introduced Mia Farrow to Woody Allen.
So all of his introductions lead to a lot of good in the world.
Anytime he can get people together.
So anyway, because this producer had also produced The Running Man,
they get cooking.
They start thinking like, oh, maybe we could get Arnold involved with this.
They literally pitched him on the set of Terminator 2.
And he said, yes, love it as long as we do Schnitzel.
Stallone seemingly big to be involved.
I think they might have told them and then was it Schnitzel or Strudel?
Or Strudel?
Might be Strudel.
OK, OK.
Jason, would you prefer a Schnitzel?
What is it?
Schnitzel is like a thin pounded pork or chicken.
And then it's breaded.
I would prefer Strudel.
I ate Strudel with you guys once.
We were eating at one of the Universal hotels.
And I had already eaten dinner.
So I just ordered Apple Strudel.
Yes, yes.
That's classic order from Jason.
It's nothing like Arnold's mom's.
Yeah, this is out of here.
Not in all the country.
Yeah.
So anyways, yeah, Arnold says yes.
Stallone begs to be involved hearing that Arnold was involved.
Bruce Willis said, yes, as long as my band can play all of the openings.
That literally was the contingent.
And now they're off to the races.
And then this, I think this is from the Esquire story.
This is so crazy that the two partners are talking about what are we going to call it?
It's not really going to be Holly Rock.
One of them says, I have a name, but I'm not going to tell you.
You have a name?
Yeah, I have a name.
I'm not going to tell you.
And as if in a scene from a movie, the two men said the name at the same time.
Planet Hollywood.
Too perfect.
I saw that too.
The most polished anecdote I had ever read, I think.
I believe that the reporter was told that anecdote, but I also believe he has been
sitting in his office fine tuning that anecdote for years.
So he just has it in his back pocket, ready to go.
Also, the story, I guess I remember.
As if in a movie, they got like just adding that in there too.
It's like Hollywood people.
The sheer amount of like Hollywood, hooray for Hollywood in this restaurant is just so
delightful to me.
It's just how we think.
We think in terms of magic.
I don't know.
It's a dream factory or something.
You know, like, you know, like you guys like if you've got like friends who are
like in the Writers Guild or whatever, or like anything they have to do, they'll
get incorporated at some point.
Oh, yes.
And you got to think your little name.
Yeah.
I've always said I've always tried to convince my friends when they do it.
I'm like, you should call it like Tinseltown Dream Factory or something like that.
Like, like, don't try to be clever.
Just make it like the night.
It's the same nerve of mine that just loves this whole planet Hollywood, you know,
T2 skeletons everywhere.
It's well, it's a yeah, it's a bygone era that, you know, like a little bit of
pixie dust falling off of the megaplex pixie dust is the megaplex production.
It's the same DNA as like never like in the 90s on Fox.
They had these like specials of like, how they do that.
And it's like it was all CG already, but it was like, yeah, remember that commercial
where the girl sucks her is a Pepsi commercial, but she sucks the bottle so hard.
She like gets sucked inside.
Oh, right.
Yeah.
It was a whole special time.
I made that video that commercial.
Yeah.
Oh, absolutely.
I would eat up anything like that.
I think, yeah, you're you're cluing into a thing that is very special about
Planet Hollywood that it is like just now that we know that everything's like filmed in a
green screen bunker in Atlanta, it's like all less all less magical.
The magic's a little bit gone and there isn't like and so being that was such an
the appeal to me as a kid is like being near the like I just watched these at home.
I never thought that I would be next to the masks mask.
And if any of that pixie dust could spill off onto me, maybe I could get into the business.
If you did.
Yeah.
If you did like if you were starting Planet Hollywood now, it would basically just be all
the restaurants would have like a hard drive or a computer near all the tables and you'd be like,
oh, wow, this Topi Maguire is like punching arm was rendered by this computer.
Yes.
In a minute, like 120 of Spider-Man.
Wow.
The computer that rendered it.
This is from this carousel.
Yeah.
So anyways, the just if I could explain a little bit more about Robert Earl,
we've talked about him before because we covered his restaurant Earl of Sandwich,
which is a sandwich restaurant as they might imply that's outside.
Well, I think we yeah, I don't remember it involved like Mike Mitchell getting
do we go inside?
Do we shrink and go inside his penis?
Or yeah, then we went what up is your eithra.
Yeah, sometimes every once in a while our show has magic and scenes in it.
Yeah.
Okay.
Not not not always.
I thought this restaurant had like a was like Mars 2112 where it's like now we're going
inside a penis.
That's a hell of a theme like the human body, the human body, the restaurant.
Did you ever do Mars?
Were you ever the speaking of Times Square?
Yeah, Mars 2112.
I went there once.
Yeah.
What was that?
What any any particular?
I mean, it was also kind of it felt a little last legs.
I mean, the saddest thing was that I mean, I'll be quick here.
I'm sorry.
I never sure.
The main thing was like the whole point is like you were supposed to get into like
you show up.
It's kind of like the Star Trek experience.
You know, the Vegas thing.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Where it's like you show up and you wait in line.
Then they're like, OK, get in this room and you're going to sit down and you're
going to go on a spaceship to Mars and then the door opens the other side.
And then you're like a video plays.
But we got there.
They're like, oh, yeah, this thing's not playing.
So just walk into the restaurant.
I was like, that's the whole point.
It was good.
I like that it's not I like that it's not a Star Trek thing.
It's like its own thing.
Original sci fi.
You're right.
Not not tied into one of the universes.
Yeah.
So it's just like but were there like kind of Battlestar cyborg kind of guys,
but like you don't know, like I don't have never seen this armor before.
Yeah, it was.
Yeah.
Nothing there was familiar to me in terms of likes.
I mean, maybe some knockoff Star Trek ship, but like it was not it was all.
I mean, there's not high quality.
It was.
You never see that that episode of 30 Rock where Tracy Morgan's like,
I think, son, who's kind of a con man has it has that restaurant
where like Godzilla's fight each other for your.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
I don't know if I saw this.
It's kind of a random poll.
Sorry, but I guarantee that restaurant is based on 2112.
Sure.
Right.
Yeah.
Godzilla fighting.
I'm sorry.
They did all play.
They did all the aliens did dance to.
Don't rock the boat.
What?
Why?
It's not about Mars.
Maybe they're like Earth's fragile ecosystem or something.
Oh, I see.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Too late.
We're all rocking the boat.
Yeah.
Sorry.
That's a tangent.
We didn't heed the aliens warning.
OK, so no, no, no.
Anyways.
OK, so Robert Earl, we talked about he basically
I became enamored with him partially off of this.
It really came from reading this Planet Hollywood article
a number of years ago where they described this guy as like the
it's about the downfall of Planet Hollywood and they describe this guy as kind of like a
he's a pear shaped version of Dudley Moore who walks around with his pants unbuckled
and his shirt tails hanging out.
And he's kind of this like flouncy silk shirt guy who's like kind of like
Robin Leach a bit raw, but maybe a little whiny.
You get a little verruca salt in there and any videos you see,
he's like T. Rex's little arms around and helping himself to morsels of food.
He's just this very odd little character.
And just really quick, I'll sit to introduce you, Pat, to
the man who brought us this establishment and continues to fight for it.
Here's a selection of photos of Mr. Earl.
Here he is at his other.
He also owns Bucatabeppo, which is why they paired up.
Well, you see on the right is actor Arnold Schwarzenegger.
That is the more buff fellow is also a governor.
And on the on the left is Robert Earl holding up a big meatball.
Is it eating meatball to Arnold?
Yeah, yeah, could be.
Eat up nummy nums.
Oh, that's another thing to know.
Somewhere in Planet Hollywood stories, I heard like the interviewer
asked him a serious question about having to declare Chapter 11 bankruptcy.
And he said Robert Earl's answer is, oh, yes, that was the start of the wobblies.
Well, wait now in the in the Esquire thing, they point out like
he was sued by Hard Rock because he basically opened a movie version of Hard Rock.
And he said the lawsuit was, quote, a real bloodbath and then added,
I'm probably fairly litigious and it would all be in a day's work.
He pauses that adds, I'm a sicko, so I was probably enjoying it.
A bit of a sicko.
What he's he's a character.
Here he is.
Just real quick.
Here he is with a young, fresh faced Will Smith jumping on his back and riding him
with the most loving smile you could give a nonparent.
Here's Robert with peak 2000s, Justin and Brittany.
Here he is at the casino with Sly Stallone and the I guess the King of Versailles,
the real guy from that documentary, the Timeshare guy, Robert Siegel.
Or David Siegel looks like according to his name badge, David Siegel, a great villain.
Did he own the Planet Hollywood Hotel?
They had a partnership.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It was called Westgate PH.
Yeah, well, he was trying to get he he kept fucking up and he was he wouldn't let go of it
and eventually did sell it to someone else.
But it was the Timeshare tower I think connected to Planet Hollywood.
Wow.
I see.
Look at this.
Yeah, I just well, I'm glad he met Stallone.
He also got some fun out of it.
He eventually bragged about like his his horrible company did an aggressive get out the vote
in Florida for their employees to vote for George W. Bush and then Al Gore lost by like 500 votes.
And when they did the survey of the employees, like a thousand employees who said they
wouldn't have voted, did end up going to the polls and voting for George W. Bush.
So he helped sway the election.
Yeah.
Oh, God.
That's his most successful endeavor, I think ever.
That building that big stupid house.
Yeah, that's right.
That's a well, America is his big, also this photo stalling rocking a kind of a one of these like,
I think he's rocking a plan of sort of one of those more chic Planet Hollywood shirts
we were talking about.
That's right.
Oh, sure.
He can make it work.
Look at that weird chain to weird like snakes or something around.
There's a there's a really I don't want to get on this tangent,
but there's a really crazy ad for a Sylvester Stallone pin.
And you watch it.
Oh, he's all about the pens.
Yeah.
Oh, is that a fair?
Oh, you know about the pins.
If you watch the Expendables, there's like one scene in every Expendables where he's like
signing the welcome to the Expendables.
Let me sign your contract.
And it's like a four thousand dollar skull pen.
Everyone loves the paperwork sequences and the Expendables.
Yes, I need to know how the arrangement starts to become an Expendable.
I need to see lawyers looking it over and in crisp closeups.
So I thought they were going to until I saw these like totally sweet ass pens.
Wow.
Scott Adkins is putting on his reading glasses and taking out his official pen.
This might get me to watch him.
Actually, this does sound good.
And then real quick, here's Robert Earl rubbing Trump's belly.
And here he is with Academy Award winner Kevin Spacey.
Planet Hollywood event.
So, you know, he hobnobs with the greats.
He's he's he's wonderful.
I don't think, though, that he like in terms of like that bad of guy, I don't know.
I don't want to say either way.
You know, you probably I should just stay out of this discussion entirely.
You never know what it's like.
Other than it sounds other than him, like, I guess, being like pear shaped.
Nothing sounds out of the ordinary.
And that was and that was a quote.
I have not said any fruit that I think he looks like.
Here's Trump.
There's Trump.
The plan Hollywood Marla Maples.
Trump in all black everything.
Look at the back.
You know, it's not bad jacket in the background that does appear to be a back.
I get in the background and a full cigarette ashtray.
Oh, man.
We used to be a proper country.
Oh, shit.
If he comes back in twenty, twenty four in the black turtleneck and a big black trench coat,
it's like, oh, fuck, we might be done.
Game over.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
I've this I've never been so attracted to Donald Trump.
I have to say that was very Bruce Wayne.
That look again to go back.
Mostly you're attracted his proximity to the back draft jacket is like, wow,
this guy is really the center of power.
I know.
Yeah.
No jealousy about being the president, being having the nuclear codes,
but being so close to that back draft prop.
So anyways, this guy is just such a funny character.
And I do think there is another quote from from from this Los Angeles Magazine article.
And this again.
All right.
So the story that I'm building of that he is a I think he's a theme restaurant addict.
This says a lot about him.
So he started he initially did some restaurant called like the Beef Eater.
He tried a lot of British themed restaurants in America and in Orlando.
He invented and operated what he estimates as 300 different chain restaurants and theme eateries.
Three hundred three different in England and America with names like Talk of London
and Medieval Banquet.
Wow.
Yeah.
Crown Place, just like whatever.
However, I can rearrange royal words.
Nice table.
Works great.
He'd give you the thumbs up.
Good.
Keep going.
More.
Are any of these medieval times predecessors or not just just regular British food?
I think they're just more like pubs or like a place where you'd go where they would make
the waiters where like the big weird like what are the like old British tutus?
You know what I'm saying?
Like the name of it, though, like it would be like on a deck of cards.
Right.
Like in your like he's like putting a big staff in the ground.
A puffy pants thing.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Totally.
Yes, exactly.
Yeah.
So they humiliated their waitstaff, making them wear stuff like that.
Quote, in all of these places, it's generally agreed the food was terrible.
Robert Earl is a very good brand developer, says Peter Romeo from Restaurant Business
Magazine.
Yet food is perhaps not his strongest suit.
The dining room experience where the fork hits the plate.
That's his weakest point.
So besides the plate, besides what's on the plate in your restaurant, he's really good
at restaurants, which continues to be true because has anybody been to a Bucatabebo in
the recent past?
Not since we had to go for the city walks for the saga.
Yeah, yeah.
No, I actually, to be honest, I only learned about it at all from your guys' podcast, to
be honest.
Oh, you didn't know the brand whatsoever.
No, I don't know.
For some reason, I just was not in my maybe I didn't grow up near them or something.
I don't know why.
For whatever reason, it looks I love Italian food.
Then don't go to Bucatabebo.
Yeah, they didn't give it.
The place where like truly like I don't understand how you mess up garlic bread.
Garlic bread, like just slather butter or easy mac on bread.
Like it's like any like just kitchen sink ingredients.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah, any markets.
Those are great.
Throw it in the oven.
I don't know how they made such awful garlic bread.
Just on a Ventura, they could just drive down the hill from City Walk, come back with the
ingredients and it would be like 10 times better.
Kroger makes a serviceable frozen garlic bread.
Just to get that.
Just to put it right.
You guys know what the origin of the name?
The name is so is so fascinating to me.
It's just like a city or something.
I don't know.
And he didn't know he owns it now.
He didn't name it.
But I am curious in the like, yeah, does that translate to something or?
Well, I know it plays a big role because one of the housewives bought into a location,
the location in Encino or Thousand Oaks.
And I was happy to learn that they also mispronounce it in hilarious ways, much like I do.
OK, who could you say?
Who?
Sorry.
He says Pepo.
He, Jason says Pepo.
I said, which apparently translates to bee pole.
I am.
And you've called it just Bucca, which I like as like as it's your friend.
He tried to get around it.
Yeah.
OK, I've got the answer here.
If we.
Yeah, it's possible we've come upon this and all three of us have forgot because that's
forgotten because that's happened a lot, I feel like, in the show.
But it means my buddy's basement because I believe the first one was started in a tiny
basement in Minneapolis.
So loosely translated into my buddy's basement.
Bucca de Beppo.
Did anyone come across Robert Earle's recent endeavors?
Kind of a horrifying epilogue to the planet Hollywood story.
I mean, I have something of that nature, but.
I yeah, you could if you if you want to read it, is it about Hollywood and Vine?
Yeah, yeah.
Let me let me let me let me go to it.
There's a little tease.
Yes, that's that's this is the story that I'm that I'm weaving here.
So anyways, Planet Hollywood starts.
They are booming.
One thing to say we haven't said, apparently there were in this time, people were not keeping
track of the movie memorabilia very well.
And you would think it'd be extremely expensive to get all this stuff.
But in fact, like nobody cared at the time now auctions, like all the stuff's going for
millions of dollars.
But they collected all of these items so easily, like the axe from the shining.
Apparently, they found in the in the garden shed of a guy who worked on the movie.
It was just sitting around all the fake blood on it.
And the people collecting props for the place said, what do you want for it?
And he said, well, I'll need another axe.
And that's all I had to pay.
Wow.
I love this guy as I love him.
Yeah, yeah.
Do you think we could get the dusting off my shoes if we just sent them our shoes?
Two for two.
Yeah, just a nice trade.
They're less scuffs.
These shoes are better shoes.
These are brand new shoes for your charge.
So anyways, the chain gets off the ground.
It's big right off the bat.
People do love eating next to this stuff, taking pictures of it.
As Jason said, Hard Rock Cafe, which he was currently working for,
he just outside of the company said, I'll do this other thing and start another thing
without asking them.
Hard Rock Cafe sues him.
He's not deterred.
I don't care.
He called the lawsuit bullshit.
That's again, theme restaurant addict.
He has to do this.
So now he's part of Hard Rock and Planet Hollywood.
How do we keep building this thing up?
Gangbusters success.
Stevie Wonder would go around and sing Happy Birthday to people if he was in the restaurant.
If it was somebody's birthday and the waitstaff went, he would follow them around.
And I'm doing it too.
That's how genuinely high wattage the star power was back then.
Happy birthday, the regular song, or he's singing his happy birthday to you.
Happy is his specific happy birthday song.
Oh, I don't know.
It's a medley.
You get every type of happy birthday in there.
Also, how did he follow them around?
Sorry.
Oh, um, hmm.
I'm sorry.
Tugged on a jacket or something.
I'm not sure.
So the stars are there.
The events are huge.
They gather up more and more celebrities.
The company goes public and understandably because the company has so much value.
As Jason said, the Orlando Planet Hollywood is the largest grossing restaurant in the world.
They make $50 million a year.
Wow.
Yeah.
Can you believe that?
50 million for one location, which was like a mammoth.
I feel like they probably could fit like a thousand people at a time in there.
Yeah.
And again, as we mentioned on the dive episode, a lot of these themed restaurants,
it's split 50, 50 food and drink, 50, 50 merchandise.
So they're just moving merchandise in Orlando and Vegas like crazy in Washington,
D.C. or Atlantic City.
Who knows how much they were really moving.
Oh, so half the half the revenue from the Orlando one, he said.
I'm saying, hey, all of them, any of them, like the profitable theme restaurant
will be like half food and drink, half merchandise,
at least back in the day when they were really cooking.
And we see how it was doing really good on both ends there.
Yeah.
They had it tight.
It was.
Yeah.
I mean, we're talking about the jackets and also you mentioned the blue drinks earlier.
Like I just have a very visual.
I feel like for some reason, I feel like I,
I an ordinate number of friends of mine have that, like my tie glass with the
Planet Hollywood logo on it.
Yes.
Which is I don't have my friends don't have logos,
spread cups from many different places.
But for some reason, I've seen that cup everywhere.
Wow.
I don't know.
I know that sounds really specific, but.
That's crazy.
I'm really jealous, too.
I would like one for sure.
Yeah.
I'll steal one for you next time.
But yeah, from one of your friends.
Yes.
So anyways, they go public when they go public at the company is valued.
At one point in time is higher valued higher than General Motors.
I don't know how that's possible, but just billions of dollars this company is worth.
But you go public and now you have to now you owe things to shareholders and you owe a certain
amount of growth, which is why they started opening restaurants to such a crazy degree.
And also, it all makes sense because when they do this, people show up in droves because they want
to see the celebrities in Nashville.
Forty thousand people stood in 100 degree heat to see the Lori Petty in Moscow.
Moscow was such chaos that people were just like climbing up on parking garages and trying to get
glimpses of people and somebody got himself into an unsafe position and fell off a rooftop and died.
These things are such pandemonium that people are literally dying at them around the world.
They start going into the trash cities like Myrtle Beach and Niagara Falls,
which those locations look so crazy.
The Niagara Falls one is essentially abandoned.
Like all of the Planet Hollywood branding is off of it.
It's all just rotting away.
It looks like Roman ruins just being reclaimed by nature.
Tons of dilapidated prop cars outside.
Just like I could see like just constructors throwing like workers throwing like armageddon
spacesuits into the river and over the falls.
It looks like suicides to passersby.
Is that spaceman okay?
Oh, I should Jeff Rubin, you know, Jeff Rubin, right?
Yeah, yeah.
He mentioned I told him I was doing this.
He's very excited.
He just he mentioned his favorite thing that he saw at Planet Hollywood was
the spacesuit from the movie Rocket Man.
Remember not the Elton John Rocket Man.
Who's the guy that's in it?
Harlan Williams?
Yeah, Harlan Williams, Rocket Man.
So just it's a big inflated like fat spacesuit.
Wow.
Oh, and it is in inflated.
It's like so it's you're looking at the version that's full of farts.
Think so.
I think it's like it looks it's like the funny one from when the I like a chip blows it up or something.
Wow.
Well, thanks, Jeff, for bringing that to our attention.
And thanks to our friend, Andrew Grissom, for loaning me a copy of Rocket Man on DVD
five years ago that I still have not returned or watched.
Yeah.
Now that there's now that there's listener heat on me, I'm going to have to do something about it.
So anyways, this yeah, this thing is growing to the probably this
unsustainable level and it's already becoming like the word is definitely out that the food is not good
because there's these openings that all of these top tier celebrities come to.
And at the openings, they always get outside caterers to make all of the food.
They bring in food from other places.
We cannot possibly make Tom Arnold eat this slop.
So that food reputation is getting out there.
Does Robert Earl say maybe we stop growing this as much?
Maybe we try to make this all a little more sustainable.
No, he wants more theme restaurants.
So with his own money outside of Planet Hollywood, again, he's always going around the back of the company that he works for.
He starts a new thing and that is called the official All-Star Cafe.
Does anyone remember the official All-Star Cafe, the sports restaurant?
I vaguely remember hearing about.
I mean, the whole the spin off, the other themed restaurants that Planet Hollywood tried to start could make their own episode.
I mean, we thought we did cover Marvel Media before because they were involved in that.
Yes, that's one. Yes. Yeah.
Yeah. Like not not enough that we're like opening restaurants in Moscow and people are falling off of buildings.
We got to be doing like every possible theme.
Marvel is a go.
Sports is a go.
He gets Shaq and Wayne Gretzky and Ken Griffey Jr. involved and and he opened their open.
And there's one of those in Times Square and Vegas and Cancun.
Disney World had one of the Wild World, a wide world of sports area.
But the thing that Robert Earl didn't realize is that sports appeal is very regional.
So if you open a Times Square restaurant that Shaq endorses, you're like, I'm a Knicks fan.
I don't like Shaq.
Fuck Shaq. Why would I go to the Shaq place?
So these started failing right away.
Immediately bad news.
But he somehow still had like a 30 million dollar evaluation from the stock market.
So he's coming in hot, even though these restaurants are all going to be gone in a year, like clearly.
But he's he's like, well, I need to rearrange things.
I have no choice but to dissolve this failing sports enterprise into Planet Hollywood and
therefore give myself more stock because my stock in the sports thing will now combine
with Planet Hollywood, thus diluting the stock of Arnold Stallone, Bruce Deme.
So his need to have this sports place also makes Arnold and Stallone all mad at him.
We're not making as much money.
And there's like a general downturn happening anyway.
Like the the.
What year is this?
This is we're talking like if the peak of it was 95, they made 12, 12.7 million.
Ninety six, they made four million in 96.
Their stock price was thirty two dollars and thirteen cents by 99.
It was one dollar.
That's how fast this plummet happened.
So this is like this is like some really insane version, even more insane version of the big
one of the big short is what you're describing right now.
Like, yeah, so much splashier money.
Yeah.
Much dumber like like with more like as opposed to like you got to really like stop and pay
attention to the bonds and whatever.
This is about Captain Crunch Chicken.
Yeah.
And the biggest stars in the world.
I have a video clip here that kind of sums up America's attitude towards this celebrity's
attitude.
And it's not a person you normally think of being a voice of reason.
Here we go.
I think of this is getting crazy.
Every one of these I go to, it gets crazier.
It's getting out of hand.
It's a lot to go through for a couple of turkey burgers and a hat.
That's Mark Wahlberg talking to an E Entertainment reporter about the Las Vegas opening where
Whoopi Goldberg is carried in.
Like Cleopatra.
Yes.
And Sylvester Stallone rides a chariot pulled by a horse.
Also disappointing to hear Mark Wahlberg of all people disparage burgers.
Yeah, really.
He would go on to start a business.
A lot of trouble into doing exactly that and a massive reality show.
And he just made this other crazy reality show that's just kind of like a stockholders
presentation for all of his various brands.
It's called Wall Street.
Yes.
But and there's a part where there's a Wall Street sign at the beginning and then spray
paint paints out the first L and turns it into an H.
And then it really is just like a PowerPoint.
But Michael Eisner appears in it very briefly.
So it's notable for that reason.
That E Reporter was familiar too.
I can't remember his name but that was a real flashback there for me.
Yeah, there's a clip, more clips of this online and the best is him talking to Dan Cortez,
who I believe is an MTV DJ.
And they go like, oh, hold on.
Take a step.
Watch out.
Mary Tyler Moore is walking behind.
But like they stay on the Dan Cortez interview and she just kind of waves.
Yeah.
This legend.
Get inside.
Yeah, get inside.
Yeah.
Look, we're going so long.
I apologize.
But the just if we're talking about crazy mashups of celebrity culture and like this is what,
thank God all this happened.
And thank God Robert had the theme restaurant addiction because we got magical moments like
this in Berlin, Stallone, Gerard Depardieu and the Fugees hanging out together.
Here's Drew Barrymore in the restaurant with a live tiger with a chain around its neck.
Here's Steven Seagal and a terrifying Donnie Darko bear in a crown.
I'm glad you got the bear too.
Yeah, I got the bear.
And in the wider shot, you can see the bear's t-shirt.
Oh, there it is.
It says Berlin groundbreaking.
So this isn't even the opening.
This is the groundbreaking with the bear.
They pulled this together just to dig up a little dirt.
That's right.
Wow.
Oh, there wasn't a Stallone did something like that where he like
plows through a concrete wall for one that never opened.
I forget where that was.
He destroyed it.
That was not planned.
Well, so we're going to start over now.
Damn it.
Is this bear some kind of Berlin like is he like the king?
He's like Berlin's official mascot or something.
He's got a little crown on it could be.
Yeah, it could just be a German thing where we're like, what is this?
He's the state bear.
I'm very scared of him.
He's the country bear.
He's their country bear.
Yes.
I didn't know Seagal was allowed.
I always thought Seagal like didn't get along with like the Bruce Willis's
and the Schwarzenegger's for some reason.
Oh, he's not an expendable.
He's not expendable.
He's like the only one.
Yeah, of that type.
Yeah, well, maybe they sent they only sent him to ground breakings.
The bear is actually in the expendables.
They hand him a fancy pen.
He struggles with his paws.
Let's go to Sydney, Australia.
Here's Charlie Sheen and a koala.
Here's Danny Glover blowing a didgeridoo with like a shirtless,
shocked up native kind of guy.
Here's George Harrison at the Miami Planet Hollywood.
It does not square to me whatsoever that George Harrison would have ever set foot
in a planet Hollywood, much less worn this bizarre shirt that is so much like all the
shirts we've been looking at today.
That's what I was going to say.
He's got Converse on too.
He's wearing Converse.
He's got a suit with that shirt and then he's got Converse on as well.
Are all these people that we've seen like the Danny Glover,
George Harrison, are they like just going there to be seen?
Are they investors or a little bit of both?
Well, yeah, it started as they would give agents and celebrities like shares in lieu of payment.
And then at a certain point, it just got so big there.
They were saying like, yeah, we just need to invite them.
We just need to get them a hotel room or fly them.
Like we don't need to pay them.
And there's probably not and there's not that many to give.
And by the time Earl dilutes it all with his sports shares, then like we can't
Harrison was begging to get involved, I bet.
Yeah, but there was no room for him.
Here's Ken Griffey Jr. looking kind of like stressed out next to
Dale of Chip and Dale in a bomber jacket.
It's Chip.
He's got the brown nose, doesn't he?
Yeah, yeah, that is Chip.
Like a chocolate chip.
Yeah.
Well, I think it's stressed out because of one of like All-Star Cafe is already failing at this point.
Good to see you, Ken.
It's me, Robert.
Before you rock the red, the red zebra carpet, you have lost 10 million dollars in the last month.
All right.
Have fun with Chip.
Off you go.
Here's here's Penny Marshall in fatigues.
What?
Yeah.
What's this?
Did she do this a lot?
She got the hat and the dog tags, too.
Maybe it's like the premiere of like what's that Danny Dan, Dan DeVito movie, Renaissance Man.
Oh, maybe.
Oh, interesting.
That's a pure guess.
Is that Laurie Petty or G.I.
Jane?
Oh, it might be Laurie Petty.
Laurie Petty's Lumen Lahr.
I got to catch up on.
I never seen Tangirl.
It's a serious movie.
It feels like this would be kind of but who knows a little like, yeah, like she's got to do.
And then what was my last?
Well, here's James Caan handing a child a giant machine gun
while a baby looks on horrified.
It's not quite a holiday.
This is like just a random photo in the middle of like Los Angeles.
Here, hide this for me, kid.
Here's oh, and this is the this is the highlight.
Yeah.
All right.
Here we have Bruce Willis in a fuzzy hat and sunglasses and a cut off mid-drift revealing
Planet Hollywood t-shirt with like his hairy chest hanging out.
He's got a harmonica.
He's got shorts kind of like riding a little too low to where we're going to start to see pubes.
And hanging off of him is Anna Nicole Smith showing as much bare breast as can possibly
be shown without nipple getting revealed.
Right.
Like there's like like that fabric is hanging on for dear life.
And then in the next one, they're sloppily making out.
Whoa.
But he's got the he's got the mouth organ in prime position.
He's got it ready to go.
You know, with the microphone on and everything.
Yeah, he's not going to look like he's like they're kind of debauched.
And but they're both so happy.
This is either like these were taken either at the
the highest peak of the restaurant success or like the day before they foreclosed.
So does it have an air of like last day before the apocalypse?
Like celebrating success or it's like Berlin and it's all falling apart.
I'd like to think that all the celebrity investors all had sex together eventually.
Big weird pile.
That's Anna Nicole and Demi and Sinbad and Tom Harcourt.
He was married to Demi at this point.
I mean, yes, it's probably their stage going like, what?
What is this?
It doesn't care.
I don't know.
The thing is really weird to me.
Yeah, I don't know.
Why am I?
Yeah, I'm like that seems more like nudity to me than what's going on with her breasts.
Exactly what you mean.
Yeah, the more egregious thing.
Yeah, a man's stomach, I guess.
Not here.
It's not like amazingly.
We've seen a lot of Stallone pictures and that guy's like pretty cut.
There's no body fat on that guy.
I'm amazed.
This is what Bruce Willis looked like.
You wanted him to be more shreddy.
I don't know if he's ever been like shredded like that.
Maybe not because that's not his vibe.
Yeah.
Yeah, I feel like John McClane's like an everyman, you know, just like a beat cop from New York.
Yeah, that's true.
Yeah.
I mean, a harmonica drinking wine coolers.
I've got a Willis.
This was in Esquire.
What are their photo collages?
This is one of the other big gets where you're like, I can't believe he's there,
but he's there in like the funniest fashion.
It's Jack.
They got wow.
Wow.
You don't say that seems like too a little too big in a way.
Yeah.
Well, here I'm trying to get the photo up again.
He's got an open bottle of Jack Daniels and a full glass of it.
Just cigarettes hanging out to who's that?
Who's that to me more than to me?
That's to me and Bruce.
Yeah, Bruce at his at his hangout spot.
You know, what is this photo?
Like, is this like 11 year olds collage?
No, the Esquire did the photos like it was a scrapbook.
Oh, I see.
It was pretty cool.
Yeah.
I was not making fun of your Photoshop skills.
Apparently Nelson Mandela would show up to like truly like the hugest people on earth.
Nelson Mandela dined with Harry Belafonte and Danny Glover at the private room at the Times Square one.
The Maryland room, of course.
The Maryland.
Yeah.
We all know.
I don't even need to say it.
In my brain, like no matter who like Belafonte or Nelson Mandela, like whenever they show up,
they come like leather jackets, sunglasses, shotgun and like,
John John John John John John John John John.
The Terminator thing.
They played that through the entire restaurant.
Yeah, that's just like a rule.
You have to wear that and that music plays.
And then they all played individual harmonica solos.
Go Mandela, go.
So anyways, hedonism, craziness, the biggest stars in the world, but it's starting to unravel.
Every one of these restaurants cost a million dollars to build and then a million dollars to promote.
But again, does Robert turn around and slow the ship down?
No.
Ahead we go.
Marvel Mania, I say.
Cool Planet, I say.
An ice cream store with a whoopee Goldberg flavor and with no further elaboration in this article.
And apparently also a flavor called Blueberrymore.
These existed.
There were a third street promenade had Cool Planet, a plant, the Planet Hollywood ice cream place.
I can't find any photos of this.
Nobody bothered to document it.
Why?
Why are we diluting things so much?
But surely he would stop there, right?
No, he decided what if there was a theme restaurant based around music?
And perhaps somebody should have said there already was that you worked for it.
You left that to do this.
No, no, I won one.
And thus he opened a place called Sound Republic.
Hard Rock is your that's your grandpa's music themed restaurant.
Sound Republic is the future.
It costs 28 million dollars to build the single location.
So how do you turn a profit from a restaurant with it that costs 28 million dollars?
So all of this to say things start unraveling.
There are way too many of these plant Hollywood's.
They start closing every one of these spinoffs closes almost immediately.
The original founder, Keith Barish left 2000 Arnold left.
So they still get together to give each other meatballs or whatever.
He would not be back.
In one case, he would not be back.
Then they're asking him in this article, what are you going to do?
You got to turn this thing around.
He says, I know it's not called Planet Hollywood anymore.
It's called Planet 2000.
Great.
That'll do it.
Apparently, that's what they did in Miami.
They just changed it to Planet 2000.
That might have George Harrison may have set foot in Planet 2000 in his life.
Two locations in Miami.
You know, always good to have two.
There's two just in Miami.
So Planet Hollywood is different than Planet 2000.
Oh, I guess so.
I want that shirt.
I want to plan 2000 sure that sounds like a limited edition kind of thing.
Yeah, they not exist.
They exist at all.
That's $2,000 at least.
And this was in the year 2000.
I assume.
Probably almost.
Yeah, a lot of symmetry.
Anyway, they were here though, because it was that and Fox was called Fox 2000 for briefly.
And then right.
Why brothers 2000 was just a movie.
They just called it 2000 in 98 way before 2000.
That's right.
Um, and then the idea was like, what if we get new cooler celebrities involved like Ben
Affleck and in sync?
What if we steal in sinks money?
Okay, do anything for you.
Well, it's no Jacob Sartorius, but that'll come at time.
He's like, not even probably wasn't alive.
Probably not.
Like he was, I think his parents were like, not even they were minors still, I think.
Yeah, I looked him up.
He's 19.
So yeah, he was 19 now.
Yeah.
Jacob, if all the listeners are like, God, these guys are so ignorant.
I went through a huge Jacob Sartorius era.
Well, younger listeners probably know him, but it would be weird if we were 36 year olds
and like, well, of course we know Jacob Sartorius.
Well, one of us is like that.
That's true.
Jason, you are like that.
I thought you would have like come across him in like the tween fest, like, like, like
as a reference point.
What medium was he on?
Was he like, who fucking knows like vine or like, uh, uh, uh, some like doomed like planet
Hollywood social media app.
They tried like pH plus.
Mike, what was the WWE one that they went in?
Well, there was a, it wasn't theirs, but it was tout.
Yeah.
He might've been on tout.
He might've been on vine.
Tout about tout.
Yeah.
So look, the wheels start coming off.
They declare, uh, they, they declare bankruptcy, a bit of the wobblies.
Um, and yet this motherfucker manages to keep the brand alive despite two
bankruptcies, despite losing the celebrities.
We of course know it is still the casino.
The restaurants are still around a little bit.
New ones are, are opening up.
And not only that, he has not turned his back on new theme restaurants.
He is a theme restaurant addict.
We know about Earl of Sandwich.
We know about chicken guy with Guy Fieri.
And this brings us to what Jason was alluding to.
A monkey's per, a monkey's paw curled somewhere.
Someone said like, I wish we had something like planet Hollywood and it just curled.
And thus, but thus, you know, Robert's generation had to combine with the
Sartorius generation.
And luckily he had a Sartor, a member of the Sartorius generation in his own family.
And that is his son.
This is Robbie Earl.
He has a kid now and his kid opened a restaurant called the Breakfast Club.
There is a new generation of Earl theme restaurant addiction.
The Breakfast Club is at Hollywood and Vine.
It is described as a restaurant where influencers and vloggers eat regularly.
Like a new media planet Hollywood with no proof.
There's no, like, there's no pictures of Sartorius hanging out or whoever the hell is popular.
Any of these Tik Tokers.
You would think that would be important to a place that's all about social media and
influencing to have a lot of documentation of it.
Well, it's an authentic place where they can create content, Mike.
You know, get yourself an $18 breakfast burrito.
You know, the breakfast meal that's usually famous for being under $10.
Delicious.
I'm a mascot.
I feel like you have to mention the man.
What's up with this mascot?
Well, he's a pretty like these are real pre NFT is what he is.
He's like he's he was an ugly animal before it was cool.
This is he's like a real like kind of sly perverted panda.
It's like a lounging stone panda rubbing a nipple.
What is the cause?
He's rubbing his own tummy like Robert was rubbing Trump's.
Do they only serve breakfast here?
I think they do.
I think they're only open in the morning.
And then you end, you know, just kind of like basic stuff.
Like, here's the pancake platter, you know, with just and they got some toppings and stuff.
And so it's a couple of pancakes with syrup and butter and it's only $24.
It's a reasonable price for what you can make at home for 60 cents.
It comes on a big piece of wood, though.
Yeah, that's true.
I'm intrigued by that piece of wood.
I don't think you get to keep it, but I'm interested why it's like it's not a plate.
It's a slab.
That was for that was touched by Harrison Ford and clear and present danger.
It's from the old collection.
I have to bid on these meals.
I got up to a thousand.
I would like to go here.
I would like to go here soon.
And it's.
You want to go?
Well, it's at Hollywood and Vine, Mike.
And I believe they love going to Hollywood and Vine.
You love that famous cross section.
I believe they also imply that Robert Earl may have helped create
helped with the developing 1600 fine, which I think not 100% sure.
I believe it's the apartment building where all the content creators,
all the vine people used to live in one apartment.
Wow, really?
Building.
And now I'm sure they pivoted to tick tock or whatever.
But it is right around the corner.
They had to find a new avenue that was called tick tock just to make the symmetry go on.
Yeah.
Wow.
I think this this proves though that Robert Earl, if we could get a hold of him,
would maybe do a podcast.
Oh, God.
Podcast restaurant.
Oh, you're right.
Oh, interesting.
Oh, he's going to launch our.
Oh, yeah.
I mean, like.
What would be called?
He called like rate and like eat and subscribe or.
That's yeah.
Yeah.
It would depend.
I mean, if it's a full restaurant.
Yeah, I mean, I guess you could go niche.
You could be ice cream like planet or whatever the name of the planet.
Hollywood ice cream place was.
I already forgot.
Cool planet.
Like there'd be like a I mean, there'd be like a Joe Rogan burger and like.
Yeah, but but.
Dak Shepard's fries.
They would all be there.
But if we want to stay within the like, you know, stay with how Robert likes to do it,
the hamburger would just be called hamburger.
And it would be just the grilled cheese.
It would be and then you would see Dax would at least be on the red carpet once.
But the cocktails would all be themed.
Though.
Yeah, cocktails would be named after podcasts.
The spooky mental haunted house.
Yeah, spooky metal.
Intrude to Whitney Cummings tweet, defending Joe Rogan,
a reference that will only make sense this very week.
Enjoy it.
You get a sampler, a sampler of different shooter, a sampler of like shots or little tasting,
like a tasting thing that says like every podcast, all three,
every podcast has three hosts who look like this, you know, that funny picture that.
That's very funny.
So funny.
Keep sending it, folks.
Accurate.
We all know who's who.
It's clear you all have the same answer for it.
The shot glasses should be little stars like for your to get your five stars that we all need so
much on it.
To this is this is the bone marrow of podcasters.
Give us our stars or we collapse.
One of you guys has if one of you guys get invited to this opening as podcasters yourselves,
you have to like one of you has to come with a harmonica or something.
Oh, yeah.
Either you're going to say has to wear a big belly shirt.
And I'll do it.
So I'll wear I'll wear I'll wear fatigues and a belly shirt to the opening.
That's a guarantee.
And a weird fuzzy hat and sunglasses and bring a change tiger as your date.
Podcast restaurant is a legit good.
I mean, sure.
Context of this conversation is a legit good idea.
Yeah, right.
Is it right now?
Right now here in this.
This guy made according to all it'll be a good idea for like five years and crash horribly,
but you'll get a couple of good years.
Sure.
There can be like a Sunday that's just vanilla ice cream, marshmallow fluff and whipped cream.
And it says a group of white men is called a freaking podcast.
That's another evergreen joke that no one ever gets sick of hearing.
Yeah, it's look, I think Robert, because Scott is saying has an addiction to getting restaurants.
So I think you got to give the addict the fix is what I'm saying.
So we get in front of him and we go, Robert, do you listen to podcasts?
And he goes, of course, I do.
Paul D.
Can you mean Paul D.
Cast?
Yeah, that's what I call them.
As a normal shape man, you must appreciate podcasts.
As someone who does not resemble any particular fruit, an unflattering fruit,
as a normal shaped man.
I mean, it is shocking that Stallone Schwarzenegger or Willis has not made
an unlistenable vanity podcast yet.
Have they?
Oh, you're right.
Maybe we just missed it.
Who?
That's a good question.
I don't know.
I don't think so, but it's possible.
It feels like that's coming this year.
Like, I feel like it's been a wave of like, didn't someone really?
Isn't Tom Hanks doing a podcast?
Oh, boy.
He's probably more.
I'm sure he's more compelling as a podcaster than Schwarzenegger would be.
But it's the beginning.
It could be the beginning of a train.
He's doing a Bandit Brothers podcast.
Okay.
So it could be the beginning of a wave of A-list podcasters.
I mean, I look I would like if all of the Planet Hollywood investors
all started a podcast network, the Planet Hollywood podcast network.
What do you call it?
Is that ho ho or whatever?
G-How.
Spendables podcast network.
On P. Oh, yeah, wait, yeah, yeah.
Play.
Wait, what was it?
Play-ho.
Play, yeah.
The Play-ho podcast network.
And every time a new episode drops, there's a lavish opening.
There's tigers and koalas everywhere that I can see.
Every episode.
We need this blockbuster culture to come back.
We miss it.
We don't know who's a star anymore.
I don't know who's popular.
I've missed Sartorius entirely.
We need to give the ball back to our betters, the 90s celebrities.
They were the best at movies and the best at blues harmonica.
If everything's moving to podcasts, then they need to as well.
I agree.
I think that we'll send an email to Robert Earl and we'll have plans drawn up.
For a podcast network and a series of 80 chain restaurants by next week.
And if we can time it correctly, then we could make it out of this endeavor
with 20 million dollars each or we all personally lose 20 million dollars.
Quickly.
Sell the stock quickly is what we have to do.
Yeah, we'll get the Queen of Versailles guy to help us funnel our money into something.
Yes.
To hide it.
We'll only be paid in credit.
We can only redeem at the Planet Hollywood Resort in Goa, India.
Which yeah, they've got deals for monsoon season.
That's the summer and monsoon season.
Seems to be their busy times of year.
Oh wait, so wait.
Yeah, I wish.
So if you never canceled the credit card, would it still be a valid credit card, you think?
I think, yeah, I don't.
I do wonder about that.
Or would it have just transferred to like, you know, whatever bank was backing it?
Would it have just been like, oh, it's a visa, you know, at Wachovia now?
Yeah, yeah, I would hope if you're not getting the logo on there, that's a loss.
Yeah, and if you can't get the reward, if you can't convert rewards to merchandise, you know.
I'd be disappointed.
All your bucks go to like All Star Grill, whatever.
Is All Star Grill, did any of those survive?
Like, can I go to like one random one that's still, you know, like there's still one
blockbuster that exists.
Like, is there still one All Star Grill or whatever?
Is there still a Planet Movies, the combination project with AMC Theaters?
Oh yes, in Columbus, Ohio.
If any listeners are from there, that looks unbelievable.
They did a big, it was like, this was a massive complex that was a Planet Hollywood restaurant
and Planet Movies by AMC of 30 screen movie theater and the All Star Sports Cafe.
There was all of this together next to each other in Columbus, Ohio that was opened up by
Kelsey Grammer and Shaq, all holding up big movie tickets.
This is where you can come to see the next Kelsey Grammer flick.
That's a real Wach, Wach Wolf, the one you feed, Wach Wolf comes out of you.
Everyone is a Kelsey Grammer to Shaq.
Grammer app announced the intro, but immediately fell off the stage and broke his ankle.
Oh no, Kelsey, stop doing these events.
Exactly.
And Gam, come on.
Scan the stage before you walk on it.
Pat, it's been so fun to have you.
Any closing thoughts?
Have you, has this invigorated you or you like, do we all need to go bang down the doors
of the Times Square restaurant and get in there again and party?
If it's genuinely closed forever, I would be sad.
I actually did like it because like I said before, it's just like, I mean, the food,
I don't really care.
The food, it's not good, but almost none of the food in Times Square is good.
So it's really just about what you're looking at around the food.
And yeah, I mean, it was such a, I would happily bang down the door because I just
feel like it is such a, it's just, it's, you know, I'm sad that it's, it failed so
spectacularly, but I'm glad that it did at the exact moment it did because it frozen
in time in this like late nineties thing, which is just so much of my heart is that
like it accidentally is a museum to be my favorite time in movie history.
Yeah.
Like they didn't think it was going to be a tribute to that and only that,
but that's how it ended up and like, Hey, it's yeah, it's when Hollywood was still on top
and things were expensive and crazy and loud and yeah.
And you know what?
There's just enough of it left.
That's what I like.
Like, unlike some, a lot of these places we're going to talk about this month are gone and
completely all star cafe to answer your question is gone completely.
But that one, I mean, as long as one or two of them, hold on, it's a bummer if,
if Times Square is gone, but we're, we're rooting for you Times Square.
Yeah.
If I, if I, if I see it open, when I walk by there, I will, I will go in and give you
send you guys a photo or something.
Please.
Please do.
Yeah.
Well, just tell it like a book plane tickets for us and we'll pay you back.
Okay.
Thank you sir.
We'll want to get right there ASAP.
Well, this was such a blast.
Pat Castles, you survived podcast, the ride.
What an awesome chat.
Thanks for giving us your time here.
I hope this was great.
Oh yeah.
So, so much fun.
Let's exit through the gift shop.
Is there anything you'd like to plug?
Sure.
Full front old Samantha Bee is at this as, as of this season, we're on Thursday nights
now at 10 PM.
All right.
So tune on TBS.
So tune in there.
I think you ever been involved.
How about, oh, here's a question on that show or college humor.
Is there any, is there like a, is there a prop or something that you would be proud to
donate to a plant?
If you had to represent some of your work in such a facility.
I, I don't know.
I mean, weirdly I, I, the college humor, I visited the New York office kind of
before they kind of, they let go of, unfortunately had to let go of a lot of
people within the last couple of years, but I visited the New York office and
they had like a lot of the old props that from my time, I felt, I felt like
Methuselah coming in there and being like, oh, like, like those are like the old
dorm room.
And I graduated 10 years ago or whatever, but I was shocked to, I couldn't believe
that a room that like a lot of the old weird props, like we had a TV show on MTV,
like for like a week back in the early, in the late 2000s.
Oh, a Viacom television show.
That should be readily available still to this day.
Yeah.
Can I do, okay.
So we got the podcast restaurant and we got the influencer restaurant.
Third restaurant is like different, like, and I think you could probably donate
some stuff here too, is like late aughts, early 2010s internet comedy restaurant.
The Kings of dot comedy era.
Of course.
Exactly.
Yeah.
Some super deluxe, some super deluxe merch.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Now we'll correct, well, you know, I'll call my friends at Funny or Die and go get the,
the forehead to Taze, Marion Cotillard's forehead to Taze.
The landlord.
The baby from the landlord.
That's the physical baby.
Yeah.
McKay will send her over.
Well, all right.
We'll start that to the Kings of dot comedy, the restaurant.
Wait, did I cut off your, your, your, your pluggery though?
Samantha B on Thursdays.
Thursdays 10 PM full frontal.
And I'm my Instagram handle is just Pat Castles.
My one word.
That's it.
Fantastic.
Awesome.
Yeah.
And of course all these future restaurants at some point.
Of course.
Yeah.
You know, we are pre plugging these things once they're up and running and,
and failing in seven years.
As for us, we'll put up a lot of these pictures and videos and garbage.
There'll be too much bonus content, I think on our Twitter,
where you can follow all the celebrity happenings at podcast, the ride.
You can also go to said Twitter to find out about tickets to our upcoming live show in
Brooklyn or visit the bellhouse and why.com and for the full celebrity episode lineup,
including the recent irresistible episode, Alan Hales lobster barrel,
checkout podcast, the ride, the second gate at patreon.com slash podcast, the ride.
You know, we talk about rides here every week, but there's nothing suddenly there's no ride
that I care about as much as the, the, the, what was it?
The deal them up.
I just want to be on a big one of those, like in a spinach and artichoke dip.
And that's it.
I'm going to dream about tonight.
I'd like to keep it as is now plus it up or demolish it.
I want to keep the appetizer wheel as is.
1000%.
Yeah.
It's perfect.
Thank you, Robert, for everything.
You're perfect.
Let's all say thank you, Robert, at the same time.
One, two, three.
Thank you.
One more harmonica blast too.
Yeah.
Oh, sure.
Right.
Hello.
It's for Bruce for Bruno for Bruno.
It's on fun time.
Beautiful.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.