Forever.
Dog.
All right everyone, looks like we're wrapping up
our celebuary.
Can I interest you in anything magic themed?
Okay, how about a restaurant run by a magician
that isn't magic themed, except sometimes when it is?
Great, and would you care for that to be an hour
outside of Las Vegas?
Excellent choice.
Okay, Eva Anderson will be right out with a big plate
of Chris Angel's restaurant, Ka Blip.
Happy Celebuary, this is Podcast the Ride.
["Podcast the Ride Theme Song"]
Welcome to the grand finale of Podcast the Ride's
a month long celebration of celebrity owned restaurants.
I'm a legitimately sad Scott Gardner
joined by Jason Sheridan.
I'm just, I've loved this month, loved it.
If you love it, set it free.
Oh, I don't think so.
Thankfully the confusion will start to override
the longing and the nostalgia with this episode.
Oh, this will feel like when you have a really great
vacation but then there's a bunch of travel hassle
on the way back and then you're like,
oh good, I'm just glad to be back at home.
Yeah, yeah.
Maybe that's where this goes.
Mike Carlson, hi.
I'm here, yes.
Look, this has been a wonderful month of saying
different names from the normal names we usually say.
Otherwise I say that.
You're Bob Gurr once.
We haven't said Bob Gurr once this whole month.
We haven't said, I don't know,
oh actually we've said Robert Earl a lot.
A little bit low on bad boys from Boston.
Not as much Aerosmith as you normally would say.
One or two, but I thought you were going somewhere else
I was gonna say, plenty of weird names today.
Well that's, yes, that's fair.
I haven't talked about the intimacy of any of these places.
So there's all these things.
Well again, maybe today.
This is an intimate setting, I feel.
You might also be, well I don't know,
listener, you might be looking at the title
of today's episode and it's not something
that you're familiar with.
This is not some in the past situation.
This is playing out in real time
and we get to talk to somebody who has experienced this
in the recent past, who's part of the story.
And hey, another sad thing about after this,
that no longer doing her residency,
closing out the residency,
but let's have one more good one here.
The great Eva Anderson.
Oh guys, I'm so sad, but I'm so happy.
Don't cry, cause it's over.
It's crying.
Laugh, cause it happens?
Absolutely.
It's something unpredictable, but in the end it's right.
Oh yeah.
No, I don't know about that.
Well, now that's a reference we use all the time.
Oh no, let's drag this one out.
No more, I want this one to never end.
Eva, thank you for joining us.
Oh my God.
And to, I think of all of the,
I think I've said this on many of the celebrity episodes
and about celebrity in general, it's been long in the works.
This one in particular, I would say, this is a,
I don't know, it's been going a while,
it's been building a while, there's a rich backstory here.
I'm so excited, you're talking to us about it.
Talking about Kblip.
Kblip, it's Kblip.
Kblip.
I guess, yeah, it hasn't been said out loud, right?
No, no.
And which kind of answers a question you might have,
listeners, when you look at this title, how do you say it?
And I don't think, remember how we didn't know
for a little bit?
I don't think he had ever clarified.
It's an awful lot of consonants next to each other.
To be fair, we also didn't know how to pronounce
grandpa's belegante before.
And you still didn't say it right.
What was it?
Gentay, I believe.
So embarrassed.
I'll edit it out and I'll make it sound like
I knew what I was talking about.
In May of 2021, we all were introduced to the word Kblip.
When the press release went out,
Chris Angel was opening a restaurant,
magician Chris Angel, called Kblip,
Chris Angel's breakfast, lunch, and pizza.
Of course.
What an intriguing rollout.
You look at some confusing consonants.
What could that possibly stand for?
Maybe if you were a real detective,
you would get that CA is Chris Angel,
but how could you possibly guess the rest?
When is this phrase ever been?
He invented a new phrase, first of all,
breakfast, lunch, and pizza.
It's kind of interesting in that pizza is not,
you think that we're going through breakfast,
lunch, and dinner, we're going through meal times,
but instead it ends at pizza.
Is pizza like sort of the prestige
as far as that phrase is concerned?
Like the, I don't know how you,
what are the parts of a trick, a magic trick?
The prompt, is it the pledge, the turn, the prestige?
Yeah, I mean, you expect it to be dinner, but it's pizza.
Like it's the turn.
Yeah.
Well, you're forgetting the part of the magic trick
where really loud corn music plays.
So maybe it's that.
Mwah, mwah, mwah, mwah, mwah, mwah, mwah, mwah, mwah.
Yeah.
Do you recall taking a stab as to what it,
how it would be pronounced before we were educated
that it was Kblip?
Oh, definitely, because we only saw it in print, right?
Until he actually recorded himself saying it,
which was months later.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It was only announced in print form.
I feel like I would have guessed like Kablp.
Kablp, Kabliple.
Yeah, I think we were trying.
Kablip.
Could be Kable P.
Yeah.
Kable P.
Could be all viable.
But I mean, how to even get into this,
and why the Criss Angel fascination, I suppose.
Like, why was there so much interest
in this odd arbitrary celebrity venture even then?
And I feel like the answer is you've had an ongoing
Criss Angel fascination to some extent.
Right.
But there was a person who got me into Criss Angel initially.
Yes, indeed.
That being Jason Walliner, who happened to be our guest
a few weeks ago for Dive,
back at the beginning of this glorious month of Celebrewery.
Well, while Jason was here with us to talk about Dive,
we took a little time to discuss his ongoing relationship
with Criss Angel.
We take you to that conversation now.
Okay, we're here in the past with Jason Walliner
and Diva Anderson as well.
Eva's taken us on a journey through Kablip,
which Jason, I know you were very versed in,
but just kind of a setup to everything,
because she's credited you as being maybe the person
who brought the wonder and the magic of Criss Angel
to kind of this group of people.
If there's anything you'd like to talk about
in terms of your Criss Angel journey.
Yeah, mine was when he first came on the scene,
we were doing videos in New York with this,
as this group, Human Giant, me and Paul Scheer
and Aziz Ansari and Rob Hubel.
It was even before,
it was before we had an MTV show, before anything,
and those guys were obsessed with Criss Angel
and we flew ourselves to Vegas.
Oh no, maybe we were there doing something
for that show, Best Week Ever,
but we were just running around the strip
with those guys in long wigs
and we filmed something called Illusionators.
That was like a Criss Angel,
it was like a parody of Criss Angel.
Where everybody, was it Paul and Aziz were?
And they had the lisp like him a little bit.
They had the lisp, yeah.
And yeah, this was pre the show, Eva,
this was like one of the first things
you guys did together was Criss Angel.
This was just, yeah, and it was before YouTube
and so it was just, I guess,
to show at like a live show at UCB in 2005 or six or something.
So it was like 15 to 16 years ago.
Jeez, it's been a long journey, I really like to have.
Everything, I feel like 10 years
got added to any amount of time.
Any, like COVID somehow added not two,
but 10 years to any number.
Anyway.
He had that show Mindfreak and then we did that
and then we got a show on MTV, we did a few of those.
And then we had gone to see him in Vegas at some point
and I've never met him.
He met those guys at one point and he was just like,
I think he was like,
Imitations, the sincerest form of flattery.
And then we all kind of fell out of touch.
I fell out of touch and then I was in Vegas,
I guess about five years ago with a group of people
and we were like, we should just go see the Chris Angel show.
I remember being nuts and we saw it
and it was just way more nuts than,
it was a totally different show
and it was completely crazy and really funny.
One of the funniest things I had ever seen.
And then wound up just telling everyone
and making people and going back,
I think I've gone like four times.
And then Eva and I and a few friends,
Tom Sharpling and maybe John Daly, was he there?
Was he there?
He left before the fundraiser.
He wasn't at the fundraiser.
He was at the show that we went back to Vegas to see it
and I got kicked out of that show.
It wasn't because I was like screaming,
laughing the whole time.
It was because there's a segment of the show
and it's kind of hard to talk about without
without being insensitive, but there's a segment.
Very, very tragically, but also currently not tragically,
Chris has a son named Johnny Christopher
that is dealing with having pediatric cancer.
And so that is one of the most important things to Chris
and he's done a lot of charity work with it
and it's very admirable.
There's a part of this show that was,
or still is in the show, Mind Freak,
that is like a 20 minute thing about pediatric cancer,
which obviously is very serious,
but also this segment of the show
is one of the craziest things I've ever seen.
Too included in a magic show with goth vibes
and industrial music and it's a real tonal shift.
It's a real tonal shift.
It gets very serious and very upsetting
when you're in the middle of this really crazy magic show
talking about his story.
But then the trick he was doing,
he doesn't quite do the same thing,
the trick he was doing was that he talks about
what a horrible thing it is and how hard it is for families,
but then the trick was that I think he wheeled out
a hot assistant on stage in a wheelchair
made to look like a kid battling cancer,
so she had a bald cap and a wheelchair
full of stuffed animals and then he made her levitate
and revealed her to be hot and floated and cured her
and floated up underneath her.
And cured her.
Yeah, yeah.
Let's not rush past that person.
He was like, but tonight is about life
and then it just immediately became like a laser dance party
with these like Jabberwocky kind of knockoffs
like doing these flips and him with like a laser
and a mirror making the laser go all over,
playing this like techno music
and it's just like so crazy and such a,
I mean, but also so personal and it just hits
that sweet spot of like very sincere and also very insane.
In a show that also includes,
like my strongest memory of it was there's a runner of,
there's people who have blue paint
kind of coming off of their,
or is it just one character,
is it like a woman who has some blue paint
streaked out of her mouth?
Oh, because she sucked the woman's dick?
She blew the blue man.
Oh, that's right.
That's when we first saw it,
it was just so full of like jokes like that
and he would bring a guy up on stage and be like,
how thick do you think this platform is?
And the guy's like, I don't know, three inches.
And he's like, three inches.
Like just like some dick jokes.
And just really, oh, and then he had this,
oh gosh, there was this like the maestro,
that was a character that's no longer with the show
of this little Latino guy, just really offensive
who was with this heavy woman.
I mean, it was just like, it was a crazy amalgam
of like jokes and serious stuff
like the childhood cancer segment.
Sorry, punctuated by Jonathan Davis music,
the guy from Korn.
Oh, yeah.
And then a guy on stage like wailing on the guitar,
playing it live, I think.
And so then we went back to see,
cause he was doing, oh, so he was doing this benefit
for his charity, Help, which does stand for
Heal Every Life Possible.
But Tony Orlando, who was the host,
kept saying that it stood for Help Every Living Person.
He just chanted, Help Every Living Person.
It wasn't correct.
And it's like, how do you do that?
And so Chris Angel's always had a kind of a problem
with acronyms.
Yeah.
It's a tough area for him.
And so we saw the regular show
and then we were seeing the benefit
and during the regular show,
we were all drinking and having fun
and just marveling at it.
But then that night he had, after the cancer segment,
he's in the audience, ladies and gentlemen,
Johnny Christopher, and he had brought his son there.
It was like 11 o'clock at night
and the kid was like, three, I think.
And then he holds him up and I was like, wow, that's crazy.
And then he had a guy from the show
walk to the middle of the aisle and start taking photos.
And my kind of drunk brain was like,
oh, I guess we can take photos of this part.
So I pulled out my phone and just started taking photos.
And then five seconds later, a guy was like, you, out.
And they pulled me out of my seat, walked me to the back.
I was like, I'm so sorry.
I was so excited.
And I saw the other guy taking photos
and he's like, delete him.
And I had to go through and I deleted it.
And then another one popped up.
He's like, that one too.
And I had taken in the span of 10 seconds, 65 photos.
And I had to delete everyone.
I was like, can I go back to my seat now?
He's like, no, you're banned.
I was like, no.
Did he do forever?
Did he take a picture?
No, it was only for that night.
I could not go back to the show,
but luckily I was able to go back to the benefit,
which was great, yeah.
It was four hours long.
There were stars in it, right?
Gary Oldman was there.
What?
Oh my God.
Gary Oldman is Chris Angel's best friend.
We all know that, right?
They are best friends.
If you look it up, it's well-documented.
Really?
Wait, Emmanuel Lewis, you said?
Oh.
Gary Oldman.
Oh, okay, yes.
Wait, did somebody say Emmanuel Lewis?
I thought you said, I heard something.
That was a phantom phrase.
I wanted it to be true so badly.
Scott has Emmanuel Lewis' name ringing in his ears.
I know, I bet you did.
Did somebody say Emmanuel Lewis?
He probably was there.
It was Gary Oldman, Andrew Dice Clay,
Carrot Top, Flavor Flav, Siegfried and Roy,
Jerry Lewis in his last live appearance.
Wow.
Ever?
So Rick Thomas, so many, who's that other guy?
Something Brown, this in person.
Yeah, it was a who's who.
Terry Fader?
At one point.
Is Terry Fader there?
I think he did, maybe.
Yeah, he did one bit.
Jerry Lewis said in his small presentation
that he had just completed a movie,
which was his last movie, that he said
was like perfect reviews right now on tomatoes.
And Tom Sharpling was next to me
and he just like opened his phone up, looked it up.
It was like a 15%.
Perfect reviews, perfect 50%.
My shining moment though was,
cause we were way up in the balcony
and you had to bid, you could bid on things from his life
and then that band Imagine Dragons
came out to introduce one of the items
and they were just like, the main guy was like,
childhood cancer is a serious thing
that affects so many families in the United States.
I can't even imagine and I just said, dragons.
And then like the whole section started laughing
and then I was like, man, if he can't imagine dragons,
we're all in trouble.
Just completely being idiots, jerks.
Do you remember this Jason, that we found out
ahead of time that there was like a,
one of the things you could bid on was to spend the weekend
in Chris Angel's house and like have the whole run
of his like weird goth palace.
Yeah, we tried to get it.
We actually like put all our money together
and then leading up to the moment you got on the phone
with a bunch of people in LA and got them to commit.
Yeah, I think Nathan Fielder was gonna go in.
Yeah, we were gonna.
She was gonna go in.
I just watched that clip recently.
I think you can hear they're like, can we have a bid?
And I think you're the first bid.
Whoa.
Because it went for like what?
Like how many?
Within seconds we were outbid.
Yeah, but I think it went for like at least 25,000,
maybe a lot more than that.
But they're like, okay, a weekend at Chris Angel's mansion
with a private cook and blah, blah, blah.
And they're like, do we have any bids?
And Eva was just like $300.
That's all you got to do between all this.
We had a high, we had a low.
We were starting low.
We were starting.
You don't wanna start with your max.
But some like, someone from Abu Jabi
clearly bought it for like, it's just a ridiculous sum.
One person as opposed to 50 compiled from multiple cities.
That's really insane.
Mike, you were saying you had some, a celebrity presence.
Oh yeah, yeah.
When you saw Chris.
So I saw the Chris Angel show, Mind Freak.
I saw it, I was alone.
I was in the last row.
I was in Vegas alone for a night.
Which I remember, I remember Bugman texting me
and saying, I'm at Disney.
And I go, well, I'm in Vegas.
He goes, on a Thursday, who are you, me?
But I was there like a night before.
There's a wrestling show.
Anyway, so I'm alone and I'm loving the whole show.
And he does the whole rave at the end.
It's a big celebratory thing.
And then he goes, I want to introduce a special guest
who's here.
Ladies and gentlemen, Pitbull.
And Pitbull comes up on stage and they just like,
they just praise each other back and forth
for like seven minutes.
There's no song, he doesn't do anything.
He was just in.
Not part of an illusion?
Nothing.
He's just there to exchange pleasantries for like minutes.
And it's even, I was, everyone around me
could have given a shit about it.
I feel like I was just like looking around
for like strangers, like what?
Do you see Pitbull?
And they're just like, whatever,
we got like comp tickets from the hotel.
And it couldn't have been a better ending to that show.
So he, Chris brings it.
It's spectacle.
He brings his A-game to everything he does.
And we're gonna find out if that is also true
of his restaurant, which I know that you're very versed in,
have not been yet.
But is there anything you'd like to say in advance
about Kblip as we start to dive in?
Is there anything you wanna make sure
that we sufficiently address?
I mean, just are you, or just how excited are you to go?
I'm just so excited to go.
I think, well, I'm trying to wrangle a group
to go in March or April,
cause Chris is unveiling a new show,
a Mystica, it's called, A-M-Y-S-T-I-K-A.
That's a prequel to Mindfreak, which is interesting,
cause Mindfreak does not have a story.
Unless it's about the first child who ever got cancer.
If we're going back to the beginnings of cancer.
The first show that split.
But it will definitely hit Kblip then.
So I know I am so excited.
I'm so excited to hear what you guys say about it.
And yeah, I can't wait.
Fantastic.
All right, well, we're gonna then go back to the future.
Eva's coming back with us.
So you stay, Jason, you survived podcast right again.
Thank you.
Let's go back to the future.
Okay, thank you, Jason.
Thank you.
No longer the Alec Baldwin of podcast The Ride.
So that fills us in on some of it.
If we can remember what he said back then.
I mean, so, I mean, point being you've seen him,
you've been enamored with his man.
We've all seen, wait, I forget Jason.
I have not seen it.
You have not seen it.
I saw the show and I saw Pitbull.
I, yeah.
Chris Angel, Jason Waller told me about the show
and I drove to Vegas the next morning and saw it.
That's how I saw Chris Angel the first time.
He, we were at the Magic Castle.
He described the show to me.
I got in my car at nine in the morning,
just drove straight to Vegas, saw that show that day.
So I'm sorry, just to confirm,
you were in one magic based environment.
Yeah.
I slept eight hours or so, it was six to eight hours.
Then in the morning, got in your car
and drove to a second magic entertainment based environment.
Yes. Okay.
Then, like two years later,
Chris opens a new show at Planet Hollywood.
The first one was at the Luxor.
Second show was at Planet Hollywood.
He announced- Incredible by the way
that he's also tied to Planet Hollywood
and therefore Earl, all the pieces of celebrity
come together.
Right, or where was the Nitro Grill?
Nitro Grill was at Excalibur.
Excalibur, sorry, yeah.
But she is right there.
Yeah. Yeah.
So I found out I was going to start a job.
I had like two days.
Chris Angel announces that he's opening his new show,
Mind Freak at Planet Hollywood,
that it's a totally new show and it's immersive.
Oh. Right.
I get in my car, I drive to Vegas that morning.
I buy the meet and greet ticket.
I get my picture taken with Chris Angel,
which should be advertising this episode actually.
Yeah, sure, yes, yes, yes, please, yeah.
He hugged me.
Wow.
As I walked away, they said,
okay, that's the last meet and greet
Chris will do for the rest of his life.
I don't know why they said that.
What?
I don't know, it's really weird.
And also the weird thing is that
the picture you took with him, he ages in the picture,
but in real life he stays the same.
Yes.
It's like a Dorian Gray sort of scenario.
The show was not immersive in any way.
It was the exact same show he had been doing previously.
What?
The only thing that was different is that you walked
into the theater under a giant head of Chris Angel's.
Right.
That it was half one makeup, half the other makeup.
Otherwise, same show.
Okay.
Still defeats pediatric cancer at the end.
It's all the same.
And still spins around all fast, like that kind of thing.
Spins fast, upside down.
Did I regret it?
No.
I never regret getting in my car and going.
You met it, was there any discussion?
Were there any particular words exchanged beyond the hug?
Oh, hey, hey.
Hey, yeah.
All right, bye.
That's what a meet and greet is.
Have you guys ever done one?
That's what it is.
It's hard to get anything in.
Jason and I waited eight hours to meet Bruce Springsteen.
Really?
Was he nice?
Yeah.
Hey, hey, hey.
I was like, how was it going, Bruce?
And he's like, this is weird.
Really?
Oh, that's sweet.
Yeah, I mean, it was an intense opera.
There were so many handlers.
There were so many people.
Couldn't really say much more than, hey, smile, thank you.
And it was at the Grove, too.
So seeing an abandoned 5 a.m. Grove shopping center.
Whoa.
And yeah, it did not go.
The wait was, I think, crazier than we thought.
They made a lot of mistakes
as far as the wait was concerned.
That's weird it wasn't at a concert.
The Grove, home of our future mayor, Rick Caruso.
Yeah.
He's gonna be our mayor.
He's the insane rich man?
He even would have built the Grove.
He's running for mayor.
Oh, okay.
He announced yesterday.
I assume that the plan includes
taking everything in the city.
I mean, like every house and library and post office
and making it look like the Grove, right?
I'm into that, yeah.
Tear down ground.
If that's the case.
Just arbitrary columns everywhere.
Bug main lives above the Grove-ish breakfast club
on Hollywood Vine.
Yes, yeah.
Bug needs to be allowed a window everywhere in the city.
And I vote for him.
So that was 2018 with Chris Angel.
And then I feel like Chris Angel's
kind of faded into the background for a long time.
Personally, like you guys,
I got very interested in David Copperfield and Blue.
Kind of took the baton in terms of,
at least in this little scene of people.
I'd say David Copperfield became the MVP of Magicians.
And I feel like in the grand scopa thing,
like Chris Angel is very much stuck in the world
of like 2006, like the mid 2000s.
And that's what Vegas is perfect for.
You, whenever you were at the height of your powers,
you can just freeze yourself
and then do daily shows in Vegas and make a fortune.
For people who like don't mind that you're stuck in that era.
Yeah, for people who want to go on vacation
and see like the famous person that they remember.
But like, I feel like the difference is,
Chris Angel was famous, like cable TV famous.
And David Copperfield was famous
when there was a lot less television channels
and had like prime time specials watched by millions.
Sure, yeah, yeah.
Chris, David Copperfield dated Claudia Schiffer.
Yes. That's true.
There's an episode of The Americans
about them watching David Copperfield.
Like that's culturally relevant, right?
He's important. Right, right.
Chris Angel, bro. Chris is fun.
Yeah, I don't think we talked with Jason
about Mind Freak too much.
Did you watch the show?
Did any of us watch the show?
Do we have specific memories about his cable show?
I've only seen the clips of like the,
like taking a person and the person,
like he takes like the legs out from under someone
and like they're just their top half.
Am I crazy that that's?
That's probably one of them, yeah.
And there's like a fly, he would like fly quote unquote.
And it was all like, kind of like street magic,
but like more intense and extreme.
But he was never doing like the dangerous David Blaine stunts.
He just was like under the radar,
I feel like in a certain way.
But a certain type of person really loves Chris Angel.
It's his stead, I mean, he's got the Ed Hardy aesthetic
kind of thing going from that time.
That's I think a lot of what you think of is like,
I mean, maybe if people really know,
then you know what the illusions are.
But yeah, what's deafening to me is that style.
And it's that all of his graphics have like
big knots of thorns in him.
And it's, you know, fire transitions
and that he looks like the crow.
Yeah.
That's all the big, you know, if I had to,
if I was, what's the pyramid or something
where I'm trying to say everything but Chris Angel
to a partner is the clue.
Yeah, yeah, thorns, eyeliner, long black hair, crow.
Moxie claw. Strange voice, strange voice.
Lisp.
Jeans with designs on the butt.
Like very like embroidered jeans somehow.
Yeah. Yeah.
But he wants to change my answer.
Now, if I get Chris Angel as a clue on the pyramid,
I should be saying,
diner, family, home cooked meals,
connection with friends,
great place to eat after fun motorbike trip.
That's the thing.
His vibes are so all over the place.
Cause yes, he has raised a lot of money
for pediatric cancer research.
He also has the weird Ed Hardy aesthetic going.
And then he is like, I would say aggressively patriotic.
Like a guy you wouldn't,
I guess it's not surprising someone who carries that aesthetic
like is really like, God bless America patriotic,
but it is still strange to hear it come out of like,
you know, the extreme magicians mouth.
Such a creepy voice.
Yeah.
We take our patriots.
He's a Jersey Shore guy ultimately, right?
His name's Chris Seren Tacos.
His father owned a burger and ice cream restaurant.
And he worked in these from like Jersey.
Yeah.
So that sort of explains some of the blue collar feel.
Yeah. And it's a lot of, I don't know,
like there's a similar vibe.
I don't know if it's all magicians.
Maybe we've talked about this before.
I forgot.
They all have a similar thing of like,
people told me I couldn't do this.
People always look down on me.
And it's like, I saw Copperfield and Chris Angel
so close together and they both have very similar narratives
in their shows of like,
people said I was a loser and I would never be a magician,
but I proved them wrong.
My dad wanted me to not be a magician and own a restaurant.
I proved him wrong.
Like, what?
I proved I could do a different order.
Never let people tell you you can't do what you want to do.
Like that's the vibe.
All magicians have like chips on their shoulder
a little bit.
Yeah.
He's a Long Island guy.
Oh, sorry. He was born in Long Island.
Not Jersey, Long Island.
He might've probably likely went to Adventureland.
Yeah, he's a Disney guy.
He's a Disneyland fan, I believe.
So yeah, he obviously likes fun.
He likes fun.
You know, tricks.
One fun thing before we get into Kblip,
that in the 2000s at the kind of the height of his powers
around Mind Freak, he filmed an episode of MTV's Cribs.
Did anybody else come across this?
I've seen it in the past, but I didn't rewatch it.
So he has this compound in Vegas called Serenity.
Compound.
Do you have the notes open?
I do, yeah.
My notes?
On the first page,
I'll be...
Oh, I see.
Oh, okay.
Oh, you're giving it.
Oh, let me get it out.
I'm sorry.
You want me to give you a direction?
Oh, yeah.
This is great.
I love this.
At the bottom of the first page,
if you'll be...
Scott, if you'll be Chris.
Yes.
Sorry, Mike, you'll be Ed.
So Chris is introducing his personal chef,
whose name is Ed Bible.
Okay, so I'm saying...
It's the first line is Chris.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And wait a minute.
Oh, and then it's an Ed Bible line,
and that's the scene.
Okay, okay.
Gotcha.
I know nothing about cooking.
I can't even boil water.
That's why I have the best chef, Chef Ed.
Always preparing, always cooking.
Basically the same meal for me every day.
Grilled chicken, rice, four times a day.
That's it.
Oh, you say it.
You say it.
That's it.
So, in his MTV Cribs,
he makes his chef talk about how he makes
grilled chicken and rice four times a day.
And that's...
Four.
That's it.
That's an odd meal amount.
That was all he was eating up till a point,
at the height of his pre-dad,
when he was not a family man.
He was on TV, was all sexy.
Very slight, slender, yeah, yeah.
There's also a part where he shows this Dolly painting
with Jesus, Dolly-inspired painting,
where he's cut his own hand and dripped blood on it.
Uh.
And made it look like it's Christ's blood,
but it's Chris's blood under the painting, on the floor.
Well, Chris is only one letter away from Christ.
That's actually my blood.
I actually cut my hand and did that.
And I just thought that was a very poetic
and profound piece of art.
Wow.
He's real sexy.
This is probably around the time he was dating
Holly Madison from The Girls Next Door.
After that show ended and she left LA and stuff.
And she talks about him being an insane man,
like being very possessive,
especially as ticket sales started to drop
or the show started to not go well.
I'm guessing the Luxor show.
And then she said he insisted on having one of his bodyguards
travel with her.
And she's like, yeah, I'd just be out to dinner with friends
and they'd be like, who is this?
I'm like, this is Christ Angel's bodyguard.
Which for me raises two questions.
One, why does a magician need bodyguards?
And second question, why does he have bodyguards to spare?
Why does he have lenders?
I got enemies everywhere.
Enemies always coming after me.
Other magicians, probably.
Well, other magicians, I mean, it seems like there is a lot.
They can disappear, they know sleight of hand.
They're not as good as me,
but they're better at magic than the bodyguards.
So they gotta watch out.
If Lance Burton gets a drop on me, I'll be ready.
It's a double, he must be using a double.
There's no other answer.
So there was like two years I lost track of him.
And then when pandemic started,
I feel like we were all kind of like looking in on,
like going back and looking in on people.
Cause like Copperfield was posting blue in a mask.
Just a photo.
Who was kind of like quiet.
If we weren't like spoiling it, there was that in the show.
Like there was not a lot of public blue stuff out there.
And then all of a sudden blue is doing little dances.
In a mask?
Did he do this, like did blue do the song about like,
wait, I'm gonna mess up the like, don't go out.
Don't stay, it's a famous song that's about.
Oh, right, right, right.
There was something like that.
There was something like where yeah,
blue was giving us a pandemic message.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
I don't remember specifically.
But pivoted pretty quickly to like,
oh, this is the worst, huh?
Like, oh, when are we gonna open back up?
I feel like today's topic, some like,
when are we getting open?
And when are we getting rid of these masks?
Yeah.
You had a restaurant.
April 2020, he's like, I'm sick of being on the island.
What's it called?
Oh, yeah, Musha Kay.
Yeah, he's sick of Musha Kay.
David, when are we gonna open up the businesses, David?
I'm sick of being in your private museum, David.
Let me out of the private museum.
We've already eaten all the monkeys.
We gotta get off of here.
But I checked in on Chris during this time
and I totally missed, he had a second child.
So we already knew about Johnny Christopher
because Johnny Christopher is part of the show.
Right.
Christos Yanni had been born
and was just part of the gang as well.
And so he's like doing little,
he's doing little kind of,
we're doing pandemic things
with Johnny Christopher and Christos Yanni,
same name backwards.
That's very strange.
Yeah, wait, wait.
That's, okay.
Well, this is a whole thing, we'll keep finding this,
I don't wanna spoil all of them,
but in the Chris Angel world,
there's a big recurring thing of reusing names.
Reusing names.
For both products and children.
More than anything, names are finite to Chris
and he comes up with a name
and then he can't come up with any more names for a while.
So that wasn't so, but then May,
so for a full year, he was like,
being a little passive aggressive
with Anthony Fauci on Instagram,
mostly just showing his kids doing stuff.
Well, he was like, I wanna believe in you.
It was like this weird tension
of him seeing Fauci briefly unmasked
and be like, I got kids, my kid needs to be safe.
Wear your mask, Fauci.
So it was like that version of his, a little complicated.
Really analyzing him.
Fauci's with the pitch out at the baseball game
and I thought that was weird.
So I'm not totally on Fauci's side.
That's when he got mad though.
But then May 18th, 2021,
we find out for the first time about KaBlip
because there's a press conference, a press release.
It was only then, this is all within the year?
Yeah, and even according to another piece of media,
I'll explain later.
He discovered, so basically he had been dirt biking
in the Moapa Valley, which is an hour from Vegas
with Johnny Christopher and Christos Yanni.
He found this restaurant called Sugar's,
which was an old dining- Sugar's home plate?
Yeah.
And he was like, I'm gonna buy this restaurant
and make a restaurant.
What my dad wanted me to do, I'm gonna do it.
I'm gonna make, and it's gonna be breakfast,
lunch and pizza.
So here's one big thing to really hit
about this establishment.
I remember seeing the general idea of it
in the headline about it.
Chris Angel's opening up a restaurant outside of Vegas.
And I thought, I see, makes sense.
Oh, maybe it's like off strip.
Maybe it's in Fremont or even, or it's some odd,
it's a mile away.
There's fun things on the outskirts of Vegas.
Of course, why not?
Makes sense.
Then you learn that it is an hour Northeast of Vegas.
It is not even clay.
It's not just like, oh, it's a little bit of a cab.
It is a massive journey to take.
Here is a visual representation of that journey
from the Koopalip website.
And if you'll also notice, they have a little tagline.
Forget Vegas, I'm in Overton, Nevada,
eating with Chris, cowboys, bikers and aliens.
But that was put over the Google Maps JPEG.
Like there's text under it.
The scale and that.
And according to the website,
how long does it take to get there right now?
It's just a brisk 45 minutes.
It's only 63.2 miles.
45 minutes, okay.
That might figure in later.
That might factor in later that it says 45 minutes.
They've managed to find a way on Google Maps
that it is from Las Vegas.
The starting point is somewhere
that is technically Las Vegas.
But I looked up from Planet Hollywood
because he pushes that.
Come see my freak at Planet Hollywood
and then come celebrate at Koopalip.
Only 40, just 45 minutes away.
But it's at least an hour three from Planet Hollywood.
So what he specifically recommend, we're adding.
And that 15 minutes ain't nothing.
And it is a big old desert drive.
Do we know the, do you know offhand the name of the park?
Like it's a big sprawling, the Ring of Fire is that it?
The Valley of Fire State Park.
Which is supposed to be a beautiful place.
Like an amazing natural wonder.
I've been in there, it's really beautiful.
But you drive through there
and you really lose track of time and landmarks.
And I remember that specifically being
like a big long meandery drive.
Which I'm only imagining here I haven't been.
Yeah.
So that's, so May 18th he announces Koopalip
and there's just a ton of negative press.
Including like the Vice headline is Chris Angel's Koopalip
the worst restaurant name of all time.
Which was when they asked a restaurant branding expert
who was like, yes.
If I could read a quote from that guy,
I think he explained it really well.
He also rationalized, like he was trying to think
of anything that could take the cake and be worse.
And he said like, well I have a distaste
for like Hooters and Twin Peaks.
Like I find those annoying.
But they're actually kind of brilliant in a way
and they say exactly what they are.
And there's double entendre.
They communicate exactly what needs to be communicated
and it's a little cheeky.
As opposed to Koopalip which like, huh?
And then what is, and it's a, he also says how like,
you know, people mispronounce Chipotle for a long time.
But then there is a real word
and there's like, Koopalip, why make up such a difficult
word to say, there's no point.
But then this quote, I think he explained it really well.
I wouldn't mind it so much if,
when the meaning of the word were unfurled,
it was profound and there was an aha moment.
But that doesn't exist.
It's simply Chris Angel's breakfast, lunch, and pizza.
For a brand spirited by a magician,
oppressed to digi-tear extraordinaire,
you would expect something magical
and it's incredibly not.
There really is something to that.
You still need explanation at the end almost.
Like, huh?
But why is he doing that?
And that's not what he does.
And he has a really specific brand and why isn't it that?
Why isn't it scary?
Why isn't it anything like, Mine Freak?
Dine Freak.
Mine Mind Meat or something.
And when you see it written out,
the C and the A are often capitalized,
but the BLP are lowercase.
So it's not even, the term is camel case.
Like when you write a few words without spaces
or like punctuation and stuff,
but you capitalize the first letter of each word.
Like if you're naming a file on a computer.
It's called camel case?
It's called camel case, yeah.
Wow, I didn't know that.
But then also the logo,
the A is inside of a backward C,
which is almost a full circle,
which is the way Chris Angel writes his name in his shows,
but it just means it looks like a blip
with a circle around the A.
I didn't know that was supposed to be a C.
Yeah, that's it, yeah.
And I've been thinking about this.
I've been looking at this logo more than a normal person.
But it's almost the anarchy symbol too.
Yeah, I thought it was that.
Yes.
So the other thing that you remind me of
is you mentioned the drive from playing a Hollywood.
Wait a minute, okay, sorry to interrupt,
but you were showing us this.
It was showing us the magazine.
It doesn't look like a C.
It looks like a circle.
Yeah, a C has a space on the right side.
It does not read as Ka-blip at all visually.
It's one of the worst logos I've ever seen.
And then it still adds his name,
Chris Angel's a blip, breakfast, lunch, and pizza.
Lots of words, lots of fonts combined.
The end for in pizza is on the P.
In the P.
Inside the P.
And it's in a bright red, it's McDonald's red.
It feels very McDonald's reminiscent.
Anyway, you were saying.
Oh, I was saying, so Planet Hollywood,
the Planet Hollywood casino,
you know, so there's a lot of shops.
It's got a mall or a half a mall in it.
There's a lot of shops.
At the start of 2020, before the pandemic,
you know what they had ample amounts of?
Their empty storefronts.
You know what they also have probably had in 2021, 22?
Empty storefronts.
You know who is doing a show next door
or within the same facility?
Chris Angel.
And I was like, well, surely Ka-blip
has just slapped his name on a casino restaurant
in those many empty storefronts.
Yeah.
You would think, absolutely.
Why not?
Well, I guess because he fell in love with the Valley
and with the biking.
That's right.
He had good times at Sugar's home plate.
So he wanted to buy it and destroy it.
I am going to do the greatest magic trap I've ever seen.
I'm going to turn this functioning restaurant
into a non-functioning restaurant.
He around, so he announces Ka-blip
and I'm like, you have my attention.
We're all like, you have our attention.
So we all start following him on Instagram at this point
to be like, what is this?
So then we start noticing like June 28th,
he announces that he's also producing coffee.
The brand of coffee is Java Freak,
parentheses be the bean.
That's so much better branding.
Yeah.
And then he only has one roast.
It's the Italian roast, which is named Aluccia.
And on the front of the bag,
it also says javafreak.com get the bean.
So it's beat the bean and get the bean
are both on the front of the bag
and also Aluccia Italian roast.
And Aluccia is also.
Not yet.
Okay, yeah.
I'm sorry.
I don't mean to jump the gun.
But I will say the branding,
a lot of the presentation really feels like
a freshmen marketing student in college
who has the project due the next day
and is scrambling to do it all.
Some of the ugliest logos, branding.
The ugliest and the videos, the short YouTube,
so much, so perplexing.
So much doesn't make sense where it's like,
you are outside a city that is full of marketing
and salesmanship and this is so,
it's not even like someone self,
this is so odd.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
No, it's all like,
looks like Angel Fire or like really, really early,
like before you could have good Photoshop's,
like it's crazy.
Yeah.
It really feels like,
and I can't think of a better example
than just like the living with Michael Jackson documentary
where he's buying, like he's just pointing at things.
I want this, I want this.
Like Chris Angel and I'm assuming in the same way,
like I want that restaurant, buy it for me,
come up with like, and just like shouts out a bunch
of things and doesn't think anything through.
It's like that kind of process of like just buying,
like I'm doing this now and then people scramble
and that's why everything looks like shit.
Everything looks weird, doesn't make any sense.
Because the same limited group of people
have to do all of it and it's all things
they've never tried to do before
because they're part of a magician's entourage,
not restaurateurs.
There's a guy like in charge of his straight jackets
and all he knows is how to hold Chris Angel up in the air
just twirl and straight jacket.
Now he's designing fonts, like he's doing new fonts for this.
Get me the liquor license.
Yeah, this is like, you know, to call it back to another,
the early Imagineers, they were animators
and now they're being called upon to make robots and stuff.
So this is the same thing.
Now they're being called up,
his magic people are being called upon to.
Well, but there were great results when Disney did it.
That's true. In this case.
There was no, there's no Bob Gur in the Chris Angel camp.
We could do it all.
Oh, we gotta go back, don't we?
The old names.
I'm trying to get us transitioned back into,
I'm trying to help.
Actually, this would be a good time then to get into
because basically July 18th,
like a week basically before the grand opening,
he opens like previews, starts previewing the restaurant.
Right around Disneyland's opening.
That's kind of an interesting overlap.
Well, so as there's like kind of,
you're gonna get some shots of like people
trying out Kblip three days
in that window between the grand opening and the previews,
the website goes alive.
And I feel like we really have to get into the Kblip website
because it's just like an embarrassment of riches.
It's, he at all times is asking you to buy into
a lot of mythology and learn a lot.
This actually just to summon Bar Rescue,
another recently referenced thing.
I feel like for maybe a smarter thing
that Taffer does is try to like say,
you know, you can't like tell this massive story,
but you can't like,
there can't be 70 things that you have to learn
and figure out about the bar before you order the drink.
If you wanna like acknowledge who you are
and your history and the story in some slight way,
they're great.
But like Chris just floods this thing
with when I was a kid and I loved this
and I met this guy and you're gonna find out about him,
but also there's this brand and also,
and then magic tricks and then there's a lot thrown at you.
Taffer would have screamed at him if you read it.
Shut the site down.
Wait, does anyone wanna read the Italian ice thing?
Cause I feel like it's all,
what you're saying is nothing's more personified than.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like page five.
Go for it if you got it.
Page five, oh, I have it here.
Yeah, go for it.
I've been crazy.
Yeah.
And this is Chris talking.
Yeah, it continues on to the next.
I've been crazy about Italian ices since I was a kid.
And I'm so proud to say that we actually manufactured them
right off the Las Vegas strip
on our own manufacturing plant located
at Chris Angel Studios.
We have over 100 different delicious flavors created
by our partner, mastermind, iceologist, Mike Gambusa,
who has been producing gourmet ices for over two decades.
Mike Gambusa.
Wait, and then save room.
Save room, I bet you can't have just one lick.
Okay, so that comes up at something I grabbed too,
which is that there's this image of Italian ices
on the website a couple times with different copy each time.
And one says, manufactured in Chris's Mind Foods plant
in Las Vegas.
They call it something different,
Mind Foods and then Chris Angel Studios.
Yes, a delicious natural alternative to ice cream.
Bet you can't just have one lick
of this guilt-free indulgence.
All right, there's like five things in there.
One, Italian ice, very popular.
We're out in Pennsylvania, New Jersey, New York.
I have never ever heard it called
a natural alternative to ice cream.
No.
A lot of places.
It's like a homeopathic medicine.
No, ice cream isn't natural, you think of it.
A lot of places do brag about real fruit pieces,
real fruit juice.
Even there, that's stretching the term natural.
Another thing is, one of the most popular presentations
of Italian ice layered with sauce serve ice cream
or frozen custard.
So I don't know, it seems like he's pitching it
as a health food, but then they're like glowing.
There's like fluorescent blue and green scoop.
Jason, are you questioning Mike Gambusa
who's been in the frozen dessert business for 20 years?
Mastermind iceologist.
I do not understand.
Jesus, I hate the disrespect.
Jason's showing Mike Gambusa.
Mike Gambusa, because you gotta respect,
he's just talking about Mike Gambusa
like we know who he is.
And then on this article from View On Magazine,
which I've been pulling from.
You have a hard copy,
you have a physical copy of a magazine with you.
He mentions pizza extraordinaire Mike Barham,
which I like because if Mike Gambusa
is a master iceologist, a pizza extraordinaire is a pizza.
So he's,
so he's,
so he's implying that he partnered with a pizza
named Mike Barham.
I've hired a talking pizza to oversee pizza.
The pizza preparation.
Here's your order.
His name is Mike Barham.
I think you'll find.
All of my pizzas are named Mike Barham.
And of course also his brother, Costa Serentacos,
who opened,
who's the one who took over the father's restaurant.
So it's almost like Criss Angel's like a reverse guy.
Like he surrounds himself with smaller guys.
Like when we talk about the guys.
The guys and these other restaurants.
Criss doesn't have a guy above him
and he's not powerful enough to be like a win or a Trump.
He's like a hoarder of weird guys.
I met an iceologist once.
There's different members of the X-Men whose mutant power
is to amplify other mutants mutant powers
and make them stronger.
And Criss is kind of like that for guys.
Yeah.
And it's also, it makes sense with like a Long Island guy.
Like, I know my god of ice guy, Mike Gambusa, he'll do it.
Like, just call Mike Gambusa and let me call Mike Barham.
He's gonna.
I've never met a better pizza than Mike Barham.
Carlos Italian ice.
I found Mike Gambusa's places.
Really?
There's one in Los Angeles.
There's one in Staten Island.
And it's got both.
I don't know.
He's probably got more too.
And it's, oh, now it's not loading anymore.
This is here.
Carlos Gourmet Italian ices.
Like, I love that.
That's a good logo.
Yeah.
So this guy does know, Mike Gambusa does know
what he's doing.
Yeah, that's a pretty normal Italian ice.
But again, I've never heard it called
like a guilt-free indulgence.
It's a guilt-free indulgence.
And also the other thing in here.
Bet you can't have just one lick.
There's a lot of oddly sexual stuff on this menu.
The menu's highly sexual.
Highly sexual.
Well, the coffee is a little sexual.
The Italian ice is a little sexual.
This guy likes to have body fun.
We're getting back to it.
We're getting back to the words.
I'm just reintroducing them.
Where will seat come into play here?
I don't know.
You're gonna want to take a seat at Kblip
to order any number of breakfast, lunch, and pizza entrees.
I thought it was weird also the thing you read, Jason,
that the one I read was,
I bet you can't have just one lick.
And then yours was like,
I bet a single lick won't be enough
to satisfy what you are craving out of the ice array.
It will not satiate your urges.
It's like these things appear on the same page.
Just like, you see the one,
you keep scrolling down the page,
you see the same image, but different copy.
And it's just like, that is like 101,
like running a restaurant and stuff.
Make everything consistent.
No, he's throwing, wait, I'm also, look at this.
Speaking of the C, here's one with the C.
Wait, why is it a C on the sign?
Yeah, wait.
Yeah, look, okay, well you're showing me on the,
what's happening?
So on the actual restaurant,
when you go to the place, there is no C,
but on the website, there's a C.
And in the place, the circle is meant to stand as a C,
but there's no opening.
And he's wearing a shirt that has the bad logo on it too.
Oh, right.
Wait, so they changed it at some,
but it's too late, we made the sign.
We booked the Play On cover, what is it?
Oh, this is a magazine called View On Magazine.
It's the official magazine of Moapa Valley.
So, which he was bragging about,
he said View On Magazine has never had a person on the cover.
I'm the first person ever to be on View On Magazine,
which I did think was a little impressive when I heard it,
but I didn't know it was Moapa Valley exclusive.
Oh yeah, it's just stuff going on in the Moapa Valley.
Okay.
It's a nice magazine.
It's got glossy pages.
So, July 23rd,
KaBlip opens to the public official.
Oh boy.
Nine days after its preview starts.
Yeah.
It's great, he Instagrams just the,
he's like an Instagram of the full restaurant.
He says, every table stall and tummy filled KaBlip,
eat blip, smiley face drooling.
Another branding thing we haven't talked about
is that the Twitter and maybe the Instagram, I don't know,
but the Twitter at least is eat blip, not KaBlip.
Okay.
Which is great, because KaBlip was probably taken,
he didn't check that before he named it KaBlip.
So-
Cable P, like some guy who has a company called Cable P.
We took it already.
Or he's like, I thought when I misspelled cable
in my Twitter name, it would be the death of my business.
Who knew I'd be squatting on valuable land?
So that's July 27th.
Two days later, Mike, do you know what happens?
No, actually I don't.
Okay, tell him.
It closes.
I knew that was coming, I didn't know it was two days later.
There's an Instagram video where just like the little thing
is just some pizza, but when you click it,
the things that just says,
must temporarily close, response beyond expectations.
I also, I remember hearing about this
from the man we heard earlier, Jason Walliner,
who I want to quote him the way he broke the news,
which is KaBlip has shut down, but don't worry,
it's only because they are so successful.
Which is how they, wait a minute, are there,
I don't want to jump ahead, are there multiple closures?
Not yet, no.
Okay, okay.
Because I, wait, I think though that they're weirdly,
I think there was a brief closure in the preview period
because, now I haven't skipped past the ad on this,
so forgive me, we'll have it in a couple seconds,
but he filmed an emergency video,
important message from Chris.
He had to rush this to YouTube
in order for 720 people to see it, we're the 721st.
Wait, okay, so really quick, he's by his pool,
it's cloudy weather, he looks kind of stressed,
and he goes into this.
I'm expecting to make this video, but I have to make it.
We, unfortunately, are completely sold out
of our food products, we ordered tons of stuff
from Cisco and US Foods, everything is depleted.
We are closing today at five o'clock,
we are completely closed tomorrow at KaBlip
due to the overwhelming response.
I want to thank you so much Moapa Valley
for the incredible food love, we really love you,
we are completely closed.
He's still slipping in that weird branding of food love.
I hate that, what I hate out,
if people are too enthusiastic about food,
I sometimes find it disgusting,
but then condensing it into little, yummy food love,
or there's a video here, every table stall and tummy filled,
oh my God, I hate that.
Thank God, I feel like you guys would love saying tummy,
though, that's exactly the kind of shit
I'd get upset about.
Yeah, it is.
My full, full tummy.
I have a thing about tummy.
My tumsy-wumsy, got a bit of the wobblies.
Yeah, Jason just doesn't like it with food,
he likes saying tummy in relation to other stuff.
Or it's like, if I'm eating and the TV's on,
I can't have the Food Network on as I'm eating other food.
I feel- Really?
Yeah, I find it unnerving.
Unnerving? That's an odd one.
Yeah, I just find it weird, yeah, I don't.
What if it's the exact same food you're watching
and eating at the same time? That actually would probably
be okay. Okay.
That's like a double, like,
you're getting an extra sensory experience in that way.
Yeah.
So anyway, I think that was actually before,
I think that was in the preview period.
That was in the 10 days.
Yes, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's all they had to do was keep things going.
And he also, I like what he reveals in there,
which is, we bought so much food from Cisco,
so he outs that they're buying from these, like,
packaged food companies.
Again, a taffer no-no.
It's preview from Cisco!
He wouldn't be happy,
but they didn't change the plan.
Because then, because that's earlier on the YouTube channel
than when he has his entire audience all yell at the camera,
Ka-blet, ka-blet!
Often if you go see him live,
he might pull you into promoting whatever he's doing,
or in one case, cheering on a Moapa Valley
high school football team.
Like, he's facing the audience, like,
all right, we got a thousand of your best friends here
who wants to say something to you.
Go Cougars!
That's right, congrats on the intermural.
Scott, congrats on the Moapa Valley Pirates
is actually the most viewed video on the EPLP page.
How many?
766 views.
That's nice.
Well, like, all the parents watched it.
I hope they got some free food.
From somewhere else.
We're actually out of free food.
The free food is gone.
So his statement, when they close,
is actually very similar to that statement.
We are grateful for the overwhelming support and food love.
In order to fulfill our promise of delicious food
and excellence in customer service,
we need to expand our operation immediately
in order to meet the unbelievable demand.
We will reopen in August once we add additional refrigeration,
freezers, more staffing, POS system, and storage.
That's five things.
Thank you for your patience and understanding
as we try to better serve you.
We will see you in August.
So he says they're gonna close for 20 days.
That is not, they close for a lot longer than 20 days.
So they were open for three days.
Yeah.
At one point he says,
our near-spotless POS system went down a few times.
It's like, well, it's not near-spotless,
it keeps crashing.
And also, why are you telling us that?
Don't say any of this.
We don't need to know.
We don't need to know you don't have enough refrigeration.
That's terrifying.
In the deep, deep heat of the Moapa Valley,
where it's so hot,
there is a bench outside of the restaurant
that has a little thing on it that says,
don't sit here if it's too hot.
They had to warn people about that.
And yet they've had it be remotely in question
whether they have enough refrigeration.
Was this all exclusively posted on that YouTube channel?
On his Instagram.
So on his main personal,
it's okay, so people would see it.
I was just like, who even showed up and,
oh, it's closed.
Like, we gotta get to social media to find out why.
Here's something that's crazy too,
is he talks about the great reviews.
And then, but that's not the case.
Yeah.
If you look at all the reviews
from the very short training period,
here's one,
reminded me of a prison cafeteria scene on CSI,
right down to steel cages over the lights,
stainless steel tables, plates, and plastic silverware,
plus the added aluminum window shades after hours
to keep the vandals out in downtown Overton.
So much for local Overton restaurant.
And the response from owner, thanks for the feedback.
This is another one, had breakfast,
no flavor hash browns,
sausage didn't taste like anything I had ever tasted,
toast without butter on table, no coffee refills,
different people writing this for me.
Plastic knife and fork,
no spoon, metal, or paper plates,
hot paper cup.
No spoon.
Everything seemed like I was on a picnic,
not in a restaurant.
And then there's this really complicated one
where somebody tries to order,
cause on the website they have Mike's,
Mike Gambou's Italian ice.
And they'll add vodka to it and make it a mind freeze.
So someone tried to order that,
and the waitress was like,
I can't pour that, I'm underage.
So she had to go find someone to pour it.
And then the person said,
he says you have a hundred flavors.
And they said, we only have six flavors.
And she's like, can I have this flavor?
Like, no, there's only three flavors
that will make a mind freeze out of
strawberry, lemon, and chocolate.
And they asked for another one,
and they said, Chris likes it that way.
So they had to get a flavor they didn't like
when they were promised a hundred.
And this is like a very, so this is one of the reviews.
It's so complicated.
And this is one of the reviews.
So the reviews were like very harsh for the 10 days.
Which is probably one of the reasons this is going on.
Yeah, yeah.
The plastic silverware is crazy.
There's no justification of that.
I think that's true of coffee,
even if you're not taking it to go, it's paper cups.
This is just chintzy stuff here.
Also, again, I do wanna point out,
Planet Hollywood Hotel and Casino,
basically center strip.
Lot of quick service bars,
walk up windows, seems like the perfect place
to have a window serving Italian ice
or Italian ice with vodka dumped on it.
Not the case.
Which is very interesting.
So we're just sitting, it's July into August.
August into mid August.
Kaploop has not reopened.
August 28th, 2021, off what you're saying, Jason,
on Instagram, Chris writes,
just a picture of a bunch of a hundred flavors
of Italian ice.
Our delicious gourmet Italian ice
is heading to the heart of the strip.
September 1st, new location to be announced.
Hashtag Kaploop, hashtag eat blip,
hashtag over a hundred flavors.
So like, this is interesting.
Maybe he's not gonna open Kaploop,
but he is gonna sell the ice.
Maybe he has a lot of extra ice.
Maybe there are a hundred flavors.
Well, that wasn't, so September 2nd,
Kaploop suddenly reopens.
Wow.
It's back.
It's been more than 30 days at this point.
So just in previews for seven days,
open for three days, close for more than a month.
Reopens.
It's like the Spider-Man turn off the dark.
So just side note, have you guys ever read
the book, Helter Skelter?
No.
Nobody's read Helter Skelter?
It's a great book.
Story of the Manson investigation,
written by Vince Bugliosi.
And there's this really amazing part that I love.
Cause the first 200 pages are basically
the third person just telling of the murders.
And then just sort of the very beginning of the cops
kind of trying to figure out what's happening.
And then Manson gets arrested,
where one of the family gets arrested.
And 200 pages then Bugliosi basically says,
and then the phone rings and I picked it up.
And he reveals, like, this is me.
I'm the prosecutor.
The guy's been writing the book the whole time.
I'm actually part of this.
And in the book he says, like, in a way,
I'm a newcomer and intruder.
The sudden switch from an unseen background narrator
to a very personal account is bound to be a surprise.
Oh.
So this is my way of telling your listeners
that two days later I went to Ka-Bloom.
Yeah.
Eva, Eva.
I got up in the morning like it happens.
What actually happened was, we had a three day weekend.
We had plans.
And my husband said to me,
Ka-Bloom is gonna close again.
And I don't wanna live with you if you like,
never went.
If you have to like know it's open
and then you didn't go and it's closed again forever.
He's like, you have to go.
So I just got out of my car, like always.
You broke plans that in order, because of the sudden,
you all ended, it was not pre-med it.
You didn't know like,
I mean, you probably knew when it was gonna reopen.
You'll go, but.
I woke up that morning.
I did not know I'd be eating at Ka-Bloom that day.
Wow.
It like, it just happened.
I threw all my stuff in a bag and I drove.
First I drove to my hotel, dumped my stuff off.
Got in my car.
I stayed at, we should talk about this another time.
Resorts World, run by the Mercurial.
The Mercurial.
The Incaque thing.
His first outpost in a minute.
I don't think it is.
I found out there is a Resorts World in Queens.
Really?
That I considered staying at for our New York show.
But it's just too inconvenient.
Resorts World Vegas, fucking rules.
I only want to stay there from now on.
Robot dogs.
Whoa.
Oh yeah.
Anyway, drove from the edge, the far edge of Vegas
in no traffic to Ka-Bloom, more than an hour.
Way more than an hour.
Of course.
Hour 15 easy.
Driving a little over the speed limit, sorry.
And that's the north end of the strip.
So you are on your way to,
it's not like you're at like Mandalay Bay
and had to go through the whole strip to get there.
I was at the Circus Circus.
I was at the pepper mill.
You're at the end.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
There's no more big casinos.
No traffic.
Jeez.
So far.
He's lying.
The website is, you click that,
that's not a Google map link.
It's just like an image he's doctored.
Yeah.
Hey, you know where I've heard has good diner food
of this kind of quality?
The pepper mill.
That's one of the best, with the 500 page drink menu,
it's the best place ever.
And that like, unlike this plate, like looks so rad.
That is the almost awesome looking
locked in time neon place you've ever seen.
So I parked, I started, we have this text chain.
I just started secretly, like I hadn't warned anybody
just sending you guys photos from the outside
and inside of Kablep.
You know what's funny is that I thought that this,
I think I thought you were with people.
I think I thought that you like dragged people
on a group trip.
Like it's this thing you'll see.
I don't think I realized that it was spur of the moment
and solo in the deep desert.
Yeah.
I just went.
Did you have a general feeling before you got there,
how did you feel about Overton and the Moapa Valley?
I mean, it's really, really empty.
It's like a way, way.
I mean, there was only like two or three,
I passed like the school and I passed like a library
and then it's like no stoplight.
It's like tiny.
What time was it when you got there?
I got there for like an early dinner.
Okay.
By the time I left, the sun was setting.
So they weren't serving L anymore, but you could get P.
I couldn't get B though.
No, B.
No, B instead.
Okay.
So you're stuck either in like pizza, the Patriot burger
or the Mindfreak burger.
Exactly.
Although, I mean, that's one thing about this,
but the menu is they are trying to serve
every type of food.
Right.
Which also feels like a kind of amateur restaurant thing.
Like maybe you start with three things and nail them
instead of like 200, because it's everything.
It's burgers and pizza and breakfast and coffee
and Italian ice and alcoholic Italian ice and fajitas.
And like things that don't all go together where you,
it's like separate ingredients have to be gotten
only for this, fish and chips.
Like maybe start a little smaller and don't run out.
It feels like what happens sometimes is the family
running the pizza place, buys out the diner next door
and now they're running both of them.
He tried to do it from nothing.
Exactly.
It's very different.
He could have just kept the diner.
Like I think he was also keeping some diner stuff
to try to keep the locals happy,
because breakfast probably is a thing people ate at Sugar's.
Sure.
But I don't know.
One thing that seemed to answer one big question
was that most of the parking lot was taken up
by two giant mobile refrigeration units.
That were clearly solving the refrigeration problem.
He was not lying about that.
He needed more refrigerators.
Yeah, yeah.
I don't think he was lying.
Right, I'm just saying.
Maybe he should have lied.
Yeah, that's true.
Maybe he shouldn't know that.
You have to say that.
What did those look like from the outside?
Just big gray boxes?
Trailers, like big white trailers
that you could walk into, it seems like,
like walk-in freezers, but they were outside
and they were run by generators.
So they're loud?
Oh yeah.
Wow.
And taking up parking spaces.
So you're like, so if there's more than four people there,
you're out on the road.
Chris has his own parking space though.
Reserved.
Reserved with the big A and what apparently is a C.
So I walk in two days after grand opening.
It was pretty sparse.
I got seated in a booth with an infant.
I was sharing a booth with maybe a six week old infant.
Regardless of that fact, which is crazy,
why are you sharing a booth?
Why is it at that point?
I don't know.
This is the pandemic still.
I was like facing, it was like a long booth
and I had my own table,
but I was like uncomfortably close to an infant.
Does that make sense?
Yeah, I've noticed this about it
that the tables seem extremely close together.
Everything's really jammed.
Oh, I should mention the first thing I did
when I walked in before I sat down
or right after I got my table,
we haven't talked about the magic room,
but the back of Koepelip is a magic room
where he, it looks incredible.
I hate the magic, oh man.
I'm in the magic room.
What's wrong with the magic room?
Well, I would say the upper half of a torso
popping out of the ceiling.
That's like the, from like chest to head.
That's like the trick I was talking about earlier.
Of the torso trick.
Of the Chris Angel that is hanging from the ceiling
and the eyes move around or looking at you.
That's when we were talking about the fashion cafe
and it's like there's animatronics of the models.
Is it like how there's technically considered,
you could consider this an animatronic of Chris Angel
in the restaurant because the eyes just dart around?
Oh, yeah, maybe so.
Maybe they have a robot.
We have to, do we, is it a robot?
Do we rule?
Is this a robot?
I think it is.
It's like the eyes are moving all the time.
It was moving when the room was,
the room was empty except for just a laptop.
Someone was working out of there
and the eyes were moving on the robot.
So they have a private room that somebody's just working in,
but the regular room,
we still have to keep everybody in the regular room
and jam you next to a six week old during a pandemic.
Yes.
And he claims that eventually you'll be able to see magic
shows in the magic room.
But I don't know from who, when, like how.
It seems like maybe you could have like
your kid's birthday party there
and then go back and see magic in the magic room.
But the magic room is pretty small.
It's pretty small.
The animatronic dummy, Chris Angel,
has a straight jacket on.
There's a frame straight jacket on the wall.
So this restaurant does have themed restaurant jackets.
Hey.
Oh yeah.
It's a jacket.
It's in almost all of them.
Yeah.
Thank you, jackets.
You really made the month.
So I sat down, I ordered,
I want to try a couple of different things.
I got a Caesar salad.
I got some Mindfreak level wings.
I got a pizza.
I got a pea.
I got a margarita pea.
Whoa.
And then I ordered a Mindfreeze.
And my waitress said, I can't pour that.
I'm underage.
Yes.
It happened to you.
Wow.
But she went and found her manager.
Okay.
And the manager said, I can make it.
And I said, okay, what flavors?
And he's like, well, we usually just do these three flavors.
And I said, can I get a different flavor?
And he said, which flavor do you want?
And I said, which flavors do you have?
And he said, they also had watermelon and something else.
So they had five flavors, five of a hundred.
Still only five.
And I said, I would like a watermelon Mindfreeze.
And he said, I can do that.
And he did it.
Oh.
So they'd solved that problem.
Okay.
Here's the thing though.
They told me that the Mindfreeze, which was expensive,
came in a collectible Ka-blip cup.
But what they did bring me is a regular, just a Ka-blip,
just a cup with a Mindfreeze,
plastic cup with a Mindfreeze in it.
And then they just handed me this empty.
This is a, just a cup from Chris Angel's Mindfreak
at Planet Hollywood.
Wow.
And he's like, sorry, we don't have our cups yet.
You can have this.
They moved a cup from an hour away.
They've moved a cup from its natural habitat.
Whoa.
Oh, that's incredible.
The food was not great.
The Mindfreeze was incredible.
Really?
It was great.
I loved it so much.
It was beautiful.
It came with like a, like a little leaf on it
and like a little strawberry.
The watermelon ice was just delicious.
Wow.
I loved it.
Mike Gambusa knows what he's doing.
Well, I think he does.
Yeah, that was, yeah.
He's a master.
20 years.
20 years of the business.
You don't earn the name master iceologist
if you aren't a master of iceology.
On my way out the door,
I asked the girl at the ice counter if Mike was there.
Oh, I also, sorry.
I saw Costa Serentacos walking around.
I saw his brother, Chris's brother,
was running the front of the house.
Yeah.
He seemed like he was doing a good job.
Also like, just to say really quick,
the whole place is covered in like word murals.
There's one that just is like,
Ka-blip, worst restaurant name of all time.
Beatles, worst band name of all time.
Like really hostile.
Trying to own the, the kind.
He's trying to do sort of a,
Tommy Wiseau who he kind of resembles, I would say.
He's trying to like, no, I know it's a bad movie.
I meant to do.
Yes, that was all the plan, you see.
So I asked the girl, first of all, I said,
hey, that place that opened September 1st on the strip
where you can get all the ice, where is that?
Cause I'm going back to the strip.
And she was like, that's not real.
Admit it, these people are, they are honest.
Well, she just was like, that's not,
she just kind of shook her head.
And then I asked if Mike Gambusa was around
and she said, Mike, no, he comes in the morning.
If you come back in the morning, you can meet Mike.
So I'd have to come back for B.
But, and it would have been really early.
And I was like, I cannot, now knowing how far it was,
I was like, I can't, someone else has to do that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you got it.
Well, like, Walnut is going to go at some point.
Walnut can meet Mike.
But I asked, or someone else has to get breakfast.
But I asked like, is Mike Gambusa nice?
And she said, Mike Gambusa is so nice.
Yeah, wow.
We love this guy now.
He is nice, he makes ice.
Mike Gambusa.
We gotta go down to the place.
We gotta go get this ice.
Yeah. In Los Angeles.
Oh yeah, well, yes, you're right.
We can have the ice without going all the way
to Moapa Valley.
Because they closed the Rita's water,
like water ice right by where Jason lives.
His favorite place in the world.
Oh.
Closed. Let's go get his ice.
Let's get Mike's ice.
Mike's nice ice.
So that was my experience at KaBlip.
Just a couple more important things that happened
in the six month period.
Because Chris Angel had a very crazy 2021.
Yeah.
October 23rd, Chris got COVID.
And he put a lot of videos out of himself getting
monoclonal antibodies from a doctor's office.
And he kept naming the doctor's first and last name,
Dr. Constantine George.
And Scott, you actually found this.
It's in the notes, the review you found
of Dr. Constantine George.
Oh, I don't remember this now.
It's on my note, here.
Okay, okay.
Let's see.
Oh, thank you for the opportunity here.
Oh, that's right.
Yes, I remember this.
Okay.
What?
One star.
If I could give this business negative stars, I would.
Doctor is cold to his patient and staff.
Talks badly about his patients to his staff.
Heard numerous times.
He doesn't care who he mistreats.
Whether it be a staff member or a paying patient.
This man has the heart of a dying fish.
And his hands have a similar texture.
He spends less than five minutes with you.
He does not address any of your concerns
and clearly is only in it for the money.
I will report him to the BBB.
This is who is treating Chris Angel's COVID.
Dr. Constantine.
It's just the theory.
That's right.
The theory that if Chris Angel ever puts anything out there,
if you just Google any proper noun in it,
you'll find the craziest thing you've ever found.
He doesn't associate with anyone normal,
even for his medical needs.
Is the doctor also a magician?
I hope so.
He also, he is a pediatrician, which I found was weird.
So I think he might have been
in his own kid's pediatrician's office,
staying overnight getting antibodies from a guy
with the hands of a cold dead fish.
That was the trick.
It was a dead fish.
And then November 5th, he has a baby.
Chris has another baby.
And finding that out right after the COVID.
Wait a minute.
And so you were like in the hospital with COVID
and then had a baby like two weeks later?
And the name's the daughter, Elucia Angelina,
which you'll remember, Mike.
What's the name of, what was it?
The coffee.
The coffee brand.
Coffee brand first, daughter later.
You could see it the other way.
Yeah, this seems like a common thing.
I named my wine brand after my daughter,
but not coffee.
You're not making money off the coffee first.
And then, oh, you know what else should have that name?
My child, this human.
I had a bag of Elucia that I bought at Kblip
and we were drinking it.
And then Instagram comes up, name my daughter Elucia.
I look at the coffee.
I'm like, that's what I was like, he's fucking with me.
Like he knows I know.
He knows I have this coffee.
Like why would he do this to me?
It felt personal.
Also, just with the level of normal that we're at
where the beginning of the story is,
I had Elucia that I bought at Kblip
after I saw Costa Saran tacos.
But I didn't see Mike Gambusa.
But I didn't get to see master iceologist, Mike Gambusa.
Who is nice.
But I hear he was nice.
Just a couple things too, from this View On Magazine,
which I got at Kblip.
There was a big pile of free ones.
So this was supposed to coincide with opening week.
And this is where I'm like, he does...
One thing that's interesting about Chris
is that he just says stuff and no one fact checks it.
So it just says like,
not only did Angel remodel the existing restaurant,
location in just six weeks,
he also plans on opening up to 20 more locations
in the next year.
In areas including Arizona, Nevada, and California,
the restaurant will also feature a youth job program
and a free meal outreach program
for underprivileged and pediatric cancer families.
Angel also wants to manufacture Kblip ice
dedicated to the Gohmir Italian ice
made and sold at the restaurant.
And then he goes on and on about that he's also opening...
Wait, where is it?
Chris Angel's escape camp?
The escape ranch.
Oh no.
But I've seen it also called the camp.
We also don't know the branding.
Is it a ranch or a camp?
This is a common thing too.
Jackets are common for this whole month,
but also very common are these big bold proclamations
about the expansion of the restaurant.
Yeah.
From dive to grandpa's restaurant.
Both of those were like, we're expanding in the future.
You watch out, here we go.
Like this is gonna become a whole thing.
Yeah. And then no.
The escape ranch will be a place where families
that are going through a difficult time
can escape for three days and two nights.
So it's not like an escape room.
It's not something you escape from.
It's something you escape to.
It's the world, but it sounds horrifying.
It's in the desert by Kaplip.
At this camp, they will enjoy the use of side-by-sides,
stay in a fifth wheel RV
and be able to eat completely for free.
There is no set opening date for the ranch.
So it's just like a bunch of claims.
And then what's really funny is that this article
is like four pages and then in the middle,
there's this big yellow stamp over Chris's face
that says that Kaplip closed three days after it opened
and they don't know when it's gonna reopen.
Editor's note.
So they had gone enough to go to press,
but just right before they went to press,
they had to stamp this thing on here,
being like, sorry guys, it's closed.
So like an editor got like in the middle of the night,
like a phone rings and it's like, hey, you got it.
We gotta do something for this story
that's coming out tomorrow.
Oh shit, what do we do?
Sometimes I hate working
at Malapa Valley's V1 magazine.
The news moves so quickly out here.
We always have to print a sticker retraction
which picks something over an article.
Oh my God.
Kaplip, they have also like a lot of merch for sale.
They don't have jackets,
but they have really like kind of offensive shirts.
Oh yeah, that's just white text on black.
It's a shirt.
What they put on the website,
it doesn't even look like they've ever made one practically.
It seems like very, you know, like those,
they're not like ours.
You got our team public and they exist.
But I don't think these, have these ever been made?
It's just a rendered, it's a rendered like shirt.
I think there was one hanging on the wall when I was there.
But they didn't look good.
Everything's like, my favorite,
there's like different ones that say like,
don't whine, drink beer, Kaplip or like,
but my favorite just says Kaplip on the back,
says Kaplip, breakfast, lunch, pizza on the back.
It says for a good time, call 702-397-8084.
So it's just the phone number for Kaplip
but like doesn't spell anything.
They just assume like someone will see you wearing the shirt
and remember the phone number.
It's long, complicated, nonspecific.
Yeah, yeah, oh my God.
There's a video, they uploaded a couple of,
YouTube has, I think they call them shorts.
And it's clearly trying to be a TikTok competitor.
But there's one video, it's only a few seconds long
of a waving American flag and it's labeled, Never Forget.
But there's no sound and it's not really,
I couldn't figure out how, see,
I'm assuming it was for 9-11
because there is one comment on it that just reads,
too bad the government knew it the whole time.
George Bush just sat and calmly read that book
to the children while it happened.
That's the proof?
That he's in, him being stoic for the children
is the proof that like, I know, I don't need to.
That's the proof that also-
Because I planned it, I pushed the start button.
Administrators of like channels can delete comments.
They just left up a 9-11 truth or?
There was also the point in time,
do you remember Eva how, when everything was going wrong
and they were closed for a long time,
they're figuring out refrigeration and food,
but they did install a flagpole and he's like,
look what just happened, bam.
He's being all braggadocious about that they,
it was so confusing in the photo, in our text,
I commented like, what is the picture showing?
What is he, and somebody had to explain,
it's that there's a flagpole now.
Oh, so the tweet is, this happened today, flag.
Go big, guest or go home,
hashtag Moapa Valley, eat blip.
I hope to reopen soon with more freezers,
refrigerators, ice cubes, and a talented welcoming staff.
You didn't have ice cubes.
And talented welcoming staff, slam on the goals.
Yeah, that's a big implication.
And then if you slide through, there's a second picture,
which is concept art of the flag.
It's concept art of what if we had a flag?
It came true, much taller in person though.
So they did best to the concept in one regard.
Aesthetically, just to say one more,
I don't know if it was any different in person,
but that way that it where it's just like white walls
with this mean black text that in some cases
is what the shirts are also saying.
And then that big McDonald's red
and tables just kind of jammed together
and they are like steel and metal.
I mean, the pictures don't do it justice.
Maybe there's something I'm missing that you get in person.
There's a big mural of Chris with his sons in the desert.
There's also some screens showing Chris magic.
There's also some mirrors that look like
they might be two-way mirrors,
but I don't know what they're for.
Also a theme of the month.
That's right.
They don't go to the bathroom.
On the patriotic kick,
I was also sitting by the baby,
but facing a man wearing a shirt
that said all rifles matter.
Oh good, oh good.
I feel like I couldn't find the picture,
but I feel like there was a Yelp comment
or some sort of where someone said like,
oh, I'd love to come,
but I don't want to wear a mask everywhere.
And they're like, don't worry.
We're probably a mask free establishment,
which doesn't seem to be the case
because there's plenty of footage
of the staff wearing masks.
Oh yeah.
That might've been the slim period of time
after vaccines were widely available
where they're like, no masks.
And then there was the Delta search
and Las Vegas and surrounding areas
where like, we have a lot of tourists here.
Everyone put your mask back on.
They were following protocols at the blip
and all over Vegas.
I thought it was very good.
Before we get to my final thing,
Mike, do you want to do a quick quiz of guys?
Oh yeah, please.
Okay.
Who is Ed Bible?
I know.
Ed Bible was, okay.
Ed Bible was early on.
Oh shit.
He was right.
He was the chef, right?
That's right.
Yeah, with the rice and the chicken.
Who's Alucia?
Alucia is a coffee and a daughter.
Yeah.
Who's Costa Seren Tacos?
Oh shoot.
What aspect of the meal was she in charge of?
Costa Seren Tacos.
Hmm.
It's his brother.
Oh, that's right.
No, no.
Damn it.
It's okay, it's okay.
You're doing great, you're doing great.
It's embarrassing, I wasn't paying attention.
Who's Mike Gambouza?
Well, the nicest man that makes the nicest ice.
Who's Constantine George?
Yeah, the doctor who gave him Regeneron.
Who is Mike Barham?
The pizza guy?
Yes, slash a pizza.
A pizza man.
A fucking pizza man.
He's extraordinary.
Wow.
Well, I have a-
By the way, also, just,
because I was going through the menu,
and there's, I mean,
there'll be some recurring people from that,
but like, they do so many like,
so and so's famous this, so and so's that,
and I just wrote down anybody who gets a meal named
after them on the lengthy menu.
Costa, Alucia, Christos Yanni, Sean, JC, JD,
Tommy Boy, Grandma, Yeeyah, Yeeyah, and Mike.
So these are, there's so many guys to learn
over the course of-
What's Mike's item?
I'm not sure, I gotta go to the menu.
Wait, what's the grandma?
Grandma Yeeyah Yeeyah?
Grandma Yeeyah Yeeyah.
I can find out if you give me a minute.
Grandma Yeeyah Yeeyah, Mike?
Come on.
Mike deserves that, I just wanna know who she is.
Okay, Mike is a homemade Parmesan,
so that might be Mike the Pizza.
Unless it's Gambouza,
but those are both Mike's, right?
Yeah.
I did like that,
because it was Parmesan, side of pasta, two garlic knots,
and I was like, oh, that's everything you want,
that's pretty smart.
Yeah, yeah.
That's good, yeah.
We also got spaghetti fo' you,
and-
Wait, fo' you, like the Paul McCartney song, fo' you?
Like F-A.
Oh, F-A, okay.
Paul's is F-U-H.
What are some other funny names on the menu?
Let's see, you got the section called
You're Getting Sleepy Appetizers.
You're getting sleepy is crossed out,
and no, you're getting appetizers,
in a font that suddenly has syrups,
but is the same color.
You got, there's like a breakfast combo
that's called Mind Fest.
The ultimate breakfast combo is called Mind Fest.
I missed a name, did I say Shawnee?
I think I might've missed Shawnee.
I don't know who Shawnee is.
Yeah, there's so many names.
Oh, how many is wife?
Shawn is either his wife,
or it's Johnny Christopher's mother.
Okay, oh, I said Shawn, but I'm not Shawnee.
Are those different people?
I can't tell.
Salads for the Stars,
and then there's a picture of his star on the Walk of Fame.
There's Sandwiches, Raps, and Rock and Roll.
And Raps is not spelled with a W, it's spelled R.
Which has things like the Rock and Roll Zinger,
and Overton Rap, spelled with an R like a rap song.
Overton Rap.
One of the videos that's like a montage,
it's either Cuplip is Open or Cold Blood Plastic Close.
There's a very quick clip where it flashes
the phrase food god,
and then it's Chris Angel and a guy.
Food god is the nickname of this guy, Jonathan Chibon.
Is that how he, do you know who this is Eva?
I don't know, no.
He's in the Kardashian sphere, Jonathan Chibon.
Okay.
Chibon, he shows up in the Kardashian circle.
So it's him and Chris,
and he was clearly making a video with him in some context,
and they're around a big Cuplip pizza,
and they do one of the weirdest things I've ever seen
when you're picking up a slice of pizza.
They grab them with one hand,
and they immediately turn them vertical.
Cause they were trying to show the cheese stretching,
but you could tell it's cutting away,
because turning a fresh out of the oven slice
of pizza vertical, you can see it's all just falling off.
And they cut right before that happens,
but I can see it on the top half just start to fall
to the right off.
Cheese don't stretch on no Cuplip pizza.
I can tell you firsthand.
Okay, so there's one thing I've been wanting to share.
Yeah.
And here we go.
Okay.
Hi Eva, this is Mike from Carlos Gourmet Italian Ices.
I just wanted to reach back out to you.
I got your message online,
and I'm so glad you came out actually.
I had our Ices in Las Vegas at Cuplip.
Call me, my name is Mike.
Call me anytime.
All right.
Leave them.
What, what?
Call me anytime?
That's so nice.
Mike Ambuza?
Mike Ambuza.
What?
I got in touch with Mike Ambuza through the website.
Whoa.
And he called me.
He's in my phone now.
Oh my God.
Wow.
Did you save the contact?
Mike Ambuza.
Oh yeah.
He's on my phone as Mike Ambuza.
Whoa.
So yeah, I had a plan to try to get some Ices.
Oh.
But the Ices actually isn't available in LA right now.
Oh, what?
No.
It can only be shipped.
The website just means that he can wholesale ship to LA.
Which means I would have to rent a commercial freezer
to hold giant tubs of Ice.
I actually ran into this
because I was trying to figure out
where to buy Martin's potato rolls in Los Angeles.
And it is only available for restaurant supply.
I mean, you could think about like,
maybe you could get rid of enough of them
if you got like a thousand Martin's potato rolls.
I mean, that's true.
I start, you know, reselling.
This is all frustrating,
but I do just want to remind everybody
that you can still get Mariah Carey's cookies
for approximately $5 a cookie.
As far as you know.
I don't know about the time.
Yeah, that was weeks ago.
We don't know.
So I didn't get the Ice,
but I did get a nice 20 minute conversation
with Mike Ambuza.
Wow.
Where he outlined some hopes and dreams.
Well, first of all, he was like, how did you find me?
And I said, you're on the website.
And then also you could just Google
and then your name's on the other website.
And he was like, oh, you're a detective.
And then he told me that currently
you can't get the stuff in LA,
but that there's a future plan
that was kind of like the one in view on
to ideally be shipping the Ice under the Kblip name
from Vegas pretty soon.
So fingers crossed we'll all be deep in Ice
at some point soon.
And he also told me that they're planning
on five new Kblip locations in the next year,
down from 20.
Okay, more manageable.
I mean, who knows?
But the most important thing that he said
was he asked me,
cause then he goes like, wait, wait, wait.
Cause this is like, he goes like, what?
Wait, you went to Overton?
You live in LA?
And I was like, yeah.
And he's like, wait, what?
And I was like, you went all the way there?
And I was like, yeah, I'm a, I'm a Chris Angel fan.
He's like, listen to me.
Chris Angel is a good man.
He's such a good person.
And he just went on and on about like,
what a good guy Chris Angel is.
He's like, we grew up in a similar part of town.
He's really loyal to his friends.
He takes care of lots of kids.
He does all that charity.
What a good guy.
What a good guy to work for.
And so I walked away just like,
I mean, I trust Mike at this point.
And he says, Chris is a really good guy.
So what better way to close out restaurant,
a celebrity than with a guy who's not a bastard.
With a good guy.
We've been talking about guys,
but maybe he's not a guy.
Maybe he's a good guy.
Like we're good boys.
That's right.
Sometimes guys can be good.
Sometimes.
And then we can sign off on them.
That sounds like a men's rights thing going on here.
But the idea that like.
Yeah, well, allow me to continue.
Yes.
He's a maniac.
He makes stuff up.
He makes terrible decisions.
He does stuff before things sit through maybe.
He gets like antibodies from like the worst possible doctor.
Names his daughter after his coffee.
But at the end of the day, like he's a good guy.
I like, that's my thesis.
That's great.
Chris Angel's a good man.
And he was, we know that Mike is a good guy.
So then obviously his word was trustworthy.
Somebody said he was a good guy
and he says another guy's a good guy.
That means they're all good guys.
Well, yeah.
And some of those other guys,
like if they're swindling from other swindlers,
it's like, well, kind of a lateral mood, you know,
like kind of evens the score.
Sure, yes.
I don't.
And I have these gifts for you guys
to commemorate Celebrary.
They're Ka-Blip Beer Cousine.
Yes, Ka-Blip stuff.
Oh, I'm so honored.
But from the side, they say, don't whine, drink beer.
And then an even worse logo than I've seen before,
because the C is under the blip
and the C is inside the B.
Multiple versions of the logo.
Yeah, this is like the worst one.
So this is for you guys to, for your beers.
Wow.
Yeah, yeah.
The beers for us guys.
Yeah, for the guys.
The good guys.
Wow, wow.
That's incredible.
And what a physical journey that you've been on.
A turn like the Manson book.
I also want to say, like, just, I looked up,
just to make sure, because, you know,
we're talking about, oh, some stuff doesn't make sense.
I looked up the menu for the old restaurant, too.
What was that like?
And it, there's, look,
there's some inconsistencies on that too.
So I think there's an improvement here.
Whoa.
Okay.
So like, it says sugars, and it's kind of a vague,
like, vague, like, logo.
It's like a sign, like, not Seinfeld,
but almost like a 90s logo.
It's hard to see it, but anyway.
Part of the menu says breakfast,
then one plate says home plate hamburgers.
Okay, baseball, right?
That seems like where we're going.
And then it goes to first inning.
Okay, that's appetizers and soups.
Great, this is a baseball themed place.
And then it says the part where they have steaks,
the main event.
That's the page called the main event.
That's not in baseball.
I guess the game is the main event.
No, they never call a baseball game the main event.
Play ball, it's time for the main event.
That's boxing or pro wrestling.
Yeah.
So this, look at this.
This is all over the place.
Sugar is needed.
The place.
Touch up.
That's what I'm saying.
He had to come in and add these special touches.
Exactly.
Including, and this doesn't top the, you talked to,
master, I saw it, just Mike Gimbusa,
but I also, I put in a call to Kblip several days ago
because I was curious about one thing that we missed,
which is the love table.
They have a magic room and they have a love table.
And I could find no further information
about the love table.
And I called and it was a similar, yes.
And it was a similar situation to you with the drink
where I was handed from a young girl to a manager who,
I just asked a couple of details about the love table.
And he said that mainly, well, you know,
the tables are all kind of close together.
So the love table is, you know, you got more space.
You're removed from everybody.
So that's what, so it's, and I said, oh,
is it kind of off to the side or in another room?
And he said, no, no, no, it's,
it's in the middle of the restaurant actually.
But, and it is a type of granite that lights up and glows.
Whoa.
Yeah, yeah.
So that's pretty good.
And I said, he asked if I wanted to reserve it.
I said, oh, I'm still figuring out when I might be there.
Is it like a problem to get it?
And he said, no, no, no.
So another good guy, another, you know, they had to,
I think Chris had to come in, apply these,
these magical things, a weird upside down,
starting around guy, a wonderful love table.
I, I, boy, it would be wonderful if we could all be
at the love table together because we love having you, Eva.
Although I don't think four people could fit at the love.
I'm almost sure that four people could not fit
at the love table.
We could go, we could do the magic room though.
I would love to do that.
Yeah, that's what you want.
What about you by your own criteria?
How do you judge Kblip for this month?
Oh, interesting.
Well, we've been doing this.
We've been saying, is there a way to Oscar it up?
Which is stuff that you add to the top of stakes.
Is there possibly a way to Oscar it up?
Well, how are they?
Generally it like knowing that it works okay.
You didn't seem to recommend the wings or pizza.
Or the salad.
You didn't take anything to go for your husband?
You didn't take anything to go?
No, I would have recommended,
I also would have liked a metal silverware as well.
It was still plastic.
The food in general, I think could be plused up.
And I would like to be, have all the hundred flavors
are on the Carlos Italian Ice website.
And I would like to be able to have all hundred.
That's too much.
Like a Rita's or a Joe's.
Usually has like 15 to 20 flavors that they rotate.
And when they're out, they're out for the day.
But like, man, a hundred.
That seems like you would want the whole restaurant
committed to ice.
I would love if it was an ice restaurant.
Yeah.
That might be the way to go.
Kblip Ice.
Don't, Kblip doesn't stand for anything anymore.
It's just the word.
It's like Epcot.
Let's get the transition back.
It's about the spirit.
It doesn't matter what it stands for.
We don't even remember.
There's Fat Tuesdays every half a block.
Like a nicer Fat Tuesdays.
Like that you carry around.
You get a little buzz.
Carry Carlos everywhere.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Send Mike's kids to college.
Help the doctor get a surgery
so that his hand isn't like a fish anymore.
Let's help all the guys.
And all these guys need our support.
Send ice to the escape camp.
All the kids who are escaping to there need ice.
Give money to master iceologist Mike Gambuza
to create an ice camp to teach kids
how to pass along his ice tradition.
We need to like help kids who don't have a place to go
and don't have a path in life.
Give them the path to become a master iceologist.
I would love.
Gambuza's ice camp.
Jason, would you take an apprenticeship
with Mr. Gambuza?
It's in Raconkoma.
That's where he lives.
Where?
Raconkoma.
Is that the name of the town in New York?
Oh, in New York.
Raconkoma?
Yeah, I never know how to pronounce that.
He lives there, the place with the weird name.
Jason Sheridan, apprentice iceologist.
The iceologist's apprentice.
Oh, wow.
That's a movie.
I have been, extended family used to run
a couple of Rita's franchises back in Veltelvania.
We would go and hang out behind,
like they had a couch and a TV.
Well, forget everything you've learned.
Oh, I'm actually.
We're slapping it out of you.
We're starting fresh.
This is all gonna be new.
Master Mike.
This is gonna be like a,
he's not gonna wanna train you.
It's gonna be like Anakin and Obi-Wan and.
I just know you gotta turn that ice over.
Like I'm wondering how long the ice
is staying in those freezers.
Cause a few days in a freezer,
ice starts to, you know, get a crusty layer.
It just gets freezer burned.
Call him up.
That's why he needs to open the storefront
and the strip.
Yeah.
I wanna go.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, I want to see Jason trying to turn the ice
over too quickly, like conducting a bunch of ice
that comes magically to life.
And then suddenly there's ice exploding out of every.
Every piece of equipment and everything.
But then there's too much ice and Jason starts to slip.
Bellagio fountains then across the way,
the ice, you know, the ice capates.
The ice, some sort of ice show.
It's built, you know.
And then a silent, glowering Mike Gambusa
in a tall wizard's hat shows up.
It's like.
Bump, bump, bump.
No, no, no.
I'm, I'll take off the ice-ology.
Just ice off, don't take the scooper out of my whole skirt.
I'm sorry.
Bump, bump, bump, bump.
And of course all ends just like on Mustafar
in Revenge of the Sith with you fighting Mike Gambusa.
It's some sort of a duel.
Instead of lava, it's the opposite of a lava.
Yeah, it's ice.
It's ice planet.
Mango ice.
It's reverse Mustafar as an ice planet.
It's a sweet ice planet.
From the planet Ellusia.
You had shows at one.
You were the joke.
Mike Gambusa cuts you in half.
You end up hanging upside down from the magic room.
Instead of Chris.
Where do you guys get those things?
Those are pretty realistic.
Yes, they are.
Oh my God.
Geez, what a journey this entire month.
And it's really made it having you with us
telling us this story.
You know, not every celebrity restaurant story is closed.
Some are even just beginning.
And we encourage you out there to drive to Moapa Valley.
Look for Mike, look for all our friends,
Costa and Chris and everybody.
Live your kablip story.
It's still happening.
And boy, all of these have been so wonderful,
especially the ones you joined us for.
Eva Anderson, you survived Celebrary.
You just survived, I don't know if you know this,
you just survived your 10th podcast, The Ride.
The first non-Ghost Boy guest to reach 10 episodes.
You get to reach double digits.
Thank you so much, Eva.
I'm so emotional, thank you guys.
Oh my God, it's my favorite podcast.
I'm so grateful that you had me
and I'll come back a million times.
I love it so much.
Thank you.
Please, please do.
Your frequent presence on it and your support of it.
Oh my God, from the beginning, even when you're not on it,
you listen and you tell us stuff that you like
and it encourages us.
And you being a part of all this makes it so, so thank you.
I do have something to plug this month.
Yes, yeah. For this final episode.
I wrote on the Apple TV drama, We Crashed,
which premieres in two and a half weeks, March 19th
with Anne Hathaway and Jared Leto.
It's super fun.
It's about WeWork and the rise and fall of Adam Newman.
Jared Leto's wild in it.
It's really, so is Anne Hathaway and check it out.
What a guy, the WeWork founder.
Yeah. What a guy.
It's a super funny story of the tech stories.
It's one of the weirdest, craziest ones, I think.
So.
Were you like, was there a lack of confidence on your end
that you could write for and tell the tale
of a long haired businessman with lots of insane ideas
and bad instincts? A weird grading accent.
And a very strange way of speaking.
Oh man.
Oh geez, great.
I can't wait for that.
So excited to see it.
And yeah, thank you for all of the celebrity.
This is wonderful.
We turn back to Podcast the Ride.
We'll see if we can manage it.
We'll start saying the names again.
We'll say all the names.
But I'm sure there's still more guys to come.
We know that there will be.
You can find us on the socials at Podcast the Ride.
Merch is available in our T public store.
Thanks to Aaron Gardner for the celebrity logo.
For three bonus episodes every month,
check out Podcast the Ride the second gate
at patreon.com slash podcast the ride.
A great month.
I had a really good time.
I can't think of any way to Oscar it.
Neither can I.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a Forever Dog Production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Bohm, Joe Silio, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts,
please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple Podcasts,
Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news
by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at Forever Dog Team and liking our page on Facebook.