Five, four, three, two, one.
Well folks, you asked for it.
It's Alan Hales Lobster Barrel at last
on podcast The Ride the Second Gate
thanks to Celebruary,
our ongoing celebration of celebrity owned restaurants.
I'm Scott Gardiner, Jason Sheridan joins us.
Scott, I'm thrilled to talk about the various preparations
of seafood today.
Bakes and broils and weird last names
after names of food that you know.
Featuring cream, lemon, paprika.
That's kind of it.
That's all you need.
Mike Carlson, hi.
I'm here and I was thinking about this.
There's probably a better example in fiction,
but this is something Jason knows.
So there's a run of X-Men comics
written by our favorite guy, Grant Morrison.
And they introduce a character at the start of his run
called Zorn.
And Zorn is like a very gentle character.
He's a healer.
The students love him.
He's a teacher.
Well, spoiler alert, cut to the end of like a multi-year run.
Zorn is unmasked as Magneto, okay?
I feel like now we've finally sort of unmasked
what's happened here with our podcast.
Yes, Disney World, Disneyland.
F off, no.
Really what we wanna talk about is a guy on a shitty show
from the 60s who had a restaurant
because it's kitschy and it's not like,
this is our unmasking is what I'm saying.
This is finally a multi-year con
we've been pulling on you listeners
to suck you in with just like rides you like.
We're three Zorns.
That's right, we're three Zorns.
Three Zorns, yeah.
And even this episode is a Zorn
because some of the appeal,
I mean, when we started talking about doing this series,
obviously the big names that you know came up.
Yes, of course.
Very quickly, Alan Hale Jr., Lobster Barrel
and some of the newspaper print ads
that advertise some of the other celebrity restaurants
in the neck of the woods.
Yes.
I can't remember what really pushed us over the edge
to do this month, but this was one of them, right?
This is one of the first things we,
oh, we gotta, we gotta do Alan Hale's Lobster Barrel.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's a show I don't even like that he was on.
Well, this is where,
you just revealed something in that intro.
This is very Aaron Sorkin of you.
Oh, yes.
Sounds like you think this is a show
that if we looked at it today,
we would say that's not very funny.
That's a good point.
Now, I don't know either way.
Now, actually, Sorkin's description of I Love Lucy
where it's like, I don't know, it was on
if I was home with a toothache or whatever,
that's kind of like Gilligan's Island for me.
I would say like it's on.
Like I have never had an opinion about it.
That's like have an opinion about the tree
outside of my house, it's there.
It's just, it's there.
Okay, I mean, maybe I was being a little,
I was exaggerating a little bit.
I have not watched a ton of Gilligan's Island,
but it never really grabbed me.
I appreciate the kitsch of it.
I appreciate the time in which it was created
and that it was a success.
But anytime I've ever watched it,
I just like it if like it's the movie version
with the Harlem Globetrotters on the island.
I appreciate that aspect of it
and like the making a radio out of a coconut.
I do like that.
It's given us a lot of good cultural references,
I feel like, and it's given, I don't know,
it's a very funny idea for a show
and a show that ran for so long
and made such a big imprint.
Well, yes, I mean, it keeps coming back.
There was a cartoon, which I have a video of.
The Gilligan's Planet, Hanna-Barbera spin-off where.
Oh, right.
Which has a terrible theme song,
which maybe I'll just play right now.
I don't know this offhand.
Gilligan's Planet, which we one day also should do.
There were so many garbage Hanna-Barbera,
just cheap shit, Partridge Family, like future.
The Partridge Family was a future one.
It was like a year.
It was the Jetsons.
Yes, it was like a 25, 23.
It was like a Jetsons Partridge Family show.
Wow, wow.
And it was like, it looks exactly like the Jetsons,
but they just plugged the Partridge Family in it.
It's just.
Partridge Family 2200 AD.
Put AD in there.
So there's just so, if you go through the list
of everything that Hanna-Barbera ever produced,
there's so much crap, there's so much shit.
Yeah.
But I would say like, just real quick,
to sum up my thought is like,
I would put Gilligan's Island, even in the stuff,
the old shows that I like.
There's shows that are like,
Lucy is actually like pretty good and holds up.
I think much better than a lot of this stuff.
Lucy held my attention.
I feel like it was given a prime time spot
at Nick and I, but yeah, Gilligan's Island
was on the other broadcast channels
in the middle of the day.
Dick Van Dyke is a better show than a lot of these shows.
Dick Van Dyke's show.
Yeah, yeah, of course.
And then there's these kitschy shows,
and I think that your mileage may vary.
Did you like I Dream of Jeannie better?
Did you like Bewitched better?
Because it just may be more, which thing do you like?
Do you think a witch is interesting?
Yeah.
Or that a Jeannie's interesting?
Now Samantha's not showing her midriff on Bewitched.
So is that a thing for I Dream of Jeannie?
You can see Barbara Eden's stomach.
Well, this is also like, I feel like the canary
in the coal mine of what was coming
of your fantasy islands or your love boats,
which are just like, guest star palooza,
like very chintzy story of the week.
So when I say shitty, I really,
I don't necessarily mean this is that much worse
than any of these other garbage that I like.
Have we explained that Alan Hale is the person
who played the skipper on the show?
I assume people know that, but I should not assume that.
Yeah, probably some basics need to be said.
Are you not playing the theme song?
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, but I have it here.
So this was a-
So now that you know that Alan Hale was the skipper
and he drove the boat, and the boat went on a three hour tour
and it crashed, and then they all had to live on the island,
and they kept going back to the island,
and I'm not sure why.
Now know that there is a space one, that was cartoon.
Good stuff.
We've got a brand new story about the castaways.
We left our tiny island after years and months and days.
We built a little spaceship.
It's crude, but it could fly.
The wooden spaceship.
We left the room and it was star way
between the stars and sky.
We went from an island to a star, lost on Gilligan's planet.
Gilligan and Skipper, the millionaire-
Just a tune-less minute long slog.
The star Mary Anne began a brand new life.
What creatures we encounter.
What riddles do we face?
Why don't they do a song?
Everybody's the main thing you don't even know.
It is strange, enchanting place.
Our adventures are the best by far.
We're on Gilligan's star planet.
They sounded annoyed that they had to do that.
Oh, I'm sure they were annoyed.
Like you could have so easily just taken
the regular Gilligan's Island theme,
which I think they were trying to do and update the lyrics.
What they did with the original Gilligan's Island,
they took it and they slowed it down
and they didn't sing it, they spoke it.
Yeah.
And added lines.
But it's them though.
It is them, yes.
It's all of them.
It's Don Wells, it's Bob Denver.
Wow, wow.
And not Hanna-Barbera, but Phil Mason.
Oh, is it right?
Similarly crappy.
All right.
I mean at times.
Hanna-Barbera was Partridge Family though.
Was it not?
I think so, yeah.
Okay.
Well, it's Sherwood Schwartz of Brady Bunch fame.
Like the Brady Bunch variety hour we discussed,
he had a hold on these people.
That's right.
He could get them to come back
and do whatever crappy iteration, all these dumb movies.
So many dumb movies.
Yeah, yeah.
Thank God though.
Thank God these people were dying to come back.
Dragging old people out
and forcing them to wear the costume.
Put on the thing.
It's what they know you for.
It'll make people smile.
But from what I could tell
about looking into the subject today, Alan Hale,
there was no dragging involved.
No, nope.
This guy loved being the skipper.
He would be the skipper for you
wherever you wanted him to be.
And that's kind of why seemingly he started
or at least lent his name to this restaurant.
Yeah, and also happy to be there,
shaking hands, signing autographs,
kind of just generally being the color in this restaurant.
I could not find a single bad thing about Alan Hale
as far as people talking about the restaurant.
Cause I found a long post
on Vintage LA's Facebook group.
It was just mountain of people going,
he was the greatest.
We ate there when I was a child
and he came by the table and he was wonderful.
It's just over and over and over again,
you have these praise worthy comments
about Alan Hale himself
and his presence in his lobster barrel.
I found one negative thing
on the website, old LA restaurants,
which is apparently run by Mark Evanier,
the co-writer on a lot of the Gru comics,
the Sergio Aragonis Gru comics.
Also a historian,
wrote a big book about the history of Jack Kirby.
He has a story about eating at the lobster barrel runs
and was quote, a bit overpowered
by Mr. Hale's teddy bear friendliness.
So the problem is that he's too friendly?
He's too friendly.
He's too nice.
He called everyone little buddy, which is cute.
Yeah, wow.
That was cute.
Yes, and he would like,
I think he would mess up like a kid's,
he would, okay, folks,
famously on Gilligan's Island,
he used to hit Gilligan with his hat or Gilligan's hat.
Someone's hat.
Forget, he'd hit him with a hat.
Whichever hat was available.
He'd hit him with a hat,
but then Alan Hale also always got hit by a coconut.
Right, yes.
Which I don't think he would do at the restaurant.
No.
He might be good natured about it.
They tried it for a few weeks, I think, but.
Guys, I hate to say,
I know you're all trying your best,
but I gotta tell you,
it's just not doing a number on the old noggin,
but hey, I love ya.
Really, let me give hugs to everybody.
Thanks for trying.
Little buddy.
Oh, you're all my little buddies.
Let's grab the coconut
and work on the lobster thermidor recipe.
Yeah, so I read,
a couple of people are like,
yeah, he must my hair up and called me little buddy.
Yeah, I saw a YouTube comment that was like,
I went here on a vacation with Mike.
I saw several YouTube comments that were like,
I went on a vacation to LA in the 70s,
and we went to Disneyland,
but the highlight might have been my trip
to Alan Hales lobster parrots.
It was competitive with Disneyland,
because he's around, he's there talking to you,
and in one case, it was like,
my grandfather was there,
and he told Alan, I loved your father, Alan Hales Sr.
I loved him in movies or whatever the hell he was in.
I don't know Alan Hales Sr.
Oh, he was a movie,
oh, well, I have something about him too.
Oh, okay.
Okay, go ahead, yeah.
But it was, just the, then it's like,
well, and then Alan sat down for an hour.
He spent the whole dinner with us,
talking to my grandfather, saying how much he appreciated it.
Like, this is beyond,
I mean, that's, I think what's special
about this restaurant situation.
We're gonna come across other things
where it's in name only,
maybe the person was never even there.
This is the definition of celebrity.
It is theirs, they're there, they own it.
They're part of it, they're in the blood of it.
You know, I think what's funny about unearthing this
is that not a lot of people know this,
not that they should know this,
that the Skipper had a place on La Cienega,
unless you lived here.
But it is funny to like go back in time and see examples of,
cause you know, we talk a little bit about Casamigos
on this podcast.
We talk about celebrity liquor.
It is funny to go see a character actor from the 60s
with something that looks on the surface like a cash grab,
which I think for many of these celebrity restaurants it was.
And this was a money-making thing for the Skipper,
but also it seemed like legit.
He loved it.
He was all in on this idea.
Like now everybody like, I have a cell phone plan.
That's what I do now.
I am of course very involved in my cell phone plan.
Well, I have an ugly, I have an ape.
I have an ugly cartoon ape.
Here's what I am hawking on TV.
I have purchased the ugliest piece of art you've ever seen.
And I can't even muster a smile for the three minutes
that I'm supposed to talk about it.
I can't convey to you at home that I even know
why I'm talking about it.
That's celebrity endorsements today.
We've gotten so far away from Alan Hale.
Exactly.
Who is the gold standard I think now.
What we will find by the end of this podcast
of celebrity endorsed anything.
Well, it's close.
I mean, I think we got one more with its competitive
in terms of really being in there
and rolling up their sleeves.
But we'll have to compare contrast when we get there.
I shouldn't, I got too excited.
But it is, I think we've talked about this before
on the show is that at least for myself,
speak for myself, it's so much more full.
Like there's very famous people that I would like,
oh, that would be fun to say hello to that person.
But nothing would excite me like going back in time
or meeting like a Bernie Cappell who was on Get Smart
and the Love Boat who is still alive.
I bring him up cause he's still alive.
Cause there's an extra generation removed.
So those people feel almost mythical to me.
And like, you know, there's very famous people
I looked up to or like I liked as a kid,
but if they were on Nick at night, that feels extra weird.
It feels like an extra, a different universe perhaps.
Yeah.
Most of the celebrities I've met in my life
was during my time at Funny or Die
where there were so many like needed a security guard
to push them away.
There were like four meetings every day.
And often with somebody who you've never heard of,
but if you're a different kind of person than me,
they're like, you met them?
I don't know, I've never heard their name
until that moment.
Now, if Alan Hale had come in for a meeting,
were he still alive in the days of, oh my God,
I would have come in with such a boatload of ideas,
would have been dropping them on him like coconuts.
You have a couple of good celebrity stories.
And the one I always think about though,
if somebody were to shake me awake
in the middle of the night and go,
Scott Garner's best celebrity story,
I'd go, Rip Taylor.
I told that, right?
Yes, yes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, him calling me.
I was at Disney World and he's,
Scott, it's Rippy.
He was mad at me because of a gift basket
he didn't understand.
That's better than any of the very famous people
who said something about it.
He used me up, Scotty.
Poor Rip.
I drove him.
Yeah, I mean, that was close.
Like, once I realized that that job could be a vehicle
to meet those kind of people.
Yes, Charro's still alive?
Yeah, yeah, if only.
I met Charro in some weird forum in the valley.
There was my family friend who's working
at a deep valley theater where she was doing a show.
And I have a photo of my dad and sister with Charro.
That's fantastic.
I guess it was cool.
I don't remember anything about the internet.
Did she play the guitar?
Not in front of us.
She might've been preparing for a show
where she was going to play.
She's a fantastic flamenco guitarist.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
And will play, I think still was playing casinos
before the pandemic.
Now.
I was like, oh, we gotta go out and see her.
That's a show.
Where does she do it?
I guess the valley.
Maybe the valley, but I feel like-
Some place on Sherman Way.
Mahegan Sun or something.
She played pretty decent-
Oh, Marongo.
Marongo or something.
Or some level.
Yeah, I think she can-
There's a whole chain.
I mean, there's tons of casinos in Vegas
that are the locals' casinos or smaller chains.
There's a chain that Samstown is in
that the killers named their album after,
where there's like, oh, there's a dozen other casinos.
Mm-hmm.
Right, right, right.
And they have rooms.
They have venues.
They can book, yeah, Charo for sure.
Yeah.
I don't think it's an impossible dream to see Charo
unless, of course, with this whole run,
we gotta be careful with the PTR curse.
Oh, God, you're right.
It's proven so strong.
Oh, no, I talked about Bernie Cappell.
Oh, shit.
This is not exclusive to us.
Lots of podcasts end up talking about someone off the cuff
and then they die.
Well, and again, we figured out why.
And, Grissom, figured out why.
We were very interested in-
Old-
Very old people.
Yeah.
Andrew Grissom, I will say, for Christmas,
bought me a photo of Rip Taylor.
Is that right?
A signed photo of Rip Taylor
that he found at like a thrift store.
Wow.
And he signed to someone else on the back, too.
I mean, signed, obviously, he didn't sign it to me.
Did I say on the show also that he,
for this shoot that honestly was bare bones,
there were like four people involved in the shoot,
and he brought white chocolate mustaches for everyone.
Fantastic.
Candy mustaches.
Terrific, fantastic.
And then made us all take photos.
All right, now, everybody put the mustache over your head.
Okay, now you, get on the floor.
I'm putting this cone on you.
He made the DP lie down.
Oh, man.
Like poured glitter all over him,
like hit him with a mustache.
I'd rather, look, I love Mission Impossible.
I'd rather meet Rip than Tom Cruise.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, it was special.
It was really special.
Tom would be great.
I'd love to work with Tom.
I'd love to have his hard eye contact on me
and make me feel special like he does to everyone, but.
I'd love to be terrified in Tom Cruise's presence, yes.
Yeah, I'd love to be on a movie where he like,
he's like, we need your body in better shape.
Like, we just simply need you to be in better shape for this.
And you're gonna be working out of my gym
with me every morning.
Here's a book you can read
and teach you how to unlock your potential
and rid yourself of the phatens.
That's right.
That cloud your mind and your body.
And are you on psych meds?
Hopefully not.
Well, then that's it.
Get off the meds, dude.
So this, I mean, so this is the,
this is a place where everybody could have
a Rip Taylor-esque experience.
Guaranteed, it seemed like.
It also seems like,
I don't know much about the history of the place,
but it seems like Lobster Barrel,
which I think we're focusing on the first half.
Yes, you're right.
Of the episode title and the name of the restaurant.
As we should, it is Alan Hales,
but let's not lose sight of the phrase Lobster Barrel.
Is a very funny. Which I think was a chain
that existed with a couple locations outside of Alan Hale.
And I think he wanted to have a franchise,
but not just buy one, but to have his name.
He bought into this location.
I think so, or I think made it exist possibly.
I think there was not one.
I could be wrong. I'm not exactly sure.
But let's, with that said, Lobster Barrel.
Boy, what a crazy phrase.
I feel like.
Not the lobsters come in barrels.
Is that how they're transported?
Is the place itself considered the Lobster Barrel?
Like the restaurant is a barrel of fun
and you'll be in it with lobsters?
It paints an interesting picture.
You run out of seafood house name,
fish house names at a certain point.
Crab trap, clam bar.
You know, these are the go-tos I feel like.
Sharts in there.
Yeah.
Yeah. Schooner, like boats, name all the boats.
You know.
Boat house, chart house, schooner house, salmon house.
Is there another like barrel?
I guess barrel is a fun.
Well, cracker barrel.
Cracker barrel, thank you.
And then there's Eidlauer on the valley.
It is a big barrel.
It's a bar and.
You can see that.
Yeah, they have food.
There's that dog in the back from the Rocketeer.
You ever been back there?
I have been back there,
but I didn't realize it was back there.
I think that's, I'm not sure it's from the move,
but you know what I mean?
Is it like in the back of the patio?
Like a facade of a dog with smoking a corn cob pipe.
It's on the patio?
Eidlauer. Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, that's, wasn't there originally, I think.
That was moved there.
Like that was a food stand.
Like in LA, car culture caught on so quickly
after they dismantled the red car trolleys.
A lot of businesses would like make novelty shaped buildings.
Often like, of course, Tail of the Pup, the most notable.
Yes, the hot dog stand that was a big hot dog,
which I think was, I'm not sure if I ever went there,
if it was still there when I was a kid.
It's supposedly coming back.
Oh, great.
It's being restored and I think will be re-opened.
I don't know how fast they're moving on this.
That's great.
Oh, wonderful.
I mean, that was on, that was La Cienega.
That was in this stretch of LA
where this, where Alan Hale did his restaurant.
A lot, all kinds of crazy other places around there.
There's a restaurant where you walk through a whale's mouth
that looked really nuts.
What was that called?
The, I don't have the name in front of me.
Oh, the Fish Shanty.
Oh, there's a, we missed a word.
We missed Shanty.
Look at this thing, like big wooden doors
with a big crazy monstro.
And there was a theme park around here, Kittyland,
which we talked about with Dumbo
because Walt consulted the Kittyland guy.
I think it's where the Beverly Center is now.
It seems like La Cienega was like a whole town,
a crazy bullshit.
You know what it sounds like is like the Beach Boulevard
where in the greatest city on earth,
Buena Park, where it's like everywhere,
oh my God, there's a castle from Medieval Times.
There's a Burger King that looks like a castle.
There's the Pirate Place.
There's knots, there's roller coasters,
there's an Independence Hall.
It seems like La Cienega kind of had that vibe
in the 60s, 70s.
Yeah, for sure.
And did we say this was part,
Alan Hales was part of Restaurant Row,
which was other celebrity restaurants.
He was next.
Well, and specifically, seemingly celebrity corner
of Restaurant Row.
Districts within districts.
Exactly, and he was next to Xavier Cougat's restaurant,
which I believe was what, Cougat's?
Casa Cougat.
Casa Cougat, thank you.
Yeah.
Casa Cougat.
Apparently, I was having trouble finding-
Mary DeCharro, by the way.
Yeah, this is what,
I feel like we've been talking about this this whole time,
and Xavier Cougat, and Xavier Cougat.
I got no clue on Xavier Cougat.
Bandleader?
Yeah, bandleader back when that was like one of the hugest
professions in the entertainment industry.
I believe it's pronounced Xavier Cougat.
Xavier, yeah.
Because I found one episode of What's Your Line,
where he's the mystery celebrity guest,
and then in-
Is that What's My Line?
Huh?
Is it What's My Line?
What's My Line, yeah.
Okay, I'm confusing it with you,
but you're a little, yeah.
So they say his name in that kind of quickly,
but then also Javier Bardem and being the Ricardos,
said it in a way I have never heard that pronounced before.
That's how I learned it said,
they don't say it like Professor Xavier,
they say Xavier Cougat.
Okay.
That's yeah, so you learned that way.
I learned one seemingly true-ish fact
from being the Ricardos.
This is the type of like-
I keep learning who bandleaders are.
That's right.
This is the 2022 on podcast The Ride,
lots of something really dirty every time,
and a bandleader.
How dirty will this one get?
Well, you have to really live up to what we've been doing.
Well, Alan himself provides some fodder later.
Oh yeah, yeah.
This is just a little example of Xavier.
Xavier.
This is Chica Chica Boom Chica.
This guy was like the biggest rock star in the world.
Listen to this shit, folks.
This guy was the weekend.
Xavier was the weekend of his day.
He was in like whatever the uncut gems of the time.
Why do you guys know about him though?
He's just, he's around.
Desi Arnaz mentions him on the Tonight Show.
I talked about this on the show before
when Desi Arnaz is like 12 minutes
and boring every one of the Tonight Show.
And he's old, he mentioned Xavier Cougat,
married to Charro.
He's around, he's in the universe.
He's in the old people, old actor universe.
We specifically, I believe Desi made a comment
we always joke about.
He was like, in Xavier Cougat was cheap.
Oh sure, yeah.
And he might've even said he was boring or cheap.
Yeah, they were just roasting each other.
But there's plenty of people I watch
on like these old roasts or something where I go,
I don't really know what that,
I don't have a deep knowledge of this person.
I just know them from being around.
They kind of like caught the tail,
the beginning era of television.
They jumped from live performance and radio
into television in the way that Tommy Dorsey
was likely dead.
Bunny Barigan, that's another guy I know.
Geez, oh my God.
I don't know a lot about Bunny Barigan.
I just have his best stuff.
Now you say Casa Cougat next door,
but we think maybe at some point there was a change
of the venue because I believe it might've been
the same place and I don't know whether one was before
the other or what happened.
But another important person had a restaurant around here
which was Caesar Romero, the Joker from the original Batman.
And his restaurant was?
Cappuccino Ristorante.
Great.
Which leads to, you can actually hear credit to,
amazingly a couple people on Twitter have tweeted
about Alan Hale's Lobster Barrel before,
including Pee Wee Herman and Cliff Nesterov
who's a historian of this kind of stuff.
And then Matt Oswalt, Patton's brother,
tweeted out an ad that is a dual ad.
Really the ads are the main thing to talk about.
But the ad was a dual ad for both Caesar Romero's
Cappuccino Ristorante and Alan Hale's Lobster Barrel,
both advertising what they were doing for Thanksgiving.
And Matt Oswalt tweeted,
imagine waking up on Thanksgiving morning
and saying to yourself, do I want to spend Thanksgiving
with the Joker or the Skipper?
That sums up why this is so great.
Yes.
That is a perfect tweet that explains.
One of them might be there truly.
This was a.
The golden age.
I think so.
Well and now you come to Hollywood,
what's Hollywood like?
And you have to figure out,
Hollywood Hollywood is the worst place on earth.
And then really it all happens in bunkers
in Delray or whatever.
What is Hollywood?
There's no, at this point in time,
you really could go to the Skipper's restaurant
in West Hollywood and you might see the Skipper there.
There was a Hollywood.
Right, it felt like, yes, it felt like,
I mean when you see it dramatized,
it always does feel like,
oh and the old stars were always around,
they were at Schwab's or they were here or whatever.
This was a concrete proof of a place you could go.
And same with Telly, same with Telly Savelle.
It's a lot like Sloppy Telly.
You knew you could go to,
unless he was in shooting, he'd be drinking or playing pool.
The universal Sherry.
Yeah.
Which was later, remarkable,
because that's the 80s, 90s.
This is before he died in the hotel.
Right, we remember.
Sloppy Telly, I want a place where I can,
that I don't have to clean up after myself
and where I can drop dead and somebody will pick me up.
We need to find a place.
I don't want my relatives to have to do it.
Baby.
The cleaning staff will dispose of the body.
They won't mind.
I'll leave a tip, I'll leave a big tip in my robe.
It's for you for cleaning up my corpse, baby.
It is, it wasn't.
It should have just said like in case of death,
there was like an envelope with the money in it.
I look, hey, Telly's no fool.
Telly could drop dead any minute.
So I'll always leave your cash tip for your death.
We're your housekeeper.
We need to find which room he died in.
There were, I mean, it wasn't unusual back in the day
for people to live in nice hotels.
It is unusual for that time period, I feel like,
for a aging television star to live in a Sheraton
next to a theme park around the corner
from an In-N-Out burger.
That's kind of different than the Chateau Marmots
who are like the French Riviera.
Celebrities are always at that In-N-Out.
Like what's their, Ghislaine Maxwell.
That's right.
It's the biggest celebrity hotspot there is.
Look, there was a time when you could go to that In-N-Out
and always see Ghislaine there.
You could always hang with Ghislaine.
I always wondered who that woman was.
She always reading a book.
She was so nice.
She'd call you a little buddy.
She'd mush your hair up.
It was just a magical time.
Her catchphrases.
But like, I'm trying to even think of like,
we've heard, we've lived in,
we've been adults in Los Angeles for so long.
I've heard stories of like,
he for Sutherland partying,
but there was never like a central location
you could necessarily go.
Cause like, I was trying to think,
is there like, there's no,
I can't think of a version of this.
Well, the documentary,
the Edgar Wright documentary taught me that
Russell Mayall from Sparks is always
sitting quietly at Earth Cafe.
Okay.
I don't think that counts.
That's, not bad.
Yeah, yeah.
At least there's one spot that we know.
That's not as, that's not,
maybe not the glamour level we're talking about.
There's something called Erawan.
Is that, do I have that right?
There's a chain of like rich people groceries.
Yeah, I just caught on to that.
There's a Calabasas one.
Yeah.
And yeah, I, well, I don't know.
Well, that's what the, the,
the Caruso mall in Calabasas, the comments,
where you might see an unfriendly Justin Bieber
grabbing a coffee and then leaving
in the ugliest car he've ever seen.
Yeah.
I mean, in Burbank, of course,
there was the karaoke bar Dimples,
one of the most cursed places in the city.
It's now a Whole Foods.
I'm sure the ghosts of just the building haunts it,
but Mr. Belding would be there.
Oh, well that's.
You can guarantee that Mr. Belding would be there.
Honestly, that is in the zone, I guess.
Mr. Belding is like the modern day this.
But, but yeah, it's a little.
But everyone was like, oh yeah, we go.
It sucks.
Like every, I never went,
it was a thing college students who lived
at the Oakwoods with like,
it was the only bar you could really walk to.
People would walk down there
and get their picture with Mr. Belding.
But he was like, everyone's like, oh yeah,
the bar sucks, the owner's a sleazebag.
There is a bar rescue episode about it.
Yeah.
And the guy.
Oh, I'm doing a lot of,
I watched bar rescue right before you guys came over.
Oh really?
Oh yeah.
There's a Dimples episode and the owner's so sleazy.
I mean, he's even wearing the sleaziest,
like short sleeve sweater polo.
If you can picture that, like,
and he's like, take the blow job shot.
Yeah.
And it's like you to put like the shop
between his legs.
The shop between his legs and they'd give it to you for,
and I was just like,
people would come back from this place.
It's like, you gotta come.
And I'm like, I don't know that I do.
Do I?
Yeah.
Taffer's like, who wants to do this?
You're demeaning women.
What are you doing?
Yeah.
The best celebrity you've got is Mr. Belding?
It's just been off the air for years.
I'm shutting it down.
Mr. Belding is leering on the 20 year olds with fake IDs,
the 20 year old film students with fake IDs.
To bring it back to Alan Hale,
that's what there's, like,
you would think it would be weird and sad.
It seems like it wasn't.
Celebrities always around, but yeah,
it seems like everybody's aglow about this.
That's what, yes, that is the difference.
There's a thing we're doing later this month
that it does seem a little more sad.
A little more sad, yeah.
Yeah, but this does seem like a nice restaurant.
It's got a giant menu of like-
Yeah, people thought the food was good as well.
Yeah, it's a steakhouse and it's doing lobster and shrimp
and a lot of preparations.
Well, do people have the menu?
Oh, of course.
Imagine we all pulled the menu.
A beautiful illustrated menu.
That's really great, hand drawn
where everything's charmingly crooked
and they're jamming a lot in.
It looks like an old Mad Magazine thing.
But I like it because there's words that I don't see a lot.
Well, you brought this one up, lobster Thermador.
Okay, so a lot of these preparations are still done
at a lot of nice restaurants back East.
Lobster Thermador is where the meat is removed
from the lobster, tossed with cream,
then it's put back in the shell, covered in cheese,
and put in a broiler.
Cheese and lobster, is that?
It is a unique combination,
but a lot of these kind of simulate like crab,
I was surprised to find crab Oscar is not on the menu.
Crab Oscar, tossed with cream, served with asparagus,
and usually a topping for like steak or chicken,
if you can Oscar an entree.
And can we Oscar that please?
That's right, yeah.
So.
Have you ever Oscared something?
Oh yeah, I've Oscared something, yeah.
Really?
It's usually tossed with not,
Hollandaise is the mother sauce,
Bernays is one of the childs.
Mother sauce.
In French cuisine, Hollandaise,
which you have on eggs Benedict is referred to as a base,
like egg based cream, mother sauce,
and then depending on.
Wait a minute.
Yeah.
I still don't know where mother sauce comes from.
It's a base, it's a base sauce,
and then depending on what you add to it,
if you add tarragon, that becomes Bernays sauce.
Mother sauce.
But did any sauce that you asked your mother for,
did that qualify as a mother sauce?
The barbecue, the yeah, the sweet baby raise.
Is that a mother sauce if your mother hands it to you?
Ask, when you asked what the mother sauce was,
would you of course do it, excuse me,
what is the mother sauce, please?
Mother sauce?
So you would, okay, so you would ask for something Oscared,
and then find out what the.
This is like in the last five years of my life,
I have ordered this.
This is a new thing, is Oscaring?
Well, I didn't, yeah, I didn't eat steak,
I wasn't a big steak guy,
because growing up, the era,
the 90s was the era of like don't undercook meat or eggs,
or you will die.
And it wasn't until when I was much older
and went to actual steak houses
where they put like care and thoughtfulness,
where it's like, oh, you can order a steak medium,
you can order a medium rare.
So a lot of those places you can add like a hollandaise to it
or mushrooms and thyme.
Good hollandaise to a steak?
You can add a lot of stuff on top of a steak.
Traditionally, usually you don't wanna,
if it's a nice enough place, the steak is good enough
and seasoned well enough, you don't need to pile stuff on it.
What's my feel about everything you're describing?
Like the lobster, we're gonna put cheese
and cream on the lobster?
Like, you want the lobster?
I mean, if you eat lobster, like a broiled,
a steamed lobster, a broiled lobster and stuff,
you're covering it in clarified butter, you're dipping it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, true.
The base way it comes involves adding something.
I like the option to like pile shit on something.
But obviously if it's a hamburger, if it's anything,
you would like, I would always like to try something
in like a very simple version
to really taste what's going on.
But it is fun sometimes to get a bunch of shit
piled on anything.
Yeah.
If it's an interesting concoction.
I mean, especially in the mid 20th century,
post-war America, like everything is being cooked,
chicken a la king, everything's being cooked
with cream and egg yolks, you know.
Well, I think if we're doing,
since it's a restaurant month, if we're doing,
maybe we don't do plus it up for anything,
it's gotta be Oscar it.
If we're gonna Oscar it, it's like, how do we?
Let's keep that in mind.
I love crab.
I think crab is much more flavorful,
like just as a base than lobster.
Sure.
And so like-
And you like imitation crab meat as well?
I do like imitation crab meat too, yeah.
That's pretty good.
I like both.
I actually don't, you know what,
now that I'm thinking, I don't really have a strong,
I like both and maybe I associate both together.
I don't have a sophisticated palette enough to even know.
I can't even imagine what the difference is
off the top of my head.
I think, I mean, a lot of places have lobster,
but like crab, growing up so close to the Chesapeake Bay,
Maryland is just crab country.
Like it's so cheap and it's so plentiful.
It's like if you go to New England,
like lobster is everywhere.
So how often would you have crab or lobster?
Oh, in the summer, at least once a week.
Really?
Crab or scallops or clam strips or flounder.
Yeah, at the Jersey shore.
Flounder, did we have flounder ever?
We haven't had flounder.
When you saw Little Mermaid,
was that a thing where you were like, we ate him?
And Sebastian.
And Sebastian, yeah, you're right.
One of each a week.
Yeah.
Sebastian day.
And you fry up a mermaid.
You fry up-
Right on the shore, you pick one out from a tank.
Flounder and fried flounder and fried shrimp
are like the kids menu go-tos,
which I have never shaken off.
Oh yeah, fried shrimp or like breaded shrimp for sure
as a kid.
Yeah.
You dip that in tartar sauce or whatever.
But flounder is very flaky.
It's not overwhelmingly fishy
and it's a great vessel to carry ketchup
and tartar sauce and cocktail sauce.
You put ketchup on flounder?
Sure.
As a kid, I put ketchup on everything.
Would you put ketchup on flounder now?
I feel like that seems like a faux pas.
And now I just mostly tartar sauce or cocktail.
Cocktails basically just ketchup and horseradish.
I guess you're right.
I never thought of that.
Would anybody do anything Columbo style,
which is a way that he served,
that old Alan served veal.
Oh, oh.
Veal Columbo is breaded with wheat germ,
oregano, garlic powder, mushroom and marsala wine.
Okay, so it goes in that, all right, so it's a marsala.
Yeah, it's just kind of a marsala.
Yeah.
Huh, huh.
Just a crazy- Columbo style.
I'm sorry, I jumped to a special menu,
which is Alan Hale's Lobster Barrel special menu
in conjunction with the American Heart Association.
So he worked with the Heart Association
to bring you the dessert pineapple cheesecake.
Yeah.
Also that veal had breading, right?
Yeah, yeah.
Baked halibut with alfredo sauce.
Yeah.
I don't know, maybe he might not have filled in
the Heart Association on the full plan.
They got a lot on their plate.
They were big hearts and what have you.
They were big Gilligan's Island fans
and they said, look,
whatever you want to do is fine with us.
We just want our name next to you, Alan.
Yeah, sure thing, little buddy.
They're calling the entire
American Heart Association little buddy.
Aw, shucks.
That's right, little buddy.
Yeah, this menu, I'm going back on the regular menu.
First of all, it is interesting to see the prices.
There was a- Oh, yeah.
They're not like, I mean, it's like a normal entrees,
like what, between $8 and $15?
And then some of the higher,
there's like bigger ticket things.
Shrimp and lobster Newberg,
you got to jack it up to $15.95.
Yeah, yeah, that's a little more pricey,
but everything seems fairly reasonable.
Norfolk style.
I mean, maybe regular run of the mill crab meat,
but when you're getting the Norfolk in there.
Here's interesting, Jason, do you know anything about this?
The chef's curry corner, seafood curry,
does it say a la Sinbad?
La Sinbad.
Yeah, I don't know.
Do you know what that is?
I'm impressed, curry, that's pretty adventurous.
Well, that's what I was thinking, is that something,
that feels like you're just getting like the older
generation in America into like curry and stuff,
which I think is, which is delicious.
I have the spiciest kind of curry,
that's what I'm, I wonder if this is a very 70s
kind of curry.
But still, like I didn't have curry
until like 10 years ago, probably.
You know, and bouillabaisse, I was surprised,
like that seemed pretty adventurous.
Yeah, so it's interesting.
Curry is interesting.
You can do that, you can do that seafood curry,
a la Sinbad with major grazed chutney.
So kinds of treasures on this thing and drawings and see,
it's a great looking little.
A little skipper on it and then a lot of barrels,
one's tipped over, one has a bunch of claws coming out of it.
It's like, that's a little, little scenes going on.
I mean, it's, it's, it's beautiful.
And this isn't the only thing that you could walk away from
at this establishment.
You could very easily find yourself the proud owner of
an Alan Hales lobster barrel postcard
with this great old line drawing of him,
which you'll see in the art of the episode probably.
And if he's there, he's signing it.
He's signing that baby for you.
He loves to do it.
Apparently he would find first timers like,
hey, I never seen you here before.
Sit down, make yourself at home.
I let me show you the menu here.
Hey, you're a little buddy.
Here's, there's an autograph, a whole skipper for you.
Okay.
So cool.
Yeah.
These have ended up on eBay and like the last episode,
you want to do a real quick souvenir smackdown.
Oh yeah, please.
I guess what you're, what are you getting?
A, I mean, I can show you,
I don't know what the hell the autograph says.
Kathy, it's fun.
All keys, alibol, the best, the stain.
I don't know what.
I don't think.
Probably not, unless he was drinking heavily that night.
He was really drunk.
I hope it's not too little buddy
or else I will find myself buying it.
I think it's to Kathy.
You know, this was an authentic,
the person said in the description,
this was like to their parents when they visited.
What do you think this is going for?
On eBay.
Yeah.
Ooh, 29.99.
Jason.
$50.
We're talking 150.
Wow.
Yeah, yeah.
Keep it going higher.
There's one more Alan Hale item.
I want to do a quick bid on.
This is a DVD set of Alan Hale's pre-
Oh yeah.
Gulligan's Island show, Biff Baker USA.
There's eight episodes all told.
Biff Baker seemed to be a kind of pre-Indiana Jones
sort of thing in the fifties where Biff Baker and his wife
were trying to find items in the world.
Wow.
But then they'd, you know, stumble across some problem
that like they, you know,
have to solve a crime or whatever.
Anyway, eight episodes of Biff Baker USA.
What are you paying for that?
Eight episodes.
9.99.
Jason.
I'm gonna say a hundred dollars.
Well, Jason gets it because the answer is $9,999.
What?
And 99 cents.
Biff Baker.
I suspect a mistyped entry.
I don't think that a Biff Baker DVD
or used to cost $10,000.
This reminds me, there's that great Simpson's joke
and I hope I'm getting the specifics right.
It's a picture of Sean Connery, autographed by Roger Moore.
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
Seems like a good show though.
Check out Biff Baker.
Wow.
Let's get Jason that role, Biff Baker.
Biff Baker.
Fun fact about Alan Hale Jr.
Hollywood High class of 1938
with graduating classmate Mickey Rooney.
Oh. Whoa.
Yes. Boy, oh boy.
Wow.
Height, oh my God.
Those two roughnecks running around
like they're doing high school hijinks.
Did Mickey Rooney just go to regular high school?
Wasn't he a big movie star by then?
I think a lot of young actors went to Hollywood High.
Yeah.
It was like you went there
and they got that mural that's everybody who went.
Yes, now they have the sun-bleached mural
and their backyard is the Jimmy Kimmel parking lot.
The concert stage.
Yeah, concert stage parking lot.
Hey, I saw Weezer there.
That stage, maybe twice.
You went to two Weezers at Kimmel?
I think I've only seen two Kimmel concerts
and I think they're both Weezer.
I think.
Anyway, I completely lost my train of thought.
Oh, the Mickey Rooney,
there was that joke going around
that someone photoshopped
of a Mickey Rooney restaurant that did not exist.
It was, what was it, Potato something?
Yes, it was all different preparations of potato
and it was in North Hollywood.
It was in the Valley where you would believe it.
You would believe like.
That Mickey Rooney would have.
I mean, I would believe.
Well, that was a part of an influence
in doing this month too
and then we were disappointed to learn it wasn't real.
But, yeah, Alan Hales lobster barrel.
Thank you.
Very real.
Yeah.
There were some other,
Carol O'Connor from All in the Family had a restaurant.
Yeah, I just discovered this.
The Ginger Man.
It was in Beverly Hills.
Yeah.
Yeah, the Ginger Man is crazy.
There's a New York one too.
You can look up photos of Carol O'Connor
hanging out with Larry Hagman and Tyne Daly.
The last time that the Los Angeles Rams
were in the Super Bowl
as they are going to be for the next Super Bowl.
I think I'm right about this.
LA Rams haven't been in it since 1980
and they cut to, let's see how the vibe is
over at the Ginger Man.
Wow.
During the broadcast.
And let's check in on our friends at the Ginger Man.
It was mania.
The Ginger Man seemed like a spot.
Yeah.
But then he changed it to Carol O'Connor's place.
Then he fully, oh and also he talks about it in his book.
Wait, what did I say?
No, no, did he call it Archie Bunker's place?
No, I think he called it Carol's place.
I was saying he called it like that because of, I assume.
Like his place is after Archie Bunker's place.
Right, I think.
The guy also, he was very open about the fact
that he just wanted to have a restaurant
to have a restaurant.
This is something that people did back then.
He wasn't worried about turning a profit
and that's why he paid health insurance
to everybody who worked there.
Hey.
Which made him just break even.
He would've made a profit if he didn't pay everybody
in the back health insurance.
That's great.
Carol O'Connor's a good guy.
Yeah, and he just wanted a place to go hang.
Yeah.
Where people would kiss his ass all day.
Who doesn't want that?
That's what Alan Hale wanted.
This is great.
This is a great way of being these kind of guys.
Yeah, I mean if you.
I need a place.
If you need, yeah, if you want a place,
if you're famous and beloved,
you would just find a room somewhere
where people would be going expecting to see you
and be happy to see you.
I mean it is a great life hack, really.
Yeah.
Yeah, we should have podcasted around restaurant
and we're just there every night.
I mean, as long as we can find somebody
to figure out the restaurant part.
Well, Jason, you heard him talking about the.
Uh-oh.
It's all, it's chicken all a king.
Yeah.
Oh no.
He cares from worrying about restaurant margins.
Yeah, yeah, it's all, that's your forte.
Guys, stop giving away Oscarings.
Oscar's aren't free.
On the house.
We want to be generous, but we can't.
We're not made of Oscars.
The market price of crab is through the roof.
Does, excuse me, the flounder,
I think it's a little bit undercooked
and Jason was like,
I just saw some ketchup on it.
It's fine.
Podcast the rights under peril.
Yeah.
Is there another Pete container though
that we could say instead of barrel?
Scott, I wish I could find flounder
that easily in Los Angeles.
It's like finding good Italian bread.
It's impossible.
I had to agree with Spielberg and Gatzelberg.
The bread out here leaves a lot to be desired.
Or you have to learn about the local kinds of,
like torta roll, but Leo rolls are delicious.
If anyone has a restaurant that's going under right now
or you think, oh man,
I don't even know if I'm gonna have six months left
on this thing, but I gotta ride out and see.
Just add us to the name of your restaurant.
Podcast Clubhouse, yeah.
Yeah, just say like, and let's see what happens.
I'm not guaranteeing.
This isn't very clever,
but it's a nod to your past to call it
podcast the rides flounder container.
Yeah, great.
A nod to the famous store.
That's good.
Unless there was a specific kind of container
you were fond of, then feel free.
You're the expert.
Okay, yeah.
I mean, I'm trying to think of the type of,
there was a thing called an AMAC box.
That's too confusing.
That's not a widely known term though.
That could be a meal.
Sterlite, is that the name of the brand?
That's a good meal.
Well, if it's a brand, we can't.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
I'd love to see any of these.
Your containers start containers full of lobster.
We saw.
Podcast the rides flounder bin, right?
That's generic, that's not a brand.
Flounder basket.
Well, yeah, you could get it in a basket.
That's not bad.
I'm just trying to think of like flounder hamper.
Podcast the rides flounder hamper.
That's my favorite sounding one so far.
That's pretty good.
If you know that your establishment is going to tank
and you wanna have fun on the way down,
I will help you turn it into podcast the rides
flounder hamper.
There is in the Valley, there is,
I've heard it used to be an H salt fish and chips,
which was another chain.
It's mentioned in Mad Men.
I think Pete Campbell, when he lives in Los Angeles,
that's H salt fish and chips is one of his clients.
I have heard that one of the locations
is still a fish and chips place,
but they had to take off the H salt maybe
because they are no longer associated with it,
which it seemed like it was falling apart to begin with,
so I don't know.
So this is a scenario you're looking for.
Yeah, well, you're looking for.
We're.
Yeah, you're gonna help run it with the guy,
whoever the person or the person is.
We're gonna take over this former H salt.
Take off this dying fish and chips restaurant.
Uh-huh, and then we'll yeah.
Let's kill it in style.
Jason.
Greasiest fish and chips I have ever had,
a notoriously greasy dish.
We can promise you Jason will put in a 40 hour workweek
there also to help you with everything.
I mean, I feel like you end up working an 80 hour workweek
running a restaurant.
Also, what's the statistic?
Like most restaurants close within five years?
Yeah, well, this one's closing.
Oh, yeah, we're gonna be dying.
We're gonna be done way quicker than that.
Yeah, it could be a matter of weeks.
Oh, nearly.
You might not even get up to 80 hours.
It'd be like the first day we'd get like five listeners
that were like, oh, that's funny they did this.
Wow, they did it.
Boy, classic.
This is my favorite show.
These guys really commit.
Oh, well, I took a picture and didn't buy anything.
Yeah.
Four days later, we're in the ground.
The tartar sauce is immediately given everyone listeria.
Jason was having a screaming match with the owner.
You son of a bitch.
I said market price on the scallops.
Not buy one, get one free.
Are you insane?
The owner found a garbage bag of shrimp in Jason's trunk.
Smuggling.
He's trying to start a second business somewhere.
He's like, I'm gonna waste the rest of the game.
He bought a big freezer
and he's trying to eat for the rest of the year.
Now you say garbage bag of shrimp.
That was one of my worst PA jobs,
production assistant jobs in Hollywood.
Did you eat on American Gladiators?
No, that was.
One garbage bag of shrimp, brother.
That at least had real,
there was, no, this was a promotionalbreak.com web series.
The lowest you could go, PAing.
And so I was shooting at this house
and this guy's house in the valley,
shot on a Friday, off on the weekend.
They had shrimp,
they had shrimp, like etouffee or shrimp and rice
for lunch on Friday.
Threw them in garbage bags in his trash can.
Came back Monday morning, they're like, okay, bad news.
You guys gotta go to a hardware store and buy some rate.
The shrimp garbage bags are covered in bugs.
They are covered in maggots.
Oh my God.
And then another guy who had a truck,
we had to throw the garbage bags in his pickup truck
and drive around to find an open dumpster.
This is illegal, by the way, to dump that much trash
in someone else's dumpster.
And after blasting it with hardware store bug spray
to try and kill the bugs,
this was the lowest point of the recession.
There's said I think of anything of your life,
of anyone's life.
Probably. Oh my God.
Jeez. Break.com.
But it was where we all remember the content they made.
Don't we?
Are they the ones who did that motorcycle stunt
that almost killed that guy?
We all got coffee mugs that said break.com we know guys.
Which I still have.
I have to get rid of that.
I hate that.
Why am I still haunted by that?
Can we steal that?
Cause we know guys too.
Like podcast The Ride.
They love Ellen Hale and talking about lobster.
This could have been,
we could have gotten a show on Spike TV if it still existed
with the content we put out.
I have some memory real quick,
just some memories here from people on that Facebook.
Oh great.
My friends and I,
I guess this is not negative cause this person was excited.
My friends and I used to go in there in our skateboards
and try to get free candy or mints.
One time Ellen Hale was there and kicked us out
of the restaurant and told us the candy was for the patrons.
My friends and I were thrilled to meet him
even though he kicked us out.
Well, here's somebody.
When I was a kid, he shook my hand right after I ate nachos
and got cheese all over his hand.
Well, hey, thanks for the free sauce buddy.
Hey little buddy, appreciate it.
You can wipe your hands, I don't skip or anything.
Yeah, I think those were the best.
Oh wait, here's one.
Jimmy Cagney was there that night also
with a 22 year old on each arm.
I remember this being not too long before he passed.
Yeah, Jimmy Cagney would have been old.
Very old.
When this was over.
Were they his nurses?
Let's hope.
Yeah, yeah.
Let me just wait, I had a couple of them too.
Well, I saw that he, I think he would like,
I saw a comment saying that he would like kick drunks
out of the restaurant.
I like that he had to do it too.
Yeah, it was him.
Why wasn't there like not a bouncer but.
Well, I think he just took charge.
Why would you hire a big old lug
when you yourself are the most famous big old lug there is?
Yeah, I guess so.
But then one, one, no, one person,
one drunk who he had to kick out of the bar
was David Carradine.
I guess I saw this, I saw this too, yes.
I like, yeah, David Carradine.
I have this here.
He started destroying the restaurant.
With his kung fu moves.
With quote, his kung fu moves.
He started, he got drunk and rowdy while at the restaurant
and had started to do some damage to the place
using his martial arts.
Alan Ayl had to throw Mr. Carradine out
and did so using a baseball bat just in case.
He was.
The real question is though,
did he ever resort to having to hit a patron with his hat?
Oh man.
Why you?
That was, in today's day and age,
that would be like an upcharge event
to get hit with his hat.
Like you go in there and you get the meal,
but you pay $50 and then it's like at the convention
when you see like Robert Englund dresses up
as Freddy Krueger once in a while,
but you gotta pay a premium.
Oh yeah.
To get a photo with Robert dressed as Freddy,
and not just a regular Robert.
So yeah, if you get a hat, if you get hit with his hat,
that would have cost money.
But I don't know, it seemed like he liked the bat better.
He seemed like he liked, he was like a pro wrestler sting
and his weapon of choice was a bat in real life.
I want that like in a street fighter level.
Alan Hale with a bat versus David Carradine.
Did they ever do that on Celebrity Deathmatch?
Back in the day?
It was that?
They did it on a relevant Celebrity Deathmatch.
That was on like note cards, like when they were struggling.
That was possible, like we don't have any ideas
we can do this one.
Slagerkuggen versus Vizierinus.
The van leader brawl.
I found the website for MeTV, which is a channel.
Oh I saw this, yeah.
A cable channel that has a lot of syndicated shows.
It's Nick and I now basically.
It's got Svengulli on it too.
That same guy Mark at Vanir covers a lot
of historical stuff on it.
And there was a blog post about Alan Hale
and like different facts.
Cause he, after this restaurant was opened through the 80s
I think he financially got out of it in like 1982.
Eventually would open a travel agency,
like a travel company.
Leisure and travel I believe it was.
Yeah and so they had different facts about it
that he advertised for a Canadian car dealership.
That he had a travel agency.
All these different things about his life.
One of the comments, this is from Jeffrey.
22 months ago, early 2020, early days of the pandemic.
Jeffrey said, ah yes, the skipper.
At least he would whack Gilligan on the noggin.
Unlike dumb ass AG to Barney, Barney was a four star
insolent, insubordinate turd.
So this guy was really mad at Barney Fife.
He's talking about Barney Fife and Andy Griffith.
Andy Griffith.
And he's saying that he appreciated the skipper
who would discipline Gilligan in an aggressive way
versus Barney who Andy Griffith never like punched Barney
on Andy Griffith even though.
Older man appears to have a black and white photo
of him in the services.
So he took these TV shows very seriously.
I believe, or at least the ranking.
Like he took rank fairly seriously.
Right, because Andy.
He wanted more discipline on his.
He wanted Andy to discipline Barney.
Barney was an insubordinate, an insubordinate turd,
an insolent.
He must have hated Hogan's heroes,
like letting the soldiers let everybody just hang out
and goof around.
Yeah, that's true.
In a fun time.
Yeah, there's almost no discipline on that.
Go to find that guy's account
and see if it's just him complaining about
like any sort of rank.
Oh, are there other Jeffrey comments?
Yeah, let me look.
Yeah, see if you can find like a few is upset.
I have many thoughts about F Troop.
Larry Storch, still alive.
Wow, you have your chance.
100 years old, I think.
At least try to get cameos from some of these.
I don't think Larry Storch is on cameo.
Well, he should be.
Let's get him on there.
I feel like we gotta talk about the best thing.
Oh, I'm sorry, I passed by the tweet just to say it.
Another time when Alan was throwing a drunk out,
the guy was yelling that his daddy's in the mafia
and he was gonna come back and kill everybody.
Pfft.
You know, Alan was an enemy of the mob.
He took on the big institutions.
It depended on what part of the mob.
I'm sure he was connected to some part of the mob.
Maybe it was a different part of the mob.
Maybe, maybe not.
Maybe I'm wrong, maybe he wasn't.
But anyways, so there's all these great print ads
which we'll try to post.
But the best one, clearly,
I mean, do you wanna do the honors?
I feel like just a reciting.
You know what I'm talking about, right?
Wait a minute.
If you don't have it.
Yeah, you do it.
I think I have it, but I'm not sure exactly
which one you're talking about.
Well, it's the Mother's Day special.
Oh, right, right.
Yeah, you do it, yeah.
Okay, okay.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I got this too.
This is some of the video.
Feel free, Jason.
Oh, no, sorry, I found Jeffrey's account.
Oh, man.
All right, you, Scott, go for it.
I don't understand a lot of these comments.
I think he's commenting on shows well before I was born.
He has bandleader complaints, you don't understand those.
The Dorsey's were lazy.
They used poor batons.
Okay, so Alan Hale advertising
the exciting Mother's Day special at the restaurant
in big old print bigger than anything else in the ad.
Alan Hale wants to mother your mother.
Smaller text.
It's the sort of thing you'd expect of skipper Alan Hale.
Besides, what mother can resist that personal touch,
especially on May 13th.
Alan Hale's lobster barrel,
828 North La Cienega just below Santa Monica Boulevard.
Call this number blah for reservations
and warm the cockles of your mother's heart.
Now cockles is a word my mother used growing up.
Cockles is something I have heard.
So your mom would have wanted her cockles warmed.
Yes, exactly.
I know she was not the biggest
Gilligan's Island fan in the world.
So maybe not by Alan Hale.
Didn't want the personal touch on her cockles.
She liked Batman though, she was a Batman fan.
Well, what's a cockle?
What's an example of using cockle in a sentence?
That's a good question,
I don't actually know the answer to that.
Do you have any guesses to how she would have used cockle?
Heart, warming the cockle of your heart.
That's the phrase she would use.
Oh, Merry Christmas.
This time of year just warms my cockles.
That's right.
Jason, have you ever said cockles?
I must have said cockles at one point in time, Michael.
Yes.
He seems upset that I even interrupted looking up Jeffrey.
No, I just said that you even had to ask.
That's fair.
I'm looking up cockle.
There was a show called Cockles in 1984,
a British television series.
This guy's probably yelling about cockles on MeTV.
Cockles, oh, oh, oh, cockles are ventricles.
Oh.
Literally ventricles, that's what the phrase is.
Do you want them warmed?
Would it help your heart if their ventricles got warmer?
I think you always want your heart to be a bit warm
if it's cold. A little bit,
but maybe not, it seems like warming too much.
But doesn't say like, you don't want them like hot.
Yeah, I don't think so.
Heating up the cockles of your heart.
Well, if you're gonna die,
is that what a defibrillator does is warm your cockles?
I think, no, well, it will warm them
with the jolt of electricity, but.
That's what I'm saying, yeah.
Maybe, I think your, I don't know.
I think your mother's cockles should only be warmed
if she's about to die.
I think they need to be a consistent warm,
a model of warmth. I think a consistent warmth.
You want a jolt of warmth. Yeah, no, basically warm,
but like, let's not get them any warmer.
It concerns me. But did the Grinch,
when the Grinch's heart grew whatever sizes,
was it warmed also because it was growing,
because it felt he felt such like love?
And did the cockles grow or only the heart,
or does the heart, I guess ventricles are in the heart,
so his cockles must have grown.
They had to have grown,
but does your heart heat up when you're working out?
Does it heat up? Your body does.
Your heart rate increases.
Right, so I bet your heart temperature
and your cockle temperature would have to increase
if you're using. If cockles might all get warm
a lot of the day. That's right.
If we're in good shape.
So when Michael Eisner had that heart surgery,
it was, his cockles were being?
His cockles were fucked up for sure.
It was quadruple, so he had to have
his cockles warmed four times.
Right, and Letterman too.
Anybody who's famously has had heart surgery.
Or some of our most famous cockles.
Checking in with Jeffrey on the post pic,
call in what would you watch on TV in 1982?
This is good, this is like a comedy tragedy.
May we see both sides of Jeffrey in this,
because he talks what he likes and what he doesn't like.
He says, facts of life,
give me an ice pick for my eyes and ears.
Okay.
Conversely, Jeffrey has to say, the happy wanderers,
coffee and cabbage rolls, am starting to laugh.
What is that?
Coffee and cabbage rolls?
I don't, I am unfamiliar with the happy wanderers.
I have heard the term before.
Yeah, I think that was a short lived show.
Ice pick for facts of life.
Doesn't care for facts of life,
but also says SCTV best TV comedy.
So. Okay.
So it's pro SCTV.
That's pretty current.
Happy Wanderers,
nationally syndicated travelogue television show,
originally aired on KTLA in the 60s.
Is this a travelogue, I guess?
This is deep stuff.
The cast included Slim and Henrietta Barnard,
Buddy Noonan and Milos Hinshaw,
who was the cinematographer for Mystery Mansion.
So now we're at the point of the episode
where the references even we don't understand.
We're talking about proto Rick Steves.
We're talking about pre.
Huel, Huel, pre Huel.
Yeah.
This is not related, but is related
because we're saying old names.
Do you know Sigourney Weaver was related to an entertainer
that I was not aware of.
And I believe it was her uncle.
Do you guys know what I'm talking about?
I knew she had some sort of relative history.
Dennis Weaver?
No, this man's name was Doodles Weaver.
What's up with Doodles?
Doodles Weaver was an entertainer.
Yeah, Sigourney was his niece.
His brother was Pat and he was an actor,
comedian, singer, musician.
He was on variety shows.
He was on a Spike Jonze track, I believe.
The old musician, Spike Jonze.
Yeah.
And I think he was just like, he was around.
He did a lot of stuff.
His name was Doodles Weaver.
Doodles.
And I was delighted to learn that.
Oh, you like Alien and Avatar, do you?
Well, Sigourney's all right, but not my favorite Weaver.
That's an opinion we can all have now.
Feel free to.
Everyone listening, yeah, have that opinion.
Feel free to clear out the party.
You're uncomfortable with Omicron still.
Have a party, say that, and then everybody will leave.
This episode is probably the most thing Mike
has shown at a party thing.
You wanna know a weird L.A. thing.
You know, like.
That energy, you mean?
Yep, that energy of pulling out your phone and showing.
Do you know the Skipper's restaurant?
The lobster barrel.
It's just, it is.
Yeah, this one is a real simulation
for being somewhere with one of us,
where you're just getting yelled at.
You're getting yelled at facts about.
It was all right.
We were having fun and then they started talking
about Alan Hill's lobster barrel and Doodles Weaver.
I don't know, they're guys you see once every couple months.
They're not bad guys, but.
A little too much.
A bit too much sometimes.
So look, I think this guy's great.
Really happy he wants to mother our mothers
and warm their cockles.
And he warmed so many cockles by signing autographs.
What if he was like Ray Fiennes in Grand Budapest Hotel
and he was just like having sex with every mother,
every older lady that came in there.
Ma'am, I would like to mother you.
And it was, and they were like, I came in here for that.
I came in here to be mothered by you, Mr. Hail J.
I saw the ad.
I will take a crab Newberg to go.
That I believe just sauteed with paprika or cayenne pepper.
A lot of it's just cream, sherry or cognac
and then paprika or cayenne pepper.
Different combinations.
I'd like something a little more than the meal tonight.
Alan, would you Oscar me?
Okay, little buddy.
A little something extra on top.
You knew what he was getting at.
You discipline men so much better
than that lousy Andy Griffith.
The hat stays on.
Discipline me better than Bernie Phife.
You can leave your hat on.
Well, I'd say it got pretty sufficiently weird.
Hey, let me say things on the way out.
You can leave your hat on.
I think you survived Alan Hales lobster barrel
on podcast throughout the Second Gate Celebrary.
But is there any, could we possibly Oscar this place?
Is there any way to make it better than I think it?
This is everything that, you know, so far,
we've only talked about dive.
I was saying, I don't think you feel the Spielberg in it.
You feel nothing but Alan Hales.
Pure Hales.
He's Oscaring all over this place.
The only way it would be better is you showed me
that the whale mouth, like if it was something
that looked like the minnow or something,
the minnow of the ship from Gilligan's Island, of course,
or that it had more like tiki,
like whatever you would call like their makeshift
living situation on Gilligan's Island.
Yeah.
This was a dang submarine restaurant.
Yes, that would have been-
This is what should have done it.
This is what deserves it.
Even something just-
There's half ideas here.
You could fill, a dive would still be around
if Alan was-
Just more nautical.
You can't tell completely,
but there's some footage of it on YouTube.
And just see a more nautical theming for sure
would have been great.
Shade the building like a crab trap,
like a lobster trap.
Sure, or a big barrel.
Or a big barrel.
Even just a big barrel simple enough.
That's really the only, like what else would you want
other than just like, I don't know,
Bob Denver being there too, maybe.
Yeah.
But honestly, it's better that it's just Alan, you know?
It's only, do you like Gilligan's Island?
Yeah.
Well, I've got a place where just the Skipper is.
And I'm not saying, Bob should have had his own place.
They all should have had separate restaurants, obviously.
We're talking about Caesar Romero.
It's like every Batman villain
should have had their own place.
Gorshians.
Oh, A-Head writes itself.
I'm saying, but the actor,
Vincent Price should have had a place.
All our waiters are dressed the same,
so they look like the goons.
It's like there's a video of Frank Gorshin
I'm sure I've talked about on the show before.
He's on Dean Martin Variety Show, I think.
And he's singing his hit single, The Riddler.
But he's not dressed as The Riddler,
but the like dancer ladies are.
Oh, okay.
They're dressed in like the question mark stuff.
And he's in just like a suit.
But he's dancing and doing the like Riddler laugh
and stuff in between singing.
And yeah, imagine every Batman,
every Otto Preminger should have had a restaurant.
All three Catwomen, Julie Newmar,
Lee Merriwether, Anne Earthquit.
That's Catwoman Row on Cassie Winnigan.
Catwoman Row on, that's a sub part of the celebrity area.
You didn't know all three Catwomen.
One restaurant should be drinks,
one should be appetizers, and one should be entrees.
So then you just go down the line.
I have a pitch for that.
Anne Harriet should have had her own restaurant.
Yeah.
Bob Denver's Dinner Diner.
That's a pretty funny name.
That's a pretty good name.
Yeah, that's good.
You know what, let's,
maybe we're gonna do more of these,
but is there an ultimate,
I ultimate like, okay, let's see,
let's add parameters of this.
And let's ask the audience about this as well.
Let's have a cutoff for when the actor's like famous TV show
was off the air.
So like, let's say it had to be off by like 1970.
That's pretty early.
1975, you think?
I don't know.
You think, well, maybe we,
people are like a lot of eighties kids.
You know what, I don't know.
Cutoff, it's in 79, I'll say.
All right, great.
79 is a cutoff.
That's generous, I believe.
So what is the ultimate actor?
Jason, it could be Frawley, it could be,
like what would you have wanted
out of this type of an establishment?
If you go back in time and also have,
like manifested one of your favorite old.
The cutoff is hard,
cause like I feel like a Peter Falk restaurant is,
but he played Colombo well into the nineties
on TV movies and stuff.
Okay, well, all right.
That's if they started.
All right, I'll give you Falk if you want,
but I don't think the listener should be allowed to pick
somebody who went into the past.
Is this a game for the listener?
Yeah, no.
They all have to agree,
and it can't be until that show has to be done and canceled.
It's too hard though,
because if I were gonna pick Fred Gwynn,
who played Herman Munster,
he reprised the role later.
After 79 did he?
Oh yeah, wasn't there one 80s one?
There was an 80s Munster revival.
Get rid of the cutoff, I said.
Fine, I'm getting rid of the cutoff.
Or open up revivals.
But they had to start with the role before 1979.
Okay.
How about that?
Like their big famous role had to start before 1979.
My answer is Paul Lin.
Mm-hmm.
There had to be like,
I would have wanted a Paul Lin restaurant.
It could have been like called Uncle Arthur's,
which is his character on Bewitched.
Uncle Arthur's, let's say he sold like stew or something,
like boiling like a stew cauldron.
You have to put on the ascot instead of a bib.
And what you would have to change is,
because what I like would happen with some of these guys too,
like George Lindsay, who played Goober on Andy Griffith.
He then started calling himself George Goober Lindsay.
Just so you remember, he played Goober on Andy Griffith,
which is why some of the signs say Skipper Allen Hale Jr.
Just to remind you that this guy played the Skipper.
That covers everything.
It reminds you of his father.
Yes.
The junior in there, it reminds you of him.
And then it reminds you of the Skipper, yeah.
So call it like Paul Uncle Arthur Lin's like stew cauldron.
And it's like a little spooky too,
because it's an ode to that Halloween special he did.
And then he would always be there.
There's also a Paul Lin Castle Dracula recording
where he like, I don't know what it's from,
but he's just like,
Ressi, Igor, what are you?
I'm Count Dracula.
Like it's on Spotify, I don't know what it's from,
but like, so he had some Halloween stuff too.
So I feel like that would be my ultimate,
the Paul Lin's stew cauldron.
Paul Lin, Paul Uncle Arthur Lin's stew cauldron.
I mean, that's incredible.
I don't know how to top that.
I would like if, and I don't know his name off hand,
but whoever played Sam the Butcher on the Brady Bunch.
Oh yeah, what does that guy do?
Make him open the butcher shop.
He's gotta do it.
And he's gotta be cutting the meat
and maybe he doesn't do it so good.
Maybe some of the chunks are too big.
Maybe people get hurt sometimes during the day.
But that's part of the fun.
You don't know what's gonna happen.
Alan Melvin is his name.
Okay.
Sam the Butcher Melvin's House of Brady Meat.
All right, that's great.
Yeah, that's great.
House of Brady Meat, fantastic.
And if it's Falk, then is like,
if you had to name, I don't know Colombo well enough,
but well, Ville Colombo, Colombo's House of Ville Colombo.
I mean, yeah, you could probably take the entree.
Or like precinct.
His precinct of Ville Colombo.
I was trying to think of a Jack Benny restaurant
then I thought of something better.
Tennessee Ernie Ford's 16 Tons of Fun.
And I think maybe that's like a kid's like birthday part,
like a Chuck E. Cheese kind of like,
or it's like a Uncle Mo's Family Feedback.
It's like a TGI frat with a lot of, you know,
chintzy stuff on them.
Maybe it's like, oh, maybe it's like a honky ton,
like a Roadhouse or something,
like a Texas Roadhouse got a lot of license plates
on the walls, like a lot of barbecue and stuff.
This is also-
I got another, I just got another one.
What about Randy Chucco Runyon's Hot Dog Sack?
You remember his name?
Randy Runyon is Chucco, he plays Chuckle the Clown.
Randy Runyon.
I didn't look it up either.
Yeah, you didn't, God.
Yeah, what's that thingy bib juice?
Bib juice, yeah, you serve bib juice there.
Which is an industry standard.
It stands for, oh God, what does it stand for?
Something in a bag?
We looked it up.
I'm gonna look this up, yeah, it's like a-
All right, well you get Randy Chucco Runyon's Juicy Bib.
Yeah, you're draped with a bib.
Oh, beverage in a bag, I believe.
So it's like if you, like a soda fountain
or like the big like milk dispensers
and like dining hall and stuff.
It's usually like a bag and like a crate
that you like feed into it and then cut the dispenser hose
and then feed the hose out.
That's how those machines work often.
Okay, so that's why, so bib juice is a good one.
Bib juice, yeah.
Because I've sure been picturing that Chucco
with a murder newborns and then like squeeze
whatever was left into a juice and makes people drink it.
Bag in a box, bag in a box, I'm sorry, I got it wrong.
Bag in a box.
I've got, you know what, I wanna just a real vague tease
just for you two too, but I have an idea for Chucco
but that's all I'll say.
Well now let's really get out of this episode.
Now you survived.
Bug has the ride, the second gate.
And again, with this Zorn reveal that you're talking about.
Yeah, we're Zorns.
Yeah, the other reveal is like,
you like, the listener might have been thinking
at some point, yeah, well there's such like kids
who are the 80s, 90s and they love deep references.
No, no, no, we've been wanting apparently
to go back to the fucking 20s.
That's what it's been, we're 100 years old at this point.
Pre seat belts, keep going back.
Pre that Tylenol scare in the 80s, keep going, keep going.
Preludes, preludes.
Preludes, not a prelude, preludes.
No, preludes, like Simpson's joke.
Well, look, if you want more of this,
if you want more of this,
we have only just begun the celebrity dive.
It's the second gate all month is this kind of thing.
You're gonna be swimming in mother sauce all month long.
You're gonna be mothered and be covered in mother sauce.
That's our promise to you for the rest of the month
here on the second gate.
I forgot to say this too about Alan Hale's father.
He is credited with inventing and holding the patent to
and or financing the creation of auto brakes,
handheld fire extinguishers, greaseless potato chips
and the folding theater seat.
No, all of that.
Alan Hale senior, that's what it says.
There's no way.
That's what it says online.
That's Alan Hale's father who was a big inventor.
He's, Alan Junior's getting drunk
and telling tales out of school.
I don't think Alan Junior got any of that money
because I saw a picture of like,
here's his house in Hollywood.
Like, and he was a pretty modest one story.
No, it was a beautiful house,
but it was a modest, respectable one story home.
So I'm saying like Alan Hale did not get like insane.
Inventor money?
Inventor money, air money.
I don't know.
Maybe that was one of his houses.
Oh, maybe it could have been.
Maybe he put it on the boats for the travel company.
He maybe invested too much money in both businesses
and lost all of it.
That's bullshit.
He probably lived in a stupid one story house.
He should have lived in a big lobster.
Missing opportunity.
Yeah.
Well, if we have a time machine, we'll go tell him.
And we'll be back on the main feed this week
to warm you or your mother's cockles.
Guaranteed.