Forever!
Dog!
Warning, the following podcast contains
sad French burgers
lightning McQueen's digestive system
face fire
and an attraction that strains relationships
that attraction being Disneyland Paris's
Armageddon, Les Effets Spatiaux
We drill into this massive
asteroid of a topic
with a returning Carly Weisel
on today's podcast
The Ride
Intro Music
Welcome to Podcast The Ride
the theme park podcast where because of
today's attraction we say go ahead
and close your eyes
go ahead and fall asleep
because we assure you, you won't miss a
thing. My name is Mike Carlson
joining me as always Jason
Sheridan. Hi.
Hi.
I'm just soaking that all in
because I was going to respond to whatever
you were saying with ah the
French, the French theme parks
have always been celebrated for their
excellence.
There is a certain attraction
that is very terrible.
Walt Disney Studios Park has always
knows a thing or two about excellence.
Well we should, I really should have worked on a
French accent for this. But Scott Garner
do you have a French accent? Do you have?
Well I did look up how to pronounce
the attraction
which if this is the place
for that. Well and there's
another French pronunciation that might
come into play later but today we
are talking about Armageddon
Les Effets Spatiaux
There we go. So I wanted to get
that right. I'm sure it was still wrong in some way.
Wait, with less?
I probably said less didn't I?
You said less, yes.
No that's completely correct.
Effets Spatiaux.
Okay so I, alright. I did screw it up.
That's not the part I thought I would.
12 words from high school French. I'm sure I've repeated them on the show before.
I know
an Orangina, the Orangina
drink. That counts?
Oh yeah, yes of course.
It's a French drink.
I know, it's hard to say what time
is it. Ask what time it is.
Kelerateel? That's how, what time is it?
And you need to say that
as American as possible.
Kelerateel?
Like an American nerd
would say it is how I'm saying it.
Kelerateel!
That's the
did I do that pronunciation.
Yeah, so we'll be doing
I don't know, there's not that much French stuff
I guess. Well if we talk about Disneyland Paris
I guess there is but
specifically like French stuff.
Well it is where we are today.
We are talking, but then this one probably requires
explanation from the ground up
that at the Walt Disney
Studios park
in Paris, that for a long time
there was an attraction based on Armageddon
and we'll explain why this
came up recently on Twitter
with our guest today who I'm so happy
is returning. I believe your fifth
podcast The Ride appearance.
Long overdue. I think so.
I got you to punch car. Welcome to five.
We got something to give you
on your sixth. Five
timers club. I know. Five timers club.
This is much more fun than doing
SNL I'm sure. Yeah.
For sure. I think you're in this breezy
garage. For our podcast, very amusing
it's Carly Weisel. Hi. Hello, hi!
I am both thrilled
and mildly upset that we have to
discuss this attraction.
At length. Sorry
to everyone listening. It's
Oh boy. We're really going to polish
a turd here. It's going to make
us as cantankerous as a late in
life drunk horse and wells trying to
read commercial copy.
Yeah, you're absolutely
right. Well, yeah, you walked in. I mean, we've
been trying to figure out the right thing to have you and did we
find it? I don't know. Maybe it's not it.
There's a horrible reason to have you. Who is
this? I feel like I come on here a lot
and I'm yelling about things and some people
agree and some people don't. Sometimes in this very
room or garage. And this
is something that I don't believe I've ever
heard a single person stan.
I don't know anybody who's like
that thing was cool.
Well, unless
I don't know. Let's do the check.
Is there a secret? Is there a hidden
stan in this room?
In the room? In today's attraction, yeah.
I've got a surprise. Oh no.
No, I'm just kidding. This
one sucks.
I'm pretty forgiving.
I try to find like, well, but I did like
this. I there's
one little odd moment where I was
like, well, that's an interesting
there's a lot of interesting stuff.
I think it's the most forgiving word you
could use. It's all interesting.
I'd say confusing is the more frank way
of putting it. Oh, absolutely.
Literally, because even going back and watching
it, I couldn't view the translation
screen in portions of it
and did not know what they were saying. Oh, yeah.
I mean, the translation screen alone is
very, very much your
choice. A lot of choices
made, a lot of very confusing choices.
Even the premise, I was like, that can't be
what this it is. What? OK, that
is what they're setting us up for. Got it.
Pretty baffling. I imagine it was
even like videos are
tough to parse, but you did do this in person
at one point in time. Oh, yeah.
And I will never live it down
because I dragged my
husband to Disneyland Paris. It was my first
visit there. I think it was 2016.
So we took a full day
to go to the parks, which he was already
not on board with. And we
were like Armageddon, first ride we saw
at Walt Disney Studios. Let's give it
a shot. Started there.
And then it kept waiting for the ride to
start. And then we exited.
Yeah. Oh, totally.
Yes. Well, especially
now. And we'll explain what it all
is. But this is it is
an attraction where you're in a space
transport vehicle,
essentially. And there's stuff going on.
You see space through the screens.
And that is something that now
in several cases qualifies
as a pre-show, a kind
of exciting pre-show in both
Galaxy's Edge and the Star Cruiser
experience. But yeah,
you might watch this and go, okay,
so now the door's open and the ride starts.
No, no, no.
This was not a different situation in the early
2000s. This sufficed
for them. Yeah. And this is
this park is was made because
of a contractual obligation.
Essentially, the whole park was that they had
made a promise to Paris,
to the people of France, to the French
government. And that they what is this deal
where they had to give up the
land if they didn't fill
it with a park. Some
yeah. Perhaps they should
have. Yeah, maybe if
you don't have a good idea, although there's
also the flip side, because I genuinely
was thinking should they just not
have. But now they have all these grand
plans and I don't know how they're progressing,
but that kind of makes you think, well, maybe
you just put your foot in the door,
get a half park or
less on the table and
then down the road you end up because this is
going to be the home of Galaxy's Edge and
some frozen stuff. And what's the other
Marvel? Avengers Campus. Oh yeah, Avengers Campus,
which is replacing what we're
talking about. Do you
does that make sense? Like maybe it is
good that they. I mean,
I went in November.
That's the last time I was there. It's a Disneyland Paris
and it's just I mean, it was a
dirt pile because so
much of the park, you know, to build all those
lands, they just had to raise
so much. Yeah, I went in
and I walked around and went, oh, that's that's it
now. That's it. There is nothing here
because it's all under construction. Were they
using the vehicle, the armadillo
to raise the ground
up just out
in front. They used to be out in front, I should
say the vehicle from Armageddon. Mike,
why did you even say vehicle? We all know what
the armadillo Armageddon
Armadillo Armadillo
and I assume we all like that's what Harry Stamp
and the crew like bear
and bear. Michael Clark. All the characters
we know. Yeah.
I yeah. And we and we of course
also all know that this is a Disney movie.
We I think we all we see the logo
for Armageddon and we all think
Disney straight to that.
It's definitely not just a it is a
they happen to own it. It's a late 90s
touchstone movie.
OK, it's a touchstone. All right. How much longer
did Touchstone go for? I feel I don't
I don't feel like it was long for this world
in the late 90s. I kind of didn't think about Touchstone
falling apart. I don't know when that
I feel like they just retired the brand a few
years later. Yeah, I guess so. Or just
rolled into something else. Maybe they rolled
it into Miramax because they bought Miramax
later in the 90s. I like Touchstone.
I like seeing that little like circle go by
in the bar and when
you say I like Touchstone, you mean I like the logo
I like the logo. That would happen before the movie.
I have a question for you. Does the
what brings you more joy the Touchstone logo
or this attraction?
Oh, the logo. The logo for sure. Yeah, yeah. All it's got
to do is fill that three seconds and then like
I don't remember what anything to Touchstone
was adventures in babysitting Touchstone
potentially. Maybe. Something I like
is Touchstone. So so like
it is the Touchstone logo is a pre-show
for something good as opposed to this
attraction. Is there something Spielberg-y?
Yes. Yeah. Probably.
God, it's killing me. What is it? Why can't I name?
I guess I guess Touchstone's not that
great of a brand if I can't think
of one. But the only I like all
these logos too, but the only thing I remember as a
kid was that I knew if it was New Line
Cinema, there was a good chance like the Ninja Turtles
were coming after that.
I remember that like they played a
tape and I would be like New Line Cinema. That's
the company that makes Ninja Turtles.
Oh, they made Lincoln apparently.
So a recent Spielberg-ish.
So it went longer than I thought. Wild
Hogs, of course. Of course.
Of course. I think Nightmare Before Christmas
and Roger Rabbit released
Undertowd Stone. Oh, yeah. Pretty woman.
Was Old Dogs?
The Robin
Williams John Travolta movie that I get confused
with Wild Hogs? That I don't know.
And which one killed the other, the sequel
to the other? Old Dogs made
there be no Wild Hogs too.
I think. Oh, okay. I believe
so. And then Old Dogs
has the Travolta Every
Little Step music video with his daughter.
I think so. Yeah. Okay.
Which if you've never seen it, I highly recommend it.
Oh, yeah, boy. Check it out. Do you want
to guess at the
highest grossing touchstone film?
I see I have it in front of me. Somebody
else. Mike Carley. I would like to not guess.
No. Okay. I would like
for it to be Pretty Woman, but Pretty
Woman comes in at number five. Number one is
Signs. Interesting.
Signs.
Armageddon and Pearl
Harbor two and three.
So kind of the ones that showed
up in the theme parks, I feel like,
because Pearl Harbor
was kind of incorporated into the
pre-show stuff at the studio tour and MGM
studios. It's in this a little in
the pre-show of this.
Before we dive
into the attraction a little more, I am like
first of all, one
thing is this attraction is opened
20 years ago this week.
So that makes it appropriate here to talk about
as did this entire park,
the studios park next to Disneyland
Paris proper, which is almost 30 years
old. Carley, you've been in the recent
past and I feel like it seems like your experiences
were pretty good.
Yeah. Yeah. You're a fan
recently. I would say that pandemic
era Disneyland Paris
is different. It's a different
because if we're comparing everything on
even playing field, like we got the Tokyo
parks in here, we
can't do that anymore. You literally can't
go to Tokyo. I don't even know how you would get into
Hong Kong or Shanghai. There's not a chance.
I don't know. I haven't looked into this at all.
So much of my not thinking. You can't
casually. I mean, I went to China
December 2019.
Like basically the last
plane out didn't realize it and you
still have to go to the Chinese consulate
to get a visa to go into
China. Just to go at all. Just to go.
So it wasn't easy to
visit in the first place. Now not a chance.
So when you're looking at it, you're kind of like
we got Florida, we got California, we got Paris.
Paris is the only like spice in the mix
that we got. It's the only fun foreign one.
Oh, sure. Yeah. Yeah. I'm like the hotels
are enough for you, but there's no rides
at the hotels. So
I don't know if this will be the case as this episode
comes out. But when I started reading about this
attraction, Hong Kong was closed.
The Hong Kong park was closed because they
had done. Oh, like this
week essentially. Yeah.
A few days ago. A few days
was closed. Shanghai, I think
partially closed. Maybe the hotels
and stores and the shopping area
open. Okay.
Oh, rides are down. That weird.
We had for a little bit. Interesting. Okay.
Okay. So this is like, yeah,
if you want something that's not the norm and you go
to these places a lot. Yeah. So
it really shook it up. Because usually it's like
look at all these foreign options. And now it's
Paris or nothing. And
Paris, I'm someone who took the pandemic
very seriously. And so for
me, I felt much safer being in Paris
because there was a vaccine check that was required
of everyone. Everyone was required to wear masks
outdoors and indoors.
Which when I went, I went twice
last year, which sounds
ridiculous.
But I was like, I'm getting it back.
I went over the summer and I went in
November. I think I made it go on like late September,
November. So. In both areas, like we're
still a little dicey. You know,
summer got okay for a second. Well in France, it was
great. Wow, wow. Yeah. Because they,
I mean, they masked 100%.
I remember going in a department store, which is usually
a little loosey goosey. And every single
person was wearing a mask. Wow.
So like going to the park was nice because you
could actually absorb the theming without
even thinking about what was happening. Geez.
Oh, that's great. Yeah. So it painted Paris
in this different light. But then
again, I found myself screaming at someone
in my family because I was so hungry because there was
no food. That was my,
because I've spoken ill of
Paris a lot. I'm the only one of
the three of us who's done it.
And there were things that I liked about it
and that I will praise
down the road. But the
big obstacle was the food thing.
And we did a whole episode about that, the
village there, city walk,
and Disney, which is, I found miserable,
just crushingly miserable.
Did you, did you find any way around?
There's like not even, no sector keeper
would be willing to exist.
They'd be like, get me the fuck out of here.
Somebody, I'm transferring
out of this. Somebody else take this assignment.
Yeah, it's pretty
grim. Did you find any ways around?
Are there any weird secret,
if you want to survive it in a culinary
sense? Yes.
And I found out about it too late, but I realized
the best thing to do is to completely
exit property and go
into the train station.
Because the train station has
like, what is it, like,
Pré-de-manger or whatever those things are called.
Like a little sandwich shop.
You find yourself in a position going,
it's like, oh, thank God, a Pré.
Nice. Yes. Literally
yes. Something with standards.
I mean, I had,
I mean, this is off topic, but I had
maybe the worst Disney meal I've ever had
in my entire life at the
Disney's Hotel New York
Art of Marvel. Really?
Oh, wow. My worst one also,
there, I was wondering if you were going to head for
California Grill, which it's
insane, they call it the same thing. It's a very
stuffy restaurant in the Disneyland
Hotel proper. Awful, awful,
inedible food for so much money.
Yeah.
And we waited forever. Miserable,
miserable experience. What was up with this place?
So everything else I ate was fine,
edible. Like, the line is edible.
I had a nice dinner at the
Manhattan restaurant where you
sit underneath a chandelier that looks like
Asgard, which was very fun.
So like, I had a great meal there,
but the downtown restaurant
was all, it was buffet
style, but it was COVID, so they brought plates
of it to your table.
And so you didn't know what anything looked like, and you were just kind of out here
taking a guess, and everything was themed
to different downtown areas in Manhattan,
so there was quote unquote
dim sum, and there were
like different cuisines from different places
that have different, you know, like Little Italy and things
like that. And I
honestly don't, I don't know if I
actually consumed any food at the meal.
You didn't pick anything.
It was so bad that my mom
asked for an allergy meal,
which was a frozen microwave meal
that took 20 minutes to arrive.
Oh my god. Because she has a specific
diet for her health, but even still was like
I can't eat this.
You've made me feel better.
I've started to wonder, like, where my wife and I were,
was I being a baby? Absolutely not.
Yeah, it is bad. It's really bad there.
Yeah, yeah. And you're just, you're walking
around that mall, just like which,
what place do I get inedible
ribs from? Where am I, like,
I just pick your poison. There's nothing
that seemed like, I know I'm not getting
something good. It's just what, what can I
survive with? Yeah.
This kind of sounds like my parents'
experience of, like,
the dining options at Disney World
in, like, 1990.
Exactly. Alright, I guess I'll
eat another slice of pizza. Like,
I guess I'll have another hamburger.
Like, you know. Yeah, which it doesn't,
it is not like that anymore.
That's been a huge change
in, especially Disney,
but I'd say Universal to some extent.
Universal seemingly upping their food
game in Orlando the last few years.
A friend of mine just posted a photo of ramen
that she got, and I think
Islands of Adventure. What? Ramen.
Wingservice Ramen. Where?
There's CityWalk has a bun
stand serving fusion, like
bao buns. I did, that's not
very good, but it's a nice idea.
Nice, yeah.
We applaud the effort. Thank you for trying.
Thank you. Not, well, I ate worse things
at Disney Paris, so it's okay.
The food in the park is
better if it's open. If the food
is open, then you're good.
But everything's closed. Everything's closed.
So that hasn't changed, because
I was there in 2014
and there was nothing related to pandemic
then, so, like, what, why,
why is it always like this? What's
up with this place? Honest to God, I have no idea,
and this time I was like, I'm gonna go prepare it.
Like, I'm gonna beat the system, and
I made table service reservations
in the park during the day, and so
we ate, and the food wasn't
that bad. We went to kind of a Moroccan
restaurant, which was shockingly
good, or edible.
But the other,
I mean, it's a crap shoot. I
have been four times
now, and the other two times I went,
I had at least one meal that was
pick and mix candy.
To the point. Oh, so like how Mike
and I eat regularly. Oh, yes, yes, yes.
They call that cereal around here. Yeah, I
like waddled in this time like, I know where I'm getting
my lunch at, and I went, and
all of it is gone.
Just, because they're like, pandemic, all
of the candy is gone. Oh, no.
Wow. Wow. That's like play
testing for their kind
of domestic COVID cutbacks
in dining that seems
to be, the wave seems
to be slowly rolling back.
Like things slowly
opening up more here in America.
You would think, like you would think that
would be a thing, because for a
famously maligned
park, you would think that would be a draw,
at least for the older people that were
skeptical of the park in general, like, oh, well,
it does have some nice places to eat.
Like, you would think that might have been a good draw,
but I guess they never considered
it. I don't know. I've even
gone to Walt's, which is like their,
it's not Club 33, but it's their like finest
dining restaurant in the park, and you're
on the second floor of Main Street, and it's very
beautiful, and I think I spent
over $60 on a burger.
Oh my god. And they gave me
nine fries.
Is it exclusive? It is. No.
Okay. So you can just make a reservation.
Well, to people who love wasting money.
Yeah,
that's what, it's like so
crazily more expensive
than fine dining in
the great city, 20
minutes away. Absolutely. But this time,
so the last trip we went on in November,
we went to a sandwich place,
and we got little baguette sandwiches
from this little man who made like
slapped butter on the bread and then put
on a bunch of meat, and I carried them in a brown
bag to the park, and I ate them on a bench,
and it was heaven.
Wow. Nice. So that's the move.
Just bringing in from entirely, it cannot
be Disney controlled.
They have like just whittled
the taste out of anything. You need off-land
food. Yeah, yeah.
Um,
well, that's nuts. Did you find stuff
to like about, that's I guess a question
because I, you know,
like the bones of that,
of the Magic Kingdom style
park I think are wonderful, but then
there's that food
and lack of staffing drawback,
and then Paris is all,
I'm sorry, the Studios Park is a whole mess,
but it's improved. How's
it feeling in 2021?
Were you charmed by anything
about the place? Yeah, it definitely feels on the up
and up. When I've been before, it's like, oh,
right, this is the one the company is embarrassed
about. Like you forget about it. Yeah. But
they're just sinking so much money into
Walt Disney Studios Park that it
feels like, like there's more to come,
and it felt very
optimistic. Okay.
And I also had a really nice time. Like I really
appreciated some of the things they do differently,
like just the way it's laid out.
I got lost at one point
because the left side
of the park is just, who knows,
just all over the place. You just keep walking and walking
and you like never reach anything.
And then they had like such good character
meet and greets and fun
costumes. And I went to
some Mexican restaurant and I got a margarita
in Disneyland,
which was very fun. Sure. Oh, you're talking
in the main, oh, interesting. Yeah, like in
Disneyland. Right, yes. That was
where my enthusiasm went, where I was getting a
beer in the saloon in Frontierland.
Like that feels pretty good.
So that's a, yeah, yeah, that's a genuine...
It was fun. I had a good time. I think once they build
out the other half and they have something new, like
the Frozen attraction, stuff that we don't
have in America, I think it'll be,
I think it's, I mean, I think it's gonna come around.
It's on the way. Can you get a
beer in Tokyo in the main park?
Or no?
Don't think so. I'm sure we've all talked about this and I know
the answer somewhere. I don't know. It's been so... I can't remember.
I only recall doing it in Disney
Sea. How many parks, how many
Magic Kingdoms can you drink and make Walt's
skeleton cry?
That's my question really. Is it only, is it
just Florida and Paris?
They're sinning. They're sinners.
His old bones
tear up still in the ground.
Carly, let me ask you, cause I
had a very hard time finding the current
answer to this question. Can you still
smoke within the parks in
Disneyland Paris? Because I mean,
I wrote down a joke about the
French smoking inside the
waiting area for Armageddon. Like
you can hear their disinterest
and they're dangling cigarettes. And I was like,
what is the smoking policy in France?
And as of 2017,
I found an article just
labeled Disneyland Paris to
enforce use of designated
smoking areas. So they had smoking
areas and they were not
but we were still just lighting
up everywhere as of a few years
ago. I don't know if COVID has changed
that. I don't smoke.
I don't want to smoke. I've maybe had
like one cigarette in my life, but I would smoke
a cigarette on Pirates of the Caribbean
in any park and be thrilled.
Yeah, that's cool. I will
drive down right now to Anaheim
and smoke a cigarette on Pirates
and it will be
one of the best experiences of my life.
I didn't see as much smoking. I don't know
if the masks were a deterrent cause
they were required outdoors both times I was there.
But I do remember
the time I went before that, which was a few
years ago. I mean, I believe the trash
cans still have ashtrays on top.
Right. So you're not like, they're not really
saying no if you're
just laying out everything
you might need to smoke wherever you'd
like. Yeah, there were some trip advisor
reviews too of what seemed like
Americans or British going like
I was in line for something and someone
just started smoking in the queue
next to me.
I'm like, uh huh. Yeah, that
sounds right. I'm kind of glad they didn't cause they
had all those partitions, which I feel I could
have very easily caught fire.
Like in a Fantasyland switchback.
Yeah, yeah.
I didn't even think about it.
Such a hazard. But
yeah, I mean, people still be smoking.
But not to the comical
extent I once witnessed.
Not to the Looney Tunes
level. Smoking a pack on a ride.
Five at once in Bugs Buddies mouth.
Turning dark green. Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Snooty laughter. There wasn't a lot of snooty
laughter with cigarettes. They only light
up when the national anthem starts to play.
That's their version of putting their hand on their
heart.
Here's the Studios Paris
question. Cause there's something I've thought
about proposing an episode on this and I don't
know if there's enough there or if people want to hear it.
But I'm really intrigued by this.
So one of the weird things about the Studios
Park is that
opening
day attractions. Armageddon is one and
another one is the Studio
Backlot Tour.
Common thing, you know,
at Universal Hollywood and the Florida Studio
parks that opened where you go take a tour
of the studio, the working studio.
This was never a studio.
Nothing has ever been filmed here
other than one weird thing I found,
which I'll talk about at the end. But
so you're touring a non-existent
backlot and this has always been
a weird why is this there? We didn't even
do it. Like we knew we'd already experienced
enough misery. Like we know what this is going to be.
But they changed
it. Now it's something called Cars
Road Trip.
And it's still OK for people who know the
Disney World Tour
that culminates in a thing called
Catastrophe Canyon where you go into kind
of a Red Rock Canyon. You experience
a big disaster scene and then see
how it was faked and how they did it behind
the facades. But it's
explosions and a gas truck and all
this stuff. And they had that.
But now they've made that
part of a Cars
thing where it seems
like it's all they've done is put a big
smiling mouth on the gas
truck. That's right.
And in the concept art too, the big
Mack truck is like on fire
and smiling.
It's a
depiction of that this is fine
dog on Twitter.
It's a template of that.
Was this weird thing going?
Did you get to experience this?
Yes, I did wait in line for this. Oh boy.
Oh great. I did wait in like a 25
minute line.
Wow. What can you tell us?
I mean I needed to know.
There's a loose
narrative which I have to like
I have to applaud them for.
For them figuring out a way to make this thing
Cars themed. Yeah. But
it was very loose.
Like it wasn't very
compelling. But I'll tell
you I went with my mom and she had a
great time. Oh that's cool. She was
delighted by it. Okay. That's something.
So you know all that stuff
happening in Catastrophe Canyon doesn't
quite make sense.
In the cars road trip
purview. But what's happening
before that? Yeah that's my question. I think
I watched a video in this there's like narration
or do you get videos on like custom
videos or no?
I was severely under
caffeinated when I did it. But I
do remember that I think there
was audio and I think they were
basically like we're going on a road trip to different
stops. And so I think
Catastrophe Canyon was like a sightseeing
destination. Oh god.
Where everything explodes.
What was it before? Like would they be like
they just say a name like empty nest was filmed
here. Was that the lie? Like was that how it
worked before? I don't really
know. I know that the big center
piece was a bunch of sets from
another I want to say a touchstone
movie called Rain of Fire.
Okay. I do remember this
now. Yeah Matthew McConaughey and the
Dragons in London. Is that right?
Oh yeah it's a re-creation of London.
I didn't know Matthew McConaughey. I always knew
Christian Bale. He got a crazy beard and a
shaved head. So they would lie
about Rain of Fire having shot there?
Yes. They did have the sets but
they just plopped them in this French
field. Okay. So it was not
but it was the real things from a movie
that people didn't really see or like.
That was a
late late summer
2001-2002
release. I just remember
like getting ready to like go
back to school. And
but seeing so they put all the
marketing. There was no
no other movies like coming out
seemingly. And so all the commercials
were like and you gotta check out
Rain of Fire folks.
I have zero. I can't picture a poster.
I don't know anything about
and you're like well I'm going back to school. Everybody's
gonna be talking about Rain of Fire.
I'm not gonna make any friends this year
if I don't. My media diet
was much different from yours growing
up. I mean I was a
for a few years there I was in Axis
Hollywood every night kind of.
Whoa.
Not ET.
Not entertainment tonight.
Somebody had a crush on Nancy. He was very discerning.
No.
I like the electronic
charisma of Pat O'Brien.
Oh yeah were you
what happened when the tapes came out?
I was buried as one in
Pat. All the Axis Hollywood
hosts have tapes.
Push head tapes. Oh yeah you're right.
Everybody's gotching.
I don't remember what the Pat O'Brien
tapes was. Bad right?
Well it was just he was revealing
some fetishes. And there was some
explicit language. So it's available
online if you want. I won't repeat
anything.
I'm not gonna lead you there. Not a thing I think about
a lot. I'm just saying that I have
some recollection of what it is.
He didn't daunt on me to just get an entertainment
weekly subscription. Like it didn't
daunt on me that that would have been. I was an entertainment
weekly kid. Oh me too.
Oh yeah. Oh and what is
Owen Gleiberman think?
We were very invested in old
Gleiberman's tapes. We seemed. What were you
doing that was not this?
I think honestly like sneaking candy.
Stealing?
I was reading Jane Magazine.
The best women's magazine
that's ever existed. That was my only
career goal and they went out of business the year
before I could get an internship. Oh really?
Yeah. Whoa. So all
I do now is just me grasping at straws
because Jane Magazine no longer exists.
You're trying to have a Jane
esque vibe in whatever
venue. I mean I had one career goal
and it went out the window and I'm just
seeing what happened since then. Can you?
That was started by someone
notable right? Didn't it? Yes.
Oh why am I blanking out her name?
I know this.
Good gotcha question.
Was her name Jane?
Jane Pratt? Yes. Who's Jane Pratt?
I know that name. I don't remember what Jane Pratt was about. Yes and then she had
XOJane.com which was like a
website version of it but it was recent
and it wasn't the same.
Can you reboot it? Is she alive?
Yeah but
I mean not to. Can you get the IP?
I'm sure a venture capital firm
that probably owns the IP
would love to partner with you. Seriously.
I mean magazines are not a sustainable
form of income
because like print media plus
advertising not great but
ideally if they rebooted it
I would run the other direction
from theme parks.
So you would have banned theme parks completely?
If Jane Magazine came back?
You would set the ride
on fire you were on and run
Oh yeah I would extinguish my cigarette
on the side of the boat and then
just pounce.
Well if you put it out there have you put it out
there publicly that you're willing you want to reboot
this? No because as someone
currently in the publishing industry I
understand why it's not rebooted. It's not the
train you want to jump on.
Yeah.
Maybe you can reboot her talk
show. She had a talk show on Fox.
Oh wow really? And she was the founder of
Sassy Magazine. Yeah Sassy was
OG Jane Magazine. Oh okay.
Wow. Sassy was cool too.
I just know that sketch that Hartman's
that might be one of the that's the top ten for me.
Which one was that again?
I don't know he's the editor of Sassy Magazine.
Is that one that he hosted? Sassy's Sassy
Sassy S Boys.
Where he draws a little map of
the SS Sassy went to Sassy
Island and I won't recap
this full.
Wow. Well we've all said the
magazines we liked. Yeah
you're learning so much about us
every week. I
well I'm really excited to hear about
Cars Road Trip. I'm glad
it was at least passed a mom approval test.
There was this oh god I have
to mention this there was this like food truck
but also I don't know to get real
heady with it I don't know where the food truck landed in
the vehicle
world of cars like I don't know if this food
truck was a car who was like serving human
food out of its car self. I'm not sure
I didn't really think about it too existential
but it did have it was sponsored by Baby
Bell Cheese and I feel like they had these
little like Baby Bell Cheese sandwiches
with cars and prints on them.
Oh. And I didn't get one
and I saw somebody when I was so jealous
and I still am. That sounds good.
I like those cheeses. That might have been a snack savior in this weird place.
It's like bunch of fun cars food
that we don't have in America. Did the car
have a face? Did the food truck have a face?
I feel like it did. Okay.
So there was a human inside the
guts of a car. Yes standing inside
the anthropomorphic car
hypothetically. Like in the intestines.
Kind of pushing its arms out through the intestines
of the car and Baby Bell
Cheese Sandwiches. Yes. Serving hot little
spreadable cheese sandwiches.
What is a food truck to you
if you're being lit up on the inside?
Too much. Don't even
worry your pretty little head with it. It is
too much. That's what like. Ka-chow!
What have you got today?
You just
went through the living room where my son
watches Pixar movies all day
and like if you
I think a lot of parents have to be this way.
Like if you have cars on a lot
you have a new question every
viewing. There's not one time that
it's on. It's on hundreds of times.
Yeah. Oh yeah. And I like
the new one for me is early on there's a
race going on. It's showing everything around the stadium
and then there's a bathroom
and the men are just going straight
in and the women it's a big long line.
You know like sporting events are. Sure.
What are the cars doing in the bathroom?
What does a car
need to do? Does anyone
have any. I have
fluid flush. Crass ideas
about what it is. I suppose.
So because they like eat oil
at an oil. It flows.
I think they go and eat oil and gas.
Yeah they do.
So it's half. They're all like half
well they're not half human but they're
human car. Are they like
are they defecating out the
tailpipe or something?
What? Defecating what? What's coming
out? Exhaust?
I guess it's just exhaust and oil?
Exhaust in front. They're exhausting
all the time. Yeah exactly.
Yes. It's not a private matter. That's why I'm
saying it's probably like
some sort of version of like excrement.
Or like an oil change.
Is it like if there's like
a well like you end up with like a gunky
build up in the car.
Yeah I mean.
The car's going by right now. Let's ask
us sir. Yeah let's ask the car.
They don't know either.
I mean they spent a lot of those movies
cursing their existence at whatever sick
god would make them this way.
It's what it should be.
It's just full and analyze.
I would just watch documentaries made in the car's
verse about why.
Just why. Yeah.
Wasn't there? Didn't someone say that
there's evidence in the movies of humans
on the planet?
Oh like they're fossils right?
What? I can't remember what maybe
it was a joke. I can't remember but I feel like there's somebody
pointed out something in one of the movies
that there's like evidence that humans did live on this
version of the earth at one point.
Geez. So I don't know.
Maybe that was a joke.
I wonder what the evidence is. If you're listening
and you know. All I want to do
is think about cars. I'm broken
by this question that you posed.
I can't go on.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It's really
I'm not happy with any
answer. I mean if they are just like you know
but they need but the oil
maybe it's like us. We eat
things and then some of it we use to power
us but other some is
waste. But what's waste for a car?
Do I use all of it?
All right.
Look I think we're all a little freaked out.
Maybe we should get back to the rock
rock solid storytelling
of 1998's Armageddon.
Clarity.
Simple ideas.
What are you looking up Mike?
Bones. Well I'm looking up all the
times that there's bones in cars.
There's an article here that says the disturbing
theory explains Pixar's cars.
But my phone is taking too long to
have it load. So we can come back to
it. We don't have to do it. When we get to radiator, springs, racers
we'll ignore the ride and focus on all
this. But for now
but the what we came here to do
let me explain why we're
doing this with you.
I was looking at Twitter and our
friend Kevin Perger defunct land
put out a prompt
and it was this. I am once again asking for
suggestions for the worst theme
slash amusement park ride you have ever been
on that is now defunct.
I saw you responded and the
response was Armageddon at
Walt Disney Studios Park. Yeah did not hesitate.
Yeah you knew it.
Oh yeah in coming up with that decision you had
no you didn't think about any other candidates.
It was like what color is this guy?
Just
can't even if I tried to think of another attraction
couldn't even think of one. Wow wow.
I got so excited
because I like oh that's right that we haven't done
that have we what an insane thing
and I feel so similar just baffled by
it. Being in there in person doesn't
help. Let me add that
Lentesta jumped on and
added a response
to you this. I left
wondering if it was some sort
of idiomatic French parody.
It was not. It was not.
So with this pile
of opinions about this ride well this
is some this is a podcast
the ride magnet. I think we got
to dive in. Were you guys familiar with
you knew this existed at least but maybe
hadn't done the dive on it. No
I don't think I actually yeah I was new
the video is when I was watching I go I don't think
I've ever watched this before so it was
on the radar but it was not I was
not well versed. Sure. No I didn't
know the specifics I knew it was
there I had heard it was bad
and I briefly remember it MGM
studios in Florida there was a
little Armageddon
thing like
like videos or a walkthrough or
something. I don't think it lasted very long.
They had a making of space that
and things would change out but you got
after in the
Twitter flurry that followed
Carly you got a response from
somebody. Well explain what the. Yes
so there was in the thread there is someone
who is responding and fully
being gaslit by everyone on the thread
who's like that was never in Florida
and then they found a map that showed
it and they also called into my podcast
very amusing and I was like you
know what I'm going to put a pin in this this will be answered
in the future I can't tell you where or when and
this is that date but there was
you were absolutely right there was
a version of this I guess
in studios in Florida.
Yeah not I
don't I remember seeing
it very briefly it's not
fully I don't think it was fully built out
like it wasn't in a room
space station and all this stuff
yeah I don't think it had the full
effects it was in the room
with like like twister back
draft which is this is kind of reminiscent
of do you think they did anything do you think
like they showed the here's the
history of special effects which happened in
this or the little Michael
Clark Duncan appearance.
I think
if they were going to I mean
they put it in the American parks I think it was probably
a lot more props and a lot
of montages with the
big movie stars
that are in Armageddon
but absent of the in this attraction.
Yes.
Other than the one you got one.
You got one you got a great performer show
up and I'll
give the Russian guy you know
that guy is he in the movie?
Is it Stormare?
Is it Peter Stormare? Who's the guy?
That's who I looked like in a blurry
Stormare type.
Yeah I'm not totally sure.
I don't know.
So alright so there was some there was a little
making of attraction but
maybe not the full thing. I also recalled
strongly the rumor
that this was going into
California Adventure and that it was
maybe being considered as an opening
either as an opening day or
as what do we draft in
quickly in the immediate
decay of Superstar Lemmo?
Because there's that big space
back there with it's that there's
that weird building that was the who wants to be a millionaire
thing and now it's like a they're just committed
to being a store I guess.
It's a Marvel thing now
I haven't seen it as a Marvel thing. Okay okay.
But I recall
seeing in some online forum
well there's a lot of good buzz about
this Armageddon thing that's going
into Paris so maybe they'll just draft
that quickly into California
Adventure and that was still in my head
when I walked up to
the attraction in 2014
was whatever commenter said
I heard this is good.
2014. Yeah yeah.
That long after. Wow.
So I still I went in actually not
knowing it was
a disaster. I was like in
my mind this could have been like oh maybe oh they actually
like took the universal
this formula of a little
bit of behind the scenes and then you're thrust into the
thing and took it to the next level.
That is what I was actually expecting
when I walked in the room that day.
As one I mean the facade is
very like the logo is very enticing
and you're like this is going to be fun and adventurous
and you are truly standing
in two rooms.
And that's it.
And one really claustrophobic hallway I remember
connecting it's this really like depressing
file through to
like it's a long walk to that
other. The sign looked like it was
a little bit DCA though as far as
like a thin
like not so
that's my. Your recollection?
It's a little small
on my screen here but this is
this view kind of encapsulates
what this park was like
at least at the time. Where is
this like kind of like
the tower of terror behind it.
Building and yeah and then the Armageddon
logo is really just kind of
it's very flat plastered on and you're looking at the
back of the tower of terror which almost no
park besides this
do you have a view of and the back of it looks like
nothing. Yeah. They didn't
put the Hollywood tower
sign on the other side it's just
blank. I think it's still that
way because they didn't expect to
be doing that. Think about when this park
opened. It's a really
depressing opening line up where there's no tower
of terror yet. Obviously there's no Rat Tatooie.
There's no there's not this crush coaster
which you said you like. Yeah I love crush coaster.
That seems cool. Yeah yeah. Wait that's another
thing about like yeah that
seems pretty neat. That reads in a
ride through. And this sign does not
have the outsider art appeal
of the rock and roller coaster sign with the big
CD. Ah, that Aerosmith.
Yeah yeah yeah. Now that is
it's yes it's at least
so far in that direction
that it is amusing. Yeah it
went from being like
okay yes CD is how we all listen
to music in 2002 to an
interesting an acronym when it
closed in 2019.
Well it's like how those you know you
go to the 50s hotel in
Disney World or the 50s wing
of Pop Century and there's big records
and jukebox. It became an
accidental 2002
period piece way after the fact.
But again
you know what I mean you bring up a good thing because
these things were these odd facades
in the back of Tower of Terror are all kind
of in the same zone
which in our rock and roller
roller coaster episode I called Aerosmith
Alley. It really is
like a full Aerosmith
zone. Which is the only thing that makes me
sad that this is gone now. Yeah.
Aerosmith had two attractions
for Aerosmith. What a stronghold.
Oh my god. If you don't recall that
they did the theme song of Armageddon
I Don't Wanna Miss a Thing as you quoted
in the beginning. And you would
hear their music I feel like in this
whole so it kind of was like
you know what is now going to be
become Marvel
and Avengers. Yeah.
Wasn't what the Avengers of rock
for sure yeah.
A team up of the five greatest
musicians on the planet Earth.
Wait that's that's the
thing that I that I looked up and I'll probably
screw up I'll screw this up
because I screwed up the first pronunciation
but here I looked up how to say this
in French. Les mauvais gossons
de Boston.
Les bad boys de Boston of course.
In French.
If you wanted to
engage with some French people
talk about the best of American culture.
They were saying that phrase they were saying
that phrase every day when they were out there.
Can I shout out to a friend of the show Julia Prescott for getting
me Joey Kramer the drummer for
Aerosmith's coffee as a gift.
Oh. Recently.
What's that called again?
I'm flanking on it.
It's some rock thing.
Wow. Joey Kramer's rock coffee.
Yeah let's call it. If I can
toss out just a big picture thing
about Armageddon
Leif-Expecio
it opened in March
2002 and closed
in March 2019.
Which is 17 years.
It was open until 2019.
2019. Like there's a world where I had
an iPhone 11 and this thing was still
open. Correct.
Get clear footage.
Oh yeah because you can look at the low
light. There's videos of this that are
immaculate actually on YouTube.
Very good HD.
Rocking and roasting coffee.
I don't know why I should have known.
And I probably could have gone
through and made a list but the thing
that stuck out to me I was like
17 that's bigger than something
right and I looked it up.
This lasted longer than Horizons.
Horizons was around
less time. Even if you
combine the first run of Horizons
and then it closed for a little while
and would operate seasonally and then of course
it closed on the eve
of the new millennium.
If you add up the two runs
of Horizons it is less than
the one run of this attraction.
Oh my god.
It's one of the longer running Disney attractions
weirdly. It beat a lot.
It beat like probably not interspersed.
It beat like flying saucers.
I think it was the ones that people had thought of that it
beat. They must
just have such a need
to put people somewhere and so few
attractions that they had
to keep it open. Yeah.
Just no choice. Because there's very little
to do at this park.
Now they're starting to close them because they have
some better stuff and they're building better stuff.
Will be great in the future. Currently
nothing. Yeah boy.
It's grim. Grim decor
wise.
And the dated
well it also leads to like
Armageddon was a big movie but the cultural
footprint of it by 2019
is very slim.
Yeah.
Not the size of Texas.
If you want to check out Armageddon
and refresh yourself, boot up
your Fubo app. That's where
it's currently streaming.
We're all Fubo heads here.
Yeah so much not Disney
is this that it's not on Disney Plus.
Yo yeah I didn't even think about
that. Yeah weird.
Fubo. I feel like
we've name checked a lot of them but
I don't think we've ever mentioned Fubo before.
Fubo I think is a mix of on
demand and some live
channels. Like I feel like
Pluto. Fubo is a
Pluto. Well let's
not denigrate Pluto. Yeah yeah
I know. Pluto is solid. Yeah yeah.
I just found the Bob. There's a 24 7 Bob
Ross channel in Pluto
and it's really it is really relaxing.
I never really sat down and watched that show and I was
like oh wow now I see
like now I get it.
Very calm.
I one thing
just before we move on from
well who knows if we can we ever really
move on from discussion of the bad boys
of Boston. Of course yes. But I did find
a video that affirms
that the man himself
was there. Visited Aerosmith alley
when Aerosmith alley was still intact.
And this is from the
this is from the Instagram
account of Miss
Leva Little and that's
Liv Tyler. That's his daughter.
So they went together.
Recently.
When was this? I thought. Or maybe
I'm thinking he went to. 2018.
So a mad cap
tour. A mad
hatted tour by Stephen
Tyler of Aerosmith alley.
Daddy where are we?
We're at Disney World
in France
and there's a rock and roller coaster but there's
this and Liv.
Liv. Liv. He means Armageddon.
This is going to take a minute.
He's running over the turnstiles.
This Armageddon character posters.
He's tripping.
He's moving
fast for a older man.
It's her. It's Liv.
His daughter.
He makes an I'll get ya face.
He's like he should have. I mean first of all
I agree he should have played her father.
What a movie that would have been.
Him glues voice as
Liv. Liv.
It's your fictional absentee father.
It's your real life absentee father.
This park is a
simulacra of a
movie studio.
And this video is a simulation of a father
taking his daughter to Disney.
The Disney park.
All it took was everyone getting
very famous and being able to use this as social
media content. Yeah.
They got it done. And pictures and
footage of themselves in this park
also assisted.
Let's hang out. Just you and me at that park
where there's visual depictions of both of us.
That's nice. You would do it with your parent.
We'd all do it if we were depicting
He you know I'll say this about Stephen Tyler.
He loves that they're in theme park
stuff like he's like I think he's
the only one in the band that's excited
about it. I could be wrong. Yeah.
But like I think Joe Perry turns his nose up
a lot at like you know
the rock and roll music.
Yeah. But then the stuff that's not like blues
I feel like Joe Perry doesn't like jaded
the song that we like.
The most. I feel like he doesn't
like all that stuff. He doesn't like pop music
as much. He wants to do 12 bar blues with Johnny
Depp and Alice Cooper in the Hollywood
vampires and that's it. I went back
and listen to the rock and roller coaster episode
to see what had come up in this negative.
Every bit of what you just said. And it's also
it's an interesting window in our
podcast chronology because
there's so much
naivete on your part Mike where
you bring up Aerosmith and maybe you're
expecting a little snark. And in fact we're both
Jason and I are both like I kind of like
Aerosmith. Yeah. I kind of like the song
jaded. You go oh so
you mean it's the finest song
ever made and I can bring up the
bad boys of Boston in every episode
from now on. It's nice to see like
the creative spark. That's like the conception
of the talk.
That's where the spark
was magic. And I was like yes
more. Your heart is glowing.
Yeah. Oh my god.
They seem so down.
Did we talk about jaded being played at school
dances because that's the memory I'm having
right now. I don't think so actually. Oh
really? I feel like
it would have come out.
Did I in that episode did I talk about the fact
that I was going I went to a high school
dance with a girl and
I don't want to miss a thing came on.
You did yes. I did say that.
But she rolled her eyes at it. She was
like this is sucks. This song sucks.
And I was like what?
What's wrong with you?
Your lot in life
is you're still experiencing
feelings about Aerosmith Carly.
No I mean I will say every time
I go on Rock and Rollercoaster I'm like they do
have a robust discography.
I have a new respect for them every
time. Hits in a lot of decades
except for the last couple. But
a lot more than most bands
have. No like preteen memories all
tied up in their songs though.
Okay. Yeah. I wish.
Yeah. That's okay. That's okay. I'm upset.
But that's okay.
It'll deal.
During that whirlwind
tour of the Armageddon campus
you get to see this is the big
decoration
outside of this building is are the
individual character posters because
Steven takes Liv to go see her
character who is of course Grace.
Of course. Yeah. We know Grace.
And we pass by a big poster.
I took this is a picture I took
when I was there is the mundanity of a
huge poster of Steve Buscemi
and above it it says his character's name
Rockhound. Yes.
Go to Disney
Ferret. Pay as much as for the Castle
Park and see a big poster of
Rockhound. Fantastic.
That stuff is all good.
I feel like if the ride wasn't even there
it would be better actually.
Just posters and like the sign of
Armageddon and then you go that was fun to take
pictures with the poster. Yeah.
Get a picture of me with AJ.
You know Ben Affleck's lead leading
man character AJ.
Mr. Animal Crackers himself.
The most
romantic scene.
Oh yeah. Well and do we talk about the Affleck
the commentary track that everybody probably knows about?
No I don't know about this. Oh really?
I think it's on the Armageddon commentary
and I don't know if Affleck is drunk or not
but he's like just talking
about Armageddon but just
mocking it like crazy.
He's just like going back and forth with the dialogue
like oh yeah that makes a lot of sense. We're going to train
drillers to go into space.
We're not going to train astronauts.
He's just like and it's much funnier than what I'm
doing here but he's relentlessly picking apart
the logic of the dialogue
in the scenes. It's gone around a few times.
Because he would have recently have won
an Oscar for writing movies.
Sure yeah. Oh yeah.
Yeah. Yeah he has some clout.
You can say that stuff. It is very funny.
So the outside is spectacular.
We all look great.
Yeah.
Olivera Smith-Ali is great.
I was excited as Stephen. But then you get
inside and you go into a pretty sure
we get very Universal Studios from here.
They very much are borrowing a Universal.
I feel like it's an insult to Universal Studios
to say that this is Universal Studios.
Yeah sure. Because those things are so much better.
Yeah yeah yeah. Back to Aerith and Twister
look like you know they're bringing their A game.
Compared to this. Yes.
Two other things that stuck around for
a while. But anytime I wrote them
the crowd always seemed like oh that was cool.
Like that was cool to see.
Stuff fall down. Stuff explode.
The effects. The music. That sort of thing.
I understand why I
saw this. And this both
pretty successful movies
too. Yeah yeah.
Lessor hits than Armageddon.
But Twister I think stuck in
the popular consciousness for a while.
Yeah I suppose. Backdraft less so.
We found that weird that there's a
backdraft thing. But a better show.
Better show. People just. Explosions
are kind of pun not
intended. Universal.
Like always popular.
Which this does have. But you go
into this room and it's one of these
where here's a guy. What are you?
You're from the studio. You
represent the director. You're a
coordinator. Unclear.
Unthemed basically.
Just a room with a bunch of monitors.
So much French.
There's a lot of
standard definition
footage. There's a lot of 3x4
screens. And there's translation
like
three different. There's two screens
with translations on it. And three
different languages each.
I believe on the screen.
Yeah yeah yeah. Okay.
So a lot to look at.
And you watch a video.
Well it's explained to you
that you're going to be in a scene
where. I'm sorry.
You're getting on a Russian
space station. And so I
guess the scene in the Russian space station
is. It's
in orbit and a hundred and seventy
plane clothes
people. Not in astronaut
gear. From all places
all around the world. They're all
just in regular clothes
standing around. Not
holding anything.
Right. Well that's what space stations are filled with.
Generally.
Yeah like one to two hundred
random people.
Who just came in to escape the sun for like twenty minutes.
Yeah. Yeah.
No space is for. It's for. Commit.
It's for scientists and astronauts and Pete Davidson.
That's what space is for.
So yeah I know it's one of these
you're going to be in a scene and remember to be
scared. And you're getting your little
low down. But then you watch
a thing about the history of
special effects and their
definition of this is like any
I mean anything that happens. Yeah.
A fan is a special effect but
also all of Star
Wars is a special effect. Like it's
the full gamut you know.
Yeah that's right. It seems
like an actor acting as a special
effect or something like is it's fake.
Like that's how broad their
definition is. Yeah.
Makeup is a special if it's
not there specially.
So you see a really unfocused
montage that's a bunch of
everything that qualifies as effects and everything that Disney
could like get the rights
to at this time
which is among the things I spotted
Rocketeer
Inspector Gadget.
Live action and
Inspector Gadget. Live action Matthew
Brajk Inspector Gadget. Not the French
Stewart. Not French Stewart no.
Darby O'Gill and the little
people in there. One of the great
special effects films.
98 Mighty Joe Young.
You see
Eddie Valiant falling and then
Mickey joins him but then they cut
before a certain other character
joins him. They don't have the rights to. Right.
Joins him.
So you know
bunch of which
Jason you're like dating
it and saying it's still around in 2019.
Who in 2019 is watching this like
really. Are they so they use special
effects in movies.
This is very educational.
Uh huh.
We've talked about Universal eventually
has like kind of gotten rid of a lot of that aspect
of everything. So
2019 I'm trying to was there anything. When did
Backdraft close? Don't know.
Not too long ago.
It closed for Transformers.
Is that right? Yeah. I think it was before
I started doing this. Which was 2015.
I'm just wondering what the last
like version of this I guess Animal Actors
are still like behind the scenes.
Kind of. But by and large. They have
special effects state. They have like one
uh coordinated off. Yeah.
One quarantined. Making of the movies.
That's like that's the last thing left
in this genre of ride.
Yeah. Yeah they're mostly gone. Are you fun
of any of this Scarlett? Like do any of these
is there a behind the scenes attraction
that strikes you like oh yeah that one's good.
I mean I think the studio tour is very
good and I'm not just saying that because of the company
that I'm in. Yeah. But I think
you know it every time I'm on it I'm like
this is not my thing. Yeah. I like it.
I still like that. Yeah. And there's enough of though
I mean those the big things that happen
in King Kong. Yeah. And the little
it's half and half with
fun stuff and then a little bit of
the subway scene great. Yeah.
I know it's gonna happen every time
but I'm always delighted. Yes. Yeah.
Absolutely. But you know
this? No.
What happens is just so. Nothing.
Nothing happens. Nothing happens.
Before you get into the room where
nothing happens the
the this montage
ends and it ends with the death star
blowing up and then
and then it cuts to
just and then the smoke dissolves the fire
dissolves and Michael Clarke Duncan
you're greeted by Michael Clarke Duncan who says like
woo oh boy
ordinarily a massive
explosion like that could really hurt a guy.
You mean the death
star? Yeah I'd say so.
I heard a guy.
Yeah. He's right. I don't think he knew
what was there. We're gonna put in an explosion.
Okay. Not like the
biggest explosion that ever happened.
The moon sized star base
blowing up. We would. Yeah. Oh boy.
That was close. So
anyway Michael Clarke Duncan and this is
the biggest thing about how long this thing
ran. This attraction
ran for seven years
after the death of Michael
Clarke Duncan. Right. There's the only way
you and I saw it was well past
his demise.
That's crazy. They just
take it out. It doesn't add
really anything. I mean
I guess then you're removing his
memory. Yeah. But it's
just weird though.
There's no acknowledgement
of it. I feel like you're right
but like with any other this is
probably the least paid attention to
in the Disney company.
You know what I mean? Like no one was even
paying attention before
when he was alive. No one was paying attention after.
So like if it was a higher
profile thing people might have gone oh you know
we'll do something in there maybe as a little
if we'll leave it as a remembrance.
There would be some thought is what I'm
saying versus I don't even know
if anybody remembered he was on there because
this is probably the most forgotten
attraction in any
park. Yes.
Quite literally. Probably. I mean it's gotta
be in the top three I would think. Yeah.
I mean I forgot it until you
tweeted about it.
Maybe it shouldn't have been you know. You
condemned yourself to reliving it here.
I mean it's like
it really is kind of like unpacking a trauma.
Yeah.
We'll talk about our
I think both of our spouses said some
it was like alright things are a little tense
after this thing happens. Jason
what are you? Well I was just there was one
moment watching someone's
camcorder footage of this
and I just thought it was so odd in this room.
There's just a moment where like
first off it's showing it starts to
show footage of Armageddon and you're
like you're gonna be on the space station.
The asteroid is coming for the space
station. That footage
again the aspect ratio was kind of
driving me a little nuts. I know in
a montage it's gonna jump around.
But later when they're talking about the attraction
you are about to go on it was like
a letterboxed like a letterboxed
scenes from Armageddon
and then it cut to full screen
and it's just a very close
up shot of the colonel
and then
That's Stormare possibly? Yes.
He's been out in space just a little bit
too long is the English translation
of what they're saying in this moment.
And it just seemed like such an odd composition
of like alright we got a big
shot of this guy's face and then we're
translating what's going on.
And then again stepping back and look at
the bigger picture I'm like okay so the characters
we've established we have the actor
Michael Clarke Duncan, the ship's
computer of course and then colonel
Andropov. We all remember
colonel Andropov.
Colonel Andropov.
All your favorites are there.
So
Michael Clarke Duncan says a bunch
of stuff.
He says
you're gonna come face to face with a rock
with a really bad attitude.
And then he says can I get a little fresh air please
and then he gets hit with a fan
and then talks over a fan.
I should see that one coming. Here on
special effects stages you have to be ready for
anything. So it's a kooky
the set's coming to life.
I am happy seeing this guy
having fun and getting to be himself
especially post
his day. It reminds you
like this guy was good. He was great.
Don't you put that
evil on me Ricky Bobby?
Oh that's right. And he's in Talladega Nights.
Oh yeah that's good. And he has a scene where
he stabs him. Brill Ferrell stabs himself.
Yeah that's a great scene. That's him.
So you at least get
to see him have some fun.
Then they say they're ready for you on the set and then
he's
at the end of it the note
that they leave it on. Cause these kinds of attractions
it's always like a little taste of what
you might experience in there.
And in this case he's like well
don't worry you're gonna be fine. There's nothing to worry about.
Right fellas? And then he joins
two gargoyles.
And then he kind of laughs viciously.
And then it irises in on his face.
What do you mean? Am I gonna
see gargoyles? Are there gargoyles
in the next room? I mean that
would have been a plus off.
I can confirm it is
Peter Stormare playing Colonel
Lev Andropov.
So
we leave disappointing room number one
and go through a sad hallway
into disappointing room number two.
You almost know already at this point you're like
this is the death mark. Also
let's track our
respective spouses. Yes, yes, yes.
Cause mine, Erin, has
started. I could see her like
lose. It's already been a day.
You started here. This was the first
attraction. The first thing we did in studios.
I think we did. I went to look up photos
and it's like it's so long ago they're not even in my
Google photos. But we started
Disneyland which I believe my
husband thought was quite lackluster.
And then from there we went to
studios and went to this.
It makes me feel better too. I feel like sometimes I feel like
have I been hard on Paris in my crazy
in this litmus test. It's weird
cause like there's a lot about Disneyland
Paris that I'll happily make fun of.
But then again like in
this current era it's really
kind of becoming its own thing.
I had the most wonderful time there. Geez
that's nice. In 2021 not
on the trip that I did this. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That was all it was still
in the doldrums a little bit. Yeah, Erin's
losing it a little bit. Erin's it's this I just remember
that this walk between the rooms just like
how quickly can this be
over. I don't think she, neither of us really know what's
coming but I'm like it might be good or at least it might be
funny. Then you get into a room
I mean like you all watch
the ride through this or the ride through
whatever. Stand through
stand up. You're
in a very tight
I mean this is this would be a COVID nightmare. It's
great that it closed before. It's
just like Star Cruiser. Oh yeah, yeah.
Oh right.
Yeah, Mastodon there now I
hear. Yep. Oh from
the jump. Oh already
it wasn't icy. Disney should have done
an immersive Armageddon
hotel. Do not give them that idea.
We've done it for like 10 minutes and it
was horrible.
Yeah, we don't need to spend more
but what if you could meet Rockhound?
Well, probably not Rockhound like a guy
that knows Rockhound.
Well Rockhound I think is I haven't
watched this film but apparently the character
Rockhound says some very cancelable
things. Oh really? I think Rockhound
is a scumbag. If I recall he's
very horny.
That's his kind of gimmick. So he's like
Pat O'Brien?
Maybe less.
He might be more horny.
Okay, well
we'll analyze this
later. One of my first exposures
to see
Buscemi
in this kind of
you know flat movie
otherwise. They stacked it up.
It's good actors. It's got great actors.
It does have a good cast.
I'm not getting to do a lot of good
stuff. So
it's Russian Space Station.
Even though you're walking into it
and it's an immersive environment when you walk in
the screens are not they don't show
space yet. They all are placeholder and they
say like Earth
feed meteor feed.
So that's taking you out of it right away.
You're on a set and that's not like
it's
just such a bummer immediately.
And then they're calling out like
lighting changes. Let's
start shooting. So there's too much of that
set. Right. Overlay.
Fake theme park. We're shooting a movie
nonsense. Yes. We're shooting
a movie that came out decades ago.
Yeah. The opening of Hollywood Studios
style or I guess Universal
Studios like of just like yeah this
doesn't make any sense. I don't know why.
Yeah. Unless it's that
superstar television where they're
like shooting new things with people on
that's what we call it. Right. Yeah. That makes sense.
We're going to shoot scenes from famous things
with actual people. Yeah. That's like
the only context where it doesn't
people shouldn't be confused or like
what. It's so insane because
like if all right we want to take you
behind the scenes and show you how things are made.
This is not how things are made.
Sets aren't immersive and
360 degrees and they don't all happen
in the course of five minutes and
with like with the real
effects coming close to hurting
you. So like you know
it's already your it's already
fantastical what you're showing.
You know what else is fantastical is
theme park. Rise of the Resistance is
fantastic. Why not just commit all
if Rise of the Resistance constantly had we're ready for
you on the first order set
to destroy
the entire thing. If
I can add something that also kind of
took me out of it because I watched two ride throughs
of this and by the first
the first minute of the second ride
through it was like God why did I find
another video.
But I was interested in that
the one there was a cast member and their
outfit was like a gray
jumpsuit with like a yellow reflector
vest. But the first video I watched
it was just someone in like
theater blacks like a black
sweatshirt and black pants.
But two different shades of black
like they truly looked like they were a standup
comic about to complain about
how you can't say anything anymore.
Like that kind of black. And that
just threw me because I'm like I find
it hard if you're going to wear all black to
sometimes find the right matching shades
but I'm like wait Disney bought this
outfit why didn't they buy an outfit
with the same top and bottom.
Unless they didn't.
Because she didn't have a reflective
vest on. So I was like wait did you
just walk in?
Did you just walk in? It's like oh we got to
start running this thing I'm just going to hop up.
They don't check uniforms anymore.
Was it a turtleneck?
It was just like a crew neck.
It wasn't like a
you know. Because I picture like
a French person. Oh no it wasn't that kind of turtleneck.
A beatnik.
I'm picturing a French beatnik from the 1960s.
I mean that would really jazz it up.
Anything.
It's so funny to me because like there's so many
attractions that are like here's how movies are made.
But I truly don't know how an Avengers
movie is made. I like I know there's a lot of blue
or green maybe. And then they
like stand on a box and somehow it looks
like they're flying above New York City. I don't get it.
I would love to know. I would love to know.
You're right. New things. I don't know how things are made
anymore. Like now if they updated
any of this it would be interesting. Like teach me how
you put all those people together in a scene.
Are they all there or not? Are they in Atlanta?
What's going on?
You would be like you would be I think is you would
drive into like a room with
like 400 people at computers
being like these are the people who make the movie.
You see it in the credits.
These many people like animating
the Black Widow's like wrist gauntlet
firing mechanism or something.
And then like they're just like tired
and upset and
not being paid enough. And those are the
people that make the movie. Filmmakers use a term
called crunch.
He's working 16 to 18 hour days.
Certain effects.
There's more effects houses that like do
the big stuff and then there's like they farm out
certain effects to like different
sometimes in Marvel movies you can see like certain
CGI scenes are like look really good and then some
scenes look like absolute garbage.
It's probably because like they were late and they were like I just farm
this out to a smaller company.
Yeah really get it done. Whatever. We don't care.
Just put a filter on the front
of it and make it look like it's dark out doesn't matter.
Yeah. I mean the one of the last
big effect stories the last 10 years
was that the company
that did the effects
and then won a bunch of Oscars for a life of
pie had gone bankrupt
in between releasing the movie
and winning the Oscars for
a life of pie.
Not an industry you're dying to. You know what they
genuinely could do. We talked about this before.
They could do like
that the Mandalorian
practical the screens that look
really good if they did something with those.
Oh yeah that'd be great. Because I would like to see
those in person and then it's like your kid
is in a scene that
shot instantaneously and you watch
and it looks like Mandalorian. That would
not be the worst. They should be
adding things of this nature. That's
something you could do in an environment like this
that would work and be cool. Yeah it's like we always
say more screens.
We love screens. Of course we love
screens.
But a forward looking like a forward looking
thing that kind of tricked like I was
tricked for the first few episodes. Like I didn't
realize they were doing that until they had like a featurette
on it.
So yeah put and then sell the tape of you
in the
Mandalorian with Fennec Shand and
that's the name of the character.
I mean they literally have empty
sound stages. There is no excuse.
Yeah sure.
Yeah it's better than literally nothing.
Yes.
This is one of those where like we could
say some things bit by bit
that happen in this
final part. But like what happened? Really?
Like can you even name
like let's name a moment of this
space station scene.
I think it's like something hits something
and then
there's like does it jiggle then or does
it jiggle later? There's a jiggle.
But I don't recall where.
And then there's way more
pyro than I remembered.
Yeah there's a lot of flames
in the room and here's another
thing I'm going to say that I don't particularly care
for is flames in
the room. I will
allow it in a set
like I acknowledge that it's cool
in the mummy coaster
in Florida. That's cool
enough that effect on the ceiling that I will
deal with that it's a little freaky.
But like I don't know if this is like a
scary cat thing. It's like
haunts or launches. I think I'm okay
I just I don't want flames in the room
with me. It's never it's not cool
enough for me to not because
I think some of it is you start smelling that
gas a little even before it happens
and you think like oh flames coming
and I just don't it's I'm unnerved by the
like gas isn't a
fun thing to smell in a thing on
my vacation. Well it's so
close it is like mall
fountain level like
proximity. Like you get really
close to this little giant fireball
at the end. Yeah, yeah.
I don't know how do we feel about flames? Am I
I guess I'm pro flame in a close
space I think. Yeah.
Yeah you're pro.
Okay Jason you're anti?
Well I want I want a little
distance. So what is a ride
comfortably? I think backdraft
that I'm comfortable with. This
like put putting
your little hands
under your head. Your little hands?
Next to like on the railing
and leaning over the railing
with your like head in your hands and a fireball
and six feet in front of you. That's
too much. You're like a teen girl on the bed
like this.
This is like the sensual part of this
attraction. Thinking about
yeah. That's interesting.
I don't know. I shoot a flame
at me. I don't like I'll make
wince I might get scared but at least I'm feeling
some I'm least I'm alive.
Outside I was fine with it. Like some of my
family I feel like we went on
the Jaws ride once at Universal
and they were like these flames out there way
too hot way too close to the boat. I'm like
bring it on. We gotta we gotta get
that shark. Outside
your pro flame. Yeah yeah.
Indiana Jones stunt show love those
flames. I've sat close at wrestling events
and they shoot a lot of pyro which is
loud as hell. See that would scare me. That's a temporary
setup. That's not a safe.
This is a permanent flame. They're
blasting them out all day. I'm not concerned.
Yeah well I guess
that's true. It's probably at this point
they've run it so many times and like
for Monday Night Raw that's
new that's fresh. They're on the road right?
In the morning yeah. That's like a carnival.
That can't be trusted. Last year
I think the WrestleMania sign caught on fire
I think. This is what I'm talking about.
I'm pretty sure. Michael I just want to
correct you. Multiple WrestleMania
signs.
Oh god. Yeah.
So. And that's the billion
dollar earning promotion.
Sure yeah. Catching stuff on fire.
I like that logic. This is interesting.
So there's a whole spectrum here. There's no flame.
There's outdoor flame. Not indoor
flame. There's total pro flame.
And then there's pro
not temporary. Permaflame.
Permaflame. Yes. Permaflame.
Should we do the flame final four?
The theme park flame final
four? The best flame
scene. That's actually not a bad idea
maybe. I figured it out.
But yeah exactly. It's all a mush.
As it's happened. And it's all around
you which is interesting. But you also don't know where
to look. I think in not a good way.
Were you close to this?
Because it's circular. It's like you're on
a donut. Because the center is where they have
the fire stuff. So were you closer
to the center or were you more towards the back?
I think maybe closer to the back.
Maybe something unpleasant happened behind me
and I didn't know where to look at. Maybe I
just felt some heats. Were you putting
your head in your little hands? Yeah.
When I was happening.
I hope this is the best show I've ever seen.
Bonjour asteroid.
Where were you?
I was towards the back and I remember
being like oh I wish I would have known what this
was because I would have wanted to be right by the
flame. Oh okay.
The center piece. The only thing to look at.
Yeah because it does culminate
in then lights are out and the
plot wise what is this?
The space station if we haven't said
is getting attacked. But multiple
Yeah a bunch of asteroids are tearing through
the space station.
There's two really big things
that rubbed me the wrong way about this ride.
One it is based on a cut away
shot from the movie Armageddon.
Interesting in the realm of podcasting.
I think very interesting.
And two
wait this ride is about you
just accepting inevitable
death. Like impending death
is coming to you. Which is a very
I mean that's very French film.
But it's a little weird that it's in a Disney park
where it's just like oh you're all
going to die. But only in a
scene. But in one scene.
But also Michael Clarke Duncan just told
you nothing bad is going to happen to you.
And he's dead so.
That's something bad happened to him.
Yeah. Yeah it's a
boy it is already in a
grim park on a grim property
in the grimest part of it.
Well maybe if you view it as
that as a reflection on death.
Maybe that's a good angle on it.
If you're not trying to view it as an exciting
e-ticket. I mean I guess I'm getting ahead of myself to
what we would have done to plus it up. But even if they had
had Bruce Willis's Harry
Stamper character like in the movie when
Liv Tyler is like at the
screen before he dies because he sacrifices
himself to save the earth.
Even something like that would have maybe put a bow
on it that were like I don't know
that were like well
I guess that's not exactly that we're
burning Bruce Willis I guess in this case.
So maybe I'm wrong. Maybe my
thought process is bad here.
I maybe your only
thought process that's bad is the idea that this could be
a good thing.
Were you satisfied then by
the because that's what I was getting at was
it's being destroyed by
so then what you feel at the end is like
that's the
final curtain kind of like
and now the flames that kill you
are bursting through the center
of your donut. Oh I legitimately had
no idea what was going on from start to
finish when I went on this.
We should be Bruce Willis. Here's the
right thing. Liv should be on
a screen mourning us.
Like all my good friends
are all my siblings or something.
She remembers
the happy ending. I like that.
I like that. So you see her.
We have to have pushed
Affleck in because remember
the movie he was going to stay behind.
Right. And and then Bruce Willis
like take care of my daughter.
Yeah right.
So it should be something like that
that we've we all collectively
throw Ben Affleck out a
hatch of some kind
and then the flame and Liv
mourns us then the flame comes through blows
us all up and then we're all heroes.
We have lived
a hero experience. So we're
dead. We are dead. We're dead. Like Mr.
Toe. There are attractions where you
die. Right. So make this
another one of those. Make it another one of those.
And the one ride through I
watched the big fire
like at the end I was
like ooh that must have been really big
because the screen just went white.
They were focused on that center
jet and I was just like
oh my god everything went white. Now it's going to be back
into focus. I was like well at least there's a big
ending I guess.
With me not liking flames I
just didn't like that happening at all.
Were you as a permaflame
fan did you at least like the ending
after all the struggle of the
experience? I don't know if I
have any recall of the
ending because I was trying to not
be actively divorced at that
moment. Cause I just
was standing next to my husband going
I forced him to come here. I
forced him to come to this park and he said
doesn't everyone say Disneyland Paris sucks?
And I said no
and let's go to both of them.
So I was really just trying
to get out of the grave I had dug myself.
So yeah what happens
right after?
This all is happening you're not
in the narrative of it. You are thinking how do
I need to save this day?
We realized at some
point in the donut room in the secondary
the worst room I would say perhaps.
They're both bad. Unpleasant. It's also
very loud. It's just like here's a room with loud
sounds. That's the bulk of what this is.
I mean we started
to realize this was the ride.
This wasn't the pre-show
for the attraction that we thought we were going
to. This was the attraction.
And that realization was
there's no amount of indoor fire
that could make that
better. So are you
apologetic?
Defensive? It's not my fault?
I mean I still can't really
live it down. It's
like Disneyland Paris will forever have a stink on it
because of this.
We have very similar experiences
here because this was
at the very end of
my honeymoon by the way.
This is the big mistake
we made is that like incredible
trip to Paris and
Rome and Florence and then we thought
well we end it back in Paris
so it can be a round trip.
And we love Disney so it culminates in Disney
but it puts so much pressure
on it. I've said all this before. Florence
is probably the best place I've ever been. Maybe until
Tokyo but they're neck and neck.
So we were coming from this euphoric experience
in this beautiful city with the best food
ever and now we're in the Armageddon
special show.
And this was really
we even like we managed to have
some loopy fun in the
in our first day which was in the
Magic Kingdom Park. But still
it was like a struggle. We had to like really press
through and like it's like
we're so insane that it's fun. It's not
the relaxation that Honeymoon
could and should be. So now we're here
we even were at the gate going do we pay
for this dumb place? And it's
like well I don't know right behind
this gate is a new Disney theme
park that will probably never be near again.
Maybe we need to do this.
Maybe it'll be content someday
for something.
And we go in and it would buy Armageddon we were thinking
maybe this was a bad it. Maybe we could have just like
I don't know gone into the city again.
Just waved at the Eiffel Tower. Almost anything
else. Actually Erin in reliving it
said I would say
it's waiting for the dentist
is more pleasant than this.
Maybe not the dentist itself if you're getting drilled.
It's at least in English.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Or at least translated well.
You can understand what's happening to you. There can be a
calm in a waiting room. I think we were
just talking about Jason you proposed that flying
can be like okay. You felt like a flight
can be fine. I yeah
like if you want to disconnect
like and just read a book or like
work on writing and stuff. I just
listened to this episode and I fully agree with you.
Thank you. Yeah. Or train travel
very much the same. I was trains I feel like
they give away the Wi-Fi on Amtrak.
But it's also
it's very bad.
Wi-Fi is free.
It's still like very expensive
for 30 minutes a Wi-Fi. I'm like American
Airlines. Like it's just not worth it.
Why is that still so? That doesn't make any sense.
But this is where I was thinking about this.
I would rather sit on a plane almost. Even a plane
with mild turbulence than go on this Armageddon thing.
It would be the same amount of turbulence
as that ride. Yeah. Yeah. Which still is
not that. Yeah. I've been there's been
more exciting turbulence on a real plane
because there's it's a real disaster.
Well that's a big drop.
That's something. So
anyways we get out of it. Just this
was the kind of the pit of the day I felt
like. And Aaron's
just staring daggers. And once we once we
slowly file out of the room I think she turns to me
and says what about rides? Are there
rides in this park? Is there a ride anywhere
in this park? I think we had
not been on on a ride yet.
And I said rock and roller
coasters that way. I'm not going to do it. I don't do
launches. You can go do it.
And I went and watched this dumb Martin
Short show where he goes through the history
of movies. Oh my god. Like that's I can
handle the kitch. Aaron's like I need to
do a thing that someone might
enjoy without levels.
And so we took some time
apart. We split up for a second.
It literally made us split up. It split us up
on the last day of our honeymoon.
It's important to have your own
interests. Yeah.
She's interested in
not ruining her own life.
Whereas I.
So we took a little time and then we
reconvened. And I said oh how was that rock and
roller coaster? And she said it was fine.
Do you want to get to the airport
early?
Pretty much how this went.
Did you watch I forget what it's called there
but in Florida it's called Lights Motor Action.
We didn't do that because by that point it was just
like what is the we need to bail on
this as quickly as let's go eat a crappy
burger in the Radisson
lobby. And then like
we cannot handle another like
sitting through a thing. I like I don't think
we haven't done Lights Motor Action.
I am a Lights Motor Action defender.
That was actually. I never saw it anywhere.
Stunt driving and like cool
car tricks. That had some cool behind the
scenes stuff. Yeah.
And then and then after a few years
Light McQueen drove in and
just did a lap and then left.
Hey.
I just feel so bad that you guys haven't
you know half of us haven't tested our
relationships inside this attraction.
It's the ultimate test.
You'll never know if it's true love.
The ultimate stress test.
But also they never will in a way
because this it's so funny we have this exact
say it's like tense in general
and then this is like
and you're on vacation because the possibilities
of what a vacation could be.
You chose that and you're
you and I were responsible for
our spouse pain.
I mean I'm still dealing
with it because we went back in November
and I had just gone with my mom
for multiple days so I had like really packed
in Disneyland Paris had a great time.
I made my husband go back for one day. I was like
we're in Paris for a week. I have to do it.
I'm there. I have to go. And I'm just now
remembering that I think he refused
to go on any ride. I don't think
we went on a single ride. He's like I will
walk in a circle around the park with you
and we brought our own sandwiches. He did not
eat. He did not ride. He was
just like this is my limit after
what happened. Well that seems like
a fair compromise.
I'm sure conversely
he struck you to like work functions
or like dinner at the boss's
house or something. And you know
you gotta give and take.
When you're using your Jason argument of it's work.
I'm here for work. I'm doing work. I'm stressed
I'm at work. Yeah. So if
you put that on it. Yeah.
I guess that's a way. Yeah. So just
remind. Listen. I don't think I hate anything
as much as he hates Disneyland Paris.
Next time you're going to dinner at the boss's
house.
So you know this is just the same
as the Armageddon ride. Exactly the same as having
to watch this Russian
cosmonaut translated
into multiple languages.
The terrific Peter Storber.
You get to see
45 seconds of it. You hear a voice that may
or may not be him. It could be a sound. It very
easily could be a sound like and there is
a computer voice. Cause he is
he is playing a Russian character
speaking English. But the computer
voice is doing kind of generic
computer voice but speaking French.
So it's a real melting pot.
You know. It's got that going.
Yeah. And then you have to hear him say like
what is generator status.
It is pretty
Boris Baranov.
Sparkling dialogue. Great accent.
This is fascinating.
I'm actually now curious with what we have
experienced if any listeners
have run into this and where you
may be pushed a partner
to the brink. Who where I feel
like you know
if you're ending up in these parks even if the
person's not as big of a fan as
you and Aaron's a major Disney parks fan
but she's got the limit.
And I'm curious of any stories of like where
did the limit set in.
I'd be curious for any
or else everybody's just like it's never happened.
Maybe find somebody who has no
limit. There was I'm trying to think but
I think I've said this on the show before. I think there was like
two Disney World trips ago. Lindsay was like
I think it was like day three or four.
And she was like I gotta
sleep in. I'm tapping out
and I go well you can meet me
in Animal Kingdom. She's like fine.
So I'm like
on the bus to Animal Kingdom
alone at like 9 a.m.
I didn't know this one.
But also as Jason was saying
you have separate you know you have different
speeds of vacation. Yeah.
Yes.
When we were there in the fall I talked about
Jane tapped out on the Friday of
like a week long trip and she's like I'm
gonna the pool and I'm gonna take a bath.
And I was just standing on concrete
in Hollywood Studios reading
like a blog that's like crowds
not seen since the July peak
on Veterans Day week. And I'm just like oh
my god.
Having to like
defend yourself as the one who made the
right choice in situations like
that. No I mean not
mean then not going on
the roller coaster that goes fast.
But I got to experience
Martin Short as a man with a
flip phone who gets
sucked into the history of
some of five movies that Disney
could afford. It was hard for me to say
I made the right choice in that situation.
But there maybe there I think
at this time there was not a right choice
to be made at Disney Studios Paris.
Oh after you do Armageddon everything's a write off.
It's just over. Your day's
done. Let's just
round up to the end I guess. Yeah. Cause in
Orlando if you tap if you need to like
all right let's get the parks today
and stuff. Disney Springs has
so much to offer. The Disney
Village does not seem like it has that
appeal. Oh my God.
Recently I'm he probably
doesn't mind if I say this friend of
the show Mac Cardona also has been to Disneyland
Paris recently and I think has sent me
some photos of the village.
It seemed to me like he was
amped on it just that he was but maybe that
was I was not amped about Disney Village.
I don't know that he had anything in depth to say.
I mean it's got a pretty well preserved
planet Hollywood. He did send us
pictures from that. We were saying it's the only
trash planet Hollywood left. A good time capsule.
Crazy looking one. Cause you know now that we're all
like there's these communal spaces
online for people who like the old stuff
to like reminisce about it and
that is one of the old places that still stands.
Right yes. But it is definitely
not as fun as we
will think it was in ten years from now.
This is true and you hate
to say it there's certain things where like look
if it's gonna be better to do something
new we all have the memories
increasingly we have like VR
walk throughs and exhaustive
videos. I can see the logic
in certain things changing
ever. Such as this.
Such as even if there is one
strange person out there who like but Armageddon
was so crazy.
I do think that the replacement
web slingers the new Spider
Man ride is going to
appeal to someone. I think
probably. More than this
trash. I am very nervous that
they're redoing the Boardwalk Hotel
in Orlando. They already got rid of
the clown slide it's all downhill.
I guess that's true. That's my outlook.
I mean we must protect
the nanny chairs. We are on nanny chair
watch 24 7 now.
There are the nanny chairs.
I don't see if anyone notices working
the graveyard shift.
I am very concerned that they're going to
get rid of them. But I also
I was talking to someone a friend
of mine and he thinks that the coffee
bar that's being added is going where the
Bellevue Lounge is which was secretly
my favorite bar that I never told people about
because it used to not be busy and after the pandemic
or during the pandemic it became busy.
But it was great. There's a wicker couch
that has cup holders built into the wicker.
This is a library kind of
study. It's like that little the little annex bar
to the right of the Boardwalk lobby.
What's it called again? Yeah they were yeah they're
Bellevue Inn I believe. I went
there last time I was down.
Bellevue Lounge? Jane they're playing old timey radio.
They're playing old timey radio.
And she's like it's 10
AM we've been up for five hours.
I don't care.
This is supposed to red eye.
This is when we were kind of land and kill time.
We land and kill time when we're trapped by
the marathon. We could not get
anywhere. Oh that marathon story.
We got trapped by the marathon. Never have we had more
sympathy for you. Our reservations
were to Epcot so we couldn't go
anywhere. You couldn't get into Epcot when it wasn't
open was the story. We couldn't
get into Epcot. We were baffled
by that story because it involved like and then there was a
cone there.
Well there were so many cones and there was
runners and people were like no no you can't come
through. But it wasn't open.
But
nothing was open.
Besides like one breakfast
stand. Would it have
been on a non marathon day?
Well even the footpaths to like
Swan and Dolphin. But the footpaths
would have been open. Yeah
you could have gone a little more. So the issue
is that at 10am the footpaths weren't open.
That's a big deal. You're trapped.
We're trapped. You're trapped at the boardwalk. Your options
are very limited.
The boardwalk was like half of everything
is closed. They half opened.
And they half opened like the walkways
around the lake
resorts. And so
like we're able to walk to the boardwalk.
But then the bus services
were only running to the open
parks that due to park reservation
systems we couldn't go anywhere.
Are you getting more of a sense of why this was
Jason's Armageddon?
And I thought oh okay
we can go to Disney Springs.
No. Disney Springs didn't open
until 10am. And this was earlier.
So like. I'm trying.
I will admit I got distracted
because on the disboards.com
somebody wrote what is the Bellevue
room at boardwalk. And then somebody
just wrote under it the boardwalk bakery no
longer toasts bagel. Just sold
as is.
No.
It's worse than a Russian space station blowing up.
I think that's what it's called though. Like the lobby bar essentially.
Bellevue lounge is what it's called. Yeah.
But I just got distracted by the
this course. That's sort of like if I was at a media
event I'd tell the people that I'm friends
with that we're meeting up at Bellevue.
And then we'd all go there after.
If you let the cat out of the bag is now
Bellevue gonna get swamped? Well I think it's gonna become this
coffee shop. Cause they just announced a whole redo.
Oh. So Bellevue is
already the dream's over. Also I tried to go there
maybe during the 50th at some point and there was a line
to order cocktails. And I was like
no no no no no.
I feel like when the other day
when I walked by the Hurston lounge at the Grand
California. It's a similar thing. There's like a little
coffee set up outside of it now.
The bar was roped off early.
There was a bunch of partitions and I'm like
oh okay this is kinda
no mans land. You gotta find your secret spots.
Yeah. They're disappearing.
Is the air bar still good?
I mean I've kind of avoided most tight
indoor places just cause the times I've visited
have been during like peak pandemic
times. But I haven't
been there in a while. I don't I feel
too old for a drink with cotton candy in it.
Do they have that?
This is an insane statement you've just made in front of Mike Carson.
Again you've made me upset but
no no
I didn't even know there was cotton candy.
Yeah they have don't they have one that's cotton candy and then they pour
the drink in and then it dissolves and they're like
magic. That's interesting cause
I've only ever gotten like a good like
Manhattan in there. Oh well then maybe
that's the move. I had like two trips
ago I had like three Manhattans
in there once. And then I hit my
then walking to Frozen I hit my hand
hard on like a metal like kind of
railing somewhere and it was sore for days.
Oh and that's where the
woman was trying to hit on my friend Luke
and I. Did you tell this you must have told
this one. I probably told this story I think.
There was like a couple
we think but then we're like maybe they weren't a couple
and this woman was like
like coming on to me and my friend
Luke who were there. I was there although
I was there with my friends who were
married and Lindsay was not there.
That was this trip. Cause I had
a third wheel trip. I was a third wheel
already. Yeah I had an annual pass.
I bought an because at the time it made
sense to get the if I was going once to Disney
World it was still a time when it
made sense to get the
premier pass. Oh yeah you're speaking my language.
Yeah. For Disneyland and Disney World.
Yeah to get both parks cause it was literally
like you may as well just get it cause then you get
more access to Disneyland.
Every day of the year. Every day of the year.
Any park. It was amazing. Amazing
time to be alive and I was like well
now it's just like if I can get a quick trip in
and my friends were flexible so I
went with them and Lindsay had work so I
was there alone drinking three
Manhattans with them in the Abra Kedabra
and then a woman was like you're both so handsome
like it was like it was not
like one of the things we were like inferring
what's going on. It was like a very strong
sort of. We saw you from across the bar
and liked your vibe. It was just up
into that. That was not what happened.
We had to bail quickly because
it was very strange.
Wait you have had a stress test
not a marriage stress test at that
time but
on Disney property. That's
true yeah you're right. Do I throw it all away
for one night with the two
babes and what if
my friend Luke. One woman in it on two
men. Oh I thought there was a second.
No no she was with a male friend like male
husband maybe like we got
a vibe it was like her husband but then maybe
it was obvious like or they have
an understanding. So that night
the swing was not isolated
at Jelly Rolls.
It was at a few establishments
at the boardwalk. I think you mean
the Fins. Fins is where
it all goes down. What's that?
Fins. Which is where's Fins? The bar
at Walt Disney World's Swan.
Swan's the bigger one.
Cause that's the Convention Center hotel so everyone's
there. Everyone's there on business.
Everyone's going out on the corporate dime.
Things are happening at Fins.
Interesting. That's where you swing at Disney.
That is if you want to cheat on your spouse at Disney World
I always say go to Fins.
Go to Fins.
Garley's tips. Fins a lock.
It's just so many hands trying to flag down
the bartender and then they all had the sunburn
and they all had the tan of the ring
but no rings on their fingers.
It's a different
meaning of Fins up at that Fins.
Wow that's the content we have
not explored on this podcast.
Swinging tits. You stay there enough
and you know to like walk around the lobby
after midnight. Interesting.
We know what the deal is at the Holiday
Inn Burbank.
I think we talked about that
not long ago. We spent like a long time
at your birthday talking about
the Holiday Inn.
Things I never knew I
what do you mean it's gone? It's a different brand now.
Hotel Burbank.
It seems real beige-y, hippie.
We'll see. We haven't been over there.
Will the swinging possibilities be as strong
as we're praying that they are?
It seems like that top floor
bar that we liked so much I think they
realized like oh wow we have amazing
we could charge a lot of money for people to come
up here. I haven't read
done it yet. It's still
crappy carpet.
In Disneyland Paris is the place to have an affair
every quick service restaurant?
Any corner. Anywhere in the park.
I don't know.
I mean maybe one of those weird motels they have.
Like the little like Toy Story
themed rooms I think. On rides.
On small worlds. Anywhere
any surface. Do anything you want.
Anywhere you want. City of Love.
We were going for a while. I have one
little treat at the end here.
I got curious if there was any
promotional material for the opening
of the Armageddon attraction
or for the Disney Studios
park in general.
And I could not find any
in English or in French.
But I did find an hour long
opening special in a language
that after watching for a little bit I
determined to be Dutch.
This was made for Dutch
television. And it very
much in, boy you think you've done
like, you think you've seen it all in terms of crazy
Disney specials. And then you find
the 2002 Disney Studios opening.
This thing is so nuts.
It is the through line of it
is it is a group of children
who are all going
to experience different
they're experiencing all the wonderful
new attractions coming to Disney Paris.
There's five kids and five attractions.
Perfect. Don't need more than that.
That's all we got.
So it's very like, you know, the skits that
Regis would do but in all of the different
rides. So we end up with
this is how they represent Armageddon.
There is a scene
that is it's basically a madcap
ride through the armadillo
through the drilling machine that you
brought up earlier. That was
sitting out in front of the ride. That is not
a ride or something that you could do at
the park. So they depict
like you'll go on a madcap armadillo
chase. But in
fact this does not happen. Another thing that
couldn't happen is the person who appears in this.
There are there's celebrities throughout
the special but none none more
special than who you
meet in inside the armadillo.
Talking about Knight Rider, right?
Kit. Yeah. So
Well, I won't reveal the other celebrities shows up a little bit later.
But like
so basically, you know, like they bump
around. He's a
the kid Yoshi is driving
with kind of weird
Dutch glasses, very euro kid glasses.
It's a big crazy
ride but they ultimately land. David
hits the emergency stop.
And then this little scene occurs.
Yoshi is
handed a big Lego
looking blue key. Right.
Fit it in.
Whoa.
Then the key glows with
then the key is turned CGI and glows
and is magic. And then it cuts to who's coming up
next. Britney Spears. Original
Britney Spears appearance in this
stupid special. You know that shitty
Main Street, the indoor Main Street
in Disney Studios, Perry, that we haven't talked about.
I kind of like it.
Oh, really? OK. I just threw out she I don't
like that. I think it's a weird like
room. A little bit closer
to the room. Is that why you don't know?
No, different. It's not always flames.
He doesn't like being transported to Hollywood
without leaving. I like seeing
the big sign shutter bugs
and gunga din.
But she Britney performs
in front of shutter bugs and gunga. This is
Britney appearance. That's great. There is a
Destiny's Child performance.
Really? Oh my God. And
Andrea Bocelli. I think these are
syndicated maybe to other specials.
These aren't only for Dutch television. Right.
But Britney hands one
of the kids a magic key. She does
stuff for this Dutch special.
But there is but then it builds
to one final cameo at the
end. So you're out in front of the park
and there is
some like big glowy mechanism
and the kids have all assembled. They all have a magic
key. And then
here's the culmination of the
special. What have all the keys been
for? Let's
find out.
Cuba Gooding Jr. for the people
listening. Cuba Gooding Jr. is
a hundred feet tall
and a ghost.
He is God.
I mean. He is the
almighty. Yeah. Because it's heavenly
life. I made you cars so that I could
see a world where everyone suffered.
I don't know why. It's also
hi. My name
is Cuba Gooding Jr. Well if they don't
know who you are, if you're American, then
the name is not going to impress these
children. Kids with big Jerry Maguire fans?
I guess. It doesn't feel like they've met
because they don't say wow. They just kind of like
listen attentively. They're meeting a strange
like if we showed up in
the Netherlands and said
my name is Mike Carlson
doesn't mean anything to unless they're
a pipe. Unless there's a pipe. They might be a pipe.
They're a right listener. Could be. Do they like
screen junkies? You may
know me from screen junkies
or for being God.
Then it cuts to this
weird other angle behind Cuba. So they did
have coverage on this and the kids
are staring the wrong way. They were
not told to look up in the sky.
So anyway, he resolves
this plot here. Each of you
is a truly outstanding individual
and I'm glad to hear you still have those keys
you found today. Because we
have one more surprise for you. Oh my God, he's so big.
Yeah, he's like Zordon in Power Rangers.
Now hold it tightly to your keys.
Now take it out of the way.
What? Those golden keys are now yours.
They are keys to the studios
for each and every one of you to keep.
For the rest of your
lives.
Congratulations.
What?
Can you clarify something for me?
You don't have to reward it with
lifetime access after you bravely
stuck your thumbs in a leaky
dam.
I, uh, yeah,
this is quite a scene, isn't it?
Cubicating Jr. is God. He
takes keys that were already
magic and glowing.
Makes them not magic anymore.
He turns them into literal keys. Well, they all turn gold.
And now they're
actual keys that they have to
keep. But they get them into the, I guess
essentially they have free admission to this
bad theme park. Maybe.
Or they just have a key to it. But they're actors.
Yeah. So there's not,
it's not like they want to contest, right?
Unless, is that maybe the premise? Maybe they're presented
as real kids. And again, I don't speak
Dutch, so I don't know some of the ins and outs.
Well, there's like, there's those stories that appear like
oh, so and so won like a lifetime
pass to Disneyland or something. Yeah.
Which like still works and
unless JPEG's taking it away.
I gotta make a reservation.
That was maybe the first thing you did? They have to start
at DCA.
Get a reservation. Look, we gotta
have rules. Uh, but I wonder
yeah, are they presenting that as if the kids
can get in forever? Maybe? I don't know.
If you're one of those five Dutch children and you're
grown, uh, let us know
do the keys work? Was Britney
Spears exciting to meet? Was Hasselhoff
exciting to be in an armadillo with?
Hasselhoff in the armadillo
is really,
that feels like you made that video, Scott.
Yeah, yeah, that's the most of my, like
these bad little, uh, you know, I
think they should have put the kit car from
Knight Rider in. Him having to drop.
I love, he's such a cheeseball
that his acting
is just speaking clearly.
Same thing. The act, acting
is the person who enunciates the most.
Isn't that right? Wouldn't you agree? Um,
yeah, this is, boy, the special.
Boy, oh boy. Wow, good find.
Yeah, check out that special. Keep a gooding Jr.'s
god and, uh, I don't know,
as he should be. Yeah, yeah, well earned
and, Hasselhoff, sorry to interrupt,
Hasselhoff though, I'm trying to think, was it, uh,
he's been in one other pre-show video, is it for
that, um, um, Europe park? That weird boat ride
and yeah, yeah, I think so. Yeah, I believe
so. It was like, it was the night,
it was the kit boats. You're about
to board a kit boat. Yeah, but they don't have
the rights, that's the park with no rights, and I can't
think of the name of it already, but they had no movie
rights. There's like knockoff Doc Brown
in the parade. You're about to get on
the Prince of Boats. And it was like they had a tower
of terror. Yes.
As well. Called that, but it's not
just a drop tower. So their Armageddon
is called, like,
Ultimate Comet 2000.
Right.
Yes.
They have to shuffle it every six months to
make sure no one noticed. Yeah,
yeah, yeah. Keep changing the name of it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, just keep because something might
be called that at this point. Yeah.
That was the one with the, sorry to keep,
that was the Flashdance show?
I believe so.
Movieland Italy?
We talked about this bizarre, there's an entire park
that is like this Armageddon,
if you want, as far as I could tell.
This seems like the aesthetics of the Armageddon
attraction, but a full
where, yeah, they
basically, they start using IP in
the park, like,
and this is in Italy, Movieland Italy.
They'll do like Batman and the Joker and
Mary Poppins until the IP rights
someone notices from it.
Pull it, pull it, get it out.
Yeah.
The bride from Kill Bill
was walking around the lot
with the orange jumpsuit.
Licensed by Quentin, I'm sure.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, anyways,
I also, now I'm wondering if like
Cuba took this as,
if a hundred foot tall god Cuba
took this as the, like,
I don't know, maybe now I can like,
is there any other hundred foot god
creatures I could swing with?
Oh.
Good question. Now, kids, do you
see any other giant swagger,
any other translucent giants walking
around here?
Thanks, you're very special.
Appreciate it.
Well, thank you for taking us on this journey
through this.
Thank you for allowing me to relive and
immediately forget everything we've been
through. And it's gone. It's immediately gone
except for the marital trauma.
It'll be fine.
It's worked out so far. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yes, yeah. We all,
our marriages have survived our trip to Armageddon
and you survived Podcast The Ride.
Thanks so much for joining us again.
Let's exit through a leg
gift shop. Is there anything you'd
like to plug? Yeah,
my podcast, very amusing.
We're back every week.
I haven't made a
itinerary or schedule, so we're
winging it. But so far so good.
We got episodes. They're coming out.
It's great. And then you can find me on social
and all the social medias at Carly
Weisel. Fantastic.
And yeah, thanks so much for being
back again. Great to do it IRL.
Of course. It's so nice to be
in person and still distanced.
Oh, great.
It's a comfortable, less claustrophobic than a
Russian spaceship.
You can, for us, you can find us on the socials
at Podcast The Ride. Merch is available in our
T-Public store and for three bonus episodes every
month. Check out Podcast The Ride, the second
gate at Patreon.com slash Podcast
The Ride. I'm a little hankering to do
Cars Road Trip.
Cars Road Trip's been calling out to me.
This, this, the Smilin,
the big Smilin tanker
is his old world lights on fire.
A lot of messages about accepting
your demise.
This park. The whole park.
Yeah. You know what? It's, I applaud
this park for getting us comfortable
with the idea of death.
Yeah. I found the
person, there's a theory, of course,
with the cars. Yeah, sure. Yeah.
This is just their hypothesis or their
questioning the fact that cars still have all the things
that you would need for a human. They have handles,
they have windows. They lock.
They, you hear in the first thing, you hear cars
go like boop boop. Yeah.
So there's, so basically, we'll talk about
this when we do Cars Road Trip very soon, I guess,
is that this person's guess
is that humans evolved into cars.
Whoa.
Wow.
What are the intermediate
steps? Those are some weird,
that evolution has some very awkward
periods. Yes, I agree.
But yes, the humans are
the cars. Maybe not evolved. Maybe like
there was something, I don't know,
a curse was put on the earth or something. Like something
happened or Jay Leno. Aren't there
too few cars? Like there would have had
to have been a genocide?
Like there had to have been something. Because there's not
that many cars in cars. In the cars?
Hmm. That's a good question. What is the population
of the earth in cars?
And if it's all cars, it's not that many.
Yeah, because you don't see a ton. Well, we
don't get a sense of the full world.
There's not even traffic in those films, is there?
In the second one? It depends. Sometimes
on the way to the women's restroom
is what they pause. That's the traffic. Right.
I can't think about it.
Yeah. So. Didn't we
say, I had the theory in our Late Shift
episode on the second gate that Jay
Leno has sex with the cars?
Yeah. How Jay Limo,
his character, was produced.
Is that the literal offspring of
He's the missing link. Jay Leno,
yes. The key to the cars universe
is that Jay Leno had sex
with one of his classic cars and miraculously
the car gave birth
to Jay's
baby. So he would be
alive. I got the miracle of life.
Have you heard about this? And he has so many
cars and he's poly
with his cars.
If we're mapping over the... I can't get locked down.
I'm married to one woman. Why would I be married to one car?
He's monogamous with Mavis,
but poly with the cars. I got a thousand
hole passes. His hole passes
every car.
One year for Christmas
she gave it to him. On one side it said hole pass
and on the other side it said every car.
So Cars is a movie about Jay
Leno's kids.
Everyone you're looking at is descended
from Jay Leno. Yes. Okay.
I'm not super knowledgeable about Planet of the Apes,
but is Caesar the one who...
Is Caesar the ape who
gains intelligence from Jay?
By his speaks. Yeah. Okay.
No!
With that by saying no it opened up
the hole. Right, right.
It was Jay saying, yes! I will
have sex with the car.
Eventually his head will
open real big like
Beetlej and it just honk.
Beep beep.
When he's still alive in
300 years. Why is he?
Oh, because he's a car. Yeah.
In the parking garage
slash ashes of flappers
at the Magic and Comedy Club.
Well, that's what that whole
episode is going to be like.
We're off to the races.
Okay, thanks for
listening everybody.
Forever
Dog
This has been a Forever Dog
Production. Executive produced
by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett
Bohm, Joe Sileo,
and Alex Ramsey. For more
original podcasts, please visit
foreverdogpodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows
on Apple Podcasts,
Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest
Forever Dog news by following us
on Twitter and Instagram
at Forever Dog Team
and liking our page on Facebook.