Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, the second gate,
which is different than the Podcast the Ride, the main feed,
just as Polo by Ralph Lauren is different
by the U.S. Polo Association clothing line.
I'm Jason Scharton, joined is always by Mike Carlson.
Have you ever encountered this?
Like you go to a Marshall's and there's like,
wait, there's Polo shirts and then there's U.S. Polo.
I guess I know what you're saying,
but this is never really a conscious thought I have.
So wait, you're saying that there's a,
like a normal Polo shirt.
Okay, bring Scott Gertner in here.
Scott, maybe you've encountered this.
He's a Polo guy.
But Polo shirts are, it doesn't have to be one
of those brands to be a Polo shirt, does it?
I don't know about the exact qualifications,
but if you notice a lot of store,
you'll see this U.S. Polo brand.
And some of the logos will say not associated
with Polo by Ralph Lauren,
because Polo by Ralph Lauren came along later.
And like, this was a big like issue.
And this isn't even today's topic.
I should look into this more.
I'm just gonna definitely bring this up later,
just in reference to the fact that I've been wanting
to do a second gate about a character named Polo Bear.
Of course.
Is this coming up on the show or did you just text about that?
I texted about it, but I think I briefly mentioned it
on one episode in the last year or two.
But it's not been a runner,
it's not been a continuing runner or anything.
But Polo Bear is a bear that has different like outfits
and you can buy it on a sweater for $650.
So.
Let's start buying them and then we can do the episode.
Well, we'll each buy one a month
and then we'll be able to talk about it.
Every outfit.
So yeah, no, we're not talking about fashion today.
We're not talking about bears today.
We're talking about a man in the 30s
who played a fancy sport for rich people
and then he got hurt.
Yes.
Vertebrae.
And that sounds like not a lot, right?
But keep in mind that that man is Walt Disney.
Oh.
Keep in mind that some of the things
that spun out of this injury changed the world.
Right.
The weaver of dreams, the keeper of stories,
Walt Disney's world famous polo injury
would go on to lead to the modern American
theme park industry.
That's right.
Yeah.
This time, Walt's polo injury,
I think we rushed this one into production
maybe more than other topics.
Yeah, yeah.
We discovered it.
We realized this had to happen.
And you know, look, I came from the world
of viral videos, right?
With my YouTube and my funnier die.
So I know the importance of a grabby title.
And gentlemen, I hope you're prepared to have gone
super viral with the title Walt's Polo Injury.
I am, yeah.
And this is gonna be everywhere.
This is gonna be on the front page of Poe.
Has Kevin Perjurer done a Walt's polo injury video?
No, right?
He's mentioned it probably, but it has come up.
But this does come up a lot.
It is like one sentence in like
quick Walt Disney biographies or like Walt's interest.
Well, it just came up because we were talking about
the story living by Disney,
the incredibly exciting development
and that they're gonna build Cotino in Rancho Mirage
and they're gonna finally tribute Walt's special connection
to the Palm Springs area that we've heard so much about
for these many years.
It seems like, okay, so there's just been like,
I'd say a glut lately of Walt mythology
that has suddenly risen to the surface out of nowhere.
There's that, there's Walt's special lamp, of course,
that means so much to Zeddy tomorrow.
There's one that I didn't even get to
in the Toontown episode that we just did,
which is that, you guys might have read this,
that one of the things that's going into the new Toontown
is a special tree.
And that is a tree that is modeled after Walt's dreaming tree,
which he of course had in Missouri.
We all know about the dreaming tree.
I actually did not see the dreaming tree.
He would stare up at the dreaming tree
and imagine we could tell stories and characters.
I did read that paragraph about the dreaming tree
and I'm like, this is like the fucking yellow cake
uranium in Iraq.
This is like when they're like,
there's actually uranium coming in through back channels
and they're building, I'm like,
you made up out of whole, this is total bullshit.
This tree in Missouri.
I saw somebody was upset
because I compared Han Solo's dice,
which somebody has pointed out
that Han Solo's dice are visible in A New Hope.
They're hanging somewhere, but he never mentioned,
he never touches it, he never gives it a little kiss.
We're not talking about Luke's belt.
So what I'm gonna say, it is all like Han's dice
in the sense that they pulled something from,
just like they saw it,
they saw a picture of Walt with a tree
and maybe he said it was dreaming tree, maybe he didn't.
And now they're sort of retconning it into being a big deal.
That little thing, STR has always been on the tie,
smoke tree, it stands for smoke tree ranch.
Now we have to really up his connection to smoke tree ranch.
Anyway, this has all been fascinating to learn,
but what worries me is that for the Disney company,
Walt mythology is a precious resource
and we are losing it by the day.
They are running out of Walt things
and that's what powers the company.
It is fossil fuels to them
and we're burning acres of mental real estate each year.
They're like more and more and more.
At this rate, we're gonna lose Walt's entire,
there's gonna be nothing left.
And they just have to be careful.
They can't get greedy.
So if Walt had like a special napkin
or a special belt buckle,
or a magic plate, a tea saucer,
save that for 2028.
Yeah, you're right.
They have to really ration out the Walt mythology.
But what they probably could start doing
is the same thing they're doing to Star Wars
where in A New Hope, there's a line about
a lot of who died for the plans, spies or whatever.
There's a line, a throw off line in New Hope
about how they got the Death Star plans
and then they made Rogue One,
which is a movie based on one single line.
So maybe it's like if Walt was in a special
and he's talking to like a short sleeve dress shirt Imagineer
and he leaves frame for a second,
they can start adding story to what he did there.
It was Walt went up and he touched this wall,
the special wall he had,
when he would shoot the specials
and it was his not dreaming wall,
it was his, it was a comfort wall.
His Enchant, Walt's wall of enchantment.
Walt's wall of enchantment
and they've recreated this wall of enchantment
for you to lean on.
Yeah.
In a new.
It's a freestanding development,
like in the middle of Nebraska.
Now you have to go drive to the wall.
Is there anything to do with the walls or a ride
or a place I can stay?
No, you touch the wall,
maybe you get a little enchantment
and live your Walt story and that will be $250.
Yeah, exactly.
There you go.
So like stuff like that or Walt's pointer
when he's pointing at the Epcot thing,
he's got like a long stick.
Oh, Walt's wonderful stick.
He loved this stick.
He used to point at things all the time with it.
And now.
His pointing stick.
His dream.
Point the way to the future.
It was more than pointing.
It was a dream.
He's pointing to.
Yeah, it was a dream stick.
Walt's dream stick.
There is a detail in this story
that they could scale pretty quickly
at all of the deluxe resort spas
and call it the five o'clock special
or Walt's five o'clock special.
Ha ha.
That's good.
You could do that tomorrow.
The closest thing,
because you're talking about when he would get
his pulmonary worked on.
Yes or?
Yes.
Yeah, I'm sure we'll go through it chronologically.
Yeah, we'll talk about it in a second.
But there was a time.
In the last chapter.
There was a regular time when he would have it worked on.
So the closest and then he would have a drink,
I believe at the same time.
Yeah, a glass of scotch.
The five o'clock special is the combo
of getting your back rubbed.
It's a back massage and a glass of scotch.
And supposedly that's what Walt needed at 5 p.m. every day
to be able to drive home to his house.
Jeez.
It's the detail that I kept seeing come up.
And I was like, oh yeah, I guess that LA traffic.
The injury is way worse, I think, than I knew.
Walt's physical state seems a lot worse
than I knew.
But this is what, you know, if Disney can spin off
every object that Walt touched
or every piece of his story into something,
it's time for us to grab one
that I don't think they're gonna hit
and that's Walt's polo injury.
And I'm excited we're doing it.
Yes, it's good.
I mean, they're gonna hear this
and they're gonna steal it from us, I think.
But we'll at least have.
You know, they should plant the flag here.
As we said, the hypothesis, the theory,
that I think Jason, you said in short a couple weeks ago,
is that it leads to the parks in a way.
And I'd say that's true,
but it's a little more complicated than that
from what I found.
I'm curious what we all thought of the story.
Yeah, it is a little more complicated.
I'd love to start by just talking about polo,
which I learned a little bit about.
Did everyone learn?
Oh please, you know, it occurred to me that I should
and I didn't and it's in philosophy.
Yeah, because the background is very,
it's like a big piece of Hollywood history,
just kind of lost to time.
Called like, basically like the social networking of its day
was playing polo with all these other rich guys.
You'd play polo and then you'd make deals.
And then, yeah, you would, you know,
make movies or whatever.
You're bringing your, this is a sport on a horse,
first of all.
Yeah, you're basically.
All mallets and horses.
Yeah, I was trying to think,
cause like some people were saying it's like golf on a horse,
but it's almost more like action croquet on a horse
or something.
Like you're.
Yeah, cause it's mallets.
It's intense.
Yeah, so you're on a horse holding a mallet
and there's a ball and you're trying to just like,
as if it's soccer or something,
get the ball down the field through a goal, essentially.
And that's the one thing I haven't looked,
I've never seen footage of this in my life.
It is a, there's a goal over here, goal over there.
You got a sport.
Yes, and I'm sure somebody,
I'm sure I'll get something wrong,
but there are four players on a team.
So it's four on four.
So you need four people and four horses for a team.
Well, and backup horses.
And backup horses.
Yes.
There are like, I guess you would call it like,
there are, I guess you call them like periods,
like there are, they're called chukkas
and they're seven minutes long.
Do you have chukka written down?
You have, you have just explained something that comes up.
Okay, okay.
I'll get to it.
You've, I had a big question about something.
So you can, you can play a match of like,
between like four and eight chukkas.
That's what I understand.
And then it's basically who, how many,
whoever has the most points.
And then there are four players.
Number one, the player number one on your team
is like the main offense guy.
I was trying to figure out who I would be on a polo team.
Number two is like similar,
but not quite maybe like not as good on offense,
but still pretty good.
Number three on the team is the tactical leader.
And they're doing a lot of hitting the ball to one and two.
So they're setting up people to make, you know,
shots or goals.
So one is the star who drives it.
Who don't, that's a Jora.
It's Michael Jordan, the ball on the team.
Okay.
And then number four is like defense.
That's probably like the last line of defense too.
So they're whacking the horses in the face with the mallet.
Yes.
That, well, you're not supposed to do that.
That's a foul.
There are penalty hits.
You're also like, it's very confusing and I can't,
I'm sure I won't be able to explain it that well,
but you're not supposed to like,
kind of railroad or like T-bone a horse on your horse.
You're supposed to, there's supposed to be,
there's like a gentlemanly agreement of like,
you kind of ride your horse next to the person
and try to get the ball away versus like,
you can't just run in front of the horse with your horse
and the horse flies.
Oh, thank God.
It's still crazy.
It's an insane, crazy sport.
Yeah, it's a bunch of rich guys with blunt instruments
riding horses at each other.
It's literally like, it's like a,
it's a cousin of the joust in some ways.
Yeah, wow.
Yes.
Cavalrys were- In only last century.
Yeah.
It was one of the, I feel like every sport
at some point was called the sport of kings,
but this is how they trained like horse mounted,
like cavalries.
Right.
Oh geez.
So yeah, I only did a brief explainer on this
cause I did not know what it is,
but it's, they're still played in places,
but it used to be very,
there were so many polo fields in Los Angeles.
25 was the number I kept coming across.
I saw that I think.
Wow.
And there's little remnants of it,
like the Polo Lounge, the famous bar
at the Beverly Hills Hotel.
Oh, okay.
I believe it takes its name from the popularity of polo.
On the story living episode, I said like,
oh, in Coachella, they're, they call the,
where the music festival is held,
those are the polo grounds because,
I don't know if it's still used for polo,
but it was used for polo.
That is not where Walt's injury occurred.
I was wrong about that.
Okay, yeah.
But he was an avid polo enthusiast.
I'm not sure I know where.
I guess we'll figure out where,
but there were a bunch around here
and he used ones around here.
That's I think what's strange is that they would be like,
this is a facility that is golf and tennis
and this thing with mallets and horses.
And horses, yeah.
Right.
Like golf and tennis still,
we kept those, very common,
polo a little bit, a little more complicated.
Yeah.
Maybe the way in is to talk about how Walt's
found himself playing polo.
Sure, yeah.
Which was the, his runaway popularity in the 1930s,
but also, so much success, but also so much stress.
And so much is being asked of him.
That the job is getting more and more stressful.
In addition, very sadly, I didn't know
that there were two miscarriages in his.
Oh sure.
Or his wife, Lillian.
By the way, I'm pulling a bunch of info
from the article by Wade Sampson and Mouse Planet,
just so I'm not stealing things he's saying.
Sure.
But Walt's doctor suggested that, oh wait.
He had a nervous breakdown, don't forget.
Oh yes, yes, suffering one of his infamous.
Infamous.
Nervous breakdown.
Hell of a breakdown, I went to pieces,
as he was quoted saying it.
Oh man.
Walt.
This is not what we're used to seeing,
the happy guy who Tinkerbell lands on his shoulder
and he tells us what the submarine ride's gonna be.
Are they gonna.
What a dark chapter.
Is there gonna be some sort of place in Katino
where it's like, come here and relax
from having one of Walt's nervous breakdowns
that you have around.
It might be, maybe they are subtly aiming it to people.
They have to show footage of people clinking wine glasses,
but it's secretly like,
you're going through a divorce, are you good?
You're having a Walt's breakdown.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, are you having an infamous breakdown?
Walt's got you covered, he's been here.
I imagine people in these days,
everyone had a nervous breakdown once a week.
Maybe that's what.
Well it was those days.
It was those days.
It was a rougher time.
People, it's only a decade plus back from World War I,
he was in World War I.
Sure.
And they obviously didn't call it PTSD at the time.
I think they were just still called it shell shocked.
Sure.
To come back freaked out and broken from the war.
Yeah. Yeah.
And he was shell shocked from driving a car around a little
and meeting Ray Kroc.
Oh yeah.
Walt was broken from all this.
And then all these other things happened
and he's so successful, he is starting to lose his mind.
So then this is what, I was about to just read this
and I forgot what was coming.
This is the copy from Mouse Planet.
Walt's doctor suggested that Mickey Mouse's father,
I don't know if we went through this.
Yeah we did, yeah.
The weirdness of that phrase.
Yeah.
Here I just run into it like wow.
Mickey's daddy, yeah.
You didn't like that I think.
Father is, I still find father weird
but daddy obviously jumps at the same time.
Well but now daddy, the whole weird thing with daddy
and like two meanings, like that's not just this problem.
You know, that's always gonna be weird.
Cause we can call Josh tomorrow daddy or zaddy
but that's a different connotation
from calling Walt Mickey's daddy.
Cause we're saying that in a fun way
and the other one is like a cheeky dirty way.
Context clues, I think context clues.
I mean I understand what you're saying.
I'm finding all of it weird.
I, there's no daddy that you said in that sentence
that wasn't bizarre to me.
No, no, I didn't like one of those.
I didn't like the daddies.
That's why you insist on your child calling you
papa, papa.
That'd be fine, I'll go with papa.
Papa is good.
I like, you know what I like?
I like the English or British thing
of calling like grandma gran.
I'm way into that, gran.
Gran.
Yeah.
It's very like.
Well then when you say like that, it sounds formal
but like if it's gran, you know, it's like,
that's less formal.
Are you gonna like, wait, British,
so a British accent is required.
No, I think you can call it gran.
Hey gran.
What do you think about gran?
Say it in a sentence though.
I'm going to gran's house.
Yes, I think it'll.
Do you want to go to gran's house?
Unless it's regularly used.
Well it'll have to be, yeah.
I feel like they call Gene Smart that in Mayor of Easttown.
Sure.
I feel like, I ain't gonna be home in time for dinner
but gran'll be there.
Gran'll put something in the oven.
Gran, you know.
Look at this voice.
Yeah, look at that voice.
What's the region of the.
That's the deliration.
That's the Delaware County.
I was curious about that actually recently.
If you have any remnants of language,
maybe the listener, people who've listened to you a ton
might even know something that you have
that you don't even know you have.
I have a lot.
Yeah, wooder kind of goes in and out for water.
When I shot one of those commercials a few years ago,
they were like really like, how is this guy saying gas?
And so it had to get to a point
where I'm just doing a million takes and going,
okay, say ass.
Okay, now add a G, gas.
And it sounds so weird to me but it's like, got it.
It sounds normal.
It's like you feel like how props
don't look like props in movies.
I guess gas sounds bizarre
but it's gonna be perfect on screen, you'll see.
Yeah, and I ran into someone else who had been on
and they're like, oh they made me say cool-lada
a lot of different ways.
And I was like, well that's like a proprietary thing,
I guess, but I apparently say gasoline, very strange.
I guess I hear it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Gasoline.
They made you say ass.
Say ass.
And then say gas.
Everyone else has been dismissed.
I am like in an empty room in a house
and they're just trying to get the line
so they can overlay it over the footage.
Oh geez, an idiot, wow, wow.
Well yeah, well Walt also stressed from film shoots
and the like.
Yeah.
He needs to take, his doctor suggests
that Mickey Mouse's father take up some form of exercise
to kick it over it to help relieve the stress.
So Walt tried a bunch of things
and this is a little montage I'd like to see
of wrestling, how is that gonna relieve stress?
How old is he at this point?
Yeah, it's a good question.
Well I don't know, maybe still late 20s
but wrestling and boxing are not gonna,
well I guess people box as an event.
Then golf, but golf drove him crazy
in the way golf drives people crazy.
It's a precise sport.
Right, does anyone amateur wrestle in their 20s for fun?
That's not something that happens anymore.
And that kind of, we know this wasn't fun wrestling.
This is like.
No, it was not.
It was not going to a wrestling carnival.
It was Greco-Roman probably.
But do people do that in their 20s every day?
Hey Bill, you wanna go wrestling?
Nobody does that anymore.
I feel like they were playing all sorts of sports
we think are old timey back then.
At the club, you'd go down to the club or the YMCA.
I'm sure you could hop in anything.
And the way that in college there's,
oh there's intramural leagues.
There's fun run kind of leagues.
Well that's different.
If you're in college, I'm just saying
once you get out of a setting like that,
when is the last time you would just for fun
in the way you would play a pickup game of basketball
or play tennis, you would go
and amateur wrestle with a friend.
Yeah, unclear.
It's a lot.
It's like a big commitment is what I'm saying.
Let's go like grunt and let me get my face
way up in your armpit.
Yeah.
Let's elbow each other a bunch.
That only happens at like a bachelor party
when somebody gets like out of control or something.
Where do you end up like amateur wrestling your friend?
That's for restraint.
Yeah.
You have to like put someone down essentially.
Get in the lift.
You're going back to the hotel.
Right.
Going back to Caesar's.
I mean, I guess we could start it up again.
I kind of liked amateur wrestling in high school.
Sure.
Jason, were you all right in it?
I tried it in middle school when there would be like,
there was a round of like intramural,
like try out different sports.
And I just got hosed immediately.
I was always little.
Like everyone hit throw spurts.
And then I'm kind of like, you know.
Scott, you ever do it?
Probably in one set.
In gym?
Never again.
There was, we had to take it in gym.
We had to do it.
No, you guys didn't have to do that?
I think they did like one or two class sessions
of like holds and stuff in gym.
But like, man, there was like one padded,
I think a wrestling practice room above the gym.
And a handful of times, my gym class got put in there
and they're like, all right, we're playing dodge ball.
And it's like, it was the size of this garage.
Those dodge balls hurt.
However you got hit with them.
Like, oh, it was just a bunch of 14 year old boys
just wanging at each other with.
Wanging.
Just wanging.
It's just, just wham.
Yeah.
The other detail about Walt's athletic pursuits
was that due to his, you know, awful childhood,
he was, he didn't play game.
Like he, it was said that he was not athletic
nor was he coordinated.
So.
His brother was worried about him
cause he said he was not physically gifted, I read.
Yes, but he did have.
But he was aggressive.
He did have what WWE would call ruthless aggression.
That's right.
This is so clearly a bad recipe.
This is meant to be stress relief.
Yeah.
But in like, he just, he has to,
but he has to make up for a lack of talent
by just like going at people, wanging them.
Wanging them.
He's going and wanging them.
And it seems like he started with horseback riding.
He got into the outdoors,
the outdoorsiness of horseback riding.
And then polo, it's just like,
he would say you're playing golf on a horse.
Like you said, Mike.
Yeah.
He was too, he was too early.
Cause I'm sure he would have loved mixed martial arts.
I'm sure he was kind of like UFC guy.
Walt would have been a UFC guy.
That's true.
That's the stress role.
That's how you get your aggression out now.
But he wasn't, you didn't have to bring a horse into it.
Okay. I take this, I guess there's not amateur wrestling,
but there are MMA gyms popping up and there's,
That's true.
They're not too far away.
So I guess that's kind of-
It seems more fun.
I would think.
Yeah.
So Walt would stroll in to the Sherman brothers
who were really composing something and be like,
well, I just choked a guy out with a triangle hold.
You just put your arm on the carotid artery
and went out like a light.
But we have to remember he hated carnivals.
Right. That's true.
He likely would not have been exposed to
what was called catch wrestling.
The early days of like wrestling.
Catch a catch can, yeah.
Yeah. With like carnies or like,
I'll wrestle whoever's in the crowd sort of,
and all of this, the outcomes predetermined,
you know, but it's like modern wrestling,
but a lot of holds, still a lot of very unpleasant,
like physical holds.
So like-
You're saying he,
he did probably go to carnivals though.
So he just may not have enjoyed it.
And you're saying he wouldn't have had an affection for-
He wouldn't have had an affection.
Classic professional wrestling, which was-
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, hold based and also yeah,
big con to try to con the audience. Yeah.
So you don't see Walt in like a,
that kind of unitard that used to be the garb of-
Right. I see, yeah.
But if, yeah, I can imagine him though,
in modern MMA gloves and trunks
with like an endorsement on the side,
Gus Disney on the side.
Yeah, with one of those bottles
that has the metal sphere in it,
like the blender bottles,
like drinking a mix of protein shake and Denison's chili.
Walt with his eye just swollen up and like bleeding.
Like, well, great match today.
Great match today, Will Rogers.
Somebody could-
Yeah, so he started source back writing
and then that leads into Polo,
where you can get this aggression out.
He started like bringing animators into this.
There were other people in the studio interested in it.
But as you said, Mike, there was the big social
and the networking component of it.
So he starts doing it, I think largely at Riviera,
which is the big fancy country club
that's in Pacific Palisades
that is primarily golf, some tennis,
and I guess had Polo at this time.
And yeah, Will Rogers is around.
I saw Jackie Gleason.
I saw Spencer Tracy.
That might be a modern Riviera club.
Cause I saw Riviera is where Paul Riviera,
I forget where the middle school or high school in LA,
like on the border of like WeHo Beverly Hills.
Oh, is that not the same Riviera?
I think, yeah, I think there were,
there might've, there's a Riviera now
and I think there was a Riviera then.
Gotcha.
Yeah, cause LA proper,
you just be filled with Polo fields.
Yeah, one of the main ones he practiced,
that was really near the studio,
which if you're in LA is where the Gelsons on Hyperion is.
And then you keep going Hyperion and Riverside,
which I think is now just Griffith,
like of some field or something.
But that was where he would go practice Polo with animators.
That's fun.
So that's where you would go, I guess, to see the stars,
really in the old days,
cause they all seem to be out there.
I see them like whacking each other,
whacking each other and then endangering horses.
That is such a crazy thing to do.
Like I just am putting myself in the mindset
of getting on a horse and then playing
where I have to like navigate the horse
on a field with seven other horses
while I'm hitting a ball.
I don't know how I ever get into the head space
to be able to do that.
Yeah, and also make sure you don't clobber Spencer Tracy.
Spencer Tracy, I read an avid Polo enthusiast.
The studios would beg him,
please stop playing this hyper-physical violent sport.
And so he would schedule games under aliases.
He had to lie to do his Polo thing?
The man had a lot going on as we've learned in the past.
Geez.
Wait, what was his thing?
What Spencer Tracy's issue?
He showed up in that guy's biography.
Oh, oh, oh, full service.
He was gnawing.
Oh, he was gnawing.
Oh, okay, he was gnawing.
I forgot who the gnar was.
He was a gnar and a winger.
He was gnawing, but he was a devout Catholic
so he never divorced his wife.
So he was never technically married to Catherine Hepburn.
But yeah.
Also, yeah, like imagine you've had like a huge meat lunch.
You're drunk off your ass
and now you're getting on the horse.
Get on a horse with a weapon.
With a weapon.
With like a Looney Tunes weapon.
Yeah.
And this is what these guys are doing all the time.
Next to a mount,
because I'm sure the Equestrian neighborhood,
it was just part of Burbank with stables and horse trails.
Like, yeah, I'm sure that came into play.
And the Disney studio is right there.
Yeah, yeah.
Did anybody find Walt's horse's name?
Oh.
I found a list.
I don't think I did.
I received Dave Smith Disney archivist.
Oh, sure.
And Jason look alike apparently.
Soon.
Playing him in a movie soon.
He has seven, just like the dwarves, there were seven.
Okay, let's go through them.
June, Slim, Nava, Aero,
Partner, Taki, and Tommy.
Anybody got a favorite?
Taki I guess.
Taki, yeah.
Partner's pretty good.
We love Taki.
Partner is second.
But like these aren't the best names in the world.
But also other places said he had a dozen horses.
Wow.
And those, so there might be five
whose names are lost at times.
His illegitimate horses?
Yeah, because he did go on to sell,
he sold everything eventually.
Right.
Yeah, do we know what age he stopped doing this?
I guess after the injury, is that immediately?
I guess.
Yeah, it would have to be then.
We're heading into the late 30s when it seems to happen.
Because that is what the article sort of implied,
but I wonder if he ever like snuck back up on there.
Maybe.
You never know, yeah.
He's got his girls again.
Let's get that girls, Tommy's boy, I think.
So where does this go?
Walt is pony crazy.
He's winging at Spencer Tracy and Jackie Gleason.
Seems like Robert Stack was around.
Yes, I saw that.
Oh, isn't that weird?
Not sure how, yeah, a host of unsolved mysteries.
I'm like, does that add up age-wise?
He would have been around.
He was old when it was on, when Unsolved Mysteries was on.
He's passed away a while ago at this point, I think.
Yeah, I think so.
But anyway, well, how do we get into this?
Well, he got Roy into it.
And Roy, out ahead of what happens,
is like, maybe you should not do this.
Yeah.
Maybe you should.
The common thing Roy would say to him about everything.
Sometimes that stood in the way of Walt Disney World.
But in other cases, yeah, maybe he was,
this feels very analog to motorcycles
and when you got a bad feeling about your friend
motorcycling and it's hardly confirmed.
Yeah, yeah.
But Walt really went all in,
in addition to buying the horse,
he had a practice cage at the studio.
He had a practice cage in his backyard.
Practice cage.
Like a cage with a fake wooden horse and a goal
that you would like sit on the fake wooden horse.
And eventually I read, his home one abandoned
and his children don't have much memories of his polo time.
They just know like, don't go near the polo cage,
the abandoned cage is filled with black spider.
That's the detail I saw.
Wow, wall cage.
We're gonna talk about Walt's cage is gonna be a thing too.
Yeah, Walt's cage.
I put toilet on the short list.
You're gonna collect all the info about the toilet.
If you've never lived in Southern California,
yeah, black widow spider is much more common
than you would think.
Like if you have a garage or a shed or something.
Watch out everyone.
Oh yeah, keep an eye out.
So Roy has sounded the alarm, there is potential trouble.
And then, stop me if you wanna tell us in a different way,
but here's where I found it.
Okay, here's the prime example of what scared Roy Disney.
Always pushing himself, Walt eventually wanted to play
with the better players, because these actors,
I think even among them, he's not the best.
But he's kind of, he was trying to match skill levels.
But then, but Walt, with his incredible gumption,
he wants to play with the best of the best.
And there was a South American team, the Argentines.
And Walt wanted to practice with the Argentines.
Actor Robert Stack, remember,
and I guess you gotta do it as like,
anytime the Argentines would come in,
they would bring their horses with them.
The reason they came, most of these great polo players
was to sell the horses and make a lot of money,
which they did.
You could see some of them red hots in our movie profession
and I think Walt was among them,
bidding these fantastic sums for these magnificent horses.
So the Argentines are, I mean, what does that mean?
They're trying to sell the horses,
they're hustling horses to these Hollywood guys
who are impressed with their skills.
But Walt can't play with the Argentines,
he's no Argentine, he's not good enough
to play against the Argentines.
That's what Roy told him.
Roy knew.
Stay away from the Argentines.
Now I'm missing some info here.
Is the injury against the Argentines?
That's what I read.
Okay.
Yeah, that's what I read as well, Actor Riviero.
He played with them.
Or this is with them, but I'm not sure if it means against.
But a ball was struck by one of the players,
it smashed into Walt and knocked him from the mount.
And then, yeah, that's when he,
I guess it crushed his four cervical vertebrae.
Yes, God.
That's crazy.
So he was nailed by one of these guys.
This is like the beginning,
which always scared me,
the beginning of D2, The Mighty Ducks.
Oh yeah.
You relive Gordon Bombay's terrible injury,
because he goes pro and maybe can't make it
in the big leagues.
I was always terrified by this depiction
of Bombay getting beat up.
Yeah.
You could film this in the same way
with quick little glimpses between opening titles.
They should make this.
Yeah.
If this had been in-
Saving Mr. Banks.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I mean, they gotta do more with Hanks, right?
You gotta do more.
Well, at this point, this is young Walt.
I mean, I guess Hanks, we can de-age him with the technology,
so Chris Evans is doing it.
Chris Evans could do it.
All right, say Hanks, let a 68 year old, Tom Hanks,
get the de-aging that Sam Jackson, Captain Marvel,
tech or the, you know what?
Deep fake Walt Disney may be coming soon
because of what they've done.
Spoiler alert on Boba Fett with Mark Hamill.
Just deep fake, different actor,
and then an AI does the voice.
So we got the Walt voice.
Much more of this.
Let's do as much of this.
I think.
So Walt, yeah, let's do it.
It's so effective, it's so settling.
It's not, you see other things that are unsettling.
I'm settled by the Mark Hamill.
You know what?
I'll say this about the deep fake.
I, the technology with the face doesn't bother me so much,
but the voice is the thing that really is odd.
That they had to, they got a bunch of Mark Hamill clips
and created a database to make so that it is not him.
Yes, that's, because we were like, you know what?
This face is like much better
than when it was on the Mandalorian.
Like the face looks pretty good in a lot of the,
not every shot, but a lot of these shots.
But what's wrong with that voice?
Yeah.
That's a computer talking.
Well, I think, I mean, that was weird
because Mark Hamill was still very much alive.
But in Rogue One, I didn't mind it for Peter Cushing
because he is long dead.
But then for-
So you won't mind it for Walt Disney when we have the movie.
Well, I was gonna say proximity, I think is under,
Carrie Fisher had just passed and then they were doing it.
In Rogue One.
And then that documentary about Anthony and Bourdain
got in a lot of trouble because they had him-
Was he deep faked?
They deep, they used AI to construct his voice
to have him read some of the narration.
Oh, I didn't know that.
Like stuff he did not say.
And then they had him read Squarespace ads
for the promotional podcast.
Oh no.
And then-
Are you having problems in your life?
Wait a minute.
And then he took baby Grogu to like a local taco stand.
Yeah.
Oh no.
Well, Walt will be-
Serve bantha meat here.
Yeah, deep fake Walt movie about the polo injury,
about maybe a big game, maybe a big polo game.
That's sort of the-
Yeah.
That's the main-
I wanna see this Argentine's in home.
I wanna see in super slow-mo 300 level of detail,
those vertebrae getting crushed.
Yeah.
And it'll-
I'm trying to think, like the ball hit him.
So it would have been hit from like farther away
and like at enough speed.
And it got some air time to like knock him.
Like it hit him in the chest or the head or the-
Yeah, I didn't see where it hit him.
Fall off the horse?
I think he falls out of the saddle.
I think the, yeah, the injury happens from wherever he lands.
I don't know if he landed on his head,
if he landed on his back.
I don't know that the ball did the damage
and the ball just threw him.
This is, what are we,
the Christopher Reeve had his injury,
his horrible injury,
didn't even involve games in a movie.
Yeah, that's just falling off a horse.
Boy, Walt is lucky it was not worse.
The other thing I came across,
and this was a kind of a weird like message board
or like publicly updated Wiki of,
did Walt Disney kill some guys in a bullet hole?
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, nevermind.
All right, if everyone else found it too.
Well, no, no, no, no.
That's exactly because I was wondering
if that's where this should go.
Well, we still, yeah,
we still talk about Hazel Jordan and stuff, but-
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, yeah, and we'll get to Hazel Jordan.
We will pay off why the polo injury is important.
But yes, this is what happened to me.
I Google Walt's polo injury.
I'm expecting to find some kind of mundane information.
And then I find this question.
Did Walt Disney accidentally kill someone
during a game of polo?
Oh my God.
So this is what I was,
cause I texted you guys.
This is a little more interesting maybe than we thought.
So all right, we've told you all that story.
Walt hurt himself and he's laid up
and he dreams up some stuff.
We'll get to that.
But yeah, this threw me off my horse.
Walt, he might've killed somebody.
What are you talking about?
Did you keep pursuing this information?
Yeah.
Yeah, there's kind of an answer.
And then there's another bit of LA,
notable LA landmarks come into play.
Yes.
Yeah, that's wild.
Okay, okay.
So why did this come,
why is this question in the air?
And this is almost the weirdest thing to me
of why this has been asked is that this was on,
this was in an edition,
this was a card on Trivial Pursuit.
Yes.
Somebody posted this on their blog at some point
and not just a Trivial Pursuit game,
but a Disney produced Trivial Pursuit game.
Yeah, that's right.
From 1985, where they control it
and only ask Disney affiliated questions.
Yeah.
And they put on a card,
how many people died from injuries incurred
playing polo with Walt Disney?
Yes, that is wild.
Like obviously that has been retconned from Walt's history
at this point in the Disney company.
100%, never ever have I come across this.
I know, I've never seen this before.
I think one of the websites I was looking,
I can't remember what it was, one of the websites,
it was like somebody remembered the card saying like,
how many people did Walt Disney kill or something?
Yeah.
And they're like, well, that's not really-
I thought it was way more severe.
Yeah, yeah.
That's not what the card said.
No, he didn't kill, but he might've been in the games.
Yeah, he definitely was in the games.
He was in this game.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
All right, and you guys all know the,
let's play Trail Pursuit,
do you know the answer to that question?
How many people died from injuries incurred
playing polo with Walt Disney?
Was it two?
Two?
Two.
I only have one of the names.
Two people in, like, and that's just like,
we don't know, like details are fuzzy there,
but for sure he played two polo games where somebody died.
If I was playing a game where someone died,
I'm not gonna be playing the game anymore.
Well, didn't also, if you know the timeline, tell me,
but I think, okay, Roy is saying this game is dangerous,
don't play it, then two people die in games with him,
and then his injury happens, right?
Because he wouldn't have been able to play
after the injury.
He keeps going.
These were two separate-
He's still playing and asking for it
after two people died.
These were two separate games.
Yes, yes, not the same.
Yeah, yeah.
So, right, and obviously there's plenty of stuff
we all do that's like,
oh, I really gotta stop drinking that diet soda, you know?
Like, but still, if I was on the polo court
and I'd be like, you know, hey, did you hear about,
hear about Jerry?
He died.
I'd be like, oh, okay, maybe, maybe that's enough.
Even your beloved tennis?
You figured somebody died on that court?
Yeah, that, well, yeah, if it was like,
because of the normal rules of tennis, then yes,
but like if, like, I don't know,
like a bison stampede happened or something,
then I go, well, that was a fluke, you know?
Another condition was aggravated.
Oh, the guy, he was a deep Omicron.
Right.
It had nothing to do with the balls and the racquets.
I mean, you likely were scared
if you watched Looney Tunes cartoons
that there was the potential for like,
the racket to be put over your head,
and then you see the rib netting,
and a big bump grows out,
maybe some birds fly around the bump.
You knew that was a possibility.
I sure did.
You could be stuck with those birds for a while.
You might have to feed them.
Yeah, I mean, my mom tried to scare me away
from every sport other than tennis,
because there was a contact element to most sports,
and she made me afraid of all the balls
until I started playing tennis.
Mom made you afraid of all the balls.
Yeah, she sat me down and she just pulled each ball out
and was like, be afraid of this,
be afraid of this, be afraid of this, and I was.
Yes, mother.
That's right.
So, who are these deaths?
Who died?
October 1935, death number one, Gordon Westcott.
Gordon Westcott, a fairly prominent actor.
Yeah.
Nothing, I haven't seen this person in anything,
but he was a Warner Brothers contract player,
was in dozens and dozens of movies.
He was in movies with, opposite,
Bette Davis and James Cagney.
He was in a Bubs, Bubs, Bubsbee, Bubsbee,
Bugsbee, Berklee, yeah.
Berklee musical, pretty prominent,
and this one, now this one is,
this one literally was Walt's horse ran into his horse,
he fell off the horse, and his own horse crushed him.
Yes.
And several days later, he passed away,
but this was contact from Walt's horse,
so this is the most one-to-one.
Right.
Of the deaths.
Could you say Walt caused it?
I don't know, there's still, there's horses involved too.
Yeah.
But that's pretty crazy.
We've been talking about this stuff forever,
and fans of it way before the podcast.
I was, what's that thing they say online?
I was this many days old.
Oh yeah.
That.
Walt's horse hit another guy's horse, and the guy died.
Yeah.
That's a little close to Walt Disney killing somebody.
Pretty close, yeah.
Yeah.
Obviously, it's basically like, this is Thunderdome,
so I guess you really can't.
A detail I came across a couple times is that,
especially in this era of Hollywood,
where actors were doing a lot of squash-buckling characters
and manly man characters,
there was a streak among the talent in front
and behind the camera of like, you know,
stolen valor of adventure, of like,
I'm a manly man like this,
and Polo fits that bill,
because it's very physically demanding,
and involves riding a horse, you know, tactically.
Adrenaline.
Adrenaline in your manhood, kind of.
Sure.
In a real situation.
But who could withstand this?
This thing is, this is so dangerous.
But that's, yeah, so that's wild,
and there's like newspaper reports of this,
of the funeral happening,
and I do feel like the Walt involvement
was kind of sidelined.
It's indirect, but that's crazy.
And then, less than a year later,
May 1936 happens again,
and Jason, it seems like you know
the weird thing about this.
Yeah.
Winslow Felix is the guy's name,
and this is not an actor,
but rather a car dealership guy.
Now, well, this one, it's not Walt's horse.
This is just, he's partied among the horses.
But imagine, you're like,
you're only still a couple feet away.
This happened to you earlier in the year.
Yeah.
And then again, wild.
But Winslow Felix, I never knew any of this.
Yeah, I didn't know this.
That it is, okay, so it's the, off of the 110 freeway,
by the Shrine Auditorium, by USC,
still this big, very old school sign
that is Felix auto dealership.
I don't know what the rest of it is,
but it's this big sign with Felix the Cat on it.
Yes.
And I never knew why Felix the Cat was on that sign.
This I did know, and it was that he had given a car
or sold a car to the Felix the Cat.
Gave a car, I guess.
Gave a car to the Felix the Cat.
Pat Sullivan, Felix cartoon producer, Pat Sullivan.
Yes, and then-
Is he a creator or just a major figure?
The article I'm reading here just says
cartoon producer, but let's see who created Felix.
Because I would like to be able to say it
every other episode.
So, and his name coincidentally Felix,
and I guess the guy had the permission to endow this,
and he's like, oh, you can use Felix the Cat
on your Felix car dealership.
Wow, wow.
And it's just stood the test of time,
earthquakes, like Felix the Cat is still,
you can still drive by and see.
You forget the, I don't know if people know
that the angels A down in Anaheim,
and that came down during the Earth.
Really?
Yeah, yeah, that was, I remember the morning of
that being a, or whenever there was no power,
we probably didn't find it out,
but I remember my dad telling me the A came down,
and that's just a pretty thin little structure,
but they had to rebuild it.
But yeah, that is weird, the Felix sign remained.
Yeah, Pat Sullivan and Otto Messmer created Felix.
So Pat Sullivan was a creator.
Co-creator.
Okay, Otto Messmer.
Of Felix.
Tougher to remember the two names,
but you'll find a way.
Messmer.
Come out of memory.
Messmer and Sullivan.
The new King Features syndicate.
Unless King Features buy Felix?
They may have.
Oh, DreamWorks Animation.
So part of Comcast, NBCUniversal.
Okay, so we'll get some weird Felix movie.
They'll jam that.
We'll either get a top of the line one,
or they'll kick it to Woody Woodpecker status,
and we'll get a weird.
Oh yeah, well, there's like a weird
top cat movies produced in other countries
that have come out in the last five or six years.
The second one is a prequel to the first movie,
and these were mostly marketed in Mexico.
Wow.
They are CG.
Yeah, like bad CG.
Everybody's so, I look, I understand IP is big,
but like, why is Top Cat have a leg up?
I like Top Cat a lot.
I'm a Top Cat fan, but I don't know why.
At a certain point, I think you could probably
sub in almost anything, and go like,
do people really, is it really a draw?
If it was a different cat with a different hat on it,
would people even go, oh, that looks okay?
Like, this is still.
When you have a better shot making,
taking the Doughboy's drawings
that Chris Van Aertsdelen drew
and turned that into an animated movie.
Yeah, whatever.
They're much more of a built-in audience than Top Cat.
And they'll like farm it out to Mexico.
Someone's grand, you know, they used to watch,
when they were at the grand house,
they'd watch. That is what they're counting on.
You'd watch, get the rabbit ears going,
and you'd watch Top Cat, and executive here.
They remember that, and they're like, let's go, let's do it.
But it's gonna be, but in the future,
someone's grand will have grown up with Doughboy's.
And oh yes, I remember. That's true.
And they'd spar with each other.
It was like a verbal polo match.
Oh, I'd love if Doughboy's drawings came to whatever,
to the meta, however content is consumed today.
I would love a reboot of the Doughboy's.
This is.
Reboot proves that anyone can be a Doughboy.
I don't think this is,
Shao Hing Lee never came up on the show,
but I wrote a one act play one time.
Or, Andy Geo. How long ago?
A few years ago. Oh, yeah.
Well, Andy Geo used to co-produce,
and Nick Mondernach was involved as well,
a show that used to be theater,
that was like one act plays.
Right. And I wrote a one act play
for me and Mike to do, as where we,
it is two guys working at an uncle's hot dog stand
at the Jersey Shore.
Because they had been run out of town
because they wrote a Top Cat movie that was so bad
that they had to flee Los Angeles
and work at a hot dog stand.
It's one of the few things I made,
never got put up.
Let's go do it.
This was never performed.
Never performed.
I didn't even know the details.
The guy wrote this in 2016 or 2017
when he was doing this. Well, let's go do it.
I'll dig it out on the old laptop.
Special Patreon tier.
Yeah. Sure.
Come see, that's a new level.
High level. Come see Jason's one act.
Well, yeah, I think, I don't know.
I'd like to see that. Yeah, I mean, whatever.
Turn it into a radio play.
Is it just the two?
Can I get a one line cameo?
No, you could do the third character.
You could do Uncle Johnny.
It's called Uncle Johnny's Fancy Hot Dogs.
Oh, it's my, oh yeah.
Yeah. Oh boy, that's a high status character, eh?
The owner of the stand.
Yeah, he's a maniac.
He's very mean.
Oh, great.
All right.
Cool.
Okay, well, this is an exciting step.
Wow, boy, that ties a ton together.
And if they, so put it up
and then they'll make the movie based on the,
it'll be kind of a meta deconstruction of Top Cat.
The movie's that.
Yeah. Yeah.
Great. Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
We all know Top Cat's many endeavors and qualities and all.
Well, I do.
I don't wanna, look, I don't wanna.
Supporting chaos. My mom was a big Top Cat fan.
I got her some Funko pops of Top Cat.
What does Top Cat sound like?
I can't do a good Top Cat.
He's not like, he's a little Phil Silvers-ish.
Okay.
To reference, man, he's a dead friend.
Yeah, dead man.
Yeah.
Sergeant Pilko.
He's like, he's always like up to, he's always scheming.
He's always like trying to, there's a cut, an idiot cop.
He's always tricking.
And then they're all just like thieves.
They're all like, just like stealing and, and carousing.
They're all like into ladies too.
It's a, I don't know, it's kind of fun.
All right.
I'm not saying it needs to be have another 100 versions.
I'm just saying there's some charm to the original.
Okay, okay.
And we're in worth the part of Winnock play at least.
At least part of Winnock play.
So anyway, so this, this is wild.
Walt, in two scenarios, somebody died near Walt Disney
while playing polo and then he still went off
and got the injury.
There's almost no literature about this,
but the, the, the, the conspiracist might say,
what if there is more, what if, I don't know.
Maybe he, I don't know what, how you cheat in polo,
but what if he did like pull the reins a little like,
what if he gave old, what are their names?
Tacky, what if he gave Tacky a little like,
a little extra nibble and whispered an idea in his ear?
Yeah, what I mean, what would happen is I'm sure
playing polo, you are just like seconds away
from falling off and really hurting yourself,
which would get your adrenaline up in such a crazy level
that you would start to probably feel like murderous thoughts
toward other people who have almost hurt you really badly.
So hey, it's possible.
The horse is too.
I know the Disney company's ability to, to,
yeah, to retcon and to take Walt mythology
when they want it, but bury other when they don't want it.
Was there a, was there a famous Disney fixer?
That's an interesting question.
That's a, yeah, cause every studio kind of had.
Especially in old days.
Yeah.
I mean, now they, now Jay Vick said, I don't need that.
I'm just doing it myself.
I'm the fixer.
But yeah, that's interesting.
Cause yeah, weird stuff would happen all the time.
Like Scotty from the full service was kind of a fixer
in addition to being a pimp essentially.
In addition to being, I guess you would say
he was a prostitute himself as well.
Yeah. Did they have like an all purpose full service guy?
Not even in the Scotty Bowers way.
That's what I'm saying.
But is there, was there a Mike from Breaking Bad
at the Disney studios or an Irishman or a,
yeah, there's got to, there would have to have been somebody.
I heard you paint Mickey's house.
I heard you use the den.
I heard you use it then.
I don't know.
And yeah, maybe we don't know his name.
We don't know who it is being that,
or it was like one of these,
that's how Keenan Wynn got involved.
Oh yeah.
Rough character actors, Walt,
he was around for that first and then like,
oh, you know what, you pop on camera too.
What'd you do this week, Walt?
Who'd you kill?
Ah boy.
You know, the fifth polo injury.
I could keep three out of the press,
but these two are going to leak.
There are other, like there's,
there's other guys, like there was,
like Sped Red, was it Harry Turtle?
Or did you come across that name?
Maybe, I don't know.
There was a guy who ended up being like,
in the long run was a producer,
but like early on.
That he was playing with you mean?
Well, like a guy, he was a polo player when he was younger
and then the depression hit
and there was like a drop off of polo
before it got popular again.
But it was like a guy who like ended up at a dinner
and then he got hired by Disney,
but he was such an avid polo player.
He like climbed the ranks
and he was in charge of the Donald Duck team.
Walt capped in the Mickey Mouse team.
Oh, they named the teams.
He capped, that's right.
And they would like, they played in like Mexico City
and they went to Arizona
and they said they were often underestimated
because they had Donald Duck
in the center of their uniforms.
Everyone thought they were,
they were like losers.
Who are like, they wouldn't be very good.
Scrappy, mad, not classic champions like Mickey.
Yeah, so he would go on to oversee
the like Disney nature movies.
Wow, so people rose up the ranks in Disney via polo.
Through the boys club,
through like the sauna and the polo teams
and like, yeah, all of the stuff you hear about.
This is what I keep telling Zach Reno
that we need to do with tennis.
We need to start playing in places
where like the wealthiest Hollywood elites are playing.
And we'll beat them at tennis and then they'll like us.
And then they'll let us be in movies.
But I don't know, I don't know if that exists.
I don't know.
I mean, I'm sure it exists.
Well, you beat them twice and on the third game,
you throw it.
So they think you, they like conquered.
But do you think they'll still respect me?
No, you just have to play so,
you have to sell it so much.
You're saying I have to take them up to the brink of losing
and then they still get to win.
So then they still feel good.
Yeah, you hustle though.
They feel good about me enough to say
that I'll be in the new Top Cat.
Yeah.
You are mocap Top Cat.
That I get to get the golf balls
or the ping pong balls on me to motion capture.
You know, Gad seemed hot and cold on the roll anyway.
He probably wasn't gonna do it,
but you seem like a good sport.
You know, you seem like a reliable one.
Can you do a Phil Silver's voice off the top of your head?
You know who he is.
These are all fat cat types.
These are all, I'm imagining the heads of the studios
are still like Louis B. Mayer and Daryl Zanuck
who also played polo with Walt.
Oh, geez. I read.
Wow.
Daryl Zanuck.
I think Hal Roach was out there.
I saw that name as well.
Well, here's what I, here's one other odd little thing.
Like in that you can't find a lot of people talking
about the possibility that Walt killed somebody
while playing polo.
But oddly, one of the only people,
I found a big Twitter thread where talking about this issue
was Connor Ratliff from George Lucas talk show
and the Dead Eyes podcast, which as we record this,
he just put out this episode where he has Tom Hanks on
the center of the whole narrative he's been weaving.
But he did a mega thread about all of this
and about how it all really relates to the classic
Walt's cartoon that hasn't come up yet, Mickey's Polo Team,
which was a big, a big short where that involved
Disney characters, but also Hollywood celebrities
like riding on horses and some of the Marx brothers.
Yeah.
The Harpo.
The Charlie Temples in the crowd with the three little pigs.
This was like the original Space Jam 2.
Yeah, you're right.
Where even the crowd has celebrities in it.
Right.
You're right.
Yes, yes, yes.
And which they, which he pointed out also is weirdly
with polo having all this stress for Walt,
that that short was the subject of a lawsuit
because somebody else claimed that they had the idea
of a short where polo, where the horses ride the people.
Somebody else had that idea, took Walt to court.
The case was dismissed.
So the thing that Walt is trying to do as a stress relief
is nothing but, it only adds more stress.
It brings him in, he gets sued because of the cartoon.
He gets hurt and there's this accident,
people die in front of him.
The other thing that Connor found that he posted
and you solved this mystery, Mike, is why this thing was
called this internal Riviera Country Club magazine
was called the Riviera Chucker.
So that was the phrase that I guess is what you do
in the game.
It's called like a period or a quarter.
Oh, that's what, oh yeah.
Yeah.
So.
But that might actually be a different term also.
I think that's the same, right?
It would have to be.
It could be a play on that term.
What is Chucker?
Chucker, Chucker looks like it was spelled C-H-E-U-K-K-A-A,
A or A-H.
This is two K's, I feel it has to be.
Well, is that what a player is called then?
Well, that's what I'm saying, yeah.
Maybe it's like what that's maybe what a player is called
and this is what like the period's called.
But this is a big article from 1935 about him being
into polo and the points.
How he, oh my God.
Over the course of doing this, and this is before
the injury, four black eyes, seven stitches,
four chipped fingers.
My gosh.
With pains and aches.
And it talks about how when he started playing,
one day he appeared at the office with a black eye
and he walked past his secretary who said, good morning.
And he said, yes, it is a good morning.
As if to say, is there something wrong?
Was there any reason on my face
it wouldn't be a good morning?
What are you implying?
You bring it up.
So it is like he was UFC guy.
It was like he was, he just got a UFC fight.
That's how bad the injuries were.
Did we all come across a celebrity cut from,
well, Mickey's Polo team.
Oh yes, this is crazy.
This is also, there's so many crazy parts of this
cause we mentioned Will Rogers.
Will Rogers you can see in the American Adventure.
Who's in the bottom of this very, of the Chucker magazine.
One of Will's last visits to Riviera.
Here he is talking to Hal Roach, little rascals producer.
An avid polo player, huge star, humorist, actor,
fake cowboy, real cowboy?
Political satire, the original Bill Maher you might say.
We should all say as much as possible.
Huge, huge star and was an avid polo player
and died in a plane crash.
So was excised from-
Supposed to be one of the silly,
oh there's a horse that looks like Will Rogers.
But then he died and they had to cut it.
Crazy.
Was in talks with Walt to be the star
of his first feature length film.
His first feature length.
Snow White hasn't happened yet when all this happens?
This was almost a project he was going to do.
Where Will Rogers is Rip Van Winkle interacting
with animated characters.
Much like the upsetting Alice in Wonderland shorts.
You just said that the other day.
I never thought about those being scary.
But I guess you're right.
Those are pretty unique.
They're a little under like the,
in the way that the voyage to the moon,
that early-
Oh yeah, that face.
The Malay movie.
The moon face is certainly an aesthetic.
Much more pleasing aesthetic.
But in probably like,
both of these things probably technologically
advanced for their time.
So ambitious, incredibly ambitious.
So Walt almost made this Rip Van Winkle
with Will Rogers but then he had to go and die.
So this was almost his first feature length,
Walt Disney movie.
Which could have changed everything.
It could have changed everything.
This polo-feel deal that's not good.
That's gonna lead to this creepy out of date
Rip Van Winkle movie that nobody's gonna like today.
Could have been a huge hit.
Could have led to the bankruptcy
that Roy was always like worried about.
Like not every Dwayne Johnson movie's a home run.
Like not every, you know, sometimes you make a rampage.
They're creative they are.
But like, oh yeah, creatively.
They're all masterpieces.
I mean, sometimes you make a rampage.
Sometimes you make a Southland Tales, you know.
Which one's which?
Yeah, I think if I had to choose one to watch,
I'd go Southland.
I know, I think that what I'm saying is like,
they didn't make a lot of money.
They are both seeded.
Well Southland is why the Rock won't take risks anymore.
Cause he took one and he fell on his knees.
But a cult, kind of a cult following now, Southland Tales.
But like what's his biggest, biggest hit?
Red Notice.
Wow.
The biggest film ever made.
Right. Yes.
Yeah.
No film has ever been viewed more than,
other than Don't Look Up like four days later.
Yeah, yeah.
All the biggest movies of all time came out in December.
Right.
Last year on Netflix.
All five of the top movies.
To Throne Snow White.
But there's a few paths.
There's a few paths that never came to be.
And it's one where Rip Van Winkle is made.
It's a massive hit.
It leads to the funding they need to build the Burbank lot
and all those other endeavors.
And there's one where it's a massive failure
and Disney is like washed up.
This is all over.
And then he's just,
he's nursing his polo injury with nobody to help him.
He has no money, no idea,
no way to get his ideas off the ground.
Just prowling on like a crazy guy.
Or yeah, it's like the Orson Welles band
where it's like makes really interesting work.
Never has a big hit again.
Never has a big,
he's never given Citizen Kane money and freedom again.
Polo is at the center of all of it.
If not for the polo.
So maybe it's time to get to the flip side of it,
which is that he has to,
he's forced to stop playing polo
because of his own injury and witnessing several deaths.
That had nothing to do with it.
I don't think so.
Yeah, no, that had nothing to do with it.
Maybe people just died around you more often.
That was the olden days.
Oh, geez.
It was the olden days.
Yeah, Penicillin still has the new tag on it.
But no, so it's not immediate, right?
He does quit polo,
but it's not as if he then says,
what else should I do?
Maybe I should do Disneyland.
It's not until the late 40s
that the injury is getting bad
and the stress is getting bad again.
So they hire,
there's a nurse at the studio
who becomes Walt's personal nurse as well.
And that is Hazel George.
And she begins enacting the five o'clock special,
a small side room off of Walt's office
where she would massage him to treat this old polo injury.
And he would imbibe on a scotch
while unloading his burdens on Hazel.
One other weird thing about all this is that,
you find this, that the side room,
there's the offices where I work,
but when it's five o'clock special time
and I need to go take a load off,
drink a scotch, get massaged,
what does he call that place?
He calls it his laughing place.
Which just came up in Cotino
that he called, it was that he called the ranch his laughing,
he called Palm Springs his laughing place.
But he also called this little room his laughing place.
So Walt's using this term.
I mean, I guess it makes sense to like an old guy
had like a bad, tired joke.
And then he just would say it about every,
maybe when he went to the bathroom and there's like one stall,
he goes, there's my laughing place.
And like you're supposed to laugh if you were around him.
I removed the name Walt Disney from this story.
A major studio head in the thirties had a private nurse
who would give him massages and scotch at five o'clock.
That's like, we're describing an affair.
Like this is a mystery.
Maybe, well, yes.
Maybe, like potentially.
We've talked a lot about water.
We were talking about Clarabelle Cowell.
Having an affair with Clarabelle.
We've talked about Walt having.
We know he fathered Rue.
We established this.
And an affair with Kanga.
But yeah, no, this, yeah.
Well, I mean, like hypothetically,
I'm interested in the world where that happened
because it's interesting in the way I'm,
I wonder if he specifically did all the horse ramming.
But in looking into Hazel specifically,
I didn't see any proof of that,
but maybe they kept the proof in the laughing place.
No, I'm not saying that's real.
Did I do a couple of Googles for it?
Yeah, I did to take a look.
Cause obviously, yeah, secret room with the female nurse
where you have a drink every afternoon at your job.
I'm just asking questions.
I hear you.
It does sound suspicious.
It does sound very suspicious.
I mean, there's so much weird suspicious stuff.
Like he was in chronic pain for all of his life.
You know, you would hear him about being very irate
sometimes or very short with people.
And it's like, well, yeah, when you're in chronic pain,
you're often very irate.
But like the detail that like he went to a chiropractor
instead of a doctor, if he had gone to a doctor
and they put him in a cast, it might've just healed up.
Instead he hurt his life.
Instead of growing massive calcium deposits.
Geez, which doesn't help kill him,
but it doesn't, I don't know.
It's not good either.
And if you're dealing with chronic pain and lung cancer
from smoking a pack an hour, like, you know.
Yeah, he seems, the health seems so much more poor
than I thought.
Here's one thing I'll say about Hazel George.
This is no slouch Hazel George,
because she was also a songwriter.
A like, credited under a pseudonym,
it credited as Gil.
And I wonder, is that some weird work around
to like make it sound like a man's name
to people not trust a female songwriter?
If so, that's insane at this time.
Be surprising.
But she wrote songs for the Mickey Mouse Club
and Old Yeller and Zorro and all this stuff.
Why wasn't she rich?
Why does she have to be this old man's nurse?
I don't know.
Maybe because, was it because of like,
when you're on the property at that time,
you're just like in the way that he says,
you the background painter also go figure out
how to make a pirate ship fly.
You know what I mean?
Like, is it just, it's an all in
when you're at the Disney lot.
I work for hire.
Like, yeah, Steve, Steve Dicco co-created Spider-Man,
but it's just like, we paid you, you created that.
And like, eventually decades later,
the estates make some money,
but like he should have lived at the top
of the Empire State Building,
instead he just lived at a regular apartment
in New York City for much of his life, you know?
Yeah, but even with songs,
like they would somewhat take care of songwriter money.
I don't know when the Sherman,
like Sherman Brothers eventually I think got paid very well
for all the stuff they did.
But if there was a way to be screwed,
cause everybody was screwed.
But everybody they were trying to screw, so.
Yeah, it's a good question.
As someone who just listened to a two and a half hour
interview with Mike Love,
who dictated every single little lyric or half lyric
he wrote that he wasn't credited for on the Beach Boys songs.
I listen to it longer than our podcast.
It was the poorest quality I've ever heard.
There's a piano tinkling in the background.
People are coughing the whole time.
You hear a vacuum towards the end of it.
I think they turned the lights out of this room,
wherever he was and he's still going on.
And then I thought of bub, bub, bub, and you see.
Like no, the interviewer left, Mike.
You were just talking about this a couple of days ago
and I think you need to do some sort of audio
to talk about this.
I can, I'll try to pair this.
It was fascinating.
No one else should have to endure the two and a half hours as I did,
but I can get it down to a tight hour 20.
There's there.
There are little tricks, you know, to to screw people out of them.
I remember it.
Lou and inside Lou and Davis, when they do the novelty song
and the producer asked them, it's like, what was it?
Do you want the session fee or do you want like those residuals
or the right or something?
He's like, you kidding?
The song's trash.
Give me the session fee.
And then it is a massive hit.
Yeah, I just learned that
Michael McDonald's fee for the sample of I Keep Forgetting on Warren G's Regulate.
He just got a lump sum of ten thousand dollars.
Little a little awareness that that would become one of the staples
of West Coast G Funk, and he could have stood to make so much more.
But it was a one time.
That's that's a pretty small.
There's a yeah, there's a collection of that.
Those stories isn't it?
I could call completely, completely wrong.
Didn't Marlon Brando take up front on the Godfather?
I think he was like desperate for money and he took like just a lump sum.
I could be totally wrong about this.
It's some movie like this where he took like a lump sum
and then lost out on millions of dollars.
Oh, something like that.
Oh, no. So he doesn't get money when the from like poorly made t-shirts at the mall
where it's like where it's dunkle around with Scarface
and would have made tons of money on that.
But anyway, I think Hazel sounds cool.
That's maybe some of my like I think Hazel sounds cool.
And like she would like, you know, give it to him a little bit
in terms of like verbal sparring, like they'd have a little, you know,
she was like one of the only people who could, you know,
like kind of just show Jester talks truth to the king.
Kind of. Yes. Yeah. Yeah.
There was even some exchange like that where he Walt described himself as one of the
what is the phrase?
One of the last benevolent monarchs.
He just said that out loud to her.
And then she said, well, I'm going to last great court gestures.
That's how that's the type.
That's how funny stories were right back in the old days.
I'm giving it. I'm reading it on a curve.
She seems great.
Like she seems like a fascinating character in her own right.
It's just so funny the way the company frames these like mythmaking
sometimes where it's like, do you know what that sounds like?
That sounds a little strange.
Yes. Yeah. Yeah. A bit.
She becomes an important figure in a number of ways.
And they will build the biggest one.
But like she so, you know, she she she gives him advice, events to her.
And apparently, OK, so down the road on the path
but to his death and by the she's advising on his health and saying,
maybe you shouldn't eat.
I was looking at a book where that describes his diet,
which we're talking about following the Walt diet, which is full and more
fully fleshed out in this book.
I saw. Oh, good.
Chilli and beans, hamburgers, potatoes and pie.
Yeah. So he got 210 pounds at some point off of all this.
There's another list that makes sure to include puddings and jellos,
although I think low fat, low fat gelatin.
You know, you got to watch that or low fat pudding.
You know, even though he's he's concerned about health in other ways.
I found this bizarre wall quote.
He said this out loud.
Smoking and drinking are sins because you are one of God's creatures.
And if you don't take care of the body he gave you, you are committing a sin.
And he said that out loud, but never stop smoking.
He knew that's his way of saying, I know, I know God hates me.
But what are you going to do?
That is a very strange quote, because like he is that the Disney brand is wholesome.
Yeah. And the Walt Disney story is wholesome and pure and American,
not often openly religious outside of like like Christmas Carol level religious.
Like one or two mentions of God.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I know. Yeah.
Religion does not come up a ton, but it came up in this bizarre way of like how you
you're you sin if you smoke and drink two things that I do a ton.
You're right. And I'm not going to stop doing it.
Any right. Very strange.
Anyway, Hazel apparently is the person who told Walt about cryonics.
So here's another bizarre part of the story in the legend.
The idea that Walt might have frozen himself and he for sure was interested in it.
He looked into it.
You know, we believe that he did not freeze himself, but his interest
in the entire area came from Hazel.
But then the biggest thing was getting him into model trains.
But specifically, the thing that she said to do was
there is this big Chicago Railroad Fair coming up
and you should go and take take an animator or something.
And he went with Ward Kimball, one of the one of the nine old men,
one of the great classic Disney animation figures.
Do you guys find any of this, the Chicago Railroad Fair?
I actually don't have much detail on that.
I saw this story where he came home one day and put a chunk of metal
on the kitchen table and was like, that's a piston. Whoa.
Like that was a memory the family had.
Anyway, she knew about this. You should go.
This is a huge deal.
This is a World's Fair of railroad stuff.
And he loves trade.
But apparently the interest in trains was not really before that.
It came from going to this.
He came back starry eyed, reminded him of his youth.
And what does this thing have?
It sounds boring when you hear about it.
What does Walt just go look at a bunch of old trains?
But it was this whole like a World's Fair.
There was all this other stuff going on.
There were a bunch of turn of the century vehicles running around.
And there were fireworks.
And there was a miniature New Orleans.
There were themed environments at this event.
There were little robots.
There was a robot of Paul Bunyan.
There was an Indian village.
There were all of these things that eventually get put into Disneyland.
He comes back from this thing.
August 1948, days after he comes back from the railroad fair,
he sends a memo to a guy and says, hey, we should build this little park
across the street from the studio.
So if this woman does not say go to this thing and Walt doesn't go
and steal all of his ideas for the railroad fair,
then maybe we don't get the ball rolling on Disneyland.
That's our at least it looks much different.
It's a different. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
You're describing the some of that basic stuff that it's like where I grew up.
And it's a display of turn of the century vehicles.
And a railroad is a big part of the robot of potential future episodes.
I mean, obviously Mickey Mouse Park, the unbuilt Burbank Mickey Park.
Yes. It's very interesting.
Also, Walt's diet, trying to find every trying to find
multiple instances of like, OK, what's Walt's diet?
Do we eat try to do we each try to eat like Walt for a day
and see how we feel after a podcast at the end of the chili into scotch, into pudding?
Just just vomit.
So I'm caking the floor of the guy.
My third eye just open like I'm just activated.
None of that sounds out of the realm of possibility for the way I already eat.
Yeah, that's all great stuff to eat.
So yeah, I was trying to pack it in.
It's great. So Hazel is really, yeah, incredibly much more influential.
Yeah. Yeah.
So that's even more of to the theory.
If not for the polo, if they had had the polar injury,
might not have hired Hazel, who might not have told him to go to the railroad
to go this road.
And then he immediately sends a memo and says, I want to build Mickey Mouse
Park across the street.
But the problem becomes money.
Where am I going to get the money for this?
He's complaining about how he can't find money to Hazel.
And he says, hey, if I asked you for some money, would you give me some money?
And she says, yes, which seems odd.
But it makes him go.
Maybe people would be enthusiastic about this.
So then he tasks her with going and raising money from the employees.
Will you start a fund to make Mickey Mouse Park happen?
And from that fund grows out the theme.
But I didn't know any of this.
So her connection to all of it is very direct.
Wow.
It's always alarming when the company you are an employee of is fundraising
for the company you are an employee of.
Look, I feel great about when Funny or Die started saying,
why don't everyone buy stock?
And then we all did it.
And if you'll notice, we're all millionaires today.
Yes, I have the famous giant sale of Funny or Die.
I have noticed.
This one maybe did work out better, although she did end up, you know,
she lived alone in a little apartment her final years near the in Burbank,
near the studio.
But she did have a friend into her her older years.
This is very bizarre.
So there's this book in the 70s about Walt called Walt Disney
American Original by Bob Thomas, I believe, is the writer.
A lot of stories from the book come from this woman, Hazel.
I know we're going to do this.
You found this? Yeah, yeah, yes.
How weird is this?
This is a big book, by the way, like before the you remember
there were in the early 2000s or so, there was a two competing biographies
came out within the same 10 year span.
Oh, really?
I think before that, the Bob Thomas book, I believe, talked about a lot.
Yeah, well for you.
Big major one that told a lot of stuff, not words and all,
but a little a little bit of words.
This book comes out and it's well received.
And then the author, Bob Thomas, is contacted out of the blue on the phone.
By a high pitched voice who says, this is Michael.
You can guess who Michael is.
That is Michael Jackson.
Michael Jackson just personally calls this writer on the phone
and what it leads to.
So they so so they meet and they hang out and he asks a ton of questions
about Walt, among which he says a certain swear word.
I don't know what the swear word is.
And he says, did Walt ever say that word?
Michael Jackson needs reassuring that Walt didn't swear anyway.
Weird.
So then they meet and then he says, oh, one more thing.
Do you have Hazel George's number?
And he said, no, I only met her once.
I'll find a way.
He contacted her.
And then Michael Jackson started visiting Hazel, this nurse, all the time,
all the time, brought her flowers all the time, brought her classical music.
Mike just showed a photo of Michael Jackson
the bedside of Walt's old nurse.
What's happening? What do you mean?
I didn't. This is all a shock to me.
I was like, all right, then he hired the nurse and I wonder.
No, the nurse thought of Disneyland, told him about cryonics
and then became close friends with Michael Jackson until they both died.
Yeah. And her 90s rice like she died in 96.
So this must have been happening in like her late 80s, early 90s.
You know, the late 80s and early 90s when Michael Jackson has nothing else going on.
Right. He's hanging out with his nurse.
Wow. Really weird.
The photo you have is that's like bad era.
That's like very like iconic.
Yeah, that's like Michael.
Yeah. This is now I feel like I have to go back to every episode
and find something we said offhanded without thinking and see if it also leads
to like national treasure, like rabbit holes.
I could be. I also get the feeling with this Hazel George stuff that there is
way more even that's been written about because she seems so fascinating
and is intertwined with so much stuff.
I wrote all these songs and like was there for his most vulnerable moments.
Yeah. Shit.
There's also some exchange where she like kind of jabs him a little and he says,
oh, you know, my next project is an audio animatronic nurse.
They have a little like sitcom banter like George and Gracie style.
It seems like they had a real act going.
That's fascinating. Yeah.
And then Michael at the end.
Yeah. And then she hung out with Michael Jackson, a bunch of Michael 90s.
Michael knew who she was like he was excited.
Yeah. Yeah. Weird.
And also, I looked at this book today.
She has mentioned on 10 pages of this page book.
Why did why did he gravitate to I want to talk to Hazel?
Yeah, right. That's so fascinating, too.
I mean, he had ultimately had children with his own nurse.
So it was maybe a feeling. Right.
Nurses. Maybe it was a nurse thing.
I guess he had wanted to be like Walt and meet the woman who worked on Walt.
I don't know. That's interesting.
There's a lot. There's more here is all I'm saying.
And we are like we have just found the two hundred and seventy
ninth weirdest thing about Michael Jackson.
He shows up everywhere in this and all of these topics.
He's constantly showing up.
Yeah. And sometimes we have to make a point of avoiding a lot of a time.
Yeah. This case, we'll go with it.
We have to say this woman became the person who inspired everything
all at the back of everything Disney does today.
Disney is built on this nurse, her ideas and Walt crushing
four of his vertebrae. This is what we have learned.
Yeah. It's why it's the butterfly effect. Right.
Yeah. Is that what they call it?
I the Ashton Kutcher movie.
You know what? I'm just realizing now I pulled up this book.
This was one of the biographies I was thinking of that were around
the same times. And it says Disney Editions 2017.
I think they reissue.
I didn't realize this.
This might have been an updated reissue of the time,
because this is the one I think the family stands by, approves.
They didn't approve of this other book, Walt Disney Hollywood's Dark Prince,
which my dad gave me as a present when I was a child.
And my mom was like, uh, thank you for taking an interest in Scott's interest.
But this seems weird.
But which I read, I'm reading about his union stuff when I'm like nine.
And it's kind of crazy.
This the Walt Disney, the triumph of American imagination came out in 2007.
If you can see, it has the like Neil Gabler is the author.
It kind of has the font, the cartoony ish font.
Yeah, I've read that one. Yeah.
Anyway, bizarre.
How much said this is I didn't think this would be this vast.
And I didn't think Michael Jackson would be involved.
And I didn't think
people getting crushed by horses would be involved.
This is unrelated, but I just found a picture of Michael Jackson
with his pet spider tarantula crawling up on his chest.
Have you ever seen that?
I'm not familiar with the mythology of Michael's spider.
OK, that's a scary photo.
We have a name on the spider.
Michael Jackson, you should know that.
I don't know that Michael Jackson's spider's name tacky
partner.
Hazel, I have a spider to name.
I need you to give me some of Walt's names.
This story. Wow.
There's a spider on his face.
Michael, do you know that's there?
Get it off.
Michael has like all these.
Wow. This feels this this story.
This episode feels like one of those novels that's like a like
infinite jester underworld or where it's like a journey through 20th
century America, like, you know, the full run of the 20th century.
Stories weaving in and out of other stories.
Yeah, Michael, we understand the 20th century now.
Here's him in 2003 with a giant spider bite.
And now we know why, because he's always palin role with spiders.
Michael, my spider's off.
Yeah, she was.
Taylor was begging him.
John Peters, John Peters tried to warn him.
Scariest thing. Big spiders.
You know, well, so look,
all the things we love came from all this.
So I guess, you know what?
There's that thing in Spaceship Earth, which wouldn't exist without any of this.
Does that line? Thank the Phoenicians in this case.
Thank the Argentines.
Thank you.
And I don't mean like everybody from Argentina.
I mean, the four specific aggressive polo players from 1930s.
If you had not crushed Walt's vertebrae, we wouldn't have a podcast.
Man, that's true.
I didn't even think about what's not having a podcast because of it. Wow.
Yeah, that too. That's crazy. You're right.
That all right. Well, that's all.
Let's all let's all thank the Argentines, shall we?
Thank you. Thank you, Argentine.
Thank you, Argentines, for Walt Disney's original sin.
Ruthless aggression on the polo field.
Speaking of which, it's been a long episode.
I think I'm going to go sin and put some scotch in my
ruined God's vessel that is my body.
Is your nurse here?
It is almost five. We should all go have a five o'clock.
We should all go to go see our nurses.
We're all we just have to be each other's nurses.
It might very well might turn into amateur wrestling.
But for now, we should get off, Mike, for all that you survived podcast.
The ride you learned all about Walt's Polo Injury and the 20th century.
Keep it tuned here where perhaps Jason's one act play
about Top Cat and Hot Dogs will get enacted unless that is on the stage
in the theater.
You know, I still got to cut out the the first play and the first play ever did.
I have some digital files.
So many plays to know there's so much plays.
Well, yeah, this is the well, we'll start a podcast.
Right. The theater program as well.
You can start as the patron, but also you can like have the seats and like,
oh, I'll see that one. Oh, maybe I'll skip that.
You know, we were talking about before we started recording,
the price of everything is up.
I think black box theaters, the only thing the price is down.
It's going for a fire sale and maybe some actual fires
for the insurance money.
You know, the UCB theater, I think you mean the PTR theater.
We bought it. See you there soon.
Bye bye.