Forever.
Dog.
Greetings, it is I, Joe Rohde.
I'm sorry I couldn't be there in person.
I'm in deepest Bora Bora,
gathering artifacts for my collection.
As you know, I'm quite the collector.
And soon, the Rohde collection will unveil
its most prized acquisition.
The good boys of the galaxy.
You see, two and a half years ago,
Mike, Scott, and Jason put on a little live show
where they made fun of my precious ear thing.
So in March of 2020, I locked them down in total isolation
where they could never do a live show again.
That's right, girl.
They can't make fun of you now.
In a few minutes, you will be taken to encounter
the good boys on the Dynasty Typewriter Gantry.
But first, you'll see my private office full of pieces
from all around the galaxy.
And soon, you'll be able to travel the galaxy
on Richard Branson's Virgin Galactic.
Virgin Galactic, we've got a fun billionaire.
You know, when Dicky Branson first called me,
he's joking, they're never gonna let you
build that second island.
All right, hang on.
Let's mute this guy.
Shut this guy up.
All right.
No way.
I like that guy better when his sound wasn't working.
Yeah.
Keep him muted, I say.
What's going on, everybody?
It's us, Three Rockets.
Yeah.
It's so good to see you guys,
but under not so great of circumstances.
Let me tell you what's happening.
That crazy Joe Roady, he has captured the good boys
in the Dynasty Typewriter Gantry lift.
We gotta do something.
We gotta bust them out of there.
Yeah, he could have at least sent them to Alani Resort.
Somewhere nice that he has access to.
The Alani prison.
But they're just up there rotten.
They've been up there since March of 2020.
That's why they couldn't do a live show.
It had nothing to do with the other thing.
Yeah, don't think about the other thing.
Don't give one thought to the other thing.
Think about the other thing.
I'm sure it won't get referenced tonight at all ever again.
Not on anybody's mind, but we gotta do something, right?
What are we gonna do, Rocket Two?
We got a plan.
We're gonna take the Dynasty Typewriter Gantry lift
up to the Dynasty Typewriter generator
in this historic, beautiful building.
Blow the generator, which will unleash all of the cages
that they have in this old comedy theater,
and free the good boys.
Yeah, that's right.
Yeah.
That's right.
Hopefully, hopefully it won't free any other podcasters too.
Just those three guys we like.
They'd get very confusing otherwise.
One, two, three voices.
Ben Shapiro ain't locked up in here, hopefully.
We never know what monsters we could unleash.
Monsters after dark, ah.
Scary.
Okay, so that's the plan.
That's what we're gonna do, and let's go to the,
wait a minute, wait a minute.
I forgot one thing.
We better address the elephant in the room,
the hitch in the plan.
Yeah, that hitch, it's incredibly complicated.
Pay attention to what we're gonna say to you now.
Take some notes, perhaps.
How do we put this?
Okay, it involves certain appendages.
Yeah.
Certain parts of the body.
How do we, it's embarrassing to talk about, really.
Yeah, let's go back a little.
Let's go back a little, okay.
You guys know arms.
Okay, the thing at the end of arms.
Now, hold on, hold on.
I know what you're thinking, shoulders?
Nope, wrong way, wrong way.
That's up.
You wanna go down, you wanna go down the arm.
Not wrists.
Not wrists, no.
Keep going, keep going.
Wrists are great, our flexibility is fine.
We love wrists, but we ain't talking about wrists.
It's really what's attached to those wrists.
Let's just, I guess, out with it.
Here's the issue.
Our hands don't skin.
Oh wow, it's like you guys were ahead of us.
You somehow knew the issue.
Well, here's really where it becomes a trivia challenge,
because do you know the second part?
It involves you, hints.
Okay, let's see.
Our hands don't skin.
Yours do.
Oh, okay, great.
They're way ahead of us on this.
Yeah, so smart, they're so smart.
Should we say it one more time, just to reiterate?
I really wanna make sure everybody's got it.
Yeah, let's say it, let's make a meal out of it.
Okay, let's all raise our voices
and make sure we understand the situation.
Okay, all together now.
Our hands don't skin.
Yours do.
Wow, wow, give yourselves a round of applause.
Woo!
With your hands that skin, ours do not.
I shouldn't keep reiterating, I think they get it.
I think they understand.
So we can move on with the rest of the plan,
and here's what it is.
When we give you the signal,
you are going to raise your hands,
and that way you get the clearance,
and the chaos can begin.
Yeah.
The chaos of three men in their 30s,
calmly talking about a theme park attraction.
Chaos.
And you know, it's been a while.
They might want to amend that.
They're pretty firmly late 30s.
We got older, folks.
We all lived a lifetime in these last two years.
Oh, there I am, bringing up the thing again.
Okay, let's cut that off, and let's get on with the show.
We understand the plan, right?
We all understand the plan.
Yeah, we know.
Then here we go, let's get this show on the road.
Here we go.
Okay, this is the part.
This is where it all happens.
We're gonna plug in this Zoom recorder,
a podcaster's best friend.
Now just ignore the scotch tape on the back
holding the battery compartment on.
It's for professional fidelity.
Don't worry about it.
Okay, so when we plug this thing,
when the Rockets plug you in,
Podcast the Right does its first live show
in over two years.
Yeah!
Hey!
Oh, you're right!
We love it.
Okay, it's the moment.
Let's...
Okay, it's...
All right, hold, I never get this right.
Hold on, again.
There's the center pad, which way does that go?
I know, it's always the center.
Yeah, okay.
You know what?
This may be more of a one person thing,
so why don't you take that?
All right, yeah, yeah, okay.
Just let me look forward there and let's see it in one sec.
You know what?
I'd say close enough.
Okay, let's do this!
Yeah!
Yeah, all right, let's see those hands, people!
You got clearance, it's Podcast the Right Live!
Wow!
Hi, hello!
Whoa, hi!
Hello, oh, I still have a tail!
I forgot about the tail.
What tail?
Us, we've been dressed for years and we're out!
We're us!
We're finally out!
And you're out too, you're out in a real place!
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, a theme park about podcasts
that's coming to you live from a room
of 200 people who are not on Zoom!
This is not on Zoom!
I think you said a theme park about podcasts.
A theme park, oh geez, I'm just so excited!
I'm getting mixed up!
We're rusty at doing a live show, folks!
So yeah, we're gonna say things tonight
that are gonna be weird!
Yes, brain farts aplenty.
Hopefully just brain farts.
No real farts.
No, we can promise.
We'll try to promise that.
That's not our humor.
It's a bit bawdy.
That would be a bit bawdy.
No, no, no.
Well, speaking of getting mixed up,
we forgot the part where we say our names.
My name is Scott Gardner, hi, everybody.
Hi, I'm Jason Sheridan.
And your names?
I'm Jason Sheridan.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Hi, I'm Michael Carlson.
Hey.
Mike Carlson, whatever.
I say Mike on the show, why did I say Michael?
You're giving your official sag registered name
to the audience.
Well, no, I didn't even do that.
My sag name is Michael R. Carlson.
Yeah.
Because there is already a Michael Carlson
or is there a Mike Carlson?
I forget.
I hate him.
Get out of the business.
Boo.
Leave room for our Michael Carlson.
Just to take things down for a sec, this is incredible.
I'm so happy you guys are here.
We've waited so long to do this.
I thought so much through those,
I probably like pathetically practiced to a wall like,
hey, if I get to ride this live,
we're back for the first time in four months
and then it kept getting longer and longer and longer.
But now we're here, we're doing it
and a dynasty typewriter, which we love.
We're so happy.
Thank you.
Oh, this feels great.
Yeah, I'm glad people are still here.
And there's still, you're like,
two years is a long time.
You're like, yeah, there's a new theme park podcast
we like now.
That's possible.
No way.
There's a bunch of people that do a theme park podcast
not just about Aerosmith.
Like they don't talk about it.
You know what I like about this theme park podcast?
No Aerosmith talk.
I could see that being refreshing.
It's possible.
Yes.
I wouldn't be mad.
I wouldn't hold it against you guys.
A podcast about theme parks that talks about rides
more often.
We have it's appeal.
Aren't there enough of those?
He's right.
Jason's right.
We're doing it perfectly.
So, but thank you for coming.
Thank you, God.
If we're getting cheap reactions from everybody,
there's one thing that I've dreamed about
in all of this time.
I've really been waiting for this
and I hope you guys can help me out with it.
Okay, here we go.
If I need to make a telephone call.
I'll use the air.
Okay, you asked for it.
That's the new one.
Asshole Mickey in the house.
Asshole Mickey's here.
I don't think I can do Mickey after Rocket.
That's not a good voice cocktail.
No.
Yeah, that's too hard.
Rocketified.
Can I say real quick as far as if we're gonna get
some cheap reactions.
Yes, that's all it's gonna be.
As I was driving here, and I didn't realize this
because obviously it wasn't on my radar,
maybe the last time I was driving through Echo Park,
there is a street called Clifford Drive.
Like five minutes from here.
And I thought that was a good sign.
I thought that that was a sign the show was gonna go well.
Yeah, absolutely.
And I got out and I kissed the sign.
I got back in the car and I drove through.
We haven't had the chance to,
the Clifford's thing is new.
By round of applause.
Somebody made a noise that they're sick.
They got sick to the stomach.
What should we do first?
Any reaction's a good reaction, right?
By round of applause, do you like the show?
Do you like being called Clifford's?
That's pretty good.
Yeah, yeah, I'm worried though.
By round of applause, do you not like being called Clifford's?
A substantial showing for the latter.
I think honestly, I think there was less people
but stronger claps.
That's my reading of it.
They've been storing it up for a long time.
Yeah, yeah.
Geez, yeah, it's been a long time.
It feels really great.
The last time that we were in front
of an audience of any kind,
it was a pop-up performance art show
in an about to close electronics store in Anaheim.
That's right.
I got to be in a video for Fry's Electronics
for precisely two days before the store shut down forever.
That's probably the reason it got to happen in general.
Was anyone here at that also?
Oh, great, okay.
Thank you. Thank you.
Well, you got to see the home theater screening room,
which seemed like it was about to collapse on us
when we were sitting in there.
Yeah, the wrecking ball might have come through
right then and there.
Yeah, knocking the asbestos right out of the walls.
Just a bunch of dorks in there, who cares?
Yeah.
So that's the last time we were in front of you.
There is a, I'm so glad you guys are back.
There was one special guest at that occasion,
which was my son, and oh geez, he was, thank you.
You knew what you were doing.
I wasn't sure.
At that point in time, he was negative six weeks old,
and he was still in the womb.
Now, so much time has passed, he is almost two years old.
And my wonderful wife Erin and I just had the great occasion
of taking him to Disneyland for the first time.
We have a photo.
Look at that!
Pretty cute, huh?
Had to get some cheap applause for that.
There he is, eyeing his next victim.
Pretty young, huh?
Too late for you.
Another one of your dad's kind, huh?
Your dad's making money off my back.
I hear, I hear him a little joke saving,
and I'm keeping score.
There's a reason we vet who comes to Galactic Starclozer.
Nonetheless, yeah, wonderful moment.
And you know, we did a lot of fun stuff with him
that day, one thing that we did not take him on,
can't imagine how this could have been possible,
but he was not allowed on the ride
that is the topic for tonight's episode,
which if you hadn't guessed already,
it is related to what we started doing earlier tonight.
We were talking- But what if it wasn't?
Hey, it's the teacups, surprise!
We did tie these things together.
Tonight we are talking about
Guardians of the Galaxy mission breakouts.
Yes.
I'm excited, you know, it was a big night,
and I think we had to do a big one and a fun one.
I've been thinking about,
I've been a little self-conscious about,
so far in 2022, it's been a lot of weird,
unpleasant shit, right?
I mean, I've been thinking about,
it's been a lot of weird, unpleasant shit, right?
Wait, wait, that we've done, or just in general?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I mean, but you know, because it's been all these,
these failed restaurant tours- Restaurants, yeah.
And-
Air Armageddon.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Not so much talking about the possibility of Armageddon,
but the ride- The ride itself.
Armageddon is good, the movie's good, the ride is bad.
Right, right.
Jay Bigga, we've had to-
Yeah.
Through, that's not the worst thing.
And ladies and gentlemen, joining us tonight.
Joining us tonight to beat the shit out of us.
He hates being called a Clifford too.
No, but this, I think, I'm so excited to do,
for a celebration, which this is tonight,
to do a ride that is a celebration that's a lot of fun
and that I think we're all extremely fond of.
I think so.
And with that, let's step two steps backwards
into our chairs.
Ah.
Yeah.
Oh, wonderful.
Oh, it's getting rough.
A podcaster's natural position.
All the way back.
Leaning back.
Scratching.
Really making a meal out of it.
Yeah, so we're doing Guardians of the Galaxy
mission breakout, which is different.
The last time we were at Dynasty, we did Superstar Limo.
Which is not as, I mean, popular for all of you.
But not for like a normal person.
And I mean that in the best way.
But-
That's when people go on.
A lot of people-
People go on it.
They get excited to go on it.
Yeah, where to start?
Well, you know what's one thing maybe is,
we're leading it by saying that we all
like this attraction, a lot of the three of us.
But what is, what are your opinions?
I keep turning to the audience.
I'm curious.
I guess I'm so excited to have one.
Gonna turn this into a Mori or something.
Let's go to the audience.
What's the question?
I guess like-
I think Tower of Terror is a ride everyone loves.
But in hindsight now, I think let's get the same
applause-o-meter that we did for the Clifford's question.
And let's ask, are you happy now that this was changed
to Guardians or are you still mad and you want Tower back?
So let's do the first question.
Are you happy they changed this to Guardians of the Galaxy?
Pretty good.
Pretty sustained.
Okay, now are you upset?
This is the same thing though.
Less people, stronger claps.
I know it.
I can hear it.
Those are sweaty claps.
Yeah.
That's like, somebody's gonna throw their shoulder
out doing it, like trying to get that, the volume up.
Stinging now.
Hard claps for the abbreviated Tower of Terror.
The abbreviated like quick fix for California Adventure.
It's like the Chili's to go of Tower of Terror.
Yeah.
Do we think there's anything about that Tower of Terror
as opposed to the other ones?
That you know, it's not this new story like Japan had.
It's not like markedly worse and boring like Paris.
The same as what we had.
I don't know what I'm saying.
But like, was there anything like, only that tower had it?
No, right?
Is there anything anyone could shout out that's like,
this is this one.
Is there something special about it?
Yeah.
Yeah, no.
The answer's not.
You're answering for.
Yeah.
Which, yeah.
It was nice to have the Tower of Terror here.
I will say that.
I wasn't mad, but I liked the Tower of Terror a lot.
Avoid some plane trips.
What was that?
No Chris Pratt.
Got him.
That wasn't picked up.
You know he's gonna be in like a Tower of Terror movie
in the next 10 years.
And they would have added him to it.
It was bound to happen.
Well, there was, you know, people were a little bit mad
when this change out was announced.
There was, I think summer of 2016,
the rumors started flying about this.
And it seemed like a weird rumor.
Oh yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
It was, I remember where I was.
I'm not kidding.
We were at Comic-Con, I believe, when the rumor popped up.
And then it was announced at Comic-Con too, wasn't it?
Yeah.
I think so.
Was all those people flooded out of the room,
screaming and flailing?
It was.
I mean, that's a pretty warm audience to announce it.
Yeah.
I feel like.
Jim Hill mentioned it a few weeks before
I think it was announced.
It was like a, Jim Hill was like a trial balloon
to see how people would react.
But yeah, it was a crazy rumor.
It did feel like it was not, there's no way that's true.
It seemed very odd.
And then when it was officially announced
and then the turnaround time,
like it's announced in summer of 2016,
Tower of Terror closes January 2017.
Guardians opens May 27th, 2017.
Same day as Pandora World of Avatar
on the other coast.
Big weekend for Rhodey.
Big weekend for Joe Rhodey.
Yeah.
That's also, I mean, that's fast for any theme park company.
That is lightning fast for Disney.
Yeah, yeah.
That's part of what seemed weird about it, I would think.
Yeah.
No, Incredible.
That was him.
That was like Phil Collins getting to be at both LiveAids.
They're taking the Concord.
My favorite semi-relevant reference of people.
It's like that Foo Fighters releasing the acoustic album
and the electric album the same day.
You know?
Everyone's thinking about it.
Look, I'm in a good mood because we're in front of people
and I'm happy to be back.
So I will throw this your way.
Do you think that a reasonable analog is like,
Guardians of the Galaxy is like a perfect Green Day album
as opposed to one that is slightly less than perfect?
The answer is yes.
The answer is it's perfect like American Idiot or Dookie
or honestly, I like Nimrod a lot.
There's maybe a couple tracks you could cut,
but honestly, why would you?
I'm not in that good of a mood.
Fair enough.
I would love to see some Green Day on the ride, but...
But...
When they go 90s, when it's the 90s refresh.
Let me say something about when this announcement was made
and people who were not terribly happy about it.
I wouldn't have known about this article
except they flashed through it really quickly
in the Imagineering story when they're explaining all this.
There's an article in Slate
and the headline of the article is,
Disneyland's Tower of Terror is Closing.
This is a national tragedy.
And I got curious what the rest of it was.
An important context for the little bit I'm gonna read
is that this is from October 12th, 2016.
Just place yourself in what was happening then.
I'm bringing up an even worse time.
Chilled the room.
Okay, so I have clicked on what I think is an article
about a ride closing and getting replaced by another ride
that'll probably be okay.
And then it starts, this past Sunday,
as I watched one of our country's presidential nominees
threaten to put his opponent in prison,
I was reminded of my favorite quote by Friedrich Nietzsche.
Where are we?
Look, I guess I can't blame this person.
This is probably what any of us would have written
about any topic.
What do you think about gumballs?
Well...
What do you think about hot dogs?
Well, Baudrillard once said...
No, it's a crazy...
And then further in, and yet shortly before,
please, sweet merciful Christ on a pony,
someone who is not Donald Trump
takes the oath of office this coming January of 2017.
Oops.
The California Tower of Terror will take its final drop.
So...
Neither issue worked out the way
this late person wanted it to go.
On the brighter side, both Avatar and Guardians of the Galaxy
feature Zoe Saldana.
So there's that.
Yeah.
That's a little brighter, huh?
Right?
She's kind of the connection between the movie.
And I think soon they could introduce
the seed bearer's big seed into both of these attractions.
The seed bearer, one of the hypothetical titles of,
I think it's the third Avatar?
The way of water is second, okay?
So you put the seed bearer in the queue for Guardians,
and then you put the big seed...
No, you put the big seed in the queue,
and then the seed bearer does meet and greets at Pandora.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Sorry, I'm just blue-skying,
I just got a little caught up in it.
I'm just interested, do you think there's a very large seed
in that movie?
Okay.
I think, because I think if it's called the seed bearer,
it's one of two things.
There's either one real big seed,
or there's a person with a lot of little seeds.
And I think they're just gonna cheap out,
I think it's gonna be too cheap to just do a lot
of little seeds in the Guardians queue.
The seed bearer would seem to indicate there's one entity
that is the bearer.
So this entity would have to be very large
to carry a large seed.
Yeah, he's an avatar.
Or whatever they're called.
Okay, wait, okay, wait, well, I don't wanna get this
completely off the rails here, but when you say...
When you say large seed, do you mean like a foot?
Because that's a large seed.
Yeah, I think like a big thing, or it could be even bigger.
I mean, not to jump too far ahead,
like the Adam Warlock cocoon that's in the Guardians queue,
they could just swap out the sign and go, big seed.
The seed bearer's big seed.
But a seed is normally this big,
so even a five inch seed is a big seed.
Well, but it's not, but on the world of Pandora,
in the hallelujah mountains, that's not gonna grow much.
A little seed's not gonna grow much.
Not gonna grow much?
I think a five inch seed would grow a substantial.
I think it would grow, yeah.
No, it'll grow something, but you want,
I mean, if it's big trees with those big mountains.
What do you think the seed looked like
when there were like forests up in Northern California?
They were little.
At some point.
That's my point.
Maybe.
I'm surprised that I'm leaning Jason's way,
and I'll scoot this way to prove that I am,
but I think, okay, yeah, you're right,
the Northern California trees are big,
but that big tree in Avatar,
that's one of the hugest trees I've ever seen,
the one that burns down,
and they need a new one of those.
They can't wait around for a little seed to grow.
They gotta start big to get big.
Oh, so you think, okay, again,
not to get off the rails here, but you think,
when the seed is bigger,
the actual thing it's growing starts bigger.
Only in this universe, in the imagination of James Cameron.
So the answer is yes.
So it's almost like,
if it's a big seed, you put it in the ground,
and something grows that's like pony size
within like a week.
That's just a root.
So in the grand scheme of the tree,
that's just a little root.
Well, I guess we'll have to wait 11 years to find out.
Yeah.
Guardian.
Guardian of the galaxy.
Guardian was where this began.
Do you, okay, the movie, okay.
I like these movies.
Yeah.
Yeah, I think that's right.
I think the box office reflects that.
I think a lot of people like these movies, Michael.
Not like cult opinion, I guess.
They're fun movies.
I mean, look, it's not Citizen Kane, but it-
Do you typically judge things on that scale?
I'm a film aficionado
who only compares things to Citizen Kane.
So when you're watching one of your favorite films,
such as the Paul Lind Halloween special.
That's true.
Is this a Citizen Kane?
Will they make a ride
based on the Paul Lind Halloween special?
So I was like reasonably, like, I definitely was like,
when I heard that, I was like,
ah, this seems, it seems like a bad idea.
I did think that, even though I was like,
oh, the movies are a fun little distraction.
Yeah, if we unpack that, yeah, why did we think,
I guess maybe the rush job nature of it,
and maybe it seemed a little gross.
Like let's just jam a currently popular thing in
as fast as possible.
That could have mixed results.
And it did seem like, I guess I was thinking
Tower of Terror seemed untouchable.
I think that's like, as much as we like to make fun of,
like when people pick it when a ride is going away,
there are still a bunch of things that like,
I go, well, I never, and I get very upset.
Like that Polynesian weird hotel thing,
like they're the expansion.
I was like, I am so, like, I'm embarrassed
that I'm like so upset about this.
But it definitely felt, yeah, like when,
when they announced the change, I was like,
well, that's not gonna, how would that work?
Show me how that would work.
And at that time in 2016, 17, you're like,
this is the angriest announcement
from the Disney company will ever make me.
Nothing could be worse.
Actually, to tie things together,
I think that the reason that this happened
is it is, it's 2016 or so, and Disney's owned Marvel
for like five years.
And they're looking around and saying,
we've not done anything like big and permanent with Marvel.
Why are we not?
And I think the person leading this charge
was the then chairman of Perks and Resorts,
whose name is Bob Shaping.
Oh, yeah.
I thought everybody could use.
We knew that was coming, sure, yeah.
Feels pretty good in this voice.
Yeah, you heard us.
Was this his last win?
Cause it's just been L after L since then.
It's a stunning record at this point.
It's really, yeah.
Of like basic corporate confidence,
or competence, I should say.
Yeah, so he was there, he was there at the.
Yeah, so I think he was feeling it.
This gets presented to Joe Roady,
who is refreshingly not towing the party line.
I feel like in every interview that I found Joe Roady doing
about this attraction, that he admits
that his initial thought was, that sounds stupid.
So if your first reaction was that, Mike,
and that was the reaction of the person who made the thing.
Right, so Joe and I, same page.
Hmm?
As far as our feelings, yeah.
That's why we wandered into his collection
to try to connect on this point.
Right, yeah.
And then we were stuck for two years.
So anyway, he fights through that.
That's what he said, that's impossible,
that's a dumb idea, but then you have
to work your way through that.
I don't think they knew it was Guardians of the Galaxy
initially, apparently they considered something
with Spider-Man, they considered something
with Doctor Strange, I don't know what those could've been,
but Guardians of the Galaxy was extremely popular
at that moment, and then the second one on the way,
they're filming it as they're having this idea,
which means everybody's in one place,
and they can actually film stuff with the cast,
which they did, all our favorites are back.
Most of the audience's favorites are back.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, it's interesting to think,
because Spider-Man makes some sense, I feel like.
You're going up and down, maybe it's a skyscraper
of some kind, Doctor Strange, his Sanctum Sanctorum
is a very famous building that we all know and love.
It's a creepy building full of portals
and other dimensional beings.
I'm sitting here thinking, do we talk about
the Sanctum Sanctorum on the show a lot,
or do Mike and I just talk about Sanctum Sanctorum a lot
in our personal life to each other?
How many people, should we ask the audience again?
Does anybody remember us saying the word Sanctum Sanctorum?
Yeah.
Not enough, apparently.
Not enough.
So we're gonna up that, don't worry.
It's gonna be on every other episode now.
So yeah, that makes sense that you would have
a weird elevator journey with Doctor Strange, I don't know.
I don't know that there's a famous elevator,
I don't know if Stanley and Steve Dicco
had a famous elevator, but you could have
retconned that in, I think.
But it does make sense, it all makes sense.
For something that's like a retool of an old ride,
it does make a lot of, it's really smartly done.
He really did it.
Joe, Joe Rudy.
He did, you're right that there's an odd,
and maybe some of what he bumped on is that
it is an elevator, ultimately, it is your vehicle.
And it was an elevator that was meant to be
an elevator in this hotel, but now almost
anything else you do with it, probably it needs
to not be an elevator.
And now we're in the world of science fiction
and comic books and fantasy, so we can turn this
into anything that we can dream up.
And where we land is Gantry Lift.
Yeah.
We are in a Gantry Lift.
Has anyone heard this phrase before in your life?
Well, Jason mentions this on the show,
that his dad dunked on him.
Yeah, I got my ass roasted by my dad,
who grew up during the space age, and he's like,
anyone who grew up watching multiple rocket launches,
they all they did was talk about the astronauts
are boarding the Gantry Lift, like again and again.
So, yeah, the boomers did something right.
Gantry Lifts, congrats, Ken.
Gantry Lift, I mean, it is good.
Like, you have to give it up for this ride,
because there's so many different things
that like just are burrowed now in our brains,
in the same way that any like ride
that's been there for 50 years, like Gantry Lift,
it's a phrase I'll never forget.
I'll be in a retirement home and I'll be like,
Gantry Lift, Gantry Lift.
I'll be like, oh, Mr. Carlson's talking
about a Gantry Lift again.
Sanctum Centaur.
Nimrod, perfect track listing.
Green Day.
Mighty Akron, something only I said.
I did that, I did that.
If Mighty Akron has a phrase
is in one of the Avatar movies, it's because of me.
It's true.
They don't say it in the movie.
It's me.
That Mighty Akron is choking on that giant seed.
If that happens in the movie,
I'm gonna be like both thrilled and upset at the same time.
Entitled to royalties, yes.
Yeah.
So we got a Gantry Lift.
What else in terms of like thinking out this thing?
Well, another step of it, I think, with Rhodey
is like, it's a hotel, what else do you turn this thing into?
Then he takes a walk, he looks at it, and he thinks,
well, as long as you take the signage off,
there's not a lot here that necessarily says hotel,
which is kind of fourth dimensional on his part
because I see hotel.
I don't think anybody could have imagined
what it would, like what it is,
which is the collector's fortress,
is not like an immediate, like it is weird and crazy.
I remember you saying that pre-podcast,
we weren't doing it, we were just doing it to ourselves.
And you were.
Yeah.
To our significant others, talking to ourself.
But I remember you being, Mikey being an early adopter
of like, as soon as that art was out,
I think you're like, this thing's weird.
And maybe weird is good.
Yes, I felt like a Jack Kirby or Steve Ditko
or some like old, bizarre like monstrosity.
Colors don't really match.
It ended up looking a little different, I feel like,
than the concept art, but like,
it definitely was like right up my alley
as far as being like a bizarre like base.
Like as a child, I was obsessed with like the base
of a villain or the heroes.
Like I was, I've said this before,
I was obsessed with where people slept.
Like I loved knowing where the Ghostbusters
were, where their beds were.
And as a kid, I, who you know what I'm talking about?
You were really hoping to see the collectors like caught
behind the desk at the office.
I would, yeah, do you think he sleeps in a cot?
Like when he shows that he wants to work long hours,
like on the Theranos show where it's like,
here's my sleeping bag.
I'm a total psycho, I sleep at the office sometimes.
I mean, yeah, I would look,
I would like to see his sleeping bag.
I would like to see his cot.
I would like to see all that stuff.
So when I saw it, it felt like a crazy,
weird comic book thing, which is like now with the,
the Vendors Campus is like such a,
and I like it, I will say this,
I don't know if we've talked about it a lot.
I think we've come around a little even more
to a Vendors Campus lately in general,
but I will say the thing that's like a nonsense thing,
the comic book thing is still the Guardians Tower.
It still looks like a crazy thing that like I would scribble
on a notebook when I was in third grade,
which I think is good.
And it's been annexed.
It's now an Avengers Campus.
Yes, it is technically an Avengers Campus
and they added the blue goo,
which I don't know, am I getting my head on myself
by talking about the blue goo already?
You can talk about the blue goo
whenever your heart desires.
The, which is the Kirby Crackle.
Yeah, it's supposed to be like energy.
I hear applause for the Kirby Crackle.
The Kirby Crackle.
We love to see it.
The Crackle is like energy,
like how Jack Kirby would draw energy or whatever.
It definitely looks more like goo,
but it looks a lot like goo.
It looks like we're trying, you know, I like it.
So yeah, cause the initial story of the ride was that,
I guess there was a Tower of Terror was there
and then all of a sudden the Guardians Tower thing
just like planted.
It appeared.
Yes. It appeared.
Yeah, this is what Joe Roady said.
This is a story just like, you know,
one day a big lock with the Avengers logo showed up.
We remember the big lock.
We should do an episode on the big lock.
Wait, when you say lock, do you mean the like thing
in the ground?
The big latch like thing in the ground.
That was more of like a manhole cover or something.
Yeah, I don't know.
Not really a lock.
Well, look, this is an hour.
We're going to have to figure out what to call it.
And that's a second gate.
And that's how the magic gets made.
Yeah.
Got one.
Collected.
A seed.
Perfect.
No, you're right.
In the story of the ride, it is that like,
this just appeared one day.
Yeah.
So I guess the campus was there and then the collector's
building just appeared out of nowhere as if it was
transported there.
And that's as far as we know.
That's all we know.
Okay. Yes.
Which is pretty mysterious, I guess.
And that leaves us a lot to figure out.
Yes.
So this ride is based around,
the collector is the character Tantalier Tavon.
Tantalier Tavon.
Tantalier, not Tantalier.
No, not Tantalier.
I like Chanticleer.
Chanticleer?
No.
I like Tantalier.
Tantalier is a little like more coy.
I'm Tantalier Tavon.
You should consider putting an extra T in there.
No, I'll just leave it to you to say.
I'll just say Tavon from this point.
Sure.
But he's from, he's from Guardians, the movie,
but it's not a big part.
So it's a little weird that there's a whole ride
with a lot of him.
Benicio del Toro being the actor who plays him.
Yes, it is.
He has like one scene in the first Guardians.
Does he have a scene in the second one?
He's in an Infinity War as well.
But again, another like one scene.
Yeah.
And they took him and then they made.
This is like the most Benicio content that exists
is in the theme park ride.
It's like he has like one.
No, excuse me.
He has a post credit scene in a different Marvel movie
as well and I can't remember what it was.
Thor.
I, a lot of Thor, the dark world fans out here.
Often considered the worst Marvel movie.
All of the Thor, the dark world fans are here.
I like the end of, I think the last 30 minutes
of Thor, the dark world are good.
I think those are good minutes.
That's how we're wrapping up the show.
We're just gonna play those.
We're just gonna show the, yeah.
So yeah, so he's, what was that?
He's also in What If.
Oh, well he's in What If.
He's in What If, the cartoon which I have not seen.
What, people upset about that?
Am I not a big enough nerd for you?
I got other things.
First of all, I have to get to Yellowstone.
I'm gonna get to it.
Saying yes.
I'm gonna watch Yellowstone.
More pressure on you.
Yellowstone before What If.
So in the same way that like Hondo and Naka,
it's like the, I like, it's a kind of a Disney tradition.
I feel like to take a character
that's not the main character and make it.
Flesh it out a little.
Yeah, make that the kind of focal point of the ride.
Or of the pre-show, I should say.
Maybe as close as we're getting in a way
because we don't get a lot of original IP.
So the most original you can get is something
that somebody we haven't really met.
Yeah. Little.
He's kind of a background guy.
Exactly, so.
Take what we can get.
Benicio's great.
Obviously he's a very interesting actor.
And I get.
People thought I meant that sincerely.
Should we put, if we're talking Benicio,
should we pull up a clip?
Yeah, why don't we?
Yes, yes.
This odd, I don't know if people here saw
the opening ceremony of this attraction.
That was a weird hush.
I don't know what that means.
It is a fun opening ceremony, I'll say that.
Because they have some executives giving very dry,
we're so excited for this new innovation.
And then they've got some celebs there.
And they do like.
Go Rooker.
Rooker's there.
Rooker.
Yondu.
Yondu, that's right.
It's his character.
Also.
Yondu.
Yeah, I like Yondu.
He's got the arrow.
He shoots an arrow.
I have no idea what he is.
He's blue.
I'm experiencing him by applause.
You are more of like a Rooker in Mallrats guy.
Yeah, remember he eats the thing with the poop on his hands?
With the pretzel.
Chocolate covered pretzel.
Why watch other movies where you can just watch
the View-ist Universe over and over and over again?
Exactly.
This video, this opening ceremony,
where were you saying something else about?
Oh no, no.
I was just setting up the clip.
This is kind of the end of the opening ceremony.
And we got a little surprise.
Well it's a bunch of celebrities are introduced
as themselves.
They come out and do nothing.
And then they smile.
And then there's a big sudden interruption.
By the way, original character I think,
Afida, might be saying it wrong, who knows?
But I think it's the pink girl who holds her hands
where I think is original to this attraction.
Yeah, she's in the movie.
No, all right, all right.
Well I read that somewhere.
So the sight was wrong, not me.
Right, that's how it works.
Say the sight, say the sight.
What is it, magicmouse.com?
Bumper car boys, rumors and news.
Boo.
Let me astray again.
You sons of bitches.
We'll get them, sorry.
All right, here we go.
Opening ceremony.
Oh my, he's here, he's here.
Everyone, prepare yourselves.
Terence, it is time to introduce James.
James is kind of saying hello to someone during this.
I have great assistance to come to your planet
and humbly grace you with this blessing.
He's like, doesn't seem too worried.
Where have you been, James?
I'm here.
Shape X having a giggle.
Shadowy figure approaching.
Who is it?
Oh my gosh.
Can't see, too much mist.
Benicio.
You're Benicio del Toro.
Hello.
You can't be here.
The collector would not be pleased.
A Terran cannot stand in his place.
Oh, I don't think you'll mind.
I'm here to
the opening of the Tyvon collection.
Ladies and gentlemen, of terror,
the Tyvon collection is officially open.
How about that?
I like that, this fireworks and stuff.
Great.
Those are maybe, those are like the two most
mismatched actors I've ever seen.
Giant theme park energy, whatever shall we do?
He does seem amused to be there.
He also, if I can remind everyone at the time,
Benicio del Toro was the spokesman for Heineken
and it seems like he just came from the rap party.
I like to think he had like three Carthay Manhattans.
And then came over there.
Knew what he was doing, he would have, yeah.
So that's great.
And that, the opening of the attraction
kind of marks the immediate turn,
where everybody's upset and there's
change.org petitions and stuff.
The people, again it's 2016, people have like
anger free time on their hands.
They don't know how busy they're gonna be
with petitions soon enough.
But pretty quickly, upon the opening of the
attraction, it like, it turns so fast.
Like as soon as anybody goes on it,
this is great and really fun and inventive.
Can I ask the audience, was anyone there on opening day?
Oh wow, that got no response, okay.
I will tell you who was at opening day, Mike and I.
We were there and I believe, correct me if I'm wrong,
we waited.
We waited like four and a half hours.
Were we there opening day?
I swore it was opening day.
Maybe it was a day later.
I thought it was opening day because we waited
four and a half hours.
It might have been opening day but we definitely
waited four and a half hours with like a bunch of like,
we were backstage, like we were in weird places.
We were waiting in weird places.
That's how big the line was.
And then we shared a Hulk donut.
Yes, filled with apple pie filling, the Hulk's favorite.
It's those little details in the parks, you know?
Those little Marvel details.
The Hulk, true believers, I wanna tell you something
about the Hulk.
He loves apple pie filling.
Excelsior.
We remember the Stan Soapbox where he said it.
We had something else too, didn't we split something else?
I think we, I think you got something at Schmoozy's
and then went, this is disgusting and I finished it.
Yeah.
The perfect pair.
What'd you do without each other?
He's Jason, as I've said many times,
he's eaten soup after me.
Well not in the last two and a half years.
I mean not, go on.
It was at Disneyland.
And it was actually a bit.
Disneyland soup?
It was at, no, no, it was a bisque.
It was the bisque at the.
Oh fancy, I'd like to think that was all sarcastic.
I don't think it was.
I was being made fun of, yeah.
I was being made fun of by the audience.
Well, so, well the four and a half hours
gave you plenty of time to admire,
well first some random dumpsters and delivery roads.
But once you got into the building itself,
the collector's fortress itself, many treasures.
Yeah, yeah, the queue itself is great.
The loop has got a lot of weird pitch down noises
and it's like, the collector's not just a collector
of things, he's a collector of sounds.
He loves sounds.
And foliage too, there's a lot of plants in the line
and I read something that the Imagineers called it
the gardens of the galaxy and I think that's real cute.
It is, it is cute.
You get this video where you meet the collector
and he kind of gives you the gist of things
and you see the guardians trapped in their cages.
A lot is explained to you there.
A big info dump video but a fun info dump video.
And they're in no mere cages, they are in cages
that are perfectly in the center of a big hollow building.
It's attached to a lot of power.
He's a collector of power too, of sounds and power
and spikes and big spiky gears which are way below
the guardians so if you think them just stepping
out of the cage will be enough, think again.
Yes, it's full of, with all this, look,
I have not seen this new Batman, okay?
But guardians are the- Yellowstone first.
Yellowstone first, what if?
Then the Pattinson Batman.
But it's full of nonsense.
The Guardians of the Galaxy is full of nonsense.
This is what I love as a kid, crazy contraptions
that could never be built.
It's not like grounding the collector,
like you go and see him buy the cages from Home Depot
which is how you would do it in the newer Batmans
where it's so grounded in reality.
You see him construct the cages and the cages
have to be a certain height and his base,
you have to watch him sign the rental agreement for it.
It's like grounded in reality.
We need to see how this happened.
We don't need to see the cages be constructed
in his tower where we- I figured out your clue, Riddler.
I listened to your podcast.
Does the Riddler have a podcast in the new movie?
No, kind of. Kind of.
I feel like I have heard that and then I was worried
I made it up.
He has a Twitch channel.
Okay, so he's hitting all the social media.
Got it, got it, okay.
Well, so this will age as well as the maze
of flip phone feeds in Dark Knight.
So many flip phones, gonna triangulate 400 flip phones.
We have to tap into the signal of all the flip phones.
We have to flip them open and then track them.
Verbatim dialogue from the Dark Knight.
Let me see. Sorry.
Let me see your Motorola razor
so I can reverse engineer your Motorola razor.
I probably will like this, man.
I'm just saying, it's all full of nonsense that I,
as a kid, I liked.
Why I liked all this stuff is like crazy bases
and stupid stuff that is impossible to build.
Well, speaking of like crazy little kid stuff in this,
very quickly in this video, you get the Stan Lee cameo.
Yes.
Who has just one line, there's like a bunch of items
are trapped and he is the first thing that lets you know
that living beings are trapped in this facility as well.
And he says, hey, do you guys validate?
And it's like as silly corn balls, anything Stan Lee does.
And now listen, I'm no Marvel person,
I've proven that time and time again.
But I love these, I love the Stan Lee cameo.
Really?
And I bet, I do, especially in this,
because it just reminded me how much I like that like,
at least there is, there'll be one part of any
of these things that feels like a seventies variety special.
That's true.
Or when we had, I think we've lost this now a little bit,
because certain Marvel things are to me,
Be careful.
endless death slogs that are very boring and confusing.
I don't know what anything is.
Well, now.
Now hold on, that endless death slog is gonna pay off
in the fifth Spider-Man.
Okay.
Problem is you aren't watching enough endless death slogs.
It's still planning, so it's like when Arrested Velming
would do like a call forwards.
Yeah.
But if there was, you know, some of these that have been
kind of a trudge recently, if there was just that one
little thing puncturing fit, like a guy who is as good
at acting as Ralph Nader hosting SNL in the seventies.
Doesn't know where to look, he's done so many of them
and still it's just as bad.
He was in his nineties.
This is one of the last appearances that I have to think.
It could be one of them, or it could be like the tenth
to last, I'm trying to think.
He was in, was he in one of the Infinity Wars?
He's in both.
He's in both of them, okay.
What's the second one?
He's in the seventies, he drives by, he says,
he's in the car.
And that's the last one, right?
Yeah.
Perfect.
Well.
A perfect way to go out is in that, is the end of the first
whatever phase.
Color me impressed, sir, thank you for your help.
Yeah, it's, yeah, it's, he's, I'm trying to think about
my feelings about Stan.
He, what I think I liked about Marvel, and I love DC,
what I liked about Marvel was like his weird nonsense,
like his jokey tone that they kept literally in the movies
with him, like he was literally in there where it was
oftentimes not completely like deathly serious,
like DC, now there's obviously like 60s Batman's nonsense,
nonsensical, but in a good way.
Maybe he did one, what if he did, he pre-filmed a post
credits for the last Marvel movie, whenever that is.
Well, when is the, when is this, when did the scientists say
we, how long do they say we have?
50 years or something, or is that just 50 years until
it's like we have to stay inside all again?
And watch all the stuff, and what then, hopefully by then
you'll be watching Yellowstone, Michael.
I hope, I hope.
Let's talk about some of the stuff that you see,
because so much like, yeah, the stuff in the fortress
is extremely cool and great for theme park nerds,
because there's so many fun Easter egg-y things.
We have pictures of a couple of them, or the, well,
feel free to call it anything that,
first, because there's Marvel stuff too.
The big one I think is, the big one in the universe
is Cosmo, which is all, like, I wanna see that robot dog,
almost as good as the ride itself is this robot dog
that's in one of the things you feel bad,
because he's like caught in a cage, but he's got,
he's very cute, I think we can all agree.
The Cosmo is cute.
Very cute.
Cosmo is very cute.
The other animatronics, the, is it Vilous?
The little guys that kinda like look around
that they added at some point, those are cute?
Yeah, like the technology where like,
I think it can see your eyes, like it knows,
like if you're looking at them.
Like motion tracking.
Yeah, which obviously is some sort of
crazy war technology.
Yeah.
But being used for cute aliens.
But those are great.
You've got a Nova Corps outfit, I believe, in the corner.
I mentioned the big Adam Warlock egg,
which really gives me a lot of joy as a comic book fan,
because when I was a kid, Warlock comics,
and a lot of the Infinity War stuff, was quarter bin fodder.
Like it may as well have been garbage,
or like you're buying it to line your bird's bird cage.
And now it is the biggest thing in the world.
Yeah, did you read, were you a big Adam Warlock fan?
That's not a character that's not appeared yet.
I believe in the next one is appearing.
I think so, yeah, they're setting it up.
Yes, I'm hearing yes.
But did you, like, were you imagining,
like living inside his egg?
I really couldn't make heads nor tails of it.
And it all looked very like stuffy and old fashioned,
compared to like, you know, Jim Lee and Mark Silvestri
and stuff, drawing giant guys with big pouches
and giant guns and sexy ladies, you know?
This is where I crack a beer.
Yeah.
Proceed, gentlemen.
What, what?
Every, there's little runs on the podcast.
Like it happened earlier when they were talking
about Green Day albums, where we just retreat
into our mind palaces.
And we were just, you know.
What do you think I'm doing?
Yeah.
Who's the, Jason, who's the sassiest
of the ladies on the X-Men?
The sassiest?
You just said a sassy lady.
Well, I said sexy ladies, but sassy.
Oh, you said sexy?
Well, yeah.
Jason, this is podcast The Ride.
Body, body.
You know, it's a cabaret, it's an old comedy theater.
You gotta be a little blue.
Is this a burlesque theater to you?
Is this a burlesque show?
I don't know.
Look at these lights.
Who knows what was here a hundred years ago?
Now let's wave those pasties around.
Yeah.
They're just, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Wait, hold on.
Let me cut you off right there.
Who's the sexiest of the X-Men?
Well, we don't have enough time.
We don't have enough time.
Scott just revealed that he liked Gadget
from Inspector Gadget, or Inspector Gadget
from the Rescue Rangers.
Yeah, why not?
You just got to select Inspector Gadget.
I like Inspector Gadget too, yeah.
I mean, imagine the possibilities.
The possibilities are endless.
So many tools and toys.
That's like your darling Nicky situation.
My what?
Your darling Nicky situation.
Prince's darling Nicky, a song about,
a body song by an artist named Prince,
who had devices.
She had a lot of devices.
I don't want to.
Michael, the short answer to your question
in terms of sassiness would be the Southern Belle rogue.
Am I right, people?
Woo!
Yeah!
The first time rogues got
in a poppet dynasty typewriter, I think.
Yeah.
Let's talk about the theme park stuff that you see.
Yes.
The people who, the characters,
the loved ones who they've trapped.
Yes.
And who we get to sort of see again.
So yeah, I mean, the big one, our old friend, Figment.
Figment.
Get him!
Through very foggy glass.
The foggiest glass.
And we asked Tony Baxter, Figment's daddy, we asked him.
Yeah.
Tony's W-2 for a long time.
We asked him when we interviewed him a few years ago,
we said, what do you feel about that?
And he said, I like it, but I wish you could see him.
Yeah.
Oh.
Has he ever put his hands against the glass,
like a prison visit?
Or like the end of Armageddon.
They, yeah, he brings them.
Don't wanna miss a thing.
So yeah, it would be nice
if they could get that glass a little cleaner.
Unless it's the new Figment, in which case stay there.
Oh yeah.
Who else?
We have.
Oh yeah, the original Yeti.
Pretty good.
That new Yeti is awesome, I will say though.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yep.
All right, so he can stay there, that's fine.
I think maybe everybody's well placed.
This octopus from Country Bear's.
Dolores.
Dolores C. Octopus from the.
Hell yeah.
Country Bear Vacation.
Beautiful world.
That's fun.
So and I've said this before on the show,
it is interesting to me that now it is canon
that the collector, Tanelier Tavon,
is a big Disney Parks fan.
He loves Disney Parks.
I assume he has Park Stars, the vinyl toys that I do.
And he's probably got a collection
that rivals Richard Crafts.
Yeah.
He will have his own.
Well now he does.
Crafts sold a bunch of that stuff.
Yeah, that's true.
Now he's number one.
Right, right.
Yeah.
But it does keep going and going,
and those are the ones that you know about
and that have been published and put in lists of Easter eggs.
But there's one, you really gotta have an eagle eye
to see some of the other ones
that you might not know about.
Yeah.
So other deep Disney lore
that is deep in the collector's fortress.
If you look close, really near the Eddie,
you can see the never installed Hillary robot.
Yeah.
We're almost done.
Just had one hand to go.
Pretty sure about it.
Yeah.
These are kind of,
you can see these kind of all over the place in the queue.
There's a bunch of crates of unsold Lasseter wine.
Terribly wanted today.
There's even this stuff on the desk,
on the collector's desk,
like for instance, you can actually see the shredded plans
for the Avengers E-ticket.
Yeah.
Don't need that anymore.
And elsewhere, if you look close,
this is kind of a recent edition.
They actually kept the secret memo for billionaires only
where Robert Iger got the early tip that COVID was coming.
You're Mr. Iger, quit now,
from the secret billionaire society.
Nice letterhead, lets you know what it is.
And this is some of the,
a lot of this is more recent stuff,
but they nodded the past two
because we love the classic stuff.
And that's why they kept Walt's strike settling going.
Yeah.
Break the glass, it's happening again.
So keep an eye out for those the next time you go.
Yeah.
Look close.
You know, you get through all of this stuff
and you get closer and closer to the office.
And this is where I should reiterate
until recently, this ride scared the hell out of me.
I was not doing it for a long time.
And finally, with some courage and alcohol as well,
I began doing it.
Alcohol is a coping mechanism.
That's a good thing, right?
Yeah.
Healthy.
But I should say, I still,
this is like as far as I go in terms of thrills
and I'm still really unnerved throughout.
But like that like engine room,
I'm so edgy during,
you guys have been with me in that.
Aaron, my wife has a bunch of times.
I'm like different.
I'm a little like cagey.
Like don't talk to me.
Let me process this.
And then I hear the ding
and I'm not excited about the ding.
Like I'm going to do it.
I will do it.
And I'll be happy that I have done it.
But as of right now, I don't feel great.
But it hasn't gotten easier.
A little bit easier.
Because I know that it's fun.
I have now started to accept that it is really fun.
And I mean, in a way, maybe more fun.
Splash Mountain, which I overcame
with the help of Figman's daddy himself.
That's still, I think the,
I think the earnest special still looms too large.
The special where Ernest was,
if I, if Ernest was scared on the guardians ride,
I don't know if I'd ever get over it.
Yeah.
I'm not fighting that.
Well, I've said this before.
I went on it, guys, a couple of years ago with my friend.
And we went on it five times in a row.
And I think that if there's a way to get over it,
that's the way maybe you should do it.
Although I guess with the new
like lightning lane stuff, it's impossible.
Because we were doing fast pass,
whatever the hell it used to be called.
And it was like grabbing it in line.
Oh my God.
Do you remember those days?
It's hard to so long ago.
This is your glory days.
You can just check.
I'm going soon with a person from out of town.
I am lost.
I don't know what to do.
I don't know how to do it.
It's so confusing what to do and what to buy and what to go.
I used to be Batman and now I'm not Batman.
Just some idiot watching the Riddler's Twitch stream.
You're a lurker.
Yeah.
Thanks for the bits.
I mean, if we missed anything pre-Ryman,
I think we sort of covered the,
I don't know if you know this,
this whole thing where the hands don't scan.
Yeah.
Which we like.
Do his hands not scan because he's a raccoon.
And that is why, as opposed to that they like
put them on a list.
Like if your credit card bounced.
Well, I thought it was that like the guests
had been bioscanning, like put in the system.
Like when you go to an art museum,
they give you that little metal thing you clip on your shirt.
Yeah.
I wouldn't know anything about art museums.
Sorry.
Pinkies, my pinkies were up for that one.
Someone's wearing a blazer on stage.
I am.
But with Popeye and all the...
Was it Popeye's shirt he's wearing?
Yeah.
I haggled down on Depop for this
Islands of Adventure Popeye shirt.
Jason and I wearing our favorite IPs.
Ninja Turtles, Popeye.
I kind of am too.
I'm in a Hawaiian shirt.
My IP is Mike Love.
Universally beloved.
Mike Love.
So, well let's...
The Rocket animatronic.
Oh, yeah.
The greatest.
Yeah.
Undeniable.
He hits his little head on the pipe.
He hits his little head.
You see his little tail move around.
And if he's not working for some reason,
there's a little video.
I don't mind that.
I mean, the video's okay.
You know, they got to play on video.
The video's okay, but it's so disappointing
when the video plays.
Yeah.
Cause like you want to see him fall.
Cause he falls out of a vent.
He doesn't really, but they make it look like that.
And he like, he's...
Well, it's possible they dropped the robot out of a vent.
Sorry, sorry.
Why are you ruining this?
I'm sorry.
I didn't know if you knew that.
Theme parks have illusions?
His little paws, maybe that's why his hands don't scan.
Cause they're really more like paws.
They are paws.
They have little paws grabs the Walkman on the way out too.
Setting up the like start of the ride.
It's maybe it's as good as the ride itself.
That pre-show.
I would just go to see that and him grab the thing and...
Excuse me, coming through and trying to get out.
Pardon.
I saw the Walkman grab and I'm out of here.
I saw the Walkman grab.
That's enough for me.
There's different, there's different in the...
Cause there's two rooms.
There's two like loading rooms or two pre-show rooms.
There's different stuff in each room as well.
There's different artifacts.
And like Colson's gun is in one of the rooms.
Agent Colson, Clark Gregg, married to what?
Jennifer...
Gray.
I was gonna say Jennifer Beals.
Jennifer Gray, thank you.
Clark Gregg's character has a big gun in the Avengers
and the big gun, Scott,
is in one of the rooms.
And I get excited when I get the big gun room.
There's also like stationary with a little memo on it
from XS Tech, the fake company from Alien and Counter.
Yes, very good.
Again, he's a big parks collector.
He loves Alien and Counter.
We should fast forward.
Also the painting of Goldblum and Benicio is really good.
With their plan.
I don't think I know about that.
It's what?
It's outside when you walk by it.
In between.
Jason, can you bring that up on the phone?
In between the...
Bring that up on your phone.
Okay.
You have to have seen this.
No, I have not.
What?
It's the Grandmaster from Thor Ragnarok.
And he's playing...
He was mentally skipping this cue.
No, no.
And then there's all these helmets,
all these very Kirby style like helmet stuff or face,
whatever you call them.
Celestials.
Celestials, thank you, Jason.
And I love...
Why is Jason pulling it up and not you?
Because I have control of this iPad
and it's very delicate.
The whole show could fall apart if I go surf the web.
All right.
These fine people came up.
They don't even wanna see a professional show.
They came out to see a guy hold his phone up
to another guy and the other guy to go, oh.
I was at least...
They're on the edge of their seats.
Thanks for your tickets.
But I love being in the room.
I am very, at this point,
I've seen the show so many times
that I really try to get out of the way of people
because it's a very tight squeeze.
And I feel that oftentimes like,
if I'm not paying attention, I am blocking a child.
And I try my best to get in the back,
but also that strategically is, you people know,
you gotta get out first so you get on the ride quicker.
Yeah.
See, you still...
Because those are the things you can teach your friend.
Like that haunted mansion dash.
Like, no, no, no, don't enjoy it or look at anything.
Go right to the door that is open first.
Yeah.
Well, if it's a...
That's what being a theme park fan is.
Here's the thing though.
It's like his first time at Disneyland,
so I want him to appreciate the cues.
Nice.
That gets an ooh.
Some reference.
Scott, here's the painting.
They're playing some sort of cosmic board game.
Goldblum's being a bad sport and knocking it off.
Have you seen that?
No.
And wait, wait, and show it to me one more time.
Oh.
All right.
Great, got it.
That legitimately blows my mind.
Yeah, I've seen him on this thing.
Wow, interesting.
You must be in such panic.
Yes, yeah, yeah.
You can't talk about it, look at it on the ground,
think about my life, take it all in
in case things don't work out.
And then there's me next to you,
like the Buddha under the Bodhi tree, a total piece.
We do have to talk about this, right?
We are losing valuable minutes.
Yeah, that's true, yes.
So to talk about, I mean, where to start?
I mean, a big thing that we have to talk about is songs,
and that is a very fun facet of this attraction.
Why don't I just like, I'm curious if there's a favorite.
So I'm gonna say them really quick.
And if you know your favorite, I'll just wait for it.
Hopefully you have it locked and loaded already.
Okay, favorites, in terms of, and it could be song,
but it could also be like, oh, this is just a fun match
with the attraction and a good amount of drops
and chaos, something about the chemistry.
All right, we got Steppenwolf, Born to be Wild.
Really, wow.
It's a pretty good one.
I like it.
Nothing there.
They're right.
Yeah, yeah.
It's not the best.
I was rolling my eyes at Steppenwolf.
I was like, is there anything interesting
about Steppenwolf?
And I found out the writer of that song,
his name, man, is Mars Bonfire.
Wow, really?
Yes, the writer of the song in Steppenwolf.
Real name, Dennis Edmonton.
That's about right.
Okay, what about Jackson Five, I Want You Back?
Yeah.
Solid candidate.
Elvis Presley, Burning Love.
Oh, yeah.
Not really, okay, yeah, I'm gonna agree with that one.
Edgar Winter, Group Freeride.
Yeah.
That one's mine, I'm gonna say.
Parliament, Give Up the Funk.
Yeah, and I think that's up there.
And Pat Benatar, Hit Me With Your Best Shot.
I was like, was it between Benatar and I Want You Back,
potentially?
Yeah, I think it was.
Edgar Winter did good, too.
Edgar Winter did do well, congrats.
He always did, with everything, with looking cool.
I thought Elvis didn't get,
I think Burning Love is more fun
than the audience gave him credit for.
That surprises me, because I forget it's there.
Yeah.
It seems like-
This doesn't match with some of the others, in a way.
Yeah.
Do we, I mean, I know this is the,
this is not about the overlay, but just out of curiosity,
who thinks Monsters After Dark is the best one?
Yeah, it is.
This is, okay, well, Monsters After Dark, really quick.
This came up on the show for a second.
That was the last step for me,
because I knew it was, at least I thought it was
a more intense drop pattern, I'm not totally sure if it is.
But I was really edgy that day.
Griffin Newman was with us,
ex-NLPTL legend, Griffin Newman.
There you go.
Try that, Griffin.
And I, you know, I was like,
he brought up later, you were pretty edgy,
and I think the reason I was edgy is because of the way
that the experience and the song were built up by you, Mike.
Because I feel like you had described it,
and maybe I was projecting it, and I'm scared anyway,
but I was imagining the most intense black metal,
like, math music.
Double bass drum.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, exactly.
Yeah, yeah, all the gear.
It's where I thought the song was going to be so terrifying
and make it just kind of an agonizing.
The scariest song ever.
That's somehow, I feel like there was something
that you said that made me think that,
and I guess this is my fault for how I processed it.
But then getting on it and then hearing,
monsters after dark, monsters after dark.
Well, hold on, Al, hold on, it's very loud, I'll say that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, that might be what you were referring to.
Were you just terrified at the concept of like,
this ride takes place chronologically
after the normal version of this ride?
Yeah.
Hoggle by the timeline.
Monsters after dark, I really like that the,
you know, the cast members wear like,
fucked up versions of their normal uniform.
There's like burn marks and like holes,
and some people really get into it.
And like, I saw a video online where like,
the guy at the end like bursts in screaming to unload you.
And the whole car like jumped, and I was like,
ah yeah, you gotta, I mean that seems really fun.
It's looked at, yeah, all that stuff is really great,
and it's gonna be in its own episode.
Yeah!
Probably for the best, yeah, we gotta move here.
Some of the theater's gonna shut down.
So, well, we should talk about, well, I don't know,
Mike, you take it.
Yeah, well, I mean, the only thing I would say is like,
on the RipRide Rocket at Universal,
they have like songs, and they have secret songs,
which is really exciting to me.
There's, I forget how you do it.
You have to punch in something on the screen
to get different secret songs.
Is that how it works, Jason?
Yeah, and if you punch in a really secret code,
it'll just stop on that lift hill for hours at a time.
If you spill soda on it or something.
Yeah.
All right, let me scoot.
So, people don't know there's also a secret menu of songs
for this ride, too.
And I'm gonna zoom through some slides of Mr. Tom Morrow.
We don't have time.
More Tom Morrow content coming soon.
So, yeah, so here's some of the secret.
My dear friends, this is the moment you have been waiting
for.
Rock it on Pro-Tunes and start Games Rock!
I'm a rube, Jamaica, blue llama.
Take it, I'm gonna get up, come on, come on, come on.
Uh, here you go.
I like you.
My dear friends.
So, yeah, there's a lot of them, actually.
We're doing six of them.
Rock it on Pro-Tunes and start Games Rock!
Oppa Gangnam Style.
Gangnam Style.
Pretty fun.
Yeah, you do like all this thing.
Jason, can you do it?
No, I don't want to do it.
Just a little, though.
Just a little, like, cause I.
One of them.
He does this, like, horse thing.
Do they have to ride?
What's that?
What are you doing?
He does, like, a horse thing.
That's a horse thing?
He does, like, after the one horse thing,
he, like, kicks to the side.
That was something from the 20s.
I'm going to blame that.
I'm going to blame that on my bum, like, ugh.
My dear friends, this is the Pro-Tunes and start Games Rock!
This is also called Monsters After Dark.
Here we go.
How excited would you be if that played?
No one would scream or anything.
No one would be lying.
I've been waiting for this.
The rocket on Pro-Tunes and start Games Rock!
I hurt myself today to see if I still feel.
I focus on the pain.
Just a solemn ride.
The only thing that's real.
It usually makes you laugh.
That one makes you cry.
The needle tears a hole.
That old familiar sting.
People might not know this one, so you have to listen closely.
The rocket on Pro-Tunes and start Games Rock!
The blast is slow, low is high, stop is go, and that is why every second Wednesday is a curtain.
From 8 to 9, all is well, then I rule over all my shell and all, because the world is
turning turtle.
Turtle.
No!
It's our favorite picture top V from Mary Poppins Returns.
This is saying something, this is saying something, might be my least favorite runner.
Might be number one with a...
Well, wait, Scott, how about this runner?
No, no, no, I asked for it!
My dear friends, this is the moment you have been waiting for.
The rocket on Pro-Tunes and start Games Rock!
I think if you could become fully aware of what existed in the cigar store next door
to this restaurant, I think it would just blow your brains out.
To have a real relationship with a person that goes on for years, well, that's completely
unpredictable.
See, that's why I think people have affairs.
Andre Gregor, Iguana, Sean, folks.
Okay.
A great film.
When I was younger, I used to care about art and music, and now I'm 36 and I only care
about hand scanning.
That's a smart joke.
Topical, it's a meme going around, folks.
You said it.
Well, geez, I mean, we've been blasting through this and our time is winding down already
in typical fashion where the ride has barely been discussed.
Anything else we want to throw out?
You know, I like everything that happens on it.
All the little tableaus are a lot of fun, very confusing.
They're like little TikToks.
It's a tower of TikToks.
There's funny Batista stuff, like two of the ride profiles.
He jumps out of the monster's mouth and punches it in the face and goes, you're welcome.
And then at the end, every version at the end when you're going back into, because you
have to go backwards into the elevator shaft, and then when you're resetting at the very
end, he goes, why are you thanking them?
They didn't do anything.
Beat it all the fighting.
It's really quiet.
It's kind of quiet.
Not really quiet, but kind of quiet, and you can easily miss it, but it is funny.
And he is very funny in those movies.
All the video things are pretty fun.
At the end, you get to see Cosmo has been freed, which is so, so satisfying.
As a dog lover of myself, you see the dog has been freed and they're getting in the ship.
Ladies and gentlemen, Edwin.
I wish if that was possible.
He humps the shit out of my leg.
Everyone starts going wild.
Pony, pony plays.
Bounce, bounce, bounce.
As you're walking out, and I've never caught this, but as you're walking out, you can hear the
collector yelling, and apparently sometimes you can listen and you can hear Howard the Duck
making fun of him, which I think is great.
They used to sell stuffed Howard the Duck and stuffed Cosmo in the exit.
They should bring that back, and we need more Howard the Duck based content.
He's on What If, and it's Seth Green. Is that all correct?
Yeah, all right.
So those websites were correct.
And then the last thing I'll say, I've said it before, I think on the show, is that at this point now I'm
spoiled from the actual ride itself on Guardians that when I go on Tower in Orlando, the ride
itself feels empty.
I feel it's not as fun because it's just dark up and down and there's no soundtrack.
There's nothing happening.
Yeah, boo me all you want.
The Hannibal Burris gif, boo me.
You know I'm right.
But they should now with all the towers, they should do, it doesn't have to be fun, but they should
have music.
It doesn't have to be fun.
They should have music and effects as you go up and down.
They should be opening the door and you see like Rod Serling or Burgess Meredith and he's
his glasses are broken.
Shatner, Shatner on the plane opens it up.
Shatner is pointing at you.
He's like, I see them.
They're there.
On the outside of this.
Yeah.
So do deep fake Burgess Meredith or young Shatner.
Oh, you're speaking my language now.
All the all the famous episodes.
You know, it is weird.
It's weird.
I think that now like that this type of attraction, the Tower of Terror ever at any point was
just one drop and that's the end.
Right.
Like like the multiple drops in the up and down in the back and forth is so clearly so
much of the experience.
And this thing is just so it's so chaotic.
You don't know what's going to happen when a door opens.
You don't know where you're going to be.
It's it's it's a blast.
They did a great job with it.
They overcame like everything, everything slate thought and everything we all thought.
I think it's just such a great fun experience.
Yeah, it's maybe my favorite ride at Disneyland.
Oh, that's an applause.
I was going to ask for and I know it was mixed and do we like that?
They did or not.
But are there people here who would say favorite ride?
Wow.
Yeah.
All right.
I'm sorry.
I wish I had a class of your choice.
What's class?
Great moments with Mr.
Lincoln.
Yeah.
Thing where you learn.
We are.
You know, we also have a mention is that Disneyland?
That's great.
See, that's what I was thinking.
Like Rocket.
So Rocket has knowledge of theme parks on Earth.
Yeah.
But is he more of a casual fan and the collector is the big fan?
It's still funny to think about Rocket going like I'm sick of universal screen rides.
Seems like JPEG stepped in it again.
He has opinions.
We know.
So but that's that's sort of bringing us to the end of our time, except for one thing.
And I would call this a plus up.
This is so you know, we talked about alternate music that they could do.
And I you know, it's it's classic rock.
Right.
There's a lot of classic rock.
But you know what else is a classic already after just five years is this attraction is Guardians of the Galaxy Edition breakout.
Every bit of it, the lore, the info dumps, the pre shows, the complicated backstory.
It's already classic.
And I think that in the future, they could acknowledge it and own it and make their own mythology part of the experience and part of the music.
And that is why we prepared a little something.
Disney, if you're listening, first of all, sorry about all this stuff up until now.
But besides that, you might want to consider throwing this this little ditty into the mix.
All right. Here we go.
Oh, yeah.
Tell you something.
My hands, they do not.
Yeah.
So I got a new plan.
They got to scan your hands.
You see the collection.
And a little bit.
You need special clearance.
They got to scan your hands.
And when they scan you in the gantry, it's fine.
You'll get the clearance because your hands.
They ain't mine.
Okay, everybody.
Oh, yeah.
Tell you something.
My hands, they do not scan.
So I got a new plan.
They got to scan your hands.
You survived.
Barcaster Red Lines.
Yes.
Thank you.
Thank you all so much for coming out.
Thanks to Dynasty Typewriter.
Thanks to Eileen in the Booth.
Thanks to Aaron Gardner for helping on the logo
and for ironing my shirt.
And thanks to all of you so much for coming out.
We've missed you so much.
Thanks for not forgetting about us for two years.
Thank you.
Forever Dog.
This has been a Forever Dog production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Bohm, Joe Silio, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit ForeverDogPodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple Podcasts, Spotify,
or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news by following us on Twitter
and Instagram, at ForeverDogTeam, and liking our page on Facebook.