Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, The Second Gate,
a show hosted by three thirsty men.
Thirsty for Coca-Cola products from around the globe.
I'm Jason Sheridan joined by Mike Carlson.
Yes, I am here and I am thirsty.
Thirsty, thirsty.
Sense us being some very thirsty boys.
I just wanted to clarify that it was for delicious
soft drink beverages.
Yeah, that's right.
And not the other definition.
There's gonna be a lot, I wanna warn everyone,
there's gonna be a lot of mouth noise on today's show,
which I know everyone out there loves.
They love us.
Not discussion of mouth feels.
There's gonna be mouth feels.
Here, I made everyone some Coca-Cola cake.
Here, let's get it out.
Okay.
Nom, nom, nom, nom, nom.
What do you think of this?
Is this good?
Nom, nom, nom, nom, nom.
So yeah, prepare for that.
Coca-Cola, very versatile ingredient.
Barbecue sauce and cake mixes,
you can really use it for a lot of things.
Is it, have you?
Have you had Coke and stuff that you like?
I have had Coke and stuff.
It helps break down, it helps tenderize meat
and I think it just adds a sweetness or sweetness.
I see that, but I always feel that that's,
I don't know, I know nothing of what I'm talking about,
but anytime I see like, oh yeah, like Coca-Cola,
not infused, but like, I don't know what you would say even,
like Coca-Cola ribs or some shit.
It never tastes like, like what's the point?
What is it?
It seems like it's a trick.
It seems like I'm being tricked.
Yeah.
And it's even, I feel that way sometimes about like,
the Planet Hollywood Captain Crunch or something,
like cereal infused something.
What are you, you were questioning the Captain Crunch,
you're questioning the quality.
Well I'm just saying sometimes when they-
This fine dish.
I'm just saying sometimes they have like something
that sounds like, oh, a fun, weird thing
that has like a big sugary addition to it
and I'm let down by it because I want it to taste
like the thing that is like the special treat in it.
You're thinking it might be like a quarter Captain Crunch
and three quarters breadcrumbs
or three quarters corn flakes or something.
Here's what I'm thinking.
I'm thinking that it's like,
there's some sort of chemical element to Coca-Cola
that's more important than the actual taste of it
because like it's some sort of weird goopy corn syrup sludge
and maybe it's like a bonding agent
and that's actually more helpful
in the preparation of the dish
than actually the taste of Coca-Cola.
That's possible, yeah.
I don't want to talk about that.
Well I think, yeah, I think you're at a very corporate
chain restaurant and then you're looking at a menu item
with the trademark in the name of the dish.
Yeah.
I think you're asking for trouble.
That just feels like, you know,
this is the product of some kind of, you know,
not merger but.
It's like, you know what it's like?
It's like, it's like, it's like, it's like barbecue ribs
like infused with Coca-Cola, a Coca-Cola story.
You know, it's like, and it did,
it's like something that's like a satellite
off of something I know.
It's Star Wars, it's a Star Wars story.
Yeah, yeah, it's a Coca-Cola story.
Well. So you shouldn't expect
what you expect with regular Coca-Cola.
It's often a big marketing, but like I've talked before
about when TGI Fridays were like,
and we've got Jack Daniel's chicken wings
or Jack Daniel's glaze.
And you're trying to get, yeah,
you're trying to get dad's mouth watering
for delicious Jack Daniels.
Getting dad thirsty, yeah.
You're trying to get dad thirsty.
And it's just like a fraction of it
and a different cut of corn syrup.
Yeah, so this is my point, yes, yes.
Or a different configuration of corn syrup.
It's interesting to say that we're talking today
about Club Cool and it's, you know,
many different forms and its predecessor Ice Station Cool.
Because Yesterland, you know, a great blog
that documents like long gone attractions and stuff,
put in, it's planted a seed of doubt
that like, are these sodas, this is Club Cool's,
has soda samples from around the world
from the Coca-Cola company.
They suggest it like, are these drinks this sweet
in other countries, some of these drinks?
Oh, really? Interesting, yeah.
And I didn't see that come up many other places.
But there is a pretty common thing
that the American palette is like,
everything is much sweeter here.
Okay, sure. Right, yes.
And that makes sense too,
because if you've had the different sodas of the world,
yeah, they all do taste as sweet as anything we have here.
But it would make sense that like,
we don't need everything to be that sweet.
And I know you're gonna say, oh, this is coming from,
this is a hypocritical statement from you.
You maniac, and maybe it is.
But I do think like- Blue goo oriented cocktails.
I think blue goo could be less sweet.
I don't think it actually has to be as sweet as it is,
I think.
But yeah, it's an interesting question.
I bet, I don't know,
whether it's true that the actual brand name sodas
we're having are not that sweet.
I think in other countries, yeah,
I've had different drinks and sodas where you go,
oh, this wouldn't fly here
is like a fun brightly colored sugar drink.
Like this would, somebody would go, what happened to this?
Something's missing here.
But they do have brightly colored sugar drinks
in other countries.
Yeah, I'm just saying- Less sugar,
or less chemical. Exactly, that's what I'm saying.
I've had other drinks like that,
where it's, in America,
you would expect a certain sugar level.
Yeah. So we say, oh, that's interesting.
Yeah, it doesn't feel to me like any of these drinks are,
I don't feel like there's a popular one in terms of,
oh, I wish we had this.
Like we, I'm sure we all saw the lists of the sodas
from around the world that are available at this place.
But I don't think there's like a super stud.
There's not a hit single in there, right?
Well, I recently back in the last few months,
I have seen what as of November, 2021
was the current Club Cool lineup.
I sampled them.
I left a hint for myself in the past
where I took a picture of the current lineup
and then drew on it on my iPhone
to circle the ones I liked the most.
So you're the- Oh, your favorite.
So, okay. This is great.
Because I was, yeah, I knew you had been recently.
So we do have a pretty recent-
Oh, good, there has been a taste test.
Exactly, because I didn't want to-
In the relative limits of the past.
Yeah, I feel like we weren't giving the listeners here
authenticity and actual reviews.
So Jason, thank goodness,
has recently tasted these on his lips.
Well, we remember, of course,
that we got the text from Jason,
one of my favorite texts from Jason,
when you told us, yeah, the park is crazy.
I made it to Club Cool by the skin of my teeth.
Or whatever, what phrase is that?
Probably not skinnier teeth.
Doesn't it? Yeah, skinnier teeth.
That may have been, was the context,
I think the crowds were overwhelming
and that Epcot construction,
it never gets old, how annoying it is.
Yeah, there's so many giant walk-arounds.
But my thing was just,
it's funny that you ended up in a scenario
where like, oh God, are we gonna make,
are we going to get to sample all the sodas in the world?
Oh God, like you're apologizing your family,
like please look, if we can hold together and bond,
maybe we can forge through the fire
and make it to the soda stand.
If memory serves, that was a combination of like,
the crowds were overwhelming that day
and thunderstorms kept like popping in and out.
Oh geez, so the elements are trying to get you-
Yeah, God himself is trying to stop Jason
from getting to Club Cool.
You will not try these fancy Fentas.
Jason's diving out of the way of lightning bolts.
We did, and Jay and Jane and my brother did wait in the,
admittedly there was a short line,
there was like five or 10 minutes to get in
because it was, they were giving each party
their own tasting fountain.
Right, which is the COVID protocol.
COVID protocol, which actually made sense.
We were able to sample everything else and even go back
and like, I wanna try that one again.
So was able to get a good bearing on it, I thought.
How many hours were you there?
How many hours did you spend?
Out?
And did you bring a big plastic jug to take any home?
Yeah, a big Nalgie, I dug out my college Nalgie bottle.
It's perfectly in a mini fridge.
This is our breakfast tomorrow.
The Super Soaker 200 backpack that usually has water in it.
Yeah, I had a Camelback.
I had a moldy college Nalgie bottle that I hyper bleached
to fill up with a country club meringue.
Yeah, so, and this was still pretty new
because Club Cool closed down in 2019.
It's had many lives.
It reopened in September, 2021.
So it was only a couple months old when I was there.
It's adjacent to the place whose name
I never remember the Creations Shop,
the new big Epcot store that is a name that means nothing.
I don't know what it means.
Yeah, that's a nice name.
Sounds religious to me.
The Creationism Shop.
Before you say flavors and flavors that you like,
let me just say really quickly,
if you don't know, if you've never been,
this is in Epcot Center, it's in Future World,
and it is a Coca-Cola store, an ongoing exhibit,
and a tasting station, as we've said,
of where you can try different Coca-Cola products
and sodas from around the world.
Just wanted to say that really quick,
but there are going to be some listeners
who think that what I just did was beyond the pale
to even stop and explain this in any way
as if this isn't the most important thing
in all of Disney World.
And I say this because I've fallen into some pits
when it comes to Club Cool.
And that's part of wanting to do an episode
to work through some of this stuff.
Club Cool came up on the show once before.
I sort of knew that this was there.
That was the thing where you try the sodas of the world.
Got it.
I'll admit fault on this one.
I laughed at you guys, and I said,
this thing is not a big deal.
And everybody went, Rob, Rob, Rob,
Scott's wrong, Scott wrong, blah.
Okay, I get it.
Club Cool is apparently one of the most
crucial attractions in Disney World.
Was this your guys point of view,
or have you ramped up your Club Cool feelings
in the wake of yet another Scott gate?
Well, no, no, no.
Yes, this is one of the many Scott gates on the show.
But I think that what happened was,
and I kind of remember it was a remote episode
a year, maybe a year ago.
And I think both Jason and I initially,
without having seen any comments or feeling a vibe,
both were very excited by the prospect of doing Club Cool.
So I don't think-
I think it was less like, you don't know Club Cool.
On our end, it was more like, Club Cool.
Well, I appreciate it.
The vibe was great on your end.
So thank you, my friends.
This was not a set sir incident.
This is not one of those.
This was like, I do think as a kid,
I was very excited to do this.
And I think a lot of kids,
then maybe I'm getting too,
I'm analyzing too much too early.
But I think as a kid,
the idea of going and getting unlimited soda
is loom so large.
Yeah, I hadn't thought of that.
Yeah, that's exactly right.
Like the idea of even being like a 12 year old,
13, whenever I was allowed to go to seven,
like inside a 7-Eleven alone.
Oh, and have free rent where you are not,
it might be tough to even remember this in the COVID age.
You're just let loose with eight different streams.
And if you're a thirsty boy,
What size do you want?
Mom only lets you get the medium.
But you know, if you're alone,
you can get the extra large or you can get the whatever,
whatever they call it now, big gulp, ultra gulp.
So like all, like I do think I like fetishized
the soda machine or whatever.
Like I definitely like it turned into this like awesome thing.
And then I only got a little bit of it sometimes.
It's a place that it's something
that you had some choice in, some free will.
Finally.
Is everything else in your life
dictated by your mom?
Yes.
Lots of rules put in place.
What you can do and listen to.
Exactly.
But as long as her back was turned at the soda station.
But when you were in club cool,
you're in charge.
You're in charge.
Well, it's almost educational if you think about it.
You're learning about the different countries
and their tastes and stuff.
I have to do this.
I have to learn.
Epcot's the educational part.
I have to give a brief presentation
that my teacher will forget about
because we came during the school year.
You could totally get away with a book report type thing.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
You could knock it out in half a day,
just talking about a couple of Epcot attractions.
Even now.
Yeah.
You could swing that.
I think so.
Yeah, there's still enough little bits of education
here and there.
Maybe even in club cool.
I mean, that's what we're essentially doing
a little book report about club cool.
That's right.
Yes.
I found some things that I found interesting.
So I guess I have to thank everyone for yelling at me
about club cool.
I don't even remember how much yelling there was about.
I don't know if it was that bad.
Well, here's what I do know
is that there was a little bit of that maybe on club cool.
I also maybe amplify.
I saw one thing and it turns into 20 things in my mind.
But more recently than that,
I felt the need to take the time to say that there,
and we'll kind of save the discussion of this,
but let me get it out now.
In a notorious part of club cool
is that you try all of these sodas
and there is one soda that is a very bad soda
or very bitter and you spit it out
and maybe it's a little prank that you play on people.
This does not taste good.
And it is called Beverly.
This was new information to me recently.
Oh, right, right.
I felt the need to say Beverly is the name of the soda
that tastes bad at Epcot's club cool.
There were people who were mad that I would even do that.
Someone wrote me on Twitter
and was so fucking mean about it.
Really?
Yes.
Somebody added me like,
you think we don't know.
As if like, why don't you explain what Jurassic Park is?
How about that?
That obscure art film.
Lindsay was mad at me during,
that's when it came up.
Lindsay said, you think people don't know what Beverly is?
Okay, I don't, look, I didn't know what Beverly may,
perhaps, perhaps.
Maybe everyone was making a joke.
I don't know.
But I have, there's just been a lot of emotion
coming my way about club cool and,
I just don't understand why there's any,
why anybody's so amped up.
We should be mellow.
This is a fun, keep it cool, everybody.
Like mellow yellow, like the flavor of soda mellow yellow.
Yeah.
I was interested to learn,
I was legitimately surprised.
What I didn't know about Beverly is they
have not really manufactured it since 2009.
Except for these various tasting locations.
At Club Cool, at the Atlanta plant,
the Vegas Coca-Cola store,
the Disney Springs has a Coca-Cola store
with a bar on top,
and some of these you can get in cocktails,
like the cocktail Beverly's Revenge.
Beverly's Revenge.
They tried to contextualize it in a better drink,
in sort of a gin and tonic kind of situation,
which still seems like it's sort of mixed reviews on that.
Right.
But I think, yeah, by the way,
I just really wanna say, you know,
we have to hold that off.
We have to hold over to talk about the Coca-Cola store off.
Wait, wait, wait, so what was that?
Well, it's just, it's a part of a different thing.
I'm just saying Coca-Cola stores, you know,
I mean, what you guys have said here is fine.
The Coca-Cola store at the Vegas
has a big animatronic polar bear.
Different story, Jason.
It always seems like it's breaking.
Different story.
Different episode.
Do they have Beverly there?
I definitely saw that it's at the Atlanta thing,
which people have recommended,
when we throw out what are some good episodes we should do,
I went and found these,
some comments that said,
you guys gotta talk about World of Coca-Cola in Atlanta.
And again, we'll do it separately.
It's a different story.
It's a different thing, yeah.
World of Coca-Cola in Atlanta,
big Coca-Cola exhibit in kind of the, you know,
the land of Coca-Cola.
There's some kind of movie or presentation
called In Search of the Secret Formula,
in which you meet a character named
Professor Rigby Addison Wet Whistle III.
Fantastic, yeah.
Because our audience has alerted us to this.
So we do clearly need to go in search of the secret formula.
But we'll deal with Atlanta later.
Yes, but basically, yeah, this soda is now,
even though they present it still on the little placard,
as it is a popular drink in Italy,
it hasn't had the chance to be popular in a very long,
because it only exists as a prank soda
in themed environments.
It's a prank soda at tourism locations.
In Italy, it was a non-alcoholic aperitif,
which you're meant to drink before a meal,
because it activates your taste buds
and supposedly helps with digestion.
Now, let me ask about this,
because, and that is the case,
that the idea is before a meal as opposed to after a meal.
Right, it's not a palate cleanser?
Because like sometimes there's things, you know.
I feel like I've seen it presented as that.
I mean, I think both could work.
Both could work, I think.
I'm no expert on this, I don't know.
I ask partially because my main experience with aperitifs
is the restaurant Little Dom's in Los Feliz,
where, which is a cool, good restaurant
people should go to.
I associate it now with it's the place
where Donald Glover had lunch with Billy Dee Williams
to learn about how to be Lando.
But non-celebrities can go there as well.
And basically, so I would,
and like, now where's the fun of your day?
A lot of fun of your day people would go every Monday
because they had this deal and we'd get,
it would be very indulgent.
We would drink so much and eat so much.
And there's this producer, Sean Boyle.
This is really specific for anyone listening
who personally knows Sean Boyle.
But he's, you know, kind of a gourmand
and kind of a Lord Michael's voice a little bit.
And I just remember he'd throw out,
there's this thing for nets.
Anybody had for net?
I know what for net is,
but I think I maybe had it in a cocktail.
Uh-huh, that makes sense.
Yeah, yeah, sure.
But I don't think I ever had it on its own.
It's one of the, yeah, it's many there to be made.
It's in and of itself kind of not a great taste,
which I didn't know until we do these big grand dinners.
And then Sean would throw out like,
I had a runoff for nuts for the table.
And we'd all get them.
And then the first time,
if you aren't prepared for what that is,
for this little shot glass of like bitter syrup,
it's real, it's just, it's not my vibe.
And we had to start saying,
it became at every one of these meals,
we're brought up for nuts.
And we'd all go, no, no, we don't want this.
And it would be at the end,
we're already like so drunk and I don't need another.
This is actually going to do the opposite.
This might make me throw up and make me feel worse.
Cause this isn't, this one is an alcoholic aperitif.
So I was no fan of that.
And if the idea is that you're supposed to take them
before you eat, that makes more sense to it.
Cause why do you take like bitter cough syrup
at the end of the meal when you're stuffed?
I think I prefer like after dinner,
if I'm going to have like a liqueur,
it's like something sweet.
Like I like amaretto and coffee.
Okay.
Or Frangelico, it's a kind of amaretto and coffee.
I guess I understand the premise of these things.
It just hasn't, I haven't really taken to them,
but this is, I guess the thing with Beverly.
Cause I dug into Beverly a little bit.
And there's this really good blog called
Passport to Dreams Old and New
that goes like really deep on,
they have incredible articles about the contemporary.
Yeah, you've been there for stuff.
They go really into Beverly and without dragging it out
and saying everything, they said,
the premise that this blog has is
what is served in the theme parks cannot be
what Coke actually sold as Beverly in Italy in the 60s.
Because from any accounts you can find of that,
it wasn't nearly as bad.
The, like his ideas, or I don't know who writes this,
but they're saying that like, okay,
if this is made, not even by regular Coca-Cola anymore,
if it only exists as a prank soda.
And basically you're like, cause of other aperitifs,
you would maybe pre-mix with carbonated water.
Like it's made that way in the factory.
And this is like carbonated theme park tap water
in like kind of a warm environment mixed with this.
Basically they're saying that drinking only the Beverly
is almost akin to drinking only the Coke sludge
and saying, here's Coca-Cola.
That's not necessarily right.
It's only part of the, part of the mix.
So like Beverly would be best put in a cocktail
as they've done with Beverly's revenge.
Almost like as if you just drank
a spoonful of vanilla extract.
Sure.
Where it's like the slightest bit can flavor a whole cake.
Yeah.
But it's so hyper concentrated, it would just be nasty.
It's nasty if you tried on its own.
Yeah, yeah.
I think the idea with, they mentioned Campari
and how Campari on its own is kind of weird,
a little cough syrupy, but you mix it with stuff
and then it transforms and brings flavors out of the,
so I think, so maybe Beverly is getting a raw D,
like Beverly is being made a mockery of unfairly.
Maybe that's the idea here.
It's taken on a life of its own
beyond its original intent.
Cause even when you have,
sometimes if you go to fountain soda,
sometimes the mix is way off.
In either direction.
Sometimes you get, when you go,
this is the syrupy as shit and it's awful.
So if you were to have a concentration
that's not what has been liked by humans,
or I don't know why,
I could imagine that easily being unpleasant.
Yeah.
It doesn't seem like it would be hard
just to get the equation wrong and have it be bad.
Yeah.
I mean, a lot of these sodas evolve over the years.
You mentioned Italy in the 50s.
That was when they, you know,
launched what we think of as the modern version of Fanta.
The original Fanta was made with like Italian oranges
in Italy.
Of course, the original Fanta was made
under the Nazi regime in Germany by Coca-Cola, Deutschland,
because there was a US embargo
before the US entered the war.
So it was hard to get ingredients.
That's why it exists.
We need to make something entirely here
where we don't need to bring in any.
So they used beet sugar, whey, and apple pommice.
I don't know what the hell pommice is.
So pommice, I looked this up just to be sure.
When you like juice grapes for juice or wine,
or you juice apples for cider or juice,
the goo that's left, the mush that's left, that's pommice.
It's not the juice, it's the like,
you know, I guess goo is the best word to describe it.
So they, in Germany and I, is it in Amsterdam,
were both, they couldn't get the, you know,
Coke syrup from America.
They couldn't get the Coke ingredients from America.
So they made Fanta.
That was how Fanta was introduced under the Nazi regime.
All of this stuff, I'm guessing,
and maybe I'm wrong and somebody correct me if I am.
All of this stuff would have tasted better initially.
Because it's all like been replaced by corn syrup
and this like shit.
Like somebody told me a couple years ago
that a lot of cereals I had as a kid,
they replaced like ingredients with just corn syrup.
And I remember being a kid,
and I've said this before, I think,
where like I ate like tricks or something one day
and I was like, oh, they taste different.
Huh, okay.
And it's like, oh yeah, they like replaced,
they don't do like necessarily whole grains anymore.
And I feel like if you went back
and had some of the original versions of sodas,
they would taste a lot less like crazy sweet
and probably have more like natural tasting flavor.
Yeah.
So when you go out weekly and get a Trix-Tini at CityWalk,
do you have any change in the ingredients of Trix-Tinis?
Well, I mean, they've been the same since I was 12, I think.
So I haven't noticed recently any difference.
By the way, a very good idea if,
if Telly's would offer it or something,
or maybe I could make it myself probably.
I could infuse it, but.
Yeah, I might've picked the wrong base.
I don't know what liquor,
if anyone's experimented at home and you know a liquor
that goes best with Trix, with ground up Trix,
with mixed, which, and then you rim the glass
with a couple of them, like for, you know, for decoration.
Oh yeah, yeah.
And so you get that one bite.
I would, yeah, I would like that
or a fruity pebbles based drink.
Is there not that?
There's gotta be that.
There's gotta be, right?
Somewhere, right?
Yeah.
Somebody has to have made that.
I feel like it's almost getting a little,
like some places make the crazy milkshakes
or they put a little whipped cream on a dessert
and sprinkle some fruity pebbles on top.
We had like funnel cake fries with.
Oh, that's true, but I was gonna say at Black Tap,
I think one of the milkshake I had
had like fruity pebbles like stuck to the glass.
It was rimmed, it was like an icing rim.
And instead of salt or sugar, it was fruity pebbles.
Yeah, yeah.
Tipsy bartender.com has a recipe for fruity pebble shots,
pink shooters that combine vodka, blue curacao.
There it is.
Oh my gosh.
Milk.
Milk, granadine, whipped cream,
and of course some fruity pebbles.
Uh huh.
Jesus Christ.
That seems a little too much.
Too much.
Yeah.
No thanks.
I mean, my current soda thing, I don't drink soda a lot.
That was like when I was in high school.
Soda wasn't like when I was growing up,
soda was a treat for a little while.
And then I think it became so ubiquitous
with like combo meals at fast food.
And then like family restaurants just gave you soda,
like unlimited soda.
And it was just like, there was one summer in high school
where I was like, all right, I'm gonna exercise more
and I'm gonna switch from drinking soda to water.
And I dropped weight immediately
from just cutting soda from my diet.
And then in my 20s, like production company offices
where I would PA, there was always piles and piles
of Diet Coke.
Like the city runs on coffee and Diet Coke.
The whole entertainment industry runs on Diet Coke.
As did the nation from 2016 to 2020.
They had a Diet Coke fueled president.
Well there was a button.
There was a button on the desk.
He did hit that button a lot.
That's true.
Well he didn't hit the other button.
I was never super crazy about diet sodas,
but the zero sugar sodas, they have hooked me.
A Coke Zero, Dr. Pepper Zero,
and Baja, Mountain Dew Baja Blast Zero.
That is my blue drink of choice.
Oh my gosh.
I don't have a ton of soda anymore,
but I will say I was feeling a little sleepy
and I had to play a tennis match recently.
I stopped into a gas station and I got a Coke Zero cherry.
And boy was that delicious.
It's really good.
I was on cloud nine.
I was so, I was like, oh my,
because I always as a kid,
Cherry Coke was like my favorite thing ever.
And somebody, they're doing retro Cherry Coke clothing
at the Coke store in Disney Springs.
And I got so excited because every Cherry Coke logo
is a masterpiece.
It's like black and purple.
Yeah, you know what I'm saying?
I get you.
You remember the old?
I remember the logo, yeah.
I'm so excited.
Even like the, even the like extreme version in the 90s.
I still have so much affection for that Cherry Coke.
I really liked it.
Yeah, Cherry Coke logo.
And every movie theater had it.
I went to the movie.
I saw Spider-Man, you know, back in December,
I was like, I'm going to get a Cherry Coke.
Discovered that that Regal had switched over to Pepsi
and didn't even have any Cherry Pepsi, which is fine,
but it's not really ideal.
Yeah. Well, you know, left the movie.
Yeah.
Throw it at the screen.
I was like, what has happened to our country?
Woke mob.
Joe Brandon, what have you done?
Regal cinema says Pepsi now?
What?
I did this little sticker of Joe.
Oh man.
I saw that.
I saw an, I did this on a toilet recently,
like at a grocery store, like a Trader Joe's toilet.
I'm like, what are you doing?
Joe Brandon messed up the Trader Joe's toilet.
I guess.
I'd be proud.
I don't, if there's any bowel movements going on
with Joe Brandon, I'd be impressed.
I'd applaud him.
Scott, can you see these or no?
That's too far.
Yeah, yeah.
There's some Cherry Coke, Cherry Coke logo.
Sure.
I love this shit.
Oh, the extreme-ish one.
Oh, the 90s.
I see what you're saying.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I love that garbage too.
It's like a 2002 No Doubt album cover.
Right.
Yes.
It doesn't look like that now.
Even that, I like the Cherry Coke.
But I did have a Zero recently.
I'm not a Mountain Dew guy though.
But I guess I would try it.
I was not in a test market either.
Do you guys remember OK Soda?
It had the Dan Clout, like the Gen X ass logo.
It had the Dan Clout's art on it.
Oh, Clout's art on a soda?
This was like the 90s, like Coke's attempt, I believe.
The 90s, like slacker Gen X.
Oh, wow, no, I've never seen this before.
That's weird, what they have to do there.
That is weird.
Yeah.
Wow, and you had that?
No, I didn't.
I remember seeing the art when I was young
and then it just comes up every now and then
on those listicles of like, remember these foods?
Yeah.
I, yeah, I'm trying to think.
When I was a kid, I've said,
sure, I've said this before, playing soccer
when I was like in kindergarten,
I could have given a shit about.
But after the game, you got a hot dog and a can of soda.
This is my baseball, we got fountain soda.
They usually got a hot dog or a slice of pizza
and just around the seventh inning, I was like,
oh, I really gotta get out of this outfield
and at that snack bar.
And what would happen is, yeah, what happened is
a parent had, like one parent had like a little like
tray of hot dogs and one parent had a tray of the soda
and they had a lot of different sodas.
It was not all the same.
Like a club cool.
So on the go.
The only time I would run very fast
is when the game was over because I knew
to get the cherry Coke or to get the grape soda,
you had to be first because kids would take those.
Yeah.
So I would sprint,
cause like depending on where you were
at the end of the game, you would have an advantage.
Oh, if that's, if it's out in the dugout
and you're in deep right field.
Well, this soccer that was, that was baseball.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Okay.
Yeah.
I'm sure we had, we think we had a similar thing
with baseball, but soccer is the memory I have.
So I would, if I knew how much left time was left
in the game, I think I would kind of try to position
myself ahead of the game to be able to run,
to get the cherry Coke or the grape soda.
You're only at the end or half point or,
or I would take orange too.
I liked orange soda a lot as well,
but the grape and the cherry Coke
were the very desirable ones.
So it's like a really mopey perfunctory soccer playing,
tripping over your own legs.
And then we get to the end and you sprint like an Olympian.
I turn into Pele.
I'm a little Pele and I'm running as fast as possible,
checking kids out of the way.
And then like,
What happened to Mike?
There's only this Mike shaped cloud
that was left in his wake.
Yes.
That was, my parents, I think noted this too,
that I appeared to move faster at the end of the game
than I did during the game.
Except for the time when my dad said, if you score,
cause I was being placed in offense, I think,
because my dad like negotiated with the coach.
And he said, if you score a goal, I'll buy you a toy.
And I scored a goal within fucking minutes,
a couple of minutes.
See, yeah, I had a similar thing too,
where it's like, if we had a Saturday morning game
or Friday, like usually Saturday morning game,
you're finished by like noon or one or whatever.
And so I'd be like, well,
does anyone need to run to the supermarket or the mall?
Like just suggesting places
where I knew there was a comic store close by.
Like, I don't know why I didn't just come out and say like,
Hey, we're out.
Can we go buy a comic book store?
Lenscrafters is in close proximity.
If anyone needs to get their prescription check.
Every two years we need to do lenses.
Yeah.
So I, and then as I got older,
I was like, there was one or two years
where I was doing like school plays and playing baseball.
And I was joking about this with my dad recently,
where it's like one coach was like,
you know, you're missing some practices
with the school play ground.
You're gonna have to make a decision soon.
And like the next year was like,
yeah, I know what I'm deciding.
Yeah, I'm going to the play.
I spend more time on stage than I do on the field.
So I think this is wherever the action is for me.
Did you play sports when you were little?
A little bit.
I made it up to, I did coach pitch baseball.
Okay.
So I first grade.
A little bit like second or third.
And then yeah, once there was an opposing team
throwing the ball, I checked out of that
when it was not a friend on the other side
of the pitching mound.
See, we had an in between that
before the other kids started pitching,
there were machines.
Yes, we did that too.
Yeah, the coaches feeding balls into the machine,
I think was more reliable than just like
nine year olds throwing wild pitches.
Like it would have just been chaos
if they had nine or 10 year olds throwing.
I did a year of whatever that was, second or third grade.
I did a year of kids pitching
and then I was out of baseball.
Yeah.
I retired from, I did the whole speech
with my cat over my heart.
You consider yourself the luckiest.
The luckiest second grader.
He's like, is he dying?
He must be dying.
He's got Mike Carlson's disease.
Yeah.
He's just a coward.
Plus my priority shifted.
I was like, mom, dad, I gotta be home
to watch the Simpsons and Seinfeld
if I'm gonna have anything to talk about
at school the next day.
This is what nerdy too smart for their own kids do
in seventh grade.
Too smart for their own kids.
Too smart for their own good.
You had kids when you were a kid.
I mean, they shouldn't have kids, you know.
Well, should we talk about some of these other,
and we've established the place
and describe what Beverly is?
Sorry.
Now let's get into Jason,
some of the tastes that you got to test.
Yeah, let's do that.
I do wanna go back and talk about the
Oh, by all means.
World of Ice Station Cool.
Yes, absolutely.
But a recent check-in.
So yeah, like I said,
me, my dad, or me, my brother, and Jane went
and tried the sodas.
I'll say off the gate,
our favorite, out the gate, our favorites,
Bon Bon Englaise from Madagascar,
and Country Club Meringue from the Dominican Republic.
Delicious.
Not like Meringue?
Probably Meringue, not Meringue.
It wasn't a Meringue soda.
Is that Meringue?
That makes more sense.
Because it's Dominican Republic and that's the music.
Okay, that makes a lot more sense.
But that is how Meringue is spelled.
It says it on the thing, how to pronounce it, Meringue.
Oh, so it does.
It's a bit in front of you, but.
This guy was being nice and I was being an asshole.
Sometimes there's other sweetness.
Some of these are so sweet or just have
a different clarifier.
Those are your favorites, they're sweeter.
Would you go out of your,
did you like this taste test and the results so much
that if these were available to you,
or at a store slightly out of your way,
would you be hitting up this Madagascar
and Dominican Republic soda?
Yeah, these two I think I would.
And I think the one I used to like
that they don't have anymore was Bebo.
I think that one was pretty good.
The Sprite.
South African drink, it looks like?
I think that was from, yeah,
then 80s or 90s South Africa.
Oh, they had characters apparently.
Johnny Orange, Taka Strawberry, and Paolo Peach.
Well, I haven't seen them, but I love Paolo Peach.
Yeah, that's great.
Yes, any mascot I haven't heard of, it's an instant love.
I can't find a photo of them.
How do we know these characters exist?
If somebody knows how to see Paolo Peach, let us know.
I think the other one, less sweet,
I think a little drier was the Sprite Cucumber from Russia.
Now who knows if they've yanked it.
We've got to do our freedom fries part.
Get Russian cats out of competitions,
get that soda out of Disney World.
Yeah, this is one of those where I don't think
anyone is even paying attention.
They're not paying attention
to the marching band's lead screen.
They're not paying attention to sodas either.
No.
Oh, right.
Or whatever that was.
They're not paying attention to the show
about socially progressive youths
doing a scene at a homeless sweep protest.
What are you talking about?
What is this?
Oh, there's this free form show called Good Trouble.
Oh, I've heard of the show.
They swept a homeless encampment in Los Angeles.
That's where the police come in.
To shoot there and what they were filming
was a scene of a protest about homeless sweeps.
Really?
Yeah.
Oh, I didn't see this.
Yeah, extremely grim stuff.
Bad, bad, a couple months for the company.
So the Russian Sprite is not on their radar
is really what we're saying.
I don't think so, but it was pretty good.
But they're still selling,
the Russian Sprite's still available,
it's not free anymore.
It's now $6.99 a gallon.
Will Brandon is letting the price of Russian Sprite,
cucumber go through the roof.
Will has JPEG though,
as it come across his desk,
he started charging per sip for.
For all the club cool.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We're giving, do you know how much soda
we're apparently giving away at Epcot?
Apparently there's this free thing.
This, I was just informed of this free soda place.
Somebody said it was a big deal.
I'd say they're wrong.
See, he wants to, when you go into Club Cool,
he's gonna have them put a magic band on your neck
and it's gonna measure how many sips you take
and then it'll charge you immediately to your app.
Oh, like it's one of those fill your own beer kind of places.
Well, no, it's like Mickey dog collar that you're wearing
that can measure how many sips you've taken
and then you can charge, get charged on the way out.
It's a hands-free tab.
Yeah.
You're putting them all in your tab,
it's scanning you at each, yeah.
And then, all right, that'll be $17.98.
Right.
So I only had Beverly.
Yes, that's what it costs now.
Yes, we know.
Beverly kind of has a prime spot in the new,
right on the end, right on the end where you can see it
in some of the earlier soda fountains is like,
it was kind of in the middle where if you weren't looking
or thinking, you might accidentally in between like,
oh, watermelon soda or raspberry soda.
No, Beverly is off on its own.
All the way on the side.
Well, and this is interesting that they have,
several times they have replaced the entire lineup
of the sodas and this facility stopped existing
and moved entirely and yet the one,
the constant is Beverly.
They've kept Beverly going despite it not being
a real mass produced drink.
It'll never leave.
Yeah, yeah.
Which I get, you know, now I'm glad I've been educated
about this now.
It is kind of fascinating that this is a,
it does actually feel like Epcot and the Disney parks
paying attention to an important detail.
You could see them missing the cult of Beverly
that seems to exist.
Yes.
But they've kept this detail alive.
Well, they want, yeah, it's like preserving
one of their like dark rides or something that, you know,
it's not always happening.
You know, they're not always keeping things around
just for tradition's sake, except for it's good to see
one thing in Epcot is sticking around
in the way that people remember and love it.
One bit of Epcot being kept weird.
Right.
Now I do need to direct your attention
to what I think I've seen some people refer to
in the same breath as Beverly in the current lineup.
Yeah.
And that is Smart Sour Plum.
Oh.
Smart is a line of soft drinks in China
and sour plum tea is listed as a traditional Chinese beverage.
So this is a soft drink version of that.
This drink to an American palette,
I would say is pretty unpleasant.
Okay.
And that it tastes like barbecue sauce.
Wow.
It is listed as like having a savory flavor
and that it is.
It is pretty overwhelming.
Okay.
And they have that now?
Yeah, it's like the, in the picture I sent you,
it's like the third one in on the right.
Oh, okay.
I see it now.
Sorry.
And yes.
That sounds weird.
That sounds very odd.
Yeah.
That is probably the most like of the new crop
or like the current crop of sodas.
I mean.
There's the potential to dethrone.
Like if anything was gonna take the Beverly spot
of the gross soda.
Yeah.
The Sweet Sour, Smart Sour Plum is on the rise.
Is that new or do you know?
I should really look and see.
It's new in the new lineup.
I think Smart is a newer line of like,
I mean, it's so wild as you go through
and you read all these different generations of soda.
Some of these are like only dating back to like the,
the eighties or nineties and stuff.
And there's one, the weirdest one that I forgot about.
I did know about this Mezzo mix in Germany,
not on the current lineup.
And it's kind of cola and orange.
And the description says Germans often mix their beer
with non-alcoholic beverages.
I was like, they do?
And then I started reading, I was like looking it up
and yeah, they do.
And it's different cocktails.
I think in America, we know the Shandy,
that's lemonade and beer.
Okay, yeah.
But then there's also a Radler,
which is a phrase I had heard before,
which is often a beer and lemon lime soda.
Okay.
And then there's cola beer, which is beer and cola.
And I think it's usually more beer than cola
because it'll be way too sweet.
I think the idea being you can drink a lot more beer
cocktails than you could just mugs of beer.
Okay.
So if you want to stay out and continue drinking,
you cut it with like something else.
Yeah, at some point you might hit that fill of beer.
None of that sounds good to me.
And by the way, I've never done any of these beer cocktails
at the Ant Man bar.
Has anybody done one of them?
Oh, we did.
Yeah, the first day I think I did.
That's what I did.
But then when I realized I accidentally ordered
an ice cream float.
What?
Remember I was not sure what I was drinking
and I was like, what did I get?
And then I was like, oh, this is a big scoop ice cream beer.
Oh, accidentally.
Wow.
You keep accidentally ordering these milkshakes.
I swear it was an accident.
You didn't again say, this is the best drink I've ever had.
Like the, yeah.
Or was it marshmallow?
Was it a big marshmallow?
Was that what it was?
It was something like that.
It was the ice cream or big, let me find a picture of it.
I had the one that was like had Boba Pearls
and it was the Golden Road mango cart,
which is a very sweet, kind of pleasant summery beer.
And then I think maybe there was a shot of vodka.
There was a float of some sort of liquor in it.
It was pretty pleasant.
I thought it was pretty refreshing.
It didn't,
Boba and beer, like in a souvenir glass
is kind of a pain in the ass.
Yeah, yeah.
You're like, oh, I gotta scoop out these Boba Pearls
and then I gotta rinse this glass out somewhere.
I don't think I get,
there was a period where I was sort of understood Boba
and now I'm not so sure.
I just yesterday, I saw a license plate holder
that said addicted to Boba.
And I was like, wow.
Are you also addicted to stomach aches?
I love it in milk tea, like a Thai iced tea
or different milk teas and stuff.
When we were doing the Carly episode,
I stopped just like,
and had a Thai iced tea.
And they're like, do you want Boba?
And I was like, oh, I could go for some Boba.
And I was like, oh, I probably shouldn't be munching Boba
as I talk into a microphone.
No, no, no, the audience loves,
the audience loves as much sound up on that mic.
I ordered the molecular meltdown,
which is a garage marshmallow milk stout
with vanilla ice cream and miniature marshmallows.
Milk stout?
So is there alcohol in that?
Yeah, stout, yeah.
That stout implies?
Stout is like a, yeah, like Guinness or something.
Okay.
Guinness is, yeah, Guinness is already a thick,
I don't know, that was good, but it was a little deserty.
You can do a lot.
I think stouts are usually like,
you can put chocolatey flavors
or like a scoop of vanilla ice cream
and make like a Guinness float or something.
Yeah.
What else in terms of,
what else in your recent Club Cool findings?
Yeah, I mean, I thought the rest were okay.
I think the Royal watermelon from the Philippines was good.
The Viva raspberry from Moldova,
I think was probably the sweetest
if I'm remembering correctly.
Okay.
Yeah, I like the tropical.
I think the tropical sodas are good.
Like I'll get a Fanta pineapple every now and then.
Sure.
If I see it or like Doritos,
we can get those a lot of Mexican restaurants out here.
I like those.
I just, I like my sugary sweets.
I just, I'm very conscious of not taking sugar in drinks.
Not like drinking sugar without thinking.
Sure.
So I can have my sugary treats.
So that you, yes, okay, okay.
Because then you feel like the drink counteracts.
Like that is, you just did your dessert as a beverage
and then you don't get to have your milk and cookies at home.
It's hard when you just want like a granola bar
or a Clif bar or something like that.
At least if that's like, oh, I just need something.
I need a quick breakfast or something.
So much of those have so much sugar in it.
And then I find myself just drinking a lot of water
to counteract that.
But even my coffee, I usually just take with like cream
or almond milk or something like that.
I'm pretty light on those.
Wait, so now did you do Beverly during this expedition?
Have you, do you,
do we know how Beverly is tasting these days?
I mean, it's still pretty shocking.
It's still pretty unpleasant.
I think there's a Mr. Morrow video where he mixes Beverly
with the Smart Sour Plum.
And it's just like a very shocking.
It's a wild, a wild episode.
He does that a lot.
I noticed he was doing that.
There was an episode where he went to Gideon's
and he mixed like the banana coffee
with the peanut butter coffee.
And he was making, so he's making his own mashups
as far as liquid.
Yeah, he's really, he's a culinary daredevil.
This is kind of a, he's kind of a food jackass in a way.
Yeah.
He dares to go there.
I think in a lot of ways, yeah,
he is doing outrageous stunts with your food mashups.
Would you guys like to attempt say
an outrageous food stunt of your own?
I would, yes.
Because I went and, you know,
we start thinking about this, doing this episode and like,
well, it'd be great to, I mean, initially I'm like,
I wonder if there's some way to find Beverly.
Then you realize Beverly doesn't exist
besides at these places.
You start looking up other of these sodas
and even at specialty soda stores in our area,
this does not really exist.
So I'm like, there's gotta be some way
to try something equivalent to one of these
or equivalent hopefully to Beverly.
And I wasn't sure where to begin there exactly.
But after some Googling, I found this is pure conjecture.
This is just comments on Reddit and on various blogs
that compared Beverly to something.
And let me read a couple comments that I found.
Let's see.
Beverly is bad, but not as bad as Chinoto.
Italy loves soft drinks that taste like poison.
Ha ha ha.
Chinoto tastes all right to me as you sip it,
but the aftertaste is quite vile.
And then, let me see.
Oh, somebody else.
Let's count your lucky stars and hope that Beverly
is never replaced by Chinoto.
Chinoto is brownish in color and might be slightly heavier.
Even its aesthetic is not appealing to me.
Looking around your garage,
trying to figure out where Chinoto is hiding.
The Chinoto is not here in the garage.
We'll have to step down for a second
and I'm gonna go grab it because I thought to be
kind to ourselves, let's keep it cold.
If we're getting lukewarm with that Chinoto,
let's try to get this in its best possible state
because as this blog said,
maybe they aren't treating the Beverly right.
Maybe there is a way to be presenting this Beverly better.
In this case, this is like a packaged soda by Pellegrino.
This is a Pellegrino product that is available
at the Italian market near where I live.
It was just in the grab and go bottle section
as if it was Coke or something.
I'm just grabbing a quick Chinoto
and then I'm gonna get to my tennis match.
So now you can the next time you do that.
If you like it, but we have to see if we like it.
Should I go grab?
Should we be brave and try some Chinoto?
Maybe worse than Beverly.
We'll see, I'm excited.
The counter point, the soda I really like,
it's not a club cool, is Barrett's ginger beer from Bermuda.
When I was a kid and we took a cruise to Bermuda,
it was just everywhere and just drank,
didn't really drink Coke that week,
it was just drinking this ginger beer.
And it does have a full day's worth of sugar in it,
but it is somehow less sweet than most ginger beers.
Oh, weird.
Okay.
Huh, huh.
There's so much ginger, it will burn your throat
if you drink too much of it.
That's how ginger it is.
Well, when I come back, I'll have a handful of Chinotos
and we'll see if you get as addicted to these.
Let's give it a shot.
Okay.
Okay, we got the bottles, we're charmed by the bottles.
The bottles are nice and cute.
Yes, we all agree the bottles are very cute.
Very cute.
And San Pellegrino branding, so they're sticking by this.
Yeah, yeah, uh-huh.
And it's brown.
As I learned from this blog, the original Beverly was,
because Beverly is clear now.
Right, right.
So that's kind of a clue that maybe it isn't what they,
what product was actually made in Italy.
So let's give it a shot.
As close to the microphone.
Close to the mic.
And try to chew it if you can.
No, here, I'll back up.
We'll do it here.
Says citrus flavored.
Oh yeah, that's an important note.
Yeah, and Wade is.
I'm smelling it too, I'm smelling it.
Do I know anything else about the,
somebody said that they thought this was like prune juice.
We'll see if that's accurate.
Somebody said it's like anise,
oh no, no, anise is more prominent in Beverly.
Beverly, I think I also saw one of the flavoring elements,
grapefruit rind.
So the most bitter part of an already bitter fruit.
Yeah, yeah, so that might be part of it.
But maybe we're dealing with more pleasant stuff here.
I don't know.
You wanna give it a try?
Let's try.
I do like the smell.
I do like the smell as well.
I think it's a pleasant smell.
Okay.
I'm fine with this.
I think it's fine.
I don't know if I'd do it again.
Everybody really get up, get right up on their.
Yeah, I kinda like it.
There is an after taste.
Yeah, yeah, it's a little bitter in the, yeah.
If this is what those Reddit comments are talking about,
and I find it hard to believe that a Reddit comment
would be incorrect in its information
or express some strange points of view.
I don't think this is disgusting whatsoever.
Mike, your thoughts?
No, no, I think it's good, yeah.
It's interesting.
It's like, there's some vaguely medicinal taste in there.
Well, I think that's what a lot of the original formulas
for sodas were medicine, essentially,
and more medicinal.
You can still buy cola syrup.
I remember once as a kid, I had a bad stomach ache,
and my mom's like, let's try cola syrup.
Oh, sure, yeah.
Which you can get at pharmacies,
and I wouldn't recommend it to anyone.
I think it kinda helps settle my stomach a little.
Yeah, and there's no corn syrup in this.
I think it is sugar.
I'll say this, the size of these bottles,
this is the amount of soda I want.
Yes, not like a massive, yeah, absolutely.
A reasonable amount.
Yeah, that would be good, you're right.
This is a little charming.
Erin tried it inside before I came out.
She's like, I would make a cocktail with this anytime.
This is great.
I think so, and I think the Beverly's Revenge cocktail
that they have at Disney Springs is gin and-
Careful.
Some other ingredients, but I thought,
my first thought was, well, you wanna mix it with gin,
because gin's a pretty potent liquor.
I would think you would wanna mix it with
whiskey or something, right? Lemonade or limoncello,
like something, yeah, or bourbon, like something sweeter.
Yeah, maybe, yeah.
I think that's interesting.
Okay, you've had Beverly in the last two years,
which I have not.
Is there any equivalency between what we just had
and Beverly? This is significantly
more palatable than Beverly, I think.
It's gotta be.
If what we just had is anything close,
then it can't be, but I've also, now Mr. Morrow,
he seems, well, maybe he's just, you know,
he's hardened to it.
He goes to these places a lot.
He seemed, I watched a video where he did Beverly
down to no problem.
He's just like, I'm into it.
I think it's, I don't know if it's like a weird
contrarian thing to say you like Beverly,
or again, you're just not getting it in the right context.
Yeah, that's interesting.
He will, I mean, he's a very positive guy.
I don't think he would go out of his way
to say no, I like it.
Yeah, no, I have.
He's more performative.
Yeah.
It's true to himself, you could tell.
I think he mixed Beverly in Sour Plum.
Did I say that already?
Yeah, you said he mixed, yeah.
And I think he was like, that's gross.
Right, I think he, when he doesn't like something,
you can tell, but he's still nice about it.
He's never. Like a bee in his pocket.
He doesn't, yeah, yeah, exactly.
He doesn't trash something, but you could tell.
He tries to understand why you might like
having a bee in your pocket.
Look, you don't want to be in your pocket,
you don't want to be in your bonnet, you know?
You don't want them anywhere.
That's what I say.
Yes, like the people who were mad
that I explained what Beverly is.
That's the definition of a bee in your bonnet.
Or the bee in the bonnet.
But you know what, we got it, we're moving on,
we're chilling out at Club Cool,
and we're doing an episode.
I think we're having fun.
Now, podcasting like comic books, every issue,
every episode is someone's first episode,
which is kind of insane to think about in podcasting
if someone's hopping in on part 17 of the City Walks.
True, true.
I don't know if people start in the middle of that,
but in the middle of the show.
Sure, somebody probably tried and probably hated it.
Spit it out like Beverly.
Yeah.
Well, yeah, my point, I know we do so many things
that we just talk about and don't give any context for,
but when you hear that like,
oh, they've said E-ticket a number of times,
and I don't know what E-ticket means.
I don't know what they're, so that makes you think,
well, maybe we should give a little more context.
But then I say one sentence about Beverly,
and it's like I went on a racist tirade.
That's what that seemed like.
You wrote that, like complaining about cancel culture
in the New York Times editorial page.
It's like, everyone was like, what are you talking about?
You're the New York Times.
Yes, well, yeah, cancel culture's out of hand.
What was, sure, it didn't stop me
from explaining what Beverly is.
Yeah.
Anyway, this is fine.
I, again, let me just quote this blog directly.
I'm not convinced that what Coke is distributing here
is actually a fair representation of Beverly.
And when I look back into like, they also,
they provide some links to some cool YouTube videos
of some very artsy, like, you know,
Mad Men era Beverly television commercials
that are so cool.
They use the Beverly slogan, which is really weird.
They had a tagline.
Cold is Helsinki, sparkling is Rio, dry is El Paso.
And then there's like a, you know, some suave guy
who's dressed like he's a cowboy when it's El Paso
when he's in a furry hat when it's Helsinki.
I don't know what the hell that means.
I don't know how one beverage can be all of those things.
But there had to have been something
to the 60s Beverly for it to, like, maybe we have,
I think we've perverted potentially
with Chinoto as the proof.
Right.
If it was anything close to this,
then maybe it's getting a bad rep today.
Yeah, that's probably right.
This is only tangential.
Oh, it's related, but like this sort of, yeah,
maybe what we're tasting as Beverly
is like the aggressive version of this or something.
Like take this.
Dialed up all the way.
Yeah.
Because they're worried that, I don't know,
that it wouldn't register even as anything.
I don't know, cause it feels weird to me
that Disney would be like, or Coke even,
like we need to make sure people like hate it
or have a strong reaction.
But maybe they think, like, do the people at Coke know
or whoever's giving, like the people hate this
and this is funny.
That doesn't make sense to me.
So like, I feel like they were like,
well, we're putting the amount of sugar or whatever
that we were saying earlier that the normal American palate
would desire for a soda.
Like I just, it's weird.
I don't, I can't quite tell.
I mean, I think a cup of Beverly
could use a tablespoon of sugar.
Like I think that could be sweeter.
Yeah.
You think that would solve its problem?
Potentially.
More sugar or like, yeah, if you're mixing it with something.
Like Beverly and lemonade might not be too bad.
Interesting.
I don't know.
Yeah, maybe they are playing into,
because it seems like kind of a recent phenomenon
that YouTubers do videos of making people try Beverly
and you get the grossed out faces.
So maybe they're like, okay,
we gotta keep these videos coming.
So I'm worried that people are gonna get calloused
to this soda or somebody with a more mature palate
might come in.
So we gotta start getting this thing grosser.
Right.
This is a new Coke scenario
in the way that that is a conspiracy maybe
to change out the formula.
And maybe that like, they're trying to,
it's a new grosser Beverly.
Who knows what they're doing to it?
Huh.
Or it's like, yeah, it's like the,
what's the Harry Potter jelly bellies called?
Bernie, the every flavor beans.
Yeah.
And there's one of his like fart flavored or something.
Fart or vomit or something like that.
Yeah.
But jelly bellies do that too, right?
There's like a couple of really gross ones.
Yeah, they do.
I think so.
Yeah.
But that's for sure like part of their fun, I guess.
Even though I find that whenever I get it,
I go, oh God, why?
Well, it also helps re the Beverly placement.
It also helps it like reinforce the idea of like,
you know, from American perspective of like,
oh, other countries, so does how they sure are something.
You know, like it's a little, you know.
Well, is it possible that this is some
anti Italian propaganda?
There we go.
Yes, here's where we're landing.
Where it's like to make you feel like,
how kooky these people could be.
They drink this is like a sweet drink to them.
Are they crazy?
Are they trying to stir up distrust
in the Italians for some reason?
Maybe, or yeah, maybe it's even less nefarious
and it's yeah, it's more just trying
to make it feel so exotic that it would shock you.
They're trying to shock you in the same way
that they're trying to shock you with a mission to space,
or they're trying to shock you with a 60 mile an hour turn
and straight away on the end of test track.
It's the palette equivalent of that.
Exactly.
It's the harrowing acts.
Splash mountain drop.
It's the big moment that makes you go, what?
Places are different than our place?
Like that's the whole point of Club Cool.
So maybe that's the reason that they need it to, yeah.
Cause like the watermelon soda, you don't have it,
but like we've had, you've had weird juice.
Cactus cooler.
Yeah, that's not so wild.
Most of it's not that wild.
So they have to have one in there that makes you feel
like it's from a different planet.
What if they're routing water from a nearby ride?
Like we're not that far from, you know, frozen ever after.
What if there's a pipe that goes straight from the water
in that river, right into that fountain for Beverly?
What if you're not, this isn't even, this isn't remotely,
it's not a formula of a soda at all.
Well, it's even closer to the living with the land.
So there could be pomace.
They could be having pomace.
They're trying to get rid of filtering the water through it.
Maybe they're diffusing like through a pipe that is nearby.
Yeah, that they've like shaved off
of some of their hydroponics.
So it's like, so it's theme park boat water running
through a pomace laced tube.
Yeah.
Hmm.
This is a good, I think we need to see, open the pipes,
Disney, we need to see your pipes.
Where is that Beverly coming from?
What are we drinking?
Hashtag open the pipes.
There's a lot of Imagineers that have been laid off
and have left recently.
And will anyone go off the record, at least with us,
that is listening now?
Do they know?
You say yes, you know, or are you disagreeing with them?
Yeah, I'm agreeing with you.
Yes, I would love that.
I mean, I would also love, you know, we,
I mentioned earlier, the previous iteration of Club Cool
was called Ice Station Cool.
And it had a very unique theme.
It looked like a big snowy cavern
with a giant snowcat like machine outside.
And just gonna read this chunk from Yesterland.
In an odd bit of theatrical theming
at Epcot's otherwise modern commuter core,
Ice Station Cool was themed as an exploration site
in a polar region.
A snow cap with Coca Cola shaped,
Coca Cola bottle shaped shreds
sat in front of a tunnel into the ice.
A plaque on the outside read,
Refreshes Maximus Expeditions,
led by Coca Cola Coolologists.
Love Coolologists.
Love Coolologists have explored
the farthest reaches of the globe.
Their mission, to discover the origins of cool.
Cool capitalized like God.
Yeah, much like God.
And...
That's better, right?
We agree that was better.
I think so.
I mean, there's a backstory.
Right, exactly.
And you really go to a place.
I mean, not to take anything away
from the theming of the club,
but it's a little more Epcot-y
that you're going into a research base.
Sorry, was there more, Jason?
Oh yeah, because there's a further audit goes,
guess all that Refreshes Maximus Expedition
had made a gruesome discovery.
The perfectly preserved frozen corpse
they called Thirsty Man was behind glass.
He was collecting a prehistoric Coca Cola.
The plaque below the glass read,
this early human ancestor,
frozen in his hunt for refreshment,
was discovered in the sub-Arctic.
The Coca Cola Coolologists named him Thirsty Man
for obvious reasons.
The object found frozen just beyond his grasp
leads us to ask, what came first, man or refreshment?
So a man frozen in his death,
clutching a bottle of Coke
that somehow existed in caveman times.
Prehistoric man, like the monolith from 2001 has landed.
And instead of reaching for a bone to turn into a tool,
he's reaching for an old Coke.
I had no memory of Thirsty Man.
No idea.
He's now a PTR favorite.
I'm gonna call it now.
We all like Thirsty Man.
We all love Thirsty Man.
Yes.
But I was saying to Jay and I was like,
hey, did you know Club Cool used to be something else?
Cause I remember going when I was much younger
and I was like, oh, it had a different name
and like a different end.
She's like, yeah, the dead guy.
And I was like, what?
And she was like, there was this,
when I was a kid, there was a scary man,
like frozen in the ice.
And I'm like.
So she knew Thirsty Man.
She knew Thirsty.
She had a memory of being scared,
having to run by Thirsty Man.
And I had no memory at all.
I'm like.
We gotta get past this fast
cause he might break out of the glass.
How dead is he?
What if he's just temporarily frozen?
And I did not understand what she was talking about
until I saw these pictures.
I was like, they had a preserved corpse?
There's no way they just have a corpse in Epcot.
That's pretty crazy.
Yeah.
Thirsty Man.
Well, am I, wait, am I crazy?
I'm fact checking this right now.
Oh, no, no, no.
I'm not crazy.
This, this,
Syndra, this,
a caveman frozen in ice.
This is the plot of a classic film
that Disney made and owns,
a film called Encino Man.
Yes.
Oh, of course.
And everything is IP crazy.
But if we,
and I could see the desire to remake Encino Man.
You know,
you know, Brendan Fraser's riding a wave.
I think people are fond of him again.
But if we want to open it up,
if people, if we want to make it more international,
if people in other countries are like, what's Encino?
The way maybe to broaden it out is to,
is to make it Thirsty Man.
Yeah, that's right.
And to make a fully funded feature film
in cooperation with the Coca-Cola Company.
We know that they're great at making movies.
People have said great things about
this World of Coke movie with Professor Wet Whistle.
Professor Wet Whistle could get in on,
I haven't seen him,
but again, PTR favorite already.
And now before you've even seen the thing.
So Professor,
Professor Wet Whistle,
let's tie together the entire Coca-verse.
Professor Wet Whistle discovers Thirsty Man.
And then the,
we'll have the polar bears and Santa Claus in it as well,
from the Coca-verse.
Oh, absolutely.
And then other Coca-Cola celebrities,
I'm trying to say. Santa Claus.
I just said him.
Oh, you said him.
I was just, yeah.
But yeah, cause our modern image of Santa Claus
goes back to like Coca-Cola ads and stuff.
Paulie Shore is Santa Claus.
Well, does then,
well, is this also,
does the Santa Claus universe tie into this as well?
Yeah.
The Santa Claus movies have always quietly been
Coca-Cola branded products.
Yes.
Coke just never stepped up and said,
give us money for that.
Right. Are we getting,
I forget, is it a,
are we getting a Santa Claus show with Tim Allen
on Disney plus,
or is it a movie?
I think it's a show.
It's a show series.
Sign on.
Yeah. We're getting more than a movie.
We're getting, finally.
We're getting eight hours of Tim Allen, Santa Claus.
It is mid seventies.
What if it was like a Sopranos or like a PG Sopranos
or Breaking Bad Santa Claus.
I think that would be a great idea.
We know it's not that.
I know.
Yeah. But we, I don't know,
but you know, in a way do we know?
Cause we're, this is the post Bel Air world.
We know we're taking stories more seriously.
And I think it's kind of,
it's, I'm a little offended honestly,
that they threw away Santa Claus's death
to create the premise of the first Santa Claus.
They do, we're so flippant about it.
I think episode one is just fully the death,
hiding the body.
I think they let Tim Allen out of it easily.
In the first one by the body just disappearing.
I think they have to dissolve it, Breaking Bad Asid style.
Can I add to this?
The new version, Tim Allen murders Santa Claus on purpose.
Yeah.
He kills Santa Claus.
This members him in a long scene.
Body part by body part into the chimney, into the fireplace.
Yeah. Yeah.
Okay. So this is like a Dexter sort of thing.
Yes.
And he did it just cause he wanted to like,
I want to see a man die.
The first scene is just Tim Allen.
The first episode is Tim Allen killing him.
It's just a long first step.
Methodical, slow, heartless, jokeless, gruntless.
He's not doing, we're pushing Tim Allen's acting.
We're going to make him go there finally,
give him like the late period performance
that lets you know what he's capable of.
Yes. I think that's what we're headed for here.
Sounds great.
Does he kill him because he wants to be Santa Claus
or kind of Jason, like what you just said,
that maybe he just wants to, he's out for blood.
Is it like, oh, and on top of that,
this man I murdered was Santa Claus?
Maybe it's a twisted version of the meaning of like,
you know, peace on earth, goodwill to men.
He's experienced that and he wants to see the full range
of human possibilities and see the mirror opposite.
Like what is the darkest?
If that's the best we can be, what is the darkest?
What is the darkest we can be?
I mean, this has so much more going on
in terms of issues and complexity
than the original Santa Claus.
This is a, it requires a complex palette,
but that's today's viewers.
We want more, we want to go there.
That's right. That's true.
But together, all quadrants,
the second episode will introduce Krampus
and Krampus will do TikTok dances.
You know, you got to hit the quadrants, you know.
Keep it fun. We'll keep it fun for everybody.
Yeah. Yeah.
Well, I think, and also, I just went looking for,
is there more Coca-Cola IP to tie in?
And I'm pretty horrified at what I found,
which is the character named Sprite Boy.
Anybody ever seen Sprite Boy?
I have seen Sprite Boy.
Yeah. He's kind of reminiscent of,
well, this is what you do.
Jack Frost, forget Jack Frost.
You kind of reset Jack Frost,
as played by Martin Short, as Sprite Boy,
because we're basically looking at Jack Frost,
but with a giant bottle cap fused to his head.
This is a freak of nature, this character.
Oddly not a Sprite promoting character.
Right. He's not a,
but he's a Sprite in the former sense of Sprite,
not the product sense of Sprite.
And if we're, if we want this thing to be terrifying,
Sprite Boy is.
It's played by a 75 year old Martin Short.
Is that what you're getting at?
Sure. Yeah. Yeah.
Or, or, or Jason.
Well, Jason, please.
Well.
More than welcome.
You know, send in a tape.
We'll look at it. Sure.
We'll look at both Martin's audition and Jason's audition.
Well, I was going to say,
if you need to broaden the cast a little,
they could do a Who Framed Roger Rabbit,
do a little licensing and get some seven up characters
in there. Cause of course we all know Cool Spot.
There was also the brief 80s character, Fido Dido.
Kind of looks like Pepper Anne.
What's Fido Dido?
Fido Dido looks like,
I don't, I don't know how to describe this.
Fido Dido is a little doodle.
A little doodle like guy in a t-shirt and shorts.
I don't know.
How would you describe Fido Dido?
Oh yeah. You're right about Pepper Anne.
Kind of a squiggle guy.
Yeah. Kind of a squiggly character.
Fido Dido.
Well, why can't the, you know,
why can't the soda companies wage war and like,
it should be about the Coke characters, you know,
going on a killing spree against the seven up character.
Oh, the polar bear kills Cool Spot.
Eating each spot, just like grabbing it,
like stripping all of the red,
leaving whatever skeleton would be under a Cool Spot.
Just the legs, I guess, spits out the sneakers.
There was a cool, I had the Cool Spot video game growing.
I loved the Cool Spot video game.
It was a little good.
Like you had to make fun of it.
But I- Like side scroll.
Visually, it seems like, yeah,
there was something going on in design.
There was a Noid video game too.
Domino's Pizza Noid.
So yeah.
So they should bring all that stuff back.
There should be a PS5 Cool Spot game.
And we'll get there.
Yeah, sure.
How many steps are we away from movies or just brands?
And then there's- Oh yeah.
Like, and Aaron brought this up the other day,
like, well, how soon is it just gonna be Target the movie?
Best Buy the movie.
And then there's people like vehemently defending,
like why, no, why can't Coles the movie be good?
I don't understand.
Like, how cynical are you that you think that Coles,
they're gonna nail Coles the movie.
Look, don't gatekeep Coles the move, okay?
Let's not, you know.
Those Jimmy John commercials with Brad Garrett.
Actually, don't make those a movie.
I didn't get the part of the assistant.
I don't want, I don't wanna see it ever again.
You say those commercials, I don't know them.
I'm not tracing them.
Oh, they're a lot.
90 year old Martin Scorsese,
like the Coles movie is just something we shouldn't,
like we should really cherish the movies that are made
by like auteurs and that and shut up old man.
Idiot.
Old man farts a lot, has opinion.
You did. Good for you.
How'd you squeeze that one out?
Show the hell, we want to see Marshall's too.
Well, I mean, hey, we're the ones pitching brand movies.
That's true.
And enjoying clubs brought to,
clubs and ice expeditions and the range
of great themed experiences, crucial themed experiences
brought to us by our friends at the Coca-Cola company.
Yeah.
You know, I, when reading about like old Epcot stuff
recently, we're coming up on the anniversary of Epcot.
Is that 40 years?
Of Epcot?
I don't, well, I don't know,
cause I'm not keeping track.
I start, it's kind of a BCAD for me,
where I started at Club Cool.
Like I don't acknowledge any Epcot before Club Cool.
But there was, you know, a window of time, you know,
you could play Genesis games
and you could drink unlimited soda.
And for as much as they're like,
what if there's a weird circus in Epcot?
What if there was a water show with a millennium
celebration and the language sounds like all language.
Like there's a lot of, you know,
negotiating from points of weakness.
But then every now and then they do know what kids want.
They want unlimited soda and they want free video games.
Yeah. Yeah.
And one went away, but one stays.
One came back even though its venue was taken away.
Come back multiple times,
like shut down for a few months
to become the first Club Cool.
Then it shut down, survived the pandemic
and became new Club Cool,
which kind of has a beveled glass center.
Kind of looks like the Coke.
If you would ever get a fountain Coke
at like a soda shop or something.
Yeah, it's fun.
I was going to say, is there a plus?
Do you have a plus up?
Does anybody have a plus up real quick
before we get out of here?
Oh, interesting.
Cause like I obviously froze the frozen man,
whatever he was called.
Thirsty man. Thirsty man.
Bring him back, animate him.
He's serving the sodas.
More for you.
Right. Yeah.
How was the plum?
If they could have,
I was going to say if they could be served by somebody
like in the world showcase,
where they have people from the separate countries.
If you could get like an Italian,
could give you the Beverly.
Okay.
Maybe you could like tell you,
or you had like a sommelier,
even in general doesn't have to be from the country
that could explain the different intricacies.
And like, then we could ask the questions we're asking here
and it could be a much more learning experience
than we have now where we just have to guess a lot.
I would love a soda sommelier.
That sounds great.
I'm sure at the Atlanta tour,
all these companies have like someone whose palette
is like the super taster or something.
Right. Yes.
And yeah.
Well, I was going to say simpler.
If you like, you know,
country club or you like Bebo,
you should then be able to walk up to the counter
and buy like a bottle.
This is a great idea.
Oh yeah.
I'm surprised they don't have.
That is strange.
Yeah.
Cause you would think it would be a no brainer
that they could sell some, at least, at least yes.
They could sell not maybe a two liter,
but sell something you could sip and drink.
A 16 ounce bottle.
Like the other size ones.
This little Pellegrino bottle we just had.
Right.
Yeah. A little sipper.
Yeah. Why not?
Right.
So yeah, that's interesting that they don't.
I think the beverage distribution is still so chaotic.
Like, and stuff like in,
especially once you get into like alcoholic beverage,
like we still can't get yingling in California.
They keep saying it's coming.
Like, you can't get yingling beer from Pennsylvania.
You can't get it in California.
I don't know about this.
Texas and stuff.
This is Pennsylvania.
Has that been, what is the start is one of the questions.
What do you mean?
Like, is it something that was available
and is not available now?
No, it's just, it's not really available much,
like a certain part of the country.
You can get it like on the Eastern Sea of board.
And like they, I think we're just figuring out
the licensing it to brewers in like Texas
to get it in other places.
So this has been something that's ongoing
that you've been tracking.
Well, I have been tracking a friend of the show,
Marissa Strickland and I regularly check in
and see what the status of yingling in Los Angeles is.
Cause there were some bars that would get kegs
and kind of serve it on the down low.
And this is your favorite.
And then they get in trouble.
Oh, interesting.
And this is your favorite beer?
One of your favorite beers?
I, yeah.
Have I had it with you?
I think we've had, I mean,
it's pretty easy to get in like New York and Philadelphia.
And they have it all over Disney World.
Oh, really?
I've heard of it,
but I didn't realize it was such a thing.
Is it America's oldest brewery or one of the oldest?
Huh.
That's a mate like, oh really?
I didn't know you get yingling at Disney World comments.
Yingling is the most popular beer.
This is a crucial beer I could do right now.
Well, I mean, the most, any time,
sometimes when it comes up, everyone sends the like,
well, and here's the one yingling son
with Donald Trump Jr.
And it's like, yes, business owners
love to give Republicans money.
We know that.
That's all we've been talking about for weeks now.
Oh geez.
Sorry, you have to carry that crowd.
That's nice.
Where were we?
Beverage distribution.
We were flossing up and then we ended up in yingling.
I would love to get like a 16 ounce bottle
of like a Bebo or Viva or any of these things.
But I think it's probably just too chaotic to get it.
Even just a shirt.
They should sell a Beverly shirt now, you know?
It's a good question.
Do they have Beverly shirt?
They have a lot of Coca-Cola,
the Coke logo in different languages,
but I don't know that they have Beverly merch.
They don't think they do.
But has anyone even on T public made a Beverly shirt?
I think there is that.
Yeah, I think there's enough of a,
so we would not be the first to attempt to.
Oh, I don't want to, I don't want to cash in.
I just wanted to know if they had done it.
I mean, I know some of the soda,
like some of the sodas like, well,
we introduced this 15 years ago.
And like the reason they introduced it is cause like,
well, this soda in Brazil,
like based on this local fruit was very popular.
So Coke introduced a competitor.
I don't know that they're pumping out merchandise
for the soda where it was like, you got to try this.
It fucking sucks.
You got to try the shitty one.
You got to try the prank soda.
Yeah, probably not.
And start, you know, get Beverly in regular stores.
Why should we have to go to this place
to have a shitty prank soda?
Yeah.
This should be a ability that we have for all occasions.
You know, for all the people,
a prank we should be able to play
on all the loved ones in our lives.
Or whether it be our dad's birthday or a bachelor party,
we need to, we should be cheersing this shitty drink
all year round.
Human Beverly-ed.
Yes, what was the thing?
What was the like, the Smirnoff,
there was some like stupid soda challenge.
Oh, you got iced.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You got iced, you had a Smirnoff ice.
That's too easy.
Smirnoff ice tastes like candy
and it's like very easy to drink.
Right, right.
Yeah, yeah, that was a being a treat.
That's not a big deal.
Depending on your taste.
Yeah, yeah, but a Beverly is,
drinking a whole bottle of Beverly is a slog
and doing it without vomiting.
Oh yeah, the Beverly challenge.
But the next time any of us are in Vegas,
we should go check.
I mean, that is my preferred section of the strip
to stay in the Coca-Cola store.
The world of Coke.
To be across from the world of Coke and the Hard Rock Cafe
that is above a Marshall's.
You stay in there until the store closes
and get like, bring a sleeping bag up
into the top of the big bottle.
Well, I gotta kiss the polar bear.
Good night. Good night.
Yeah.
All right, well, we'll all get a room in the world of Coke
soon enough.
As for now, you survived podcast the ride,
club cool edition.
I'm so glad we chilled out and kept it cool today.
You guys keep it cool day to day
and talk to you next time, I suppose.