Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast contains secret trombos, Ewok sadness, the big zerg, and many,
far too many Tom Cruise tangents.
to talk Buzz Lightyear astro blasters on today's podcast, The Ride.
We're going to podcast The Ride, which today, just to be clear, isn't about Lightyear, the
movie.
This is the ride based on the movie about toys that the origin story about the human
Buzz Lightyear is based on.
I'm Scott Gardner.
Hi, Jason Sheridan.
Hi.
Yeah, I'm glad we settled that.
Yeah, yeah.
That's just to be clear.
That's the only reason that was said.
Mike Carlson.
Hi.
Yes.
And then we should also clarify, this is a podcast not about The Ride.
It is a podcast based on the concept of The Ride as a themed entity.
Okay, so I don't want to make that because people might be confused about what this podcast
is even a few years in.
And it's about the idea of The Ride being something that's bigger than just an actual
ride.
So that's clear.
I just want to make sure that's very clear.
Like, just to be clear.
We're also really going out on a limb because we're probably going to touch on one, two,
three, four, four different four different rides.
There's a lot of names, a lot of names to play.
It gets very complicated.
So let's make sure all of our names get out before we start to do that, including our
guest for today joining us for the first time in person.
Finally, not a Zoom, doing the real podcast The Ride experience here in a hot garage.
It's the only real way to do it.
From Get Played, it's Matt Apodaca.
What's going on?
I just want to clarify that I'm actually not the Matt Apodaca, but I'm based on Matt Apodaca.
So that's just like just so we all just are clearing the air there.
Oh, jeez.
We're one level removed.
Yeah, I'm the guy that like, no, I'm not going to.
Would you say you're in all?
I was going to say, are you like an homage?
Yeah, maybe a Matt Apodaca pastiche.
OK, got it.
Got it.
It's not all of it, but it's like you sort of get it.
Yeah.
OK, then I guess that word.
If you hear like, dare to be stupid, you sort of like get Devo.
You're like, oh, I sort of understand.
Oh, sure.
Yeah, it's almost better.
It's almost like combines a bunch of things into one potent.
Yeah.
Matt, in this case, Matt Apodaca ish piece.
Well, that's great.
It's good to have you, whatever you are here.
I'm excited to be here.
I love this show.
So it's it's it's an honor to be in the garage.
Oh, fantastic.
Yeah.
So it's so happy to have you and wanting to get folks who were so much fun over Zoom.
But we.
Yeah.
We haven't actually done one in person.
So this is wonderful.
We're to look in the in the eye.
Finally, all this this stuff is done.
It's all this crazy covid stuff.
It is over.
We are celebrating.
I was on a plane the other day and I freaking cheered.
I freaking laughed.
I was like, finally.
Oh, open the I opened the emergency door and threw my mask out the door.
You were on the flight.
I was on the flight.
Yeah.
Wow.
I hit pause on Ghostbusters Afterlife and they're like, I got a clap.
I got a clap.
I was ready to clap when the plane landed.
I got a clap now.
We ran after the movie.
Yeah, yeah, of course.
Yeah.
Ever.
But because this did happen, my parents are telling me about it.
They were not on one of the planes where this happened, but they knew people who were.
Oh, wow.
Got the announcement.
Ladies and gentlemen, you can remove your masks right now.
There was like a minute of mid-flight where it happened.
Yeah.
Were there videos of it?
Yeah, yeah.
It was like on Twitter.
I can't think of a dorkier thing to do.
That's like way wackier than like wearing your mask.
Yay.
I don't have to anymore.
Well, making the biggest deal out of the removal, which is a very simple process.
It can happen in less than a second.
Oh, thank God.
Each strap whipping it like as if you're breaking through shackles.
Yeah, using like the jaws of life to take it off your face.
Metal chest, belt on your face or something when you literally everybody had it off to
snack on pretzels minutes earlier.
Yeah.
Or you're like Houdini with this like locked like vest.
It's like, oh, it's like it's that big of a deal.
Yeah.
It kind of revealed for me how few people actually have noise canceling headphones because
that was a game changer for me.
Really?
Like investing in decent noise canceling.
Like I feel like for me, that would have been like pulled that your ear, you know, you're
saying people up and like here I go, OK, and like just put it back to my book or something.
You're saying you ignore all the announcements now that you have the noise canceling headphones
on a plane.
I'm saying I don't like I don't catch some of them.
I have it up loud enough.
Yeah.
I remember the last plane I was on, I was watching Venom to let there be carnage and
I did miss some of it, but only because I had my my AirPods just blasting and everybody
near me heard that there'd be carnage as well.
They're not great, but thank you for saying the full title.
I got you know, I got to give credit where credit's due and, you know, give art the respect
it deserves.
Yeah, you know.
Yeah, of course.
Yeah.
Film and this carnage to be gotten.
I mean, it's in the movie.
He says it.
He doesn't.
That phrase said in the movie.
He says it at the end of the first one and they were like, you know what?
That's the title of the movie.
Oh, yeah.
They're like, we have a title.
Yeah.
Like, OK, Andy Serkis, get to work, baby.
Man, I am so behind.
I haven't watched that and I have not watched Morbius, the living vampire yet.
Yeah.
There's no way that I'm going to see Morbius within the next two years, but maybe in three,
I'll give it a watch.
I'm going to out myself that I was how this is a little I pay attention and I've only
seen that word just while flipping past on the Internet or on Twitter or something.
And I just thanked friend of the show, Andrew Grissom, for saying the title out loud in
front of me because I said it was bound to happen that I would on the podcast would just
dive in and call it Moribus.
I was so close to that happening.
Now I've essentially let it happen now.
But I really did think that I so much I have not come across Morbius before.
Yeah.
He was like kind of a big character in the Spider-Man cartoon in the 90s, but not memorable
like weird as like me and Mike.
Like yeah, more.
Yeah.
More Michael Morbius.
Michael Morbius, the living vampire.
Dr. Mike Morbius.
Yeah.
He's playing Dr. Michael Morbius.
Felicia, Felicia.
He was just like very.
Yeah.
He would say Felicia, which is Felicia Hardy, the black cat who I am by Felicia.
No, not by Felicia.
No, by Felicia.
Although now you've probably created an internet sensation.
Oh man.
You just edited that.
Let me go.
I'm walking over to funny or die real quick.
Edit, edit, edit.
Post.
Money rolls in.
All of them so much money.
For me.
Cha-ching.
It's a hit on our web, on our page, on True Social.
It's a hit on the True Social page.
Yeah, they're partnered with True Social now primarily.
Congrats, guys.
So, yeah, so happy to have you and happy to talk about, I think this topic makes a lot
of sense that we landed on it as a gaming attraction.
Yes.
Just sort of where we were leaning with other stuff you were talking about.
Yeah, yeah.
You're very gaming-versed.
I love games.
Yes, yeah.
You also were talking about though like, you know, carnival games.
Or the game, because there are carnival games in theme parks.
Yeah.
Do you ever stop and take advantage of that?
Do you give those a whirl?
I feel like when I was a kid, that was definitely something that I was like more interested
in.
I was like, oh, well, like, because like, I feel like when I was a kid at Knott's Berry
Farm, for example, they had like, like they would have like Pokemon plushes.
Like they weren't like necessarily like in theme park exclusive.
They would just like get like Stewie or whoever.
Right.
Any sort of thing they could get that people would then want to spend like five dollars
on three balls or something.
Like I would always try to do that.
And I would always try to like figure out like how to like, how to win.
Because those games are sort of like they're not impossible, but there's there is like
a trick to them for some of them.
But I always do pretty well with the one where you have to like blow up the clowns like balloon
head or whatever it is with water or something.
Yeah, the straight water gun basically.
And you it's a little tiny target and like a big rectangle.
And it's like sometimes it's like moving too.
So you have to like follow the moving thing.
But I would always do well with that because the other people playing that are usually
younger children.
So I'd be like, OK, well, I'm 10.
I got smoke in that.
Yeah.
And they're upset.
And I get to take home my Stewie.
Did you win a Stewie?
I don't know if I ever got a Stewie.
But like I think the last time the last time I did one, we got a an off color bullseye
from one of the ones that California Adventure.
And it was like for my birthday, my girlfriend like paid for like the round of games.
And I still was like I didn't even try to like let her win.
I was like, I'm going to win.
And I won.
But I let her pick the plush.
I don't know where it is now because like I guess I don't keep track.
That's the horse racing game where you throw the ball like the sir like there's like three
different targets and they're like the hard you get farther in the race if you throw it
in the more like far away, far away target.
And I feel like they had they had a different I wanted to play again because like if you
then you know, if you win more than once, you can like sort of get a bigger prize.
And they had like a Mickey with like a Hawaiian shirt.
And I was like, that's sort of more the vibe.
I was like, yeah, that's good.
California Adventure.
Yeah.
Well, yeah, this guy, you know, just by look of him, you know, he's got a little bit of
just by look of him, you know, he's got stories.
I wanted to see what he was all about.
But we didn't even play that much.
We didn't play more because more people then showed up and I was like, I don't like our
odds.
We got to get out of here.
Yeah, yeah.
That's I've talked to real.
I talked about accidentally winning a homer on the Santa Monica boardwalk.
I realized after I was done, it was the horse racing game.
I had beaten eight children.
Ten years ago.
So I was in my 20s.
Yeah.
Is this the way maybe you both have stumbled on the hack here?
If you want to win one that it has to be competition, because if it's you versus somebody,
nobody, right, you end up empty handed.
But if it's you versus many children.
Well, right.
That helps a lot.
The water gun game you're talking about and then the horse racing game both has to have
a winner also.
Some games where it's just you got to get three strikes or whatever.
And then that you can just fail at and win a target like a ping pong ball in like a weird
round dish.
Yeah.
Like that's a sometimes like a frog based game.
You have to do something like that.
I'll still like there'll be a lot of winners, but maybe like you're not going to get a bigger
prize.
No, no, no, no.
I won against no one back.
I won.
I think I talked about it on my trip report episode, but like we were at Animal Kingdom.
It was pouring rain all day and there's a carnival games by the rubble of the primeval
world.
And Jane played cheap.
She paid for a round.
It was a wiffle ball.
You were given like X number of wiffle balls and you had to get it in like a wooden like
surface that was filled with holes.
Yeah.
And it, you know, so eventually it goes in a hole, but it had to be a colored hole to
win a prize.
And she, she didn't get it in or bounced out.
And I was like, all right, I'll give it a shot.
And I just went like wild card with it.
Like I got, I just didn't aim.
I just threw it high and it came right down and went right in the medium prize hole.
That right.
And it was, yeah.
Pretty good.
He just held for applause.
For the listener at home.
Like they're going to be applauding.
They lifted you up on everybody's shoulders and they locked you down main street and like
this man's a god.
They put him in the tree, the tree of life.
Waves to everyone.
Yeah.
The, I think I've said this before too, Mike, I would love these carnival games too, because
there would be a local carnival and there would be a guy who most years who would like
loudly tell you how the price system worked.
And he would be like, we're playing for another big and we are playing for another big and
you go to big and for a jumbo.
And like, we love this guy and we would play this game.
And I don't think we ever even want to big in.
I think we got a small, the smallest version.
We did not get a big.
Small and big.
We did not get a big and small ones, but I don't think we spent enough money.
Yeah.
If somebody's shouting that they're about to do one with a big in, you're immediately
more interested than you were a second ago.
But when you didn't hear anything, he was like, wait a second, a big in a big in sounds
fun.
It's such an ear worm.
It's not a word you're used to hearing.
Yeah.
Maybe only hear it there.
A big in two big ins for a jumbo.
I do think like carnival barking is like an unsung art.
Like I always am like so impressed with everybody.
Just like working their ass off at a carnival there because that's, you know, it's hard.
It seems hard to me.
Yeah.
You do for hours.
Yelling for hours.
And you got to pack it up and move on to the next city.
That's crazy.
Yeah.
It is.
It's an interesting, interesting life, I would assume.
Yeah.
I wonder how many people are still like on the road 300 days a year with a carnival.
A decent amount, I bet.
I would assume so.
I watched that movie, the Nightmare Alley, and I kind of wanted it.
I wasn't, I didn't love it because it wasn't as interesting as I wanted it to be, which was then just seeing more carnival stuff.
It was not enough carnival.
You want a documentary.
Yeah.
I guess I wanted to see like POV footage of carnival.
Somebody experiencing a carnival.
Unedited raw footage.
Security cam.
You should, there's an old movie called Gun Crazy.
Okay.
And it's about two people doing trick shots at carnivals.
Like they're like marksmen.
Yeah.
And then they start robbing banks.
But like that sounds awesome.
The way they seduce each other is by like they put apples on each other's head in front of an audience and then they shoot a gun at it.
Oh my God.
And that is like, oh, everyone's just cool with this.
That, I mean, that's like, I love heist movies too.
So that's like a combination of things that I'm in.
What's it called?
Gun Crazy.
Also known as Deadly is the Female.
Wow.
Crazy tight 1950.
It's a Trumbo.
It's a, it was blacklisted.
Wow.
But it was, yeah, it's a Trumbo.
It's a secret Trumbo.
Secret Trumbo.
That's a biggin.
Yeah.
It's like a B movie.
And then, but it is like, this is better than you think it would be.
Like it's like in the national film registry.
Oh, okay.
So I forget where it was on HBO Max.
I don't know if it's still up there, but yeah.
So, so Matt, you were like, you were very, I would say like, because I feel like the same way.
I was very game obsessed when I was young too.
Because I liked video games a lot.
But then, yeah, going to a place where there was the winning aspect.
That was like really exciting.
But also like some of these places, like, like Disneyland had an arcade for a while.
And like even in the, what it's called now, the, that thing in Tomorrowland,
it's now like an Avengers, like, or sort of like a Marvel, like presentation place or something where they had Osimo.
Oh, I'll know all that.
Yeah.
The launch, the launch.
What is that?
Star Wars.
Yeah.
In there they had like, they had like, I feel like I played Guitar Hero in there one time.
Like they like had it like set up.
Probably.
And was like, I think it might've been like even like, or it might've been Lego Rock Band.
Oh, wow.
And so I was playing with other kids, like probably to like Taylor Swift or something.
Yeah.
What's different about the Lego?
It's more like, I think it's a little more like these are like radio Disney, like type hits or something.
Sure.
Less likely to be raunchy.
Yeah.
Exactly.
No Buck Cherry or anything like that on there.
Damn it.
Filthy Buck Cherry.
A lot of Microsoft sponsorship there.
Yeah.
You got a lot of Xbox stuff.
So I think it was like on an Xbox.
Yeah.
And I was like, I don't have this.
Windows, whatever the current Windows at the time was where it's like, look you can run a whole house with Windows ME.
I feel like I remember like Windows 7 being like a big deal.
Yes.
Like just in my lifetime, I remember hearing everybody being like, wow, Windows 7.
Wow.
We should do an episode on the Windows house.
I remember that being like kind of interesting because I remember a friend of mine, you know what?
I don't know if you've had Ify Wadiway on the show before.
We have.
Okay.
I've been to Disneyland with him quite a bit because he's one of my oldest friends.
I've known him for like 16 years.
Former employee as well.
Yeah.
Well, yeah, we were former coworkers.
We worked at the improv together.
And he also, he's just, he's, I mean, all going on and on about how much I love him.
But we went to Disneyland a lot and we went into the, that display room and we got everybody around us because you can like change the music stuff.
We put the cha cha slide on.
We got everybody in there to do the cha cha slide.
Wow.
You turned it into a actual interaction.
Wait a minute.
This is going to be fun because I mean, there's a certain type of person that I feel like they're probably all at Disneyland.
If you hear a cha cha slide, you're going to participate.
Yeah.
Yeah. I do it there.
Yes.
This is sorry.
This is still the this is Lego Rock Band or is this is the Windows?
This was in the Windows house because you can like change this.
I think there was like the music.
There was a thing in the room.
You're like, oh look, you can put on whatever songs you want on this thing.
And one of them, one of the preloaded ones was the cha cha slide.
They tried to do a call back to the house of the future or the house of tomorrow.
The one that, you know, was the sixties attraction.
Yeah.
That like they had to get so many wrecking balls to destroy.
Solidly made.
Right.
And then at the end of the interventions out here, they recreated like the inside of a house that you could like, look, you can run this with Windows 7.
Yeah.
This is pre like Nest or like smart home stuff is just catching on.
All the product that I remember the screens and stuff you were supposed to like the touch screens like it was like you had hit it.
Yeah.
Really.
Like it was just the really.
I love our smart homes.
Perfect.
So yeah, we love our smart homes.
Sometimes I'm like, well, I barely touched this thing.
Yeah.
I already just did it.
I knew where you were heading.
Yeah.
I was thinking.
I love my fridge where I can see what's inside the fridge.
That's great.
Yeah.
I love that.
In my house.
All the effort you save.
Yeah.
Because those things can stick.
Oh yeah.
Force sometimes.
Sometimes I'm just so, so weak.
Can't even open my fridge.
I just like to know that there's food in there if I need it.
Lack of food.
Yeah.
Because you're weak because all you've done is look inside and not eat anything.
Of course.
Well, let's take a few steps over in the embattled land of Tomorrowland.
You know, it's a spotty realm in almost every park.
Perhaps save for this attraction, one of the only things that has worked in Tomorrowland
and that packs them in the Buzz Lightyear attraction.
I guess, I don't know, is now the time to discuss the names.
Sure.
I got it in front of me.
There's so many.
Yes, Jason, please.
I don't know if you know this.
It has a different name in almost every, it's in, it has been in six different Disney parks
with slightly different maddeningly similar names.
That's, yeah.
Which we of course have to go through.
That's very good and not confusing.
Do you want to?
Yeah.
At one period of time, there was a very small window where It and Dumbo were the only things
six castle parks throughout the world.
Wow.
And then Hong Kong closed theirs to build the Ant-Man and the Wasp ride.
Nano battle.
Yes.
Exclamation point.
So in Walt Disney World in Florida, it's Buzz Lightyear Space Ranger Spin.
In Tokyo Disney.
Hang on though, because there's an important thing.
Is it a possessive?
It is.
It's a posthorpy.
This one is possessive.
This is the only possessive.
Sometimes Buzz Clank.
Okay.
Yeah.
Only in this case does he claim ownership.
It is his.
Otherwise, his name is just kind of butted up next to the name.
Yeah.
It is Buzz Lightyear Astro Blasters at Tokyo Disneyland, Disneyland in Anaheim, and Hong
Kong Disneyland.
That's also the order that those opened.
And then it's Buzz Lightyear Laser Blast in Disneyland Paris and Buzz Lightyear Planet
Rescue at the Shanghai Park, which is noticeably different.
Like a massive upgrade.
Wow.
Oh, that's good.
Okay.
Gotcha.
What do we call this episode?
That's a good point.
Yeah.
I was going to sort this out now, I guess.
I think it's Astro Blasters.
Which one do we like the best?
Oh, does everyone have a favorite?
I was going to say Planet Rescue seems to be like the only one that like rings true to
me for some reason, even though that's like not what it's called.
It's sort of like, because I don't know, based on what you do in the ride and the experience,
I guess you also blast Astro.
So it's hard to say what is actually happening.
You blast Astro.
Yeah.
In your mind, you mean by because you're blasting and there's space stuff around that qualifies
as blasting Astro?
Yeah.
You're like an astronaut.
So you're blasting.
It's like, oh, well.
Here to blast some Astro.
I'm here to blast some Astro.
I mean, hopefully he says that in the new movie.
He does.
Or at least he does.
We could be maddening and like combine a few in a wrong way.
That's funny.
And make people mad as soon as they open it up.
Laser, Laser Ranger Blaster.
Ranger Blaster?
Space Astro.
Jumble them all.
I think Astro Blaster, because like.
That one has three of them.
Yeah.
Three of them.
Majority wins.
For me.
There's three of them and four seem like the same.
They have the guns you can take out.
It looks a little better than the Florida one.
Okay.
Which kind of made, I didn't dawn on me like the order these opened in where I was like,
oh, they kind of did on the cheap in Florida.
They went all a little more all out in Tokyo and then they just kept cloning the Tokyo
one until Shanghai where they were kind of building everything from scratch.
And they went a little harder.
A little fancier.
Yeah.
Matt, I assume you're primarily familiar with the Disneyland one.
Yeah, I've been to the Florida park, but not for now probably like 20 years.
I went when I was young.
Sure.
I assure you it is exactly the same.
I'm sure.
I see there's even been any paint put on it.
I want to go back.
I got to see this Avatar area.
Oh yeah.
I'd love to see that.
Yeah.
That's like, that to me is almost worth like booking a vacation around.
I really want to go see it.
I would, yes.
I would disagree.
Yeah.
It's something.
Because we watched the, my girlfriend and I watched the, those Imagineer documentaries
too on Disney Plus, which are great.
And I had no interest in any other Disney parks like around the world.
And I was like, I want to go to all of them.
They all seem like they have their own cool, I mean they made their own great propaganda.
Like, you know.
Yeah, sure.
I was like, this looks awesome.
I love this.
I film them very well.
Thanks for showing me Disney.
You're watching big ads, but they're very well done ads.
Yeah.
But yeah, I used to have an annual pass to Disneyland and California Adventure.
And I would frequent the Buzz Lightyear Astro Blasters quite a bit.
Because it's like a, I don't know.
It's fun.
I think it's fun and good.
And I feel like nowadays you can get in there under 10 minutes.
It's pretty, it's a pretty low, low census in that line.
Not a lot of people go in there, but you can, you know, when there's a long line for something
else you're like, wait a minute, we can just go do Astro Blasters real quick.
And then, you know, what's 45 minutes in 10 minutes, you know, it's the same thing.
Yeah, yeah, sure.
It's a good like wind down the day ride.
Especially, you're probably not looking at much of a line.
No.
Often the last thing I do.
I feel like they're blasting the AC in there too.
So like on a hot day you can get in there and, you know, get some, get cool before you get
back out in the heat.
And also the line moves because it's the omnimover system.
So the thing's constantly moving.
So the line generally, even if it's a little longer than 10, you're, you just need movement.
You need movement really, which is bigger sometimes than the actual length you're waiting.
Yeah.
There's a slight outdoor line if it's really crowded.
You usually get through it pretty quickly.
So yeah, if you need to cool down, you can get inside pretty fast.
If I see that outdoor, I'm like, yeah, I'm doing it.
It gives you a good.
Yeah, yeah.
If it's outside, I'm like, okay, there's something.
Yeah.
A lot of people are getting involved today.
It gets a little like, I don't easily get claustrophobic, but like between the outdoor
line for that and then the outdoor line for the Astro orbit, like with these very narrow
path like, yeah, I haven't figured out this crowd flow.
Yeah.
Since the late nineties, this weird choke, one of the few choke points.
Yeah, yeah.
It's very jammed over there.
Yeah.
When it gets jammed in that area, I almost like don't know what to do.
Like because there's like, there's not a great flow of traffic in that, in that particular
section that you're talking about.
And there's people coming in both directions.
And I often feel like I'm standing completely still behind someone sometimes.
And I'm just like, well, I'm supposed to be moving.
I want to be walking.
I missed it.
And then the group is all the way over there and I'm stuck behind someone who forgot how
to like participate in walking traffic.
Yeah.
It's got overwhelmed.
So then it's best to go the other, like if you see the Omnibus pulling up on Main Street.
I'm going around the Matta Bar.
Yeah.
Like run for the train or run for the Matta Bar.
Like just get out of that area.
I don't recognize offhand what the Omnibus is.
Is that the double Decker bus?
Yeah.
You ever done the Omnibus?
Oh yeah.
Oh, I think I have.
Both levels.
Wow.
Oh, I like to be high up.
Oh yeah.
Height miser.
Yeah.
Does that cover the Omnibus?
Did we just do the Omnibus episode or is there more?
Oh no, there's a lot more Omnibus stuff.
All right.
Okay.
Just checking.
Seeing if I can get out of it.
You got to get on this bus.
Separate episodes for bottom level.
Look, I've already compromised today.
There's like multiple different Buzz Lightyear names and it should be like four or five episodes.
I wondered if that would get, yes.
Technically, look, Space Raider Spin is a whole other.
It's very like, this is a ride deployed to do a lot of rescuing, just as Buzz Lightyear
is rescuing planets.
It's always filling spaces where things have kind of come unraveled.
Disney World, it was filling the space left by this progression of weird airplane advertising
rides.
I don't know if you ever got to go on any of those for any reason.
Just like there was this spot that was just rides that were blatant ads for first Eastern
Airlines and then Delta.
Eastern which is gone, right?
There's no like for a long time.
Yeah, no Eastern, but was the official airline of Disney World.
Now is the official airline of hell.
Yes.
Weird Delta ride, which is I kind of liked the Delta one.
We're going to get into some of the other ones.
Dreams, that's Dream Flight, which we all got to go on.
If you had wings, that's my mother loved if you had wings.
So like that was like a beloved ride by people.
I never got to go on it.
But my mom loves soaring.
Like she can get choked up talking about soaring.
Yeah, she asked me to my mom to do things.
It's the greatest, like one of the best things she's ever seen.
There are so many moms that have this story.
Yeah, and that is true.
Like I like soaring.
I like it too.
She's like she goes nuts for it.
Yes, moms go nuts for soaring.
This is a fact.
So Josh Groban of rides.
Point.
Well, you know, we missed the you know, there's a New York freestanding soaring.
There's like a one off.
Oh, right.
Yes.
Times Square.
They're everywhere.
We should have done that.
Toronto, I think.
Yeah, Vegas.
I did Vancouver.
And there's two different movies in the Vegas one.
I forget what it is.
I think it's like soaring over Red Rocks and Las Vegas.
And I don't know what the other one that plays is.
There's one that I didn't mention it when we talked about Heritage USA.
We're talking about religious parks.
There's one a guy who tried to buy that place and revamp it and failed.
He later in San Diego, there is something called Wings Over Israel.
Wow.
What is built that is a there is a religious soaring.
Except they don't do the part where you lift up.
You are just in shaky chairs.
It is a big dome and you take wings over Israel.
I don't know what you see exactly.
Pigeon Forge has one in Tennessee.
Wings Over Pigeon Forge.
Yeah.
Would you know what it is?
Become a pigeon.
Yeah.
I mean, that's cool.
I would like to see what a pigeon gets up to, what they eat.
Poop on a statue.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
If you could.
Yeah.
If there's like vibrating haptics on your chair that were like make you feel the feeling
of a big relief.
I'm doing it.
Thank you.
That's a million dollar idea.
It's mine.
OK.
All right.
Then in Disneyland, what this it took over a space, there was a bunch of things.
It was Circle Vision movies.
But the last thing that it was before was it was all the line for the rocket rods.
This weird.
Did you do that?
I don't remember.
I really don't remember that.
I know that because I mean, I'm from here, so I've been like going to Disneyland like
my whole life.
But like, I don't remember.
I feel like I don't remember the park.
I feel I remember when Astro Blaster is like was new and it was like exciting.
But I don't remember anything before that.
Maybe when I was there before, it was like still like under construction or part of the
line or something.
Oh, maybe.
But I don't.
Yeah, I don't remember.
I don't even remember the rocket rides.
I remember.
Oh, no.
Maybe this is that Knott's Berry Farm.
They had these like rides that like they had to shut down because people kept falling out
of it.
And they were like these like singular cages or something that went high up or something.
Is that like a was that a parachute?
I think it was like a parachute.
Yeah.
That's not there anymore.
No, no.
I think.
One too many people fell out.
I think reason.
Yeah.
They're like that.
We got us.
We got to knock it off.
But I also feel like I mean, where are we all at with Buzz Lightyear as a character?
I feel like I love Buzz.
Oh, I loved him.
I love him.
I still like him.
Yeah.
Yes.
There's been I guess he's a little out of this, but my son was so it was just there
was multiple Toy Story's a day for a little while.
Sure.
So I got familiar.
I got re-familiarized with them to the point where like I knew it as well as the animators.
Yeah.
Probably did.
There is a stretch in time, but they never really like occasionally.
It was just like we've done enough one.
Let's do three today.
Sure.
That's all.
But there's enough of the and the shorts are fun.
So it was kind of a pleasure to be to just have constant Toy Story's around.
And Buzz is great.
And the kind of the world that the ride is pulled from because it really is kind of the
implied Buzz Lightyear universe that's in the cold open of two where you're fully in
his world and you meet Zerg.
And it's just it's a really neat that fake out I think works really well.
You're really wondering what the movie is up to and wait, are we going to stay in Buzz
Lightyear world?
I remember being like disappointed a little bit like when I was a kid and that came out
as a wait a second.
I want to see this movie like that's cool.
Yeah.
It's pretty neat, I'd say.
But is any of the theming in Astro Blaster is based on the cartoon?
So we were.
Yes.
So yeah.
Yeah.
So the queue has art in the style of the short lived one season cartoon Buzz Lightyear of
Star Command.
Yeah.
And the direct to video Buzz Lightyear of Star Command.
Oh, there's a movie.
Yeah.
We my creative subtitle.
I've never heard.
We loved it.
We liked it too.
Yeah.
I really liked it.
And because I think Patrick Warburton is is Buzz in the cartoon, I think.
That's a good.
That's a pretty good.
And switch out.
I don't know.
I think I was just like a young Seinfeld fan.
I was like, oh, this guy's funny.
Yeah.
Oh, for sure.
I would have been like wrapping up middle school or starting high school.
Yeah.
But still at the age where it's like if there's nothing good on cable, what is in syndication
on broadcast?
Yeah.
And then they would come on UPN during their very, very odd kids block.
We're always changing.
And it was always stuff where it's like Bats Master, the fifth most popular Saban read
show, stuff like that.
And that's where Buzz Lightyear ended up oddly enough, because at that point, I think Disney
had bought ABC and the Disney Channel was chugging along.
I just remember being very interested in the extended universe of Buzz Lightyear, because
you don't get that in the movie.
So to know that he has this other life as this space hero.
I was like, oh, that's kind of funny.
Now I guess it doesn't exist because this movie is coming out.
Yeah.
Doesn't it?
This wipes out that show, essentially.
We're saying that is not the Buzz.
Unless that was a show that was based on the toy, that was based on the movie that Andy
saw.
We're back in this territory.
Oh, man.
I don't know why I forgot this.
I saw yet another clarification of what the Buzz Lightyear movie coming out is.
I think I saw this too.
And it's like, they're like, it's basically like a movie that Andy would see.
This is his Star Wars is what I saw.
I think what the clarification was.
The bar, hi.
Yeah.
The clarification, I think, was like, okay, Andy would have watched that cartoon we were
just talking about as well.
But this would have been like the big budget version that Andy would watch.
Lightyear, the movie coming out.
So these are both not true.
Like these are fictional stories, even though that's kind of contradicts what the Chris Evans
initial tweet was.
Yes.
But I think the director, yeah, the director was maybe the director, somebody worked on
the movie was trying to clarify that this is like Andy would have seen Lightyear and
it's just like the.
Yeah.
It's the big budget version.
There's multiple versions like there are with IP in our world.
Yes.
Yeah.
So that's what it's like.
Well, like Ninja Turtles, there's a big Ninja Turtles movie, but then various TV.
Yeah.
The toy maybe doesn't look like the one in the movie.
Right.
Yeah.
Where it's, it's actually the confusion is kind of doing a good job recreating how like
or Batman even more so than like cartoon that doesn't look like the movie.
And that the toy is different than that.
There are three actors playing Batman currently like.
Tough to keep.
It really keeps you on your toes as a kid to learn all of this.
Yeah.
So no, no wonder you tuned out Morbius.
There's no real.
I'm not going to learn.
I don't have time for this.
I was busy with Batman.
Batman to wrap my head around.
I'm now regretting that I didn't look into Buzz Lightyear of Star Command earlier because
all these I'm catching names that are wonderful.
Brent Star kisser.
Yeah.
It's a reporter.
That's pretty good.
Wait, there's another guy.
There's an evil Buzz who is also war Burton.
There's Petra Hammerhold voiced by Nikki Cox.
Plasma Boy voiced by Michael Showalter.
Wow.
Director of Tammy Faye movie.
Michael Showalter.
Is this on Disney Plus?
It's not.
I just looked it up.
Wow.
I think it'd be under like in the way that they put up some of the older Star Wars cartoons
and stuff as they're like.
Yeah.
It's like Star Wars stories.
No, it doesn't count.
Lightyear stories.
Yeah.
Oh, I see.
That's their way of saying it's a little make them up stone.
Don't worry.
Don't concern your little head with these.
They did.
They did like I think last year put up the Getty Tartakovsky like shorts that are really
cool.
Yeah.
Those are awesome.
And then they also put up the limited animation droids cartoons and the horrifying Ewoks movies.
Oh, those are the Ewoks movies on Disney Plus.
I was talking to the other night.
I feel like I was talking about that where like in the one movie she she has an indicator
like wrist cuff thing and she watches the like each of her family is a light.
Each member of her family, she watches them die one by one.
Oh my God.
And this is a kiss movie.
Very upsetting.
What a cold way to watch.
She watches the lights just go out.
And the previous movie was all about reuniting the family and the star.
Oh, no.
I swear.
If I'm misremembering this, something happened to me where I like hit my head watching this
movie.
But I swear like this is glued in my mind in the way that like I graduated elementary
school, got taken out to lunch, and then we saw the live action Casper movie and something
just froze in my mind of just hearing Devin Sawa go, can I keep you?
Like it's just an early like, oh, he's going to become a comedian.
He's hung up on something weird.
Oh, should have caught that.
Can I keep you?
It seems from my conversation seems like women of a certain age, their coming of age was
that moment for like there's dozens of people.
I feel like this is true.
Every year.
Almost everyone I know attuned.
Yeah, he's like horny for Devin Sawa.
Horny is the word.
Yes.
It was like Casper or Devin?
I think Casper.
I mean, Casper is funny.
And Fatso and Stretch and all the other guys.
Yeah, sure.
That's how you know.
Yes. The girls whose sexual awakening.
Yeah.
Stinky or whatever.
I mean, Christina Ricci is who I'm speaking of.
Oh, yeah.
I found the exact quote real quick about Lightyear.
From the writer director.
Yeah.
Lightyear, it's the movie that Andy saw that changed his life.
Andy's Star Wars.
So that's officially what it is.
Yeah.
Is that because he is.
What do you mean?
You heard it.
I used to direct or said it.
Because, yeah, he played with the toy a lot, but then he ends up giving the toy away.
What's really the permanent trajectory of Andy's life?
Yeah.
If he likes this movie, if it changed his life, why did he give the toy?
Do we give Buzz away right away?
Woody's the only one that had a chance at college.
Yeah.
Well, what is he going to college to do?
Do we ever find that out?
I don't think we know Andy's profession.
No.
Okay.
Presumably going to be working the rodeo.
Yeah.
If he's thinking about keeping Woody, yeah.
He's going to rodeo school.
He's doing lasso tricks.
He's learning.
He's learning for years.
He's very involved.
So we don't know.
And then we don't see Andy in the four because it's Bonnie.
So we don't know how it changed his life yet.
We know that he's not in animation or a podcaster because he gave the toys away.
Yeah.
The worst ending of a movie I've ever seen is when he gives those toys away.
He became cool.
It's Mike's nightmare.
We don't know what's Bonnie's handy.
We don't know if he gets into bowling shirts and rockabilly.
We don't know.
Frantically searching eBay and behind the scenes.
There should be him in his mid thirties rebuying all the toys off of eBay.
That should be a Toy Story movie.
But then they don't all know each other.
So when they all meet, they're strangers now who talk like the ones that we knew.
That's the reboot.
That's like, yeah.
What a good idea, by the way.
Yeah.
Okay.
That's ours.
Yeah.
Well, yeah.
Okay.
Why doesn't he play with us?
Why does he just put us in an Ikea Billy bookshelf and look at us sometimes?
The D-Tolf is the real...
Oh, excuse me?
The D-Tolf is the ultimate toy displayers shelf.
That's the D-Tolf.
D-Tolf.
D-E-T-O-L-F.
That's an Ikea, though?
That's an Ikea, yeah.
And that's the optimum display cabinet for...
I'm a Calax man myself.
Yeah.
That guy was like the scariest man to me when I was like a little kid.
I was like, this is horrific, what he's doing to these toys.
I don't think he should be allowed.
Sid or the Toy Man?
Oh, I mean, I was less afraid of Sid, but I was more afraid of the Toy Man.
Oh, okay.
There was something electrifying about his behavior to me.
He was like, he was a craven.
I just didn't care for his personality.
Thank you.
His design is like, you know, many of like...
He looks like dozens of the people who ultimately were me-tude when that movement was in full
swing.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, for sure.
I mean, he does look like one of those.
That's what I was responding to as an eight-year-old.
Would Al have been me-tude had he...
We don't see what he does, but I'm sure...
He's definitely like an MRA-like type guy.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
That's true.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
It'd be funny though...
He backs the blue.
I know the director has clarified, it's like, this is a big budget movie in this world.
It'd be funny if it was like a big budget flop.
If it was like, oh yeah, if Andy saw the Tom Cruise-y mommy.
You mean in continuity a flop.
Oh.
Oh, Andy saw Gods of Egypt and it just changed his life.
Yeah, yeah.
You know?
Or it's like Flash Gordon or something.
Or it's sort of like a cult sort of hit.
Yeah.
Andy was mesmerized by Sky Captain and the World of Tomorrow.
So it changed his life by like ruining his social life for many years because he couldn't
go talk at school about the thing he loves because no one else likes it.
Listen to me, it's two movies.
It's Death Proof and Planet Terror, okay?
And there's fake trailers in between.
You can watch them separately.
My mom told this story growing up that the weekend that E.T. came out, she saw Tron and
she was the only one of her friends that saw Tron and everybody else saw E.T. and she was
absolutely like eviscerated at school.
Like what's Tron?
Oh.
And then there's no further detail you could produce that doesn't sound like the dorkiest
thing you've ever.
Nothing you could say about Tron helps.
Well there's a guy named Ram you see.
Boo.
Go play with someone else.
So they're like computer graphics.
Yeah and they look good.
No.
They look.
They're literally in the movie, yeah.
There's bikes that make hard right angles.
That would be impossible in our world.
It'd have to be a little curve at least.
You don't know who David Warner is?
What?
You can repeat this in like X number of years where it's like Daft Punk to the soundtrack.
Sounds cool.
That was cool though.
Yeah.
That was, they were pretty cool.
It took the world a little long time to catch up with your mom.
No I don't.
I feel like when I saw, was it Legacy?
Tron Legacy.
People in my theater were like cheering before the movie started.
They were all very excited about Tron Legacy and then they all sort of walked out sort
of like, oh alright.
Then you have to be up at an hour in.
Well I got a nap in.
I mean very cool vibes between that music.
Great vibes.
The visual, I feel like the visuals still look great.
Yeah.
I still give it up for that more than I don't.
It's just.
I like that one.
Both movies, like once it really kicks in you're like, okay.
Last half hour.
This is interesting.
Yeah.
I'm a, I would go as far as to say staunch defender of Tron Legacy.
I really like it.
Yeah.
Do we have, is there any movement on the rumored Leto Tron movie?
Oh man, I hope not.
Are we going to see Moribus?
Is Moribus going in?
Is Moribus?
Yeah, Moribus is in that one.
Moribus.
Mitchell Moribus.
I feel like I've been hearing about the Jared Leto Tron since I moved to Los Angeles.
It's always been with you and it always will.
Yeah.
I.
The idea of it will always be, the movie itself won't get made.
It's real to me.
That's right.
The, to get back to the ride a little bit.
Yes.
I mean we can, we can break off details of it, but is there like, is there a part of
the experience you enjoy the most?
Do you feel like, well here's the question is how do you, how do you approach it?
Do you care about getting a high score or are you just hanging for fun?
Well, I guess I care about getting a higher score than whoever I'm sitting with.
Like, so I want to do better than, you know, my brother or whoever I'm there with.
I like, I don't know, there's, cause I know that there are like, there are hidden targets
too that are.
Oh yeah.
That if you can get them, you get like more points for getting these, like these special
targets.
But I feel like a vast majority of my profile pictures on like MySpace were the picture
from that you get at the end of the ride.
Cause like they take your picture in there that you can email it to yourself.
Had to do the email.
I have countless, God knows if I comb through my Gmail.
Yeah, absolutely.
Countless email pictures.
The only one I could find was with you.
It was, I think you forwarded it to me.
Yeah.
You kicked my ass too.
You were like double me.
I mean, I don't think either of them were, I think we're both still under a hundred K,
but you were like handily ahead.
Yeah, I don't, I'm not good at, I'm not pretty, like when we did the Toy Story Midway Media,
like Griffin smoked my ass immediately.
I think I like to chase the trick shot, like the far away targets.
Yeah.
I just learned about the sequence targets where it's like shoot the box, shoot the
target on the lid when it opens up, that activates a monster who has the triangle target that
has the highest scoring ones.
Right, right.
If you just do a quick search in your email, Galactic Greetings.
Yes.
That'll be where, what the email says when they've been sent.
And I have one, I have like a 2009 through a couple of years ago.
You got a lot of them?
I have a good amount, I think.
I have not done it recently.
Is the email feature turned on?
I don't know.
I don't know the answer.
I have not done it since COVID.
I feel like I, I think I stopped doing it because something about the way that look,
the tech is, it went in in Disneyland in 2004 and I think you kind of feel the 2004 of it.
And I just, if, if that it's a slow keyboard and if it ever gets stuck, I'm like, I just
want to stop and not finish my, not put in my entire email.
Yeah.
For some reason I lose pair if I feel like that keyboard is not keeping up.
So I think I just stopped wanting to make that stop.
And it often, as I said, it's often the last thing I'm doing for the day.
So I just like choose to go home instead.
Oh, I've got to pick, I've got you and I for some reason have that photo you were just
talking about Scott.
I have you and Jason in my email.
Wow.
I searched it and I'm sort of the date on this photo is kind of harrowing.
It's March 8th, 2020.
Oh my God.
Whoa.
So you're looking at your, so you're looking at a different man.
Yeah.
This is a person who's person anymore.
They're, they're sort of like, I remember this day because we went and we were well
aware of, of COVID of course.
And we were all sort of like, we probably shouldn't be here.
This is crazy. Right.
And then we were there all day.
Yeah.
And my girlfriend did get sick that day, but it wasn't a COVID related thing.
Okay.
That's right there.
I realize now that you forwarded me this picture of you and Scott, and if you look, I have
a draft that I never sent and all that's written in the draft is why.
That absolutely could have been just on autopilot.
Yeah.
If we were doing it late at night and I, I'm like forward and I'm thinking about show stuff
and I just auto did it to you or I ought to just did it to both.
Who knows?
When did we start this podcast?
Wasn't it later that year?
No, it was before that.
I think it was 2016.
No, it was 2017.
So that was July 2017.
This is before the podcast then.
Wait, what year did you say?
Maybe the picture was a proof of concept.
You're like, Hey, look at this.
Oh yeah.
I thought this was 2018.
I have one from two.
I have one from February 8th, 2017.
Okay.
That's the, that's us.
Really?
You and J. Yes.
That's you and Jason.
So it does predate the podcast.
Before the podcast.
Wow.
You, uh, Scott, Jason has 84,900 and you have 30,200.
I hate to out you guys.
Oh, he's more than dirt.
Yeah.
Um, I'm looking through my scores too and my best score is 450,000.
Geez.
Oh yikes.
And that's from 2019.
So I got back and get, I started in 2009 and 250,000.
You were, you were sending me, you were sending the email.
Why did you send this pit of the score for me to laugh?
If so, thank you.
This is an arrested development style call forward or like a lake house situation where
I sent it.
I didn't know why.
And maybe the reason was for this day, right?
Future.
I did.
My score on this photo is, uh, 230,800.
Not a bad score.
I think you're maybe, well, maybe you're both good at it with that score, Mike.
That's very solid.
That's much then that's higher.
We must've gotten, that's 2019.
We must've gotten stuck right in front of the secret target.
That's nice.
Cause it seems like two 50 is my normal ish zone.
Yeah.
Um, I also, there have been times where I'm in an odd number of.
People in my group and I'll opt to sit in it by myself so I can dual wheel.
Yeah.
Oh, that's, that's fun.
That is I've tried that, but that I'm not good at that.
It's not, I don't get one score is going to be a lot better than the other one.
But it's, it's still pretty fun.
Like a John wick scenario.
I'm thinking I'm back in there and Zerg is fucking scared.
I've never seen unprecedented.
I'm sort of like kind of, I wish there was more Zerg.
I like Zerg.
I like Zerg a lot.
Is Zerg in light year?
Yeah, he is.
Yeah.
I've seen there's the, you could, he's in the trailer now.
They've, they've revealed Zerg.
That's right.
But it's sort of, I think the approach is kind of anime is what they're thinking.
I think it's kind of a robot suit is the idea, which I guess is consistent with, you know,
he's sort of a Vader.
He's like a kid's Vader.
Yeah.
We don't really know what's inside that or if he is fully a robot.
Right.
Maybe he is because he's deploying robots in the raw.
Like that's kind of a lot of who you're facing off against, at least for the first part of
it.
Like it's big boxy robots, almost like rock them, sock them style robots in the first
couple of rooms.
But then you get to planet Z where there's now aliens in play.
Yeah.
I'm really guessing here because in thinking, in prepping this episode, I was like, I have
no landmarks in my head or moments from this ride.
What the ride is to me is there's a Z, there's a Z, there's another Z.
I really do not stop and take it in.
Yeah.
Sticks out to me watching the ride footage is how many of the robots have little plaques
that say Zerg rules.
It's a pretty funny detail.
Yeah, that's good.
I hope they're in the movie.
This is, and maybe I'm getting ahead of myself, but this is a ride that I almost appreciate
that it doesn't look great.
It's not, especially now and it doesn't hold up so much.
I've always liked it.
And especially when it came out first, I thought it was because it was the first thing that
was a big video game.
So I was ecstatic about that aspect.
But unlike Men in Black, which has crazy, it's in the Orlando ride, Men in Black at
Universal, has like very elaborate animatronics and it's still a shooting game.
Big sets too.
Big sets of stuff.
That sounds awesome.
But you're still like, you have that panic of trying to get a high score so you're not
taking stuff in as much.
So I do like, because I agree with you, Scott, where I'm like, I remember like a couple things,
but I've been on this ride so many times and I don't really have a good like geography
for where things are because I'm in a panic to get a high score.
But it's good that the ride, so what I'm saying is it's good the ride kind of looks like shit
in places.
That's what I'm saying.
Well, the storyline of the ride, it kind of like that Toy Story 2 opening.
It kind of splits the difference between the reality of the world and the reality of
a bunch of toys with AA batteries.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The squeak, the little green men.
There's cool, cool stuff.
When I say shit, I'm exaggerating.
Yeah.
But it is.
Yeah, yeah.
No, it's neat and fun in there, but it is very, it's like a, it's a high end laser tag.
Yeah.
That's good.
That's the most, that's the most amount of theming I want for a ride that I'm like panicking
trying to get scores and not taking the theming.
I hear that word a lot of times now.
Does that describe your frame of mind?
You do, it is a panic for you.
Maybe it's a panic, but it is definitely like very focused.
I'm very focused about getting a good score.
I don't like to mess with the, cause there's like a directional like toggle on the ride
too that you can sort of swerve in either direction.
I like to, I like to be in control of that.
Yes, me too.
If it's going to move at all.
Yes.
Cause I don't necessarily trust who I'm with all the time to know where to go, where to
point it.
There's kind of a lesser necessity for the later versions of the ride where you can take
the gun out of the holster and there's the cable.
The Florida one, the guns are mounted like a carnival game kind of thing.
Still?
Yeah.
God.
And so it's kind of more necessary.
Also the Florida one, very much more clearly painted flats like the Tokyo and the Anaheim
ones, a little more depth to them, a little more movement.
They have some more like robot three dimensional things that are like look cool and are not
just like cheap.
When you get to the big Zerg, the big Zerg is good.
I really like the big Zerg.
Yeah.
And that's pretty dimensional.
You get a lot of Zergs.
You get this Zerg early on, there's a Zerg flying by in the background.
So if your desire is to see him, which I do like him.
Last time I was there, I bought a Zerg for my kid who like one of the first things he
ever said was just a, was he's like a grrr.
He points at it, he knows exactly what it is.
He's obsessed with it.
I was thinking about bringing it in to see if we could do anything with it or just to
inspire us, but I don't want to take it away from him.
He'd be upset if Zerg was gone.
You did what with it?
That is for me, that is not content, dad.
It's not content.
He learned the word content.
I'm a broadcasters home.
One Zerg piece of trivia involving the ride is that I didn't realize that the ride in
Florida was there before the movie.
So this, so actually in 1998, Space Rangers Spin was the first place you could ever see
Zerg who was only spoken of in Toy Story.
Wow.
Sort of like Boba Fett in the holiday special.
Is that really the first Boba Fett appearance?
Whoa.
In an animated cartoon.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Right.
Another great thing about the holidays, but my favorite, my Star Wars.
Mike, I have similar memories to you.
This opened up.
It's kind of like a video game.
And like 1998, it was like, oh, this is so cool.
And then a year later, Men in Black opens up and I don't think I wrote it for a couple
years and it was instantly like, I was like, oh, getting to hold the gun is much more
preferable than like hunching over this mounted cannon thing.
And then when I came out here for the first time, I was like, oh, the Buzz Lightyear has
the gun, like the guns with the cable.
It's so much easier and the noises are more like appealing, like more pleasant.
That no, I'm trying to look over the noises.
Are they still unpleasant in the Florida?
They're not unpleasant.
I just think they're a nice kind of like little bouncy.
Florida Buzz Lightyear almost every time I've gone.
And I'm sure I've ever done it.
I wonder if I've done it.
That backs up a lot worse, I feel like.
Yeah, I have obviously done it when I was younger, but that's OK.
Next time. That's an ugly exterior.
I do not like that exterior.
That is just like a weird, gackey frame.
It just looks like, you know, like paste on art for a kid's room.
Yeah, I don't really like that.
Yeah, yeah. That's but I think it could all I think there is a way to aesthetically
I don't know, improve plus up this.
I like the I believe the Shanghai one has screens.
And it's weird to say screens is the remedy, but I feel like there's something
there's like something in digitizing or the way they've updated the Fantasyland rides.
There's a way to get some, you know, just more subtlety and texture and depth.
That might be I don't I don't love Toy Story mania.
I feel like you got it. You got to do too much.
Like, I feel like shooting a gun is easier than like pulling this like rope, like ball thing.
Well, it certainly hurts less. Yeah, yeah.
Absolutely less pain. Yeah.
You buzz. Maybe the true admission is I'm too out of shape to do Toy Story mania.
It's all wrist shape, though.
It's really like carpal tunnel causing because we've talked about it before.
And I really like me and we mean it.
But I think everybody has a similar experience.
By the by the end of that last bonus round, you are like, all right, let's go.
Like they can take one screen out and I'd be like, that was fine.
Like it would be. Yeah. Yeah.
Oh, you want one less round? Yeah. One less round.
Get me out of there.
But like because I also didn't just feel like screen like
I went to Universal in Halloween this past Halloween.
And I was there early so I could do some of the rides I didn't see in a long time.
And I hadn't done the Harry Potter stuff.
And I was like, I'm going to throw up.
I was like, this feels so bad to me.
Those are. Yeah, that one's that one's rough for sure.
And then the the the last one that I did was the Transformers one.
And I was like, I can't do any more of these today.
This is like rattling my brain. I can't do it.
Yeah, I'm totally with you.
I think I've just started to like screens that amend
others because sort of rise of the resistance is that you'd have to say.
And I like that screen elements, but it's never fully.
I guess at the end when you go into that pod, but, you know,
little screens all around or even the Jurassic World
like the screen section of that ride, I think is fantastic.
I wonder if we'll get a light year update for it.
There are rumors of Griffin.
Yeah, there are rumors.
Are there legitimate rumors?
Yeah, I don't know if they're so strong, but I've seen it speculated here and there.
Because I wonder, I mean, it feels like they're really pushing this movie
by saying that it's going to like that changed Andy's life.
That's a big that's a, you know, we don't know what else has changed his life.
Yeah.
So I wonder if they're they're expecting this movie to do well.
Because I also think this is going to be the first the first Pixar movie
in like two or three years that's like released in theaters.
That's right. Yeah.
Yeah. That's interesting.
Mm hmm. Yeah.
They they gave the animators of color a chance.
Yeah. They dumped all their movies on the streaming service.
Absolutely. Yeah.
But light year and light year, the character who's been in nine movies already.
Yeah. Yeah. He's going theatrical.
Looks like truly like what you picture when you picture like a white guy.
He's now he's now more of a generic white dude.
Yeah. He has less specific than ever before.
I I have a couple of weird things with this.
Like the one is that like the face in this upcoming move,
like the face of the toy makes sense because toys are often caricatures of humans.
But then the face looks pretty similar in the light year one
where it's supposed to be more realistic.
But other complaint is that I I just over the weekend, I was like, man,
it's a lot of people still talking about light year.
That must be out next week. Right.
And the answer was no.
Six weeks like five, six more weeks.
There's more talk about light year than there was for this new Fantastic Beasts
movie that was shocked came out last week.
Like, yeah. Wow.
It did. Yeah.
Geez. Got shrounced by the bad guy.
Yeah. Yeah.
Well, there were some issues in terms of getting the cast to promote the film.
Oh, OK. Oh, yeah.
We weren't as aware. I know.
I remember that. Yeah.
So available to. Yeah.
OK. Got it. Now they could have gotten mad out there.
Everybody loves mad.
No one, you know, mad.
Yeah. The fate of the franchise rests with you.
Guy who's known for being like a very personable, like cool guy.
Oh, that's good.
Guy who's like, yeah, going to do a Broadway thing after they're due to,
like, one million dollar movie.
Yeah. Yeah.
A guy who, like, doesn't look scary.
Well, we'll see.
We got more weeks to ponder this.
Yeah. See if we get more.
I think after Dr. Strange. Right. Right.
There's more promotion or more interviews about Lightyear.
I think the way it goes now is that like because it still feels like they're not
confident because they're not doing Jungle Cruise 2 yet.
No. So it feels like that, like an overlay gets greenlit
as soon as like Jungle Cruise 2 or as soon as Lightyear 2.
Yeah. Gets greenlit.
I don't know. That could be wrong.
But like it feels like they need like an extra bit of confidence.
Yeah, they need to know that it's going to be sticking around.
For a 10th Buzz Lightyear. Yeah. Yeah.
Exactly. So then promotional tool tool for a future movie.
It's not just enough to have it in the park.
It'll be built into Chris Evans' contract that he's going to have to record
Vio for the ride.
And that's that's already in there.
Yeah. I think they can lock that down now.
They're not losing these actors.
Well, the big rumor right now, Matt, the the Tarzan tree house is closed.
I was going to ask. Yeah. And they're they've announced
they're going to re theme it.
And they're I haven't seen in Canto yet, but there is a tree house in that movie.
Yes. I have not heard like the tree house is vital to the plot of the movie.
But there is a tree house. Yes.
And that is an existing tree house.
Does it seem like the best place to have like a hit movies ride?
Like this very narrow 1950s pathway?
Yeah, that's not like ADA, like accessible in any sort of way.
No. OK. But what?
Hear me out here in Canto. Fine.
But what if Lightyear had a tree house and we could go in and visit that?
That'd be good. Yeah. I'd be interested.
Like the light buzz Lightyear saw a movie about a guy who had a tree house
that inspired him to explore the universe to want to go get up high.
That's what I want. I love being up in my tall tree.
But what if I could go even higher than this?
Well, where's higher than a tall tree buzz?
What are you talking about, doofus?
Maybe up there, maybe somewhere like infinity or even beyond.
I don't know where the where the catchphrase came from.
Well, you got to know where the catchphrase is.
We have to learn.
Oh, I think that's all coming.
He either says the catchphrase or says half the catchphrase gets it wrong.
And then there's like a they fly now kind of bit about.
Yeah, sure.
Somebody's going to say that happened.
You know, they got to have a moment like that in there.
I want to try that one again.
I think you need a punch up pass.
Who says that?
I hope so.
I just saw a tweet going around that I was so fascinated by,
which is that we're coming up on the 10th anniversary
of the release of the first Avengers movie and early press screenings
did not have the swarm scene in it because it had not been filmed.
Like it was a few weeks before release.
No, I believe it. I believe it was filmed at the premiere.
At the premiere, I believe after the junket, like they got them all together
for the junket and then put them in.
It's either the junket or the premiere.
But it like it might have been the premiere because that was the only time
they were all together again.
And they quickly. Yeah. Oh, crazy.
And Evans has a beard in that scene.
And he's that's why he's like he has his hand over his face. Yeah.
Because he was shooting a different movie.
So it's their solution.
They should have done something cool like like Mission Impossible
Fallout where he reloads his fist and his beard gets a little thicker.
In the movie.
Does that happen when he when he does the when he does that?
I just saw this clip going around when he does the punch, watch his beard.
And a little thicker. It does.
I don't know. I think it's a you see this.
I've seen it. It's like it's it.
I don't know how or why it's yeah.
It's certainly not because he did it, but like because.
But it's like some sort of editing, like mistake that like they might
maybe use two shots or something.
But it's a cool idea to pump your own beard up.
Yeah. Like what is it?
And then the implication of what does that do?
Like you certainly have a little more testosterone.
You're probably a little stronger. Sure.
Yeah. I mean, it is.
It's interesting in the in the story of like, oh, this is when you see this.
It is. I gets a little more evil.
His beard gets thicker and his fist punches.
Icon as you keep doing it, describing the story.
I can picture it exactly.
In the trailer. And it's a great moment.
It's really cool because you just sort of know right away.
This guy's like really strong.
Like you like you only do that.
You're not going to do that if you're like me.
It's not going to communicate this thing.
But if you're Henry Cavill and you're like jacked as shit, you're like,
I better stay away from this guy.
Yeah. Yeah.
Just looks like a failed dance move otherwise.
You're a normal person getting the water off your hands because there's no paper
towel. Yeah.
The Dyson didn't recognize. Yeah.
Yeah. My arms are so thin that Dyson couldn't recognize them.
It is a franchise.
It's a franchise of cool movements.
I mean, the first one where he like drops into the room.
Yeah. Steady.
The second one, people might not think this cool, but where he gets the message
through his Oakley sunglasses and throws them at the camera.
And they explode.
All that like pointy running he does.
Oh, all the pointy running.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah. The craziest running
that when he breaks his leg.
Oh, yeah.
It's in there and they use it.
I love them.
They're simply the greatest films ever made.
I don't disagree.
He's an absolute freak.
He's like the greatest movie star of all time.
The greatest movie star.
I saw that anecdote that
what's is it Jake Johnson from New Girl and the new.
When he did the mummy with him.
Where he did the mummy and they jump off a collapsing three story building.
And Jake Johnson lands on his back.
He goes, oh, I'm hurt.
And Tom Cruise goes, are you injured or you hurt?
And he says, what's the difference?
He's like, well, injured means like something's broken.
Can you go again?
He's like, yeah, I can.
I can get up and go again.
He's like, OK, then you're hurt.
Oh, my God.
Of course, you're hurt.
You fell off a three story building.
What a normal man.
Yeah.
Look, I look, I'm going to cut it off here because I have three Tom Cruise stories
that I've seen on talk shows that I want to talk about.
But we're no that's not what this is about.
I just want to cut it off here because there's no theme park presence.
You have nowhere to put that's absolutely shocking to me.
Well, they've they've they bungled the mummy, didn't they?
We could have got a new mummy overlay.
Yes, I know.
Yeah. And Mission Impossible, because Tom is just talking about him again.
Mission, he just he just apparently squashed the idea of doing
Mission Impossible streaming show, which could I say make it special.
Yeah, yeah.
We don't need that on.
But come on, Tom, where's the Mission Impossible ride?
Where is it?
Yeah. Make it the best ride of all time.
Put it at Six Flags or something.
Yes. Oh, yeah.
It's just a Riddler repainted.
It's a possible ride.
Go. Well, how do you but how do you get a ride to Tom Cruise?
Standards like how do you does it have to like push us to the brink?
Yeah, we have to not injured.
It has to be built into the ride that like you might die for real.
Well, you sign you are doing this.
Yeah, you sign.
It's not some like bland legal entity that you're signing for.
It's like a paper that he wrote.
Yeah. Or you watch a video where he's addressing you.
And he's like staring your eyes and like, I feel like
if Tom Cruise is in his room right now and he stared in our eyes
and told us to do something, we'd all do it no matter what.
100 percent. Because he has he has that power.
100 percent.
He would because he makes he's like one of those like politician guys
who like you looking at you and you're like, this guy is in love with me
and I will do whatever he says.
He activates your injury in mode.
Yeah. All I would want to do is make him laugh.
And I know I couldn't know.
You know, I couldn't.
But also, I don't know what he thinks is funny.
Like there's no way he thinks anything normal is funny.
Well, he jumped. I bet.
Like there's a clip where he like jumps over Keegan Michael Key.
They were. That's a deep.
Oh, that was a deep.
Yeah. You got fooled, my friend.
Fooled. I thought it was real.
But that does seem like something he would think is funny.
Like doing a job.
If he saw that, he'd probably be like, yeah, you'd love it.
He'd like talking about Tom Cruise.
Yeah, it's not the back to the podcast.
Yeah. Well, let's talk about that.
Why don't we talk about the star of this ride?
Not Tim Allen, but Pat Fraley.
Yeah, it was fake Buzz Light.
We've talked about fake Woody Jim Hanks.
We haven't given due to fake Buzz Lightyear, Pat Fraley.
Pat Fraley is a Ninja Turtles voice.
Oh, yes. He is.
Crane Crane on the original Ninja Turtles.
So major credit from that and like eight billion other shows.
But usually if you see my crank real quick, of course,
to enter
the end, you're one is.
That's all I got. Tom Cruise.
I want you to know I don't laugh very often.
But what I'm about to produce
a ha ha ha.
And that's as much as he goes.
But you did make him laugh. I love shredder.
I absolutely loved your crank.
Do you understand?
Oh, it's all I could dream of.
Vienna.
We have a safe cracker roll.
It's only one scene.
But if you can do your crank voice.
That's how he cast his movies.
He sees somebody do one thing that he likes and is like, all right, you're in.
That's it. You're done.
It's work. There's a lot of henchmen.
Like there's a lot of guys. Yeah.
You know. And then he OK, I'm going to tell the story.
He was on the talk show.
He's on Graham Norton with Rebecca Ferguson.
And she said the first time that she did a stunt where they went down
a building or whatever, it was like a scary thing because it was so high up.
And then they landed and he looked at her and he went, welcome to mission.
Oh, my God.
He was on the show, too, and he claims he didn't do that.
But she goes, yes, you did say that to me after the stunt was over.
He probably was so mad.
Yeah, yeah, of course.
Do you think you could tell if we put a mission style clock on it?
Could you tell both stories?
The other two stories?
How much time does he have? How much time does the fuse take?
No, I don't. I don't want to.
That's too much pressure.
That's more pressure than I was.
Anecdote, I have the clearest in my mind.
So if you get up the gumption to do another one, so funny.
Let me think.
The I was going to say that I like the
I think one of my favorite gift shops in the park is the one that's outside of the bus.
Uh huh. It's like a sort of it's called.
I don't remember either, but I feel like it's like a good I like the theming in there
because it's it's consistent with the ride.
So it is very like it's very buzz like it's like very like green and purple
and blue in there. And I don't know.
I like it in there. Kid friendly.
Yeah. Pixar stuff.
Yeah. Mm hmm.
Like sometimes. Yeah.
I know there are cars.
You can buy cars merch there a lot, too. Yeah.
So there's a lot of pin racks.
I feel like I used to be so interested in the pins.
I and now I'm just like, I mean,
they're the same that like they're like Funko Pops now, too, right?
Or they're sort of similar in that way
in popularity, I think.
But I don't know if pins, I guess, reached further than this.
I've been so seldom on the show.
We're not the pin guys.
No. By you being ever a pin guy, that makes you the you're the biggest pin guy in the room.
I think I mean, I say that and I probably had it.
I probably had 10 pins like that's like as many as I had.
I had a pin face. I had a pin face.
You have a few dozen pins.
And now they like threw houses.
Have you you in the pin wars?
Yeah, it was in the pin wars.
I feel like now when I see them, it's not as big of a deal like at
at the parks.
I feel like now it's sort of like these people are off to the side,
whereas it was more of an like not an advertised thing,
but it was more an out and proud sort of thing in the park.
And now I feel like I see people with their like little felt
background or something with the pins in it, the book sometimes.
Yeah. And like a flashlight.
Like they're doing it under cover of darkness now.
Yeah. What's the thing? Yeah.
I've seen these like little shit where it almost feels like a street performer.
Yeah. Where it feels like is this this can't be or they're like on
canal street or something in New York.
Like it's like a very like we're like, hey, we got pins.
We got pins over here. You want the pins? Yeah.
They encouraged pain trade.
I mean, they've always got a pin trading. Yeah.
The little felt boards that the cast members have at some spot,
like that's the official like park one.
But then what's happened, this happened with lightsabers recently.
There was a big there's lightsaber meet meet up sometimes at Galaxy's Edge,
where it's like people organize them this themselves.
So like pin traders, I feel like just an earlier version of that.
Yeah. Are they? Yeah. Sorry.
Oh, I was going to say they just set up at that tomorrow land terrace.
And then they got the books and the binders and stuff.
I think this is what you're saying, man. And I agree.
Sometimes it feels like you turn a corner and it's almost as if you caught
like two people kissing or something. Yeah.
You're like, oh, I don't need to see this. Yeah.
No, I didn't. I didn't. I'm not.
I'm not involved in your trading.
Go ahead, please. Please don't mind me.
I will say my favorite pin and Emperor Kuzco pin. Very nice. Oh, cool.
And you have it. I still have it.
And it's pre transformation.
So it's him as the guy.
And I always I always really love that that movie.
I remember this and I guess I don't.
I'm remembering that we've talked the one time we talked about pins
is that Jason said you could buy the pins this and I'm selling you out.
I was going to this is a whole thing.
Jason talked about how you could buy the pins on Amazon.
And apparently those are knockoff pins. Oh, no.
Yeah, I saw multiple blogs recommend this as like, hey, families,
if you want to go and do pin trading with the members, you can just buy bulk
things of pins and then you trade them.
And and there's as many like family blogs or message words
as it's all doing this.
There's the counterpoint where people are like, you're putting false
pins in the ecosystem. Yes.
Yeah. Circulating scrapper pin.
And so Jason is a purveyor of false pins.
I didn't like to trade trading even as a kid, like even at the height
of Marvel trading, like I felt so anxious trading.
Yeah. And this is mine.
Especially with a stranger.
Yeah. Yeah. I got to talk to you. Yeah.
Yeah. And like, I don't really know.
Yeah. As a child, you don't know the I mean, you kind of know the value.
But yeah. Yeah.
So I I don't know.
So I would buy them once or twice.
I trade it with cast members.
But like now it's fun, like fully crying.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
But now he does all the fake ones.
So he's he's doing it constantly.
Yeah. These are scrappers.
Get it. You're banned for life.
Bite him to see if they're so thin.
I don't know if they are supposed to break or not.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Honestly, if you bite them.
But I think right around the same time as Fast Pit, like the official dizzy
pin trading marketing and logos came right around.
My memory is like the very late 90s.
Like it was a millennial thing.
You got like they had like the lanyard that you can put pins on and stuff.
And then you can be like, oh, like, yeah, cool.
Too slick now.
That is what it's like.
Too slick now. Too expensive.
Yeah. I say. Yeah.
Hmm. Can we talk about the like the game itself, the Buzz Lightyear game?
Yes. The stuff I didn't even know until looking for this.
Yeah. I didn't know much in the way of secrets like just really how you do it.
Right. Right. I was going to say, like, just the just the basics of like,
what do the different shape targets mean as far as points?
Like, I didn't even really know this.
I knew instinctually I knew what was right and I knew it was lit up.
It was more. But just to see it like circle is 100 square is a thousand.
Diamond is five thousand. Triangle is ten thousand.
And then if they're lit up, they're worth ten times that amount.
Yeah. You can go. You can get home.
There's more. And obviously there are more circles because they don't want you to
be getting, you know, a million points in the first one minute.
The first minute of the ride. We're not made of points.
We can't just give them away.
Could you imagine what would happen if we just gave away all the points
at the start of the ride?
He landed bankrupt.
You'd have to add another nine.
We have to slightly expand the LCD.
I wonder what the highest documented score is.
And that's maybe only interesting to the four of us.
But that's OK.
I'm sure there's people.
I'm sure we're really proud of it who lorded over people that they got it.
I think that so it maxes out when it's all nines on your board.
So that's like it's nine hundred ninety nine thousand.
And I know. Yeah.
But I think if you go do that email, you can see the full score,
which is higher.
So you can see a score that is up in the millions range.
I'm not sure what I think maybe a nine million is possible.
I don't really know offhand.
Yeah, I don't know how far you can go in the like off the books score.
Honestly, I didn't really know like the glowing
meant more points.
I knew the shapes meant different points.
I kind of knew they were hidden.
What like the chest plate of the Zerg?
There's a hidden one. Yes.
I didn't know that. Why does everyone know this?
Do you have to have looked this up?
I just want some videos today.
That's how I. Yeah, I didn't know.
It was like a thing that I had heard, like in the park, like a friend of mine.
It was a big Disney parks like fan, and I think maybe she told me.
But, you know, that's probably she looked it up.
So it's between he's got big chest plates.
And if you aim between, it's on marked.
It doesn't have a big Z, but that's the that's the big.
And I don't think it lights up either.
So you would never know.
No. And I think like one or two of the circles are secret, like 50,000 ones.
Yeah. Really advertise that.
There's other stuff that I knew like never stop firing.
Like if you hit a target, you can just keep hitting the target. Yes.
I only saw this one place
mentioned the better luck next time score where every five shots,
if you don't hit something, you get points.
And the other thing I said, yeah, like sympathy points
because you aren't getting anything. That's nice.
And so that adds to the like never stop firing.
And Matt, what you were saying about like riding alone. Yeah.
I had never seen this advice like
you can probably get more points if you sit on the left to most one
and then take the other one and put it on the seat, because at a certain point,
it's just going to start firing. Oh, wow.
So for the to cut down on confusion of the little dots,
which you can see sort of your target.
A little bit like what it's lining up as if he has a scope or something.
Now this I have a lot of I would say that I'm not great at this, some of which is
I get OK. So it is the green.
It's like it is the green like site at the top is what you're going off of.
Right. Not the going off field, baby.
Circle in the back.
I just if I'm trying to visualize it, I'm screwing up.
I never think too much.
I think because you have to do much.
Yeah, because you have to see like that little red thing that's going.
Like, yeah. And you eventually just yeah, you're only I'm just doing it on instinct
where it's like I'm realizing because I can't even explain to you what I'm doing.
Visual really, except for the red.
They're obviously aiming at the thing, but like it takes me a couple.
I feel like it maybe even takes me 30 seconds to lock back into it
because it's not something that feels so direct as far as being able to like perfectly aim.
I think as soon as the gun activates, start shooting the wall close to you.
And then you can see how much it's wavering left or right or up or down.
And then you can course correct.
That's my trick. Uh huh.
I'm just a few off.
I'm just pure. I just I turn feral and I.
Yeah, I sort of have like a Max Payne like bullet time sort of.
Yeah, it slows down linear.
You put sunglasses on.
My favorite is the one that's not lit up in the dark hallway.
That's a good one, because it makes me a favorite.
Yeah, because if you don't know, yeah, that's it's all of a sudden illuminates
the dark hallway if you start getting it.
And especially if you I think I got stuck there once, which is that's a big thrill.
Yeah, it's so direct and very close.
Yeah, you're so close to it.
There are a few, too.
I feel like there's one on the ceiling in there also, I think.
I mean, yeah, I'm trying to remember in that hallway.
Yeah, I think so.
There might be one on each side and then on the ceiling.
Yeah, one for everybody.
The best one I just learned about is when you get to the big Zerg at the end,
swing the car to the opposite wall and you're really close to like a toy box thing.
Shoot, get the toy box target that activates a triangle that is so close to you.
And you would just.
Oh, wow. I usually never see it if you were.
Everyone is facing the giant animatronics.
Yeah, but there's a secret.
If you face the other.
A last dash for like, yeah, whatever it is, like 10,000 points or something.
Yes, it's it is.
Yeah, it doesn't hurt, which is good.
Because I don't leave it being hurt.
Yeah, but but it does.
It is like a totally different.
Your brain is in a different spot.
Yeah. Than a normal ride.
And you're like, you're kind of in there for a while.
I feel like, too, like I don't feel like it's a very short ride.
It feels like it's a long.
Do you have the time of it?
Four to five minutes is what I. Wow.
Yeah, kept coming across.
But it feels like you're in there for 10 or something.
Yeah. Timely time slows down.
Yeah, it's bullet time.
It's bullet time.
So you don't even know what what the actual real time is.
You're busy.
Yeah, the Shanghai one, it seems like a lot of the complaints or criticisms
we have, they solved in Shanghai, where it's like a mix of practical sets
and screens enhancing it.
A lot of screen enhancement stuff in Avatar.
Yeah, OK. And that works really well.
Yeah, I'm all in.
Yeah. And I don't know what it is.
I'm just I'm ready. I'm ready. I'm ready for more of it.
I'm great.
I'm going to be fine.
It sounds good, but I kind of want it to look worse.
Just like make it look worse because I don't need it.
I mean, I'm just wanting to win.
I was going to say, I like it.
I like it to be flatter.
Yes. Yeah. Wow.
This is the. So what does that mean?
Do you take things out?
Yes. Less stuff.
Take the Zerg out at the end.
Take make just put up a painted flat.
Yeah. Cardboard.
How do you feel?
Because, like, again, the Shanghai, the targets are screens.
So I don't think you have to hit a precise infrared dot.
And so it's a wide screen and it makes the screen.
No, too easy. That's too easy.
Yeah. I like having to hit that perfect target.
Beginner mode. Yeah.
That's like the cardinal game we were talking about earlier.
Yeah. That main circle.
The this I was just thinking the Snow White ride has
some screen enhancements now.
I guess that way I wouldn't be so mad at that.
They did a nice job with that. Right.
Subtle. Yeah. Yeah.
I really like it. Yeah.
So, yeah, I just think, you know, even more basic,
the children should draw the characters and they should use those flats
for the ride, because again, I do not care when I'm competing.
Yeah. It's I don't know.
There is something the competition element of it,
because you can't compete on any other rides.
Like, not really. Right.
Yeah. Midway mania. And is there another one at Disney?
The cars ride like is sort of a race, but you're not really.
Yeah. You're not doing anything.
Whipslingers. And I think you're.
Yeah. Oh, yeah. I haven't done that yet.
I've been back once during the pandemic, but I haven't.
I haven't gotten the California adventure yet.
Well, if you want exhaustion. Yeah.
Like if you thought Toy Story Mania was exhausted.
I got to go out there and do flips pretty pretty much.
It's quite feels close to that.
It is because you're just like both red and the arms.
I will hurt your full arm.
I'm actually. Yeah.
I haven't felt the rush to go to the Avengers campus yet.
I was more excited to go to the the campus.
You should edge. Yeah. Yeah.
The ride itself is fine. Yeah. The campus is good.
I think we like it. I heard the food is good.
Food and drink is good. Yeah.
They're really filling it out.
Kind of the promises they made with Galaxy's Edge of like,
and they'll be characters and updated stuff.
Yeah. Haven't so much paid off as much as they have at Avengers campus.
They've done a much better job.
I well, isn't it just so weird, though, because like
you can do that at the
at the Avengers campus because it's not themed to a certain location in time.
Right. Yeah. It's like, yes.
Whereas like the Galaxy's Edge is what it would Jakku
after this movie or whatever.
Yeah. It's in between two movies.
Yeah. It's like there's a one to one day.
Yeah. Stuck on this one day in between eight and nine.
Yeah. Forever.
But they establish all the Marvel campuses that are going up
at a bunch of the parks.
That is not the Marvel Cinematic Universe.
It's a Marvel theme park universe.
And that's why everyone is still alive.
Yes. Oh, I see.
I see. And they have done some made up crap like that.
I think they could still do it if they want.
I want to do is change the story like the they could keep it
Jakku or whatever and just have it be like.
It's it's it's like a force.
The force. Yeah, it's the force.
There is crystal. There's magic.
There's time.
Somehow Palpatine is returned.
Some of those have to have time.
Just say the dead speak as you walk in.
Yeah, that's OK.
All the old care, every one of these.
There's a rumor. Oh, I don't even spoiler alert.
Maybe I'm so sorry, but I'm so excited by the runtime.
So yeah, give me 30 seconds ahead if you don't want to know this
about maybe the Obi Wan show.
People are acting like maybe Dexter Jets to is coming back
in Disney pluses Obi Wan.
That's what that was.
And I'm so excited about the idea.
I'd be interested in seeing him again.
I've been playing Lego Star Wars
and he has a fun little sequence in the game.
He's great. Yeah. OK.
Well, would you like to see him cooking up?
Oh, what kind of stains do you want on his apron?
Well, I want him to yell at someone for like smoking a death stick in the diner.
Yeah. And I want him to.
I'm trying to think what's the iguana that Obi Wan rides in?
Is it is it Attack of the Clones?
I think so. Yeah.
Yeah, I think it is. Yeah.
So like whatever that is, I want him to eat a cook that things eggs.
Yeah. Giant eggs in the.
Yeah, it is an attack of the clones in the end sequence right before
Django Fett is murdered by Mace Windu.
Right. A bogus. Yeah.
OK, so bogus eggs is what I want.
Very fun memory of that movie of like one of my
dorkiest fucking thing.
One of my friends had just gotten their license.
And it was a Friday afternoon and they're like, hey,
we should go see that new Star Wars.
And it's like, yeah, there's a three o'clock showing at the mall,
like next to the mall. It's like, let's go.
And we all just got in the car and drove over, bought tickets.
Yeah. Went inside and sat down.
It used to be that easy.
And wait, the story is you went to see a movie.
But it was the first feeling of like, wow, someone has her drivers.
We can just go do that.
This is a thing we can.
This is open to anybody.
No drop offs.
OK, OK. And then three days later, my family was.
And I saw it again. Yeah.
And I was like, I don't want to spoil it.
But at the very end, something cool happened.
Yeah. The I.
This is before the financial crash and before the Trump administration.
So this was all that to it.
And this is Jason's peak. Oh, yeah.
This is. Yeah. Never got any better than that.
I mean, I well, no, it was exciting.
Shrek came out right after.
Oh, man. Rouge came out.
Yeah. Wait, is that right?
Wait a minute. Am I getting the time?
I was in 2002, right?
Oh, OK. Well, maybe. Yeah.
No, that makes more sense.
OK, so that was the previous summer.
There was all that was before 9-11.
It was even better.
Is it that was the greatest summer?
That was the last summer.
So when when they say that this like that, the light year movie is
Andy Star Wars, they could be talking about anything like
it doesn't necessarily have to be like Star Wars.
Yeah. His life went a bad way.
Yeah. It's like he saw evolution and he's like, that is funny.
That head and shoulders bit.
That's funny.
Let's see, what have we not gotten to that we enjoy?
We've not feeling good at this.
I like some of these tips next time.
I will. Good tips.
The claw gag at the end of Astro Blasters,
where they've got Zerg in the box, the box, and they're like dangling it.
That's right. Little green men.
That's pretty good.
You know what I think we haven't really talked about?
It doesn't get enough credit.
Is the Buzz animatronic in the cube?
Yeah, yes. Yes.
It's like a low key really good addition to a cube of any cube.
But like it's sort of you don't think about about it when you're thinking
of like the famous classic good robots in the cubes.
Well, it's been kind of exceeded a little bit and the technology has.
But the first appearance of it was really how does this work?
Where is that projector? Yeah.
If well, assuming you figure out it's a projection.
But really, the first time you see it, like, I don't know what I'm looking.
I don't know how he's moving this much.
And the head is following.
I guess it's a little projector inside.
And the only thing in the projection is just is the face.
And I don't know.
It's so it's so well that you can look up on YouTube.
Just the raw video. Yeah, it looks worse now.
I remember being like, why does this look so bad?
I remember it being like, he's here.
Like, but maybe that's like where they could put a new screen.
Yeah. It's just like, yeah, update with the Chris, the Chris Evans.
But oh, sure. Yes.
He's like that new face in there. Yeah.
Oh, there is a thing I was going to say about Pat Fraley, but fake Buzz Lightyear
voice, which is he he had been doing.
He now doesn't do anything new as Buzz.
I'm not sure why they try to make it maybe somewhere in this confusion.
If now it's Chris Evans or they try to make Tim and Tom do more.
But at the height when he was doing a lot of Buzz Lightyear,
at some point he was talking to Disney people and he said, you know, I've
I've never met Tim. I've never met Tim Allen.
I feel like I'd like to be funny.
That guy and he and his well, and Disney said,
we don't think that's a good idea.
And he was like, why?
What's what would be wrong with meeting Tim Allen?
And they said, well, he's been around.
He's been stomping around before asking why his brother
isn't the voice of Buzz Lightyear.
Like, because Tom Hanks, his brother is always Woody.
So Tim is like, why don't I get that?
Why doesn't my brother get that deal?
But as far as I know, I think he's got a few brothers
and I don't believe they are actors.
So why is a brother automatically,
regardless of with with zero interest in in acting? Potentially.
Yeah, this is I have a story that I can't say it now,
but I'll tell you a story after we stop.
All right. Yeah. After dark.
That's great. Yeah, I don't know.
Look, if Tim wants to put his brother's auditions, I'd love to.
We could all rally behind them if they can do the voice, too.
At this point, I don't know.
All I'm hearing here is that this is a man who loves his brother
and wants him to have work.
That's so nice. Yeah. You know. Yeah.
But obviously, if you did Cranes voice, I think you should get any job.
You're for. Yeah.
Well, yeah, perhaps a little more qualified.
They tried. They auditioned the brother, but he swore too much in the first five
words. All right.
Just you know, and just have fun with it.
Make it your own fucking buzz light.
I'm fucking listen up, mother.
Listen up, little bitches.
I'm going in there. I don't know if they'll like it, but they'll remember me.
Kids got to learn swearing sometime.
If a voice you need a brother, a brother.
Damn it. I had a.
Oh, I got to know if a voice you need.
I like where that was going.
Brothers brother of a brother.
A brother is the choice.
I had it. I lost.
If a voice you need a brother, take heed.
A brother. Yeah, that's as close as I can come.
Anyway, there's brothers indeed.
He's more loyal to his brother than he is to all his coke buddies.
Yeah, maybe my brother.
He meant, oh, wait, oh, that's right.
Oh, yes. He's a rat.
I forgot. I forgot that story.
The voice of Zerg and Space Ranger spin in Florida is Frank Welker.
Oh, yes. The greatest.
Oh, and the voice in Astro Blasters is director Andrew Stamp.
So the guy who yelled action on every day on John Carter.
That's right. Was also that same voice.
Which is on Disney Plus.
Oh, I don't know. I think it is.
But Buzz Lightyear Star Command. No, no.
They should. They should.
Just do it.
I think it's been enough time we can reboot John Carter.
I think it's time.
They're going to keep trying everything.
You would think. Yeah.
Like soon. Taylor, another shot.
It might be cheap.
I mean, Netflix had a bunch of Roald Dahl stuff.
They bought like a huge Roald Dahl licensing.
And I. Oh, yeah.
And their current troubles, I believe, has all been paused or canceled.
Those bright two has been effectively canceled.
Like everything is crazy.
How are we even getting through this record knowing there's no break to.
Star Wars changed my life.
John Carter is on Disney Plus.
Wow.
And Gods of Egypt is on 2B
because I got recommended it in my weekly 2B update email, one of my favorite marketing emails to get.
Jason's picks of the week.
Gods of Egypt and Gunn Guys.
What was the movie?
Oh, Gunn Crazy.
Gunn Crazy.
I actually have not seen all of Gods of Egypt.
I did bookmark it to watch.
Gunn Crazy is such a good name for a movie.
Like that's I think that no, no, it's a perfect title.
Yeah.
That's your reboot.
That's how Netflix turns it around.
Yeah.
Gunn Crazy is back.
I'm listening.
It was in, I think restored like in the 2000.
It was in one of those sets.
Like the DVD sets were all the rage.
Okay.
It was like Warner Brothers crime, you know.
What did they did?
Like, I mean, is like the new release of it like lovingly like remastered like the Jaws Blu-ray?
Like when I feel like when Jaws first came to Blu-ray, they were making such a big deal about it
because like Steven Spielberg like got his hands in there and like remastered it.
And it looked like a like,
I mean, for my money, it looked like a brand new movie.
I was like, this looks crazy that this like old movie looks this nice.
Yeah.
Did they give the same treatment to Gunn Crazy?
I mean, they have, it has gotten some restoration.
So, but yeah, I love a poor cake.
But then they get the Jaws treatment.
Gunn Crazy.
Gonna make everyone's eyes, we're gonna make them more bloodshot to make them look more Gunn Crazy.
Yeah.
Get some smoke coming out of their ears.
You gotta see it's just constant spirals.
Yeah.
We gotta make sure they really-
The guy in the background going like this, cuckoo, cuckoo.
Yeah.
Are these guys Gunn Crazy or what?
You never know with those Blu-ray.
I mean, I think the Godfather ones are pretty well received,
but I think there's some Kubrick Blu-rays where they're like,
ooh, no, they made this worse.
I just heard that on the Back to the Future 4K,
you can see like bad makeup that you wouldn't have normally seen in a cut.
Oh, yeah.
It looks worse.
Sure.
Oh.
There's a shot somewhere in one of them where a DeLorean flies away
and you can see like a black box around it.
Like, I don't know if they just weren't, the monitors were,
or something was wrong with my monitor.
I'm not sure.
But watch out for that black box.
Star Trek, yeah, when they up-res'd all those Star Trek shows,
it's like all the alien makeup.
Yeah.
Maybe didn't hold up.
This wasn't supposed to be nice.
Yeah, this was on TV.
Although the Star Trek motion picture, they just did the same thing
where they have a new version that looks amazing.
Wow.
It's on HBO Max.
And there's a lot of like, I get a lot of like Epcot vibes from this movie.
Just a lot of like aesthetically pleasing.
Yeah, like aesthetically like smooth surf space surfaces.
And it's still a pretty boring movie.
But that's why it's still like early Epcot.
Yes, exactly.
I have no memories of Epcot.
And I know that I've been there, but I just have like,
gun in my head, I couldn't tell you a single thing that I did when I was there.
Wow.
You didn't try sodas from around the world?
That sounds like something I would have been interested in because I loved soda.
But I couldn't tell you if I actually did it or not.
Do you remember rows and rows of Genesis game demos?
That feels like the eight, that's what you would have remembered.
Maybe, but I can't.
That's not ringing a bell either.
I know I spent a whole day there too and I couldn't tell you a damn thing.
Huh, what year?
This was probably, let's see, 9-11 had happened.
So it was certainly 2002.
Oh, they might have packed up the video games.
The video games might have been gone.
Yeah, yeah.
But the soda was there.
Okay.
Well, now I'm upset that I missed it.
Maybe I missed out on the soda, but maybe I didn't.
I don't know.
Go see, go ride the mighty Akron in Pandora and go try their sodas.
Okay, so I haven't missed my shot completely with the sodas.
No, you can still get the sodas.
The sodas.
Pandora is at Epcot?
No, it's Animal Kingdom.
You gotta buy a ticket for Pandora and you gotta buy a ticket for the sodas.
Okay, okay.
You know what?
I mean, I'll do it is the thing.
I am interested in seeing both.
I can't think of anything else to recommend but the soda.
Just do the sodas and then go.
But I guess they aren't free at that point because you're paying that ticket price.
But at a certain point, they're paying for themselves.
If you can make it, if you refill 90 times or so, then you refund that ticket.
I think about cutting the cost out from like traveling to a different country to get this soda.
You know, then I'm saying you're making money.
You're making money in a lot of ways.
Those fucking rubes.
Hopefully they hear this.
Yeah.
We should figure out, we should do an episode on like, here's how you can actually make money.
That's a good, well, you should just go start scheming on that and bring us your findings.
Yeah, I'll take a look at the stretchy.
Get your chalkboard out and your headlines.
The toppings bar have returned and your lunch is now free.
That is a good, you really should.
But for now, final thoughts on Astro Blasters or whatever we're calling it.
Is there anything, talking about some secrets and stuff, is there any way you're going to approach
this differently when you go back?
Anything you're going to stop and appreciate more or try harder on?
I'm definitely going to freaking like whip my little cart around to go right after Zerg
to get that triangle.
I'm not missing that ever again.
You won't ever catch me missing that.
But as far, I mean, I don't know.
I just like to get in there.
It's like a sort of nostalgic ride because I mean, I remember when it was new.
And it's old now, I guess, right?
When did it open?
It opened in 2005.
So for the 50th for the Disneyland.
Okay.
Yeah, Disney World was earlier.
Yeah, Disney World was 1998.
Tokyo was 2004.
So I think they just cloned the Tokyo.
They probably were working on those both at the same time.
I'd hate to see it go.
I don't want it to ever leave Tomorrowland.
Maybe we've talked about this before.
I don't know if we talked about this last time.
We talked about Knott's Berry Farm, but I feel like Tomorrowland as a land is struggling.
Well, look, it's usually what we're talking about.
Yeah.
If you woke us up in the middle of the night, it's what we'd start talking about.
Because I mean, this is not a new observation, of course, but the promise of Tomorrowland
is that it's showing you tomorrow.
But now everything in there is kind of old and we've sort of passed some of that.
So I don't know what to do.
I don't know what to do with the land, but whatever you do, leave Buzz where he is.
Maybe update it with the new hunky Buzz.
They're kind of stuck because the land itself, we've been saying for over a decade now,
the land itself needs some work.
But very popular rides in Space Mountain, Star Tours, Buzz Lightyear, very popular rides.
And I just don't know if there's like, I mean, this is me not being plugged into modern art
or design in any sort of way.
But I don't know if there's a futurism movement like there was when they came up with Tomorrowland.
I don't know if people are right now looking at what 22 is looking like or something.
You know?
Yeah.
That's some of the...
Yeah, because there was so much futurism in the 50s and every time they did a new pass.
I'm thinking go back.
Go retrofuturism with it or something and make it like 1950, like what the Jetsons looked like
or something and make it old looking but new.
Yeah.
When they found solutions, the solutions have been akin to that.
And then the Tron ride, do you know about the Tron ride?
Yes, I want to get on that.
It's coming to Disney World.
Where's that one?
Well, it'll be in Disney World soon.
Okay.
So another reason to head down.
That seems like...
I'll honestly plan a trip around that because when I saw that ride in the Imagineering thing,
I was like, that looks great.
And that feels like future.
That actually, it's 80s infused but not fully retrofutur.
Who's got Ratatouille the ride?
Evcon.
Is it now too?
Okay, okay.
Man, I'm going to Florida, baby.
You gotta...
Yeah, let's open up.
It's quite a queue.
I gotta get this Ratatouille ride.
Yeah, there's a Guardians coaster opening up, got no...
Oh, but Hong Kong gets the Ant-Man and the Wasp?
Hong Kong is what has...
Yeah, they took...
They're the only place that's taken Buzz out.
It looks kind of like...
Fine.
Right?
Yeah.
It's kind of a lateral move.
Yeah, pretty much.
Yeah.
Sure.
You have to keep her as the Wasp then they can't...
Oh, with Angelina Lilly.
Yeah.
I have heard as they expand it more and more in the Asia parks and the movies got more and
more popular there.
Some stuff that they have chosen, it's like Iron Man, Darth Vader is very popular.
Iron Man, Ant-Man, Wasp, they all have helmets on so anyone could be behind it.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
So that's good then?
Well, that's I think why they settled on those characters.
That makes sense.
For those parks, I'm sure a lot of sound-alikes.
I don't know.
Is it Downy?
Is it Downy in the Iron Man thing?
No, that has never been Downy.
He's the only one who escaped the contracts.
Yeah, exactly.
Paul Rudd...
And the franchise in general.
Yeah, for now.
Paul Rudd is in the ride though.
Paul Rudd and Evangeline Lilly, they did all the voices for him.
I believe that because they were there I think.
They made him go.
Yeah, they were at the opening.
She can't go back.
She got to get that shot.
She got to get that...
Yeah.
She couldn't come back either, is the thing.
She's kind of a...
She's like a terminal situation.
Yeah, yeah.
She's a real Victor Navorski.
In between.
She's just there in the terminal clapping because she heard.
If she could go on the plate, she wouldn't have to wear the mask.
Well, excellent.
Matt, thank you for joining us.
We're going to...
I'll give you the high score of Galactic Hero.
Thank God.
You ranked Galactic Hero and you survived Podcast The Ride.
Thank you, thank you.
Thanks so much for being here, IRL.
Let's exit through the gift shop.
Is there anything you'd like to plug?
Yeah, check out Get Played.
Show that I'm on with Nick Weiger and Heather Ann Campbell,
where we talk about video games.
Is this coming out in May?
No, I think it's out this week.
Okay.
I believe so.
Then for all of May, just coming up, we're calling it PokMay,
and it's going to be Pokmon stuff all month long.
Oh, jeez.
Look forward to that.
Oh, great.
Oh, that's a great month.
Wait, you know what we didn't talk about is there was a video game you could play,
and still can if you download an EXE file.
On, because the old pictures you used to get said Disneyland.com slash Buzz.
Yes.
So if you go to the archives, Disneyland.
You won't do it now, but if you go to Webarchive.org,
download the old, you can play a weird janky Buzz Lightyear, Aster Blaster game.
I'm remembering trying to do that and just being like, come on.
I'm alive, would I have a life to live?
They said there was a very limited window of time where they're like,
and it's going to affect the ride in the park.
And it's like, how long did that land?
Yeah.
If ever.
And like in how?
How would anyone know if you were on one side of the other?
Someone at home.
The thing moved slightly.
That comet rotated five degrees to the left.
We've been compromised.
Two other oddball video game things.
The game shows up in Kingdom Hearts 3.
The Buzz Lightyear ride shows up in Kingdom Hearts 3.
And then in Disney Quest, if you recall, there was a bumper car
cannon kind of attraction that was also called Buzz Lightyear Aster Blasters.
But even slightly different.
It was singular.
Buzz Lightyear's Aster Blaster.
Possessive and singular.
What?
Why?
If you're in a tank, it's Aster Blaster.
But there's multiple people, right?
Yes.
Why aren't they all Aster Blasters?
No.
This one's referring to the gun.
The gun is the blaster.
And that's the reason for the title.
Maybe entertainment was better when everything did not have a Bible.
Like everything did not have a series Bible or a canon Bible.
Hey, look, I love the sloppiness.
That's what gave us the Star Wars Holiday Special.
More sloppiness, I say.
And for more sloppiness from us, you can check out
the social on the socials at Podcast The Ride.
Merch is available in our T public store and for three bonus episodes every month,
check out Podcast The Ride, the second gate at patreon.com slash podcast the ride.
No downloadable EXE games.
Not yet.
That'd be a hell of an incentive.
When we do it, it'll be you'll influence the show if you play.
You won't know how, but you will.
Butterfly effect.
We all cough.
You made us cough.
And we will pilfer your NFT wallet.
Just go on like that.
Forever
Dog
This has been a Forever Dog production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe
Cilio, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com and subscribe to our
shows on Apple Podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at Forever Dog Team and liking our page on Facebook.